Getting ready to depart for
American Idol auditions.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
It's sort of surreal, because I've
been waiting for it to happen,
For such a long time,
and it's finally here.
It's an indescribable feeling.
I just can't wait
to get in there.
I'm really anxious right now.
Okay, let's have it.
Take a deep breath.
This is our first trip to Oregon.
And with an eclectic
crowd like this,
There's no telling who
or what we may find.
This is Portland, and...
This is American Idol.
We've finally come to
Portland, Oregon.
A jewel of the Northwest.
Welcome to Portland!
And even though the city may,
be known for its cloudy skies...
The thousands we met in line,
were colorful and bright.
And our judges were definitely
feeling the love.
Today's the day.
We're gonna find the one.
That remains to be seen.
But we are set
to blaze a new trail,
Hopefully making Oregon History.
Seems nothing was
going to stand in our way.
Portland, Oregon, come on.
Who's going to get the first Ticket?
Me!
Let's go.
Everyone in the crowd
has a story.
Everyone in the crowd has a dream.
Whoo, doggie!
But it might not be about
what you may think.
My name is Britney Zooka.
I'm 21 years old, and
I'm from Portland, Oregon.
So, I had a dream.
I was on the stage with
Sara Bareilles, who I love.
And, I was singing "Gravity" with her,
and it was this amazing duet.
So I wake up, and I'm really
bumped that it didn't happen,
It was just a dream.
Some dreams just slip away,
but not this one.
And, so, it was my birthday, and
I got two tickets to a sold-out
Sara Bareilles concert,
My Mom somehow
managed to get.
And I just had this epiphany,
This moment of thinking:
"Hey, this is going to happen for me."
And I hold up a cardboard sign.
That I ripped from a box,
last-second, and it said:
"Will you sing gravity with me?"
She reads it, she winks at me,
She lets me up on stage
and we sing.
From that moment on, I said:
"Okay, I'm going to go for it."
I'm going to take this
as far as I can take it,
And nothing's going to stop me.
Whoa.
Oh, careful.
Did you fall for me?
God, I'm much too young to be
this old.
What?
What's your name?
They call me,
"Tripster the Hipster"...
"Tripster the hipster", okay.
Yes.
What are you going to sing
for us today?
Today I'm going to be singing
"The Story" by Brandi Carlile.
Wow.
It's a beautiful song.
♪ All of these lines across my, ♪
♪ Face tell you the story of, ♪
♪ Who I am, ♪
♪ So many stories of where, ♪
♪ I've been, ♪
♪ And how I got to where I am, ♪
♪ Oh but these stories don't, ♪
♪ Mean anything when you've, ♪
♪ Got no one to tell them to, ♪
♪ It's true that I was made, ♪
♪ For you, ♪
You're one of the prettiest
voices we've heard.
Just the tone of it's so pretty.
Yeah, dude, I really like
you, and what's crazy to me,
What I love...
You come in here, you look
nothing like what you sound.
I should take off my glasses.
I'm not as nerdy as sometimes...
Okay, take off the hat too.
That's it.
Uh, okay, take the boots off!
No, I'm just kidding.
I'm only kidding!
No, no, no, no, no.
Leave the hat and the glasses off,
see the sass comes out now.
This, the edge
comes out, I like it!
She gets wild with the
hat and glasses off.
I loved the end of that,
it was so good.
Thank you.
-Shall we take a little "votey"?
-Yes.
Yes, yes, I'm gonna say yes.
-Yes, yes.
-No way!
-Yes, please yes!
-For real though?
Yes, for real.
Okay, this isn't like "Play a
joke on the girl who trips.",
-You know, this is for real?
-No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah! Okay, awesome.
See you in Hollywood.
Oh, My Gosh!
Britney Zooka.
Great voice, great voice.
She's funny, dude.
They need to be
a little bit crazy.
Over the next hour...
Extreme talent is on parade
in Portland.
The minute you opened your
mouth, I was like, "Wow!".
Thank you.
You've got that gift.
This guy's great, he's great,
he's fantastic.
But watch out...
There's a storm a'brewing.
"Randy, yes for you?" No.
What the [Bleep]?
I just feel like I'm never
good enough.
Welcome back.
It's 10:00 A.M., and we're off,
to a strong start here in Portland.
More than can be said for our last trip
to the pacific Northwest a few seasons back.
Sounds real good.
But this is season 11.
And contestants know how to
better prepare for this chance of a lifetime
Portland!
Right?
Your name, your age, and
where you are from.
Okay, hold on.
Ugh, okay.
Oh, right now?
Hi, my name is Ben perdum, and
I'm 18, and I'm from
Philadelphia.
I'm-I'm not feeling that great
today.
I've been sick since like
Tuesday pretty much.
My throat usually sounds a lot.
more clear than this.
It's just a little, um, "cloggy"
in the throat.
What do you do?
I-I sell-I sell cable TV on
the street pretty much.
On the street?
Yeah, we just sit behind the.
Table and just yell at people,
like, "sign up today!" And...
What's your pitch?
Like, "225 channels is $34.99 a month, get three
free months of-", and all these channels.
And, you know, I don't want to say, like,
the company names, obviously, because-advertising.
Yeah, well-no, I get the pitch.
But if your singing is as good as your pitch,
anywhere near the pitch...
-Let's just get in there.
-All right.
Good luck.
All right.
Straight ahead.
It's great.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
What's your name?
Uh, my name is Ben, and I'm
from Philadelphia.
Hi, Ben.
Hey, I like that, Ben.
How old are you, how old are
you, Ben?
Um, I'm 18 years old.
And how did you happen here,
onto our little stage?
Uh, well, I went into work
one day, and I sang for my co-workers,
And he's like, "I know talent when I see it,
so I Want you to go audition."
-Really?
-And so I did, yes.
Okay, well.
What do you want to sing?
Um, I was gonna do
"Born This Way", by Lady Gaga.
Okay.
♪ My mama told me when I, ♪
♪ Was young we were all born, ♪
♪ Superstars, ♪
Holy [Bleep].
♪ She rolled my hair put my, ♪
♪ Lipstick on in the glass of, ♪
♪ Her boudoir, ♪
♪ So hold your head up girl, ♪
♪ And you'll go far, listen to, ♪
♪ Me when I say, ♪
Ay yi yi.
I'll stop there.
"I'll stop there."
So-you're-because you knew,
right?
I think I went up too high,
there.
I can do-can I do a different song?
-Sure.
-I think I went too high.
There, okay.
[Nicki Minaj's "Super Bass"]
♪ Can't you hear that boom, ♪
♪ Badoom boom boom badoom boom, ♪
♪ Bass, got that super bass, ♪
♪ Boom badoom boom boom badoom, ♪
♪ Boom bass, got that super, ♪
♪ Bass, ♪
♪ Boom boom boom bass, ba ba, ♪
♪ Ba boom bass ba ba ba ba, ♪
♪ Boom badoom boom boom badoom, ♪
♪ Boom bass got that super, ♪
♪ Bass boom badoom boom boom, ♪
♪ Badoom boom boom bass, ♪
♪ Got that super bass. ♪
In the craziest, weirdest way,
that was actually better.
Yeah, it was.
Still was terrible, it was still terrible,
but it was better terrible.
Take that rubber band off the bottom of your
[Bleep] and lay up a little, will you?
I'm feeling a little stuffy today, so...
Yeah.
"You got to be kidding me."
You're cute.
Shall we vote?
Yeah.
Yeah, we should vote.
Oh, I'm feeling like it's
"no," though.
Yeah.
No, well, you don't know.
You don't know yet.
Steven, yes?
Not your best audition.
No, it wasn't.
Jennifer, yes?
It's a "no" for me too, babe.
Wish I was feeling better.
Randy, yes?
Definite "no."
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Wish I was feeling better.
All right.
It was fun.
All right, have a good day.
-Okay.
-You too.
Any regrets in there?
Um, just that I started too high,
and that I wish I was not feeling so sick.
He's been a little sick.
Oh, have you?
Since Tuesday, yeah, I'm...
He's lost some of his upper range.
I mean, I'm sorry-yeah.
But I can't do falsetto
right now.
As Ben departs, tragically,
We are left to wonder,
if he had not been too sick,
What would that falsetto voice
have sounded like?
♪ Boom badoom boom boom badoom, ♪
♪ bass, got that super bass, ♪
Yay, you made it, baby!
Coming up, Portland shows
serious heart.
We still have life and we still have
another chance to keep going.
Wow.
Plus, a showcase of talent
that simply can't be beat.
♪ American Idol, yeah! ♪
Welcome to American Idol.
Judges were a little soft this morning....
The eggs in Portland weren't.
treating them too well, but now,
We're here after lunch with a
little bit more energy.
That's nice, I like the way
you ad-libbed that.
Welcome back to American Idol.
Here in Portland.
Slow start to the morning here,
but after a nice healthy lunch,
it seems everybody's energy is back.
♪ I'm feeling good, ♪
And Jermaine Jones might be able to
take the judges' spirits over the top.
My family is all music.
I began singing in church
when I was young.
It's my life, I eat it, I breathe it,
I sleep it, it's just me.
That's my mommy.
I'm a mama's boy, I guess.
The night that I delivered Jermaine,
I did a whole church service and a concert.
So we were saying that
he came out singing.
We don't know anything else.
That's what we were founded on.
-It's true.
-It's very real.
It's not like somebody who just decided
that they were going to try to be a singer.
We were born this way.
It's just amazing the gift that
God has placed in him.
And, yes, the world needs
to know it.
They need to know it.
It's time, I believe it's time.
It's my time, it's my turn.
And that's where my tears...
Like, they're tears of joy
and excitement.
Mm-hm.
I am extremely proud of Jermaine.
He has the stature, the
attitude, he has "It".
And he can do it.
He can do it.
He will do it.
I love you, mom.
How tall are you, dog?
6'8" and a 1/2", and don't
take away my half.
6'8" and a 1/2"...
We won't, we won't.
Wow.
What are you going to sing?
I'm going to sing "Superstar"
by Luther.
Awesome.
Whenever you're ready.
♪ Long ago, ♪
♪ And oh so far away, ♪
♪ I fell in love with you, ♪
♪ Before the second show, ♪
♪ Don't you remember you told, ♪
♪ Me you loved me, baby, ♪
♪ You said you'd be coming, ♪
♪ Back this way again, ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, baby, oh, ♪
♪ Baby, ♪
♪ I love you, ♪
♪ I really do! ♪
Mm, nice.
Mm.
When you show the dynamics with the low,
with the power, with the softness, I love it.
-We haven't had someone...
-You just don't hear it, it's,
A natural gift that you have...
Thank you so much.
In the way that you sing that
you don't hear every day.
Really spiritual voice.
Took me away.
Oh, thank you.
Um, I can see you're really nervous.
Mm-hm.
I actually heard the song
through your nerves,
When that happens, that's the magic.
You've got that gift, you know?
And, man, when we hear that...
Thank you so much.
Definitely got something
unique jumping off, vocally.
Yeah, for sure.
I say yes.
Just one more thing before I
v
ote: Loosen up a little bit.
I know you're super-nervous...
I mean, I'm...
You're sweating like a fool.
Up in here, dude.
I can't-I mean, really bad.
Either way, I'm going to say,
Yes.
Dude, I'm gonna say yes.
Welcome to Hollywood, Jermaine!
Yeah, you made it, baby!
The gentle giant goes to
Hollywood.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you so much, I greatly
appreciate it.
All right, man.
Oh!
I'm going.
I'll be there.
He's a big guy.
6'8...
Is that what he said, 6'8"?
Yeah.
He felt gentle-spirited,
though, no?
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
A gentle giant.
Yeah.
Hello?
Guess what, mommy?
You're going to Hollywood?
I'm going to Hollywood.
Be quiet.
You're going to break the
speaker!
All right, shut it down.
After the break...
What great naggers!
Oh!
The talent in Portland has
everyone at attention.
Ah! I love that.
We are feeling you right now.
You're going to Hollywood!
Yes!
Ow!
It's another beautiful day
here in the city of roses...
Portland rocks!
And our day two auditioners are geared up
and ready to rock out for the judges.
Steven and Randy arrive,
raring to go.
Ryan, what's up, man?
Randy's had his coffee this
morning apparently.
Ryan's here!
What do I think of Portland?
God, I had a couple of
Girlfriends from here.
But there was a little snag
for Jennifer.
I'm waiting for a pair fo tights...
I'm missing my black tights,
and I'm ready to kill somebody.
Oh, you know what?
I'm sorry, I meant to give them back.
That's all right, I swear.
We need to borrow your
tights, Meghan.
She's getting the black tights!
Wardrobe malfunction averted,
the judges take their seats,
ready for a busy day.
Let's get it in, Portland.
All righty.
Let's go.
And a tight schedule is something
our first contestant knows all about.
You've got a whole bunch of
people here.
They're all with you?
Yup.
Is he with you?
All right, come over here.
That was a real mom tone.
"All right, come over here,
come over here now."
So, you've got your hands full,
right?
To say the least.
Why was this, personally,
something that you wanted to do?
Um, I've been held back from a lot of people,
and just told that I couldn't do it.
Do you think mommy can do it?
Is mommy a good singer?
Yeah.
Okay. We'll take your word for it.
My mommy's the next American Idol.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Hi, how are you?
Hi, baby, what's your name?
I'm Britney Kellogg.
How old are you?
27.
So tell us, why are you here?
It might make me cry.
Mm.
Two beautiful little boys.
And I was married, and he held me
back from doing what I wanted to do,
And this is what I want to do.
And he's a basketball player,
and I pursued his dreams with him.
Then he decided to go and pursue
other women instead of basketball, so...
Here I am.
Wow, that's, uh...
Sorry.
Well, you have your two little boys.
Yes, so...
And here you are.
And here I am.
So let's make it happen.
What are you going to sing?
I'm going to sing
"You're No Good".
You think?
Wonder that, yeah, really.
Perfect, right?
Are you sure, are you sure?
You have a beautiful
sense of humor.
Yeah, this is great.
Thank you.
Come on, mama.
Okay.
♪ Feeling better now that, ♪
♪ We're through, ♪
♪ Feeling better 'cause I'm, ♪
♪ Over you, ♪
♪ I learned my lesson it left, ♪
♪ A scar, ♪
♪ Now I can see who you really, ♪
♪ Are you're no good you're no, ♪
♪ Good you're no good baby, ♪
♪ You're no good, ♪
That's right.
♪ I'm gonna say it again, ♪
♪ You're no good you're no, ♪
♪ Good you're no good baby, ♪
♪ You're no good, ♪
All right.
Britney, I'm feeling you right now.
All right, yo, yo, I like the attitude,
I like the vibe, I like you getting, "Ah!"
Yeah, all of it.
I love that.
The rasp, the tone...
Thank you.
Everything, love.
Yes.
And yes, so you're going to
Hollywood.
Keep that passion, though,
about whatever you're singing,
you know what I'm saying?
Put your heart in it.
Thank you.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure, baby.
How is it being a mom?
'Cause there's so many people
that say, "you can't do this.
You're a mom, like, how can you.
Leave your kids"?
No, you don't leave your
kids, we never leave the kids.
Look, the kids are right here!
Oh, my God, the kids are
right here!
See, your...
Hey, you guys.
Britney.
Your kids are right here, my
kids are right out there.
Those are cute kids.
You have to be happy so
they're happy.
Look at all the blessings that are here with
you and those two special ones.
It takes a village to raise babies.
My mom's here with me too.
You make it happen.
When you have dreams,
you make them happen.
And they're only better for it.
Thank you so much.
God bless you, mama.
Yeah, yeah.
God bless you.
Congratulations.
See you in Hollywood.
Woo!
Britney, Britney!
Bye.
Good-bye, boy
bye, you guys.
Thank you so much.
He blew me a kiss.
Aw.
Look at that, "my daughter's.
The next American Idol."
Is that right?
By the way?
She just might be.
Mommy's going to Hollywood.
So day two starts off on a
positive note.
And 21-year-old Sam Gershman...
Was hoping she could keep the
party going.
Turn.
It seems she already has the
support of the holding room.
Let's see how she does with the
Judges.
Hello!
Holy [Bleep] Sticks.
How are you?
Hey, what's going on?
Wow.
Not much.
Who are you?
This is crazy.
I'm Sam... Gershman.
Sam Gershwin?
Gershman.
Oh, I was gonna go, "wow."
But wait, my dad's name is Ira.
All right, what are you
singing, baby?
I'm going to sing,
"I'm a Woman".
Okay.
♪ If you come to me sickly, ♪
♪ You know I'm gonna make you, ♪
♪ Well, ♪
♪ If you come to me hexed up, ♪
♪ You know I'm gonna break the, ♪
♪ Spell you know, ♪
♪ If you come to me hungry, ♪
♪ Well I'm gonna fill ya full, ♪
♪ Of grits, ♪
♪ But if it's love that you're, ♪
♪ Likin' I'll kiss you and, ♪
♪ Give you the shivering fits, ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a woman, ♪
♪ W-o-m-a-n oh I'll say it, ♪
♪ Again-uh, ♪
"Again-uh."
♪ Oh woman ohh, ♪
♪ Yeah, ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, ♪
♪ Ow!, ♪
♪ A woman, ♪
Sam, the one-act show,
I love the...
I'm nervous.
Could you have been
any more perky?
I know, my voice gets high.
I'm a little nervous right now.
Wow.
You're going to make a good
Easter Bunny.
Well, I'm jewish, so...
Oh, that's okay.
She's jewish.
It's a little too "Broadway" for what
this Idol has been pulling out of people.
That's who you are, that's okay.
Your personality is so Bubbly,
you obviously belong on a stage.
We're not saying, "don't do
this," you know what I mean?
That's not what we're saying.
Go ahead, baby,
you want to take your vote?
Uh, I'm going to say no.
I don't think you're ready.
Steven?
I don't think you're ready either.
I think you should keep going,
but I think you need to
Work on some things if you want
to do this, specifically.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you.
Well, the party may have
ended for Sam, but the one here,
In Portland is just getting started.
Coming up!
Will this unique
Performance thrill the judges?
♪ Bah, ♪
Or leave them spechless?
And American Idol gives new hope
to a liberian refugee.
Never thought we'd make it,
'cause I saw so many people
just, like, perish.
So you sang for your life?
Yes, I do.
We're back in beautiful
Portland.
With its lush landscapes and
environmental consciousness,
Portland is one of the greenest
cities in the country.
And the next contestant was
hoping that Oregon green would,
Turn into gold.
Hi.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
What's your name, dude?
My name is David Weed.
David Weed, is "Weed" really
your last name?
It is, I did not pick that name, no.
You're just lucky nobody gave you
the first name of "Smokey", huh?
No, no, they weren't thinking ahead.
-I like that.
-"Thinking ahead"?
-Where are you from?
I'm from Mountain Home,
Idaho.
And what do you do there?
I work in the fast food Industry.
So you're tired of asking people
if they want fries with that, right?
Exactly.
Every time I say that, I die a
little inside.
Mm.
Aw, come on.
Man, oh, man.
It's not that bad, it's not
as bad as I'm making it sound.
"Paper or plastic," it could be.
So you work in fast food, but you
want to be an American Idol, right?
I do.
What are you singing?
I'm singing "Tom Sawyer" by
Rush.
Okay.
♪ Though his mind is not, ♪
♪ For rent, ♪
♪ Don't put him down as, ♪
♪ Arrogant, ♪
♪ His reserve a quiet defense, ♪
♪ Riding out the day's events, ♪
♪ The river, ♪
♪ What you say about his, ♪
♪ Company is what you say, ♪
♪ About society, ♪
♪ Catch the mystery catch the, ♪
♪ Myth catch the spirit catch, ♪
♪ The spit. ♪
In your mind, is that the way Geddy Lee,
from the band, sounds to you, from Rush?
Aw, I'm hoping I don't sound
exactly like him, but I mean...
No, he actually sounds
really good.
What's the dream here, other
than singing?
I don't know, I like stand-up
Comedy, I guess.
Do you have a good joke you
can tell us?
Not the richest family growing up, so we
played a game called "earthquake," uh...
Okay.
It's when you take your glasses
and you go, "earthquake."
That's your joke?
Yup, that's one of them.
Wow, okay.
All right, David.
All right, all right, David.
We're going to take a vote,
okay, sweetie?
Okay.
I'm going to say not yet.
I'm going to say definitely.
No.
Okay.
It's a no for today, baby.
It's a no?
Okay.
Nice to meet you, man.
Thank you, okay.
Thank you.
See you later.
Hey, David, empty-handed?
I am.
Where'd you misfire?
Oh, man, I was pretty nervous.
I mean, they just didn't
seem to like it at all.
Sorry it didn't work out.
Oh, thanks, no problem.
All right, thanks.
Okay, buddy.
It's just so strange to...
Everyone for 22 years say that,
It's, you know, you've got a,
Phenomenal voice, and then walk
up to these three people and,
They just say,
"no, that's not even close."
Don't have the chops.
And while David may be feeling
a little down, I'm up to no good.
What are you seeing?
Is Ryan bored?
Ryan must be bored.
Wow, man.
He must really be bored today.
That's insane. That...
That was great.
My attempt to turn
the day around is working.
Let's see if our next contestant
can continue the trend.
Come on, Portland.
Hi.
Hello.
How are you?
Good, how are you?
I'm good.
What's your name?
My name is Romeo Dionne.
I'm 22 years old.
I'm from Liberia.
Tell us your story, baby.
In 1990, there was a civil
War in Liberia.
My father was an immigration
Commander, and he heard about
The war, so he sent us to Ghana.
And we lived in a refugee camp,
hoping there was a chance for us
to come to the U.S for a better life.
Waited so long, and never
thought we'd make it, 'cause I
Saw so many people just, like,
perish.
And we finally got that chance
to come here.
It was a great day.
That day, I got a chance to know
what "better life" means...
On that day.
There is no pot of gold in America.
But if you have patience...
Then you make it.
[Bob Marley's "Is This Love"]
♪ I want to love you, ♪
♪ I want to love and treat you, ♪
♪ Love and treat you right, ♪
♪ I want to love you every day, ♪
♪ And every night, ♪
♪ We'll be together oh oh with, ♪
♪ A roof right over our heads, ♪
♪ Is this love is this love is, ♪
♪ This love is this love that, ♪
♪ I'm feeling ooh is this love, ♪
♪ Is this love is this love is, ♪
♪ This love that I'm feeling, ♪
He's in there doing his thing.
So, who are you?
I'm Ryan.
Junior.
Junior, I would've guessed that.
I know.
I love that you sing in
your heart, you know?
And how long were you in the Camp for?
Um, from 5 years old all the
way to 2001.
Oof.
Wow.
So you sang for your life.
Yes, I do.
Wow, I hear it in your voice.
Thank you.
Jennifer, what do you think?
Man, I love your vibe, and
your flavor.
I'm a little bit worried about,
Where you're going to go in the,
Competition, and the songs,
You're going to
have to sing and stuff
Let's take a vote, let's see.
Steven, yes or no?
I'm going to say yes.
Jennifer?
I'm going to say little tiny
Yes.
Aha.
I'm going to say yes too.
Guess what, baby.
Going to Hollywood.
Going to Hollywood!
America, I'm coming, I'm.
Coming.
Different vibe than anybody
else we've seen yet.
It's a completely different vibe.
And probably won't have
anybody else like that.
And, dude, refugee camp?
Oh, my God, dude, I don't know,
man.
I feel so good, I feel so
alive, I feel so nice.
Coming up...
The Ryan Seacrest donut.
Steven and I get a sugary treat.
I would really love to sing
one of your songs, Steven.
Nice.
And is this the sweetest face in Orego?
Everybody loves [Bleep],
okay?
Stick around for a
Lip-smacking good time.
It's just after 2:00 here
in Portland.
I'm the next American Idol.
Everyone is searching for the
recipe of that golden ticket.
There you have it, the
Ryan Seacrest donut.
Too short!
And now 22-year-old Naomi
Gillies has a treat for Steven.
What are you singing today?
Um, if it's okay with you, I would really
love to sing one of your songs, Steven.
If that's all right.
Which one?
"Cryin'".
Oh, nice.
♪ There was a time, ♪
♪ When I was so broken-hearted, ♪
♪ Love wasn't much, ♪
♪ Of a friend of mine no, no, ♪
♪ But the tables have turned, ♪
♪ Yeah, me and them ways, ♪
♪ Have parted, ♪
♪ That kind of love, ♪
♪ It was the killing kind, ♪
♪ I was cryin' when I met you, ♪
♪ Now I'm trying to forget you, ♪
♪ Your love is sweet misery, ♪
♪ Yeah I was crying, ♪
♪ Just to get you, ♪
♪ Now I'm dyin' to let you, ♪
♪ Do-, ♪
Nice.
Ah, nice, very interesting.
Different, good, yeah.
You belted it out, we've been
missing that all morning.
Yeah, big, nice tone.
Love your voice too.
Nice, round tone.
The minute you opened your
mouth, I was like, "wow!".
Very, very nice.
If you got it, you got it,
you got it.
See, that's how you do it.
Yes.
And I'm going to say yes,
because you're going to
Hollywood.
Yes, baby.
Naomi keeps Portland's hopes
alive with her ticket to Hollywood.
But for the next two hours, the dreams
Of so many others were
laid to rest.
Not yet, no.
Listen, dog, didn't quite
do it for me.
Yeah, I think you need some
work, okay?
No, no, no, no.
I didn't make it.
A lot of broken hearts, man.
[Bleep] Off.
You're going to make me go
Naomi Campbell all over you.
Get out of my way, move!
Really?
[Bleep] Serious!
Would've meant a whole lot to me.
Just feel like I'm never good enough.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm watching this thinking,
This is getting way
too depressing.
There's got to be someone who
can make us smile.
Rock 'n roll, ow!
Eh, maybe not that much.
I'm Ben Harrison, I'm 28 years old,
I'm from Eugene, Oregon, and I'm adorable.
I'm adorable.
It's my time to shine.
I'm going to have a ball.
Oh, yeah, everybody loves
[bleep], okay?
American Idol 12 rock 'n...
Or it's 11.
American Idol 11, rock 'n roll.
Rock 'n roll.
Wah-ow!
That last beat definitely
Rock'n Rolled.
All right, we're good.
-All right, so we're out?
-Yeah, we're out.
This next one, if they're
boring...
That's what they're getting.
Ah, yeah.
Here he is.
Hi.
Finally, finally.
Finally I have arrived.
Okay, so now that we've met
already, what's your name?
I'm Ben.
Ben.
Ben Harrison, I'm 28 years old
from Eugene, Oregon.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Says here you played in rock bands
with a lot of old dudes, man.
Like, what do you mean by that?
I don't think they dig
the Baby face.
Oh.
So they, uh, keep me for two
weeks and then say, "We want
Someone with more experience."
You think they don't kick you
Out because you're not good or...?
I rock it, man.
Oh, yeah, man.
That's not the reason.
They're jealous.
This guy's going to lay it
down, watch this.
What are you going to sing?
I'm going to sing.
"Somebody To Love" by Queen.
Okay.
♪ I get down on my knees, ♪
♪ And I start to pray, ♪
♪ Till the tears roll down, ♪
♪ From my eyes, Lord, ♪
♪ Can't anybody find me, ♪
♪ Somebody to-o-o-o-o-o-o, ♪
♪ Love, ♪
Oh, wow.
Okay, that did it.
Well, uh...
No ticket?
Didn't make it.
Why? Why? Why? Why?
What happened, man?
Uh...
Come on.
Come on, let's get some love.
Come on, come on.
So glad my family was here to
support me.
We're going to have some pizza.
What was that audition?
What was that?
I didn't puke or pee my pants.
Or any of the stuff that I was scared
about, so it wasn't that bad.
No one has more fun than me.
Take it easy, man.
When we return, one more audition
that leaves the judges stunned.
When he did wake up, he
didn't know who I was.
Wow.
The sun is setting on our
Portland auditions.
For many, the journey to create a better
life has unfortunately come to an end.
I'm going to say not yet.
No for me too.
It's a no for me. Not yet.
I'm sorry, baby.
Aww.
We love you, Nicky.
It's very emotional.
I'm just glad I did it.
But for Jessica Philips,
this is more than
a single fream.
It's another step
towards a miracle.
Hello.
Hey, hey.
How are you guys today?
Great.
Good.
What's your name?
My name is Jessica.
Jessica, where you from?
I'm from Brooklyn, New York.
Tell me about your boyfriend.
Well, his name is Angelo and
we've been together five years.
We fell in love, it was like we
were meant to be together.
But last Easter Sunday, he actually
had a stroke, a massive stroke.
We were out, celebrating a
Friend's birthday.
And I turned around and his
entire face was just washed.
I shook him and he didn't
respond to me.
He stayed in the hospital for
about a month and a half.
When he did wake up, he didn't
know who I was.
The entire relationship itself
has changed.
Now, I'm really a caretaker.
And there's a different type of
love that I feel now and,
A different type of responsibility
that I have now to him and just,
To life in general.
Let's start with these words.
Speech therapy is an everyday
thing for us.
Every day is just a struggle,
but every day is
also a blessing.
Because we still have life and
we still have another chance to keep going.
It's the hardest thing I've ever
done in my life, still going through it.
And I just pray every day that
I'll be able to continue.
I love you, I do.
I love you too.
I know, I know.
Wow.
So this is the dream right, now?
You're going to be good, I feel.
-I hope you like it.
-Well, let's see.
-What are you singing?
-We got our fingers crossed.
Come on, mama, what you gonna sing?
"Again" by Faith Evans.
♪ Now I done felt, ♪
♪ A lot of pain, ♪
♪ I done seen a lot of things, ♪
♪ From struggling, ♪
♪ And broken hearts, ♪
♪ To fancy cars, oh yeah, ♪
♪ And even though, ♪
♪ My money change, ♪
♪ I tried my best, ♪
♪ To stay the same, ♪
♪ But you know with more money, ♪
♪ More problems came, ♪
♪ But if I had to do it, ♪
♪ All again, ♪
♪ I wouldn't take away, ♪
♪ The rain, ♪
♪ 'Cuz I know it made me, ♪
♪ Who I am, ♪
♪ If I had to do it all again, ♪
♪ I've learned so much, ♪
♪ From my mistakes, ♪
♪ That's how I know, ♪
♪ He's watching me. ♪
Wow.
Nice, I like you, man.
You did that really well.
I know you ran out of breath a
little bit at the end there.
-But...
-I love it.
Shall we vote?
Yeah.
Go ahead, baby.
I'm going to say yes.
I'm going to say yes too.
You're through to Hollywood, baby, yes!
Thank you, guys.
Thank you so much.
Yeah.
American Idol will change my life
in that I'll be able to get back into music.
That's how we met, doing music.
And with all the health things
that have been going on,
We haven't been able
to do anything really.
So this will really kick the
music back into gear for us.
You all right?
Yeah.
I love you.
I love you too.
With the Portland additions oficially
coming to a close...
That talent in the city of roses
definitely delivered.
Yes!
As 45 contestants seized
their opportunity and earned
Their golden tickets to
Hollywood.
I had all three yeses.
Oh, my Gosh!
This poor young boy.
Yes, you're going to
Hollywood!
Yes!
I can't believe this is happening.
I'm going to Hollywood, baby.
What!
Portland redeemed itself.
They really like me.
It was so, so good.
A nice ending.
I'm telling you something,
there's some hot talent here.
Portland, all right.
Woo! Yes!
I got on!
Whoo!
Tomorrow night!
Hey, everybody, come on, let me
hear you.
Our auditions finish at
the gateway to the west.
Where are we?
St. Louis!
Where we find the loud...
The strong...
Want to taste your dream?
You chase it!
And the next big thing!
You know you're gonna
be a star, right?
So meet us in St. Louis!
For the best of the midwest!
Well, mostly.
Out of my face!
-Don't quit your day job!
-You're awful!
Sorry I was a little off.