Every time American Idol
comes on, me and my parents
sit down in the living room and
watch it on television together.
We always decide who should win
and who shouldn't.
I'm all done here.
Wish me luck.
We are going to St. Louis to try
out for American Idol.
There's the arch.
The winner is...
Carrie Underwood!
Thank you.
Now a new crop of talent
will take that same trip...
Bye!
There's the arch!
Hoping to create the magic
all over again.
St. Louis, here we come.
Can they do it?
We're about to find out.
This is St. Louis and...
This is American Idol.
It's a beautiful day here in the
gateway to the west...
Good old St. Louis.
Welcome to St. Louis!
The crowd of 10,000 has shown
up for the chance of a lifetime.
Louie, Louie,
aye-yi-yi-yi,
Let's get the auditions started.
Let's go.
Everybody, come on!
Let me hear you!
It's too bad that not everyone
shares that same enthusiasm
We gotta blame somebody for
all this congestion that your
people are gonna create.
I read about this a while back,
that this was gonna occur.
They says there are 20,000
people here, gonna be here,
all trying to get
their day in the sun.
Beats the hell out of working,
right?
Say that to the judges, who
have thousands of hopefuls
waiting to get their Idol on.
Last time they were here in St. Louis,
they found Carrie Underwood,
so we should be so lucky.
While Jennifer is all business,
Steven and Randy arrive
in rock star fashion.
Where the hell are we?
Where's the arch, man?
Where's the arch?
Other than the arch and the music,
what do you know about this town?
Um, a couple girlfriends from here.
Actually, their old addresses.
All kidding aside, the Steven
Tyler fan club was on hand
as usual and putting us behind
schedule.
All right, guys, they gotta
go up.
Thank you very much.
Hello, St. Lou.
Are you ready?
Yeah, let's go, St. Louis!
So the city that produced one of our
biggest stars is center stage once more.
Come on, bring it on.
And the pressure is on for
our first contestant.
My name is Johnny Keeser.
I'm 22 years old, and I'm from
Pompano Beach, Florida.
When I was three years old, my
parents divorced, and my father
and I, it's just been us two
since I was little.
He's-he's a pretty good mom and
a dad.
I would pack his lunches.
I loved packing his lunches.
I can make a mean peanut butter
and jelly sandwich.
Like, really-
Meanest
I love him.
I really do.
And he's... He's great.
We always took the boat out.
We're just boys.
He's like my brother more than
my dad.
We've got each other's back.
I knew as soon as I was in the
air, I was like, nah, I'm going down.
Hey.
How's it going?
What's your name, man?
Johnny.
Johnny, what's going down?
How old are you?
22 years old.
Where you from, dog?
From Pompano Beach, Florida.
And what do you do in
Pompano?
I'm a server at an Italian
restaurant and I'm going to
school at the university of
central Florida.
But your dream is to be...?
The next American Idol.
Aha!
Outside, Johnny's family are treated
to a firsthand glimpse of all the action.
So what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing "Change is
Gonna Come" by Sam Cooke.
Beautiful song.
One of my favorites. Do it.
Knock it out of the park.
I was born by the river,
In a little tent,
Oh, and just like the river,
I've been running,
Ever since,
It's been a long,
Should we just vote now?
No, keep singing.
A long time coming,
But I know,
A change is gonna come,
Whoa, yes it will,
How old are you?
22.
It's been,
It's been too hard living,
Ooh, yes.
But I'm afraid to die,
What do you do right now?
I work at an Italian
restaurant.
Keep singing.
'Cause I don't know,
What's out there, yeah,
Beyond the sky,
You know you're gonna be a
star, right?
Keep singing.
Keep singing, keep singing.
It's been a long,
Oh, my God.
A long time coming,
But I know, whoa,
Yeah,
A change is gonna come,
Thank you, God.
Oh, man.
Oh!
Oh, yes it will,
Just stop.
Whoo!
Dog, that was crazy!
So what do you think when
you watch the show and you see
these Idols come out, year after year?
I could do that.
Yeah.
In your spare time, right?
Johnny's in the house.
Johnny in the house, man.
That was great.
Oh, my God, man.
I can't take it.
Uh, where's this boy going,
Jennifer, Steven, Randy?
Oh, my God,
You're going to Hollywood!
Yes! Yes!
I let them watch.
Oh.
We let 'em watch.
Randy's doing this, and Jennifer, you know,
they're all singing along and enjoying it.
They're awesome.
Yeah.
I figured you'd think that.
I like them.
I think they thought the same
of you.
He is sexy.
Are you [Bleep] kidding?
Yes! Yes!
It's been a whole waiting
game, and it's over now because
now this is in my hand.
It's a great start for Johnny
and the judges.
Exciting!
Dude, that was good right
there.
All right, St. Lou!
So good.
St. Lou.
Get ready, America, 'cause
I'm coming to Hollywood.
Over the next hour, St. Louis
proves why it's a gateway to
Idol success.
You're one of the best female
voices we've heard.
You wanna chase your dream,
You chase it.
Wow.
But for some...
Terrible.
It's the end of the road.
Don't quit your day job.
She bangs, she bangs,
oh, baby,
when she moves, she moves,
Over the past 11 years, we've
come across every kind of singer.
Yeah!
I feel the earth move,
under my feet,
any way the wind blows,
doesn't really matter to me,
The one thing we've learned is
some auditions are best seen and not heard.
What the-?
Welcome back to St. Louis,
Missouri, where inside the
audition room, dreams are on the
line.
I'm gonna say no, not yet.
Oh, man.
But outside, the crowd is
still optimistic as they get to
know one another.
It's very-the coolest thing
about it is that, like, the fact
that we are all from so many
different places and that we all
came here for this one reason,
to sing, and we're all friends now.
Yeah, but whci one of you
is the next American Idol?
I am, right here.
After all, American Idol is
where this generation comes
together...
Everyone's singing,
everyone's having a good time.
One experience shared by
thousands whose paths would
otherwise never have crossed.
We just-this is, like, how
we do.
This is like our new family
here.
Each of them has a story to
tell.
My parents auditioned for
American Idol during season four.
They just told me I wouldn't
be able to do nothing...
And I do everything they said I couldn't
do.
Maybe you know one of them...
One day I got the courage to
sing in front of somebody, and
they said, "hey, that's pretty
good."
Or maybe you are one of them.
My name is Jarrod Salmon.
I'm from St. Louis...
I'm Justin Thiel.
I'm 26 years old.
My name is Rachelle Lamb.
I'm 26 years old, and I am from
Mountain view, Missouri.
I am doing American Idol for my
daughter and I.
Aren't you the next American
Idol?
No, you are.
Aah!
So tell me how you ended up
here today.
Well, I am actually going
through a divorce, and one of my
big dreams has been to chase my dream
of singing and actually accomplish it.
He held me back from it.
Doing American Idol is something
that I've always wanted to do,
and I know it's something that
can give us a better life and
show her, you know, don't let
anybody hold you back.
You want to chase your dream...
You want to chase your dream,
you chase it, and mommy will
always be behind you.
Good luck, mommy.
Aw, thank you.
Hey, now, who-who's her?
Hi, how are you?
This is Madison.
You are-?
And I'm Rachelle.
Hi, Rachelle.
Tell me a little bit about
yourself.
Um, I used to be a
professional singer, and then I
went off and fell in love and
got married, and he took all
them dreams away from me.
And then we decided-
we do things for love
sometimes.
Yeah.
Then we decided to split up, and
my girlfriend said, "let's go
try out for American Idol," and
I said, "I've got just the song,"
and it was one he didn't like.
Perfect.
That's the one we want to
hear.
And Madison was down with you
trying out, too, right?
Maddy wanted to come out here
and meet you guys and-
aw. Hi, maddy.
I saw you this morning,
Maddy.
Did you see me?
Mm-hmm.
So cute.
What are you gonna sing?
Um, "Find somebody New".
It's by Faith Hill.
Okay.
Wow.
Find somebody new.
Madison, you gonna dance
along with mom?
No.
Tap dance?
You gotta tap dance along with
her.
Maybe-maybe it'll dance it
up.
All right.
Good morning, dearly beloved,
We're gathered here today,
To watch two people we know,
Make a big mistake,
They'll stand up,
at the altar,
and solemnly swear "I do",
they'll be together forever,
till they find somebody new,
the bride is a flirt,
and the groom is worse,
as he's putting the ring,
on her,
he's checking out,
the bridesmaids,
thinkin' that he might make,
the maid of honor honor,
I thought that one was pretty
fun.
It is pretty funny.
Oh!
...at everybody's wedding.
I think you sing great.
Thank you.
I think you've got a great
sense of melody and, you know, I
like your moxie.
Yes, yeah.
A lot of energy in your voice,
a lot of passion.
It sounded really, really great.
Thank you.
A lot of pure tone.
I love it.
Yep.
I mean, I'm-I'm impressed.
Thank you.
Wow.
Maddy, mommy's good.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, who taught me everything
I know?
You?
Let's take a vote.
Randy?
Yes. I'll say yes.
Oh, my gosh.
I'll say yes too.
And I will say yes, and
you're going to Hollywood.
Whoo!
Mom and maddy, going to
Hollywood.
Yeah.
Let's go tell everybody else.
Thank you.
Wow, a real cowgirl.
Yeah?
Cute little girl.
Wow.
Ah, I made it, I made it, I
made it, aah!
You let Maddy go back.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
How'd you feel when you were
singing up there in front of the judges?
You know what?
I actually felt totally at home
at something that I want to do
and that I had my little girl
there beside me, and it was just
the biggest dream I think I've
ever done in my life.
Coming up, we meet more of St.
Louis' finest...
Hmm.
I will [Bleep] hit you.
Or maybe not.
Plus, two incredible stories of
courage in the face of
adversity.
My dad had to go to drug and
alcohol rehabilitation.
I kind of got pushed around
and bullied.
I'll tell you what, man.
That was so beautiful, you made
me cry.
That's how good that was just
now.
Welcome back to St. Louis,
where the "show me" state has
shown us some pretty sweet
sounds.
That's what all this is.
People with a good set of pipes.
Okay.
-Correct?
-Yeah.
I don't know if 20,000 of 'em
all have a good set of pipes.
I wouldn't want to listen to
that many people.
There used to be,
a graying tower,
alone on the sea,
you became the light,
on the dark side of me,
love remains,
It says here, "music is my
wife," right?
Yeah.
Your wife's gonna be looking for
a divorce, dog, you keep singing
like that.
So the good streak appears to
be over, and as midday
approaches, St. Louis is turning
into the gateway to the worst.
You just gotta ignite,
the light,
Here now,
between the other side,
it's a crime,
we could have had it all,
rolling in the deep,
The thunder rolls,
the thunder rolls,
and the lightning strikes,
Whoa, whoa, man, hold on.
This is not candy store, rock
'n' roll, corporation jellyroll,
play the singles, it ain't me,
it's programmed insanity,
you ascap, if bmi could ever
make a Mountain fly, if Japanese
can boil teas, then where the
[bleep] Are my royalties?
Hmm.
Okay, so we hit a little snag
here.
Maybe the judges need to channel
some good energy back into the
room.
Okay, let's do it.
Wonder powers.
Wonder powers, let's go.
That's right.
Yes, we give each other good
energy.
We can, yes, we can.
In the form of...
Superstars.
That's right.
Will our next contestant have
the power it takes to get that
golden ticket?
Hello.
Hi.
How are you guys doing?
Good, how are you?
Good.
What's your name?
My name is Reese Glockner.
Where from?
St. Louis, Missouri.
Hometown boy.
Yes, sir.
Nice.
So, now, tell me about you
growing up.
Um, it was kind of difficult.
In High School, I got pushed
around and bullied.
I came from a 152-student
lutheran school.
I was swooped into this massive
public High School.
I was so young and so small, I
guess, kids thought they could
take advantage of me.
I debated dropping out of high
school, and so it was kind of
tough.
It was my senior year.
I was just singing down the
hall, and one of the choir
teachers said, "hey, you should
try choir.
You sound really good."
Once I joined choir, it was a
major turning point.
I found a couple friends who
were really supportive, and so
they helped pull me through.
I definitely gained a lot of
confidence, and I think it's
made me who I am today, and I'm
a lot tougher because of it.
It gives you a lot of stuff
to sing about if you write your
own songs, though, right?
Yeah, exactly.
What are you singing today?
I'm gonna sing "Lean On Me"
Do it.
Sometimes in our lives,
we all have pain,
Mmm.
We all have sorrow,
Mmm, mmm.
But if we are wise,
we know that there's,
always tomorrow,
lean on me,
when you're not strong,
and I'll be your friend,
I'll help you carry on,
oh, for it won't be long,
till I'm gonna need,
somebody,
to lean on,
Mmm.
I'll tell you what, man, that
was so beautiful, you made me
cry.
Wow, dude, that's-
that's just how good-that's
how good that was just now.
Wow, that's crazy.
You made me tear up and get
all crazy inside.
Don't even say that to me
right now.
I think.
I haven't heard anything like
that.
Oh, my God.
So, that-is that a yes for
you?
It's a-yeah.
Yeah.
That's a yes for me too.
Oh, my God.
Dude, it's a definitely yes
for me too.
Welcome to Hollywood!
Hollywood!
Hollywood, baby!
You made it!
Thank you so much, you guys.
Whoo!
Sweet!
Hollywood!
Yes!
That-that's phenomenal,
that was.
Congratulations, Reese.
Now, you want to tell them?
How did it go?
It went awesome.
They, uh, said that I was one of
the best singers they've heard.
How'd that make you feel?
Um, pretty amazing.
Wow.
Looks like Reese will fit
right in when he gets to Hollywood
After the break, the day-two
talent comes on strong.
Holy crumb cake.
But first, a father/son
story...
Unreal.
With a surprising outcome.
You look nothing like the way
you sound.
Well, you're not really gonna
use this, are you?
Oh, yeah, they will.
They absolutely will not use
that.
They will use it.
Back with you here in St. Louis.
Look at this crowd.
Look at these people.
With this group, faces like
that, there has got to be some
good talent for our judges.
However, Steven wasn't quite
ready.
He was backstage, giving our
next contestants a little pep
talk.
Listen, you know why you're
here.
Whatever you've got, you know
you've got it.
Yeah.
Right?
You watch Idol.
So just come out and go,
"boo-yah."
I know it's easier said than
done, but I know you can do it.
The pep talk we just had
helped me a lot.
It kind of brought me back down
to earth a little bit and, I
don't know, I feel completely,
completely different than I did
about three minutes ago.
Come on, now.
Let's do this.
There he is.
Hey.
How are we?
Good.
Great, man.
What's your name?
My name is Ethan Jones.
And how old are you?
I'm 22 years old.
What is up here, man?
What's going on?
I had a cut on my forehead,
and in nervousness, I just went
like that, and I scratched it,
and it got open.
Wow.
Hmm.
You're gonna be okay, right?
I'll be fine.
Wow.
Tell me a little bit about
yourself.
Well, I, uh, dropped out of
school...
Yeah?
To be a full-time musician,
and it's with my dad and
basically my extended family.
Now you're in a band with
your dad?
Yeah, he's-he's not, uh, in
the band anymore.
Mm-hmm.
Decided to take a hiatus and
left it to me.
Tell us more about your dad.
My dad helped found one of
the biggest bands in the St.
Louis area.
When you're out all the time
and you're around alcohol and
you're around drugs, it's tough.
My dad had to go to drug and
alcohol rehabilitation.
We had all decided that he
needed to go away and get
counseling for it.
It's been-it's been hard to
talk to him.
I'm not mad at him for
everything that's happened in
the past.
I just want to move forward and
I want that positive synergy to
bring us closer together.
-I can relate to that.
-I like it.
Wow, it's so good that he can
be a power of example to you and
everybody else around him.
I know I work hard to do that as
well.
He's a great man.
Good for you.
You tell him I said hello.
I will. Thank you.
Nice, man.
What are you gonna sing for us?
I'm gonna sing "I'll Be" by
Edwin Mccain.
Oh, let's have it.
Mmm.
The strands in your eyes,
that color them wonderful,
stop me and steal my breath,
and emeralds from mountains,
that thrust towards the sky,
never revealing their depth,
and I'll be,
your crying shoulder,
I'll be love's suicide,
and I'll be better,
when I'm older,
I'll be the greatest fan,
of your life,
-Nice.
-I love the way you sing, man.
Thank you so much.
I just really love the way
you sing.
I like the kind of whole
unassuming thing.
You walk in, you look nothing
like the way you sound.
And when he was sing-when
you were singing-
I hope that's good.
The "I'll be" at the end of
it-
yeah.
And you were kind of smiling
there, I could almost see you,
like, in a country video or
something, your face.
Well, I play in a country
band, so I guess that's a good
thing.
But you didn't sing a country
song.
No.
Unreal.
I play country music because
that's what I was born and
raised on, and I love to do it,
but my heart's in soul.
Well, listen, I mean, we all
love your voice, so-so let's
take a quick vote here.
Jennifer?
I say yes.
Randy?
Steven?
I say yes, man.
Oh, God.
You're going to Hollywood!
Whoo!
And I want to meet your
father, man, when he gets out.
Sure thing.
I'll be setting that up.
Tell him God speed, work it
out, man.
Thank you very much.
Stay strong.
Thank you very much for your
time.
Yeah.
Congratulations, bro.
Yeah!
How does it feel?
Hearing Steven Tyler say that he
loved my voice...
Yeah!
Oh, my God.
Boy, that was good.
Good, natural voice he's got.
Wow.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And I just wanted to call and
tell you that I love you.
And we need to get together
soon.
So proud.
Me too, so...
I'm so proud of you.
Coming up...
All right.
The busiest man on the planet
takes the stage...
And he's brought some backup.
You guys heard him sing while
he was on the job?
I think he's great.
Go get 'em, baby.
Hmm.
Plus, an amazing voice...
Wow.
Ooh, wow.
You don't want to miss.
You're one of the best voices
we've heard.
Oh, my God.
And during this break...
You, me, Madonna,
An exclusive first look at
Madonna's hot new video,
"Give Me All Your Lovin'".
Watch out, St. Louis, here we
come!
St. Louis or bust.
Whoo!
Welcome back to the ultimate
road trip, where contestants
from all over have descended
upon St. Louis, chasing their
dreams.
We're gonna go on a journey
together, you and me, little
camera.
I'll be giving you a tour.
And lifelong memories are
made every step of the way.
This is Katie's first time
ever seeing the arch.
There it is, up there.
And just before kicking off
day two, Steven can't help hide
his enthusiasm.
And that's what it's like
backstage here at Idol, day
after day, night after night.
Jennifer arrives dressed for
the part.
I feel good, hopeful, looking
for stars.
Well, that should be easy.
And no pressure, right, St.
Louis?
As ac/dc put it, it's a long
way to the top to-if you want
to rock and roll.
I think what he means is,
you've got to start somewhere.
I'm a pharmacy tech.
Photographer.
Freelance audio engineer.
What do you do?
Nothing.
But for our next contestant,
his dreams of stardom began
right here.
No, literally right here.
I understand you work here.
I do.
Okay.
So, what's your job here at the
hotel?
I'm a hotel auditor here, so
I do a lot of stuff.
I'm always on the go.
I inspect the building, secure
each entrance, make sure
accounts are settled, guests are
checked out, rooms should be set
up, our vips should be done,
compile reports, revenue
reports, outlet reports, look
for variances in our budget and
revenue, compile that into a
report.
Where's the staff?
What's everybody doing?
Let's get some of the staff
here.
Sure.
Okay, let's go.
Come on.
You're up.
It's your shot.
Go.
It's my shot.
Service with a smile.
Good luck.
Okay, let's go.
Uh-oh.
Wow.
Hi.
What-uh, mark, who are all
these people?
These are my staff members.
They're here with me today.
Oh, you work in this hotel?
All right.
All right, so have you guys
heard him sing while he was on
the job?
Yeah.
Yes, every time, all day.
Yes, yes.
All the time.
He sings all the time.
I do.
But he sings good.
He sings good.
So did you guys all think he
should try out for Idol?
Yes.
Of course.
Yeah.
Yeah, we pushed him.
All right, so what you
singing today?
I'm going to sing "Overjoyed"
by Stevie Wonder today.
Love it.
Is he ready?
He ready.
I'm ready, bird.
Aw.
I like this.
Yeah.
All right, baby.
I've come much too far,
for you now to say,
that I have to throw,
my castle away,
and though you don't believe,
that they do,
they do come true,
for did my dreams come true,
when I looked at you,
and maybe too,
if you would believe,
you too like I,
overjoyed,
over loving,
over you,
Hmm.
All right, baby.
Okay, uh, uh-
i'm nervous.
Hotel staff, what did you
think?
I think he's great.
Go get 'em baby.
Thank you.
You know what, man?
I love how much of life you're
all up into.
But, man, your-your-your-your
voice, you know, and melody,
and keeping that tune, uh, was
lacking a little bit.
I can keep that tune.
Hmm.
A little nervous.
Your voice gives out on you and
everything.
You're like-
and though you don't,
believe that they do,
they do come true,
What do you think, Steven?
You know, man, I love
everything about you except the
melody.
May I please sing a different
song?
Oh.
I want to say yes to you so
bad.
Say it.
I really do, but-but I
can't.
I think I know something that
could change your mind.
What's that?
We are undercover passion,
on the run,
chasing love,
up against the sun,
we are strangers by day,
lovers by night,
Okay, okay, okay.
Look, I'm gonna say no.
You're not quite ready for this.
Jennifer, what do you say?
Yeah, baby.
No, I'm sorry.
Steven?
Man, I'm gonna say no.
But we love you.
We love the staff.
We love all the-
thank you.
It's all right.
All the confidence.
You've got everything else.
Just one audition.
That's all it is.
Nice to meet all of you.
Thank you, guys.
See you later.
Wow.
Thank you, Ryan.
I needed that, 'cause it is hot.
Those stage lights are killing
me.
Oh, Fanny, you lost your
number.
I made it!
Even if they say no, my heart
says yes, so I'll continue to
grow and I'll continue to sing.
What'd you think of your
man's singing?
Uh, he definitely needs a
little work, but he'll try again
next year, though, for sure.
Right on.
If you're ever in St. Louis,
come on by, and I'll sing you a
song.
Well, I don't know about you,
but I, for one, cannot wait.
And maybe too,
if you would believe,
you too like I,
Up next, a father's love
inspires one last audition.
I've always been daddy's
little girl.
I've always followed in his
footsteps.
And it strikes a chord with
one of our judges.
I didn't need to hear that
song right now.
Right, Jen, right?
Welcome back to St. Louis,
where the Idol auditions for
season 11 are coming to an end.
There's one voice left to hear,
and that belongs to Lauren gray.
So you're, uh, in the family
business, huh?
Yeah, of course.
Everybody's in the family
business.
My family is very unique and
kind of, like, famous in this
little, small town.
My family owns and runs their
own one-stop wedding shop.
We work together.
One cooks and one sets up the
wedding stuff.
And I sing every weekend with my
father in a band.
My father puts together weddings
by day and rock star at night.
My father and I are extremely,
extremely close.
I've always been daddy's little
girl.
I've always followed in his
footsteps.
American Idol has always been
a big deal to him.
He is a big part of why I'm here
today.
It would mean the world to me to
go to Hollywood.
It's been a dream of mine
always, but also my father's
dream as well.
I've worked my butt off getting
here already.
Today is make it or break it.
Ladies and gentlemen, miss
Lauren gray.
Bring it on.
Next.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Hello.
What's your name?
Lauren gray.
Lauren, how old are you?
22 years old.
And where are you from?
Hardy, Arkansas.
What do you do in Hardy,
Arkansas?
Uh, well, I perform in a band
with my father.
It's a Southern rock band.
Cool.
And we do it every weekend.
I've been doing it since I was,
uh, in the band since I was
about 18.
So you guys are her parents?
Mm-hmm.
What do you guys do?
We're florists, a bridal
shop.
Uh, have a band all my life.
The band I would have
guessed.
Floral shop I wouldn't have
Me?
Yeah.
All right, so what are you
gonna sing today, because you're
in a Southern rock band like the
allman brothers or skynyrd or
something.
Well, I have more of a-a
bluesy type voice, but I will be
singing Adele, "One And Only", for
you.
Okay.
Do it.
New.
All right.
Said you've been on my mind,
I grow fonder every day,
lose myself in time,
Wow.
Ooh, wow.
Just thinking,
of your face,
but God only knows,
why it's taken me so long,
to let my doubts go,
'cause I'm the only one,
that you want,
I don't know,
why I'm scared,
'cause I've been here before,
every feeling, every word,
I've imagined it all,
you'll never know,
if you never try,
to forget your past,
and simply be mine,
you've been on my mind,
I hang on every word you say,
lose yourself in time,
just at the mention,
of my name,
Okay.
Wow.
I didn't need to hear that
song right now.
Right, Jen, right?
Okay.
All right, cool.
You broke a little bit on the
top there.
I know, I know.
I cracked bad.
Lost some notes.
Do you usually do that?
No, not at all, not at all.
I wouldn't imagine so.
All right, so what do we
think, Steven?
So I think I love the way you
break, and I love the way you go
up there and you're fearless
about it, and that's really
important because when people
sing, and you deliver a chorus
line and you can break like
that and get up there and hit
the note and break, that's the
sexiest thing on the planet.
And your delivery was great.
Thank you.
That's a great compliment.
But at least you're fearless
about it.
That's what I like.
You know, I mean, you've gotta
be willing to take chances and
jump off that ledge as a singer
if you're gonna be a great one.
Yes.
Well, hopefully there'll be a
little ray of sunlight coming
your way here.
She's a ray of sunlight
anyway, man.
You're one of the best female
voices we've heard.
Wow.
Yeah, man.
Oh, my God.
And I'm gonna say absolutely,
100% yes.
Oh, wow. Wow.
I say yes too.
You're incredible.
Love you.
And you are going to
Hollywood.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, baby!
It's going down in Hollywood!
This is the biggest thing
that has ever happened in my
life.
It won't be the biggest thing
ever.
Short of your daddy lovin'
you.
This is great.
Thank you, guys.
Well, tell your dad to play
"Whipping Post" and dedicate it
to me.
Oh, that's one of my favorite
songs.
That's one of my favorites,
too.
All right, see you in Hollywood.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys, so much.
Big thing gonna happen for
her.
She's gonna make it.
Uh, yeah.
I mean, wow.
I love it.
Okay, I have two words for
today.
Thank you.
Lauren Gray.
Yes.
Yeah.
And thank you.
You can't be taught to sing
that way.
You can only learn it on your
own and have some inside
influence from-passed down from
generations.
It's so amazing.
Ooh!
So amazing, so amazing.
Eight years ago, Carrie Underwood
launched her career from St. Louis.
Maybe this is the start for
Lauren Gray, or one of the 46
hopefuls headed to Hollywood.
Hey, God bless 'em.
I hope they all have great
success.
I'm going to Hollywood.
Ain't gonna happen.
This is amazing!
Whoo!
Country girl's going to
Hollywood.
See ya there.
I said today, all I want is
to hug an astro pop at the end
of my day.
Astro pop.
He's saying my shirt reminds him
of an astro pop.
Like a what?
Like a giant [Bleep].
Good night, America.
America.
All right, that's it.
And on that bombshell, we
wrap up the road.
People have traveled from all
over the country...
Portland!
And from all walks of life
for a chance at their dream.
I have a voice to speak with,
you know, a voice to sing.
Way out in the middle of the
woods, I live in a tent.
Yes, I do.
Ooh.
Wow.
And we lived in a refugee
camp, hoping there was a chance
for us to come to the U.S. for a
better life.
I know this is my chance and
my opportunity to show the world
what I have and I can't let it
slip out of my hands.
Together we shared the ups...
Whoa!
And the downs of this tour.
Ooh, baby,
Terrible.
But along the way, we've
unveiled a new crop of
incredibly talented fresh
faces...
Somebody who was born to do
it.
Thank you.
Making this the most
successful road auditions we've
ever had.
Major talent, man.
I'm gonna say yes, and you're
going to Hollywood.
Whoo!
I've never seen anything like
that.
Whoo!
It's a dream come true.
I'm, like, shaking.
I don't-
oh, my goodness.
When you have dreams, you
make them happen.
Oh!
You know what's wrong with
this girl, Steven?
Absolutely nothing.
Very spiritual voice.
It took me away.
Take that kiss to Hollywood.
Aah!
Aaaaaahhhh,
You know you're gonna be a
star, right?
Keep singing.
But this is just the
beginning of their journey.
Guess what, mommy?
You're going to Hollywood.
I'm going to Hollywood.
Aah!
Because next week...
We hit Hollywood.
Feel good in Hollywood,
With show-stopping performances
and breakout stars.
More of that, more of that.
But as the pressure builds...
This is where everybody goes
wrong.
It's about survival of the
fittest.
You've got to have that one
word: Courage.
Oh!
Will your favorite survive
the cut?
This is the make it or break
it time right now.
Will they survive the night?
Give one more chance
I can show you
tune in to the most emocional
and exhausting Hollywood week ever.
Baby I'm sorry, you're going home
there's so many people out there
and I'm not leaving. I'm not leaving.