-You're in the top 24.
-You made it.
-I'm in the Top 24.
-It was unanimous.
You're going through!
-I say yes.
Never stop
Believing in yourself.
Hold on.
It's going to be quite a ride.
I'm on American Idol right now.
Can you even believe it?
I'm just so grateful
for all of this.
I really want this.
This is actually my dream
coming true.
It's so crazy.
I'm just, like,
so overwhelmed,
by everything that's
happening.
How did I get here?
I don't even know.
Go from being a waitress
to a face everyone knows.
I want to be here for a long
Time.
I don't know what's gonna happen
From here.
There's a lot riding on it.
I'm not gonna stop now.
I'm about to go see the stage.
-Oh my God.
-For the first time.
Oh my gosh,
I'm really excited.
It's a competition,
And somebody's
got to go home.
We've got some amazing
Singers here.
Some of the best in the world.
That's what I was
Waiting for.
That girl can really
Sing.
Your voice is
Perfect, pitch is perfect.
Crazy, crazy.
America's got their work
cut out for them.
It was a bit of a nightmare
instead of a dream.
You have the voice
the world's been waiting to hear.
This is what singing
Is about.
-Can I get an amen up in here?
-Amen!
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your judges,
Randy jackson, jennifer lopez,
And steven tyler.
And your host, ryan seacrest.
Hello once again.
We are coming to you live from
Hollywood,
and welcome to the
First results show of the Season.
It is a pivotal night in the
Competition
as we officially
Find out
who has made the top
13.
But getting to that point will
Involve a massive cut.
First, the good news.
Over 33 million votes came in
Over the last two nights.
Thank you very much for that.
It shows how talented this
Season's finalists truly are.
Let's say hello to the guys in
The competition.
And keep it going for the
Ladies.
These are your top 25, america,
But the harsh reality is half of
Those faces
will be leaving our Stage
before the end of the Evening.
Exactly.
It's not my fault.
It's gonna be dramatic.
Also, a lot of pressure on our
Judges
after we announce who
You've picked as your top ten.
The judges will also be selecting
one Contestant each
as wildcard Contenders.
These spots will complete the
Top 13 tonight.
Now, when we come back,
those Seats will be filled
with the Five most popular girls
and the Five most popular guys.
Drama about to go down live on
"american idol."
Don't miss a minute!
Here we go!
Back with you live on
Results night here on "idol."
This evening, five girls and five Guys
are going straight through
To the next round
based on over
33 million votes.
Then three remaining spots
will Be chosen by our judges as
Wildcards.
Let's start by building
America's top ten.
First, we are going to focus on
The guys.
Gentlemen.
Let's get serious now.
Can I have chase, phillip, and
Jeremy.
Come on down here center stage.
How you doing, gentlemen?
How you feeling tonight?
Phillip?
Feeling all right.
How nerve-racking is this?
it's just -- I don't know
How to explain it.
It's beyond belief how nervous
We all are right now.
You seem pretty calm,
Though.
I am. It's a hard way to keep
Composure
and be able to stand
Here at the same time but --
-You're doing a good Job.
-thank you.
Jeremy, what's going
Through your mind right now?
I'm not gonna lie.
My heart is beating outside of
My chest.
I'm excited.
I love you guys.
Thank you so much.
let's take a look at how
They did Tuesday night,
plus What our music mentor,
interscope chairman jimmy Ivene thought.
Take a look at this.
Here we go.
Some people are
Just blessed from god
with a Voice that when they open their
Mouth, they affect people.
That's you.
You're one of those people.
That was beautiful.
You couldn't have picked a
Better song.
America saw two faces melting
during that performance.
Those two.
Look at that.
I am not ashamed.
jeremy has got a great voice
And gets the award
for the nightest person probably
I've Seen in a long time.
But that isn't going to cut it
On this show.
You have to have much more than
That these days to win this thing.
Well, well, well,
Welcome to "american idol,"
Cowboy.
You got a kind of brendan Fraser, "the mummy"
kind of look About you, man.
You're going to set
America's hearts on fire,
lot of mummies
At home.
You sounded great tonight
As well.
And you've grown so much through
The competition
and I look
Forward to seeing where you go.
I want this so bad.
I hope I've got what it takes.
chase is a good-looking guy
But there are plenty of those on
Tv right now.
To win this show you've got to
Bring something
fresh, original
And exciting.
And I saw none of that.
You hit your stride
With that, man.
You maude it beautiful.
There so no doubt
You are one of the most special Talents
we found this year on
The road.
I'm not sure I was
Jumping up and down
about the Reharm of the melody.
Stick with the Melody
I think is what he's Saying.
Some people may like it
and some people don't,
it's america's turn to vote
and not the judges to choose
so it's gonna be very intense.
we desperately need
Originality on this show.
Phil phillips has that.
A lot of people try to sing like him
but come off really
Affected.
I believed every word he sang.
I'd sign this guy on the spot.
So that's how it went
Down on stage.
Now we find out what america
Thought.
Dim the lights.
Here we go.
First, randy.
Do you agree with jimmy about
Jeremy
and what he had to say
about him
not making the cut in
This competition?
I agree that it's Gonna take more
than just having Good looks.
But I think he's got a good
Voice as well
so half and half With jimmy.
What do you think,
Jennifer?
I think voices
Supersedes some things.
It's true we're looking for the
Full package,
but at the end of The day,
I believe jeremy has
That.
Phillip, what went
Through your mind
when you Watched jimmy
say that seconds Ago?
I don't know, I have a little...
I don't know.
It's crazy just to hear that
Kind of stuff. I don't know.
You're not humble
Enough.
Steven, what do you make of
Chase standing on this stage?
Do you think he has what it
Takes?
You know, I
Understand what jimmy's talking about
about the commercial side
Of it.
Sometimes a voice can come
Through like yours.
Climbing out from the inside.
Here we go.
After the nationwide vote,
Jeremy...
you have not made the
Top ten, my friend.
But take a seat.
Hang tight.
Still have a shot at the wildcard.
We're left with phillip and
Chase.
I can tell you one of you has
Made it into america's top ten.
After the nationwide vote,
Chase, you are not in the top
Ten.
Phillip, you're in the top ten.
Congratulations.
He's in the top ten, america!
You're going to be lonely for
Just a second.
I'll bring some other people
Over in a second.
Can I get you anything?
-you look like you need something.
-just keep going.
you got it.
Let's turn now to our ladies.
Can I have jessica, hollie,
Brielle, and haley center stage.
come on down, girls.
Making the slow crawl to the
center of the Stage.
How you doing, ladies?
You okay?
Come on in tight.
Let's take a look at last night
And what jimmy had to say about
The girls, watch this.
you hit the notes
so perfectly,
There was nothing left to that song
except Passion.
My hope is you'll let your hair
Down next time.
>> okay.
I told you last year
that I thought that you can win this
and I Still think that.
I look forward to america seeing
What you really do do when you
Do let your hair down.
Do do, that do do Thing.
I was like --
Wait a minute.
Ma kind of show is this, man?
Steven, did you Literally mean
let her hair Down?
-Yes.
-ok.
steven tyler told me to let my hair down
and I can do that.
there it goes.
please vote!
hollie, little girl, big
Voice.
Could have been a little more
Believable
given the right
Material.
She can do some real damage in
This game.
You got a great sent
Of blues.
Georgia!
It was beautiful.
You are a true
Performer.
You come out there and you eat
It up.
You understand what it is to
Entertain.
Brielle von hugel.
that's not a very
Staten island name, is it?
My nephew went to school there.
My sister lives there.
I spent many a thanksgiving
There.
Lot of chrisma in this girl.
I agree with jennifer, real
Entertainer.
But she got to pick her own song
This week.
Why pick "on the dock of the
Bay" by otis redding?
Why not pick something young and
Contemporary and hit it?
I think it's gonna hurt her.
you look like a star.
-a star!
-yes you do
You look beautiful.
You sounded beautiful.
Your voice is tiny
And old-fashioned.
I hope it's coming back
and Adele proved it will
and I think
You're going to be part of it.
-thank you.
-Nice going.
just a few weeks ago,
I was Waiting tables in baltimore,
and Now I'm on a stage in front of
All these people.
so I'm having a blast.
this is hollie's best show so
Far.
Really poised, restrained great
Tone in her voice.
Lot of blondes on this show.
Wow.
I'm not sure who the audience is
Going to vote for, though.
May not be her.
The whole thing is Just really,
really so beyond Your years.
-It's crazy.
-The growl.
The growl, the soft
Spots, the yelling, the all of It.
Let me just say this,
That girl can really sing.
I would say one of the best of
The last two nights right there,
Jessica sanchez.
jessica, she has talent from
A to z.
I'd sign her on the spot tonight.
If anybody has a pole position
In this race, it's jessica.
She's the one to beat.
All right.
Let's see what the nation Thought.
Dim the lights.
Here we go, the tough part.
Brielle, let me ask you, jimmy
Wasn't a fan of your song Choice.
You still stand by it?
yeah, I definitely stand by
My song choice.
I love putting a twist on old
Classics.
That's jusr Brielle
and that's what I love do.
So if jimmy were
Watching right now
and I have to
Guess he is,
what would you say
To him?
-what would I say to him?
-To jimmy.
I am so respectful of jimmy.
He's the best in this business,
And I love him.
Now, jennifer, you
Loved hallie when we met her.
Do you think she was a standout
This week?
You know, it's hard
To say.
There was so many
you could Really tell
who the standouts Were.
She had a good performance.
You sounded good.
I don't know.
I don't know if it was a standout
to the point that she's
In the top five girls.
I'm not sure.
Here we go.
Good luck, ladies.
After the nationwide vote,
Brielle, I'm sorry,
you're not
In the top ten, so hang tight.
You may get a wildcard shot,
Okay?
Head to the couches.
Girls, come on together.
I can tell you three that two of you
have made it into the top
Ten.
After the nationwide vote,
Hollie, unfortunately, are you
Not one of them,
but hang tight, Okay?
Have a seat.
Which means jessica and hallie,
Congratulations, you're in the
Top ten!
So that is how it looks so far.
Phillip, hollie, and jessica,
Safe.
And in the top ten.
More seats to fill, live,
stay With us on "american idol."
Back with you live here
On "american idol."
Last night you voted.
Tonight we find out who has made
It into your top ten.
So far, phillip, hollie and
Jessica are in.
What's going on at the table
Here?
During the break, you guys are
Bickering, arguing,
chatting
Back and forth.
We're just discussing
Life, ryan.
Sometimes life's little issues,
You know.
Are you still debating
About the wildcards?
We started a bit of that.
Now that we're
Seeing how it pans out,
we're Like, uh-oh,
what are we doing?
I can hear them arguing
Up to the last second
and then
It's like, okay, we're back.
Let's get to more results.
Gentlemen, joshua, heejun and Adam.
Center stage, here we go.
What's up, man?
I brought my tissues.
Both pockets.
Adam, let me ask you,
just take
Us behind the scenes.
What's it like before a night
Like tonight
and these results
And the intensity of all of it?
it -- it -- it'sverything.
We're backstage.
You're excited and you think,
Oh, I hope I did a good enough
Job.
And then you're thinking,
Everybody did a good job, and
You're back there
and now you're
Nervous and your feelings,
they keep
Neutralizing each other.
It's nerves.
It's excitement.
We all love each other so much.
It's so cheesy and corny to say,
But I mean, it's just -- it's a
Blast.
Whatever happens, it's a blast
So --
Let's take a look back
At how they did on Tuesday night
And what jimmy's thoughts were.
Here we go.
-Can I get an amen up In here?
-Amen!
You are the voice the
World's been waiting to hear.
I just don't even
Know what to say to you!
I just want to punch you.
I don't know what I want to do
To you.
Why you want to punch
Him?
why punch him?
why you wanna punch, they guy's
working and you wanna hit him.
Because I love it.
Punches for jennifer,
Man.
this joshua is the real deal.
He sang great on the show.
And there's no question in my
Mind he's gonna get through.
And I'm looking forward to work
With him.
But if he does get through,
it's My job to make sure that we
Don't turn this
into sister act 3.
I love the throwback
Vibe you got going on.
You definitely
Delivered.
That's what I was waiting for.
I love that you got
Your own name,
white chocolate.
we love that.
Steven what kind of
Chocolate do you prefer?
I prefer dark Chocolate,
to be honest with You.
steven loves that I'm white
Chocolate.
Randy loves the throwback.
They get me.
They get me as an artist,
and I Hope that's what america wants
Right now.
supposedly adam has a large
Black woman
trapped in a white
Body.
So as of right now,
he's not Pulling them both off at the
Same time.
If america's not gonna be
Confused about him,
he's got to Merge them and come as one
Person.
You have a voice
That's smooth as silk.
Really. I'm not sure
that that song Showed off
all of how beautiful
Your voice is.
I don't think it was
The right song,
but I still love
Your voice, man.
-thank you.
-you're welcome.
Heejun, you sure can sing
the judges didn't like the
song choice, of course,
but I knew this was
gonna happen.
my dad's my only hope for this point,
cause he has 20 cell phones
and he knows how to dial.
hopefully.
let me tell you about heejun.
This guy completely confuses me.
I get the personality.
I get the -- schtick.
I get the whole thing.
sort of a good voice.
This isn't american comedian.
This is "american idol."
Back now live.
Let's get to the results.
Dim the lights.
here we go.
Booing?
Is there some booing?
Boo, jimmy.
Heejun, what do you think about
what jimmy had to say about
America's comedian?
who's that?
Touche.
But to pick up on his point,
are You taking it seriously,
this competition?
of course, I do know
it's a singing competition.
I have a lot to work with
Alongside with comedy.
I definately do.
Whatever.
You're the total
Package.
Joshua you grew up singing in
The church.
How has that platform helped you
For this one?
it just Taught me to sing from my soul
And from my heart.
I mean, whatever I've been
Through in life,
I learned that
I could help through my music.
And you tap into that
When you're on the stage.
most definitely.
Now, adam, you were
clapping a little bit
when jimmy
Was giving you some feedback.
What was that about?
that was one of those
Things that as it came out,
Those sentences you just want to
Pull back.
But I understand what he's
Saying.
I mean, I do -- I hope that
America gets me as a person.
Here we go, guys.
After the nationwide vote,
Joshua...
top ten.
top ten, you're in!
congratulations.
Heejun and adam, one of you is
Also in america's top ten.
After the nationwide vote,
Heejun...
it is you.
Congratulations.
Adam takes a seat.
waits for a spot, hopefully.
Now back to the ladies.
Baylie, chelsea, skylar
and Shannon, come on down here.
Let's hear it for them.
come on down here girls
right there.
There you go. Perfect.
How we doing, ladies?
-You all right?
-I'm okay.
Let's see how it all
Played out last night. Take a look at this.
I don't think we've Ever had
somebody with your Voice
that performs like this.
Dude, you were rockin' out.
You're like the rockin' country
Girl.
She's like reba mixed
With kelly clarkson
or something crazy Wild.
-Or tina.
-altogether.
-It's wild.
-I love your energy.
The audience brought that out of
You. I love that.
That means you're a natural-born
Performer.
this dress is really tight,
I can't even talk.
How did you have breath control
running around on stage in that dress
And jumping up and down
and doing Your tina turner thing?
thank you, lord.
skylar laine did herself a
Great turn this week
picking That great Faces song
written by rod Stewart and ronny wood.
She blended soul with country
Which is a great formula for
Rock 'n' roll.
The judges loved her.
I think she brought a lot of
Charisma.
I agree with them.
A lot of stage presence.
I would have voted for her.
I think at lot of country is
Going to vote for her too.
It started off a
Little shaky for you,
a little Pitchy in spots.
I think you just never seized
Control of the song.
I'm not sure if it's
The best song you could have Picked.
But I enjoyed.
And you're very pretty.
>> thank you.
You're not pretty.
You're beautiful.
But when come out here
and You're competing against the
Likes of what you're competing against
it's got to be solid.
I know what they're talking
About.
I can hear myself sing.
And I could just tell that it
Wasn't perfect.
But I'm singing live for the
First time on television.
So it's gonna be a little shaky.
baylie brown seem seams to
Have all the pieces
but they
Didn't come together tonight.
Beautiful girl, nice tone, but
She lost the plot.
Out of tune, I believe outta
Here.
You definitely can
Sing.
Gut huge big voice.
I just I was wondering if that
Was the best choice.
I feel like Everybody really got to hear the
Best part of you.
I can feel your heart
Pounding from here.
I thought you sound good
Tonight.
Watch your phrasing.
Watch your timing.
And when it's time to belt it
Out, belt it out good.
Because you're
Great singer.
chelsea's got a really nice
Voice.
But what I saw on the show just
Wasn't original enough.
Carrie underwood karaoke, it's
Just not gonna fly.
I think we need more from her.
I think she's gonna be in
Trouble this week.
What a way to come out
Swinging.
Now, that's what it's all about.
You sing with such
Passion for a 16-year-old.
Really, it's not something that
You see every day.
You gave me gooseys, my first
Gooseys.
You took it upstairs
And it went beautiful. It was just gorgeous.
That's taking it up a notch for Me.
Thank you so much.
So this is the first time
you've been in the same room
with steven tyler since the
Auditions.
yeah.
Do we have a wrestling mat here?
Stevie, do you remember
Him?
I didn't mean it!
shannon, I really like her.
Really good voice, great poise,
Sang beautifully.
Tonight she was dressed more for
the prom
than for a live
Performance.
Can use some help in the styling
Area.
I say she does well tonight.
Back now live.
Shannon, what's behind those
Tears here?
right now I'm just so happy
And so excited to be here right now
and I can't help myself but cry
because I've gone through so much
and this has just been
Such amazing opportunity for me.
And I love to do this and I
Don't want to quit now.
I don't want to stop now.
I don't want it to end.
you're gonna feel really good
if it all works out.
Now, baylie, after
Seeing that
and thinking about
Your performance,
what would you
Have done differently in Hindsight?
sing on key, I guess.
Try not to be so shaky, but I
Don't know.
That's crazy.
How's the heart now?
uh, good.
it's more the knees.
My whole body's shaking now.
All right.
Stand for a second.
Skylar, where does the
Confidence come from?
well, I think it comes from
Me just lovin'
well, I love That song
so that's where that Came from.
And I got to rock out on stage
And all the people here were
Getting into it with me,
and That was just amazing.
And I just am confident because
I know what kind of artist I
Want to be,
and I just -- that's
What I showed,
and that's what I
Always want to show in Everything that I do.
Ladies, good luck.
Here we go.
After the nationwide vote...
Let's start with you, shannon.
Congratulations.
You've made it to the top ten.
Come on over here.
Now we've got the country girls
Up here.
Randy, is there room in this
Competition
for more than one
Country girl?
There's definitely
Room for more than one.
One of these?
Definitely room for
Probably more than one of these,
But one of these up there, ryan,
Really stood out last night.
Let's see if america
Agreed.
Is it -- skylar laine.
Congratulations, skylar, you're
In the top ten.
You did it!
Okay, girls.
Take a seat.
To the couches and hang out.
So far look at the group at the
Stools.
They are in america's top ten.
Congratulations.
After the break, more results.
Plus find out who will sing for
A wildcard spot.
Anything can happen.
More "idol" live after the
Break.
Welcome back to "idol."
Over the past two nights, you've
Weighed in
and tonight we tell
You how the vote has panned out.
So far this group, they are in
The top ten, america.
There's this room for three more
Plus, three wildcard picks.
Now let's get back to your
Results.
Gentlemen, we turn to you.
Can I have aaron, come on down,
Aaron.
Let's hear it for aaron.
Creighton.
And reed.
What's happening?
how are you doing?
gentlemen, how are you feeling?
Is that confidence?
It may be confidence from you.
I don't know.
Let's take a look back at
Tuesday night's show
and also
What jimmy iovine had to say.
Watch this.
You're definitely a
Very musical guy.
this was kinda wild,
You were scatting.
You were like sheila e on the
Timbali.
Everybody knows
That song so well.
But this was great way to show
America
who they are dealing with
with reed grimm.
I hope I did enough to get
America's votes.
at this point it's up to them.
thanks a lot America, vote for me!
I watch reed.
Real talented.
Playing the drums, moving
Around.
All the such judges seemed to
Like him.
maybe he thought he was in a nightclub
Way too kitschy for me, way too
Cabaret.
Not gonna make it on the show
Like that.
I always believed
In you.
I don't know what it is about you.
Your voice just takes me there.
And you can sing anything.
That's how you sing
Some vocals, man.
that run that You did at the end was
Crazy.
You raised the bar for
Yourself.
You got to beat this next time.
Okay, man.
oh, man.
I feel amazing.
I feel absolutely amazing.
Aaron, now, this
Confused me,
because the judges
And the audience
gave him a standing ovation
and I'm
Watching it saying, this is Cheesy.
It's a bit don cheadle.
but everybody seemed to like it.
It did not work for me.
Dude, you can
Definitely sing.
You know, cyndi Lauper did a beautiful,
Beautiful job of that.
I know she's home crying along
With j.Lo.
That was stupendous.
It was a perfect
Song for you.
You are so individual.
That's what the song says.
You sang it from your heart.
That was so beautiful.
I mean, to think that half of
These guys are going home.
America's got their work cut out
For them.
I don't want to go home.
I have a lot more to do.
I have a lot more to say.
I have a lot more to sing.
I wanna stay.
Vote for me.
Creighton has an
Interesting voice.
top end It's screechy and annoys me.
Judges loved him.
I didn't.
All right, all right.
Let's hold for oo for a second.
I want to go to the judges and
Get their reaction
to some of
The things jimmy is saying.
Jennifer?
Maybe jimmy should
Come to the show.
maybe he should come here.
I respect jimmy and I respect
What he says,
and I see a last
Things that he's saying.
But I think what wee hear in
Here sometimes
could be a little Different
than what people hear
At home
or even what he's
Hearing on a monitor
in that Little room that he's in.
But...
-Little, small room.
4 x 4.
No, no.
But, you know, I don't know.
There's some things I just want
To punch him,
but other things I
Agree with.
Here's the other
Thing.
I said Monday night it was our
First live show.
I came back Tuesday night and I
Looked at the boys and I said,
We were a little bit too lenient
On a lot of you tonight.
And jimmy's got some points.
It wasn't as good when I watched
It home as it was in the room.
So, jimmy, we give you a pass on
That one.
Jimmy iovine,
&#*$(%
Unfortunately he's been right on
With a lot of it.
I wasw gonna ask, He is being too
Critical, too tough, jennifer?
No, I don't think
He's being too critical,
but
Some of the ways he says things,
I wouldn't choose to say them
That way.
So, randy, aaron got a
Standing ovation
for his Performance.
Do you still stand by that?
Aaron had a very good
Performance.
After the girls, like, did their thing
and the guys did the rest
Of their thing,
I don't know if It was good enough
to be in that Top ten.
I'm not really sure.
But by the way, aaron, I love
Don cheadle. Dude, he's dope.
Let's talk about reed
For a second.
Why is reed a relevant artist
Today?
I think reed is good
Because he shows off everything
He can do.
He can play the drums.
He can sing.
He can play the piano.
I think that's good.
I don't think that's a bad
Thing.
I think there's room
for all different types of artists
you know, and that's
Just something that is always going to be
talent is always
Going to be relevant.
It's a tough night,
Ryan.
It's a tough night as I look at
Those who made it through.
it's a tough night, It's hard.
let's get to it.
Dim the lights. here we go.
Good luck, gentlemen.
After the nationwide vote --
Aaron, you have not made the top
Ten.
I'm sorry, my friend.
Hang tight.
Maybe a wildcard shot.
Okay?
To the couch.
oh, boy.
Creighton and reed.
After the nationwide vote --
I can tell you that creighton,
Are you not in the top ten
Either.
And reed, unfortunately, neither
Are you, my friend.
So hang tight on the couches.
Maybe a wildcard shot.
Let's hear it for them.
Now back to the ladies.
Can I have elise, come on,
Elise.
You look pretty.
thanks.
Erika.
Here's erika.
Let's have haley.
And jen.
Come on, jen.
Here's how it went down last Night.
Take a look at this.
I thought it was
Beautiful.
I felt the feeling in the song.
I thought did you a really good
Job.
I think you're one of
The greatest singers in this Competition,
so good looking
Out.
There's something
About confidence.
Makes a voice fly and yours is
Soaring.
You got to what it takes.
You got it.
oh, my god, that was amazing.
Jen has a really nice
Voice.
But if I were on this show, I'd
Stay miles away from adele.
Too many adele wannabes on tv
Right now.
Lot of vocal power techniques in
Place of soul.
It's not gonna work on this show
and it's not
Gonna get her through.
Be very, very careful in this
Area.
There's something magical
about the confidence you
Have.
It just breathes wings into a
Song and you just nailed it.
You are one of our
Power voices.
I think you could have gone even
Further knowing you.
Come on, erika.
We know you what you can do
Already.
I want to put it all out on
That stage.
Of course, I can push a little
More. And I will.
I like this girl.
She has music in her blood.
It's very, very natural to her.
She has great restraint,
Something to show needs more of,
Not less.
The judges asked her to push it.
I don't agree.
If she stays where she is, stay in pocket,
she Can go all the way.
Kind of pitchy all
Over the place,
so it kind of Left me like
I was like,
Where are we going?
I'm a little dizzy.
How do I say this?
I'm a little stuck.
It was a bit of a nightmare for
Me instead of a dream.
what randy said was kind of
Hurtful
because I felt like I
Put myhart and soul into it,
and Randy, I'm definitely going to
Prove you wrong next time
Because I can sing you a sweet dream.
Wow.
She sang out of tune the entire Song.
I can get around that,
but I Can't get around the robotic
Mimicking.
That's going to kill you with me
Every time.
I think that randy was right.
Her "sweet dreams" turned into
a nightmare tonight.
You blew it out of
The water.
That was beautiful.
You're definitely a
Force it be reckoned
with inThis competition, boys, girls,
Whatever.
I felt real good about the
Performance.
I felt the energy of the crowd.
It was amazing the judges said I
Was one of their standouts.
That makes me feel like they
Appreciate me.
The judges like her.
I agree with them on this one.
She has a lot of character.
I'd like to hear her sing some
Of her own material
or material Crafted just for her.
Usually afraid of adele songs
But she brought something to it.
She sings a little high.
She's pushing a little much.
She has to be careful.
It's a long competition.
She has to hold on to that
Voice.
As you know, right now
There's only one spot left for
The ladies.
Before we get to the vote,
Jennifer,
what did you mean when
You said to erika,
you need her
To did a little bit more,
push a Little harder?
I just know what
She can do.
We watched her over these last
Few months.
really do some amazing things with her voice.
I know how strong her voice is.
I know what her range is.
I just felt like I always want
Them do their best up there.
And I want them to have their
Best performance each time,
Better than the last time, and
So that's what I wanted.
That's what I wanted america to
See.
And I -- you did great!
I'm just gonna push you.
I'm here to help you.
Elise, how's your
Confidence right now?
what is that?
I'm really distracted.
I'm just thinking about
everything so much.
What are you thinking
About?
I'm really sad about some
People leaving.
I'm excited for people making
It.
I'm hoping I make it.
My heart's pounding.
-All natural.
-you know.
Haley, let's talk about
Your you performance.
What regrets, if any, do you have with
Yours?
I don't have any regrets.
I wanted to choose a song nobody
Else was doing.
I love annie lennox and I felt
That I performed to the best of
My ability.
And I wanted to prove to you guys
that I can perform and I
Believed in myself.
And I felt in that moment, I truly,
Truly did.
I know it wasn't perfect but I know
that I can really sing
Wonderfully for you guys.
Very sweet.
All right.
Dim the lights.
Here we go.
Ladies, good luck.
After the nationwide vote --
One more spot for the girls,
in America's top ten --
Haley, unfortunately, you have
Not made the top ten. All right?
You can take a seat on the
Couches.
Thank you, haley. Stand by.
Wildcard's coming up.
Erika, after the nationwide vote,
I'm sorry to say you have
Not made the top ten.
Thank you very much.
You can have a seat.
Let's hear it for erika.
Oh, elise and jen and one spot
For the ladies
in america's top
Ten.
After the nationwide vote,
that Lady is...
elise.
Jen, you can take a seat.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Let's hear it for elise.
So the people on the Stools
are officially in the top
Ten, america.
Now back to the guys.
Can I have deandre.
Also eben.
Colton.
And the gentle giant jermaine.
-jermaine, How you doing?
-great.
Colton, how you feeling?
I'm nervous.
I am nervous.
Eben, you've got a
Girlfriend here apparently.
-How you doing, buddy?
-I'm really nervous.
Deandre.
freaking out.
Gentlemen, good luck to you.
After the nationwide vote --
I can tell you
results after The break.
Are you locked live on
"idol."
Just to recap, the people in
These seats
are in your top ten,
America.
But the fate of deandre, eben,
Colton, and jermaine
is still Hanging in the balance.
Let me go to the judges.
What do you think about
America's top ten so far,
and What's going through your minds
In terms of possible wildcard
Picks?
Jennifer?
I hate seeing some
Of these people go home,
but I
Have to say I agree with america
On every single one of the
People that they put in so far.
Amazing.
We have a hell of a competition
Crazy brewing right now.
There are amazing singers and
Artists over there right now.
Agree with every single one.
Stevie, where's your
Head?
I like to give
Everybody the confidence
to see
What they'll do the next time,
Because so many people up here
Have just blown us away with the
Next one.
They weren't so good tonight but
The next time they were better.
I have to agree with america and
Jimmy.
I look over here and it's
Everybody that just made my Heart stop.
Randy, we've done this
For years and years.
How we looking this season?
Dude, we're looking
Amazing.
America, you're on fire,
because This is an amazing top ten
Brewing.
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
Each one of these kids that are
Up here
could win the whole
Thing.
Who will fill these
Stools is the question.
Let's take a look at Tuesday
Night.
roll the tape.
here we go.
The gentle giant
Returns!
Thank you for proving to us
why we asked you to come
Back.
thank you.
What a beautiful
Thing, man.
Somebody's gonna come
Out and give you a hug.
I knew she couldn't resist that.
Here comes gentle mom.
Maybe not so gentle.
I'm so grateful.
The way that the crowd received me,
it was just so warming,
like All my nerves that were there
Were gone.
I am the biggest competition
This year.
So look out.
I'm so glad the judges
Brought jermaine back.
What a beautiful voice.
I can listen to an entire album
Of that voice
which is very few
People I can say that about
in today's business.
We got to figure out how to get
Him through this show.
Could take a bit of variety,
a Bit of excitement and a little
Creativity.
But I'm rooting for him.
Deandre!
Yo, this kid's got it
All.
you're one of the most
commercial guys I've seen
Just out of the box, you ready
To go now.
I told you this was
Gonna happen
if you kept singing
Like that.
Good for you, man.
You picked a song to show off
Your voice
as well as it did
Tonight.
I'm where I'm supposed to be
Right now.
Deandre has an
Enormous amount of potential.
What he needs is a coach.
we should start now.
When you take someone like
Phillip baylie
from earth wind And fire,
you have to crush That.
He's just not ready for that
Yet.
Eben, you got a
Really true, straight beautiful Voice.
The melody's a little
Pitchy.
It wasn't all perfect,
But you collected yourself
A pro
and came back and nailed
The end.
What impressed me
Is you really, really held on.
You held on and you put the
Bravado on the end.
Good job.
Eben's a talented kid
With a lot of great potential.
But in my opinion, not ready
For prime time.
Not yet.
He sang a song that was way too
Mature for him
for where he is
Right now.
If he doesn't make it, I'd like
To see him come back.
The way the rules work, he can't
Come back.
They've got to change the rules.
It's about time that We on "idol"
had all own little Indy alt rocker
singing like
Paramore, dude.
I didn't even know
you could perform like that.
You're a relevant
Artist.
I can hear you on the radio
Right now.
When you sing, you really sing
From your heart,
and it just
Gets me every single time.
I want to see more of that.
it's insane
seeing him up on that stage.
We've been watching the show
Since season 1.
Just to see him up there is
Amazing.
Colton's really Talented,
probably one of the
Most talented kids on the show.
But he can't do too much too
Soon,
jumping on the piano.
He's got it take it slow, pace
Himself
and he can really win
This thing.
Colton, let me get your
Reaction to jimmy there.
man, I appreciated jimmy.
Wow.
I don't have words.
Just wow.
Wow's a word.
Eben, do you want to defend your
Song choice
or what were your
Thoughts from watching that Back?
when I first heard the song
On the radio,
I was like, oh my
Gosh, mom, I want to sing this Song so bad.
I love the song so much.
I felt good about my
Performance.
And I think the judges have
Given me
real good advice on my
Melody and everything.
it was really great
and next time,
if america lets me through,
I'll Definitely step it up a notch.
All right.
Dim the lights. Here we go.
After the nationwide vote --
Deandre,
you unfortunately are
Not in america's top ten.
Take a seat.
Hang for the wildcard round.
Colton --
Are you not --
-- Going to be disappointed
Tonight
because you made the top
Ten.
Congratulations.
Take a seat on the stools.
Oh, here we go.
One stool remains in america's
Top ten.
Eben and jermaine.
Take a look at that shot.
I know the feeling, brotha.
After the nationwide vote --
The person in america's top ten
Is --
Jermaine.
Eben, take a seat.
Hang for the wildcard, okay?
Congratulations.
So here it is.
These are the five guys and five
Girls
you've chosen as america's
Top ten!
But don't sweat if your favorite
Isn't one of these faces.
The judges are going to reveal
The six contestants
who they Want to sing again
for the three Wildcard spots.
That's coming up live right here
On "american idol"!
Be right back.
Very exciting night
Here on "american idol."
Before the break, we officially
Named americas' top ten.
A huge congratulations to them.
Excellent.
Jen, are you pleased with how
This has all gone down?
I am.
But it's also one of the most
Painful moments for us, too,
Because we have to look at that
Group
and we only get to choose
A certain amount
to come out and
Sing for their life.
And trust me, we're battling it
Out out here right now.
Here's where we stand.
15 people are eligible for three
Coveted wildcard spots.
Eight guys, seven girls.
Randy, jennifer, and steven are
Going to call upon six of them
To sing again.
And after that, each judge will
Pick one person
to enter back
Into the competition.
If last year's any indication,
This will be very, very
Emotional.
Randy, on behalf of the judges,
Who's going first?
Our first pick, ryan,
Tonight is jen hirsh.
Jen hirsh, come on,
Darling.
So where do you think it went a
Little wrong when you sang?
I'm not sure where it went
Wrong really.
I just don't think I stood out
As much,
and I think that I
Really can.
And I want to prove it to you.
And you've got that
Shot.
Right now.
All right.
Jen hirsh, take it away.
♪ oh darl darling
Please believe me ♪
♪ I'll never do you no harm ♪
♪ believe me when I tell you
I never do you no harm ♪
♪ when you told me
You didn't need me anymore ♪
♪ well you know I nearly broke
Down and cried ♪
♪ when you told me
You didn't need me anymore ♪
♪ well you know I nearly broke
Down and died ♪
Oh darling
Please believe me ♪
♪ I'll
I'll never do you no harm ♪
♪ believe me when I tell you
Jen hirsh!
Singing for her life.
Good job.
Hang right with me for one
Second.
Let's go to the judges, get
Their feedback.
Jen, we were just
Commenting.
We like when you guys come out
And sing for your life.
-It's crazy.
-You started pulling it All out.
You started kind of slow and you
Went for the gusto.
I think it was a good
Performance.
I think you showed the reason
That you're here
with those big
Old pipes and everything.
You know what I mean, with the
Big vocals.
I love that.
I'm -- we'll have to see how we
Fare after this,
after the other
Singing.
But that was good.
-you went for it.
-You went for it.
Jennifer?
I feel the same as
Randy.
We have five more people to go.
We're really going to try to be
Fair
and just listen to
Everybody.
You did your thing.
You sang for your life.
You really did.
You know, that was a
Little obvious at the beginning.
I thought, oh my god, here we
Go.
But then you took it home.
You really nailed it.
There's somebody with a big
Voice.
And I love it when it ends up
Like you just did.
I love it.
Where you went with your voice
At the end was beautiful.
All right.
thank you.
Good luck.
Hang tight.
As jennifer said, five more
Songs coming up.
singing for your life.
"idol" continues live after
This.
Back with you live on
"idol."
It's already been a crazy night,
And to recap, the people sitting
On those stools behind me
are Officially america's top ten.
We got room for three more.
Those places are reserved for
Our judges' wildcards.
Let's find out who's next
Fighting for a spot.
Jennifer, on behalf of the
Judges, who is up?
We have chosen
Jeremy.
Jeremy, jeremy rosado.
alright.
So you got your big moment.
What are you going to sing for
Us?
I'll get that for you.
I know you won't, carrie
Underwood.
ready to go?
jeremy rosado one more time
Singing for his life on
This stage,
good luck my man,
let's go.
I know you don't mean to be
Mean to me
Cause when you want to
You can make me feel like we belong
like we belong
I buy into those eyes
and into your lies
you say you'll call
but I know you
you say you're coming home
you say you'll call
but I know you won't
but I know you...
thank you.
Come on in.
Come on in here.
somethings going through
your body right now huh?
How badly do you want this spot,
Jeremy?
How badly do you want this shot?
this is my dream, man.
I may not have been able to show
You guys on Tuesday
what I can Do, but I promise you
that if You do this for me, I promise
You you won't regret it.
I just want to thank you guys
From the bottom of my heart
no Matter what, and thank lord
for this and thank you so Much.
Let's go to the judges.
Go first.
you just want me Because I'm about
To cry.
I believe in this kid.
I believe in jeremy.
I think he has one of the most
Beautiful voices I've heard.
In a long time.
But we'll see.
there's still four more to go
and like I said,
We're going to be fair about it.
You have to do your thing up
There.
But you did a good job.
I'm happy for you.
You love you coming
Out in this moment
bearing your
Soul.
This guy has such a big heart.
He's such a cool guy.
I love the person you are.
I love your voice too.
All of you are here because we
Love your voices,
but I love What you just did up there.
that was very nice.
You always had the
Biggest heart.
You've got the most passion.
When you sing like that and you
Make us cry,
america just saw
That.
They saw the real.
You are so real.
D that's a beautiful thing.
hang tight, take a stool
for a sec, jeremy rosado.
This is intense.
Steven, on behalf of the judges,
Who gets the next shot?
All right.
We have decided on brielle.
Brielle von hugel.
Brielle, come on down here.
Come here.
All right, sweetheart.
So tell me what you're going to
Do.
What's your game plan?
the song that I'm going to
Sing means so much to me
and I'm
Gonna lay it all out
because you Guys don't understand
that this Is my life.
Like I do it all day every day
And I live for it.
So this is it.
So much riding on this
Moment.
Good luck, okay?
Here we go.
Take it away.
♪ I heard that you settled down
That you found a girl
and you're married now
I heard that your dreams came
true
Guess she gave the things
I didn't give to you
♪ never mind I'll find someone
Like you
I wish nothing but the best for
You two ♪
♪ don't forget me
I begged
I remember you said ♪
♪ sometimes it's lasts in love
But sometimes it hurts instead ♪
♪ never mind I'll find someone
Like you ♪
♪ I wish nothing but the best
For you too ♪
♪ don't forget me
I begged
I remember you said ♪
♪ sometimes it lasts in love
But sometimes it hurts instead ♪
But sometimes it hurts
Instead ♪
All right.
I know mama liked it.
I saw mama up on her feet.
Now, steven, let me go to you on
This.
What do you think?
Wow, you know what,
Brielle?
I heard you -- a little pitchy
In some spots in the turnarounds
And I just didn't hear it this
Time.
I'm really sorry, baby.
Randy j.
Yeah, I think after
That rhyme,
brielle may be in a
Little trouble.
That wasn't great to me.
I felt your passion,
Baby.
I always do, which is why I Think
you deserve to get another
Chance out there.
You've been fighting through
This whole competition
and you Should be proud of that last
Effort as well.
we'll find out if  you're top 13
in just a bit.
Taking a quick break.
More second chances coming up
Live next here on "american
Idol."
Thanks for making
"american idol" part of your Evening.
So far tonight we've already
Named america's top ten
and now We're in the midst
of our Wildcard singoff.
We've got jen, jeremy, and
Brielle
waiting to see what
Happens for them.
Randy, who is next for the shot?
Next we've chosen
Deandre.
A second chance for
All right, man.
This is what it's all about.
Dig deep right here.
Okay?
You're going for it.
What are you gonna sing?
georgia, georgia on my
Mind.
-you ready?
-I'm ready.
let's do this.
singing for your life.
Deandre, let's go.
other arms reach out to me
another eyes they
smile tenderly
Still in peaceful dreams I see
♪ the road leads back
Back to you ♪
♪ georgia
Georgia ♪
♪ no peace
No peace I find ♪
♪ just an old sweet song
Keeps georgia on my mind ♪
♪ my my mind
♪ just an old sweet song
Keeps georgia ♪
♪ you got to keep georgia on my
Mind
Deandre!
Hold on For a sec.
Come here.
A standing ovation.
All right, judges, randy.
Nice way to come out, baby.
Nice way to come out.
thank you.
That's how you put it
In to try and stay in this.
I love this fight for their
Lives, ryan.
This is great.
This is great tension.
It's a great moment.
Bringing out greatness in all of
Them.
Right, jennifer?
Yes I'm feeling the
Fire from you and everybody.
That's exactly what you have to
Do.
You have to dig down deep.
You should sing like that every
Time you get up there.
I loved your voice
From the very beginning.
Last year and this year too.
You got such a dynamic range and
All over the place
and you go so
High.
I love it, man.
I just love it.
All right. Thank you, deandre.
Take a seat.
Good luck, my friend.
Let's hear for deandre.
All right.
Jennifer, who's next?
Oh, gosh.
Um, erika.
Erika van pelt.
I mean, this is serious tonight.
This is what it's all about
Here.
-Are you ready?
-this is so serious.
Are you ready to let it
Go?
yeah.
I'm letting it go tonight. Here we go.
What are you singing?
"edge of glory," lady gaga.
here we go.
erika van pelt.
♪ there ain't no reason you and me
should be alone tonight yeah
Baby tonight yeah baby ♪
Note I got a reason that you're
Who should take me home
Tonight ♪
♪ I need a man that thinks
it's Right when it's so wrong
Tonight yeah baby
Tonight yeah baby ♪
♪ right on the limits where we
Know we both belong tonight ♪
♪ it's hard to feel the rush
Push the dangerous ♪
♪ I'm gonna run right to
To the edge with you ♪
♪ where we can both fall over in
Love ♪
♪ I'm on the edge of glory ♪
♪ and I'm hanging on a moment of
Truth ♪
♪ out on the edge
Of glory ♪
♪ and I'm hanging on a moment
With you ♪
♪ I'm on the edge
The edge
The edge ♪
♪ I'm on the edge
Of glory ♪
♪ and I'm hanging on a moment
With you ♪
♪ I'm on the edge
The edge
The edge ♪
♪ I'm on the edge ♪
♪ of glory ♪
♪ and I'm hanging on a moment
With you ♪
♪ I'm on the edge with you ♪
Erika van pelt!
Judges.
she's singing like she's got
To have it.
I like someone who
Can fight through the tears.
and still deliver.
and that's not easy to do.
Your emotions get throug the best of you
and you fall apart but you
Did not.
You did not.
Beautiful, erika.
We're living on the edge without
A doubt.
Out of the park, baby.
Out of the park.
thank you.
Erika.
fate still undecided.
Head to the stools.
Next after this, find out who
Will be
the last person to get
Their shot.
More right after the break.
Stay with us live.
You're aled into
"american idol."
So far america's top ten have
Been named.
Give it up for that group.
And those on the stools have
Already taken the stage
to try
And earn a judgers' wildcard pick
but one more person will
Get an incredible shot.
Steven, who is that person going
To be?
Well, ryan, last but Not least
and after much
Deliberation...
reed grimm
Reed grimm.
Stay there for one second.
Let me have the rest of you down
To the center of the stage.
Unfortunately, that means the
Journey
officially ends for this
Group here.
On your feet for them, ladies
And gentlemen.
Let's hear it for them.
Thank you all very much for an
Incredible job.
We're gonna miss you.
We'll miss you, sweetheart.
All right.
I'm gonna have you exit right
Through here, just this way.
Keep it going as they exit the
Stage.
Good luck.
All right?
-Good luck.
-thank you.
Pleasure.
Good luck.
Good luck, adam.
Thank you.
Okay, reed.
Here we go, reed!
Come on.
Business to take care of, my
Friend.
I'm not quite sure what's
Happening.
I just...
I want to take this
Shirt off.
All right.
As long as you're stopping
There.
Okay.
Good.
Here you go.
Here's the microphone, tell me.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing use me by bill
Withers.
-are you ready?
- I am ready.
You're gonna do this.
I am gonna do this.
reed grimm, here we go.
This is about all of us.
♪ my friends
Feel it's their appointed duty ♪
♪ well they keep trying to tell
Me
All you want to do is use me ♪
♪ well well well my answer
To all that use me stuff ♪
♪ break it down
It feels good ♪
♪ use me up
Come on ♪
♪ oh come on
Come on
You got to use me up.
♪ use me
Use me ♪
♪ come on hey ♪
Thank you, reed!
All right.
Catch your breath.
Randy.
Yo, listen, man, we
Just had to see that again
Because you're probably one of
The most different artists
we've
Ever had try out for the show.
You are truly, truly unique and
Very different.
That was definitely
Entertaining.
I think we felt
Like last night you did a good
the night the boys
Performed,
you did a good job,
But people really didn't get to
See you
as we've gotten to know You,
and we wanted to give that
You one more chance.
We thought you deserved that one
More chance.
Steven tyler.
Reed, man, I love the
Artist in you, singing, drummer.
You nailed it tonight.
All right, reed.
Take your seat.
So what's gonna happen with the
Wildcard contenders?
During the break, the judge also
Deliberate
and make their
Decisions.
Each of them will pick one
Person
to stay alive in the
Competition.
Do not miss the dramatic news
Live next.
This is one of the most
Tense and emotional moments of
The season.
We're about to reveal who will
Complete this year's top 13.
So far based on your votes,
the Ten people in those stools are
In and safe.
Congratulations to them.
Steven, jennifer and randy will
Each
pick one person from the
Other group
to join them from
Their wildcard picks.
You got jen, jeremy, brielle,
Deandre, erika, and reed.
They all sang for this important
Second chance.
Judges, have you made your
Decisions?
-Yes.
All right.
Randy, first wildcard pick.
Let me just say, oh,
What a night.
A crazy emotional night.
Our first wildcard pick --
Erika van pelt.
Erika has made it.
Congratulations.
Okay.
Now let's go to jennifer.
After all of this, who is it
Going to be?
Who is your wildcard pick?
Jeremy rosado.
thank you so much.
Thank you.
-jeremy rosado!
-thank you so much.
-You want to go hug her?
-I do.
Go hug her.
thank you.
Thank you so much.
Don't fall.
thank you.
I'm so grateful.
All right, jeremy.
Come on up here
and take your
Stool in this group, my friend.
Let's go. Come on up here.
Jeremy rosado.
And finally, that last stool,
Steven tyler, who is it going to
Be?
All right.
You can let your hair down one
More time, deandre.
Deandre brackensick
Makes the final spot
in the top
13!
thank you.
You got it, buddy.
Jen, reed, brielle, come down
Here.
One more time.
as we say goodbye to you 3.
thank you very much.
It's the end of the road for
Them, but fantastic. thank you.
So we have got your top 13.
What a night.
Thank you very much.
You may exit.
Top 13, come on out here!
Let's go!
eat this up.
Your next "american idol" is
Standing on this stage.
Next week, we're back
as the guys
Take on the music of stevie
Wonder
and the ladies pay
Tribute to whitney houston,
all Mentored by the legendary
Mary j. Blige.
It is going to be a huge week.
Congratulations to all of you.
Thank you very much for
Watching.
Thank you for being here.
Good night, everybody.