Scotty mccreery!
Lee dewyze!
Kris Allen!
David cook!
Jordin sparks!
Taylor Hicks!
Carrie Underwood!
Fantasia barrino!
Ruben studdard!
Kelly Clarkson.
-Hi.
-Come on in here.
American idol has been in my life
since I was about six years old.
Hello. How are you?
I've been watching it since the
first season, and I've been
dreaming about being on the
show ever since Kelly Clarkson.
When I was six years old, I used
to stand in front of the TV
and act like I was the next
American idol.
We've been watching American
idol since the very
first season, and it's just
always been a dream.
Yeah.
I've been looking forward to
this moment for so long.
It's what I've been waiting
my whole life to do.
You get one shot at fame,
and that shot starts today.
And after 10 years, the phenomenon
continues with another incredible journey.
This could change my life.
Forever.
As new voices prepare for
the biggest musical platform
the country has ever seen.
This is the singing show.
This is the one that started it.
There is only one place where
you can make your dreams come true.
American idol's like the icon
of American society.
This is...  All: American idol.
There you go.
Time to start the process.
Who's fired up?
We'll be sharing this adventure
together.
American idol, here we come.
I'm just ready to get out
there and, like, chase my dream.
And, this year, the
contestants are going to help us
tell their story
through their own eyes.
Wish me the best of luck as I document
my journey to American idol.
It's gonna be a great year.
I loved that idol last year
took it over the top.
After going through last season
and looking at the talent this
year, I'm beside myself.
I loved it.
I'm so happy to be back
with Randy and Steven.
They're like my family now.
It's a new beginning, baby.
Season 1-1.
Freshest, hottest show ever.
Let's go.
Let's make some history.
Jennifer, Randy, and Steven
are back to find
the best of
America's undiscovered talent,
and the decade of preparation
has really paid off.
Hey, hold on.
It's gonna be quite a ride.
Do this.
My God, I think I just had
an ear-gasm.
Dude, I love you.
There's nobody singing like
her out there.
Ooh, I love that.
Yes!
Yes.
You're going to Hollywood.
That is hot.
Yes!
You know you're gonna be
a star, right?
I think America's gonna so
fall in love with you.
I'm scared, but, at the same
time I know this is what I want.
This is my saving grace.
This just-this is everything
to me.
But you know what?
You don't give up.
I know I can do this.
Please. I'm begging you.
I fell on my face a lot of times
and completely gave up on music.
No matter what happens, neve3r
stop believing in yourself.
'Cause we'll never stop
believing in you.
It's our very first time in
Savannah, Georgia.
Across the country, thousands
of hopefuls are waking up to
what could be the biggest day
of their life.
It's American idol time.
This marks the start of
their epic journey.
We're Savannah-bound.
Here we go.
I'm 26 miles from my dream.
Hello, Savannah.
6:00 in the morning sucks.
Are you ready for today?
Today's a big day.
Absolutely.
Because today is the day that
dreams are realized.
However, 12,000 others are
chasing that same goal.
Auditions begin right now.
Let's go.
This town is known for its
laid-back attitude.
And Randy definitely got
the memo.
Savannah, Georgia.
This is the jump-off right here.
Season 1-1.
Hi, guys.
I always have high hopes that today
is the day that we find the one.
You never know.
Good morning.
How's Savannah treating you?
Oh, Savannah's treating me great
but I didn't know you knew her.
What's up, everybody?
The crowd was pumped and ready
for its shot.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's hit it.
First day of school.
Savannah, Georgia.
First day.
We're back.
I can't stand the heat.
A new beginning.
Season 1-1, idol, a new
beginning.
If a 16-year-old from north Carolina
can win American idol...
I could do that.
So we are officially ready to
write another chapter.
And Scotty has left some pretty
big shoes to fill.
But our first contestant might
be able to walk all over the
competition.
My name's David leathers Jr.,
and I'm 17 years old, from
fayetteville, north Carolina.
My friends call me
Mr. steal your girl."
People say I'm somewhat of
a ladies' man.
That's cool, because I'm always
talking to the girls.
And girls love me.
What's your name?
My name? Fatia.
What's yours?
I'm David.
How old are you?
Doesn't matter.
Oh, age ain't nothing but
a number, but...
I don't really have an
exclusive girlfriend right now.
Couple of years ago, I just so
happened to be
in a local
contest with Scotty mccreery.
And we both placed first and
second.
Well, who was better, you or
Scotty?
Well, it was a tough
competition, but I came out on top.
You beat Scotty?
Dave?
Did you beat Scotty?
I guess you could say that.
You could say that.
Oh, this is gonna be good.
No pressure going in there, my
man.
Now are you gonna...
Wait, that's the sound of the
audition bell.
I was gonna ask you if you were
gonna leave the glasses on, but
we're out of time.
Get in there.Good luck.
Who's going first?
Hey!
Dude, David, what's up, man?
Look at this.
Oh, here he is.
I'm good. I'm doing good.
How about yourself?
How old are you, bro?
I'm 17.
Where you from?
Fayetteville, north Carolina.
Fayetteville, 17.
So I assume you're in high
school.
Yes, sir.
I know it may not look like it,
but it's my senior year.
You do look very young.
You look like you're 12.
Yeah, I know, right?
Well, you have any nicknames
they call you?
Uh, some of my friends call
me Mr. steal your girl.
What? You steal girls?
Just like, when I sing, all
the girls just like, "David,
i love you."
You know how that is, don't
you, baby?
Ooh, yeah, Steven knows a lot
about that.
So, dude, what are you singing
today, man?
Remember the rain? By
century 21.
Okay.
Do it.
♪ We used to play ♪
♪ out in the rain ♪
♪ your mother scolded us ♪
♪ she said that we were bad ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ I thought I better go ♪
♪ on home ♪
♪ you watched till I was gone ♪
♪ oh, girl, you looked ♪
♪ so sad ♪
♪ I picked you up ♪
♪ when you fell ♪
♪ and cut your knee ♪
♪ I told you not to cry ♪
♪ and held you close to me ♪
Nice, nice.
That's beautiful, man.
Interesting.
He looks like he's 12.
I know. Like a young Michael.
Do you know any
Michael Jackson?
I do.
Come on.
Give us a little
Michael Jackson.
Come on, man. Come on.
Young Michael?
♪ Can't say good-bye ♪
♪ no, no, no, no, I ♪
♪ never can say good-bye ♪
♪ even though the pain ♪
♪ and heartache ♪
♪ seems to follow me ♪
♪ wherever I go ♪
♪ though I try and try ♪
♪ to hide my feelings ♪
♪ they always seem to show ♪
♪ then you try to say ♪
♪ you're leaving me ♪
♪ and I always have to say no ♪
♪ tell me why ♪
♪ is it so ♪
♪ I never ♪
That's enough.
Nice. Nice.
Well, yo, listen, I mean, should
we make this, like, really simple?
Both: Yes.
Like, I mean, really easy?
One, two, three.
All: Yes!
Yes.
Let's go, David leathers.
Dude.
We love you, man.
You're going to Hollywood.
You're going to Hollywood,
dawg. You made it.
You're gonna go where
Scotty mccreery went, dude.
We'll see you in Hollywood.
Wow. Wow.
Yay! Good start.
Thank you for a decent
breakfast.
That was nice.
Very impressive.
A ticket to Hollywood would
be a dream come true.
Wow, he sings super high.
That was beautiful.
Yes.
All right.
All right, yes.
Are we having fun yet?
Come on now.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's keep it going.
Over the next two hours...
Savannah sizzles with fresh,
hot talent.
I'm gonna blow you away.
Wow.
I've never seen anything like
that.
That is hot.
That's crazy right there.
Thank you, God.
Stop it.
But later... what?
Everything goes South.
Awful.
No!
What's going on?
It's 10:30 A.M. in Savannah.
Big day.
Idol's in town today.
Season 11 auditions starting
at the coliseum today.
Over 9,000 people in line.
It's really awesome out
there.
And so far season 11 is off
to a sweet start.
God, that makes me feel good.
Backstage, Connecticut native gabi
carrubba hopes to keep the spirits high.
Oh, my God. I...
Shaking I'm so nervous.
But this 16-year-old is more than
used to soaking up the spotlight.
Besides singing, I'm a champion
tap dancer.
I'm always moving, I'm always
dancing.
I have so much energy.
I've been dancing since I was one
years old in the diaper dancers.
And I haven't been stopping
since.
I've danced every day.
I've been waiting to audition
my whole life.
I've been watching the show since I
was a little kid, since season one.
I'm excited to meet
Ryan seacrest.
Standing by.
That's who I'm really excited
to meet.
What's the reaction that you dream
of getting from the judges?
Okay, well, Steven Tyler, he
does this thing where, when
he listens to somebody
good, he goes like this.
He, like, makes this face.
What do you think he sees in his
head when he makes that face?
Well, good luck.
Nice to meet you, gabi.
Thank you so much.
Hello. How are you?
Can I give Nigel a hug really
quick?
You-wait a minute, guys.
Hang on, hang.
This girl walks in and she wants
to hug Nigel.
What is this about?
I love Nigel.
I watch him on
so you think you can dance,
like, every-every day.
Wait a minute. Hang on.
So what is your name, lover of
Nigel?
I'm gabi carrubba.
'Cause you're 16 now, so
you're ready?
I'm ready.
What you gonna sing?
Sunday morning by maroon 5.
Okay.
Go for it.
♪ Sunday morning ♪
♪ rain is falling ♪
♪ steal some covers ♪
♪ share some skin ♪
♪ clouds are shrouding us ♪
♪ in moments unforgettable ♪
♪ you twist to fit ♪
♪ the mold that I am in ♪
Nice.
♪ May be all I need ♪
♪ in darkness he is all I see ♪
♪ come and rest your bones ♪
♪ with me ♪
♪ driving slow ♪
♪ on Sunday morning ♪
♪ and I never want to leave ♪
That was so wonderful.
That was so beautiful.
I loved the choices that you
make.
Very, very nice.
The way you played with it-
nice tone.
You nailed it. You nailed it.
It was like, thank you, God.
This may be your magic moment,
darling.
Should we vote?
Yeah.
Steven? Yeah... Jennifer. Yes.
You were born to do this.
Yes. Welcome to Hollywood.
You better.
Thank you so much.
She had one of those natural
voices.
It's just so simple for her,
like Luther vandross.
It just comes out...
It's so natural.
I'm like, where has she been
hiding?
'Cause she took her time.
She's only 16.
She hasn't been hiding anywhere.
The choices-but I'm saying,
I mean, my God.
Steven Tyler did the thing.
He did this.
And, over the next two hours,
Savannah was definitely
delivering a taste of the good
life.
♪ Oh, I want to dance ♪
♪ with somebody ♪
♪ I want to feel the heat ♪
♪ I'll catch a grenade ♪
♪ for you ♪
♪ throw my hand on a blade ♪
♪ I'll jump in front ♪
♪ of a train for you ♪
♪ you're no good ♪
♪ baby, you're noooo ♪
Beautiful.
♪ Come on and get it ♪
♪ while you can ♪
♪ come on and get when you ♪
♪ want to need it, baby ♪
♪ don't you turn your back ♪
♪ on love, no, no, no, no ♪
Wow.
Little spitfire.
What do you think, Steven?
I think so yes.
Guess what?
Welcome to Hollywood.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm gonna say yes.
Guess what?
You're going to Hollywood.
Hello, Hollywood.
This is a great day for
talent.
Amazing, amazing.
What's going on?
Amazing first day in
Savannah, dude.
I'm saying.
A lot of young kids too.
15, 16, 17.
This is better than you
expected it to be.
Way better.
Day one?
First city? Forget about it.
That's right. Hollywood.
On a hot streak this morning.
Every single person that's come in has
gotten a yes and a golden ticket.
One of the best starts we've
ever had on th show.
And our next contestant might
just have the credentials to
keep the momentum going.
I'm Jessica whiteley, and I'm 19 years
old, and I'm from cuyahoga falls, Ohio.
I started singing around,
like, maybe ten years old.
I sing the national anthem a lot
in a lot of basketball games,
football games, and, you know,
the talent show every year.
Singing's just everything
I want.
It's all I think about.
Hello.
Hi.
How are you?
This is awesome.
It looks like I'm looking at
a magazine.
I love your hat, by the way,
Steven.
Beautiful. Thanks.
What's your name?
Give us your whole name.
I'm Jessica whiteley.
Whiteley.
And you are how old?
I'm 19.
And you're from?
Cuyahoga falls, Ohio.
Okay.
12 hours away.
Well, we've had a really good
run this morning.
You ready?
I am ready.
What are you gonna sing?
Um, I'm singing in this song
by charice.
♪ 'Cause this is my destiny ♪
♪ it depends on me alone ♪
♪ alone ♪
♪ so ♪
♪ just sing this song ♪
♪ and it takes me right back ♪
♪ where I belong ♪
♪ 'cause every day ♪
♪ there's a new bridge ♪
♪ to cross ♪
♪ and I'm never far from home ♪
♪ I get my heart ♪
♪ my soul ♪
♪ my own in this song ♪
♪ in this song ♪
♪ in this so-o-ong ♪
Awful.
That was not good.
It was like, you were just
really shouting.
I don't even know if I would
call that singing.
It's just not...
Baby, this is not your vibe.
This is not your groove right
here.
I don't know.
You got the ball, you got the
shot, you go and you shoot,
and it's just not quite going
through the net.
Can I sing you another song?
No!
Do people say that you can
sing?
I mean, what happened?
Yeah, I think I'm just
a little dehydrated.
I'm not gonna complain.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, so we're sorry.
It was not remotely good
today.
It's a no, sweetie.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
We'll see you in Texas then.
Both: Okay.
All right, nice to meet you.
Did she say see you in Texas?
Is she coming to audition in Texas too?
Oh, no. Oh, no!
Can we say no?
Don't come to Texas, please.
We should tell her not to
take that drive.
Steven's going, "oh, no!"
You guys are gonna see me
in Texas, so get ready.
'Cause I'm coming back.
We'll look forward to that.
But before Jessica leaves us
in Savannah, let's hear how
her audition song really sounds.
♪ In this song ♪
♪ in this song ♪
♪ in this- ♪
♪ song ♪
After the break, the judges
put on a happy face as
the competition heats up.
Fire.
And Savannah explodes...
With more incredible voices.
You're going to Hollywood!
All: Welcome back to
American idol!
Nowadays, it's hard to
keep the same gig forever.
All right.
And after 11 seasons of
practice, it seemed many were
gunning for my job.
My name is Ryan seacrest,
and this is American idol!
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Next.
Next?
Next who?
I know.
Next on American idol.
Ready? Big.
Big right to that camera.
This is American idol.
Nice job.
But one contestant who showed
up in Savannah
was taking it
to the next level.
What's your name?
I'm Sean.
Hey, Sean.
Nice to meet you, Ryan.
Nice to meet you, buddy.
People tell me all the time
I look like Ryan seacrest.
And they ask me if I try to look
like him, and I don't have
a great answer for it.
I do my hair like this every
single day.
Well, you dressed like a
host.
Yes, I dress like my
inspiration Mr. Ryan seacrest.
Hi, how you doing? Hi.
You may actually be better than
the original.
No, no.
No one's better than
the original.
If you wanna text the word vote
to 866-idol-05.
Good luck to you.
Well, thank you so much.
We'll be here on the other
side, hoping to see that golden
ticket.
The results are in.
Dim the lights.
Here we go.
This... this... this... this...
This...Is American idol!
Let's go!
Okay, buddy.
How old are you?
26.
Exactly.
Twins.
Hi.
How are you?
What's your name?
Sean.
Sean?
Yes.
Sean what? What?
Who do people say you look
like?
Sometimes I get
Ryan seacrest.
Say it again. Say it again.
Very-you sound just like
him.
Thank you.
Wow.
Thank you, it's a compliment.
Definitely a compliment.
I guess.
Ryan's an inspiration for me.
Do you-oh.
Keep going.
This is weird!
This completes the look.
Wait a minute, Ryan.
Wait a minute, stay right there.
Stay right there.
When I say who do you look
like, what do you say?
Ryan seacrest.
I say Sean.
Sean crissman.
Ryan seacrest.
Do it again.
Here, why don't you go-
go through the whole-
no, no, take the cards.
You guys look weird together,
Ryan.
You're dressed for the
finale, so here we are.
It's the moment you're about to
announce the winner.
Okay.
I like "the votes are in,
dim the lights."
Go for that one-3, 2, 1.
We're taking requests.
The results are in.
Dim the lights.Here we go.
This is American idol!
Let's go!
Oh! Nice job!
Yo, listen, you know what?
You're making it look too
easy.
I was-I'm working on that.
Will you work for half of
Ryan's pay?
I told him I'd work for free.
Oh! Got the job!
All right, back to
the singing.
Back to the singing.
Hire this man.
And what are you gonna sing
for us today?
I'd like to do oh girl
by the chi-lites.
Okay.
♪ Oh, girl ♪
♪ I'd be in trouble ♪
♪ if you left me now ♪
♪ but I don't know where ♪
♪ to look for love ♪
♪ I just don't know how ♪
♪ oh, girl ♪
♪ how I depend on you ♪
♪ to give me love ♪
♪ when I need it ♪
♪ right on time ♪
♪ you will always be ♪
Okay.
I would've liked it better if you sung
it like Ryan seacrest, though, actually.
I wonder what Ryan sounds like
singing.
I always wondered.
I always wondered if he sang
too.
He's very comfortable in
front of the camera.
He gets that from you.
Well- as a singer, no, man.
But personality you brought in
here is over the top.
No.
Brother.
But you know what they did
say?
They said yes to Ryan.
They did give me the yes for
that, but not singing.
I don't know if that's a good thing
or- oh, I'm gonna take it as
good, 'cause the other news
wasn't any good.
He looks just like Ryan.
Nice to meet you, buddy.
Good luck!
See you next time
on American idol
it turns out discovering the next American
idol is turning into a tall order.
Something 15-year-old
Shannon magrane knows all about.
How are you?
Good, how are you?
Good, what's your name?
My name's Shannon.
Shannon magrane.
How old are you?
I'm 15 years old.
You're 15?
6 foot tall, size 11 shoe.
Wow.
Okay, tell us about yourself
a little bit.
Well, actually I am
a volleyball player.
I'm a middle hitter.
How'd you get into sports?
I mean, is your family into
sports?
Yes, my dad is actually- he was a
pitcher in the world series, 1987.
Wow!
What's his name?
Joe magrane.
Wow. Get down, dude.
For what team?
Um, cardinals.
St. Louis cardinals. Nice.
We're gonna have to meet them
in a minute.
Yeah, man.
Yes, can I bring them in to you?
Okay. Go get 'em.
You know.
Oh, my God, can I really?
Yeah, yeah.
Sister?
This is my sister.
Rest of my family.
Mommy?
This is my mama.
Mom, hi.
This looks like my family.
All girls and the dad.
One guy.
Dude, world series!
World series!
No, still the world series at
all.
Aren't you lucky with
all these girls, huh?
That's right.
Yeah.
How's things in b-town?
Oh, great. Beautiful.
Hot, humid, and happenin'.
Absolutely.
Yeah, just like your
daughter.
Ri-ight.
What a beautiful family.
All righty, what are you gonna
sing?
All right, I have
something's got a hold on me by etta James.
I don't know if you know that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
♪ Oh, sometimes ♪
♪ I get a good feeling, yeah ♪
♪ I get a feeling ♪
♪ that I never, never, never ♪
♪ never had before ♪
♪ no, no ♪
♪ and I just gotta tell you ♪
♪ right now that I ♪
♪ I believe ♪
♪ I really do believe that ♪
♪ something's got a hold on me ♪
♪ right now, child ♪
♪ let me tell you now ♪
♪ I never thought ♪
♪ this could happen to me ♪
♪ my heart was heavy ♪
♪ when in misery ♪
♪ I never thought ♪
♪ it could be this way ♪
♪ love's sure gonna ♪
♪ put a hurtin' on me ♪
♪ I said whoa ♪
All right, all right, all
right.
We were, like, vibing and
rolling with that one.
Um, so, mom, you were singing
every word.
Are you a singer?
I'm not.
But I hear it, and I have to turn it
down-it ricochets throughout the house.
Dude, you were cool with your
family-no nerves.
And you were ready to go.
Nerves of steel at 15 with your
mom and dad and all your friends.
That is hot.
That's crazy right there.
Nerves of steel this girl.
Yeah.
To not care enough where your voice
has to come out, that's the secret.
And that's what you did.
Shall we vote?
I say yes.
I say yes too.
I say yes too-three yeses!
You're going to Hollywood!
Dad, you gotta come and
help out the Dodgers, dude.
Can't happen soon enough.
Thank you!
Great meeting you.
It was so nice to meet you.
Good luck, Shannon.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Wow, to have such a family like that.
That's a great family.
That's a good family right
there.
Coming up, Savannah wows us
with their talent... ♪ so far ♪
And one inspiring story.
I live in a tent.
Wow.
Expectations continue to be shattered
as it's midday in the garden of good...
Nice, beautiful.
And evil.
It's high noon in the heart
of Savannah.
In the South, we don't sing.
We sang!
That's right!
I love this day.
Good one, Savannah.
Next person, please.
But even though Georgia appears
to be on a hot streak,
looks can sometimes be
deceiving.
I hope you can sing.
Today I'll be singing i
think I'm in love with you
by Jessica Simpson.
Okay, let's hear it.
♪ Boy, you really blew ♪
♪ my...♪
Next.
♪ Just wanna tell you ♪
♪ how I'm feeling ♪
♪ we could've had it all ♪
That was awful.
It was great.
Shut up before I smack you.
But there are certainly no
disguises on the Tennessee
native walking into the room.
Hello.
Both: Hi.
Wow.
Hi, beautiful girl.
What's your name?
Amy.
Amy what?
Amy brumfield.
How old are you?
I'm 24.
And where are you from?
Gatlinburg, Tennessee.
Tell us a little bit about
yourself.
I live in a tent in
the woods.
Yes.
You do?
Way out in the middle of
the woods, I live in a tent.
Yes, I do.
Wow.
Really?
Well, we're kinda struggling.
Major struggling.
Can't afford like a $100-a-week
hotel room, you know?
The only thing we can do is
live in a tent in the woods.
Welcome...To our humble home.
Come on, we'll show you around.
This is where the magic happens,
guys.
Right there, you know.
We cook our soup over the fire
pit...Yes.
And we enjoy it.
This is the closet.
Emergency tarp.
And this is our bathroom.
Bathroom area.
All this way-bathroom.
All this way.
Blake is awesome.
I've never been treated so good
by anybody in my entire life.
I didn't think I could ever
be treated good.
Then he came along.
He is working every single day,
and even on the weekends he does
side jobs and stuff like that
just to try to come up with
enough money for food, gas.
The necessities.
That's it.
And just work hard to try to
get out of it.
Try to get out of the tent.
And times are tough out
there, so it's been-
extremely tough.
That's why I live in a tent.
That's why you live in the
tent?
Yeah.
I would rather be outdoors and
happy than indoors and
miserable.
Good.
My boyfriend's mother- she
fixed up this little dress
and earrings and necklace and
shoes and the whole nine.
I've never been dressed this
nice before in my entire life.
I have had a lot of blessings
that I had to learn in life
to get to where I'm at mentally.
I mean, if there's any perfect
time for me to be doing this,
it's now.
Should we do some singing?
We should.
What song?
I'm gonna sing superwoman
by Alicia keys.
Do it.
All right.
♪ For all the mothers ♪
♪ fighting ♪
♪ for better days to come ♪
♪ and all my women ♪
♪ all my women sitting here ♪
♪ trying ♪
♪ to come home before the sun ♪
♪ and all my sisters ♪
♪ coming together ♪
♪ say yes, I will ♪
♪ yes, I can ♪
♪ 'cause I am a superwoman ♪
♪ yes, I am ♪
That's my jam.
Very interesting tone.
I like the kinda hoarseness.
The roughness.
Raspy.
It gets pretty there...
I like that.
When you open up like that.
I like this Amy girl.
The spirits and the children
of the woods snuck into you.
And I like that.
I'm a hippie baby.
Hell yeah.
I love it.
You're hipsy.
A hipsy-I like that hipsy.
I'm a hipsy.
All right, let's vote.
What do you think, Steven?
I think so positively yes.
100% yes from me.
Me too!
Out of a tent and into
Hollywood.
Hello, Hollywood!
What a story!
Hey, can I pitch a tent
behind the mansion?
If that's where you feel
comfortable.
Go right ahead.
Okay.
Congratulations.
Good for you, congrats.
Totally knew you had it!
What!
That is wonderful.
Special voice.
I like that word hipsy,
though.
She is a hipsy.
Hipsy.
Well, good luck to you guys.
Thanks for coming.
Nice to meet you.
Good to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Blake.
You look a lot taller on TV.
So do you.
Hollywood!
I'm totally going to Hollywood.
Whoo! Man!
Ah, going to Hollywood!
Anybody else wanna come?
Up next, can this 15-year-old
conquer her nerves to achieve
her lifelong dream?
I've never done something
this big before.
I'm gonna say no, not yet.
And with a trip to Hollywood
on the line, which contestants
will be ready to seize their
moment?
Let's do this!
All: Welcome back to idol,
y'all.
Nice work, fellas.
Hanging out in Georgia, we
thought we'd met every brand
of good ol' country boy.
We like our shrimp and grits,
and we like our boys Southern
too!
And then we met 23-year-old
Joshua chavis.
I'm here to audition today
'cause it's been a dream of mine
ever since I can remember to sing
in front of a live audience.
My biggest dream is to sing a
national anthem at a nascar
race, and that's for my mama.
Every time I sing, all my friends,
they say I'll be famous.
I'm gonna leave my nerves out
the door with my boyfriend.
I'm gonna go in there
and do the damn thing.
Randy's gonna love me.
Steven's gonna love me.
J-lo's gonna love me.
J-lo, I love you.
Oh, my God. For real.
I know you're still Jenny from
the block, but oh!
You gotta come to my block.
There's an inner excitement
there, right?
Yes, it's ready to come out.
I feel like you've been
excited all day.
I got this American idol
thing in the bag.
I have what it takes.
I'm going to go and blow this
audition out of the water.
Yikes.
Let's do this.
Who's this?
Yeah, yeah!
Hi.
About time you got in here.
Tell me about it.
I been waiting.
Is that you who sneezed
back there?
I was letting some stress
out.
So that was you yelling.
Yes.
Oh, okay. Okay.
What's your name, dude?
I'm Joshua chavis.
I'm 23, and I'm from Camden,
South Carolina.
Who are you compared to,
if anyone?
Um, some-my voice has been
compared to Chris Daughtry,
Brad paisley.
It's kind of like a country, pop,
rock all thrown into one.
Nice.
And I'm not leaving this
stage without a ticket.
So you better be good.
I'm good.
What you gonna sing, man?
I'm yours by Jason mraz.
Do it.
Okay. Please be good.
♪ Well, you done done me ♪
♪ and you bet I felt it ♪
♪ I tried to be chill ♪
♪ but you're so hot ♪
♪ that I melted ♪
♪ I fell right through ♪
♪ the cracks ♪
♪ and now I'm trying ♪
♪ to get back ♪
♪ before the cool done ♪
♪ run out ♪
♪ I'll be giving it ♪
♪ my bestest ♪
♪ nothing's gonna stop ♪
♪ but divine intervention ♪
♪ I reckon it's again my turn ♪
♪ to win some or learn some ♪
♪ but I won't hesitate ♪
♪ no more, no more ♪
♪ it cannot wait, I'm yours ♪
Thank you, Joshua.
Wow.
Okay, then.
Um, should we hear one more,
Steven?
What are we thinking?
You have -you ran out of
breath?
Yeah, no, it's all good.
You know what, you're sweet
and you're cute and-
oh, my God, Jennifer Lopez
just told me I'm cute.
I don't know that
the voice is really up to par
with what we're doing this year.
But you know, you have all those
other things going for you.
I'm gonna sing-
let me sing something else.
No, no, no, no.
Please. No, no.
Steven, what do you think?
What do you think, Steven?
I agree with her.
The voice just ain't there, man.
What do you think?
Actually, rlly- ♪ today I don't
feel like ♪
♪ doing anything ♪
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm just gonna help you out.
I'm gonna help you out.
I mean, really? Right.
Me and you, right.
Terrible.
Nice to sing at birthday
parties, weddings, friends.
I wouldn't.
The bar's so high this year.
I mean, dude.
Singing-no, dude.
No, no, no, no.
But good luck to you.
Thank you.
Good luck, man, thank you.
Please don't cry.
It's all right, Josh.
Don't worry about it, man.
Please don't cry.
Don't cry.
I always get worried when they say
"I sound like
Brad paisley or Chris Daughtry."
I'm like...Eek!
That's when you know they
sound nothing like them.
Exactly.
That's a clear sign.
Get out of my face.
I just wanna be alone.
Seriously, get out of my face.
I don't wanna talk to y'all.
Don't get mad now.
I didn't make it.
I didn't make it, it sucks.
Would you stop following me?
Get your [Bleep] back in there
and do your [Bleep] job!
I just had a little hissy fit
outside.
While Joshua heads home to finish his
hissy fit, backstage the pressure has
pushed the contestants' nerves
to the edge.
None more so than the 15-year-old
about to step into the room.
Oh, my gosh.
I've never done something
this big before.
Stephanie Renee.
I got it.
Bring it on!
For Stephanie, this moment has been
nearly a decade in the making.
When I was eight, I watched
American idol all the time.
My favorite one was
Carrie Underwood.
I loved her.
She's inspired me so much.
My mom has pictures of me next
to a TV with a shirt that
says I'm the next American idol.
Hey! Where are we going?
American idol!
It's what every girl dreams of.
Just to be on American idol.
I want a golden ticket so bad.
This means so much to me.
Be calm. Don't freak out.
Have fun.
That's what it's all about.
I'm just shocked right now
'cause I'm actually living
what's really on TV.
Hey, get in here, girl.
Hi.
Hey, sparkly baby.
Sparkly.
What's your name, sparkles?
My name is Stephanie Renee.
Yeah?
It's just amazing to be here
right now.
Aww, bless you.
Oh, bless you.
And how old are you?
I'm 15.
I just turned 15 actually.
Yeah?
So I just slid right in
there.
Nice.
What are you gonna sing us?
I'm gonna sing you, um,
inside your heaven
by Carrie Underwood.
Okay, let's hear it.
♪ I wanna be inside ♪
♪ your heaven ♪
♪ take me to the place ♪
♪ you cry from ♪
♪ when a storm blows ♪
♪ you away ♪
♪ every bit of air ♪
♪ you're breathing in ♪
♪ a soothing wind ♪
♪ I wanna be ♪
♪ inside your heaven ♪
Nice, beautiful.
Really beautiful.
What a natural, beautiful
vibrato you have.
Thank you.
So pretty.
And I love when you open up
and those notes-
you sing a little bit nasally.
Yeah, a little in the nose.
If you could correct that-
oh, my God-you would be, like,
so amazing.
'Cause it's already really
beautiful.
Thank you.
I really needed that, 'cause
I've always wanted to ask you
guys, like, "what should I do
to, you know, help me?"
Open your mouth-ahhh.
Let it out.
Couple of vocal lessons.
Yeah.
Okay.
That will help you with that
kind of stuff, you know what
i mean?
All right, cool.
And lay on a couple of words
that mean something to you.
So you get the inflections out.
All right.
You know what I mean?
Let's take a vote.
Steven, yes or no?
Oh, positively yes.
Uh, I'm gonna say no, not
yet.
Okay.
It's all on Jennifer.
I'm saying yes too.
You're going to Hollywood!
You're going to Hollywood
anyway.
Two yeses and one no.
Welcome to Hollywood!
I think she needs some lessons, a
little bit more experience.
No, it was so natural.
She has one bad habit.
Yeah.
One bad habit.
We'll see-listen, we'll see.
That's why, you know, there's
three of us.
You guys said yes, I said no.
So you know, she proved me
wrong.
Just to make sure that, you
know, you weren't crazy.
I'm still
a little crazy.
Come on. A little, man.
That's right, what am I
thinking?
A little bit, come on.
Right, Stevie?
Right, right, right, right.
Next.
I won.
Well, I didn't win!
But I-I don't know!
Where are you going?
I'm going to Hollywood!
When we come back,
a brother/sister rivalry plays
out on center stage.
You auditioned for us last
year with your brother.
He's not auditioning this
year.
What?
You don't give up.
It's 4:00 P.M. in Savannah, and,
as the day pushes o so do
the dreams of the thousands who
have come here to audition.
My big sis is the next
American idol!
It always helps when your
siblings are cheering you on.
But our next contestant,
schyler Dixon, is hoping to
redefine herself, this time
on her own terms.
Colton, my brother, auditioned
with me last year.
You know, I kinda leaned on him
for everything, and, this year,
I'm just branching off and doing
my own thing.
She's the one that got me
to audition last year.
I've kind of taken a backseat this
year and let her kinda do her thing.
I'm excited to see what she
does.
So you are not auditioning?
I am not auditioning.
I'm a little nervous without him,
but I'm definitely excited
to be able to break off and do
my own thing.
I definitely feel like this is
my year.
I'm in it to win it.
Both: Hey!
Hi!
What's going on, man?
How are you?
I've been pretty good.
Yeah?
You auditioned for us last year.
I did, I did with my brother.
With your brother.
Where is he?
[Whispering] He's out there.
Is he auditioning next?
No, he's not auditioning
this year.
Yeah, he's out there.
What!
He almost made it.
He could've made it into
the top 12.
We're gonna make you bring him
in here.
Go get him.
Yeah, go get him.
I have to go get Colton.
Come on.
Oh, no.
Having been put on the spot,
you have to wonder if schyler
is willing to share her
spotlight.
Colton!
Dude, come on!
What's up?
What's up, guys?
Dude, come on!
What?
You're not auditioning?
You almost made it last year.
I was close, I don't know.
It was hard to go through.
You guys experienced it
first-hand, didn't you?
It was awful for me.
It was really hard.
It was terrible.
But you know what?
You don't give up.
Dude, you can't give up.
Oh, no way giving up.
You were so close.
You gotta audition again.
Both of you.
I remember how good you were
too.
Come on.
Ah, I don't know.
You're gonna sing.
First your sister's gonna sing.
Ladies first.
Stand over there.
Come on, Colton.
We're gonna let you get away
that easy, come on.
What are you gonna sing for
us today?
Um, breakeven by the script.
Okay, go ahead.
♪ I'm still alive ♪
♪ but I'm barely breathing ♪
♪ just praying to a God ♪
♪ that I don't believe in ♪
♪ 'cause when a heart breaks ♪
♪ no, it don't break even ♪
♪ even ♪
♪ you know ♪
♪ what am I supposed to do ♪
♪ when the best part of me ♪
♪ was always you and ♪
♪ what am I supposed to say ♪
♪ when I'm all choked up ♪
♪ and you're okay ♪
♪ yeah, I'm falling to pieces ♪
♪ yeah ♪
So pretty.
Come on, Colton, it's your turn.
Colton, come on.
Come on, Colton!
Colton, come on, Colton.
Make us feel stupid for last
year, come on.
Come on, Colton.
My name is Colton Dixon.
I'm a repeat offender.
I'll do permanent by
David cook.
Okay, cool.
♪ Is the moment when ♪
♪ I look you in the eye ♪
♪ forgive my broken promise ♪
♪ that you'll never see me cry ♪
♪ see me cry ♪
♪ and everything ♪
♪ it will surely change ♪
♪ even if I tell you ♪
♪ I won't go away today ♪
♪ but will you think ♪
♪ that you're all alone ♪
♪ when no one's there ♪
♪ to hold your hand ♪
♪ when all you know ♪
♪ seems so far away ♪
♪ and everything is temporary ♪
♪ rest your head ♪
♪ I'm permanent ♪
Come on over here, schyler,
baby.
Come on over here, schyler.
The brother, sister.
Both of you.
You know how I feel about your
voice.
But you've come up a couple
notches.
I think you have grown.
I think you still need to work
hard.
Again, you're 16, right?
Yeah.
Colton, you're amazing.
Thank you.
I think you both have grown.
It's really funny.
Yeah, he has too.
I think you've grown more, Colton,
into who you really, really wanna be.
You know what makes you
better too?
Pain.
Exactly.
I agree.
All right, let's take a vote
here, Steven-yes or no?
For chutzpah alone, you both
get a yes.
I want you both too.
And guess what I want.
I'm having both of them!
They're both going to Hollywood!
Come on!
Oh, my God.
Yay!
Did you really think you were
gonna come here- no, he didn't.
Come on, man.
Did you really think that, man?
He knew.
I'll hug you when you win.
Okay.
Come on, man.
Family Dixon.
Pack a bag!
I- really?
Why are you shaking?
I have no idea what happened
in there.
We did it!
We're going to Hollywood!
Look at this!
She sucked me in again.
Look what she did.
Like it or not, schyler shares
her big moment with Colton.
We'll see how this sibling
rivalry pans out in Hollywood.
After the break... the Savannah auditions
continue to impress the judges
with overwhelming talent.
That was beautiful!
Goosies!
But this journey isn't going
to be easy.
I tried so hard.
Oh, God!
Day one auditions in Savannah
are coming to a close.
And, while there are many high points,
for some it's been more of a downer.
I can't sing.
What happened?
They said I was emotionless.
This ain't the end.
I will continue.
Stop crying.
I don't wanna talk.
Oh, baby, I'm gonna say no.
No, no, no.
♪ I fall to pieces ♪
It's a good thing the next contestant
is in the business of spreading joy.
Hi!
How are you?
I'm doing good.
How are you all doing?
Very well. What's your name?
My name is Lauren mink.
Lauren mink.
Ooh, I like it.
25, and where you from?
I'm from Winchester,
Kentucky.
Okay, cool.
And what do you do?
I'm the director for a program
for adults with disabilities.
That's cool.
My job is pretty much, I think, the
best job imaginable other than singing.
You ready?
I get to work with people with
intellectual disabilities.
They have down syndrome,
autism, and things like that.
And I get to play every day
for a job.
All the people in our program, they are
ages 16- and we have some that are as
old as about 65 years old.
Are we gonna dance tonight?
We sure can if you feel like
it.
Are we gonna have hors
d'oeuvres and stuff?
We're gonna have lasagna.
I've tried to incorporate
some music into it.
American idol... all: Rocks!
Getting ready to have a big
fundraiser, so we're trying to
do choir for that.
And, yeah, there's no harmony
or anything in it, but they
just have so much fun.
And it always brings tears to
people's eyes just watching
the joy that they have.
I would love the chance
to be able to be a role model
for people.
You know, you can-
you can do anything that you
set your mind to.
♪ I know you see me ♪
♪ like some wide-eyed dreamer ♪
♪ that just rode in ♪
♪ off a dusty midwest bus ♪
♪ yeah, on the outside ♪
♪ I look fragile ♪
♪ but on the inside ♪
♪ there's something ♪
♪ you can't crush ♪
♪ 'cause I'm country strong ♪
♪ hard to break ♪
♪ like the ground ♪
♪ I grew up on ♪
♪ you may fool me ♪
♪ and I'll fall ♪
♪ but I won't stay down long ♪
♪ 'cause I'm country strong ♪
Mm, you sure are.
That was beautiful.
Goosies!
So good. Really.
Jennifer's got goosebumps.
You know, come on.
Goosies!
I love this day.
Can I just say that I love this
day?
Oh, you got so much passion.
Can we just vote? Okay.
So much passion behind
the notes.
Thanks.
And the notes were so on
that it was just perfect.
It was beautiful.
Thank you.
Nice little audition there,
girl.
It was like you started
opening up and really getting
your confidence and growling at
us.
Oh, my God, I loved it.
And I liked the little
Jennifer nettles-ish
sugarland-ish kind of like thing
in there.
I like that.
Thanks!
That's my favorite band right
now.
I could tell, I could tell, I could tell.
I like that.
Very nicely done.
So, Jennifer, yes?
Yes.
Randy, yes.
Steven, what are you telling this girl?
Steven, yes.
You're going to Hollywood, girl!
Thank you!
See you all there!
Yeah, see ya there!
That is so good.
Wow.
That is wonderful.
Special voice.
Did you know that was going
so well?
Could you tell it was going your
way?
When j-lo got some goosebumps
and she was sitting there-
yeah, so she was getting
goosebumps, so I thought, oh,
gosh, this is a good sign.
I'm going to Hollywood!
Coming up, it's a new dawn
in the South...
And a new day of auditions.
Next American idol!
But will the day two contestants
be able to stand the heat?
I'm telling you, dude, you're
gonna get eaten alive.
I promise I'll make you
proud.
Plus, an audition you'll have
to see to believe.
That's so good.
Super special.
As the sun rises on day two
in Savannah, we have just one
question for this massive crowd.
What is up with this heat?
All: Everything's hotter
in the South!
It's blazin' hot down here in
the South.
Each of our judges arrive...
In their own time.
Did they lie to me and
get me here early again?
Here we are once again.
This is the earliest I've
ever been late.
One just a little more tardy
for the party.
Wow.
Where's Randy?
I feel like we're gonna find some
really hot contestants here today.
I'm still always first.
I'm waiting for these guys to
put on their makeup.
Do their hair and make out
before they come to set.
Isn't that crazy?
Laughing, giggling, tickling
each other.
With all hands on deck,
it's time to set sail.
Steven, is this your yacht
out here?
This is my yacht.
Really?
Yup.
I brought it all the way from
Maui.
Yes, I did.
And, as it turns out, our first
contestant, mawena cujo,
has traveled a great distance
himself.
Where are you from, mawena?
I'm from Togo, west Africa.
Really.
Well, this doesn't seem
convenient.
Yes.
What are you planning on
singing today?
Um, trying to sing
rascal flatts.
Rascal flatts.
Yes.
So you're a country guy.
Yes, I'm a country guy.
I've been singing since I was a
little boy my voice is low and high
I can do any kind of
voice I want to.
I can go...
Any kind of voice I want.
Last year I watched American idol
and I really loved "skatti macrri"
and I told my family
he should be the winner.
And he won it.
There's no doubt about it
I'm the next American idol.
Well, have fun.
Is this our next country
superstar right here?
Hello.
Yo.
How are you?
Good.
What's been going down, man?
Comment ca va?
Comment ca va? Good.
What's your name?
My name is mawena cujo.
Oh, okay.
Tell us a little bit about
yourself.
What do you want to do?
I just want to get my ticket,
man.
You just want to get
the ticket.
Yeah.
I'm gonna blow you away anyway.
I like that.
I like that confidence,
Jennifer.
What are you gonna sing?
Mm, rascal flatts'
i won't let go.
Rascal flatts.
Oh, you like country music.
Yes.
Okay, cool.
Wow. Okay.
♪ You think you're lost ♪
♪ but you're not lost ♪
♪ on your own ♪
♪ you're not alone ♪
♪ I will stand by you ♪
♪ I will help you through ♪
♪ when you've done ♪
♪ all you can do ♪
♪ and you can't cope ♪
♪ I will hold you tight ♪
♪ and I won't let go ♪
♪ go ♪
Yeah, don't let her go.
She's-Jennifer's a good one.
Don't let her go.
She's so pretty.
Thank you, baby.
Wow, mawena, you got
the confidence, man.
But you ain't got the song.
Your pitch is way off to say
the least.
Oh, foul.
But you threw the ball, so, I mean,
I got to give you credit.
[Laughs] He threw the ball.
You know, it was just a
little bit all over the place.
Dude.
Dude, it was really terrible.
Bad.
I can prove you wrong.
You should go out, find some
people, and say, "Randy's wrong.
Randy says that I was terrible
and I'm not a good singer."
Go. I'll give you a shot.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
All right, mawena.
Come back with some people.
Prove me wrong, dawg.
As the auditions carry on... both: Hi.
Hi. Good morning.
Mawena and I pound the
pavement to see if he can prove
Randy wrong.
♪ Like a storm ♪
♪ that cuts your path ♪
♪ breaks your will ♪
He's auditioning for
American idol.
Well, good.
So... he looks like the right guy.
Well, the question is, does
he sound like the right guy?
♪ Think you're lost ♪
♪ but you're not lost ♪
♪ on your own ♪
Okay, hold it right there.
What'd you think, girls?
He was good.
He was good?
Would you argue with the
judges to put him through to
Hollywood?
Yo, you back, man.
Mawena, you came back.
You're bringing kids?
A whole family?
We were out on the street...
Oh, look who showed up.
Trying to find some people
that liked mawena here.
Ryan, you love this guy?
I was out there just
facilitating this for them.
My job is to host, not judge.
But I present you...
You guys heard him sing?
He was great.
You guys think he should be
on American idol?
Have you seen American idol?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, look.
We want him to go to
Hollywood.
Girls, you want him to go
too?
Yes.
Why?
Based on his voice or that he's
a nice guy?
Both.
His voice.
Mawena, nice guy... yeah.
It's still a no.
Sorry, man.
All right.
Both: We tried.
Kids, work on your ears
a little bit.
Get mommy to wash the wax out
of there.
Thank you.
Thank you, Merlin.
Thank you, mawena.
Still no good.
Randy said it's still the same.
What happened, you guys?
You froze up in there.
You froze up.
I did?
I'm not gonna give up.
I'm gonna prove them wrong
next year.
I'm gonna be the first...
African country music superstar.
Thank you.
The judges haven't quite
found what they're looking for
yet today.
But perhaps that's about to
change.
Wait, I want to think what I
want to say.
I want to sound good.
My name is Ashlee altise.
I'm 28 years old, and I'm
a sales associate.
Are you excited today?
I am overwhelmed.
Yeah?
I've been joy-hopping all day
since I've been here.
Joy-hopping?
That's my dance when I'm
excited.
I have been at the joy hop just
from being joyous and happy.
Go, girl.
That's it.
And what are you gonna bring
into the room today?
What will the judges see?
Why will they put you through?
Funk.
Energy.
Confidence.
Where I go? Where I go?
Where I go?
Can I outdance j-lo?
I'll give her a run for her
money.
Hey, baby.
Come on in her baby.
Come on, get this, baby.
Get this. Aw, yeah.
Look, dawg, she getting this.
♪ Gitchy-gitchy-gooey ♪
♪ ya-ya ♪
Get it, get it, get it, baby.
Have y'all heard-seen my
new dance that I made up?
Yeah, do it.
Let's see it. Let's see it.
Well, what it is, is it's a
dance that I came up with when
you're happy, overwhelmed,
excited.
Right.
Or joyous.
And you just...
That's the joy hop?
Then you just take your arms
and you swing.
Yeah, work 'em, work 'em.
Right, right, right.
Okay, she's mine, she's mine.
What's your name?
My name is Ashlee altise.
Y'all ready for me?
We are so ready for you.
♪ Here come old flat top ♪
♪ he come groovin' up slowly ♪
♪ he's got juju eyeballs ♪
♪ he one holy roller ♪
♪ he's got hair down ♪
♪ to his knee LA ♪
♪ got to be a joker ♪
♪ he just do what he please ♪
She's a performer up there.
That's right.
I like you.
Thank you.
I like it.
I like the whole package.
You got fire and spirit and
spunk and your voice.
A little bit crazy.
Yeah.
The right kind of crazy, though.
That's right.
We like a little bit of
crazy, yeah.
So I'm gonna say yes.
Thank you so much.
I'm gonna say yes too, man.
I'm gonna say yes too.
You're going to Hollywood!
Both: Joy-hop! Joy-hop!
To Hollywood.
Joy-hop!
Did you get all that?
Joy-hopping all the way out
of here.
It's a dance that the world's
gonna soon figure out about.
But this joy wasn't gonna
last forever.
When we come back...
Get that camera out of my face.
The hunt for the golden
tickets is off target.
It's just [Bleep].
What?
But Savannah declares open
season on Mr. Tyler.
Both: Steven! Steven!
It'll probably be very hard
for me to control myself.
It's an audition you don't want
to miss.
What's going on?
Day two auditions are in
full swing deep in the South.
And, while many contestants
continue making memories to last
a lifetime, most of the talent this
morning has been more underdeveloped.
That was a rough audition,
baby.
You didn't nail it this time.
No.
It needs to cook in the oven
a little bit longer.
It's a tough room today.
Nope.
It was everything I wanted,
but I'll come back next year.
Not this time.
Are you... no, I'm not hiding-
yeah, no, we're serious.
They said that it wasn't even
really singing.
I'm telling you, dude, you're
gonna get eaten alive.
I hear your voice, man,
but I'm not sure if you're ready
to be an American idol.
Sorry, buddy, you still got a lot
of good news here with the family.
That's right, I got a baby
on the way.
I'm w.T. Thompson.
I'm currently unemployed.
I'm from appomattox.
I'm 25 years old.
Appomattox is one of those
towns, if you drive too fast
and you blink, you might just
pass it.
I worked for a federal prison,
and I had to quit my job for
a chance at American idol.
They were gonna give me the time
originally, and then they
couldn't do it.
I had to make the decision
either a job or a dream, and I
chose the dream.
Laura, my wife, is pregnant right
now, and she's 61/2 months.
It's a dream, you know.
You make it or you don't.
♪ I feel no shame ♪
♪ I'm proud ♪
♪ of where I came from ♪
♪ I was born and raised ♪
♪ in the boondocks ♪
♪ one thing I know ♪
♪ no matter ♪
But he said that you
encouraged him.
You supported him.
I did.
What did you say to him?
Um, he's just never gonna get
this opportunity again.
I mean, once we have children,
you can't just quit a job, so.
He's got a short amount of time
to make something happen.
I was gonna say, how much
time does he have?
Short amount of time.
♪ Water running ♪
♪ through my veins ♪
♪ and I can hear ♪
♪ that lullaby ♪
♪ of the midnight train ♪
All right, cool.
What do you think, Stevie?
You know what, I hear your voice,
man, but I'm not sure if
you're ready to be an American
idol.
Just gonna tell you Frank.
I think I got it, man.
You do?
Yes, sir.
I don't know.
He got a little twinkle in his eye.
Voice is good.
It could use a little-a little
work, but it's there.
I'll do it.
And I think it's there to be
worked with.
I don't know.
I think-I'm gonna take a chance
on him.
I'm gonna give him a yes.
So, Steven, you say no?
And he got a baby coming.
Jennifer says yes.
Right, Stevie?
Yes.
That's the score thus far.
But I'm telling you, dude,
you're gonna get eaten alive.
I promise I'll make you
proud.
Sorry, brother.
You still got a lot of good news
here with the family, you know.
That's right.
I got a baby on the way.
So w.T.'S dream survives
the cut.
We'll catch up with him again
in Hollywood.
He had a good voice.
And the things that weren't
right about his voice can be
fixed.
You know, singing the song
in front of the judges is
tougher than anybody thinks.
It's a whole lot different when
you're standing in front of 'em
and actually looking at 'em eye
to eye, you know.
But, you know what, I did it, and
now I'm going to Hollywood.
Hollywood!
More from Savannah coming
up after the break.
Stay where you are.
I like it here.
Coming up... calm down, mama.
The girls go gaga for Steven.
And one takes it to a new
level.
Steven Tyler is my future
ex-husband.
Plus our last contestants of
the day send sparks through
the judging room.
It's like you have
electricity going through your body.
You know, each year our
contestants show up with one
thing in mind, and that is to
get a golden ticket.
This year in Savannah, it seems
like they want to get a little
Steven Tyler too.
Calm down, mama.
I am so excited to meet
Steven Tyler.
All: We love you!
I love you more.
He's kind of cute for
an older guy.
He is a hottie.
Does my [Bleep] look good?
Call me.
I'm on fire, right, baby?
Fire.
He's hot, he's sensitive...
I'm here to tell you that I am...Moist.
What is going on with this
program again, dude?
And his... go ahead. Ten-inch record.
What was her name?
There's no doubt Steven is
loved by all the ladies.
I got to kiss Steven Tyler.
No matter what age.
Grandma.
Grandma, she's going to
Hollywood.
But perhaps nobody was as fully
committed as Erica novak
from buffalo, New York.
Steven Tyler is my future
ex-husband.
He just doesn't know it yet.
I think he's smoking hot.
When I walk in the room and see
Steven Tyler, it'll probably
be very hard for me to control
myself.
But, if allowed, I would kiss his feet
or anything else for that matter.
I mean, I might go out when
security comes, but who cares?
I'll get to say I kissed
Steven Tyler.
Ha.
I want to cry before I even
audition.
No, baby.
My future ex-husband.
Mr. Steven Tyler.
Ex-husband.
You know what, I think you guys
should have a hug before you sing.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, just-just have a hug.
Hell with the golden ticket,
just give me a [Bleep] hug.
Come on.
No, I like their little
rapport.
I like that she stays there.
Hands will remain at my
sides, I swear.
Okay.
Really?
If I get any closer, I'll be
on the other side of you.
Wow. What's going on?
Hey! Hey!
Hey.
You better sing good.
All right, I'm ready to go
home.
Nice to see yous all.
Thank you. Good night.
All right.
All right, so what are we
singing?
Super duper love by
joss stone.
Super duper love.
Do it.
♪ All the time I knew ♪
♪ that you loved me ♪
♪ because you were ♪
♪ always there ♪
♪ could I be that mistaken ♪
♪ believing that you ♪
♪ really care ♪
♪ in the presence ♪
♪ of all my friends ♪
Best note you hit was when
you grabbed my [Bleep], you know
that.
'Cause that was whoo-ee!
Well, um... don't be jealous.
I'm not jealous.
Don't be jealous.
I am not jealous.
Go up and give her a hug
then.
Come on now.
No, you should come to me.
Oh, see.
Don't gotta ask me twice.
You need a road map to grab
his [Bleep].
Ow, my wife-wifey, I love you.
I might not have got a golden
ticket, but I got some of
Steven Tyler in these hands.
I can't ask for more than that.
By the way, he has an amazing
behind.
You know, last season, every
now and then, Randy and Steven
were a little liberal with
pretty girls in the room.
However, now it's a brand-new
season.
And whatever will they do with
nba dancer Brittany kerr?
You're welcome.
Hi.
How are you?
Good. How are ya?
Good.
Very good. What's your name?
I'm Brittany.
I say yes.
All right, so what are you
gonna sing for us?
I'm gonna sing spoiled
by joss stone.
Okay.
Go for it.
All right.
♪ I kind of thought ♪
♪ that I'd be better ♪
♪ all by myself ♪
♪ but I've never been ♪
♪ so wrong before ♪
♪ you made it impossible ♪
♪ for me to ever love ♪
♪ somebody else ♪
♪ and now I don't know ♪
♪ what I left you for ♪
Great.
That-that did it for me.
I like that.
She's adorable.
That was amazing.
Come on now.
You want to hear more?
No.
What do you think?
I think that's good.
I liked it.
I liked your melody, you're on
pitch, and you're good-looking,
and just got to push it out a
little bit more, you know what
I'm saying.
All right.
Make her sing a note.
Help her get it out.
Help her get it out?
You know what I mean?
You help her get it out.
Tell her she's got it.
You're good at that.
You listen to some old blues,
and listen to the words, and,
when it comes time to sing
it, project like that.
Okay.
Well, let's take a vote.
I'm gonna say yes.
I think there's something there
I think she can develop.
Jennifer?
I'm gonna say no this time.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Uh, what do you think,
Stevie?
Yes or no?
I say yes.
Looks like you're going to
Hollywood.
Yeah, girl.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Thanks, y'all.
Brittany kerr.
I actually thought she had
a pretty voice.
It just wasn't strong enough.
I think she's not gonna survive
for a week.
She might if someone shows
her what to sing.
We'll see whose prediction
proves to be correct when we
catch up with Brittany in
Hollywood.
Coming up, one last contestant.
I got a funny feeling about
this.
With a surprise performance
everyone will be talking about.
Wow.
Very nice.
Last one of the day in Savannah,
Georgia.
Welcome back to Savannah.
We are nearing the end of our
visit here, and, from
the thousands who auditioned, the judges
have discovered some new standouts.
♪ Clouds are shrouding us ♪
♪ in moments unforgettable ♪
♪ you twist to fit ♪
♪ the mold that I am in ♪
Nice.
♪ Your mother scolded us ♪
♪ she said that we were bad ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ I would go through ♪
♪ all this pain ♪
♪ take a bullet ♪
♪ straight through my brain ♪
♪ yes, I would die ♪
♪ for you, baby ♪
♪ but you won't do the same ♪
Nice. Beautiful.
♪ You may fool me ♪
♪ and I'll fall ♪
♪ but I won't ♪
♪ stay down long ♪
♪ 'cause I'm country strong ♪
Goosies.
Holy crap, I'm going to
Hollywood.
But before we close up shop,
let's meet a guy with a name
you won't soon forget.
I'm Phillip Phillips.
I'm 20 years old, and I'm from
leesburg, Georgia.
Yes, that is my real name.
I work at my father's pawn shop.
It's really exciting, and
sometimes it's scary.
But you never know what'll come
through the door.
My dad is really proud of me
for doing what I do in music,
and he supports me 110%.
To see him succeed, you can't
even put words on it.
Because it makes especially a
parent feel so proud, I mean,
you swell up as a man.
You just swell up and you so
proud that, ooh, it just makes
you want to just bust.
American idol will change his
life, because this is what he loves.
I know this is my chance and my
opportunity to show the world
what I have, and I can't let it
slip out of my hands.
I think you're ready.
Born naked and ready.
They just put clothes on me is
all.
And, in this moment, I'm glad
you did.
Come on, Phillip.
Phillip Phillips.
Last one of the day.
Representing.
I got a funny feeling about
this.
Hey.
How are ya?
Doing good.
How about y'all?
So you're here with your family,
or you came up by yourself?
I'm here with my parents.
They're excited about it.
My mom's so excited.
She wants-she's been waiting to
meet Ryan seacrest.
Oh, no! Really?
I've got to tell you, I've
watched it every year since
you've been on, and you are
more handsome every year.
Not as handsome as my husband,
but you are close. Close.
Thank you. You're sweet.
Thank you.
All right, well, what are
you gonna sing?
My version of superstition
by Stevie wonder.
Okay, let's hear it.
All right.
This is the final one of
the day, man.
You the last one in in Savannah.
Show you-show what I can do.
Represent the South.
Last one, dude.
Tie it up with a pretty bow.
♪ I'm very superstitious ♪
♪ oh, no, yeah ♪
♪ the writing's on the wall ♪
♪ oh, yeah ♪
♪ I'm very superstitious ♪
♪ oh, all them ladders ♪
♪ 'bout to fall ♪
♪ no, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ the 13-month-old baby, yeah ♪
♪ broke the looking glass ♪
♪ the seven years of bad luck ♪
♪ all them good things ♪
♪ in your past ♪
♪ but when you believe ♪
♪ in things ♪
♪ that you don't understand ♪
♪ and then you suffer ♪
♪ superstition ain't the way ♪
Wow.
Over the top.
It's like you have
electricity going through your
body or something.
Grab the guitar, man.
Let's see this.
Come on.
Yeah, man.
Play us a little guitar.
♪ It's close to midnight ♪
♪ something evil lurking ♪
♪ in the dark ♪
I like when you get those
feet going.
♪ Under the moonlight ♪
♪ you see a sight ♪
♪ that almost stops your heart ♪
♪ you start to scream ♪
He's like a little James brown.
♪ Terror takes the sound ♪
♪ before you make it ♪
♪ you start to freeze ♪
♪ as horror looks you ♪
♪ right between the eyes ♪
♪ you're out of time ♪
♪ 'cause this is thriller ♪
♪ thriller night ♪
♪ no one is gonna save you ♪
♪ from the beast ♪
♪ with 40 eyes ♪
♪ thriller ♪
♪ whoo, thriller night ♪
♪ you're fighting ♪
♪ for your life ♪
♪ inside a killer thriller ♪
♪ yeah, chiller thriller ♪
♪ night ♪
Nice.
Very, very nice.
Very nice.
Last one of the day in Savannah,
Georgia.
Very nice. Very nice.
Like I was trying to say
before, it's like you have
electricity going through your
body.
Yeah, I just love it.
It's super special.
Thank you.
I like what I heard.
I think everybody else is gonna
love it too.
Amazing, man.
I mean, I love it.
I mean, true artist.
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
Let's take a vote, guys.
Let's see, what do we think?
Is he going to Hollywood or not,
Steven Tyler?
Casey with a lightning rod.
You're going to Hollywood.
To me.
Hello.
Uh, Jennifer?
Is he going to Hollywood?
We get a vote too.
Okay.
Jennifer?
I just think you're really,
really special, you know.
It's just not something you see
every day, which is what an
artist is.
It's something that is new and
fresh and makes you just-
everybody stop and stare.
And that's who you are.
That's what you are.
It's a yes for me.
It's a yes for me too, man.
I love it.
I really, really do.
So welcome to Hollywood,
Phillip Phillips Jr.!
Yes!
Thank you so much.
Good job, baby.
What a way to cap the day
off.
That guy was amazing.
Let the games begin.
Good to see you.
Thank you very much.
Phillip Phillips, season 11,
American idol right here, baby.
I just want people to see
what I seen all his life and
what kind of man and what kind
of musician and singer he is
and just share with the world.
Phillip Phillips caps off a
successful first visit here
in Savannah with 42 singers getting that
coveted golden ticket to Hollywood.
Welcome to Hollywood!
I'm gonna say yes.
Guess what?
You're going to Hollywood!
Thanks.
Yes!
Hello Hollywood, baby.
A good day in Savannah, guys.
Yup.
We came, we won, we saw, we
are.
What?
Yeah!
All: Hollywood! Hollywood!
Hollywood!
See you in the next city.
That is...
Wraps up.
Both: A wrap.
Savannah, end, over, done.
Out.
Crispy, fried.
It's a wrap.
Bric-a-bric-a, firecracker,
siss-boom-ba.
Good night, America.
Ryan seacrest, Ryan seacrest,
ra-ra-ra.
Tomorrow night, we head for...
Pittsburgh!
As the city of champions
share their true colors.
I love it.
So did you make it?
All: Yes!
We dig deep.
Got to be a singer.
It's my dream.
And shake it up...
I love it.
As more outstanding talent...
You're going to Hollywood!
Yes, Hollywood! Hollywood!
Takes us all by surprise.
Yay!
He is the next American idol.
But it's a rough ride getting
there.
This is a national disaster.
Would steel town bend under
the pressure?
Scared makes you do things
that you wouldn't normally do.
Sync by GriotsTeam
for addic7ed.com