Hundreds of thousands
auditioned...
American idol, here we come.
I'm ready to chase my dream.
For most, the idol dream
came crashing down.
Never stop
believing in yourself.
I didn't make it.
This was my last shot.
But for a lucky few,
the journey has just begun.
You're going to Hollywood!
Tonight, we raise the stakes.
Leave nothing to chance.
This is it.
Unstoppable drama...
-I'm so far from being done.
-Incredible talent...
I like that feeling.
And unbelievable passion.
Season 11 is my year.
Get ready for the one,
the only Hollywood week.
This is American Idol.
Sarah?
Rise and shine, baby.
You're going to hollywood.
Yeah.
Shannon.
-My god, is it time?
-It's the day, the big day.
Across the country, 302 of
the nation's elite are packing
their bags and leaving home
for a chance at a new life.
You've got a long journey.
Make us proud,
make us proud.
This marks the departure from
everything they've ever known.
I don't know
what to expect,
but I know
that hollywood
is the place
where dreams come true.
But that dream
is a long way off,
because this week
is no vacation.
Ladies and gentlemen,
at this time,
please discontinue use
of any portable electronics.
Make sure those are turned
completely off.
Let's go!
As they arrive in Los Angeles
the future looks bright.
Say hi to Hollywood!
It kind of feels
like a dream.
It doesn't really seem
completely real right now.
It feels good to be out
of the pawn shop.
I'm so excited.
It's my first time
in California,
so I'm ready to perform.
Today, half the contestants
will take the stage,
so for them, it's do or die.
I'm so excited right now.
Actually, I'm really scared.
As they arrive at the theater,
the anxiety is escalating.
I'm come up this aisle.
It means a lot to be here,
so I really hope I do well.
The judges arrive
and share some words of wisdom.
What makes the dawn rise
with thunder?
What makes the sphinx
the seventh wonder?
Courage!
What makes the hottentot
so hot?
Who put the ape
in apricot?
What do they got
that I ain't got?
Courage!
Don't let the nerves
get to you.
I love you guys.
I hope you do great.
Season 11 is on!
So the judges have given
their pep talk.
They've settled in.
Hollywood week, season 11.
Another chapter
begins right now.
This round will work just like
it has in the past.
Contestants will come out
in groups of ten.
They'll sing
a cappella a song
of their choosing
and receive no feedback.
Even though it's similar
to years past
nothing can prepare
them for sudden death.
Half of them
will go home today.
And that harsh reality
sets in
for the first group
to take the stage,
including two guys with
two very memorable auditions.
Johnny keyser blew the judges
away back in st. Louis.
But I'm afraid to die
What do you do
right now?
I work
at an italian restaurant.
Keep singing.
I don't know
What's out there, yeah
You know you're gonna
be a star, right?
Keep singing!
While heejun got off to a
shakier start in Pittsburgh.
That should be
the chorus.
But jennifer fell hard
for his voice.
I love you!
Here in hollywood,
the two could not
be more different.
Very, very, very nervous.
Nothing but confidence
right now.
I'm not nervous.
I'm excited.
I just want
to get it over with.
Hit those marks for me,
you guys.
Good luck.
First up is johnny.
I'm ready.
My name is Johnny Keyser.
I'm from ft. Lauderdale,
Florida.
I'm gonna be singing dreamin'
by Amos Lee.
My soul
Is as open as the sky
Oftentimes it's just as blue
sometimes
it's full of glory
And but mostly, yeah
It's for the love
and it's the love
Nice.
It's the love
-Johnny!
-Amen, amen, amen.
-It's the love.
-Amen.
Johnny appears confident,
which only raises
the stakes for Heejun.
I've never heard
anyone sing
Like that before,
and I realized
The person who's going
before me
was the guy Jennifer Lopez fell
in love with, so I'm like,
"what do I do now,"
you know?
Shake it out, shake it out.
Yes, shak out, puppy.
For Heejun, confidence has
never been his strong suit.
So my mom decided
to help me with packing.
Maybe I should just tell her
this is not gonna be that long.
Great, so I just checked in
in Hollywood,
and I feel nervous
because I got here
and everyone's so tall,
so pretty.
Season 11!
Even the guys are so pretty.
I don't know why.
I don't know
what they eat,
but they're so good
looking
and I just have
to figure out
how to overcome
the beauty.
Hi, my name is Heejun.
I'm 22 years old.
I'm from New York.
you got it, baby.
Tell me how am I
Supposed to live
without you
Now that I've been
loving you so long?
I love him.
How am I supposed
to live without you?
to carry on
When all that I've been
living for...
Is gone
Yeah, okay, all right.
Yeah, you think?
Whoo!
Lord have mercy.
-Brought tears to my eyes.
-Yeah.
Now, once each group
has a chance to perform,
the judges will deliberate.
They'll go one by one,
talking about each contestant,
and then give them
the results right away.
Remember, half of all
the contestants performing today
have to go home.
With 304 talented competitors
in Hollywood,
will Heejun
and Johnny make the cut?
I have a "maybe," so,
we can go one more.
Yeah.
I had no, man.
He has nos
on both of those.
He's a no for me.
I didn't even recognize
the song.
He has a yes,
and you have a yes.
I have a yes.
two yeses.
-Okay, we've got it.
-Okay.
Gabi, please step forward.
Johnny, please step forward.
Heejun, please step forward.
Front row, congratulations.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Congratulations.
So heejun and johnny live to
see another day in hollywood.
I thought everyone's too
pretty for me,
but guess who's
really pretty now?
And as the morning progresses
in the theater,
it's the beautiful voices
that are wowing
the judges,
like charleston's Elise testone.
Well, it's a crazy world
we're livin' in
and I just can't see
that half of us
immersed in sin
is all we have to give these
futures made of
Why else do I want you
Like I do texas native
baylie brown.
if I'm not in love
with you
<iWwhy in dreams
do I surrender
like a little baby
Let her go.
Pittsburgh audition Hallie Day
also delivered the goods.
Before the day I met you
My life was so unkind
But you're the key
to my peace of mind
'Cause you make me feel
You make me feel
you...
Thank you.
-So, that's great.
-Congratulations.
You guys are all through.
Thank you.
You made it.
it was an easy yes
for all three ladies...
So hollywood week
is looking golden.
After the break, the best
singers of season 11 stake
their claim to becoming
the next American idol...
As new stars rise...
Wait, don't stop,
don't stop!
And old favorites fall.
Sorry, you've got
to stand out.
I didn't think about losing,
And it hurts.
They're dropping like flies.
And as the tension mounts,
the results will be shocking.
I want to see some yelling,
some freaking out.
They done kicked me off
the stage.
Holy.
Welcome back to Idol.
You know, this week is filled
with stress and anxiety...
A true roller coaster
of emotions,
And the nerve center
is right here in the wings,
Backstage,
as the contestants
wait to walk out
and make their mark
In front of the judges.
My hands are sweating,
heart's beating.
I'm just ready to go in
and go ahead and do it.
J.Lo, Steven Tyler, and
Randy are all out there.
My gosh.
Anxiety didn't seem
to be an a issue
for 25-year-old Jen Hirsh,
Who first impressed
the judges Galveston.
I think you have a really
nice sounding voice.
I like where you went
with it.
We've got a pro up
in here at 25.
Thank you.
Now in hollywood,
she is feeling the pressure.
I'm a little nervous,
doing this process.
Everybody hit your marks.
Important.
Today, my game plan is going
to be not to fidget,
Feel like I do
that all the time.
I've watched videos of myself.
I'm, like, touching my hair
and everyth...
I did it again.
Try not to fidget, guys.
I'm Jen Hirsh.
I'm from Agoura Hills,
California
and I'm gonna sing
"Up to the mountain"
by Patty Griffin.
I went up to the mountain
because you asked me
to up over the clouds
to where the sky was blue
Sometimes I look down
Afraid
Afraid I will fall
Then I hear your sweet voice
Come on.
All right now.
-Wait, don't stop.
-All right, Agoura.
Come and then go
Just for you.
Thank you.
That was beautiful.
Jen seems to have
conquered her nerves.
Now she must wait patiently
as her entire line performs
before Hearing the results.
But st. Louis stand-out
Lauren Gray is not quite ready
to give up the spotlight.
You'll never know
if you never try
to forget your past
and simply be mine
so I dare you to let me be
Your one and only
I promise I...
-All right.
-Sorry.
Sorry.
-Thank you.
No, thank you.
Yep.
Nice.
Finally, the judges can take
a moment to deliberate.
Okay, the first one
we have was a little yes.
No, no, two nos.
Three nos, yeah.
I had a maybe,
so that's a no.
I loved her tone,
and she totally screwed up.
Jen Hirsh and Lauren,
congratulations,
you guys are going through.
Thank you.
So Lauren and Jen now
have reason to celebrate,
but for many other girls,
the first day of hollywood
is off to a rough start.
So let me go crazy on you
Let me go crazy on you
Should I give up
or should I just
Keep chasin' pavement
Thank you.
You have my heart
now I want it back
I'm starting to see
everything you lack
I started that a key too high.
A little bit too high.
Is my mic on?
I have never had my heart
Beat this much for so long.
is there any way
I could stay...
Just do the chorus again,
Lower?
can I sing a little bit more?
Please?
There's a lot of dynamics to it.
I just don't feel like I've
Shown you everything.
Just a little bit, please?
A tiny, tiny bit?
Pretty please?
I think we're good,
though, I mean, you know.
Just a tiny, please?
I won't disappoint you.
Okay, one note.
There you go.
-That wasn't one, but okay.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Is that... Are we sure
we're done with that?
After the break, two of our
Most electric performers
from the auditions will fight
for their spot
in the next round.
I've been on stage
since two years old.
It's like home.
I can't believe
I'm here at all.
I want this very badly.
And as the competition
heats up,
only the best will survive.
Sorry, it's the end of the line.
My gosh.
Welcome back to Idol.
It's midday
in sunny Los Angeles,
where the brightest voices
in america have converged
For an audition of a lifetime.
Hollywood week begins today.
After a rough patch
of auditions,
Steven takes a trip
backstage to deliver
a much-needed pep talk.
I want to see some snapping,
Some yelling, some freaking out.
I want to see some camaraderie
go astray here.
But will steven's warning
Have an effect
on the next line
To take the stage,
including Phil phillips,
who's a fish out
of water here in LA.?
I've never flown
before on a real plane.
I've flown on
a on a plane before,
but I jumped out,
So I've flown
but never landed.
We're getting ready
to take off,
So I'll see y'all
when we get there.
It's a completely different
world from where I live.
I can't believe
I'm here at all.
I can't even sleep
at night.
I want this very badly.
Back in savannah,
it was phil's
Version of thriller that caught
the judges' eye.
'Cause this is thriller
Thriller night
But without his guitar
on the Hollywood stage,
would he shine as bright?
Come here, sister
now, now, yeah
Papa's in the swing
Yes he is
He ain't too hip
No
about that new breed, babe
he ain't no drag
no, no, no, no
papa's got a brand new bag
-Okay, man.
-Thank you.
As Phillip waits
to hear his fate,
up next is a familiar face
from Pittsburgh.
Unlike Phil, reed grimm has
had a lifetime of experience
in the spotlight.
I've been onstage
since two years old.
It's like home, really.
It's just where I live.
I'm gonna be singing
"I got a golden ticket"
from Willy Wonka
and the chocolate factory.
Come on now.
I've got a golden ticket
I've got a golden sun up
in the sky
Well, I never thought
I'd see the day
when I could face the world
and say good morning
hey, well, then look
at that sun
I got a golden ticket
and so does every one
of us what?
Reed gets an overwhelming
Response from the crowd,
with only puts more
pressure on
Travis orlando,
who's next in line.
Just last year,
travis missed the mark
and was sent home
from Hollywood
right after round one.
Tonight, travis not only has
More to prove to himself,
he has more at stake
if he goes home
Empty-handed.
My mom walked out.
She found
another relationship
That she obviously loved more
Than her family
and my mom
Broke my dad's heart.
At the end of the day,
all we have is each other.
I love you, dad.
I've thought a lot about
the mistakes
I've made on the show
Last year and I know what to
look out for this year.
I know what the judges
are expecting out of me.
You know,
I've been practicing
Enough in here
and long enough.
I'm gonna prove the judges
wrong this time.
Season 11 is my year.
You've made my soul
a burning fire
you're getting to be
my one desire
You're getting to be
all that matters to me
and let me tell you, girl
I hoped pray
each day I live
a little more love
I have to give
all I do
-Thank you.
Phillip, we're gonna
see you tomorrow.
Thank you.
And Reed, you're staying too.
Travis, I'm sorry, baby.
Not this year.
Reed and Phillip move on to
the next round, but for travis,
Saying good-bye is more than
Just another year
of shattered dreams.
It's about starting over.
I have to go back to nothing,
To nothing at all.
It's kind of hard to face
That now.
I didn't think
about losing,
and it hurts a lot, man.
And as day one winds down,
It's not just travis that
we say Good-bye to.
Among those going home,
Ramiro Garcia,
whose story inspired
in Galveston.
Tamiro, I'm sorry.
It's the end of the line.
I'm still going
after my dream.
It's not the end of the road
for me.
My best days
are still to come,
And and I'm good.
We got booted off!
And mechanic Wolf Hamlin.
You either go big or go home.
Today, I'm going home.
And even though jenni schick
got a whole lot of love back in
Aspen...
I'm sorry, you're going home.
It was the cold shoulder she
Received in hollywood.
All in all, 69 people departed
The Idol stage
by the end of day one.
Coming up, the daughter
of a living legend
gets her mom on the spotlight.
I'm Jane Carrey.
A young father chases
his own dream of stardom.
It just kind of hit me
that I'm gonna be away
from my daughter
for the first time.
Take nothing for granted...
Front row, it's
the end of the line.
Because this
is hollywood week.
It's day two here
in Hollywood,
which means the second half
of contestants get
To take their shot
at the ultimate dream job.
it's gonna be a fun day.
I'm really excited.
A little nutrition, you know?
It's gonna be a long day.
The judges arrive,
poised and positive.
-How are you?
-it's a beautiful day.
-Hollywood week.
-Another day, another dollar,
Another man to give out
a Holler.
But that's a stark contrast
to the mood inside the holding Ro.
Everybody is here,
waiting anxiously.
But adam brock
is staying upbeat.
They're dropping like flies,
but not me.
I'm flapping my wings still.
Adam breezed through his
Audition in Pittsburgh
with his deep, soulful voice.
I have been told that there's
a large black woman trapped
inside of my body.
Everything I had
is gone stormy weather
One of my favorite albums
is all times
is Walking In Memphis,
Marc Cohn,
and when you started singing,
it reminded me
of that a little bit.
But adam's golden ticket
didn't come without a price.
It just kind of hit me
That I'm gonna be away
from my daughter
for the first time
For multiple days
You're gonna be good
for mom, okay?
In one breath, it's hopeful that
I get to stay in Hollywood for
As long as possible, but there's
This little part of me that's
Gonna miss her every minute
that I'm gone.
Can he rise above the emotions
for today's performance?
I am singing my song...
I guess the catalyst was because
Jennifer asked me to sing this
song at the auditions.
-I did?
-You did.
Good.
So here's "Walking in Memphis".
Come on.
There'll be catfish
on the table
and gospel music in the air
And reverend Green
will be glad to see you
if you haven't
got a prayer
You've got a prayer
in memphis
-Beautiful, baby.
-Thank you.
-Nice.
Next up is Jane Carrey,
who first met the judges
on the U.S.S. Midway
in san diego.
Does father know
you're here?
Father does know
I'm here.
-Who's father?
-My dad is Jim Carrey.
Everyone growing up has kind
of their issue with identity
and trying
to find themselves.
It is difficult, kind of,
Growing up in the shadow
of something
and trying to find
Your place in the world
underneath this huge shadow.
And after making it
to Hollywood,
Jane Settled in
for a long stay.
Well, my expectations of this
week are that I'm going to stay
Here.
I will be here
the entire week.
So get used to me.
doo doo doo
lookin' out my back door
just got home from illinois
locked the front door Boy
got to sit down
take a rest on the porch
imagination sets in
pretty soon I'm singin'
doo doo doo
lookin' out my back door
-Hi.
Now for the hard part,
as the jues make some crucial cuts.
I had a yes.
I had a no.
No.
It's too bad, too.
-Yes.
-Yes?
Let me have, let me have
Joe step forward.
Let me have jane step forward.
Back row,
see you tomorrow.
You're on to the next round.
Front row, it's the end
of the line.
Thank you.
So adam is in, but we say
good-bye to Jane Carrey.
I freaked out when I was
There and so I was really,
Really shaky, and I know I can
Do way better than that,
and so I'm really disappointed
with myself.
With the disappointment
hanging heavily,
Jane reaches out to
the one person who knows
Exactly what she's going
through.
I talked to my dad,
and he was kind of comforting.
He said, "look, you know,
I've been said no to bunch
of times," and it worked
out well for him in the end,
so hopefully I have a shot.
As Jane leaves
the competition,
Adam brock gets
to share the good news
with his family.
So, I'm not...
Gonna be coming
home tonight.
We knew it.
It's huge and it's cool
to think that one day, Whitney.
Will talk about the things
that I've done.
It's just cool.
After this, three
captivating voices
from the road
take center stage.
And as the competition
intensifies...
None of you should
ever have to beg.
Can I sing another song?
Three votes.
Please, please.
One simple misstep...
Give me one more chance.
Will cost someone...
Everything.
Welcome back
to Hollywood week,
where over the past two
elimination days,
we've learned
that some take the bad news
in stride...
I'm sorry, you guys
didn't make it.
But others just couldn't
take no for an answer.
Please, please.
Please, please, please, please,
It's just not my vote.
-Whose vote is it?
-There's three votes.
I just don't think you
brought it today.
Hello.
Can I sing another song?
Can I get one more chance,
Please?
Give me one more chance.
Let me show you
what I've got.
-it wasn't as good today.
-I can sing my butt off.
None of you should ever have
to be on that stage and beg.
Maybe what our judges can use
Is a new group
with a new attitude,
like the confidence displayed
by 17-year-old David Leathers.
My journey has definitely
been a long one.
And I'm here for one reason.
That's to become american idol.
Hollywood,
are you ready for me?
We first met our resident
Ladies' man in Savannah.
And here in hollywood,
he hasn't
slowed down one bit.
I think I just met my new
boyfriend.
What do you think of the ladies
so far in hollywood?
Amazing.
Almost as amazing
as everybody's singing.
Have you found
any you like?
A couple.
We're not implying anything,
but also in this line
is fellow teenager
and Savannah auditioner
Shannon Magrane...
Hello.
Whose Idol journey
started off as awkward.
How's things in Beantown?
Great, beautiful.
Hot, humid, and happening.
-Absolutely.
-Yeah.
Just like your daughter.
Right.
I am singing "Falling"
by Alicia keys.
I...
never felt this way
how do you give me
so much pleasure
cause me so much pain?
Just when I think
You've taken more
than would a fool
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Next up is David.
-How you guys doing?
-Good, baby.
What's up, man?
You know David
talks a big game.
Let's see if he can step up
and deliver.
I'm David Leathers Jr.
I'm 17, and I'm from Fayetteville,
North Carolina,
And I will be singing
"Because you loved me"
by Celine Dion.
You've been
my inspiration
Ghrough the lies
you were the truth
My world
is a better place
Because of you
You were my strength
when I was weak
Hello.
You were my voice
when I couldn't speak
Lifted me up
when I couldn't reach
You gave me faith
'cause you believed
I'm everything I am
because you loved me
David.
Thank you.
How does that happen?
I have ties that are older
than you are.
You saw it here.
It's a tough act to follow
For portland auditioner
Jessica Phillips,
but her strength and
perseverance has gotten her
and her fiance
through the toughest of times.
Last easter Sunday,
he had a stroke.
When he did wake up,
he didn't know who I was.
I love you.
I do.
My boyfriend angelo
is in LA,
and having his support is
something that I really could
not put a price on.
I feel like I'm standing up on
everybody's shoulders
and I'm just gonna take
and all of their dreams for me
and all of their wishes
and bring that to the stage today.
I used to cry myself
to sleep at night
but that was all
before he came
it's not the same
He fills me up
he gives me love
More love
than I've ever seen
He's all I've got
he's all I've got
in this world
but he's all the man
That I need
-Hello.
-Okay.
She's here.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
Guys, here we go.
Can I have Amelia step forward?
Can I have Jared step forward?
Front line, sorry.
It's the end of the road
for you.
Back line, congratulations,
you're through to the next round.
David, Shannon, and Jessica
all advance in the competition.
You did it, baby.
I love you.
I love you too.
They will be joined by more
familiar faces, including aspen
auditioner Angie Zeiderman
and Nba cheerleader
Brittany Kerr.
Up next is group round.
But not before we have more
Breakthrough performances...
I know this is gonna be good.
as round one of hollywood
heads to a close.
But before the night ends,
one of the most
shocking moments
in Idol history.
She hit her head too.
It's 1:00 p.M. in LA
and as round one continues,
some early standouts
from the Pittsburgh auditions
Are stealing the show,
including mobile DJ Erika Van Pelt.
It's only half past
the point of no return
the tip of the iceberg
the sun before the burn
there you are
Sitting in the garden
clutching my coffee
calling me sugar
you called me sugar
I like that feeling
right there.
Good way to start off
the afternoon.
More of that, more of that.
And they got more of that
with New York's Creighton Fraker...
I've spent
all of my years
believing in you
And I just
can't get no relief
lord
Somebody
can anybody find me
Somebody to love
Nice.
Come on, give it up for him.
As well as music teacher
Aaron marcellus.
Ladies, jennifer,
I will be singing for you.
I know this is gonna be good.
Starting here
starting now
Forever
Thank you.
I told you.
And all three got an easy yes
to the next round.
See you tomorrow.
And those solid performances
only put more pressure on those
About to take the stage.
Take your mark.
Good luck.
Here we go.
Hi, guys.
I'm Lauren Mink.
Lauren shared her story back
in savannah.
What do you do?
I'm the director
for a program for adults
with disabilities.
That's cool.
All the people
in our program,
they're really proud of me,
no matter what.
Obviously I would be missed,
you know,
if things were to go
really well today
and I was here
For a little bit longer,
but they're just excited
that I'm doing
what I love to do
and trying to make
my dream come true.
I'm going to sing
"Alone" by Heart.
the night goes by
so very slow
and I hope
that it won't end, though
Alone
till now
I always got by on my own
I never really cared
until I met you
and now it kills me
to the bone
how do I get you alone?
Okay.
Also making it to hollywood
from the savannah auditions
is our next contestant,
Jeremy Rosado.
How are you guys
doing tonight?
What's up?
You are breathtaking.
My goodness.
-Thanks, man.
-You made my day.
Thank you.
-Thanks, dude.
-Randy, be quiet.
My name is jeremy rosado,
Aka Dirty, as I was nicknamed
by my dog here,
Mr. Randy jackson.
Doity, doity.
A unique profession helped
Jeremy earn his dirty nickname
When he first met the judges.
What do you do?
I am actually a front desk Clerk
at an infectious disease
Doctor's office.
But I'm a complete
germaphobe.
So do you wash your hands
all day long?
And I sanitize, you Know,
the chair, the computer, the phone.
Dude, you are a sicko.
I came to hollywood all
germed up and ready to go.
I'm excited about tonight.
I tell you, I thank you for this
opportunity, truly...
You're welcome.
From my heart.
I'm gonna be singing
Luther Vandross, "Superstar".
My favorite.
Don't you remember
you told me you love me
said you'd be comin' back
This way again, baby
baby, baby
I love you
I really do
-Thank you.
-Thank you, baby.
-You think?
-Goosies.
Hello, hello.
Also hoping to get
the judges' attention
is our next contestant.
My name
is Symone Zaire Black.
I'm 16 years old.
I'm from Rancho Cucamonga,
California,
and I auditioned in San diego.
That girl right
there has got it.
That girl right there.
I could have listened
to the whole song.
My dad is with me
during Hollywood week,
and he is my mentor,
he's a critic,
he brings out
the best in me.
He tells me
what I need to work on.
Go ahead.
You don't have to sing
this loud, but just go.
My dad is definitely
a stage dad,
and he's so supportive.
I love him so much.
I want
to show the judges
that I have
a lot of confidence
and I'm not afraid
to be out there
and be myself
just because I'm 16.
Hello.
hello.
hi.
I will be singing
"sitting on the dock of the bay"
by otis redding, for you guys.
I'm sittin'
in the mornin' sun
I'll be sittin'
when the evening comes
Watching the ships roll in
and I'll watch 'em
roll away again
yeah
I'm sittin' on the dock
of the bay
watchin' the tides
roll away
So why'd you choose
that song?
I wanted to reach
out to a older crowd,
an older audience.
Are you saying
that we're older?
No. No.
Medic, please!
My god.
Oh, man.
-My god.
-She hit her head.
He's coming right now.
Medic, please.
Tomorrow night,
find out what happens to Symone
as the pressur builds.
As we get ready for...
The group nights.