Greetings from
the International Space Station,
the world's largest
orbiting research laboratory.
We're currently flying
250 Miles above the earth.
Below us is the great state of
Texas where over 10,000 people.
Are in line for their
chance at stardom.
So good luck to the auditioners.
Take it away, Ryan.
Thank you very much,
International Space Station.
Right now, we're conducting our
own search for superstars here.
And we have got
high hopes for Houston.
This is American Idol.
Welcome to Texas, everybody.
Houston!
It's our ninth visit here to
the grand old state of Texas,
a place where
stars are discovered,
including our very
first idol, Kelly clarkson.
And when we roll into town,
everybody knows it.
American Idol auditions
are here in the bayou city.
This is the day.
This Texas-sized
crowd is ready to go.
You know, it takes one day
to change the rest of your life.
Pick me!
- And so am I.
- Come on in.
Here we go, Houston.
I just took a picture
with Ryan seacrest.
While Houston
is our headquarters,
just down
the road in galveston,
the judges set up shop.
I am excited,
I'm really excited.
The bar is always raising.
We've been saying, you know,
season 11, a new beginning.
It's still hard for me to
tell somebody they suck.
And our first contestant
of the day is starstruck.
- Yes.
- Who's that?
Steven Tyler.
Right, Steven Tyler?
Yeah, yeah.
See, I know
the judges right away.
Steven Tyler, baby.
- What's your name?
- Phong vu.
- Yeah, fong vu!
So, what's the best part
about today so far?
Um, all the camera
action in my face.
I can see myself.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Can you hear me?
I want to look perfect, I'm...
My name is phong vu,
I'm 25 years old
and I was born and raised
from Houston, Texas.
Today, my spirit
will come alive.
I will make you shock
and wow and, ooh!
Just look like a superstar.
I want to be
the next American Idol.
It feels so good inside to have
something big achievement.
And being born
and raised in America.
And being an American Idol,
it's just so phenomenon.
It's amazing.
God is on my side, I know it.
- Hello, hello.
- Good evening.
- Hey, man, what's your name?
- My name is phong vu.
- Yeah, what are you all about?
- All right, your stance.
I am 25 years old.
What's with the hand here,
phong?
And I'm from Houston, Texas.
This is my powerful movement.
- Right now, for right now.
- That's right.
Yeah.
And I love you, Steven Tyler.
I love you so much,
Jennifer Lopez.
And, Randy Jackson,
I watch your dance show,
I love it so much.
- Thank you, thank you, man.
- Thank you, baby.
So tell us about your voice,
about yourself, where you're
from, all kinds of things.
I love to sing, like,
female pop artist music.
Especially Celine Dion
and yours as well
from Jenny from the block.
- It's in my soul.
- Cool.
That's why I want to bring it.
- Okay, baby, bring it.
- Bring it on. Come on, phong.
Un-break my heart.
Okay.
Don't leave me
in all this pain.
Don't leave me out in the rain.
Bring back those nights.
When I held you "besize" me.
Un-break my heart,
say you'll love me again.
Undo this hurt you caused.
When you walk out the door,
and walked out of my life.
Un-cry these tears.
Dramatic pause.
That I cried so many nights.
Un-break my heart...
Un-break my heart.
My heart.
Thank you, baby.
- You're welcome.
- When you sing,
you hear her, don't you?
Yes, I do.
The energy, the emotion,
the sympathy.
I feel the pain.
It's coming through me.
I want to channel it
back to you.
Toni Braxton,
un-break my heart.
- What is this show?
- Thank you. Thank you, baby.
- Who are we talking about?
- He's sharing.
- You're welcome so much.
- Is this an audition?
It all depends on
how you get it out.
- Look, he's crying.
- Yeah, you know what, listen,
you know, you got the passion.
- Yes.
- But your voice, man.
Your voice is not interpreting
what she's sang.
- Okay.
- You brought Toni here today,
but there wasn't
enough of you in it.
And the melody was missing.
- So for Idol...
- I definitely had more songs
- coming.
- That's okay, sweetie.
- I think we can make a judgment.
- And I want to show you my
iconic moves.
Okay.
That's me. Phong vu.
Thank you, phong vu.
It's not gonna
work this time, but...
Okay. I appreciate it.
Thank you, sweetie.
- What up, brother?
- I didn't make it.
- No?
- No.
- What...
- I performed with all my heart,
all my energy.
He felt it. He felt it.
He had a tear.
God bless him, dude.
- I mean, wow.
- I mean, I was like, oh, my God.
I really thought this is
my year, this is my time.
Your hands are sweaty.
- Sorry.
- I will tell you that.
But thanks.
Nice to meet you, Ryan.
Good luck.
Mama, dad, I tried.
You're a fun person
to be around.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
America, you will
see me next year.
I promise you that.
So it just wasn't
phong vu's time.
But, over the next hour, the
exceptional talent in Houston
proves why
everything is bigger...
And better in Texas.
You're going to Hollywood!
Leading to a whole different
Texas revolution
in the lone star state.
Revolution! Revolution!
- I don't want to fight.
- Then say you're sorry.
- For what?
- She wasn't that good yet.
Are you guys crazy?
Welcome back to Texas, y'all.
Yes, Texas.
The state you don't mess with.
Where the land is rugged,
where the cattle stand tall...
And a man is a man.
They say I'm crazy,
i really don't care,
that's my prerogative.
They say I'm nasty.
Oh, my God.
I'm so excited.
And I just can't hide it.
I know, I know, I know.
I know, I know, I kn-n-now.
I know I want you.
Come on, this is Texas.
Where are the cowboys?
Baby, lock them doors.
And turn the lights down low.
Put some music on.
That's soft and slow.
Baby, we ain't got.
No place to go.
I hope you understand.
You rode that into the sunset.
Let's face it.
We were not going
to find the next Scotty here.
Baby, lock them doors.
And turn the lights down low.
Put some music on.
That's soft and slow.
Okay, this is when things
start happening, and I'm like,
"what's happening?"
The galveston guys
were striking out.
I'm lost.
Maybe a girl would
have a better shot.
Meet 17-year-old skylar
Lane from Brandon, Mississippi.
I love to go mud riding.
So now it's time
to get changed...
And go kill a deer.
This is the deer that
I shot when I was 15.
Ain't it pretty?
So you're a very girly girl?
I don't think the average
teenage girl around America
has a deer in her room.
My family owns a restaurant in.
Downtown Jackson
called beatty street groceries.
And it's been in our
family for 71 years.
- Hey, papa.
- Hey, baby.
Oh, man, I love you.
Love you too.
My mom describes it as
a little hole in the wall.
It's really fun to work here.
I love cause my whole family's
here and my papa and my mama.
- There you go, sir.
- Oh, she sings like a little.
Meadowlark. I tell you.
Our store has had
a rough ten years.
It was really, really tough.
We lost maybe 25%
of our business.
My mom doesn't like
to talk about
the hard times at the store,
because she doesn't really
want us to worry about it.
If anything ever came from
singing for me, I'd really want
to help out my family with the.
Store so we can keep
it in our family forever.
How much longer
will we be open, papa?
As long as the customers
keep coming.
What are you gonna sing for us?
Pistol Annies' hell on heels.
Nice.
I'm hell on heels,
say what you will.
I done made the devil a deal,
he made me pretty,
he made me smart.
I'm gonna break me.
A million hearts.
I'm hell on heels.
Sugar daddy.
I'm coming for you.
- I love it.
- Ooh, I like that.
I love it.
- I love that song.
- Well, we know exactly
who she is, and that's
part of what I love about her.
I'm ready to vote.
- Thank you. Oh, my gosh.
- Steven, yes or no?
Positively.
- Yes, positively.
- Steven, yes or no?
- Positively yes.
- Jennifer?
- Yes.
Randy?
Yes!
Welcome to Hollywood.
Oh, my gosh,
my friend loves you.
She has a poster on your wall.
She would love to give you a
hug but I don't know if she can.
- She would, like, faint.
- Where is she?
- She's right out the door.
- She would faint?
She's obsessed with him.
Tell you what,
why don't you go in?
- I'm gonna die.
- I'm scared of you.
- No, don't be scared of me.
- I am scared of you.
- Don't be scared of her, Steven.
- Where's my security?
- How old are you?
- Wait. Stay right up there.
- I'm 19.
- I need a hug from you.
Oh, I need a hug from you.
I love that. Dude, I love that.
Nice.
That was easy.
We liked that.
Hollywood, here I come.
See you there, baby.
Up next...
I'm about to pee myself.
- Go right ahead.
- We get the juices flowing.
Sweet.
Because boys will be boys...
Uh, uh, hello.
And Jennifer's
all fired up about it.
Are you guys crazy?
I didn't get it.
Somebody help me.
Welcome back to American Idol,
as our Texas-sized
auditions continue.
It don't get
no better than this.
Contestants from all over
are hoping to strike it big
with a ticket to Hollywood.
And when facing the biggest
moment of your life,
you can never be too prepared.
Some practice
with a vocal coach.
Others at karaoke night.
Some in their car.
Or even in front of
their neighbors.
Then it comes down
to the final touches.
Is that what shirt
you're wearing?
- Can you at least iron it? Dang.
- I ain't got time.
- I got to go.
- I think I know
what I want to wear.
It's this white little dress.
And while preparation
is vital...
Where are my shoes?
It takes serious determination.
This is what I want. I want
to be the next American Idol.
I know that it's gonna happen.
Especially if you've been
turned down once before.
- What's your name?
- I'm baylie brown.
- Hi, baylie.
- Baylie's back.
- I'm back.
- Back?
It's been five years.
It's been...
Has it been that long?
I was 16. I'm 21 now.
It's been a long,
long, long time.
Ooh, I want to see that tape.
Back in season six, I auditioned
in San Antonio, Texas.
I actually made it to Hollywood.
Group round was definitely
my least favorite moment.
I was paired with two
best friends from Jersey.
Our personalities
didn't really mesh well.
Each time, I te...
And then, of course,
I forgot the words.
Those Jersey girls actually
made it, and I went home.
It was a really
tough experience.
I was just a baby at the time.
I was 16.
Definitely grown and matured.
And I'm ready.
I want to lay you down.
In a bed of roses.
For tonight I sleep.
On a bed of nails.
Ooh, I want to be.
Just as close as.
Your holy ghost is.
So lay you down.
On a bed of roses.
I'm ready to vote. Are y'all?
- Yeah, I'm ready to vote.
- Baylie's back.
Baylie is back.
- I know.
- Steven, what you think?
I say yes.
- Mm, no-brainer.
- I say yes.
I wonder what you were like when
you were 16, but at 21...
- I was a little baby.
- You're great,
I hope you hold it together
for Hollywood this time.
She was a little baby, but
she was almost there, but
I'll tell you what, you've got
significantly better.
Three yeses.
You're through to Hollywood!
Baylie brown is back!
That's a...
That's a movie star name.
Baylie, I like it.
- Baylie brown.
I like it. Well, it's a
country singer star name.
Yeah, right, it is.
So baylie's persistence
has earned her
a second chance in Hollywood.
But for our next contestant,
today's audition is her one
and only shot
to change her life.
Hello.
- Hello.
- What's your name?
My name is Kristina sorio.
- And how old are you?
- 28.
So this is it.
This is your last time.
This is it.
Yup, first and last.
I've always done music.
I did little bar gigs
and cafe gigs,
and then I met my husband.
We had a band together
for a couple years.
And then I got pregnant, so that
all kind of got put on pause.
I have three kids.
I have a seven-year-old boy.
His name is Diego.
I have a five-year-old girl.
Her name is Isabella.
And a two-year-old
girl named Sophia.
I am currently
going through a divorce.
I've never been a single mom.
It's gonna be hard, but it's
definitely gonna be a journey.
It's been hard
for me to find work.
So I try to do stuff
out of my house
and simple little things
just to get some extra cash.
Took out a loan. And that was
supposed to pay for my lawyer.
And instead of paying my divorce
lawyer, I got a plane ticket.
To come to American Idol.
Sing like mommy.
A new beginning.
Yes.
Okay, let's hear it.
Come on, mama.
You've been on my mind,
- i grow fonder.
- Thank you, God.
Every day.
Lose myself.
In time.
Just thinking of your face.
God only knows.
Why it's taken me.
So long.
To let myself go.
You're the only one.
That I want.
- I heard enough.
- I heard enough too.
Well, I happen
to love your high warble.
And I love when you go upstairs.
Your tenderness is beautiful.
Uh, I'm just gonna say yes.
- Jennifer?
- I'm gonna say yes too.
- Steven?
- I'm gonna say yes.
- You're going to Hollywood.
- Welcome to Hollywood.
That's how you
do it right there.
That's how you do it.
- Nice.
- Beautiful voice.
- Beautiful, natural.
- That break in her voice.
- Oh, I love it.
- So the sea of Texas talent.
Is on the rise,
I'm thinking I want
to go jump in the ocean.
As another Hollywood
dream becomes reality.
Coming up...
- I'm gonna say no.
- Are you guys crazy?
- I didn't get it.
- The judges can't see
- eye to eye.
- She wasn't that good yet.
- Oh, my God.
- As Houston becomes
a battle of the sexes.
I'm gonna say yes.
Oh, my God.
Welcome back to American Idol
from the international
space station.
Good luck, contestants.
Thank you, commander Burbank.
Back down in the state of Texas,
remaining contestants are ready
to rocket to the big time.
But behind the judges table,
our own stars weren't
exactly aligned.
We are halfway through
the day here in Texas,
and there seems to be a little
dissention in the ranks.
It is Jennifer versus
the boys' club.
And I want to, uh-uh-uh.
- Do it.
- I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say no.
Me too. No, not yet, dude.
For you are mine.
At last.
Okay. I don't think you're quite
ready yet, so it's a no for me.
- Are you guys crazy?
- I didn't get it.
She wasn't that good yet.
She can get there.
Oh, my God.
And I'm misery,
now I'm misery.
Tell me why does this heart.
Make a fool out of me.
Steven, what'd you
think of Cheyenne?
You know, I'm not sure if
you got it for this year's Idol.
- You're joking, right?
- No.
I'm not.
I thought you were amazing.
Soulful... soulful, rich.
I just loved it.
I just don't think it's
quite ready yet.
- You guys are crazy.
- I think there's something there
I don't think you're
quite ready yet.
- Are you crazy?
- I didn't feel it.
Anybody else in here think that
they're freakin crazy right now?
Oh, my God.
I say not yet, baby.
- I say not yet.
- I would have said yes,
if I had two people who were
hearing correctly right now.
They would have said yes.
And then we would be putting
you through to Hollywood.
- We agree to disagree.
- And you might make it very far.
We agree to disagree.
Steven and I didn't get it.
But sorry. I'm sorry.
But you'll be even better
when you come back.
You guys are gonna look at it
and be like, "what the heck was"
I thinking?
What was I thinking?"
Really?
Some of the people
you put through today?
- No. No.
- Against her?
I won't lose any sleep
over that one.
Okay.
Oh, oh, I...
Never felt this way.
I start falling.
Baby, you can sing.
I love your voice.
I'm about to pee myself.
- Go right ahead,
- you guys...
'Cause you were that good.
I feel like I'm in
the twilight zone.
What do you think, Randy?
- You know, I like...
- Well, I know what I thought.
Okay, Jennifer,
what did you think?
There was something in your
voice that, really,
I couldn't connect with.
I think you got something there.
I want this more than anything.
Wake up. Honestly.
I feel like somebody
slipped you something.
Let me just say this.
That was some
beautiful singing, girl.
- Thank you.
- Jennifer, which way
are you voting?
Which way are you leaning?
I think you need a little more
experience. Maybe next year.
I think you're worth
one more shot.
I'm gonna say yes.
And I'm gonna say yes,
so guess where you're going?
- Hollywood!
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
That was awful.
- It's a big voice.
- That was awful.
So Linda is through.
But back inside the room,
Jennifer is just
getting started.
- That was awful.
- Why was it?
Were you guys watching
her walk or something?
- It wasn't... it wasn't...
- Yes, it was.
- That was so not awful.
- It wasn't that bad.
Baby,
you're gonna watch it back.
I promise you, you're
gonna say it's awful.
The one girl who came in here
and blew you away,
she was sounding like Janis
joplin, you sent her home.
That was a different
type of singing.
It was a different
- This is the kind of singing...
- Somebody help me!
Jennifer says
we've got a roofie.
What is happening right now?
They're sending the good singers.
Home, and they're letting
the bad singers through.
J-lo, even though I was a
little crushed
'cause I idolize you,
I'm gonna prove
you wrong in Hollywood.
I literally... I was so angry,
I almost had an anxiety attack.
I was like, I cannot hold it in.
- Coming up...
- Grant me the power
to bring revolution
to the world.
Is this the man to restore
peace on the panel?
No, no, no, no.
Or has the real
battle just begun?
The revolution is here.
And if they're not down with
that, they can all just @?$&£!
Welcome back to the Idol
smackdown in Texas.
As the day winds down,
Jennifer is all wound up.
I don't think you're
quite ready yet.
- Are you crazy?
- I'm gonna say yes.
Oh, my God.
That was awful.
I literally... I was so angry,
I almost had an anxiety attack.
I was like, I cannot hold it in!
Meanwhile, I scoured the
holding room to find someone to
return a sense of peace
to the auditions.
It has to be a good pick.
Ooh, I think I found him.
- How are you?
- I'm pretty good today.
Good to see you.
You just hanging?
Yeah, just waiting around.
Just doing what
needs to be done.
And what is that?
Well, apparently take a lot
of orders, follow them to a tee,
stay on top of timing.
- Right.
- But what I'd really like to
be doing is be in front
of those judges,
blowing their minds.
My name is Alejandro cazares.
I'm 26 years old,
and I am from Houston, Texas.
Today is the first day
of the revolution.
And anybody
that just happens to be around,
they're gonna feel that heat.
Oh, my God. This is it.
I want to be standing
in front of America
and I can finally
tell everybody,
in front of the entire world,
I made it.
The revolution is here.
I am the revolution.
Every single one of you
has got to bring it on.
The revolution is here.
And if they're not
down with that,
like my good friends say,
they can all just @?$&£!
Revolution.
Revolution. Revolution.
I don't want to fight.
Then say you're sorry.
- For what?
- See?
So you want to keep
the fight going.
- I haven't done anything.
- Okay.
- Hey, man.
- Randy.
- What's going on?
- Jennifer. Steven.
- Hi.
- Grant me the power
to bring revolution
to the world.
What kind of revolution?
Revolution where the underdog.
Can actually win
once in a while.
A world where unique people like.
Lady gaga become
platinum sellers.
A world where a man like Barack
Obama can become president.
That kind of world.
Aren't those two things
truths in the world today?
Isn't that the world we live in?
I've been on the
sidelines all my life.
And you have a lot of
support in your dreams?
I have a girlfriend. I shouldn't
even call her a girlfriend.
I told her, you know,
"wish me luck",
and she said, "I can't wish
you luck."
It's something
I don't believe in."
There's a lot of people
that are rooting against me.
What do you say
we maybe sing now?
That sounds like a plan.
>> What are you singing?
It's called looking up
by paramore.
Great band.
Things are looking up,
oh, finally.
I thought I'd never see.
The day you smiled at me,
and it's not a dream any more,
no.
It's not a dream any more,
it's worth fighting for.
I can't believe
I almost gave it up.
No, no, no, no.
It's all I've ever wanted.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Your voice is not, you know,
good enough for American Idol.
I know what I can do.
I know that I can prove to you
that, if you let me through,
if you give me that chance,
I can go out there and I can do
something most people never do.
I want to be your
age one day, Steven.
- Easy, easy.
- You may never get there. No.
I just want to be even on the
cusp of where you got to.
You wrote dream on before
aerosmith even formed.
I never thought I'd be...
You got to love him, I mean...
And if you just...
I'll fight for it harder
than anybody.
I'm gonna say this to you.
The voice is terrible.
Honestly your voice is terrible.
Never a career
in singing for you.
- It's not gonna happen.
- And I wrote dream on back.
When the dead
sea was still sick.
I know I can do this.
- Please.
- We have to take a quick vote,
okay? Steven?
Not yet, man.
- Randy?
- Never.
- I'm begging you.
- Vocally never.
- I'm begging you. One shot.
- No, don't beg us.
Sweetie, you have too much
integrity for that,
too much dignity.
- So, listen...
- Can I sing in Spanish at least?
Please?
What can I do?
- Nothing.
- This is, this is... I've heard.
Other singers that I honestly
know aren't better than me.
I've heard worse.
There is worse.
Truth is, if you think you're
good and you're here,
you shouldn't even listen
to anyone else
or have any comment cause
you won't even know.
- I'll be back next year.
- Here we go.
Okay, baby.
Ouch.
Our forefathers fought,
you know, months, years,
to get to where
this country got.
And life's not about
how hard you can hit,
but how hard you can get hit
and keep pushing forward.
The revolution is not over.
Not till I say it's over.
After the break,
Steven's at it again.
Look at those legs...
You show a little belly,
and it goes crazy around here.
Plus day two
delivers more talent.
You are what
we've been looking for.
But can the judges
keep it together?
How are you gonna stop him?
He wasn't even warmed up.
No, no, no, I know.
So what else you got?
What do you mean?
Welcome to Texas!
We're at it again
here in Houston,
as another day of
auditions is set to begin.
A stellar start on day one
leaves Texas
with a lot to live up to.
The day two contestants
have their eye on the prize.
But Randy and Steven
are eying something else.
What can you say
about Jennifer Lopez?
That's what I was saying.
Oh, my God, today.
Look at those legs...
You show a little belly,
and it goes crazy around here.
- For real, though.
- Next time, long shirt.
It could be
a long day for Jennifer.
I got it.
Here we go. Come on.
And as the guys settle down...
Do it.
Our first contestant
is ready to shake things up.
- Cortez, where you from, bud?
- From garland, Texas.
Now tell me,
what do you do there?
I'm a warehouse worker
and a college student.
Yeah, and what do you envision?
- Being the next American Idol.
- That's good.
That's a good goal.
Hey.
Wake up. It's a big day.
I grew up in a single
parent household.
My mom was the breadwinner
for the household.
Me and my brother.
And my mom was so strong.
We were homeless at times,
like, for two years.
I got made fun of at school,
'cause we had to live
with friends at that time.
Just had a really hard
childhood, struggled a lot,
but no one can put
a definition on your life.
Only you can determine
what happens in your future.
I really want
to show people that,
through hard work
and determination and passion
in what you believe for,
you can really do it.
It can be done.
There is hope.
No matter what happens in life,
you can still
achieve your dream.
American Idol
is opportunity at its greatest.
- Hi.
- Hello.
What you singing, baby?
I'm gonna sing Adele,
someone like you.
- Okay.
- Wow, do it.
All right. Here we go.
I hate to turn up.
Out of the blue uninvited,
but I couldn't stay away.
I couldn't fight it.
I hoped you'd see my face.
And that you'd be reminded.
That for me. It isn't over.
Never mind, I'll find.
Someone like you.
I wish nothing.
But the best.
For you two.
Don't forget me.
I'll beg.
I remember you said.
Sometimes it lasts in love,
but sometimes it hurts instead.
That's what
that song sounds like.
Nice.
No, no, I like it. I like it.
A lot of people have
tried to sing that song.
I'm like, oh, God.
Thank you.
How are you gonna stop him?
He wasn't even warmed up.
No, no, no, I know.
So what else you got?
- What do you mean?
- I want to hear something else.
Ah, come on, Randy.
Give me some love.
- No, it was good enough.
- You're my favorite judge, man.
- Come on now. I love all you.
- Swear?
He's not your favorite judge.
Swear. Swear, don't lie.
Don't lie
on national television.
I love all of you.
I mean, I love all
of you of course.
You're beautiful, talented,
but you're my favorite judge.
- You've been here the longest.
- I really like this guy.
This guy has a certain...
Charm, a special...
What do they say?
- Je ne sais quoi.
Yeah, you have
a special something.
Listen, you're good-looking.
- Thank you.
- You're sweet.
- You have a great voice.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Leg up.
- Steven?
I say yes.
I think you're
a good-looking guy,
not like me and Steven,
but you're a good-looking guy.
I think that you have
a really good voice.
Thank you.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
What does that mean,
Jennifer, what does that mean?
Hollywood.
Oh, my God.
See, he was middle
of the road for me until he...
- No.
- No, but actually, that was...
No, I was like, are you crazy?
- Don't stop him.
- To get this golden ticket
is like everything
I've ever wanted.
I'm this much closer
to winning American Idol.
I'm gonna win American Idol.
Oh, my God!
Cortez Shaw.
What a name, huh?
When we come back...
We're on the final stretch to
the finish line with more words
of wisdom from Mr. Tyler...
As our galveston auditions end
with a story
of incredible odds.
I wasn't born normal.
I came out a bit different.
It's an audition that wasn't
supposed to happen.
I guess we're taking
a leap of faith with you today.
It's late afternoon
in galveston,
and, like the hot Texas sun,
the Idol dream
is still burning brightly.
I have what it takes
to be the next American Idol.
And I'm ready to be big.
I'm here to be
the next American Idol.
Fact.
But for some that golden ticket
is gonna be a bit of a stretch.
We could have had it all.
Yeah.
We're rolling in that deep.
You had my heart
inside of your hands.
But you played it.
You played it, you played it,
you played it to that beat.
I bet you're crazy in...
On the dance floor.
Oh, what, Steven?
What, Steven Tyler?
I bet you are crazy
on the dance floor.
Yeah.
I didn't like any of it.
I thought it was all terrible
and screaming and screechy.
Don't you know it?
I heard it through
the grapevine.
Not much longer.
Would you be mine.
Baby, I heard it.
Through the grapevine.
Oh, I'm just about.
To lose my mind.
- Me too.
- Honey, honey, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Well, then.
Undo this hurt you caused.
When you walked out the door.
And walked out of my life.
Uncry these tears.
- Stop it.
- I cried so many nights.
Yeah. Sorry, baby.
It's okay. I...
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you, baby.
What in the hell?
Looks like someone's
getting a little slap happy,
so I head in the room
to assess the damage.
What do you think about how
it's gone so far today, Steven?
Which is...
You know what I'm saying?
What do you think about the
kids that are coming through?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
It was down to the last
contestant of the day to redeem
the sound of the South.
- Hi.
- How you all doing?
- Good. How are you?
- Good, good.
- Okay, what's your name?
- Ramiro Garcia.
- Yeah, where are you from?
- Houston, Texas.
- And what do you do?
- I'm a worship leader
here at a church.
- Church...
- Big church?
- Yeah. Lakewood church.
- Tell me a little bit
- about yourself.
- Growing up, it was really
tough, man,
to be honest with you.
I wasn't born normal.
I came out a bit different.
I came out with no ears.
I had nothing
on my left ear and
on the right I just had,
like, an earlobe.
Doctors gave
my parents the worst news.
"Your son's not
gonna be able to hear."
He's not gonna be able to speak.
"You know, he's gonna be mute."
At age four,
I started to have surgeries.
They actually had
to create a ear canal.
Through there, they were able
to discover that I had, like,
an ear drum and there would be.
Possibilities that
I would be able to hear.
I remember every year having
to go back for another surgery
and for another surgery.
It was pretty intense.
It would be surprising
to someone
that have known you forever
to hear about this audition,
- really, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
Not many people know about that.
Luckily, through time
and through faith,
I have a voice to speak with,
even a voice to sing.
I can't wait to hear you sing.
That's great. That's great.
Nice.
Amazing grace.
How sweet the sound.
That saved a wretch.
Like me.
He sing in another level.
Different to this world...
- For us, you know.
- Yeah, yeah, I understand.
It's a big deal for us.
- Yeah, I can imagine.
- Yeah.
I see.
My chains are gone.
I've been set free.
My God, my savior.
Has ransomed me.
And like a flood.
His mercy rains.
Unending love.
Amazing grace.
Nice. Glad you sang that verse.
- Thank you.
- You know what,
I like what I'm hearing.
I like your insides
as well, man.
- Thank you.
- Let's hope he's got a ticket
when he comes out there.
Wwell, I know he's
the best for me.
Good.
You're a power of example,
to say the least.
- Yeah.
- And you can sing so,
I'm happy with you, man.
So you say yes?
- I say yes.
- What do you say, Randy?
I love what you said, "that
I'm used to being the underdog",
because I'm hopeful, man.
- I'm just hopeful.
- Yeah, yeah, for sure.
- You know what I'm saying?
- I guess
we're taking a leap
of faith with you today.
It's all right.
You can get emotional.
It's okay.
Don't you worry about it.
This golden ticket is for
my family, for my mom.
Here's the proof now that I can.
Make it and I can fight through
and I can be
a part of this thing.
Your father is very
proud back there.
As he should be.
I remember when
the doctors say...
He no speak.
He's not well.
He no hear.
Guess what?
- I'm happy now.
- We're grateful.
Congratulations.
Thank you, guys.
Good job, my man.
Bye-bye. Thank you.
With his family by his side,
it's an emotional
victory for ramiro...
And it was shared by 24
other hopefuls in Houston.
You are going to Hollywood!
Welcome to Hollywood!
Hollywood!
We're going to Hollywood!
And with that the curtain closes
on our auditions in Texas.
I believe it's a wrap.
Good thing going,
for real, today.
Better than I expected,
actually.
Go cool off and celebrate.
Go for it.
I actually was kidding.
I didn't think they'd do it.
Oh! God!
You know what they say.
Don't sweat the petty things
and don't pet the sweaty things.
I can't see.
Next week, we head
to the pacific northwest.
Welcome to Portland!
It's a shocking
night of auditions...
Man, I'm feeling you right now.
In the city of roses.
I loved that.
And for some, it's been
a journey against all odds.
I saw so many people perish.
You're gonna be good, I feel.
There's a different type
of love that I feel now.
You've got that gift.
It's an inspirational evening
you won't wanna miss.
Nothing is gonna stop me.
They call me
tripster the hipster.