They call this place the city
of champions, so it is the
perfect spot to find our next
superstar.
It's our first time here in
Pittsburgh.
You ready?
This is American idol.
In our 11 seasons...
This is the first time we've
held auditions in Pittsburgh.
Pittsburgh!
Everything we do, we do it big.
A city that has its
own unique language...
Goin' downtown for that.
American idol now, down there
by the crick.
Younse guys.
Its black and yellow sports
legacies, and, well...
Pittsburgh all day, baby.
On its hometown pride.
And with the nickname "the city
of champions"...
We need to be entertained.
The judges have high
expectations for the 'burgh.
You get one shot at fame,
and that shot starts today.
And as they settle in for the
first day of auditions,
22-year-old heejun han can
hardly contain his excitement.
Why are you here today?
Uh...I don't know.
Do you think you have what it
takes to be the next American
idol?
I don't know.
After I saw all these crazy
people...
They're good, first of all.
And then I thought I was a
little good, but then...They're
just crazy good.
And I'm thinking, "I'm not that
good."
And now I'm thinking, "I'm not
good at all."
Your face is this small.
My face is that size?
Yeah.
Really?
It's good-looking.
Oh, thanks.
I've never been compared to a
fist.
Yeah, I mean, it was just so
small.
Mine's really big, so...
Your head's big?
Yeah. Just...
All right, well, I think
we look the same size.
I don't think so.
Really?
No, it's just, comparison's
too much.
All right.
I was nervous before, but...
I think I drank plenty of teas
and stuff, so I'm okay.
So what's your name?
Heejun.
And where you from?
Oh...Originally from Korea,
but now I'm-I live in New York.
Yeah.
You guys are so unreal, ohh.
You look like one of those,
like, wax museum dolls.
You know, you're just unreal for
me right now.
Like three supermodels, right?
One, actually.
Thank you!
Steven!
Thank you, baby.
We just got dissed.
I'm sorry, I was just
kidding, you guys are all...
oh, yeah. Oh!
Oh, don't take it back now.
I like this.
Don't take it back now.
You're crazy!
All right, heejun.
Does he sing to you guys?
Around you guys?
We've actually never heard
him sing.
You've never heard him sing,
and you call yourself a friend.
What do you like to sing the
most?
I love when you do that.
What do you like to sing?
Um, soul, R&B.
And what are you gonna sing
for us tonight?
How am I supposed to live
without you by Michael Bolton.
Oh, okay.
That should be the chorus.
♪ I can hardly believe it ♪
♪ when I heard the news today ♪
♪ I had to come and get it ♪
♪ straight from you ♪
He sings nice.
♪ They said you were ♪
♪ leavin' ♪
♪ someone swept ♪
♪ your heart away ♪
♪ from the look upon your face ♪
♪ I say it's true ♪
Listen to him sing, now.
♪ So tell me how am I ♪
♪ supposed to live without you ♪
♪ now that I've been ♪
♪ loving you so long ♪
♪ how am I supposed ♪
♪ to live without you ♪
♪ to carry on ♪
Shaky hands.
I love it!
That was great, man.
How do you say your name?
Uh, heejun.
Heejun, man, you sing great.
Oh, thank you!
You have a beautiful voice.
Surprisingly.
Yes, really!
I was shocked.
Look at-I love you!
Randy, you look better in,
uh, person, I'm sorry.
Thank you, I knew I loved
this guy.
This guy...Thank you so much.
This guy's full of compliments.
But, listen, seriously.
On the serious note, right.
Seriously.
I am really impressed and
shocked.
You have a beautiful tone to
your voice.
Really, really good voice.
I'm very impressed.
And great, like, control in
your...
Yeah, good understanding of
where notes should go.
Oh, nobody told me that...
those kind of stuff.
But you guys are telling me,
so this is just...
yup, I think you're really
great.
I think you could be an American
idol.
So let's all vote here.
What do you say, Stevie?
I say yes.
Jennifer.
Randy.
I say yes.
The model!
Welcome to Hollywood!
You got it!
You finally got it right.
Welcome to Hollywood.
Wow, man.
Thank you.
I got it!
Oh, my God, he was adorable.
Are you surprised that you
have a ticket in your hand?
Yeah.
♪ Hollywoo... ♪
I'm coming.
After the break, Pittsburgh
delivers some unpredictable...
What's he gonna do next?
And unforgettable moments.
A gazillion percent yes!
God, I think I just had an
eargasm.
Welcome back to steel
city!
Pittsburgh pride has arrived
to the auditions.
And inside the holding room,
it's a battle to conquer those
first-day jitters.
You gotta have guts for this.
Guts, I'm telling you.
When inside the audition
room, our panel of judges are
nothing but seasoned
professionals.
Does my ass look good?
So good.
Time for a limerick.
Oh, yes, please, please.
There was a young man
from St. Paul's...
Uh-oh.
No, never mind, we won't do
this one.
Uh, maybe not so professional.
And it's time for the next
auditioner.
Send in the next person!
My name's reid grimm.
I'm 26 years old, and I'm from
ellsworth, Wisconsin.
My mom and dad met in a band,
fell in love, got married,
had kids, and as they had kids,
they just added them to the
show.
So I've been on stage since two
years old.
It's like home, really.
It's just where I live.
What are you singing, man?
The theme song to
family matters.
That's a first.
Yeah.
♪ Well, it's a rare condition ♪
♪ in this day and age ♪
♪ to read any good news ♪
♪ on the newspaper page ♪
♪ love and tradition ♪
♪ of the grand design, well ♪
♪ some people say ♪
♪ it's even harder to find ♪
♪ days go by ♪
♪ well, it's deeper than love ♪
♪ in a family ♪
♪ yeah ♪
You are crazy.
That was genius.
You...
I love that!
You have been on stage since
you were two.
Yeah.
It's so...
wow, dude, the passion.
You had us all, like,
enthralled, you know what I'm
saying?
The mark of a great performer
is that you never know what
they're gonna do.
Yeah.
So you can't take your eyes
off of them, you just follow
them back and forth on the
stage, like, "what's he gonna do
next?"
And you have that.
It's so exciting to watch.
Thank you so much.
Thank you!
Let's vote!
Oh, come on, Randy, go.
A zillion percent yes.
A gazillion percent yes!
Supercalifragalistic...
Expialidocious!
You're going to Hollywood!
Yes, Hollywood!
Nowfound real music.
Reid grimm, you're in, man.
So the boy who has been
singing since the age of two
makes it to Hollywood.
Wow.
Awe...Some.
Where did you find that?
And Pittsburgh just keeps on
delivering.
♪ A long time comin' ♪
♪ but I know ♪
♪ a change gon' come ♪
All right.
Yo, listen, you know what?
You can sing!
♪ Well, I got one thing ♪
♪ left to say ♪
♪ is you can lay ♪
♪ in the bed you've made ♪
♪ well, I been doin' fine ♪
♪ without you ♪
♪ forgettin' all the love ♪
♪ we once knew ♪
Bingo.
Yep, there it is.
Bingo!
Stop, stop.
Yes!
You're goin' to Hollywood!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Way to go!
Awesome!
The way the golden tickets
were flying out the door in.
Pittsburgh made us wonder why
we waited so long to come here.
So did you make it?
Wow.
So cute.
All right, Pittsburgh.
It's fair to say the judges
are loving this city.
But you never know what lies on
the horizon.
Are you the same in terms of
singing styles?
I'm not a singer.
I'm a planker.
Okay.
And, um, I'm just planking
her to Hollywood.
I'm Patricia bell, also known
as, famously, Patti the
Pittsburgh planker.
And this is my younger sister,
Samantha.
Originally, planking is a
yoga position.
You lay on your belly and you
lift your feet up.
Yep, yep.
Look at that.
Whoa.
Planking has been a hobby,
but now it turned into something
that I can do for my sister.
Hi!
She sings better when I
plank, that's it.
It's true.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing like we never
loved at all by faith hill.
While your sister's there...
Planking?
How long can you hold that?
She can't talk while she's
planking, Steven.
That's hilarious.
Yeah, this is serious business.
Okay.
♪ You, I hear ♪
♪ you're doin' fine ♪
♪ seems like you're doin' well ♪
♪ as far as I can tell ♪
♪ so tell me ♪
♪ what your secret is ♪
♪ baby ♪
♪ to letting go ♪
♪ letting go like you did ♪
♪ like you did ♪
♪ how can you just ♪
♪ walk on by ♪
♪ without one tear in your eye ♪
Okay.
Uh, does Patti want to cease the
planking?
Yeah, Patti, what's goin' on
down there, man?
Jennifer.
I really loved it.
I felt like there was some guts
behind the voice.
And it made me very pleased.
Very happy.
I agree.
I liked you as well.
I liked your tone, I like your
voice-I like it.
Sweet, clever, great notes.
Thank you so much.
I like the vibe, I mean, very
pure kind of sounding that you
got going on, reminds me...
Like, oh, faith hill.
Yeah, a little faith hill,
a little carpenterish.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say yes, and you're
going to Hollywood!
I'm proud that she would come
out and plank while her
girlfriend sang.
It was her sister.
I get it, but still...
It's a family thing.
So it's another golden ticket
for Pittsburgh, and an entire
family lying face down on the
floor.
Season 11, everybody.
Coming up, Randy and Jennifer
adore the talent.
I love it!
Love it.
And Steven brings the noise.
Say hi. Hello!
What's your name?
Uh, I'm creighton, and this
is, uh, my little hometown,
New York City.
Right now, I don't really have a
job.
I'm a starving artist, I guess
you could say.
New York is rough.
It's-it's a crazy place.
There's a lot of people trying
to do what I'm trying too
there.
I'm just singing and writing
music and hoping that
something's gonna happen to get
me to the next level.
This is the long line to get...
For the bus.
Bus.
From New York City to
Pittsburgh, it's like a
nine-hour bus ride.
So I have some time to come up
with a little something to sing
for the judges.
I'm sure something will come
out.
Let's hope.
What are you singing, man?
I'm gonna sing, uh...
I had a bunch of options, and I
couldn't decide, so I just wrote
a song on the way here.
And so I'm...
Okay. Sing that.
Really? I love this.
All right.
Come on. Make it look easy.
All right, I'm gonna try.
♪ Randy Jackson ♪
♪ you've been part ♪
♪ of the action ♪
♪ for 11 whole seasons now ♪
♪ and you two are the new few ♪
♪ who gonna choose who ♪
♪ gonna be the next ♪
♪ American idol ♪
♪ the next American idol ♪
♪ it's gonna be me ♪
Wow.
That was like jamiroquai and
Justin Timberlake had a baby.
A little bit.
Kind of a wild thing, but
there's something about it that
I kind of am intrigued by.
That was genius.
That was great.
Thanks.
That was really good, that
you have the...
The what?
You have the something.
The...
The [Bleep] to just spit that
out the way you did, man.
That was beautiful.
We like-I liked it, too.
Yeah.
All right.
Sing something that's got,
you know, beginning, middle,
and end.
♪ Whe-e-e-e-en ♪
♪ I-I-I ♪
♪ had you ♪
Wow.
♪ I treated you ba-a-ad ♪
God.
Who does he remind me of?
Who is he right now?
You are beautiful, you know
that?
♪ Since you been away ♪
♪ don't you know I ♪
♪ sit around ♪
A singer from the old days.
♪ With my he-ead ♪
♪ hangin' down ♪
♪ and I wonder ♪
He looks like Paul anka.
♪ Wonder ♪
♪ who's lovin' you ♪
You're a beautiful man.
Do the next part, do the next
part, do the next part.
♪ Don't you know that I ♪
♪ sit around ♪
All right.
♪ With my head hangin' down ♪
Wow.
♪ And I wonder who ♪
Oh, boy.
♪ Who's lovin' you ♪
All right.
Damn.
Yo, listen, you know what?
You can sing!
You got like a weird kind of
wild, crazy voice, but I love
it!
You know what?
'Cause you had the balls to come
in here and sing something you
wrote on the way to become an
American idol, and then...
Bold.
And then you sang something
that was so beautiful that you
are going to be one.
Michael Jackson.
That's the most amazing thing
I've ever seen.
Why not, man?
Let's go big ostay home, right?
You gave a really great
audition.
You are sweetly insane, man.
Can we, like, vote, guys?
Yes, please.
I'm gonna say...
A million percent...
Yes.
Wow.
Jennifer.
I'm gonna say...
Two million percent yes.
Steven, can I hear a billion?
I'm gonna say three
gazillion percent.
This is why I joined idol, to
say to you right now, dude, you
are so Hollywood!
Thank you, thank you, thank
you, thank you so much.
So Hollywood is correct.
Thank you, I can't wait.
I can't wait-I won't let you
down.
Good for you.
Thank you, man.
Write some stuff on the way
to Hollywood.
Are you kidding me?
Next on idol...
One kid begins his journey.
He is the next American idol.
And a comeback kid begs for a
second chance.
You're singing the passion,
but you're not showing it.
This means a lot to me.
Eben...What's going on?
Packing for American idol.
Yeah?
I'm eben frankowitz, I'm 15
years old, and I'm from milford,
Ohio.
Vote for me.
All right.
Have a great time.
I've been preparing for weeks
on end, practicing, trying to
pick out the right songs to do.
It's been hard, but, you know,
it was definitely worth it to
get here.
Taking off for Pittsburgh.
Is he going to win everything?
He is, he is the next
American idol.
My parents help me like no
other.
They drive me everywhere.
They're super supportive in
everything I do.
Let everybody else do their
thing.
You do eben's thing.
Okay.
I've come here to follow my
dream.
Where are we?
We're in Pittsburgh.
You're only 15 years old and
look what you're doing.
It's great.
I'm really, really proud of you.
No matter what happens.
All right, let's do this.
Showtime.
All right.
All right, let's go.
Hi, my name is eben.
So what does this feel like,
to be standing here with all
these older people?
It's a privilege, you know?
I hope I'll be able to get that
golden ticket, go to Hollywood.
You ready for this?
Yeah, I'm pumped.
Okay.
Let's go, man.
Let's do it.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
Nice to meet you.
What's going on?
What's your name?
My name's eben frankowitz.
Eben-great name, man.
Thank you.
Who do people say you look
like, dude?
People say I look like Justin
bieber.
Wow, what do you think,
Jennifer?
He's cute. Look how cute he is.
Don't let that go to your head.
I won't, I promise.
All right, so what are you
gonna sing for us?
Today I'm going to be singing
ain't no sunshine.
Yeah, give that a shot.
♪ Ain't no sunshine ♪
♪ when she's gone ♪
♪ it's not warm ♪
♪ when she's away ♪
♪ ain't no sunshine ♪
♪ when she's gone ♪
♪ and she's always gone ♪
♪ too long ♪
♪ any time she goes away ♪
Mm, really interesting.
Nice, man.
What'd you think, Jennifer?
Some people just have it.
Some people just born with it.
Some people just born to do it.
I think you're one of those
people.
Thank you.
Yeah, me too.
I think you got it.
Thank you.
Yeah, it's only going to get
better.
I like you, too, man.
You definitely have a natural,
God-given gift that is pretty
amazing and spot-on.
Let's take a vote.
Yes.
Jennifer, what say you?
100% yes.
You're going to Hollywood!
Thank you, guys, so much.
Oh, thank you, man.
You got a great voice.
Yes!
How cute is he?
I know.
So cute.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
Eben coming through that door
with some purpose.
Good job, buddy.
Congratulations, man.
Thank you very much.
You're very welcome.
I got my golden ticket to.
Hollywood, yeah!
It's a dream come true.
I'm, like, shake-I don't-oh,
my goodness.
As one of our youngest
contestants in Hollywood, eben
will get his first shot at a
lifelong dream, but for Travis.
Orlando, who last year shared
his story of strength, today is
about second chances.
Who remembers Travis?
Travis.
I do!
What are you going to sing for
us this year?
I'm going to sing isn't she
lovely?
Okay.
♪ Isn't she lovely? ♪
♪ isn't she wonderful? ♪
♪ isn't she precious? ♪
♪ less than one minute old ♪
♪ I never thought ♪
♪ through love we'd be ♪
♪ making one as lovely as she ♪
♪ but isn't she lovely ♪
♪ made from love ♪
Your voice has gotten
stronger since last year.
There's still a part of it that
is not all the way-you're not
coming all the way out with it.
I really want you to do that.
I really want you to do it,
you know what I mean?
You're singing the passion,
but you're not showing it.
I've got to show it.
Yeah, and you're singing it,
so it's like, "come on, come
on."
So you're in High School?
What's your story now?
I dropped out of High School.
This is a all or nothing thing.
This means a lot to me.
Last year, after idol aired and
everything, my mom walked out.
She found another relationship
that she obviously loved more
than her family, and that really
hurt me.
We got evicted from our
apartment and I moved into a
shelter with my dad and my twin
brother.
My mom could have prevented this
from just sticking with my dad,
and my dad was just getting even
sicker and sicker.
My mom broke my dad's heart.
Even though we went through
all those trials and
tribulations, we're
inseparable, we're very tight,
because we know that the
bottom line, at the end of the
day, all we have is each other.
I love you, dad.
I'm doing this not only to
show myself, but to show my mom
that, you know, I am worth
something, I can do this, I'm
not a good-for-nothing lowlife.
I can do something with my life
and something positively.
Is your family here
supporting you or...?
My dad's in dialysis, my
brother started college.
I got my best friend Aaron,
like, right outside waiting.
I'm scared, but at the same
time, I know this is what I
want.
Scared is good.
Let's take a vote.
Scared makes you do things that
you wouldn't normally do.
I'm going to say yes, man.
I think you're worth another
shot.
I think you've gotten stronger.
I think you've got a ways to
grow, though.
He's only 17.
There's a lot more growing to
do, and I think that, from what
you've shown us, that definitely
you're going to keep growing, so
I'm going to say yes, too.
I think you got something
there, too, but you've got to
jump out of your shell, man.
I will.
All right, so guess what?
You're going to Hollywood!
Yes!
Oh man, oh man, oh man, oh man.
Thank you, thank you.
Yeah, go tell your dad.
I'm going to tell everyone.
Yeah, go tell your dad, man.
Yeah, you've got to tell your
family, man.
Thank you so much, thank you.
Okay.
Way to go.
That's awesome, man.
That is awesome.
I guess I'll see you there.
Yes, you will.
Congratulations, buddy.
Thank you, thank you.
He got better.
He definitely got better.
Hey, dad?
Yeah?
I'm going to Hollywood, dad.
Man, everything that we
prayed for is just this closer.
I know this is the year.
Coming up...Day two begins.
And Pittsburgh's got some
surprises.
It's day two of auditions
here in Pittsburgh.
Welcome to Pittsburgh!
Yesterday's great talent,
but...
We forgot the map.
Which is something Jennifer
could well have used, because
she was running late.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Steven and Randy are taking
this opportunity to put on their
own two-man show.
Idol season 11, the greatest
singing talent show ever.
♪ pink ♪
♪ it's my new obsession ♪
♪ it ain't even a question ♪
♪ pink ♪
♪ is the love you discover ♪
I love this guy.
With the crowd riled up...
I'm ready.
And the team now reunited,
day two has got big shoes to
fill.
Come on, Pittsburgh.
What a slammin' day yesterday
was.
Let's hope that we can find
that same level today.
Dude, it was crazy yesterday.
Let's get it on, Pittsburgh,
let's get it on.
My name's Erica van pelt.
I'm from South kingstown, Rhode
island, and I'm a mobile dj and
a wedding singer.
A mobile dj is a dj that moves
around from place to place.
I move in and move out of a club
or a bar or a venue six nights a
week.
In addition to owning the dj
business, I also am a wedding
singer.
Here we go.
For a lot of people, when they
hear "wedding singer," they
automatically see Adam sandier
and they see mullets and sort of
goofy, goofy singing.
Wedding singing, for me,
honestly is just another outlet
to be able to share my love of
music and my love of singing
with people.
This could possibly be the
biggest, most important day of
my entire life.
My time to shine. Let's rock.
Hello.
What's going down?
Hi.
What's your name?
Erica van pelt.
Erica, where are you from?
Rhode island.
My neck of the woods.
I'm liking that.
What-what do you do?
I'm a mobile dj and I, uh,
and I sing weddings.
Great, so what are you going
to sing for us, yeah?
Um, I'm going to do Carole king,
will you still love me tomorrow?
Wow, my favorite song.
Nice song.
♪ Tonight you're mine ♪
♪ completely ♪
♪ you give your love ♪
♪ so sweetly ♪
Nice.
♪ Tonight the light of love ♪
♪ is in your eyes ♪
♪ but will you love me ♪
♪ tomorrow? ♪
♪ tonight with words unspoken ♪
♪ you say that ♪
♪ I'm the only one ♪
Yes.
♪ Only one ♪
♪ but will my heart ♪
♪ be broken ♪
♪ when the night ♪
♪ meets the morning sun ♪
Wow.
This is how you do it.
I love that you got this low
alto, this low tone.
Oh, my God, all the turns, the
phrases-beautiful.
Thank you.
You turn sexy, very sure of
yourself.
That was great.
Thank you.
The voice matches her, you
know what I mean?
It kind of all works together.
I did-must say, I had a
feeling when you walked in,
like, "you know, this could be
good, Pittsburgh."
It's in the water up there.
Should we just vote?
Yes.
Some kind of magic.
So that means vote?
Yes.
Yes, you're going to.
Hollywood.
Oh, my God.
That's how you put it down,
that's how you do it.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
I got my golden ticket, I'm
so excited.
Pelt can belt.
I am going to Hollywood.
I will see you guys there.
Next up, this coal miner digs
for gold.
I just gotta be a singer.
It's my dream.
And a girl saved by love.
If it wasn't for my husband.
Ryan, I would not be sitting
here right now.
He loves me like I've never been
loved before.
It's 3:00 in Pittsburgh.
And the good times are rolling.
No one is enjoying the auditions
more than Steven Tyler.
I've got the secret
weapon-my red box.
Thanks to his colleague's
sound machine.
"This is a national disaster."
Yes, exactly, exactly.
Wait, what? Cut.
Anybody remember that...
that would be him.
"You've got to be kidding me."
Maybe so, but a serious
number of yellow tickets flew
out of those doors.
Yes.
You're going to Hollywood!
As more and more futures
looked golden.
Hoping to alter his path was
Shane Bruce.
I'm 19 years old and I'm from
moundsville, west Virginia.
Well, about a year ago, I
graduated from High School.
I decided to follow in the
family trade and go to the coal
mines.
To go into the mine, you go
straight into an elevator.
The elevator takes you down
about 400 feet.
One of my jobs underground, we
build crib.
Keeps the roof up, man.
My pap, he was a coal miner.
My Uncle, he was a coal miner.
My entire family does it.
It must be something we're good
at.
I'm proud to be a coal miner.
Yeah, definitely.
But...if I had to choose
something to be for the rest of
my life, it's got to be a
singer, man.
I just-it's my dream.
♪ In the still of the night ♪
♪ I held you ♪
♪ held you tight ♪
How's that, guys?
Got to win it.
Now get back to work.
Okay.
What's going on, guys?
Hi.
Dude, hopefully you are, man.
Oh, man, I hope.
What's your name?
I'm Shane Bruce.
Hi, Shane.
Yeah, I'm 19, I'm a coal
miner, so, uh, chasing the
dream, you know?
Really, a coal miner?
What made you want to do that?
You're kind of young.
What, be a coal miner?
Yeah.
My pap, he's a coal miner.
He's stable.
You know, he's got a stable
income, stable everything, so
that's what I want, you know.
I want to have a stable life.
But nothing's stopping me from
chasing a dream, you know what I
mean?
Right.
Nice, nice.
And that's why I'm here, so.
Okay, baby, what are you
going to sing?
Have you ever seen Shrek?
Yeah.
Okay, you know that
hallelujah song that plays
through there?
Mm, cool.
Okay.
♪ I heard there was ♪
♪ a secret chord ♪
♪ that David played ♪
♪ and it pleased the lord ♪
♪ but you don't really ♪
♪ care for music, do you? ♪
♪ oh, it goes like this ♪
♪ the fourth, the fifth ♪
♪ the minor fall ♪
♪ the major lift ♪
♪ the baffled king ♪
♪ composing hallelujah ♪
♪ hallelujah ♪
Okay, all right, cool, cool.
You look disappointed.
Yeah.
I usually hit that better.
Well, I gave you all I had, you
know.
Mm-hm, that's all you can do.
Sometimes routine is the secret
of life, you know?
Not always about running all
over the world, singing a song.
Yeah.
Even though I know that's a
dream, certainly was mine,
and...You know, you singing to
them down there, maybe that's
your forte.
I hate to say that, but...
Yeah, no, man.
Yeah, got to have the truth, you
know, something to build on, but
but you know, look, man,
listen, you got a great start.
I don't think it was the best
audition I've ever seen.
I think you definitely have a
voice there, but you need
clearly a lot of work on it for
something at this level.
But, I mean, you know what I'm
really impressed with is that
you knew that.
Oh, yeah.
You know, that's something to
really build on.
Plus you're just a young'un,
aren't you?
Well, 19, you know, but...
Well, let's take a vote here.
Steven, what are you saying?
I'm gonna say not yet, man,
but that don't mean to stop.
I think you have a real
pretty voice, but I think you
can work on it a little bit and,
maybe next year, come back.
Yeah, definitely come back.
Okay, guys, I really
appreciate it.
Hey, man, I love it.
Thanks for giving me the
time-oh, thanks, man.
Thank you.
See you guys next year.
All right, man.
Good luck.
Wow.
He's disappointed.
He didn't do as good as he
wanted to do.
♪ Hallelujah ♪
It's all right, you're still
my idol anyway.
Yeah.
Yes, you'll always be our idol.
Just got nervous.
Didn't do as good as I know I
can.
You went for it.
Got to chase the dream.
Gotta chase it.
Get bruises, scrapes, and
cuts along the way, but can't
stop it, you know?
That's right.
That is my dream and I
just...I kind of watched it
float away, but...What are you
going to do about it?
It slipped from my fingers.
Slipped right through 'em.
Up next...The Pittsburgh
auditions come to a dramatic
end with a story and a voice you
don't want to miss.
She could win.
So what happened?
Um...They just told me I need
to work harder and...My voice is
strong, but they want it a
little bit stronger, so...I'll
come back.
At the idol auditions, the
last thing anyone wants to hear
is...
I'm gonna say no.
I say no, not yet.
Not yet for me either.
Just keep practicing.
But after two days in
Pittsburgh,
we learned the steel
city never gives up.
I'll be back.
Everybody better be watching for
me, too, 'cause I'm coming
strong.
Just-you're going to see me.
I'm telling you, it's not the
last.
I am definitely going to get
the golden ticket today.
I'm going to say no, not for
this.
I think I'll be okay.
And after all the tears have
fallen...And the promises
made...
I promise you I can do it.
I'm sorry, baby, not today.
The Pittsburgh auditions have
come down to one final name.
Is that her name, hallie day?
Did someone just say my name?
Wow. Yeah.
How are you?
Good.
Steven was announcing you.
Well, hey, everybody.
Wow, hallie day.
Yes, Steven Tyler.
What a great name.
That is a great name.
Hallie day.
You're so beautiful.
Thank you.
Hallie, how old are you?
I'm 24 years old.
Where you from, baby?
I'm from Baltimore, Maryland.
B-more, Maryland.
What do you there?
I'm a waitress right now.
Yeah.
And-yeah, and I just got
married six months ago.
Nice.
Is he a nice guy?
He's a great guy.
He's the reason I'm here.
Music and my husband saved my
life.
At 15 years old, I dropped out
of High School.
I moved to New York and joined a
girl group called plum crazy.
I was determined to be a
superstar.
But I became very lonely, I felt
very disconnected, I was in
debt, I wasn't able to pay my
rent, I was...An addict.
I decided to leave New York.
Moving back home was really
rough.
My mom wasn't really around at
the time.
Neither was my father.
There was definitely a lack of
structure in my life.
I was very insecure and I had
very little confidence in
myself.
I didn't want to...Sing.
I didn't want to perform.
I just wanted to kill the pain,
so I went into the bathroom and
I shut the door and...Just drank
a bottle of pills.
And laid down on the floor and
felt myself starting to...Um,
drift off and, um...
You know, I ended up in the
emergency room that night.
After hitting that bottom, I
came up a little bit, and I met
a man who, years later, became
my husband.
He loves me like I've never been
loved before.
I did encourage hallie to go
audition for American idol,
'cause I just believe in her.
She has the ability to inspire a
lot of people with what she
does.
Whether I come out of that
room with the judges with tears
in my eyes 'cause I didn't make
it or I'm jumping up and down
'cause I did, he'll be there and
we'll go through it together.
We'll just take it on, whatever
it is.
No matter what happens here
or with this competition or
whatever, never stop believing
in yourself.
Thank you so much, Jennifer.
Nice.
What are you going to sing for
us today?
I'm singing I will survive
by Gloria gaynor.
Okay.
Good title.
♪ First I was afraid ♪
♪ I was petrified ♪
♪ kept thinking ♪
♪ I couldn never live ♪
♪ without you by my side ♪
♪ but then I spent ♪
♪ so many nights thinking ♪
♪ how you did me wrong ♪
♪ and I grew strong ♪
♪ and I learned how ♪
♪ to get along ♪
♪ and I, I will survive ♪
♪ oh, as long as I know ♪
♪ how to love ♪
♪ I know I'll stay alive ♪
♪ I've got all my life to live ♪
♪ and I've got all my love ♪
♪ to give ♪
♪ and I'll survive ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
Yeah.
Can you sing something else?
Really?
Yeah.
Because you haven't made up
your mind that she's amazing?
What are we doing?
'Cause I like watching her
when she sings.
You like watching her when
she sings?
How about listening to her when
Steven asked me to sing
something else.
I can-I just-I can see you.
I can see you up there, I can
see you stealing the show, on an
album cover.
I just see it.
You do have a gift, your husband
is right.
Thank you.
And you know what's wrong
with this girl, Steven?
Absolutely nothing.
That's correct!
You guys are awesome, thank
you so much.
You're going to Hollywood.
Yes, say yes.
Yes, yes, yes, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
When you got it, you got it, and
you got it, baby.
I know this is obvious, but
blondie?
Going to Hollywood!
That was a good way to close
out Pittsburgh.
I'm telling you, a good one...
that's outrageous.
That was a good one right
there, right, Stevie?
She could win.
Great.
And it's good feelings all
around as idol's first ever trip
to the steel city comes to a
close.
Oh, my God, Ryan, it's
Jennifer Lopez.
Oh, my God.
We love you!
I am glad we came to
Pittsburgh.
I feel like we got one more
today that was super, super
special.
Blonde girl.
Going to Hollywood.
Very exciting.
You know what, the plot
thickens.
Oh, my God.
Well, it wasn't just the
bloodies that got a call to
Hollywood.
In all, 38 left with golden
tickets in hand and the dream of
becoming the next American idol.
All right, America, that is
it for Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
Next stop is...
Effect in.
We're actually back this
Sunday night after the big game,
as we roll in to San Diego
for our most adventurous
audition ever.
Did you not think there'd be
jets flying over top?
And there's plenty of gold
in the California sun.
Mad, mad good.
You're gonna be big.
A special Sunday night idol
after the game.
My God.
Did I mention it's on Sunday night?
Yes!