Washington.
This guys are pumped and
ready to audition.
Here they go.
Over the years we've really got around.
Welcome to New York City
Cleveland
Austin, Texas
Minnesota.
Say hello to Los Angeles.
But isn't it time we just
get away from it all?
This is Colorado.
And this is American idol.
The family vacation.
A ritual rooted deep in American culture
so after eleven seasons
the idol family is loading
up the station wagon
and heading for the mountains.
This isn't an ordinary trip to Colorado.
Welcome to colorful Colorado.
The altitudes' car gives
me a bit of headache.
Does anyone got an Aspen?
Known for its extraordinary slopes
and breath taking beauty
Aspen, Colorado is now known as
the next stop of the
American idol's auditions.
Welcome to Colorado!
Big day here in Colorado
American idol is back
lots of us have been here since about two
two-thirty in the morning,
- it's been a while.
- For ten years.
It's chilly, our first chilly city.
This is Aspen, beautiful place
I hope beautiful people.
I think we can find our one out here.
It seems this fresh Mountain air
has bring a whole new energy for the gang.
Steady by.
It also makes us a little loopy
I mean it's just unbelievable.
The colors.
God's paintbrush.
The art of making the perfect snowball.
You are amazing.
And you are pretty.
Hey, have the vibe here, check this out.
- Good vibe.
- Look at this.
It certainly is.
Peaceful, tranquil and, oh,
so quiet.
Let's meet our first contestant of Aspen.
I'm Jenny schick I am 24 years old
I am from sterling, Virginia
I've always been overly energetic
to the point where people
have to tell me to stop
I am a music teacher.
And I teach kindergarten to six-grade.
My least favorite part
is definitely recorders.
Cause 30 recorders in one room
with beginners recorder players
makes me wanna vomit
Jenny isn't shy about much
but the prospect of meeting one judge
does have her on edge.
I will get nervous about
sing to Steven Tyler
because he's gorgeous.
Ever seen aerosmith?
No, I wish!
But I going to meet Steven Tyler!
What will your boyfriend think?
Will he be the scar of you turning red.
No. We have a list of
celebrities that we're allowed to kiss.
So who's on your list?
- Steven.
- Steven Tyler.
Lady gaga.
- That's on your list?
- Yes.
- Adam levine.
- Ok
I think that is all for me.
He has Adam levine, lady gaga and you.
- And he's not here today.
- I know! He couldn't take off the fork.
- Oh man.
- Can I get a kiss for him?
Unlucky. I tell you what,
why don't we see how it goes,
and on the ohter end there
will be lots of hugs
- ok.
- I think so
- good luck sweetheart.
- Thank you
all right.
- I'll take this one.
- Really?
Come on now.
What is your name?
I'm Jenny schick
Jenny shick? Oh, chic.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Virginia.
Sterling, Virginia.
- What you do there?
- I'm music teacher.
Holy chick!
Wow, wow, what?
You know Steven
me and my boyfriend have a list of people
who we can kiss and it's not cheating.
And you're on mine.
Wow, you better be able to sing good girl,
- do it quick, what are you singing?
- Come on
I am singing "heartbreaker
" by pat benatar.
- All right now.
- Sorry.
Your love is like a tidal wave.
Spinning over my head.
Driving me and your promises.
Better left unsaid.
You're the right kind of sinner.
To release my inner fantasy.
The invincible winner.
And you know that you
were born to be
good.
You're a heartbreaker, dream maker.
Love taker, don't you
mess around with me.
You're a heartbreaker, dream maker.
Love taker, don't you mess around.
No, no, no.
And I like it!
Yes, I kinda like it too.
Kind of wild, crazy, anything can happen.
Exactly.
- Should we take a vote?
- Yeah, let's take a vote.
I think we should just go to voting
or kissing, what are we doing Steven?
- Voting and kissing, ok?
- Voting and kissing!
I say yes.
I'm gonna say yes too.
I like your energy.
And you may kiss the judge!
- Come on.
- You may kiss the judge!
Oh my God!
I love you people.
- Don't fall.
- Don't fall!
Take that kiss to Hollywood!
Thank you!
Hollywood is that way!
I got to kiss Steven Tyler.
I think on the lips, too, didn't you?
Wait 'till your students hear about this!
- You laid one on her there.
- I'm going to get trouble for that!
- Steven, wow!
- Yes you are!
His lips are very soft.
Very soft!
And voluptuous.
So, it's a wet start to Aspen auditions.
And over the next hour,
I love your voice, so much.
Can we reach new heights
in the rocky mountains?
Of course, yes!
Or will fall into the
valley of no return.
Stay tune.
As the idol auditions explode from Aspen.
Good morning.
It's about six o'clock.
Slept wicky good, last night.
Unbeliveable, how good I've slept.
Like every auditioner knows
trying out for idol takes a
certain amount of dedication.
- Waking up at the break of dawn.
- It's 3:45.
Dressing for sucess
and making your way to the stadium,
to wait in line
with the thousands who sahre your dream
of super-stardom.
Ready to get my voice ready!
And altough he might
not have look it at 6am this morning
Curtis gray is up for the challenge
I've been playing music since
I was a young buck.
Singin' in the church with mom,
my grandmother
I'm in a five piece group
I play keyboards and vocals.
And we've doing that, a
year and a half now.
If I come out of that room
with a golden ticket and say.
"Finally! All those voice exercises!"
"Coming in hot, baby"
the good times.
That made us laugh.
Outweigh the bad.
Ooh-ooh-ooh.
And if we get.
To see tomorrow.
Well I hope it's worth.
All the wait
'cause it's so hard.
To say goodbye.
To yesterda-a-ay.
Eeeeh.
And I.
- Yo yo.
- Hey hey.
Listen, listen, very nicely done.
Song selection was brilliant.
I'm gonna start this off
I'm gonna say, definitely yes!
- Jennifer?
- Yeah!
You're good looking, I think you sing great
and I'm gonna say yes, too.
- Steven Tyler!
- Major talent, man.
I'm gonna say yes
and you're going to Hollywood!
- That's how I go!
- Thank you guys!
Here we go!
We're on a roll y'all!
- That was character...
- Really good!
Everything!
Curtis is rolling on to Hollywood
as he kicks off a hot
streak in the judging room.
I wouldn't be a man.
If I didn't feel like this.
If a woman like you.
Was anything I could resist
nice
you have a strong and
powerful voice right there.
Got some words on cardboard.
Got your picture in my hand.
Singing.
If you see this girl.
Can you tell her where I am
'cause I'm not moving no.
I'm not moving
- naturally.
- Nice.
Natural voice.
Remember.
To let it under your skin.
Then you begin.
To make it better.
Better better better.
Better better.
Yeah.
Yes!
Oh nah nah nah.
Nah-nah-nah nah
I said oh nah-nah-nah
of course, yes!
Wecolme to Hollywood!
Thank you guys very much!
- Yes.
- I agree.
Yes!
You're going to Hollywood!
Thank you guys so much!
Thank you so very much!
You are going to Hollywood, baby!
Let's "hey" for Richie!
Hoping to keep Aspen's golden ticket
rush coming,
is our next contestant
for the 19-year-old talena
singing is no longer a sister act
I have a twin sister named Stevie l.
She is going to a school for performing
she is an amazing performer
she's my best friend
Stevie and I are totaly different.
We have a different personalities
we have different voices.
Even though she is so good at
performing and acting stuff
I am more of the outgoing person
I am more of the person
that would go up to you and be like.
Hey I like your shirt.
- Like, I get goose bumbs when you sing.
- Thank you oh.
That's sort to complements me.
- Because I sing too.
- I guess that's true.
I've spent my whole entire life
living in her shadow
when I was younger, all my friends would
come up to me and tell me
how talented my sister was.
And, it sucks.
She's amazing at what she does.
And I know that.
But I can be amazing too!
I feel like she's so much better than me.
And, so glad I'm going in there alone!
I'm just gonna go in there confident
by myself, on the solo and rock it.
Come on in. Bright sunshine!
What's going on?
Not much!
What is your name?
My name is talena Ron.
But you can call me dog if you want to.
- Really?
- Yeah! Go ahead!
Hello dog,
so tell me something interesting
about yourself.
I have a twin sister
I've just been living in
her shadow for 19 years
she is so talented.
She is amazing!
But I'm ready to do it.
I'm ready to let myself shine.
Cause I don't want to be
in her shadow any more.
Cute. Cute.
So what are you going to sing today?
"Bring me some water" by Melissa Etheridge.
Nice.
Tonight I feel so weak.
But all in love is fair.
I turn the other cheek.
And I feel the slap.
And the sting.
And the foul night air.
And I know we're only human.
And I haven't got talking room.
If you ask her for another song,
I'm gonna kill you.
But tonight while I'm
making excuses.
Some other woman.
Is making love to you.
Hey, somebody bring me some water.
Can't you see.
I'm burning alive.
My baby's got another lover.
And now I don't know how.
I'm gonna survive.
Somebody bring me some water.
Can't you see.
It's out of control.
My baby's got my heart.
My baby's got my mind.
But tonight the sweet devil.
The sweet devil's got my soul.
Ok.
You are funny, man!
- I like you.
- Thank you, thank you, I try.
Good in the drama! Have you ever
recorded your voice and listened back?
- No.
- You gotta do that.
- 'Cause then you'll hear what we're hearing.
- Yeah.
All right baby, we're going
to take a quick vote, ok?
Steven, yes or no?
I'm gonna say no.
Ok.
I'm gonna say I think you adorable
but it's a no for the singing.
Love you. You're so cute, man,
we love that,
but the singing is not there yet.
Ok.
- Sorry sweetheart.
- I'm sorry baby.
It's okay.
That's okay, honey.
Didn't go your way?
No, I just...
Well, will always be my idol.
Yeah, sure.
So talena find solace with their twin
sister Stevie by her side
as they embrace the music together.
I am lonely, pondering.
Who would want to.
Join this madness who would change.
This song's just not working.
What do you want to sing then?
- I don't know.
- What's wrong?
It's just...
It wasn' working for me.
Ok.
When we come back!
Turkey has [Bleep]?
What are we talking about?
The judges aren't quite
on the same page.
You know I just want to shut you up.
But one audition will bring
them back together.
I am honored to be here,
listening to your voice.
Welcome back to Colorado
in the magnificent west.
And someone who knows this mountains
like her own backyard,
is 18-year-old hayley Smith
I live in a log cabin
in the middle of nowhere,
I love nature.
I definetly love being outdoors,
it's where I feel most at peace.
You could say I guess.
Where I enjoy the most of
my reckoned get away.
The landscape is to die for.
If you would die for anything.
It's beautiful.
And there is a reason why she needs that peace
and quiet that only mother nature can bring.
I've acquired three new jobs
I house-clean and am a bussel
for a restaurant
and I'm a vegetarian working
at the meat department.
You're making the sausage?
Yeah.
What is in the sausage?
Ground and free-think.
This is the reason you're a vegetarian.
Even more so now.
Let's see if you can get another job
here as a singer.
That sound's a plan.
Well, all right.
- Thank you.
- Head on in.
- Hello.
Come on in, what's your name?
Hayley Smith is my name.
And hayley how old are you?
I am 18 years old.
Tell me about yourself,
are you a performer,
do you play?
Yeah, I do.
I feel like a 70's vibe from you.
- A '60s, 70's vibe.
- Wow! Yeah!
I really do enjoy that era of music.
What are you gonna sing today?
Rufus and chaka Khan,
"tell me something good"
yeah! Come on written
by the great Stevie wonders here we go.
Yeah, yeah.
You ain't got no kind
of feeling inside.
What I got is sure to set
your stuff right on fire.
What I got will knock
all your pride aside.
Tell me something good.
Tell me that you like me yeah.
Come on tell me that
you love me yeah
I just laughing because
you put in your own spin
on a great R&B classic with chaka.
- You're doing it in like more of flower...
- Johnny mitchel way!
Johnny mitchel sort of way!
But you know what?
It's not, like, perfect for the song.
But I actually kinda like that!
- I love your voice so much.
- Thank you.
You're right at my era.
And I'm honoured to be here.
Listening to your voice.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome
I bet you're even more comfortable
when you have a guitar or,
you have music around you too, huh?
Yeah. Definitely.
I just love the commitment to you
just being who you are.
And just the natural gift.
We always say to people,
make it your own.
You don't need to sound like the record.
Yeah.
And, you know, you defintely been doing
your own thing with this. I love that.
I love that.
Let's take a vote.
Jennifer, yes or no?
I'm gonna say yes,
I want to see you more.
Randy. I'm gonna say yes.
Steven?
I'm gonna say so yes.
- And what that's mean, Steven?
- You're going to Hollywood.
Thank you so much!
Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
- A real flower chow.
- She is...
- Yes.
And now all these new jobs
you got leave behind.
Ooh. Darn.
At 18, that's impressive.
- Flowr chow.
- Uniqueness.
She's not following any
of the artists out ther.
She's just herself.
Warm weather and Hollywood,
here I come!
Looks like the rockie Mountain
originality is showing up!
After the break:
Colorado leaves us high and dry.
Ok. Is that for real?
I hope is no.
Plus, one contestant inspire us all.
I want to show people that bipolar
doesn't define who you are.
- Beautiful.
- So beautiful.
Beautiful!
Welcome back to Aspen!
After a busy morning.
We are done with lunching
and ready to go.
- Great lunch.
- Maybe that means we're gonna have a good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
But looks like one of
our judges is stil...
And this rockstar certainly knows
the importance of a balance diet to
make it through the day.
Now let's see if Steven can stomach
what our
next contestant is serving up.
My name is Elena snare, I'm 22,
and I'm from Florence, Colorado.
I am a bartender-waitress
at a bar that is famous for selling
rockie-Mountain oysters.
Most people might be like:
"Oh, oysters from the sea."
But they're actually bull testies'
which is something a lot of people are like,
couldn't get, and not really into it.
But we got a lot of regulars in there.
If you are a little adventurous,
you'll try it.
Here we go.
At least once.
Hi, what's your name?
Elena snare.
- What a great musical name.
- Snare.
What do you do?
I'm actually a bartend-waitress
at a bar that is famous for selling
rockie-Mountain oysters.
What is that?
- They're bull testies' actually.
- No!
We actually have Buffalo
and Turkey ones as well.
Yeah.
Ah, turkeys have [Bleep]?
They do, but actually they're internals
so you don't get to see them.
Gaable gaable.
What are we talking about?
- True.
- Yes.
What are you singing?
I'm gonna sing "jolene" by Dolly parton.
- Do it.
- Good.
Jolene jolene jolene jolene.
I'm begging of you please
don't take my man.
Jolene jolene jolene jolene.
Please don't take him
just because you can.
Your beauty is...
Have you eaten those preary oysters?
I have.
You're all over the place with
melody and it's just...
It's bad.
I mean, I really like you
as a person, I think you're cool.
Singing is just not your thing, man.
It was terrible.
Can I sing something else?
Just try to...
No. I think we heard,
I think we heard.
- I thinks we're okay.
- I think we heard what's going on.
- Steven, would you say yes or no?
- No.
It's a no from me.
Thank you.
Seems like Jennifer has had enough
animal talk.
No, and no.
Let's see if the next country girl
can win her over.
- Hi.
How are you?
Great, man. What's your name?
Shelby.
Yeah. Where're you from?
Mankato, minessota.
And how much do you love to sing?
I love it, you don't even understand.
It kind gets me emotional these days.
I don't know why.
Cause it's made so happy and
gotten me over so much stuff,
it's kind my safe harbor.
Like what? What do you mean?
I was diagnosed bipolar in march,
but I have been strugling with depression
since forth grade
American idol has gave me a reason
to stand in my meds,
I wasn't focusing on sing with them,
because I didn't really care.
When I'm off my meds, I'm incoherent
and...
- She's not the same person.
- I'm not myself. Yeah.
She doesn't have the
light, you know, in her.
There's been times where
I've had hypomenic episodes,
I'll be shaking, I'll stutter
I can't control my body.
And my mom will be like:
"Well, let's sing together."
And I'll sing and...
And, like, it really helps.
American idol has given us
something to believe in.
And, uh... it's really
important to me because
I do wanna show people that.
Bipolar doesn't define who you are.
I can't even tell you
how proud of her I am.
I just stomp, feel like I could have
my daughter back a little bit, so..
I love you.
Young mom on her own.
She needs a little help
got nowhere to go.
She's looking for a job
looking for a way out.
Cause a halfway house.
Will never be a home.
At night she whispers.
To her baby girl.
Someday we'll find a place
here in this world.
This is our temporary home.
It's not where I belong.
Windows and rooms.
That we're passing through.
This is my temporary home.
- Beautiful!
- So beautiful.
Beautiful!
Something going on here in Aspen!
I got tears to my eyes!
- I love that.
- Got tears to my eyes.
I mean, I love that song too, but...
Somebody's got to really sing it so,
you know...
Do you know what's cool about you?
To me is that you got a great voice,
dude, you're good to go,
'cause you feel us as a singer.
So I love that.
- The sound of your voice.
- Dude!
And the little rasp in it,
it's just all in the right place.
- Just so beautiful, I just love it so much.
- The potential, yeah...
- Let's take a vote Jennifer.
- Please.
I think everybody knows, yes. Big yes.
- One hundred percent yes!
- Big yes.
Yes, big huge yes!
You're going to Hollywood, baby!
Shelby Lynn at Hollywood!
- See you guys!
- See you later!
- Awesome!
- She is great.
Another star!
That's huge potential, right there.
When the sound of somebody's voice
is so beautiful.
And that's a tough song to sing.
Everyone told me I couldn't do it.
And I was like, you know what?
I'm gonna prove y'll wrong someday.
I'm gonna do it.
See you later minne "snow" tta...
I'm going to be at Hollywood!
Hollywood Hollywood Hollywood!
When we come back,
one contestant.
Just may have what Jennifer
is searching for.
You are a lover!
Uh, yeah, I'm a lover
and not a fighter.
I can tell.
And... where did this guy come from?
I'm originally from Davenport, Iowa.
Davenport, Iowa?
What is this?
This is crazy!
Welcome back to "American idol"
where is turning in a bit of winter
wonderland here in Aspen.
Let's hope this cold snap isn't affecting
the judges inside the audition room.
We got it?
We're good. Thanks Ron.
Every guy grab a girl.
Everywhere around the world.
Keep dancing.
If I go crazy then will you
still call me superman.
Yeah.
Ok. Is that for real?
I hope is no.
Just as long.
As you stand.
Stand by me.
Now is death.
- Is that enough for you?
- Yeah.
That rough path has left
the judges felling cold.
But maybe our next contestant
can break the ice
with something new.
My name is jairon Jackson
I'm 19 years old,
and I'm from Denver, Colorado.
My song choice is actually an original
piece that I wrote myself.
I had to cope with people, tell me
I shouldn't sing it
because it's not something
that's known.
But I've a lot of fate in this song.
I've a lot of faith in it.
Door to stardom!
Jairon's door to stardom.
Yo, come on in, man!
Come on in, come on in!
- How are you?
- I'm doing beautiful!
- What is your name?
- Jairon "don't forget the" Jackson.
- Yeah baby!
- Don't forget the Jackson.
Brothers!
- Another Jackson in the house...
- Yes, yes, yes.
What you gonna sing, man?
I'm start of with an original piece
that I wrote
about a year ago, is called "so hard"
- do it.
- All right.
I'm so scarred.
And I don't know what to do.
I'm so lost in love and
I don't know about you.
So tell me baby.
Are we in this together.
Supposed to be my friend.
Through the stormy weather.
I wonder.
Do you feel the same pain.
I'm crying from my heart.
Trying to love you through my vans.
Have you ever loved someone so deep
he great love ah.
I can't even sleep.
It's so hard.
I can't feel my heart any more.
Do you want to love no no no.
- Nice!
- Very nice. Very nice!
- Original too man.
- You ready for the charts already, dawg.
You like, let me get my own!
Crazy dude, right there!
- Thank you. I appreciate it.
- Crazy.
You're a lover!
Uh, yeah. I'm lover
not a fighter.
- Definetly.
- I can tell.
- We take a little vote?
- Yeah
Steven?
- Beautiful, I loved it. Yes.
- Thank you.
- I think tou got some special there.
- Thank you, thank you.
- And the fact that you wrote that song as well.
- Thank you.
- You know, the melodie, everything about it.
- It's a good song.
- Yeah.
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
- Also a yes from me too, man!
- "So hard" it's good.
On three!
One, two...
Hollywood!
I just want to say you're beautiful.
All you guys are beautiful!
- Thank you.
- Thank you, man!
- I love you.
- Continue the luck, man!
Tickets is that way!
- I'm going to get to Hollywood!
- Yo yo!
You're gonna leave me hanging?
That kid is a real artist!
That kid is a real deal right there.
I'm coming!
Let's go!
Oh, snab is that?
This is not good, is it?
Sorry.
My bad!
Coming up, one contestant creates.
A continental divide
between the judges.
That turns me off.
I just want to shut you up.
Plus...
Who is ready.
To battle.
Magic cyclops?
Bring in the kraken!
Isn't it "release the kraken"?
- It's "release".
- "Release the kraken"!
As we look out upon the ever
changing Colorado landscape.
We hope our luck will continue
here in Aspen.
So while the auditions push on,
and the judges prepare for yet,
another serenade.
Our next contestan is ready for her
moment in the spotlight.
My name is Angie zeiderman
I'm 25, and I'm a waitress and
a part-time singer.
People would call me lady gaga sometimes.
When they see me walking down the street.
She makes everything a performance
and that's sort of
how I like to sing.
I would look to open for her
and then
be best friends with her.
I am the next American idol
I think because there hasn't really
been anybody else like me.
- You seem very confident.
- Thanks.
It's working.
It is time for vintage glitter queen
on "American idol" and
I'm here to provide that for you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you.
- I'm so excited to be here.
- I like the dress.
- Thank you.
- Way cute dress. And the hair.
- And the hair.
And the earrings.
The hair matches the dress, exactly.
- What is your name?
- Angie zeiderman.
- And Angie, how old are you.
- 25.
What kind of artist do you see
yourself being, you know?
I love the lady gaga.
'Cause I love to put on the whole show
I like to sing and dance
and have the outift...
Ok. Well sing a little song for us.
All right.
Then I was just a
little girl in Sweden.
My thoughtful mother
gave me this advice.
If nature blesses you
from top to bottom.
Show that top to bottom
don't think twice.
When you got it, share it.
Let the public feast
upon your charm.
Buh-nee-nah-nee-nee.
Dah-dah dah-dah.
Don't be shy be bold and cute.
Dah-ch-ch.
She is not shy.
Show the boys your birthday suit.
When you got it.
Shout out.
Hoora-a-ay.
- Okay.
- Thank you, baby.
I usually get down a little more.
- But this dress is a little constricted.
- We get now, we get it.
- I don't do just show tunes.
- No, no.
What I don't want to know about all that
the show tunes definetly it turns me off.
But any way, let's vote.
- It does.
- I love musicals.
- I love musicals but...
- Let me tell you...
- Musicals performers...
- I do not like her vibrato.
How many people came in here and
could do what she just did?
- Not many.
- No, no.
- Not many!
- I love that.
Do you wanna see me doing something
that's totally not show tune at all?
- No, no, no. I'm good.
- Yes!
I just want to shut you up.
- I'm good, dawg. I'm good.
- You wanna hear it?
I'm coming back someday.
Come what may to blue by you.
Where the folks are fine.
And the world is mine
on blue by you.
- I like it.
- I do too.
Oh, that boy of mine by my side.
The silver moon and
the evening tide.
Oh, some sweet day gonna take away.
This hurting inside.
- Ok. That really change my mind, actually.
- Ah, yeah?
- That was nice.
- Great little voice, girl.
I like it. You're in your own world.
- She doesn't have one wounds of nerves in her.
- I love her!
Jennifer?
- Yes.
- Steven?
- So yes!
- You're going to Hollywood!
Hollywood, baby!
- This is a little spit fire.
- Yeah, she spit fire.
I love her.
She is definetly on her own world.
In Hollywood you'll expect to see more
of this, and more of this...
She has such a strong
voice with a good tone.
To me, what turns me off about
all musical is that.
That vibrato. I just got, it turns me, it's like graving
in my nerves, like fingernails on the chalkboard.
- It's learned.
- It's learned, that's what...
- That kind of crap.
- But it's hard to get a...
- I like her, she's like interesting.
- No, she was cooler, yeah.
See you in Hollywood.
Coming up, as we near the end of
our Aspen stage.
We have one last question.
Do you...
Believe...
In magic?
Scared the [Bleep] of mem
I don't know what happened!
Welcome back to Aspen, we're near in the
end of our day here,
and, while it's still the picture
of peace and tranquility outside.
Back in the audition room, it's
turned in to party centrum.
But like they say, every party has
a trooper.
My name is magic cyclops
I'm from Davenport, Iowa.
We have riverboat gambling.
I had to personally leave Davenport
because I owe'd a lot of
gambling debt.
We should be probably blurring
my face out of this point,
because there are
people looking for me.
No one to talk to me
because I'm frightening
and I look homeless.
How is it going?
I have eleven thousand air-guitars.
And I know there is a guy in Belgium
that has, I think, five more than me.
A master at air guitar.
Magic has had years to prep for
thir audiction.
Let's do this thing!
I'm not ready at all!
But that's when I did some
of my most dangerous work.
There is a storm brewing,
and it's called magic cyclops
and it's coming for them.
- Bring in the kraken!
- Isn't it "release the kraken"?
- It's "release".
- "Release the kraken"!
Dude, okay. So first of all.
Who are you?
I'm the thy magic cyclops.
How old are you magic cyclops?
It's not polite to ask a lady
her age.
- A ladie?
- Yes.
- A ladie with the beard!?
- Bearded lady, yes.
What? What? What?!
Come on, Aspen!
It's a weird city.
- Where are you from?
- I'm originally from Davenport, Iowa.
- Davenport, Iowa!
- This isn't Iowa accent...
I grew up extremly poor...
And we only got the local pbs station,
which massively aired BBC programing.
So that's why you're speaking
with the accent?
- Yes.
- That's hilarious!
What are we doing here man!?
What, on earth, could you be singing today?
Well, it's judges choice day!
So you have the choice between
Neil diamond or James buffay.
- Who?
- James "buffay".
Jimmy buffet.
- So we gotta "margaritaville" or...
- Is it buffett?
What's the other song by Neil diamond?
"Cracklin 'rose"
let's hear it.
- This is really silly, I just want to tell you that.
- Yes.
All right.
Cracklin 'Rosie get on board.
We're gonna ride till there
ain't no more to go.
Takin' it slow.
And oh lord don't you know.
I'll have me a time
with a poor man's lady.
Hitchin 'on a twilight train.
Ain't nothin' here that
I care to take along.
But maybe a song.
Sing when I won't.
Don't need to say please to a man.
- Dear can you sing something else?
- Really?
- I can.
- Really, no Jennifer? Really?
- Yes.
- I can.
Wastin 'away again
in margaritaville.
Searching for my lost
shaker of salt.
Some people say.
That there'sa woman to blame.
But I know it's my own damn fault.
- I'll have to go to the bathroom.
- Ok.
- I'll let you guys do this, Jennifer, Steven.
- Actually I also have to go to the bathroom.
- I'm gonna go to the bathroom. This is a joke!
- Wait! Hold on!
It scared the [Bleep] out of me!
Jennifer, Steven; Yes or no?
- Is that your [Bleep]?
- No?
- He should do another songs!
- One, two, three...
No!
At least take the glasses off.
They're prescription!
Let's see your eyes!
I have no eyes!
- What is this!?
- I have no soul!
- This is crazy.
I'm going to the bathroom!
All right, I've never
take what just gone on.
- I don't know what is going on.
- I don't know either.
- All right.
- Let's get a drink!
I don't know how what happened.
No, really. I literally don't.
If someone could explain it to me
that would be apreciatted.
Steven, I've helped put
you where you are at.
Because I own several aerosmith cd"s.
So do a brother favor?
Call me!
Can you guys play "the incredible hulk"
theme music while I'm walking away?
Thank you.
So, felling a little dejected
magic cyclops signs off.
And the time has come
for us to do the same.
Our get-away to the mountains
was certainly worth it...
Aspen has been good to us 'yo.
As 31 singers are soaring
ro Hollywood.
You know, let me start this.
Yes!
- Jennifer?
- Yes!
- Where is she going?
- Hollywood!
All right!
Our work is done in Colorado!
Ryan I want to make
some predictions running.
It's gonna be a hot season though.
I'm going to Hollywood!
- Goodnight everybody!
- Peace!
Tomorrow night!
We touch down in Texas!
This is American idol and NASA.
Take you beyond earth to
the international space station!
Space city brings out
the brightest stars!
Take a voice like that,
right up to the top!
And a maybe a few
form another planet.
What is this show?
After this trip to Texas.
Judges are gonna need
their space.
Are you guys crazy?
- Say you're sorry.
- For what?
Houston...
We have a problem.
Somebody help me!