[indistinct chatter]
What the hell is
going on out there?
- Somebody stole the rig.
- Again?
Hey, where do you guys
think you're going?
We'll be back in
two minutes max.
Antoine is going to show
us his new motorcycle.
Great.
We always need organ donors.
Yeah, someone stole your rig.
Yeah, you weren't
watching the screens?
- How'd you miss it?
- Oh, I saw it pull out.
But I figured you were in it.
Why'd you leave the keys in it?
- It's protocol.
- No, it's not.
That's what I said.
Yes, it is.
And I... who steals a fucking
ambulance at 10:00 a.m.?
Easy... junkies, meth heads,
thinking they just stole
the candy store.
Or a psych patient
kicked loose last night.
Y'all don't know.
That thing is getting
stripped, chopped, and shipped.
- That's a pro job.
- Shut the fuck up.
Maybe another driver took it.
Did you call your dispatch?
Of course we called
our dispatch.
- Did you call the cops?
- I can,
but there are two having
breakfast in the cafeteria.
Help yourself.
Hey.
I'm good. Thanks.
Protocol.
Come on.
I'd put $20
on the psych patient.
Oh, I'll take that action.
Hey, do we have crutches?
Yeah, ortho locker
just restocked.
Okay, great.
Can you bring back
Sherry Davis next?
Sterno mom with the hand burn?
- Mm-hmm.
- She split.
Shit.
When?
I gave the kids
two breakfasts each
off the boarders' cart,
and they left.
In school probably?
Did she say anything about
coming back for wound care?
Not to me.
Fuck.
I need rooms cleared
and cleaned,
so I'm shuffling the deck.
Yeah, but why are you
moving him into Pedes?
I'm just about to extubate him.
There's no kids
in there at the moment.
The family can have
some privacy.
There's nice pictures
on the wall.
What's the problem?
There's no problem.
Mrs. Smith does not
need a cardiac monitor.
She can get her Vanco
in the hall.
We've got one
tele-bed available.
Let's give it to Otis before
someone else snags it.
- Yep.
- Leave the family
in Central 7 alone
until nuclear medicine
is ready to take the kid.
There's no sense in
moving them twice.
Aye-aye, Cap.
[chuckles]
Hey, Robby.
- You're going to extubate?
- Yes.
Good.
You shouldn't have intubated.
Yeah, I remember
you saying that,
just like it was this morning.
You want me to do it?
No, why?
- Adamson.
- [woman screaming in distance]
- Jesus!
- Okay.
There's something
moving in there!
- Ma'am, hold still.
- Get it out!
I can't help you if you
keep moving your head.
Get it fucking out!
I can feel it!
Arthropod in the EAC.
Oh, my God.
[sighs] I better get in there.
Yeah.
[monitor beeping]
How long will he live
without the oxygen?
It's difficult to say.
Once the tube comes out,
it could be anywhere
from 30 minutes
to several hours.
When I extubate, we're gonna
suction the back of his throat.
We're going to give him some
glycopyrrolate drops,
which will cut down
on his secretions.
He'll get morphine for any pain.
[monitor beeping rapidly]
And we'll give him
some oxygen in his nose
as a comfort measure.
[beeping stops]
Jesus.
I don't... I don't think that
I can go through with this.
I mean, this...
this is happening?
Like, now?
Like... like, today?
We... we just decided
that Dad is gonna
die in this room,
in a room with cartoon
forest animals all over it?
If you think about it,
it's kind of perfect.
[chuckles softly]
Our... our dad worked on
"Mister Rogers' Neighborhood"
the whole time
that we were growing up.
Oh, no kidding.
That's very cool.
"Mister Rogers,"
the television program?
- That's right.
- Here in Pittsburgh?
At WQED on Fifth Ave
for 33 years.
Dad worked with Jack Guest,
the art director.
So he helped, um,
paint and build all those sets.
I don't think
that I can do this.
[crying]
Okay.
Just to be clear,
your father is dying,
and you're choosing to allow
that to occur naturally,
rather than subject him
to a torturous amount
of procedures, which would
only delay the inevitable.
I just thought that
it would be different.
And I thought that there'd...
we'd have more time.
Is your family religious?
Oh.
God, no.
No God.
[chuckles]
I had a teacher, mentor,
who told me about
a Hawaiian ritual
called ho'oponopono,
or "the four things
that matter most."
It's basically just
a few key things
that we can say when
we're saying goodbye
to a loved one that
can really help
at the early stages of loss.
What are they?
They're gonna sound
really simple,
but I swear I've seen them work.
Okay.
I love you.
Thank you.
I forgive you.
Please forgive me.
That's... that's it?
Yep.
Told you it was simple.
[sighs]
Okay.
Mr. Spencer, I'm gonna
take this tube out
of your throat now.
What I want you to do is
to take a very deep breath.
- Breathe in.
- [inhales]
And now blow it out.
[exhales]
There we go.
[choking]
[coughing]
[suction hissing]
Okay.
I'm gonna give you
some oxygen in your nose.
[labored breathing]
A couple drops
under your tongue.
- [sighs]
- You okay?
Tired.
You can rest.
Close your eyes if you want.
Your children are here.
Uh, Dad, you just...
you just rest, okay?
We're right here.
I'm right here.
[cries softly]
[labored breathing]
Come find me.
Okay, take a deep breath for me.
Jesus, everybody's going
to this concert tonight.
I wonder if there's
any decent passes left.
Another deep breath.
[phone dings]
Oh, my God, Jenna.
You're never gonna
believe who DM'd me.
I fucking told you
this would happen.
I'm sure Jenna is happy
you're here to support her,
but perhaps you could wait
outside until we finished.
Excuse me?
Excuse me, I'm in the
middle of an examination.
Yeah, and I'm gonna stay
with my friend for as long
as she needs me.
I'm the one who
brought her here.
Gold star for you.
Hey. It's fine.
I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
[phone buzzing and dinging]
Thank you.
I wanted her to leave.
How are you doing?
I called Nick's dad an asshole
and told him to go ask his son.
Why would I say that?
Uh, why don't you
tell me about school?
What are you studying?
What?
Do you do any sports?
Are you into any
extracurricular activities?
I don't...
I don't know why
you're asking me that.
Well, it's important that
you focus on the good things
in your life right now.
How?
A boy... a very sweet boy
that I barely even knew is dead.
And I just fucking
made it worse.
You just need to...
And his father thinks
I killed him,
and you're asking me
if I play sports?
Jenna, Jenna, I can tell
how upset you are right now.
I see how painful this is.
We don't even do drugs.
We were studying.
I mean, how does that happen?
I can't imagine how hard
this must be for you.
I just really want to go home.
Well, your vitals are excellent.
When your parents arrive,
they can take you.
Thank you.
We're here if you need anything.
Oh, well, that went south.
A couple of observations?
Please.
How thin is your skin?
- Rhino.
- Good.
Distraction is
a terrible strategy.
When a patient says,
"I'm hurting,"
we don't respond,
"What's your major?"
Oh, I wasn't
trying to diminish...
Additionally,
"I" statements work better
than "you" statements.
"I can see how painful this is"
acknowledges
the reality of the
situation and invites
further examination.
"You need to move on"
has the opposite effect.
Understood, but in
my personal experience...
Your personal experience
isn't germane here.
Germane?
Relevant, pertinent,
appropriate.
Well, I respectfully disagree.
My life gives me
a perspective that's...
Are you aware you have an
aggressive energy, Trinity?
Even this conversation
feels confrontational.
We bring our education
to the job, not our baggage.
Got it.
Thank you. Will do.
Good news or bad news first?
What's the good news?
Ear canal is numb.
Simple flush with saline
will fix the problem.
What's the bad news?
You've got a dead bug
in your ear.
[liquid squirting]
A cockroach.
[screaming]
We were in here for maybe
35, 40 minutes, tops.
I go outside, it's gone.
Seriously, there's
nothing on the radio?
Not yet.
The keys were inside?
Yes, I leave them in there in
case somebody needs to move it.
You're not supposed
to leave the keys.
That's what I said.
You take the keys
so nobody steals it.
So what the fuck
is security for?
Oh, I'm about to show you.
- Oh, yeah?
- Hey, guys,
can we congregate
somewhere else?
Give a little room.
We got a new guest checking in.
Guys, Ahmad, we got to
keep this area clear.
- Everybody, please.
- Hey, 5 bucks on "Chop Shop."
Wendell Stone, 52,
chief rigger from Pitfest.
- Isolated trauma...
- Get Cecil and Tony.
To the left chest...
Tell them to bring their guys.
When a speaker tower
came down on him.
Looks like multiple
rib fractures.
Pulse 110, BP 130 over 85...
They gotta go back
over everything.
Decent sats at 96.
- 50 of fent in the field.
- Got it?
How we doing, Mr. Stone?
Mr. Stone was my dad.
Just Stone.
[man screaming]
Damn.
They woke the Kraken.
When's he due
for his next round?
[indistinct yelling]
40 minutes ago.
- Perfect.
- [muffled yelling]
Mr. Driscoll?
Mr. Doug Driscoll?
About fucking time.
See you later, suckers.
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
"Jiya" Yi Chen?
I have some Tylenol
for "Jiya" Yi Chen.
Yes, please.
Over here.
Jia Yi.
Jia Yi Chen.
Here you go.
How much longer until
we can see the doctor?
Uh, we have to wait
for a bed to open up.
Might be a little while.
Pretty popular today.
The medicine should help.
Four of morphine.
No abdominal tenderness.
- What have we got?
Jinx, you owe me a Coke.
- Isolated chest trauma with...
- Stop.
I want to hear from Dr. Santos.
Isolated chest trauma
with obvious flail chest.
No hemopneumo on POCUS.
Good sats and vitals.
Excellent presentation.
Sir, I'm Dr. Garcia
from Surgery.
I need surgery?
Not necessarily.
No blood in the belly on FAST.
- [groans]
- You got this?
Abdomen is benign.
CT chest, abdomen,
pelvis with contrast,
which I trust way more than
your ultrasound skills.
[exclaims and groans]
And more morphine,
for God's sake.
No, no, no, no.
Don't knock me out.
I gotta stay on top of
the crew doing the put in.
- The what?
- The festival.
We'll block all the nerves
going to the broken ribs.
Roll to the right.
You'll be awake and pain-free.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about. [groans]
That's a ton of
intercostal blocks.
Nope, one shot.
Serratus anterior
blocks down to T-9.
You kids and your
crazy regional blocks.
Dr. Santos, call me
with the CT results.
Extension 1121.
Gabe's the same age that I was
when we made our first layout.
You remember that, Dad?
The... the two level track
in the basement
of the Clovis house?
- [weakly] O.
- That's right.
Yeah, it was an O gauge.
It limited the cars
we could use, but...
[sighs]
That layout was a beauty.
Hmm.
Doctor, does that
sound he's making
mean it could be any minute?
No, no.
It just means that
he's having trouble
handling his secretions.
[raspy breathing]
Mr. Spencer,
this should help.
[suction hissing]
I'm also going to give you
a scopolamine patch
behind your ear.
That will cut down
on his secretions
for the next 24 hours.
Do you think he has 24 hours?
There's really no way to know.
Let's give another
two of morphine.
Repeat PRN.
We're going to
give him something
to keep him comfortable.
Doctor, what were
those four things again?
I love you. Thank you.
I forgive you.
Please forgive me.
That's easy.
I love you, Dad.
I've loved every minute we've
gotten to spend together.
Thank you.
You're the best dad
a boy could have wanted.
You... you never missed a game.
You always made time
for me to play catch
or to build models or...
[raspy breathing]
When you helped me
with my homework...
[chuckles]
[high-pitched ringing]
Or when we would wake up
before everybody else...
[voice fading]
And make sandwiches.
[tense music]
[monitor beeping rapidly]
♪ ♪
[high-pitched ringing]
Be right back.
[breathing deeply]
[clears throat]
[ringing stops]
[breathing heavily]
[breathing deeply]
[laughs]
[sighing]
[unzipping]
[urinating]
[sighs]
They spotted it.
East on 376.
Ho, ho!
Oh, let's go.
It is on now.
$15 on crash,
another $5 on junkies.
Give me $8 on catch
with another...
Uh-uh-uh.
Multiples of 5 only.
I'm not touching
your stripper bills.
Yo, what's that shit?
Hey!
Wanna keep it down?
This is a hospital,
not Rivers Casino.
Keep talking.
I'ma find Robby.
Mm-hmm.
I'm alive!
Psych wanted to
transition him to oral meds.
There's an order for an
olanzapine tablet at 9:30 a.m.
- [screaming]
- Yeah, that's on us.
I've been with criticals
all morning.
He needs to go upstairs
to behavioral health.
We're too busy down here
to dispense
psych meds on a schedule.
Understood.
What options are we left with?
Either we let him
tire himself out,
or we go in and stick him.
I'm worried he's
gonna hurt himself.
He's in partial soft restraints.
What we really need is
a Pavulon blow dart.
[blows]
[clicks tongue]
Hold it.
You caught me!
And I was almost over the wall.
Go easy on me, warden.
I need an order for an
agitated psych patient.
Been here for days.
Methamphetamine
induced psychosis.
The Kraken?
We really shouldn't
call him that.
- How about a B-52?
- No, no, no.
That would take way too long,
tie up the staff.
- QTC?
- Normal.
Five of midazolam,
five of Haldol, and Mister...
Krakozhia.
- You're joking.
- No.
Mr. Krakozhia will be out
like a light in under a minute.
[baby crying]
It hardly seems as offensive
to call him Kraken
if his name is actually...
- Irritable five-month-old.
- Clearly.
I'll be right there.
Um, I need more coffee.
You doing okay, Cap?
Yeah, why?
Can't have you
going over the wall.
Tomas Cordera,
Mr. Tomas Cordera,
please come to the window.
I have your insurance card.
Tomas Cordera.
- Yes?
- Cordera.
It's actually Tasha Cordera,
and "Ms."
Okay.
Do you want to come on back?
Go through those doors.
You cut your arm?
- Yes.
- Okay.
No problem.
Hi.
I'm Dr. McKay.
This is Victoria Javadi,
student doctor.
Hello.
Tasha.
Hi.
Sorry for the long wait, Tasha.
Do you mind if I
take a quick peek?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
All right.
Not too bad.
Definitely gonna need
a few stitches, though.
Why don't you come on back?
And we'll get you
patched up, okay?
All right.
Okay.
How big is the pneumothorax?
Got it. Thanks.
What's a pneumothorax?
Uh, just a little air leaking
from the big bruise
in your lung.
Oh.
Getting short of breath here.
Pain?
No, all that's gone.
Good. The block worked.
Sats are down to 85 on 5 liters.
His lung contusions
need some help.
Start BiPAP, 10 over 5.
That'll open up the
bruised parts of your lung.
Thanks.
Good news is,
you don't need surgery,
but I'll let Dr. Garcia
know about the CT.
Oh. She likes you.
[laughs]
I met her two hours ago.
[chuckles]
Must have made
a strong first impression.
[baby crying]
Any fever, vomiting, or cough?
None of that.
Good feedings?
Was she full term at birth?
Normal delivery.
Childhood vaccines?
Um, yeah, two months
and four months.
To get an accurate
temperature...
What's your
differential diagnosis?
Gotta rule out the worst first.
We need to check
with a rectal thermometer.
Is that really necessary?
It's really important.
Ooh, I know.
I know.
We gotta rule out any
serious bacterial infection,
sepsis, pneumonia,
pyelo, appendicitis, meningitis.
You think she has meningitis?
No, we're just discussing
hypothetical possibilities.
Temp 99.2.
Making meningitis
extremely unlikely.
Heart rate 164, sats 99.
This is Dr. Robby,
our senior physician.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Hi, hi.
Afebrile, alert, good vitals.
Doctors Mohan and King were
just about to start
their physical.
Why don't you go check on our
students, and I'll handle this?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
[crying continues]
So why are you
sticking me again?
You came in an hour
after the chest pain.
If it's a heart attack,
it can take
more time for the heart damage
to show up in the blood...
put your finger on that...
even with the normal EKG.
That's why we repeat the test.
Lift your arm up.
Thank you.
All right, let's get you back
to the waiting room.
- What? No.
- Yeah.
No, all I've been
doing is waiting.
I'm supposed to
see a doctor now.
Soon.
I'll let you know.
[laughs incredulously]
This is a fucking joke.
Yeah, it's good to laugh.
Laughing our way to being
a third world country.
Remind you of home?
Okay, I know we're not supposed
to pick favorites here.
I'ma keep my eye on you.
Yeah.
You do that.
Oh, yeah.
So, Tasha, it was a decanter?
A beautiful Baccarat carafe.
I was, uh, showing a
colleague how to polish it,
and the neck broke
with my arm still inside...
- Mm.
- So not my finest.
Did it shatter?
No, no, it cracked
cleanly in two.
But as a reflex,
I jerked my arm back,
and that's what did it.
Reflexes, I have
regretted a few of my own.
Good.
Now inject to other side.
Single layer, straight edges,
about as straightforward
as it gets.
Oh, good.
That's a relief.
- [monitors beeping rapidly]
- What's going on?
Hypoxic to 78.
BP's crashing.
Systolic's 82.
Pulse is thready.
I should intubate.
Does he need a massive
transfusion protocol?
No. Absent breath sounds
on the left,
tracheal deviation to the right.
14 gauge angiocath now.
Put him on a non-rebreather.
What are you doing?
Tension pneumothorax from
the BiPAP's positive pressure.
[groans]
[grunts]
[hissing]
You hear that?
Who the hell ordered BiPAP?
Garcia?
No, his... his sats were down.
I did.
You did?
Without running it by me?
Can I put in a chest tube?
He doesn't need a chest tube.
He needs a pigtail catheter.
And I'll be doing it.
Sats and pressure
both coming up.
Draw up 75 of ketamine.
[monitor beeping steadily]
Why is she still crying?
Fontanelle soft and flat.
Pupils equal and reactive,
tracking across midline.
Dr. Mohan,
keep it focused, please.
Mucous membranes nice and moist.
[baby wailing]
Hard to hear over the crying,
but lungs are clear.
Heart rate's tachy but normal.
Soft abdomen, no obvious
signs of tenderness.
- So basically a normal exam.
- Then what's wrong?
Give us a little time
to finish our exam.
Yeah, I know. I know.
What am I looking for,
Dr. King?
Uh, cellulitis?
Edema from nephrotic syndrome?
- Diagnosis made.
- What is it?
Hair tourniquet.
Mother's wet hair can wrap
around the toe multiple times.
When it dries, it tightens
and cuts off circulation.
My hair?
I... I showered
before nursing her.
Easy to miss, Mom.
But we caught it early,
so there won't be
any permanent damage to the toe.
Treatment, Dr. Mohan?
Uh, it's too tight for scissors.
- Do we have Nair?
- We do indeed.
Nair?
Like from the drugstore?
10 minutes,
should dissolve it right off
and stop the crying.
[baby crying]
Hey, you're okay.
- [indistinct shouting]
- What's up?
We're gonna give
the wild one a shot.
Have the order, meds on the way,
but we need bodies.
I call the head.
- I got kicked last time.
- Right arm.
- Left arm.
- Right leg.
- Need one more.
- Uh, two more.
I'm just here to observe
and speak with the patient
- once he's under control.
- Oh.
Hey, Robby!
Can... can you help us
with Mr. Krakozhia?
- No.
- Coward!
Whitaker...
just the man we need.
Come over here, please.
Whoa, what did I miss?
A little drama
from a tension pneumo.
You could have called me.
- We got it under control.
- Good.
And Dr. Santos learned
what can happen
when you put a patient
with a small pneumothorax
- on BiPAP.
- Ah.
Thumb scalpel.
He was hypoxic.
I thought it would help.
But you didn't discuss it
with me,
and he almost died.
Dilator.
You need to run every order by
a senior resident or attending.
That's why it's
a four-year program.
Now, when you do this procedure,
you want to make sure to never,
ever lose this guidewire.
That gets sucked in the chest,
you're screwed.
Now, ready for the pigtail.
What the hell are you doing?
Pneumo is tiny.
It'll resolve spontaneously.
Yeah, it was tiny until
the patient went on BiPAP.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Guidewire out.
His sats were down.
I... I gave the order.
Without clearing it with me.
Honest mistake from the rookie.
That's how we learn.
If she knew everything,
she'd be your attending,
not an intern.
That is very true.
Besides, it could
have happened on its own
without the BiPAP.
Wow.
Beautiful moment.
A lot of love in the room.
If you'll excuse me.
Nice save.
It's Wheeler.
Dr. Abbot said
to come back at 6:30,
and he'd still be here,
but we overslept.
I forgot to charge my phone.
I'm really sorry.
Okay, let's see.
Wheeler, Kristin?
It... it's Kristi, and...
and I'm her mom.
Dr. Abbot went off duty
at 7:00,
but that's no problem.
We'll get you back.
Have a seat until
we call your name.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Next.
[man coughing]
[indistinct chatter]
- How you guys doing?
- Good, thanks.
We missed our appointment,
but otherwise, we're fine.
Oh, no.
[chuckles]
Have you been here long?
I've been here about four hours.
Oh.
We were here two nights ago.
We waited seven hours.
Hmm.
It's all bullshit.
Can't believe somebody
hasn't died out here.
[sighs]
How we doing?
- No change.
- [raspy breathing]
I... I've been doing
all the talking.
Do you want to...
say some things?
What is there to say?
I'm sad.
I'm angry.
I don't want him to go.
There's so much that
I wish were different.
- [raspy breathing]
- It's not fair.
Tell him.
I am telling him.
I'm telling both of you.
It's not fair.
I wanted what you had.
[rasping]
I love you, Dad.
And I'm thankful for everything
you did to provide for us.
But you weren't the dad
I wanted, because I didn't...
I didn't play baseball
or build models or fish.
My friends' dads all
had grown-up jobs.
They didn't tell silly jokes
or talk in character voices
or make up stories.
I was embarrassed, and I...
I didn't want my
friends to meet you.
- Helen.
- It's true.
I'm ashamed to admit it,
but it's true.
I left for college, and I...
I stayed away.
[crying]
I could have gone fishing.
I should have gone fishing.
And I'm... I'm curious now.
And I forgive you, Dad,
for not being the man
that I wanted you to be.
But I am...
I am so grateful
that you weren't.
The world needed you
to be exactly as you are.
It got... it got serious, and...
and it turned ugly.
And you and your friends built
the Neighborhood
of Make-Believe.
What an incredible gift.
[sniffles]
Oh, Daddy.
I am so sorry.
Please, please forgive me.
[sniffles]
[crying]
[whispering]
Come find me when it's time.
[Krakozhia shouting]
No news chopper coverage.
No eye in the sky.
Not even a damn drone.
No mystery here.
The cop said east on 376.
They're headed to Swissvale.
I have a cousin in Swissvale.
Says it's crazy.
Fellas, they are not
going to Swissvale.
They're crossing the line.
Canada, baby.
That's the other way, genius.
See, I'm taking all your money.
- No, you're not.
- You're taking his money.
You think so?
I'm breaking up
this sewing circle.
Antoine, you're supposed
to be in triage.
Dennison needs a knee
immobilizer and crutches.
Go on.
Paolo, take postural vitals
on Thorpe in North 5,
and a repeat potassium draw
on Fontaine in South 18.
Larry, you're coming with me.
Okay, we have a quorum.
- Meds finally here?
- Yep.
- Guy's got some energy.
- Let's do this.
Donahue, right leg.
Larry, left leg.
Kim, right arm.
I call left arm.
Perlah takes the head.
And our young man here
will inject. Clear?
- Yeah.
- Pulse ox?
- Right here.
- Good luck.
IM injection to
the mid-anterior left thigh.
Everybody ready?
Yo, Whitaker.
You play any ball?
What, football?
No, dodgeball.
Of course football.
Yeah, some peewee.
You know, I was actually
a pretty good kicker.
Not helpful.
Look, Larry and I are
gonna block for you.
Come in right behind us.
When we split
and go for his legs,
you go right up the middle.
- End zone, baby.
- Okay, yeah.
- Got it.
- Okay.
You ready?
One, two, three.
[Krakozhia shouting]
Okay, Mr. Krakozhia,
we're here to help you.
We're here to help you...
oh, God!
What do I do? Ahh!
- [shouting]
- Shit.
Ahh!
Oh.
[sighs]
That's it.
[sighs] Congrats, kid.
You just earned
your yellow wings.
Okay, midazolam will take
him down in a minute.
We'll monitor him for 20.
After that, the Haldol
will have kicked in.
Yeah, he's settling down now.
Do I really need to be here
for 20 minutes?
Why?
You got a date?
- I mean, I'm covered in...
- I'm kidding.
Thanks for your help.
[laughs]
Go get cleaned up.
Okay. Thanks, everyone.
Good work.
I know I don't need to say it,
but let's try
to stay on top of
Mr. Krakozhia's med schedule.
- Ugh.
- Sorry.
Yeah, thanks.
Can I help you get new scrubs?
Oh, no, it's good.
I'm gonna...
Uh, thank you for
the offer, though.
[grunting]
So, Tasha, you work
in a restaurant?
No, take it in two bites.
- Okay.
- Rotate your wrist.
Follow the curve of the needle.
Exit at 90 degrees,
same distance from the wound.
Good.
Yes, I'm the sommelier
at Altius.
Oh, Altius is supposed
to be amazing.
Sorry.
What... what is it you do?
I'm the sommelier,
the wine steward.
Ah.
We have the best cellar
in the city.
I don't mind bragging.
Ah, it sounds like a great gig.
Do you have to go
to school for that?
Oh, my.
Yeah.
Yeah, I have a degree.
- Mm, cool.
- Okay.
How's that?
Really good.
First tie is a surgeon's knot.
Wrap the suture twice.
Grab the short end.
Pull with just enough tension.
Bring the wound edges together.
Not too tight or she'll
have railroad tracks.
So, Tasha, what's your favorite
wine you've ever tasted...
or most expensive?
Same answer for both...
a 2011 Domaine
de la Romanée-Conti.
[chuckles]
Three more instrument ties.
Great.
Square knots, single wrap
around the needle driver.
Is that French?
As French as it gets,
- a burgundy.
- Ah.
And how much does that cost?
I sold that bottle for $18,000.
- [laughs]
- Not here.
That was in New York.
Are you kidding?
18 grand for a bottle of wine?
I mean, was it really that good?
Life changing.
And I know something
about life changing.
[chuckles] Maybe one day.
I'm still not old enough
to drink... legally.
That's a little scary.
[chuckles]
And I'm about 18 grand short
and a friend of Bill's,
so I'll have to take
your word for it too.
My only extravagance
these days is moisturizer.
[laughs] I hear you.
Jenna, I have some
people here to see you.
- Jenna, oh.
- Oh, my God.
Hi.
Oh, my God.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm so sorry.
I have no idea how
this happened, I swear.
Is she, um...
Yes, she's cleared medically.
You may take her home.
Here's some discharge
instructions,
but no more pills unless they're
from a doctor or pharmacy.
Yeah. I won't.
We're giving you some
fentanyl test strips.
These work on pills and liquids.
And this is a Narcan spray.
Please, just keep it in
your purse just in case
if you're at a party,
and someone's out of it.
Yeah, thank you.
You realize how lucky you are?
Yes?
Yeah, I... I do.
Mr. and Mrs. Bradley, I just
spoke to nuclear medicine,
and they are ready to take Nick
for the cerebral perfusion
study test in a few minutes.
Can we stay with him?
Absolutely.
The test itself involves
radiation imaging,
so you'll have to wait
just outside the door.
But Dave will take you down.
I'll show you where you can be.
He'll also bring you back here.
The results take
about an hour or so,
and I'll come find you
when I get them.
And we'll take it from there.
Thank you, Doctor.
Okay.
So sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Dr. Heather Collins.
You must be Kristi
and Lynette Wheeler?
- Yes.
We were supposed
to see Dr. Abbot.
Yes, Dr. Abbot is
an amazing physician,
but even he needs sleep
occasionally.
I guess I just got tired.
And I forgot to charge my phone,
- and we overslept.
- Mm.
I use an old-fashioned alarm
clock since med school.
Never fails.
That's what I have at home.
I just forgot to bring it.
Okay.
I see we're doing a medication
abortion today, correct?
Yep.
Well, since I didn't
initially assess you,
do you mind if I
ask a few questions?
Get up to speed?
No.
Thanks.
Is this your first pregnancy?
Yes.
And you're 17?
When did your last
menstrual cycle start?
Um, I'm not exactly sure.
End of June...
23rd maybe?
Any allergies to medication?
No.
Any surgeries in the past?
I need to do another
quick ultrasound
to make sure everything
is okay for the medication.
Do you want to put on a gown
to make sure you don't get gel
all over your clothes?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Thank you.
Joyce, our sickler,
is doing well
on the exchange transfusion.
Awaiting a telemetry bed.
Quinn, the midnight vaper,
is still in sinus
after cardioversion.
Uh, four hours of cardiac
monitoring starting now,
and you can discharge him.
Our Good Samaritan's hanging in,
stable vitals and neuro checks.
Yeah, I want to get
a repeat head CT in an hour,
rule out any increased bleeding.
And Mr. Gold was stool
positive for campylobacter,
has gone home on azithromycin.
Well, I hope he loads up
on water and electrolytes.
The guy filled up
half a dozen bedpans.
Must be a record.
Without sounding
like a broken record,
everything okay with you?
That's your third cup
before 11:00.
Yeah, I'm not sleeping great.
It's fucking with me
a little bit.
But I've got four days off
next week.
I think I'm gonna get out of
Dodge and head for the hills.
I wish you would.
What'd Shakespeare say...
"Physician, heal thyself"?
What? Have you been
talking to Collins?
Not Shakespeare.
Luke, the disciple,
who probably heard it
from Paul the Apostle.
But what do I know?
I'm Jewish.
It's not my book.
Shakespeare had nothing
to do with it, though.
Yeah.
Maybe a little time off
would be good.
Oh.
You have everything?
Yeah, I think so.
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
Is that...
Yeah.
Let's go, sweetheart.
Wait.
Um, Mr. Bradley?
I just wanted to apologize
for the way I spoke to you.
Please wait. Please.
There's no excuse.
I was gonna ask a nurse
to give you this,
but it's my number and email.
If I can ever be of any help
in any way, please.
I don't know who you are.
- Oh.
I'm sorry.
I'm Jenna.
I met Nick at orientation,
and he was really sweet.
We were in the same econ class,
and we had this really
big test coming up.
So some of us made this
kind of study group.
And we'd stay up way
too late drinking coffee
and then have a really
hard time falling asleep.
And one girl said
she knew how to get Xanax,
but was too afraid
to go pick it up.
Nick was just being nice
when he said he'd do it.
I am so sorry.
I really hope
he pulls through this.
I'm praying he pulls
through this.
He will.
Uh, yeah.
Thank you.
You should go.
I'm sure your parents
want to take you home.
All right.
Come on.
[clears throat]
Sorry about earlier.
I think I still have
a lot to learn.
You do.
Looks good.
Nice job, Doc.
Thank you for the trust.
Now keep it clean and dry,
and we'll see you for
a wound check in two days.
You did great.
I didn't feel a thing.
Sutures out in a week,
but come back sooner
for any redness,
fever, or drainage.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Thank you.
Um, I couldn't help but notice.
There's a misgendering error
on your chart.
I'm really sorry about that.
I've gone ahead
and fixed it here
and on your insurance data file,
but it shouldn't happen again.
Wow.
I am...
Thank you.
Truly.
Thank you both.
Yeah, of course.
That was cool.
Didn't think to check that.
Good catch.
Oh, any other medications?
The only medicine is Tylenol,
and she has no allergies.
Hi, I'm Dr. Mohan.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, let me catch her up.
Jia Yi is a 12-year-old
with six weeks
of constant pain
in the suprapubic area.
There's no fever, no dysuria,
no nausea, vomiting, diarrhea,
no vaginal discharge.
And the urine pregnancy test
is negative.
A... a pregnancy test?
Of course it's negative.
She has a stomachache.
Tell me a little bit
more about your pain.
Can you give me a number from
1 to 10, 10 being the worst?
It was like a two
the first few weeks.
Then it went up to a five.
Now it's worse, like a seven.
And when was your
last menstrual period?
- Haven't had it.
- This month?
No, never.
A few of my friends got theirs.
I'm still waiting.
She's only 12.
Okay.
We'll be back for an exam.
Why don't you change into
a gown open in the back?
It's weird.
I mean, no period,
but she has early secondary
sexual characteristics...
you know, breast development,
widening hips.
Yeah, it's primary amenorrhea.
What are you thinking?
Could be a pituitary
dysfunction or...
Okay, how are we doing?
Are we moving
anybody out of here?
We're trying.
Asthma cleared after two nebs,
went home with steroids
and albuterol.
I like that.
Who else?
Uh...
Hire scabs that don't know
zip ties from airline cable?
[scoffs]
Fuck around and find out.
Come Monday,
that promoter is gonna have
my lawyer's shoe
so far up his ass,
he's gonna be flossing
with the laces.
How are we doing in here?
Vitals are perfect.
Satting 98 on 4 liters.
Nice.
So I can go back to work now?
With six rib fractures,
a bruised lung,
and a catheter in your chest?
Not the best idea.
But I do respect the work ethic.
[exhales] Ritchie,
get Cecil on FaceTime again.
I need to see this shit myself.
Do me a favor.
Call Dr. Gregorian
in thoracic
and see if he'll take Stone
as a personal favor to me,
and make sure he knows
he doesn't need
any real babysitting.
He's stable.
- We just need a bed.
- Copy that.
Projectile vomiting is
better with ondansetron.
Labs normal,
awaiting a PO challenge.
What about Minu, the fall lady?
Antibiotics on board, pain free,
on the OR schedule at 3:00 p.m.
We parked her in the hall
for a few hours.
Okay, good.
A little jelly on the belly.
Sorry.
It's cold.
And just to be sure,
you're not being
treated for any blood clots,
taking any anticoagulants?
No, I don't take any medicines.
[beeps]
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
There it is. There it is.
Chopper 7, I knew
you wouldn't let me down.
Here we go.
Wait, where is it?
Well, it sure as shit
ain't Swissvale.
- Hmm.
- They're out in Monroeville...
- Mm-hmm.
- Trailing PPD.
What are they doing out there?
They're driving till
the wheels fall off.
And it's almost
outside our catch.
I got $10 that say they don't
make it to the county line.
- They coming back.
- I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'll take that.
They're Westmoreland's
problem now.
- Mm.
- Yep.
- Uh-oh.
- It's on the news?
[clears throat] Yes, ma'am.
Where are they?
They're headed east
toward Monroeville.
Let me see.
[static buzzing]
Give me $20 on junkies,
caught, outside our zone.
Well, damn.
- [laughing]
- All right.
- Soft, non-tender.
- Okay.
Jia Yi, we're going
to check below the waist.
You'll be all covered up.
Would you like Dad to stay?
Yes, please.
Don't go.
Okay, I'm here.
I'm here.
All right, knees up,
but keep your feet on the bed.
And let the knees flop apart.
We're just gonna take
a quick look.
You'll feel me
touch your upper leg
so we can see where you pee.
Any pain?
No, it's okay.
Okay.
You can put your legs back down.
You did great, and we know
how we can help you.
Thank you.
Dad, can we step out
for a minute?
Yay. Good job.
What's... what's wrong
with her?
Her mother died of colon cancer.
Is it...
No, that has nothing
to do with this.
Do you know what a hymen is?
I... not really.
When the baby is
developing in the womb,
there's a membrane
called the hymen
which blocks
the vaginal passage.
Before birth,
most of it goes away,
but sometimes it doesn't.
- Is that dangerous?
- No, not at all.
The good news is
that your daughter
has an imperforate hymen
totally blocking the vagina.
We saw what looks to be
about three months of
violaceous menstrual blood
bulging from behind it.
Oh, my God.
It's totally curable
and an easy fix.
Your daughter needs
minor surgery
best done under anesthesia
in an operating room
by a gynecologist.
Then she'll be okay?
Yes, totally back to normal.
Thank you.
We, uh...
we lost Jia Yi's mother
when Jia Yi was six.
And I do my best
to fill her place.
But as she gets older...
Her mother would have
known what to do.
I'm sure you do great.
She's going to be fine.
Thank you.
[sighs]
We should let her know.
I'll do the talking this time.
Housekeeping is
turning over South 20.
Damn, we're good.
What's it like
when I'm not here?
I hate to break it to you,
but I run a tight ship
with or without you.
More fun with me, though, right?
- Jokes are better.
- Always.
But your tell is
the hairier it gets,
the funnier you get,
and you are on fire today.
Dr. Robby, it's time.
Hey.
[raspy breathing]
[sighs]
Is he still with us?
Those are called
agonal respirations.
Close to the end.
[rasps]
He said our mother's name
a few minutes ago.
Marge.
Did he?
Like she was here
in the room with us.
And... and then he smiled
and just closed his eyes.
[shallow breathing]
How are you both holding up?
I'm exhausted.
Yeah, I... I...
I think I'm doing okay.
Oh, Jereme, I am so glad
that you are here.
Same.
I... I couldn't go
through this by myself.
You don't have to.
Sara and I are here.
I know.
Thank you.
I need you.
It's good that your
families live close.
This becomes
a primary relationship now.
You're the last witnesses
to each other's lives.
You hold the memories.
Scary thought,
the way my memory's going.
I just had the craziest idea.
[chuckles]
You know what we should
think about doing?
Why don't we take the boat out,
like, this weekend?
[rasping]
[groans]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
[sniffles]
[sobbing]
Oh, no.
[crying]
[indistinct chatter]
Bactrim twice a day, warm soaks,
and we'll see you here again
in two days for a wound check.
- Do you have any questions?
- Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, I need a gurney in here!
Now!
Gurney!
[grunting]