There is no way
this is happening.
Not now, not ever.
Mom, stop!
This is what you had in mind
for your fun weekend
with your aunt?
- All right. Can we...
- I was trying to help her.
No, what would have
been helpful is telling me
that my daughter is pregnant!
Instead, I find out
from a confused teenage boy!
- Jackson told you?
- Yeah, he did.
Whoa, whoa,
everything OK in here?
This is Mrs. Wheeler,
Kristi's mother.
Lynette is Kristi's aunt.
She doesn't want
to have this baby.
This has nothing to do with you!
- OK, maybe we just take...
- Mom, I called Aunt Lynn, OK?
I don't want to be a teen mom.
Well, then maybe
you should have thought of that
before you started having sex.
OK, emotions are running high.
I think a private conversation
between mother and daughter
is in order.
Lynette, let's you and I
step out.
I'll buy you a cup of coffee.
[indistinct chatter]
The crashed ambulance thieves
are en route.
ETA, 10 minutes.
Trauma 2's all yours.
Great.
They better be meth-head junkies
'cause Abby wants a Birkin
for her birthday.
What's she gonna do
with a Birkin?
Hopefully forgive me for getting
the kids a goldendoodle.
You want to be a good husband?
Send her on a vacation
without you or the kids
or a damn puppy.
Are you mean to everyone
or just me?
Just you.
Hey, what's the status
of the head CT on Joseph Marino?
Uh, still waiting on results.
He's postictal
and sleeping in North 2.
- No more seizure activity.
- Good.
Let me know as soon as
those CT results get back.
Yeah, of course.
[indistinct chatter]
How's, uh, Travis,
our tonsillectomy patient?
Oh, I, uh, just dropped
him off at surgery.
- He's doing well.
- Good work.
- You kept him from bleeding out.
- Oh, no, come on.
That was all you and Dr. Robby.
I mean, I could never have done
what you guys did
with that airway.
Not yet.
That's why you're here.
But you stayed with him
the whole time.
He would have died
at most other hospitals.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I guess you're right.
Yeah, I usually am.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm sorry about all of this.
I didn't think
that Eloise would find out.
Yeah, well, she did.
Kristi should make
her own decisions.
Unfortunately,
she's still considered a minor.
Why don't you take a seat?
And we'll come find you
if there's an update.
[taps glass]
[buzzer sounds]
- What do you need, Robby?
- Escaping.
Go, go.
- Dr. Robinavitch.
- Gloria.
This is Dr. Tracy Morris,
regional manager of ECQ America.
The contract management group.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Likewise.
But if you'll excuse me,
I'm a little slammed,
as per usual.
We were upstairs
with the executive team
going over a proposal.
- A proposal?
- Mm-hmm.
We're interested in having
your emergency department
join us.
The 500 or so ERs
you have aren't enough?
What can I say?
Business is good.
Yeah, for who?
- Everyone benefits.
- Do they, though?
Your contract management's
corporate mandate
is profits for shareholders
above everything else, yes?
- Robby.
- Dah-dah-dah.
Your hospital's board
was very impressed
with ECQ's metrics
on patient satisfaction,
throughput time,
and billing collections.
Does your proposal
include the part
where you cut the pay
for all my doctors?
Maybe I can find
an incentive for you.
How does regional
medical director sound?
Lighter workload,
better benefits, stock options.
Did you go to business school
or medical school?
Both.
We look forward
to your decision.
Of course.
Hopefully we'll get a chance
to work together soon,
Dr. Robinavitch.
I can't believe you're
seriously considering this.
Bottom line is, our current
numbers aren't good,
and theirs are.
Just because
their dashboard is pretty
doesn't mean
it's good for patients.
If you want to keep this ED,
improve metrics.
There's a lot of OFI.
Opportunities for improvement.
Well, you could have
just said that.
I need you to care about
patient-satisfaction scores.
I would love nothing more.
But right now the average
wait time is six hours,
and that's before
you see a doctor.
You need to hire more staff
so we can open
more inpatient beds.
Are you prepared to do that?
I need you to improve scores
with the resources we have,
or we will explore
what ECQ has to offer.
This is bullshit.
You know this is bullshit.
And if you don't,
then we are all in trouble.
- Maybe you need some time off.
- Hey, we got a ladder fall.
A couple of minutes out.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter,
distant telephone ringing]
Mint?
Who would have guessed
frat boys?
Collins.
Damn it.
I knew they were gonna crash.
Then why didn't you bet crash?
I didn't want anybody
to get hurt.
- It's bad karma, man.
- So who won?
Oh, Doc Collins hit
the full parlay...
in our zone, crash,
and frat boys.
That's uncanny,
bordering on spooky.
And the rich just get richer.
You need to practice
more gratitude.
I'd be a lot more grateful
if my paycheck was bigger.
That part.
Any luck finding
Ginger's daughter?
She was supposed to be right
back to take her mom home.
I just tried her cell again.
Still no answer.
Let me try the cafeteria
one more time.
What do we tell her?
No, don't tell her anything yet.
Oh, boy.
Um, you should consult
with Kiara
just in case this goes south.
[distant siren wailing]
- What do we have?
- 45-year-old Silas Dunn.
Fell off an 8-foot ladder.
Right chest hit
the carpeted floor.
No LOC. Good vitals.
No meds, no allergies.
I'm Dr. Santos.
How are you doing?
Fine.
My wife called 911.
These guys said this was all
necessary, but I-I can walk.
We're gonna keep it on until
we get you all checked out, OK?
What are you thinking?
What made him fall could have
been cardiac or neuro.
- Any headache?
- I was a little dizzy.
He needs a head CT.
EKG and troponin.
- Exactly.
- On my count.
- One, two, three.
- [groans]
I was installing
a lighting fixture...
Dr. Santos on E-fast, please.
I'm Dr. Garcia.
Can you spell "world"?
W-O-R-L-D.
Start with D,
spell it backwards.
Oof. D-L-R-O-W?
Excellent.
Your brain is fine.
Pulse 92.
BP 132 over 78.
- Sat 98.
- No pericardial effusion.
- Ow.
- Oh. Tender?
- Yeah.
- OK, ribs 7 and 8, MCL.
You probably cracked
a rib or two.
Check for lung sliding.
That could be a pneumo.
Ah, I was gonna paint
the living room next.
My wife has
a whole list of things
she wants us to get done.
I'm afraid
the only home renovations
you're gonna be doing
in the next couple weeks
are the kind you watch on TV.
Can you tell my wife that?
[chuckles]
Lungs are up.
What's your sign?
- Scorpio.
- Spicy.
And I'm focused on our patient.
- Um, belly's clear.
- [phone rings]
Dr. Garcia.
Shit. Be right there.
Wish I could stay.
Post-op hemorrhage.
You're in good hands.
Tier One Trauma, ETA now.
Trauma Tier One...
OK, call me if anything changes.
Stolen ambulance versus tree.
PPD maintaining custody
of suspects.
This one doesn't meet criteria.
Zac Dawson, 21, restrained
front-seat passenger,
was ambulatory on scene.
Lacerations to the anterior
thigh from broken glass.
Otherwise no injuries.
Good vitals.
- You hurting anywhere, Zac?
- Where's Miles?
Miles Hernandez, 18,
unrestrained driver
of the stolen ambulance.
Right chest, left leg injuries.
Short of breath.
Sat 91.
Tachy 120s.
BP 105 over 70.
- Can I go with him?
- Is this your friend?
He's my pledge.
We're gonna find a room for you.
- Let us take care of Miles, OK?
- I'm Dr. Collins.
- Can you talk?
- [wheezes]
Breath sounds bilateral
but lots of stridors.
Set up for intubation.
We got to fix this fast.
Posterior hip dislocation.
Good pedal pulse.
We need induction meds,
ketamine and rock.
Ho, ho, ho,
look at this clavicle.
Depressed centrally.
Sternoclavicular dislocation.
It's compressing his trachea.
Let's reduce it, see
if it helps his breathing.
All right, stabilize the leg.
One, two, three.
Four of morphine.
Draw a rainbow, type and screen.
- [rapid beeping]
- Heart rate's 125.
Langdon, get on the airway.
Collins, E-fast.
No blood in the oropharynx.
Clavicle is
dislocated posteriorly.
Chlorhexidine swab.
10 of lido with epi.
Time is of the essence.
BP's 108 over 74.
All right, Miles,
your collarbone
is pushing against
your windpipe.
We're gonna pull it back up.
I'm going to inject
an anesthetic.
You're gonna feel
a pinprick and a big burn.
[groaning]
All right, towel clip.
All right, go deep.
You want to get
a really good grip
on both sides of that bone.
[groans]
Got it.
All right, Miles.
It's gonna hurt for a second.
You ready?
[groaning]
[cracking, pops]
Oh, motherfucker!
- Ooh.
- Screaming is good.
Who are you torturing now?
Reduced a sternoclavicular
dislocation.
- How's your breathing?
- Better.
What happened to your
post-op hemorrhage?
Panicky intern.
False alarm.
- Who is she?
- Right?
This is Dr. Garcia. We're gonna
get your leg straightened out.
After we do a CT.
OK, looks like
you got it from here.
You know
you guys were on the news?
You stole an ambulance.
What were you thinking?
It wasn't my idea.
Does he look like
a meth head to you?
Seriously,
what is wrong with you?
This was a terrible idea.
OK, Chanel, all set.
How bad does it look?
I'm gonna be honest with you.
- It doesn't look great.
- [sighs]
Thankfully,
there's no signs of infection.
I'm such an idiot.
And now I'm having
a panic attack.
Excuse me, Dr. Mohan...
I'll be right back.
I've only been in with her
for a few minutes.
I didn't say anything.
What's the case?
Chanel Sutton, 22,
complications from silicone
butt injections.
So call the clinic that did it.
She found the guy on TikTok.
He did the injections
in his living room.
She thinks it was maybe
silicone caulk from Home Depot.
Jesus.
Really?
Kids today.
She is tachycardic
and tachypneic.
I think it's a panic attack.
But if a piece of silicone
hit a vein,
she could have
a pulmonary embolism.
- We should scan her.
- Good.
How's Joyce,
our sickle cell patient doing?
Holding up.
She's intubated
and waiting on an ICU bed.
Good. Keep it up.
Will do.
Team rounds. CWA.
Come join us
when you're finished.
As soon as I put in
a few orders.
- I'm so sorry.
- Hi, how's she doing?
Better. Faster.
Still need ten more of her.
Never thought I'd see the day
where you'd wish
for more Samiras.
You can blame Gloria for that.
If I don't get
patient satisfaction scores up
around here, they're bringing in
an outside management company
to run things.
- Mother of God. Really?
- Yep.
Holy hell.
Any word back on Nick Bradley's
- cerebral perfusion test?
- Still waiting on results.
What about ipecac mom,
Theresa Saunders?
On fluids.
Should be good to go soon.
See, we do have patients
that appreciate you.
You're done with triage
for the day.
I'm sorry.
Did I do something wrong?
Because I know I said too much
to the unhoused mom.
No, don't...
don't worry about it.
It's cool.
One of us just covers
the waiting room
and triage
for the first few hours,
try to thin the herd out there.
We're back here
for the rest of the shift now.
OK, great.
Hey, do you think
they're gonna give us lunch?
It's past 12:00,
and I'm starving.
Oh, you can pack a bunch
of these for your next shift
or grab a sandwich
from the patient bin.
There's no time for breaks
around here.
Thanks.
Wardrobe change?
Oh, I caught a gusher.
Helped save his life.
- How's triage?
- It was good.
I-I'm back with you guys now.
Cool.
So you're feeling OK?
Yeah, I'm feeling fine.
I slipped hours ago.
I'm great.
Ready to go.
Let me guess.
You got these ones
from the lost and found.
The scrub dispenser
was out of my size.
Well, it's a good look,
Huckleberry.
Show off those ankles.
Aren't board rounds at 2:00?
These aren't board rounds.
I just want to remind you all
of a few things, OK?
So we do a great job coming up
with the right diagnosis
and treatment plan
for our patients,
but there are still some...
opportunities for improvement.
- Not this bullshit again.
- First off...
always sit down at the bedside
of a stable patient.
It will make you
a better doctor.
Second, if there's
a discharge to be done,
do it before you pick up
a new patient.
The patients are very aware
of the time
that they spend with us,
so please
don't keep them here any longer
than they need to be.
They complain about the wait.
I get it, but for
the sake of efficiency
and running smoothly on our end
and opening up beds
and opening up rooms,
let's discharge
before we start
with somebody new, OK?
Thank you. Lastly,
in your medical records,
make sure that your
decision-making and your notes
reflect not just the diagnosis
but all the thought
that you put into ruling out
all the critical illnesses
- in the differential.
- More work?
I do enough charting as it is.
The hospital won't admit this,
but it's less about charting
and more about profit.
OK? Good.
That's it. Goodbye.
Go.
[indistinct chatter]
Are our pregnant teen
and mom still talking?
Yeah.
No more yelling from that room?
- Not that I've heard.
- Good, maybe it's working.
Either that,
or they killed each other.
I'm good with either one
at this point.
And you wonder why your patient
satisfaction scores are
in the toilet.
[chuckles]
Always appreciate your support.
I need to check
on my Nepali patient.
She likes me.
Everybody likes you
when they're on morphine.
All right, I think we'll
follow up with Gillian Dupree,
the four-year-old we saw
in triage with the fever.
- OK.
- Yeah.
Dr. Javadi.
Um, sorry.
What... what are you doing here?
Oh, I'm down to see a consult...
young man with a hot appy.
- Are you a med student?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
This is a great case
for the students.
Can they come with?
I'd be happy to do
a little bedside teaching.
- Oh, we have a four-year-old...
- Oh, yeah, I would love that.
Do you mind if I join?
Maybe I can learn something new.
- Sure.
- Great.
I just...
I don't need anyone else
associating me with my mom.
I know, but I just can't
say no to a hot appy.
These are student doctors.
- Mind if I do a little teaching?
- Go for it.
Now, everyone knows
McBurney's point.
But who can tell me
the name of this sign?
Tim, raise your right leg, please.
- Oh!
- Psoas sign.
Causing friction
of the psoas muscle
over the inflamed appendix.
Excellent.
Now, back in the day,
appendicitis meant
you went straight to the OR.
Who can tell me
about the CODA study?
Uh, well, it's from a 2020
"New England Journal" trial
comparing surgery
to antibiotics, you know?
It, um... it showed that
without an appendicolith,
there was a 75% success rate
in the antibiotic-only group.
Exactly.
Honey, we discussed
the study at home, right?
"Honey"?
Wait. She's your mom?
It's... it's Victoria...
or Javadi, Dr. Shamsi.
Uh, hello?
Oh, yeah, I'll be right there.
Mrs. Grant now has chest pain.
If you'll excuse us.
Oh, yeah, go.
Patients come first.
- Who's Mrs. Grant?
- Nobody. I made her up.
[laughing]
Sorry.
You just had
that look on your face
my son gives me
when I give his basketball team
pointers from the sideline.
I'm sorry.
[laughs]
- [elevator bell dings]
- No, I think renovations
should be treated
like dental care.
- Leave it to the professionals.
- [chuckles]
They're the only ones that
should be climbing on ladders.
Um, is my family here yet?
I'm not sure. We'll check.
How was the CT?
Head and neck normal,
but tech found
a small hemothorax on the right.
- What's that?
- It's a little bleeding
around the lung
where you broke a rib.
He's also been
more short of breath
- since after the scan.
- Is that from the pain?
Silas?
Hey, Silas, wake up.
Lost the radial pulse.
Thready carotid.
His BP'S crashing.
I think he might need
a chest tube.
Check another hemocue.
Get type specific
from the blood bank.
[rapid beeping]
BP 72 over 44.
Pulse ox 89.
He just dropped his BP and sats.
Put him on 100% nonrebreather.
- Call for two units.
- Already done.
Normal head CT.
Small hemothorax on the right.
Which has now turned into
a huge collection of blood.
Prep for a chest tube.
20 French.
I would love to do
the chest tube.
You got it.
I'll guide you.
Sats are low.
Should we intubate?
Not until after
the chest tube's in.
We wouldn't want to cause
a tension pneumo.
She won't make
that mistake again.
Ten blade to Dr. Santos.
There's a lot of breast tissue.
Focus on the chest tube.
[clears throat]
Fifth intercostal space,
- anterior axillary line.
- Perfect.
[beeping continues]
Long Kelly next.
[scalpel clatters]
- Fuck!
- Oh, my God. Are you OK?
Oh, that's got to hurt.
- Leave it!
- OK, but...
- OK, I'm stepping in.
- No, you're not gloved.
I got this.
- I-I...
- On my own.
[grunts]
Glove up.
You're sewing this in.
[steady beeping]
- We're good. No need to hover.
- OK.
I'll be next door
if you need me.
- [groans]
- [sighs]
- Sats and BP look perfect.
- Mm-hmm.
- We ready to go in here?
- We're getting there.
- You good?
- Absolutely.
You start feeling
lightheaded, just speak up, OK?
Yeah.
OK, you're gonna pretend
you're a pirate
with your foot on a keg of rum.
- Are you serious?
- Yep.
This is the Captain Morgan
technique for hip reduction.
- Who's Captain Morgan?
- [chuckles]
The guy on the rum bottle?
[bed whirring]
I'll stabilize the pelvis.
OK, you're gonna step up here.
Actually, let me just... sorry.
Yeah, and you are gonna put
your right leg behind his knee.
- Like this?
- Yeah.
And you are gonna use
your leg as a hinge
to put anterior force
on his femur.
Physics.
Push down on the lower leg
with your left hand.
You got this.
Put your back into it.
The hip is a big joint with
lots of muscle stabilizing it.
OK.
[crack]
- Whoa!
- Oh, shit.
I mean, shoot.
And that is what
a hip reduction feels like.
Nicely done.
Thank you.
I hear you have
an 85-year-old patient
who may have been abandoned
by her primary caregiver.
Well, maybe.
I-I hope not.
I don't really know what to do.
We can't find the daughter.
And I'm really worried
about the mom...
Slow down.
We'll figure this out.
What do you think happened?
Um, well, Ginger has
schizophrenia, and she fell.
And the daughter was already
so overwhelmed, I mean...
maybe she ran.
I don't want to say
this is elder neglect, but...
Don't jump
to the worst case yet.
I'll see if I can get ahold
of any other family members.
You know,
I-I told the daughter...
I told her to take a break,
you know, to prioritize herself.
And I-I just... I didn't think
that she was gonna dump
her mom, so...
This isn't your fault.
We're seeing more cases
like this
as Baby Boomers age.
It's really tough
on their families.
Thanks.
Dr. Robby, Nick Riley's
cerebral perfusion study
is back.
[sighs]
No blood flow
past the brain stem.
OK.
Let me know when the transplant
people from CORE arrive.
Will do.
[indistinct chatter]
- Any news?
- There is.
Why don't we step outside?
Mm.
Let's go this way.
So I have the results of Nick's
cerebral perfusion scan.
Unfortunately, it shows
that there's no blood flow
to Nick's brain.
Uh, what am I looking at?
It might help you
if I showed you.
This is a healthy brain.
See the black?
That's blood flowing
to the cerebrum.
When there's no blood flow...
It's white.
Yes.
He's brain-dead.
I am so very sorry.
[sniffles]
I prayed. I had hoped...
We all did.
So he's not...
he's not coming back?
No.
The apnea test and now
the perfusion scan prove that.
What happens now?
He's hooked up
to all those machines...
Take some time.
Try to process this news.
A family support specialist
will come in very soon
and help you
through the next steps.
Thank you.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
I just had to show
the parents of the OD'd teen
the perfusion scan results.
How'd it go?
Oh, it never gets easier.
Is that Dr. Robby?
You owe me a dance.
Looks like an opportunity
to boost
your patient satisfaction.
Well, I am a little rusty,
but let's give it a go,
shall we?
Mm-hmm.
- Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Whoo!
- [laughing]
Xeroform first,
then two cut 4x4s.
Kim will show you
how to do it right.
I absolutely will.
Thanks.
Only 500 out.
- He won't need the OR.
- [breathing shakily]
- You, follow me.
- [door opens]
[elevator bell dings]
I totally fucked up.
Tell me something I don't know.
You're confident. That's good.
But there's a fine line between
confidence and cockiness.
[sighs]
Should I draw your blood?
You already did.
Yeah, I-I mean for the HIV
and hepatitis panels.
I can do Silas', too.
No, I'll have Dana do it
after the wound repair.
[exhales sharply]
C-can I suture for you?
Hell, no. I'll do it myself.
You can assist.
Set me up a chux,
suture tray, betadine,
irrigation saline,
syringe on splash guard,
and 5-0 prolene.
1% lido with epi, 5 CC syringe,
27-gauge needle.
- [exhales deeply]
- [drawer closes]
[groaning]
Mom and Kristi still
talking in there?
Mm-hmm.
I'm giving them
as much time as I can.
Within reason.
Do you think Mom will consent
to Kristi terminating
the pregnancy?
A woman should only have
a child if she wants to.
Well, if you'd just gone
with Abbot's measurements,
they would have been
discharged an hour ago.
Are you serious?
I need a doctor in triage ASAP.
- What's up?
- I have a teen
with severe scrotal pain.
I need to rule out torsion.
Pull four of intranasal Versed.
- I got this.
- Be my guest.
- [groans]
- [knocks on door]
Hi.
Look at this
beautiful Black queen.
- Are you our doctor?
- Thank you.
Uh, yes,
I'm Dr. Heather Collins.
And I take it this is Dillon?
Mm-hmm.
And I'm his mother, Tina.
- It's nice to meet you both.
- [groans]
Dillon, when did the pain start?
It started, like, an hour ago.
Did you get kicked or hit
with a ball or anything?
No, it... it just came
out of nowhere.
- [groans]
- Oh, God.
OK.
I need to do an ultrasound
to make sure
your testicle didn't
twist on itself
and cut off the blood supply.
Is that all right with you?
Can I get, like, a dude doctor?
Come on, Dillon.
This is the doctor you want.
I promise you.
[groans]
OK, fine.
It really fucking hurts.
- Language, baby.
- Thanks.
- I'm sorry. It really does.
- OK.
We're going to squirt
some medicine up your nose.
It'll help you relax and help
take away some of the pain.
Then do it.
OK, Dr. Collins says
it'll help.
I know, Mom. I heard her.
My ears are fine.
It's my junk that's killing me.
Please.
- OK, sorry, baby.
- Come on, bro.
Hold still.
All good, Beto?
All good, Doctor.
- That'll be us one day.
- [laughs]
You sooner than me, of course.
- Shit. Thanks.
- [groans]
I was one crack pipe away
from winning the whole thing.
So Collins won, huh?
You guys ever find out
why those kids stole the rig?
Uh, undeveloped
prefrontal cortex.
[scoffs] Idiots gonna do
prison time now.
Dr. Langdon, I have
Joseph Marino's CT results.
Our seizure patient.
[whispering] How's Garcia?
Uh, she's fine.
She's getting her labs drawn.
I'll go visit her in
a minute, start a chart on her.
What happened to your old bud?
Oh, long story.
Let's take a look.
You see what I'm seeing?
Neurocysticercosis.
Be gentle with this one.
Patients don't usually handle
this diagnosis very well.
Got it.
There is no blood flow here
at all.
Is that dangerous?
If it goes untreated
for more than six hours,
he could lose a testicle.
I could...
I could lose my balls?
One testicle.
And we're going to try
and prevent that.
What the hell
were you doing, Dillon?
I'm taking that lock
off your door.
It's difficult to know
what causes a torsion, unfortunately.
Dillon, hey,
it's really important
that I try and fix this now.
OK.
And I see we're gonna have
a new prescription sent to...
To the pharmacy.
And, uh, it's just one pill
every morning.
OK, up next,
nausea and vomiting in North 4.
Oh.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Forearm X-rays are back
on Mr. Ofori
in the south corridor.
You can discharge
with a volar splint.
Notify ortho. ADF.
Always discharge first.
Got it.
Four-year-old with a fever.
Your medical decision-making
says otitis media.
Yeah, she had an ear infection.
Did you also consider
and rule out
meningitis, mastoiditis,
malignant otitis externa?
I did.
Then you should document
your cognitive work in the MDM.
You want me to pad my chart?
No, I want you
to show your work.
Billing is a side effect
of that.
[sighs] Did anyone listen
to what I said earlier?
Most of the time,
the torsion is to the inside,
so we rotate outward
by opening the book.
[yelling]
The testicle might have
twisted the other way.
Uh, let's go back 180
and then try
another 180 to the inside.
[groans]
That's good.
That feels good.
- I think I'm OK now.
- It's fixed?
For the time being.
We need to admit to Urology.
He'll need minor surgery
to tack it down
and prevent it
from happening again.
Thank you.
Dillon, say thank you.
- Thank you.
- [chuckles]
I'll call Urology
and see about the wait.
- Thanks.
- Thank you, too.
Any other questions
I can answer for you?
Yes, can you please let me know
how we can sign up
for you to be our doctor?
I specialize
in emergency medicine,
so I only work at this hospital
and not in primary care.
Damn.
Please let me know
when you get your own office
because you have been wonderful.
And you have a great
relationship with your son.
[laughs]
He is my heart in human form.
Oh.
Do you have any?
Uh... [chuckles]
Not yet, but, uh...
hopefully soon.
Hey, I've been in triage.
What's the update
on incel kid's mom?
Please don't refer
to her that way.
Theresa is rehydrated,
and her electrolytes
have been replaced.
I'm gonna let her know
that she can be discharged.
Did she hear from her son
who ran off?
- I have no idea.
- [scoffs]
I'm ready to get
law enforcement involved
- whenever you are.
- [sighs]
If he's not here, he could
be out there hurting somebody.
I'm not ready to ruin a kid's
life over a thought crime.
We just need to make sure
that he's not...
OK. OK. OK, I get it.
I heard you loud and clear when
you brought this up before.
I will speak to Theresa.
I will see if she's talked
to her son.
Fine.
We should admit her.
She's recovered.
She's good physically,
but she made herself sick
to get her son here.
She's clearly not coping,
and she needs professional help.
Neurocysticercosis,
a parasite in your brain.
I thought I just had
a migraine, but I have...
bugs in my head?
Well, not exactly.
You had larva
from a pork tapeworm
that made multiple cysts,
but they're all dead now.
A worm?
In my fucking head?
Are you kidding me?
No, no, you don't have
a worm in your head.
You just said that I have...
I said you had a worm
in your head,
but it's dead and long gone.
What we're seeing
on the CT is scarring
around those dead cysts.
- Like dead worm eggs?
- Larvae.
[groans]
Is my brain like Swiss cheese?
Am I dying?
- No, no, you're not dying.
- Joseph, you're gonna be OK.
The... the cysts are tiny,
and they're calcified over.
There'll be no further damage.
- [sighs] Can you fix it?
- Unfortunately, no.
The... the little calcified spots
will stay there.
So there's gonna be a worm
graveyard in my brain forever?
Yeah, but they're
resting in peace.
[knock on door]
Hi, Theresa.
Any word from David?
Not yet.
It's still important
that we talk to him,
so keep trying.
In the meantime,
you are cleared to go home.
But I had a thought.
I'm concerned
that you took so much ipecac.
I don't want you
to do that again.
Oh, I won't.
How have things been
at home lately?
Different.
One of us is always sad
since my husband died.
Would you be willing to speak
to a behavioral health
specialist?
I don't need that.
Did you talk to anybody
after your husband passed?
Friends, family.
Anybody professionally?
Therapist, clergy,
social worker?
Devastating personal loss
can be very hard
to manage on your own.
It's OK to need help.
It might even improve
your communication with David.
- OK.
- Great.
I phoned in a favor
with behavioral health.
They can get you in to see
a psychologist at 1:30.
Today?
Mm-hmm, in an hour.
- O-OK.
- Great.
Oh, hey. I was just coming
to check on you two.
- Are... are you leaving?
- Yes, we're going home.
Were you able to come
to a decision?
Kristi is gonna stay
in school until she's due.
Is that what you want?
[retching]
Morning sickness.
- I hate this.
- [lid thuds closed]
OK.
Let me get you
some anti-nausea medicine.
It'll help you feel better.
And you've got a long drive
ahead of you.
OK, fine.
I never did meds, but sure.
Dr. Santos?
Susan and Alana Dunn...
here for an update on
Silas Dunn, your ladder fall.
- Thanks, Mateo.
- Yeah.
Is it serious?
He broke a few ribs
on his right side
from the fall, which caused
some bleeding around the lungs.
So he has a drainage catheter
in his chest.
And with the trauma,
his oxygen levels
were really low,
so he needed a breathing tube
in his windpipe.
Good Lord.
Could he die?
His condition is serious,
but it's... it's stable now.
Would you like to go see him?
He won't be able to talk with
the breathing tube in, but...
Yeah. Where is he?
No, we'll wait
in the waiting room.
- But, Mom...
- Alana, please.
Just let the doctors do what
they need to do for your dad.
We will find you
with any updates.
Thanks.
Doing OK, kid?
Oh, yeah, I was just
checking something.
I should get back to work.
Anything I can do to help,
I'm available.
Thank you.
It's just that I have, um...
I have a dependent patient
whose daughter
might have ditched her.
You don't always get to see
the best side of people.
I guess it just
kind of makes me sad.
It is sad.
But you can't dwell on it.
That'll tear you apart.
Look, you've taken
some time to step away.
That's good.
Don't forget,
your patient needs you.
- She still here?
- Yes. I've...
Mm, I've kind of
been avoiding her.
I don't really know what
to tell her about her daughter.
Well, you don't have
to have all the answers.
Sometimes just asking
how someone's doing is enough.
You got this.
Come on.
Will Miles be able
to walk again?
Yes, he will recover.
None of this
was supposed to happen.
You want to share
how it was supposed to go?
'Cause you stole an ambulance.
- [clears throat]
- He did.
That was dumb.
Haven't you ever
done anything stupid?
No, not really.
We were gonna drive it
and bring it back to campus.
I wanted the guys to see Miles,
think he was cool.
He has a hard time.
He doesn't really fit in.
That's actually kind of sweet.
Some cops started chasing us.
Miles freaked out.
I'm pretty sure
you saw the rest.
It was just supposed
to be a joke.
Now we're going to jail.
My mom's gonna kill me.
Emma, no offense,
but I can't exactly say
I'm happy to see you.
It comes with the territory.
Is there anything more you can
tell me about the parents?
Lily and John Bradley.
Middle class,
college educated, Catholic.
- How's their demeanor?
- About what you'd expect.
Nick was their only child.
Got it.
I'm ready.
You?
[inhales deeply]
Never.
John, Lily,
uh, I want to introduce you
to Emma Isaacs.
She's a family support
specialist
that works with me and families
in the emergency room.
She's here to answer
any questions that you have
and to keep you informed.
Hi, Mr. and Mrs. Bradley.
Oh, uh, John and Lily, please.
OK. I'll let you talk.
Doctor, can you stay?
Please.
Sure.
I'm happy to be here.
Emma is really
the expert, though.
I understand your son is
in here and not doing well.
Can you tell me
what Dr. Robby has told you
about Nick's
unfortunate situation?
There's no blood
going to Nick's brain.
He's... he's brain-dead.
So...
he's dead.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
He was a wonderful son.
- He was the quietest baby.
- [laughs]
He slept... slept
through the night.
It was perfect.
Um, if any one of his friends
had a problem,
he was there to listen, to...
to lend a helping hand.
He...
he would have been a great man.
Oh, I can't believe
this is happening.
I know how difficult
this must be for you.
Can you tell us
what happens now?
Yes.
I can walk you
through all the next steps.
[indistinct chatter]
How are you...
If you ask me how I'm doing,
I swear I'll punch you.
Did I miss something?
I just didn't get
to do my chest tube.
He did.
There's a little more to it
than that...
Not another word,
unless you want
your tongue stapled.
All right, fuck it.
I dropped a scalpel,
and it stuck into Garcia's foot.
Oh, that's bad.
It might actually be worse
than fainting, so...
Well, at least
I didn't kill anyone.
- Day's only half over.
- You killed a patient?
Not really.
You kind of did.
I'm sorry. You did.
It... it wasn't fully
Huckleberry's fault.
It was a fluke.
He caught some gomer
with a sneaky bad ticker.
His name was Bennet.
Oh, great, you can get his
name tattooed on your chest.
At least I'm not
the only fuck-up here.
I got nosebleed.
So long, fellow losers.
[both chuckle softly]
I'll reach out
to a funeral director
and get the paperwork started
on arrangements.
- What's the name of your church?
- Um, St. Mary's.
- Great. Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Do you have any other questions?
Uh...
[softly] No.
I think we should talk
about something else
that is very important.
Your son's driver's license
indicated
that he wanted to be an organ
and tissue donor upon death.
That means he's given
his permission for that...
No, no, I...
I don't want to talk about that.
No, he was too young
to make that kind of decision.
I can understand
why you would think that,
but he was 18.
No!
You didn't know him!
He is still my son!
[door closes]
Sorry.
They need more time.
850 bucks.
I'll Zelle you the rest.
PayPal is also fine.
Winning.
It never gets old.
Hey, I'm serious about
that vacation for your wife.
- What about me?
- What about you?
Your wife has
two kids under four.
Abby works her ass off
every day.
I'm a doctor.
[mimics explosion]
They're all clueless.
What, is this...
is this a female thing?
You should go, now. Go.
Beat it. Go ahead, go.
So what are you gonna buy
with all that hard-earned cash?
I have had this
bookmarked for months.
Oh, James Bond makes
strollers now.
Convertible is the way to go.
- Ah, I'm gonna buy it.
- You should.
You and baby
absolutely deserve it.
[chuckles]
Yeah, we do, right?
Yeah, it's good to be excited.
Just ran into a totally lost
Uber Eats driver.
- Where do I put these?
- I got this. Thank you.
[steady beeping]
Poor guy.
Not everyone's cut out
for the home-reno life.
[chuckles]
Um, I'll... I'll be right back.
- Dr. Robby?
- What's up?
Silas's chest tube output
has slowed down after 650 CCs.
- Good.
- But on re-exam,
I noticed
some breast enlargement,
bilateral and symmetrical
with no palpable masses.
What's in
the differential diagnosis
for male gynecomastia?
Definitely alcoholism.
But then there's pituitary
and gonadal tumors
or pathology.
So what do you want to check?
LFTs for alcohol abuse,
and for the rest,
hormonal levels...
estrogen, testosterone,
Prolactin, hCG, progesterone.
Good. Go.
[exhales sharply]
Ugh!
Oh, the things I would do
for pastrami.
- Is there a turkey and cheese?
- Uh, yeah.
- Oh, what is all this?
- Lunch. Primanti's.
It appears that we have
at least one grateful patient.
Hope is alive.
- Who do we have to thank?
- I don't know.
I think there's a card...
bottom of the bag.
Mmm. My God, that's so good.
Enjoy your lunch.
What was that?
I don't know.
- Aww.
- What?
It's from Shelby Adamson,
Dr. Adamson's sister.
She sends something every year.
- He doesn't like her?
- It's not about her.
It's about him.
Dr. Adamson was Robby's mentor,
and he...
he died during COVID, so...
Mr. Randolph in Central 10
can be moved to a chair.
Done.
[phone chimes]
Hey, if you're hungry,
there's Primanti's
in the staff lounge.
Sorry.
Uh, daily reminder
to call my sister.
You were saying?
There's free lunch
in the lounge.
Do you need
to take care of that?
I do. I just, um... I want
to check on a patient first,
but thank you...
- Jesse. Jesse.
- Yeah.
Hello, Mrs. Kitajima.
How are you feeling?
Ginger, please.
I'm getting tired.
I want to go home.
Where's my daughter?
Um, I'm sorry, but I don't know.
But we're doing
everything we can to find her.
Can I do something for you
while we wait?
I wouldn't mind a snack.
I can have someone
bring you a sandwich.
- Wonderful.
- [phone chimes]
Feel free to bring that
Dr. Robby back around, too.
OK, yeah, I just...
I have to make a quick call.
Um, can you get Mrs. Kitajima
a sandwich from the bin?
Yeah, you got it.
[door whirring]
[exhales sharply]
[line trilling]
[phone chimes]
Hi, Becca.
- Mel!
- [both laugh]
- Uh, how was lunch?
- It was good.
We had paninis
and watermelon salad.
That sounds delicious.
Are you coming to get me?
Um, yeah, remember,
I'm coming, uh, to pick you up
after my shift.
Have you found a boyfriend yet?
- Uh, no.
- Hurry up.
You have to find
somebody to kiss.
- You're right. I do.
- Yeah. [giggles]
I got to get on that right away.
Yeah. [laughs]
[doorknob rattling]
[sighs]
Hey. Is everything all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Where's Kristi?
- She's using the bathroom.
Hey, Kristi,
it's Dr. Collins here.
Is everything all right
in there?
- No, I want the pills!
- Absolutely not.
Eloise, why don't you find
a place to sit, and I will...
You're gonna what,
give my daughter
- the abortion I've forbidden?
- Hey.
What's going on?
Kristi's texting.
- Is she OK?
- You can't be back here.
- She's begging us for help.
- Lynette, I got this. Come on.
You are treating Kristi
like Mom treated you.
Oh, fuck you!
Hey, let's take it down a notch.
This is none of your business!
I am not abandoning Kristi.
Just get the fuck out of here!
- Fuck you.
- Hey, ladies, that's enough.
- She is my daughter.
- Just step away.
- Give her a chance.
- She's mine!
That's enough!