- [screaming]
Damn bloody--[speaking Swedish]
I'm not having this!
How's it going, bros?
PewDiePie.
You're about to watch me
get the absolute shit
scared out of me.
[yelling]
This show takes what I
already do--
getting scared
of horror games--
but taking it to the next
level,
a really fucked up level.
[screaming]
So if you love watching me
get scared shitless...
Fuck this! Fuck this!
Fuck this!
You're gonna love
"Scare PewDiePie."
- Oh, Mr. PewDiePie?
Hey!
- Hey!
Should I go around?
- No.
Come on.
Come over the top.
Stop goofing around.
- Why do we do this every time?
- Don't grab on to that.
That's what broke last time.
All right!
- All right.
How's it going, bros?
It's PewDiePie.
- Tonight, we're gonna go
to a doctor
who wants to discuss the results
of your medical test
we did the first day.
- They're gonna talk about
my results?
- Yeah.
Yeah, so there's someone who
is new to our crew tonight.
Jeff, this is Felix.
Felix, this is Jeff.
- Felix.
- Whoa, what the fuck?
Oh, my God.
- Let me go!
Let me--
I'll find you!
I'll find you, Felix!
In case something comes down,
they just asked me
to have extra people.
- Sounds good, 'cause I don't
trust those doctors anyways.
- All right.
Let's go.
- Okay.
- So you've had a couple
great game day plays, right?
- Yeah, last one was awesome.
- Excuse me.
Are you PewDiePie?
- Yeah, yeah.
I'm PewDiePie.
- Jeff--
- I'm sorry.
I'm packing tonight.
I just wanted you to know
you're covered.
- What does packing mean?
- Oh, you have a weapon?
- What did he say?
- He has a weapon,
a gun?
- Yeah, oh, fine.
- So what are we doing today?
Well, meeting doctors
at 9:00.
That's not weird at all.
- Kay, why don't you
put that on.
- God damn it.
Great. Great, guys.
Great hospital, guys.
My favorite so far.
Why is it so freaking hot?
- I just want you to
start concentrating,
'cause I feel like--
- What is that?
- You just need to use
your senses.
- What is that?
- Keep walking.
- [shrieks]
- Damon, fuck.
Why do you have to do that?
- Good-bye for now.
- Mm-hmm.
- For now.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
[girl laughing]
- [yelling]
It's time to do it.
Take it off.
- Okay.
Good to go.
I can do this.
[shrieking]
Hello?
Oh, shit.
[chuckles]
Oh, fuck me.
Okay.
How's it going over here?
- Bananas, bananas, bananas...
- Where's Sean?
[screaming]
- Fuck!
[scattered chattering]
Okay!
Jesus Christ!
What the fuck?
What was that?
[screaming, laughing]
- What are you doing
outside of your room?
- What? Me?
- You're agitating
all of the patients.
both: No, no, no, no, no.
- Let's go to your room.
It will be much safer.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Now just go up
to your room.
It's after curfew.
It's the time for you to relax.
- No?
- This is what they
always say.
Just come and sit.
Sit and relax.
Just take a load off
and relax your feet.
Sit down.
And we want to make sure
that nothing happens to you.
Everything will be completely--
- No, no, no!
- Just a--you need to be
in seclusion room.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Not kidding you.
We have had this
discussion before.
Felix, I'm sorry.
We must keep you safe.
There's nothing to worry about.
Don't struggle.
It will be less comfortable.
Remember, no one is released
until their paperwork
is signed by Dr. Yates.
I would kill to know
where your papers are.
- Fuck this.
- It's curfew!
Into your rooms, my lovelies.
Let's go.
- This is fucking bullshit.
Aw, come on.
Oh, no, hey, how's it going?
How you doing?
- Sean!
S-E-A-N.
- Okay.
- Not S-W-A-N.
S-E-A-N.
Got it?
- [stutters]
Thank you.
- Look what I got.
Look what I got.
- Would you mind?
- No, no, no, no,
I would not mind.
- Okay.
- Psyche!
[cackles]
- You got me.
- Yes, I got you.
Look at that, though.
There you go.
- Oh, cool.
- S-E-A-N!
- Sean, okay.
- I'm his favorite.
[yelps]
- Well, S-E-A-N.
Thank you very much.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Which one is it?
Come on.
Guys.
Okay, none of these fit.
Ha, ha, really funny.
Thanks a lot, Sean.
They're way too big.
[shrieking]
Fuck this.
Oh, shit.
[chuckles]
Come on!
How the--
Okay.
Oh, great, oops.
There you go.
Genius strikes again.
Not a problem.
Okay.
Cool.
Put this right back.
[groans]
Okay.
Good, great.
Gonna go home,
get a hot chocolate.
What the--
- Oh, hey.
- What?
- Hey, Pewds.
- What is--
- Come on, buddy.
Take a seat.
- Mr. Chair!
- Yeah!
- Will you help me out of here?
- Yep, but first, we need
to get your paperwork.
Hop on in, and I'll take you
to where you need to go.
- Okay, great.
This is amazing.
Take me to the exit.
- Come on, buddy.
- Okay.
I don't think--
No.
Mr. Chair,
what are you doing?
Oh, shit.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Mr. Chair, stop!
[chuckles]
Calm down.
- All right, Pewds,
I got to get you
through this hall of crazies.
Then we're gonna go
to the chapel.
- We're gonna go to the chapel.
Great, can't wait.
Okay.
[nervous laughing]
[yelps]
[whispering, cackling]
Yes.
Okay.
Oh.
Okay, okay!
Oh, shit.
What the fuck is this
doing here?
- All right, buddy,
hop on out,
head on into the chapel.
- [chuckles] Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Chair.
You're so nice.
Will you come back?
- I'll be waiting for you.
- Okay.
Just wait there.
What the fuck?
Okay.
What do we got?
Flicking lights, check.
This is my favorite chapel
of all time.
- [yells]
- [speaking Swedish]
- Look around.
And I'm supposed
to be crazy.
[chuckles]
You're gonna need those!
- Oh...
- You're gonna need those
when the lights go off.
- Oh, fuck.
Fucking hell.
Ugh.
Oh, dude.
No.
Oh, come on.
Thanks for keeping it warm,
guys.
Okay.
I can see with this.
This is great.
[shrieking, cackling]
[whispering]
- Oh, hey.
- Can I sit down?
- Yeah, take a seat.
- Okay.
Yes.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, oh, shit.
- I'm gonna take you
somewhere real fun.
- Oh, come on.
Oh.
Where are we going?
- I'm gonna take you
somewhere real fun.
- Where are we going?
- [distorted low voice]
Somewhere real fun...
- [yelling]
Okay, okay.
Ahh! Ahh!
[high-pitched cackling]
That's just great.
Oh, fuck you.
[screaming]
Okay!
Let's just go. Let's just go.
Let's just go.
Keep going.
What the fuck are you?
What the--
Oh, dude.
Hey, how are you doing?
- Bananas, bananas, bananas,
bananas, bananas...
[distorted voices]
Okay!
Okay.
Yes.
I'm ready to go home now.
Okay.
- When I ask questions,
I need answers.
- Oh, shit, Sean.
- I don't want to hurt you.
I just want to know very simply
where can I find the files?
- [yelling]
- Um, is this a bad time?
- Tell me where they are!
I hate asking multiple times.
So one last time, where will I
find Felix's file?
- Dr. Yates's office.
- That's all I needed to know.
- Please, Doc.
- I know now you're
very tired.
I'm going to give you just
a gentle--
- [screaming]
- Whoops, that was
Dr. Schwartz.
We need to go to Dr. Yates'
office
and get your paperwork.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
[nervous laughing]
[shrieking]
Go, Mr. Chair.
Go faster.
- Where is it?
- Right there.
It's right there.
I mean, right over there,
right over there.
It's over--it's over there!
Yes? Okay, great.
- I think we're here.
- Oh, great, thank you.
- Hop on out and go
into the office.
- Kay, just fucking great.
What the fuck is this?
What?
- Attention, all medical staff.
Dr. Yates will be in the
testing lab
for the next few hours.
If you need Dr. Yates
for any reason,
please stop by the testing lab.
Again, that's--test--
[static] Dr. Yates--for
testing--
- What?
Okay, great.
[phone ringing]
- [static] Hello?
- Hello?
- If you're looking
for the files,
proceed to find them
in the cabinets.
Crank them to open.
- Okay.
Crank...
Okay, I got this.
Not a problem.
Easy, there we go, files.
Files for days.
Protein shakes, my favorite.
Um...
Oh, it's a code.
I'm gonna put Sean.
It must be.
I can't get it open.
Am I an idiot?
Yes, I am an idiot.
Oh!
Okay!
Yes!
I did it all by myself!
[chuckles]
I don't know how these work.
Okay, all right.
It was a rough start,
but we can do this now.
Okay.
What?
Okay, what is this?
Okay, yes.
"Does this patient have
new psychiatric condition?"
What?
"And a history of mental
illness, Felix Kjellberg.
Yes."
- Attention, all medical staff.
If a patient wants to fill out
their full release paperwork,
they must get a signature
from the practicing physician.
- [chuckles] What?
Okay.
- You'll find Dr. Yates
in the lab.
- Don't want to--don't
want to do that.
"Has the patient been medically
cleared
in the emergency department?"
What the fuck is this?
I don't want to signature this.
This is bullshit.
Okay.
Here we go again.
Just great.
[shrieking]
Fantastic.
Where is it?
[yelling]
Oh! Fuck.
[scattered chattering,
cackling]
Oh, shit.
Okay.
No, I--they're over there.
They're over there.
Okay, great.
Okay.
I did it.
Hello?
Excuse me?
Are you okay?
Oh, fuck.
Okay, I just came--
- What are you doing here?
- I'm not doing anything.
What are you doing here?
I said answer me!
- I came for a signature.
- "Release paperwork for
patient Felix Kjellberg"?
Is this your release paperwork?
- Mm-hmm.
- This way to Dr. Yates.
- Okay.
[cackling]
Oh, shit.
[screaming]
Oh, what the shit?
Okay.
I'm--all right.
Jesus Christ.
Okay.
Oh, chair!
Shit! Shit!
Okay!
Fuck this! Fuck this!
Fuck this!
Where the fuck do I go?
Oh, shit!
Okay, I'm gonna go here.
Okay, exit, exit.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Fuck this place!
Where the fuck is the exit?
Where does it end?
No! No!
Jesus Christ.
Okay!
What the fuck?
- [yelling]
I got him!
You're safe.
Go back.
What's going on?
What happened?
- I never ran so much
in my life.
- What's your opinion
of American hospitals?
- You know, I can tell you
don't have health insurance
and stuff going on here.
It's a little bit more
sketchy here.
Hello.
- Hey.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Good, good, good.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- So I brought the paperwork out
for you to sign
so we can get started on your
restraining order
with Nikki.
- Tell them how much--
no, we love each other.
This will not be the end!
You can't stop real love.
- Okay.
- Have you had any other
incidents since we last spoke?
- Sorry, sir, I would like to
be--I mean,
I'm kind of his security detail,
so I'd like to sort of--
- So you want me to talk to you,
and you talk to him?
- I think that's the best thing.
- That's fine, but I normally
need to talk to him
because he's the person that's
gonna sign his name
on the dotted line.
- This is officer to officer.
- Well, I don't want to be
disrespectful,
but officer and security
are two different things.
- So we're both security.
- Okay.
- No, I haven't had any
incident with Nikki or anything.
- Did you ever see packages?
Do you understand, packages--
- Well, it's from fans.
- He did receive packages,
but not from Nikki.
- Well, okay.
This is for us
to get the temporary
restraining order going,
and then I'm gonna
need your signature
right down here at the bottom X.
- Is there a box that you can
check all packages?
- What is he talking about?
- He's your security guy.
You tell me.
Okay, so I just need you
to sign right here.
- Okay.
- And then I'll fill
this information in.
- Uh, right here?
- Yeah, right there
on the X.
- Is that it?
Is that it?
- That's it.
We're good.
- Thank you, officer.
- Appreciate that.
- Thank you so much.
- Keep an eye out.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Jeff, this is Felix.
Felix, this is Jeff.
- How's it going?
Felix.
- I generally do overnight
things,
donut shops or late-night
riding.
Hey, it's a one-way street,
guys.
It's a one-way street.
Could you guys--
- It's not a one-way street.
- People think security guards
are not prepared,
and I am fully prepared.
- He has a weapon,
a gun?
- Okay, good.
Just wrapped up another day.
Crazy as always,
but I did it.
And I'll see you
in the next one.
Brofist.
- You don't trust me.
I know you don't
trust me.
You probably haven't been
getting a lot of sleep.
So we got you--
- A pillow?
Okay.
[chuckles]
This is my favorite pillow.
Yes.