- [screaming]
Damn bloody--
[speaking Swedish]
I'm not having this!
How's it going, bros?
PewDiePie.
You're about to watch me
get the absolute shit
scared out of me.
- You're gonna be shot at today.
- What?
This show takes what I
already do--
getting scared
of horror games--
but taking it to the next
level...
Oh, fuck.
A really fucked up level.
[screaming]
So if you love watching me
get scared shitless...
Ah, God!
You're gonna love
"Scare PewDiePie."
[haunting music]
[upbeat music]
- Mr. PewDie, come on.
- PewDiePie.
Oh, my God,
Jeff is here.
What the fuck?
- It's a one-way street.
- No, it's not.
- I have a lot of love
for costumes.
- He has a weapon--
a gun?
- Rachel said Jeff is to
stay with you guys all day.
I don't care if he's
in the shot,
'cause Felix's safety
is of utmost importance.
- All right.
- Can you please put this on?
Is that--
- If it'll make you quiet,
yeah, I'll put it on.
- I'll put it on you.
I'm security.
If you're lost,
as you've been in the past,
you blow it,
and I'll be there.
[whistle blows]
There you go.
That's exactly
what I want to hear.
- Great, all right.
Let's go.
- What?
- Let's go.
♪ ♪
- All right, here's what
I can tell you.
You're gonna be shot at today.
- What?
- Tonight's is gonna be...
- Oh, come on.
- Pretty insane.
- Will I be in pain?
- Yes.
Oh, yes.
- Jeff, what do you have
to say about this?
- I'll be there.
- Okay, yeah, Jeff,
have you ever fired a gun?
- Of course I've fired a gun.
2006, .38 caliber,
six-round chamber,
and he was shot
in the lower abdomen.
- Okay, yes.
- All right.
- I think I'm here
for a good reason.
I'm here because of threats.
- What threats?
- There are some threats online.
What I deem, out of six,
a level six.
- Which is not--
But we have a restraining order
against--
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Is Nikki doing something?
- She posted something online.
- What did she post?
- She posted a video.
- So that's why Jeff is here?
- Yes.
- Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
- PewDiePie!
Hi, Felix.
I miss you.
- What the fuck?
- [giggles]
- Okay.
- Is it weird that
I think I'm your penguin.
- "I'm your penguin"?
- It's the best!
[chuckles]
Swedish Fish, how many
can I fit in my mouth?
Can you guess, Felix?
I'll show you in real life.
- This is a level six threat?
- Yeah.
- That threat is the reason
I've been outside your house
the last couple nights.
- Okay, let's go, guys.
- No.
Can't we have the googly eyes?
This is all for you.
- What the fuck is this?
What the fuck is this?
- All for your protection.
- All for my protection.
Yeah, okay.
No, come on.
Kneepads, are you kidding--
- Can we get the baseball bat
to test the knee pads?
- Jeff!
I can't reach the whistle.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Does that hurt?
- No.
- Remember the safety phrase.
Say it twice.
- Bananas, bananas.
- That's not the safety phrase.
- Is after this the parachute?
- Yes.
- The--
- This is where I leave you.
The next person you hear,
the next voice you will hear
will help you through the game.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
- Damn it, okay.
- I love you.
Stay safe.
- Thanks.
- Okay?
- [shrieks]
- Why?
[sighs]
Hard to breathe
in this fucking thing.
- Stand by, private.
- Oh, Jesus Christ,
that's loud.
- Remove your blindfold,
private.
- Okay, okay, I'm removing
my blindfold.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is this?
Hey, it's my logo.
- Do you know where you are?
- I have no idea.
- You are in a military
installation.
- A milintary
insfallation--installation.
Okay, great.
- We have infiltrated
a deadly military faction
known only as "Barrels."
Your mission is simple.
You must sneak
into their headquarters
and find a clue to bring back
to your home base.
- Well, I'm guessing this--
this thing
has something to do with it.
- You will bring back
three pieces of a clue.
When you connect the pieces,
you will have a code
that will help you escape.
- I already know I'm gonna
fail at this shit.
But okay.
Let's give it a go.
- Your mission can be
easy or hard.
- Do I get to pick?
- Private,
I'm gonna ask you a question.
The answer will determine
the alert level of the enemy.
- Ugh, okay.
- Level one: what do you call
the scary monster in "Amnesia"?
- The Bro, easy.
[electronic chime]
Whoo-hoo!
Yes.
- All right, Private Pie.
You get to go through
the easy door.
- Yes!
Awesome.
- That means the enemy
is on low alert.
- Oh, shit.
- Look for the symbol
of resistance
and find that clue.
- Okay, symbol of resistance,
find the clue.
I get the easy door.
Fuck yes.
Okay.
- Even though the enemy
is on low-level alert,
they're still out there.
Watch out.
- Find the symbol
down this alleyway.
Don't be seen.
- How many of them are there?
- Proceed with caution.
- Okay, okay.
- Do you see the symbol?
- Open the case.
Oh, shit.
How the fuck do I--
- Are they coming?
- What?
What the fuck is he on about?
- Remember, this is
the easy level.
- Oh, shit.
I got it.
Yes, I did something.
Yes, yes.
Fuck yes.
- Okay, okay.
Got the first one.
Fuck yes.
Hmm, what could it be?
I don't know.
Yes.
Nailed that shit.
- Question two,
what is the name
of the doctor who you needed
a signature from
in the mental hospital?
- Pfft, are you fucking
kidding me?
- No one is released until
their paperwork
is signed by Dr. Yates.
- This way to Dr. Yates.
- Yates! Yates!
[yelling]
- Dr. Schwartz.
[buzzer blares]
- The correct answer
is Dr. Yates.
You're going to have to
go through the hard door.
- Okay.
I can do this.
This is for my bros.
I'm guessing I have to
unlock that shit later.
Private Pie is going out.
- Remember, the soldiers
will be on high-level alert.
- Don't breathe.
- Proceed with caution.
- What?
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Get back to base!
Get back to base!
- Holy shit.
Okay.
I'm the worst stealther ever.
So there is hope.
Okay, there we go.
That's where that belongs.
- You need one more piece.
- Private Pie is ready.
Give me--give me the news.
- Here's your final question.
What is your safe phrase?
- Are we doing a safe word?
I think we should
do a safe word.
- Yeah, okay.
What are you--
what are you thinking?
- Pineapples.
- Okay, guys,
we're sticking with pineapples.
Feel safer now?
Feel good?
- Yeah, I'm glad
we got a safe word.
[chuckles]
Bananas, bananas.
[buzzer blares]
Okay, that's just great.
Not right.
Fine.
I'm up for a challenge.
- Listen up, Private Pie.
You got to go deeper
into enemy territory
than you've ever gone.
- Holy shit.
- You've got to find
the third and final symbol.
- Third and final symbol.
- Hard door,
you know where to go.
- Hard door, got it.
My favorite door.
- Remember, the enemy
will be on high alert.
- They're delivering something.
- You've got to find
the third and final symbol.
- No, I don't.
- It's on the other side
of those barrels.
Stay low.
[cans clanging]
- Find the piece!
Find the piece!
Hide! Hide!
Shut the door!
- Fuck me.
- Scramble! Scramble!
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Private P--Private P--
Private Pie, 100%.
100% Private Pie.
3, 8, 7, 5--is that the code
to the lock?
This better fucking work.
Eight...
- We trained you
for this, son.
- You didn't train me shit.
Yes! Okay.
What's in here?
No!
Oh, fuck.
Ah, yeah!
- Remember your mission.
Be ready to take them down.
When you have eliminated
the enemy,
we will rendezvous
at the extraction point.
- That can't be right.
We have heat signatures
on 40 soldiers.
- 40? Are you kidding me?
- Don't worry, you can be hit
up to 30 times
before you lose your life.
- 30?
Are you fucking kidding me?
- Why don't you create a
distraction to draw them out?
[can clangs]
- Who threw that can?
- Go, go, go!
- Take him down now!
- Smoke him!
- Get him!
[all talking at once]
- Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck!
[screaming]
[speaking Swedish]
- Fire back!
- I don't want to fire back!
[squeals]
- Fire back, God damn it!
You got to shoot them.
- Ha, ha!
Got you, bitch!
Take that motherfuckers!
[explosion booms]
- Reload, reload!
- [squeals]
Ahh!
Whoo!
I'm out.
Shit, I wasted so many--
Ow! Fucking ass!
- Remember, their head
is their weak spot.
- Why are you telling me
this now?
[yelling]
Oh!
- If you can make it
to the third symbol,
you can reload.
- [screaming]
[whistle blowing]
Is that the--oh, shit.
- How many of them are left?
- Too many, dude.
Too fucking many.
- No, they've got a grenade!
- Shit.
Shit!
[yelling]
- Your health bar is critical!
- Yeah, no, I'm pretty sure--
Ahh!
Fucking ass!
Got your dick!
This is my final seven.
[slo-mo screaming]
[screaming]
I'm gonna use my last G.
This one's for Timmy.
[explosion booms]
This is it for Private Pewds.
Sergeant, I don't think
I'm gonna make it.
I'm out of ammo.
Tell my subs--
tell the bros--
do it for the--
- Private Pie,
I got good news.
- What?
- You've taken out
the enemy.
They're all dead.
- Really?
Oh.
Well, how about that, bitches?
- We're gonna help you
find a way out of here.
- I need a medic
for my ass, dude.
- Go to the green light.
That's your extraction point.
[siren blaring]
They're coming in behind you!
They've triggered the
explosives!
Run! Run! Run!
[explosions booming]
- [screaming]
- This way, this way, this way!
- This way.
- Straight, straight,
straight in.
Out, out, out, out, out!
- Yeah!
[cheers and applause]
- What's up?
Central command,
central command.
- They got me in the ass.
When that happened,
I was like, "I'm done."
I want to see, 'cause I got
hit in the head so many--
oh, Jesus Christ.
Look at this.
[applause]
- Really good job, man,
really good job.
- Want to learn
how to work these weapons?
- Ready to kick some ass.
- You ready to win?
- Fuck yeah.
- We lost a lot of good men
out there.
- Well, it ain't gonna be me.
- You sure about that?
- Nope.
- Where you from?
- Sweden.
- They have men in Sweden?
- Yes.
We have men in Sweden.