Previously on This Is Us...
My nephew came back
into my life.
No matter how much
I told him to scram.
You should come
to Philly with me.
For Thanksgiving.
Deja, I'm sorry we haven't
taken you to see Shauna.
I'd actually like
to invite her here.
For Thanksgiving.
Aw, open up.
- There you go.
- Oh, my, this is...
Well, this is terrible timing.
Kate, you did it.
He's eating it.
First solid food, buddy.
I'm not gonna go see some doctor
just because
you're overreacting.
- I'm just worried that there could be...
- I said I'm fine.
- Mom.
- Randall!
Enough.
- I hate Thanksgiving.
- Shh. Nicky.
And Layne finishes it out,
hitting the 101 mark
in touchdown passes
for a Lions win, 28 to 24.
- Yes.
- Dang it.
Pay up, daddy-O.
Jack!
Nicky! Where the hell are you?
It's okay.
What, too much thankfulness
going on in there?
Huh. Grandpa's three sheets
to the wind and won't stop
asking me if I'm scared
of being drafted next week.
Mom burned the bird
and Dad's about to blow.
And it's only 11:00.
Well, it's the best day
of the year, every single year,
like clockwork, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
You want to split?
And just ditch Thanksgiving?
Shoot.
Yo. Ready to, uh,
hit the road to Philly?
Wow, well, look at you.
You look sharp.
- I look like I'm in a Viagra commercial.
- You do not.
You look very, uh,
you know, newly sober chic.
I'm not sure about this, Kevin.
I'm telling you.
I'm 100% on this.
Pleated pants are in.
GQ did a whole spread.
I'm not talking about
pleated pants, you nitwit.
Uh, coming to your brother's
for Thanksgiving,
you know,
with your whole family.
- Nicky, everyone's really excited to see you.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They are... It's gonna be
perfect, trust me. Okay?
What are you gonna
do about that monstrosity
of a trailer out there?
Uh, I don't... I haven't, you
know, called to return it yet.
I don't...
I-I was thinking, you know,
after Thanksgiving,
I'd drive you back here
and maybe spend
a little more time in Bradford.
- Really? Hmm.
- Maybe.
All right.
Good morning, my turkeys.
Good morning, my giblets.
This would be easier to do
if you had two hands, you know?
Hey, why are we setting up
a card table in the foyer?
'Cause our dining table
only seats eight,
and we've expecting 13 guests...
with all the birth moms
and long-lost uncles.
Yeah.
- Just lean in, baby.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hey, Deja. You look nice.
Uh, you sure it's not too fancy?
- I think your mom will love it.
- Thanks.
Um, I don't know.
I'm still gonna change.
I'm not feeling it.
Oh, dear God,
please let Shauna be okay.
Deja is so nervous. I just want
today to go well for her.
Amen.
Just go talk to her.
It's Thanksgiving.
She probably wants to make up
as much as you do.
Hey.
You guys are up
and cooking already, huh?
Mm-hmm.
So, Randall, I'm putting, uh,
chorizo in the stuffing.
- Barefoot Contessa-style.
- Nice.
Mom, Kevin and Uncle Nicky are
en route and Kate just texted.
- Their flight is on time.
- Great.
Okay, so I'm gonna go set up
the VCR for Police Academy 3,
and let you guys have
an opportunity to talk.
Cool.
I got all
the traditional staples.
The saltines, the hot dogs,
the Kraft Singles.
Randall, I did not forget.
I was just gonna
make myself some tea.
I'm sorry. I didn't realize.
You know, I also managed to make
the cranberry sauce this morning
- without blowing up the house.
- Of course you did.
Mom, I didn't mean
to overstep last night.
- I'm sorry if I...
- Yeah, you know, I-I...
really want to try
and put last night behind us.
I know. Me, too.
But at some point,
we need to talk about
what's going on with you.
- If we think this...
- Okay. I need some space.
I need to get out of here
for a minute.
- Where are you going, Mom?
- I don't know.
I'm gonna go get dressed
and just take a walk,
clear my head, I don't kn...
Maybe I'll go see a movie.
I'll be back in time for dinner.
And I would, um, appreciate it
if you kept this little argument
of ours between us.
- Of course.
- Okay.
I will pick up a pie
on the way back.
Dad, I can't find
the Thanksgiving box.
The Pilgrim Rick hat is in it.
Oh, and there's this really
funny hat that your Grandpa Jack
used to wear.
Oh, and we'll be listening
to Police Academy 3.
Which is kind of like PAW Patrol
but with humans and swearing.
My CrossFit group text
is going crazy for Jack's
first solid food video.
They love it, buddy. Huh?
And-and my Insta is-is,
like, blowing up.
The likes just keep rolling in.
- Toby, I have to tell you something.
- Okay.
Um, and listen,
I am, I am so, so sorry.
It was a total accident.
But, um...
Jack's first avocado was
actually at Gregory's house
when you weren't home.
What?
Yeah, he just, he wasn't
taking food that morning,
and-and when he went...
When Gregory went to feed him,
I just, I didn't stop him
and then...
Wow. This is...
So-so, you've just been lying
to me for the last 24 hours?
Tobe.
You feeding Jack was still
a real beautiful moment.
Was it, Kate?
'Cause thinking back on it now,
it seems kind of humiliating.
Okay... Toby, I'm home alone
all day with Jack.
Okay? And things
are gonna happen.
So what if he takes
his-his first steps
when you're at CrossFit?
What am I gonna do?
Should I, should I
just knock him down?
Yeah, okay, no, so it's my fault
that you fed him an avocado
and then lied to me about it.
Because I was at the gym.
Okay, got it.
I did not say it was your fault.
I meant that... You know what?
I'm sorry,
a-and I'm just, I'm tired.
Yeah.
- It's okay.
- You know what? It's okay.
It's okay.
We're all tire...
We're all tired.
It's probably why
I am overreacting
to AvocadoGate here.
There will be plenty
of firsts, right?
Right.
Like his first Thanksgiving.
- Yeah.
- This is your first one, buddy.
It's gonna be awesome. Yeah.
You know, I can't believe
you bet against Dallas
just because Dad
loves the Cowboys.
And with Jonny?
- Yeah.
- Touchdown Cowboys.
The extra point will tie it up.
Hey, how much did you bet,
- anyhow?
- Mm. 200 bucks.
- 200? Jesus...
- It's not like I can bring it with me.
You know what, stop.
You're not going to Vietnam.
You are not gonna get
your number called next week.
And the kick is good.
The Cowboys are going to
escape with a 24-24 tie.
Oh, co... What are you
grinning about? I-It...
ended in a tie.
All right? You got lucky.
It's a push.
No, it's not.
What do you got, points?
Jonny gave you points?
Happy Thanksgiving.
Thanks, Jonny.
- How much money is that?
- It's a lot.
It's really nice
- to finally meet you, Nicky.
- Oh.
Hey, this place is amazing.
You call this downsizing?
Don't test me, brother-in-law.
And, uh, what fell on your face?
Uh, walked into a wall.
- All good.
- Uh, it would be in the attic.
Yeah, the cardboard box labeled
"Thanksgiving" or "Holidays."
- Thank you so much for checking.
- Come on. My brother.
Happy Thanksgiving.
What happened to your face?
Eh, fly ball to the face.
Yeah. Nicky.
You look amazing.
Kevin Queer Eyed you, huh?
I don't know what that means.
- He does.
- Uncle Kevin!
Hey! There she is.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Thank you
so much, yes. I'll see you soon.
Great news.
The new owners of our old house
found the box
- of holiday stuff in the attic.
- Randall...
- Yes.
- You are really not gonna drive
all that way just to get a box
of our old Thanksgiving
tradition stuff?
I'll go get my coat.
That's my girl!
All right, well,
hurry your ass up,
because Shauna's
gonna be here at 2:00 and
I don't want to be here alone
if she shows up in a bad way.
- Understood.
- Uh, think I could ride along?
You... They're going to Jersey.
I don't mind. Gives me time
to get to know Russell.
- It's Randall.
- See?
Uh...
It's fine, Kev.
Annie, you're driving.
Where's my mom?
William?
Hey.
You know, I've been here for,
like, ten minutes.
You didn't come down and say hi?
Hey, Uncle Kev.
That is not my niece's
beautiful smile.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Testify! Get it?
Tess-tify.
I don't really want
to talk about it.
Oh, come on.
Besides, I need something
to get my mind off of
worrying about my uncle so much.
Fine.
There's this stupid meme
going around school
that everybody's posting
on Instagram.
"Post a pic of your number one
celebrity crush." Oh.
So what's going on?
I haven't come out
at school yet.
So I could post nothing
and be left out.
Or I can post the truth.
I have a crush on Zendaya.
Yeah?
That's my choice, too.
But your life won't
completely explode
if you say it.
Hey, let's get out of here.
Let's get a bite.
- There's so much food here.
- Yeah, but I need air.
You know? I need air.
- Let's go get some air. Come on.
- Okay.
All right, we're off to get
a pre-turkey snack.
And then there was Beth.
Uh, what am I, chopped liver?
Aw, Migs...
You know I love you.
Shauna, hi.
I know I'm crazy early...
Oh, that's no problem.
Come on in.
How you doing?
Good, Beth. Really, really good.
Good. Deja told me
you got a new job.
- How's it going?
- Pretty good.
I'm working the front desk
at Delaware General Hospital.
The hours are long but
the benefits are really good.
Wow. That's fantastic.
This is a pineapple
upside down cake.
It's Deja's favorite, so...
Oh, she's gonna love that.
You're early.
Tater Tot. Oh! Mm...
My God, you are so grown.
And you're so beautiful.
You look better than ever, baby.
You, too, Mom.
Um, you want to help me
make cookies?
Lead the way.
William?
Excuse me, William, it's...
Can I help you with something?
I'm sorry, I thought...
I thought you were someone else.
Oh, well,
sorry to disappoint.
Uh, are you all right?
I'm... I am, I'm just
not from around here.
Actually, um, could you tell me
if there's a bakery nearby,
because I need to
pick something up.
- Hmm, a bakery?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, there is a nice grocery
store around the corner.
Fresh-made whipped cream cakes.
Yes. Yes.
That's what I'm looking for.
Perfect.
Thank you very much.
Thank you to Dad
for loving the Cowboys,
and thank you to me
for hating Dad.
Could you just... Could you
put it away, all right?
- Look, people are gonna start watching.
- Let them watch.
It's probably more dough
than they've seen
in their entire life.
Well, it's more money than we've
seen in our entire life.
Here's to that. Whoa, hey.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
You realize this is
five pounds of shrimp?
- Oh, we realize. Mm-hmm.
- Good luck.
Don't need luck.
This is a Thanksgiving
dinner, huh?
Cheers.
Good job.
Hey, Deja, check this out.
Whiskey Business.
- You get it?
- What?
Come on.
You don't know that?
You're too young.
Oh, Deja, come here, come here.
Look what just popped up
on my Facebook timeline.
Nine years ago today.
- My first Cupid Shuffle.
- Oh, look at your little feet go.
I remember that night.
Mrs. Henderson was so pissed.
Hey, Beth. You okay?
All right.
Here's the thing about AA, okay?
A big part of it is
sort of taking things
one day at a time, okay?
One step at a time,
one person at a time.
Okay.
Okay, so it got me thinking
instead of coming out
to everyone all at once, right,
well, what if you just
come out to one person?
Just a complete stranger.
Someone you don't even have
to look in the eye. Right?
Just to see how it feels.
You want me to come out to...
The drive-through speaker. Yeah.
Yeah. No pressure, though.
Okay? No pressure.
Only if you want.
But, I mean, think about it.
All right?
What could be less scary
than coming out
to a-a plastic clown head?
Oh, here we go.
Welcome to Happy Burger.
What can I get you?
Tell you what, I'm gonna do
a number four
and a chocolate shake.
I'm Tess Pearson, and I'm gay.
Uh, cool.
You want fries or onion rings
with that number four?
Fries, please.
- Hey, happy Thanksgiving.
- It's so good to be here.
Oh, my gosh, guys,
he's so beautiful.
Must be all the avocado.
I'm on the Gram now.
BigMig45. You should follow me.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
- Yeah, our boy loves avocado.
Hey, do you guys have room
for this in your fridge?
It's, uh, it's my tempeh.
I'm on a special diet.
- We travel with tempeh now.
- Oh. Yeah.
- I'll find some room in the fridge for it.
- Yeah, thanks.
Oh, my God, this apartment...
This is downsizing?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Wait, where is everyone?
And every year, someone wears it
and pretends to be Pilgrim Rick.
Wait, you're Grandpa Jack's
brother, right?
Yes.
So why haven't we met before?
Because your grandfather
erased me.
Hey, Annie, why don't you
go ring the doorbell?
We'll be right there. Nicky...
are you okay?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I...
I thought I could handle this,
but it's too much.
I mean, his own granddaughter
has never even heard of me.
I knew he'd never talked
about me that much,
but I don't know...
- Hello?
- Yeah.
You must be Randall.
- I am.
- Come on in.
Thank you.
Whoa. Everything is different.
But I love what
you've done with the place.
Thank you.
It's such a beautiful house.
It really was... is.
It really is.
- Here's your holiday box.
- Thank you.
Grandpa Jack's hat!
- Now we're talking.
- Yes.
Oh, I also found these.
Uh, are these yours?
Um...
Yeah.
Sorry, my mom gave me these
as a housewarming gift
when we first moved in here.
Nobody loves music like my mom.
Excuse me. Hi.
Could you tell me where
the bakery is?
Yeah, it's just straight
down there
past the checkout aisles,
you can't miss it.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Ooh, so pretty.
That'll be $16.05.
Okay.
These...
bottomless purses,
I tell you what,
they're all the rage, but you
can never find anything in them.
Sorry. Okay.
I haven't eaten anything today.
I think that's why
my brain's a little fuzzy.
Good Chinese place
down the street.
Oh, that does sound good.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Wait, so there's
no dairy in this?
- 100% cashew, m'lady.
- Wow.
This is some
damn good nut cheese.
- Right? That's what I'm saying.
- Yeah, best I've ever had.
That whole tray is nut-based.
- What?
- Look, you get in the box with me for one week,
come meet my trainer KJ,
we'll get you on a meal plan,
you'll lose five pounds...
Bang... like that.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Not a bunch of weight, just...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm ashamed. It's evil.
I'm evil, you know.
I can't even say it out loud.
OKAY, WELL, HOW ABOUT THIS:
you tell me your evil feeling
and I'll tell you mine.
I hate that Shauna's
doing so well.
Okay, that is bad.
I know, I know.
I was praying for her
last night.
Like, praying on my knees
that she would show up here
today in a good place,
but then... I see them
together watching
home videos, or busting out
inside jokes, and I don't know.
It's just simpler for Randall.
He's the only father
she's ever known,
but she already has a mom,
you know?
Where does that leave me?
Okay, I said my terrible thing,
you say yours.
I hate CrossFit Toby.
I do, I do.
I hate his food charts,
his "fat blocks,"
his CrossFit acronyms.
- What?
- Yeah.
You know, the first thing
I said to him when we met
was that I couldn't fall
for a fat person
'cause I was determined
to lose the weight,
I don't want anyone
to get in my way,
- and we-we broke up over it.
- Yeah.
And then we committed
to losing the weight together,
but we didn't.
And then we had a baby,
a baby with special needs,
and I have never been
more stressed, more tired,
more overwhelmed
in my entire life.
And then he goes
and loses the weight,
which is amazing,
but all I can think is he did it
without me.
You sh... you should tell him
how you feel.
N... I wouldn't even
know how to.
Honey, just figure it out
'cause if you're only going
to other people
about what's happening
in your marriage, it's...
it can be dangerous territory.
Why don't you pick one of those
and pop it in, Uncle Nicky?
Leonard Cohen?
Oh, man, my dad
used to love this song.
"So Long Marianne."
Loved listening to it.
Loved explaining it to us
even more.
Over and over...
This next song
was requested via mail from one of
our brave troops in Vietnam.
Hoping you're having some kind
of Thanksgiving there, boys.
Your loved ones
sure are missing you here.
No, no, no, no. Leave it.
It's Leonard Cohen. He's a poet.
Nicky, if I wanted a poem,
I'd read a book.
No, you wouldn't.
Just listen.
He's singing about
the love of his life
moving on from him,
but there's no bitterness
in him.
He's just grateful
to have loved her.
He was lost before he met her
and then she became his home.
And in the chorus, listen,
he's saying goodbye,
but he can't quite let go.
He's sending her away
and calling her back
in the same breath.
I just hope that
she came back to him
and that they laughed again.
I hope she went back to him
and they laughed together again.
Something my dad
would always say
whenever he listened
to this song.
Uh, nope, he called it a poem.
He'd give us all kind of hell
if we called it a song.
Can we, uh, make a quick stop
on the way home?
Sure.
- Everything good?
- It was delicious.
Thank you very much.
I just had it.
Come on.
Um, ma'am? Hi. Sorry.
Um, I need to call my son,
and I can't find my phone.
Um, uh, do you,
do you have a phone
that I can use?
A telephone?
- To call... Yeah.
- Oh.
Uh, great.
God.
I don't know his number.
I can't...
His number is in my phone,
and I need my phone to call him.
I need to call my son.
You're not helping me right now.
I need to call my...
You found it.
- There it is.
- Hey, Tobe.
- Yeah?
- Talk to you for a minute?
Yeah, of course.
Just give me one sec.
These are sweet potatoes.
They are orange.
They're like the regular
potato's sassy aunt.
What's up?
Happy Thanksgiving.
All right.
Oh, come on,
that was pass interference.
Hey, you like football now?
Oh, Dej,
I'm a die-hard Eagles fan.
- I bleed green and white.
- Since when?
Well, some friends
from work get together
every Sunday
and watch the games.
We all bring different dishes,
do a potluck.
I've gotten really into it.
Sounds like fun.
Um, excuse me a second.
After you.
Hey. Shauna.
You're early.
It's good to see you.
You look great.
Uh, Nicky, this is Shauna.
She's our, uh,
- adopted daughter's biological mother.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Um, I need a platter.
Oh, it's in the pantry.
Right here.
- Oh, got it.
- I'll be right with you, Shauna.
I can't wait to catch up.
Is my mom here?
- Not yet, baby.
- Huh.
- How's Shauna?
- She's good.
She has a job and an apartment,
and, um, made
an upside down cake.
That's a good thing?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I'll be right back, okay?
Okay. Hey, guys. One sec.
You're reached
Rebecca Pearson. Please leave a message.
Hey, Mom. Uh, you haven't
returned any of my texts
and now your phone's off.
Trying not to worry, but, um,
it's almost time to eat,
so hope you're close.
Please come home.
Bye. What's up, sis?
- Hi.
- How're you doing?
Hey.
We're gonna sit down to dinner
as soon as Rebecca gets back.
Cool.
Your mom seems like
she's doing pretty great.
She is. She-she loves
her new job,
and she has a whole bunch
of friends.
She has a new apartment
and it sounds real nice, too,
um, even has a fireplace.
When I was growing up,
we'd always say one day
that we'd have a fireplace.
Now... she finally has one.
Why couldn't she
be like this for me?
Oh, honey.
Hey,
tell me the story
about that video.
What?
With you and your mom
and the dancing.
- Oh.
- Tell me about that day.
Um...
Yeah, I got it.
Our downstairs neighbor,
Mrs. Henderson,
um, she was as mean
as they come,
and... on that morning,
she was out front and
she asked me what we were doing
for Thanksgiving and I told her
we were bringing in takeout.
And then she said something
about how my mama
wasn't raising me right
and how maybe
if she knew how to cook,
she'd be able
to keep a man around.
- Ugh, Mrs. Henderson.
- Right?
And my mom knew Mrs. Henderson
hated when we made noise,
so there was no better revenge
in her mind
than teaching me
the Cupid Shuffle.
I mean, music cranked
all the way up,
feet stomping as loud
as we could stomp.
- Genius.
- It was... it was perfect.
Hey.
You may not have gotten
the fireplace, but...
don't let yourself
forget all the times
you had with her
when she was absolutely perfect.
Yeah.
Thank you for the
ride, Officers, but this is all
really unnecessary.
You're a long way
from Los Angeles.
Yeah. I'm out here
visiting family.
We always get together
for special occasions.
- Hey, hey.
- So...
Tell me, how did... you know,
how'd it go with Uncle Nicky?
Dude, it went great.
- Really?
- He's in the kitchen fixing something
to add to our dinner. Been very
secretive about it. It's cute.
- He is cute.
- Yeah.
- And still no Mom?
- No.
Why would she go off by herself
on Thanksgiving?
She must've really wanted to see
that new De Niro movie.
- Do you know who Steve Guttenberg is?
- Yeah.
He is one of my
top three favorite...
What about Michael Winslow?
- Excuse me.
- A sound effects genius.
Excuse me. Uh...
Well, I've learned that, uh...
traditions inspired
by Jack Pearson
are sort of the backbone
of this shindig.
So...
So, uh... here goes.
Uh...
Thanksgivings growing up
weren't... you know, jolly
like this.
But... we made do.
So how bent you think
the old man's gonna be?
I think this one's
gonna be a doozy.
It was actually
the best Thanksgiving ever.
Okay, so then,
we'll do it again next year.
And the year after that.
And then again,
the year after that.
And we would've
kept that promise.
And we would've kept
that tradition.
But life, you know?
Got in the way.
So...
Here is five pounds
of Thanksgiving shrimp.
Yeah.
It's for Jack.
My brother. And, uh...
Yeah, to new...
family traditions, so...
- Enjoy.
- Hear, hear.
Jack, five-minute warning.
Everyone'll be here soon.
- Those hot dogs smell amazing.
- I know.
Our baby and I
need to eat them stat.
Have some shrimp.
There's five pounds.
It was really beautiful,
Uncle Nicky.
Eh... Hey, kid.
I think it's time for you
to get back to L.A.
Live your own life.
I'm gonna be just fine, Kevin.
And if I need you,
I'll call you.
If you need me, you call me.
- Okay.
- Good.
Okay. Yeah.
Feel like you disappeared on me.
- Look at this Pilgrim Rick.
- Pilgrim Rick.
I know, I know, I know.
Kate, will you grab my phone
real quick before he melts down?
- I got it.
- This is a special moment, Jack.
- Oh...
- There we...
That's what
you call full circle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Kate?
Can you say shrimp? Can you say
five pounds of shrimp?
- Kate? Photo? Huh? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- We don't want to miss this; he's gonna melt down.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, ready?
- Say "shrimp."
- Got it.
Kevin!
Yo. What do we got?
How we doing?
The comments.
- That's what's up! See, this is great.
- I know.
Look at this.
These are great... oh.
- I sense joy here.
- Yes.
- I could use some. What's happening?
- Well...
Yeah, you can tell him.
Your daughter
came out on Instagram today.
- What?
- Yeah.
Wow, Tess.
- This is huge.
- Yeah. -Thanks. My phone is,
like, blowing up.
I've got to go deal with this.
- Yes.
- Yeah, of course, no.
My goodness.
- Well, look at you, Ray Donovan.
- Yeah.
- Just fixing everybody.
- Well, I don't know about that.
Brother. What's next for you?
Uh, next is, um...
I don't know, man.
You know, I-I spent two months
in that small town.
You know, spent every day
with-with two virtual strangers,
and, uh... I got to tell you,
I haven't had that feeling
since I was a kid.
You know? Just...
a feeling of, um...
just being responsible
for other people. You know?
Sense of a family. So...
I liked it. You know?
I liked it, so I think, um...
I think that's what's next
for me.
Yeah. For sure.
Absolutely. By the time I'm 40,
I'm gonna have a wife,
I'm gonna have a kid,
- the whole shebang.
- You should probably date somebody first.
You know, it's only nine months
till our birthday.
Why you always got to be a buzzkill? Huh?
By the way, where is Mom?
I'm starving.
Are you starving? I'm starving.
Uh...
All right, ma'am, you're home.
Everything's gonna be okay.
- Mom. Come on in. Hi.
- Hi.
Thank you very much
for bringing her home.
Thank God.
Mom, we've been, you know,
- calling nonstop.
- I'm sorry, I-I went out
to try and get you
a birthday cake to surprise you,
and then I got all...
turned around.
- I hope I didn't ruin your whole party.
- No.
- Happy 40th, sweetheart.
- Thanks, Mom. Thank you.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you, Mom.
- Here, I got you this.
- Thank you.
You came back.
I was getting worried.
Of course I came back.
That movie was
three and a half hours long,
and then the line at the store
was huge.
I left you a bunch of messages.
Oh. I turned off my cell phone
for the movie.
I must've forgotten
to turn it back on.
I'm sorry.
Hi, everyone.
All right, thanks.
Oh, how's she doing back there?
Uh, she's laying down.
She's a little nauseous.
My fiancée's
got morning sickness
at all hours of the day, so...
Oh, try ginger tea.
- That always worked for me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Ginger tea. Good tip. Thank you.
And, um, thank you very much
for bringing my mom home.
Yes, thank you.
Good luck with that.
Thank you.
Kevin, is Randall here yet?
No, Mom. Randall's not coming.
We're not speaking, remember?
Mmm, looks delicious.
Hey.
- And I'll just take that off your hands.
- Don't... Now...
Stop. Hey.
- Hmm?
- Um...
I'm really sorry, Mom.
About last night.
I was probably overreacting
and...
you know.
I was halfway through
the trailer of Cats...
when I couldn't remember
what movie I went to go see.
I think I need to see a doctor.
Okay.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH