Previously on
"This Is Us"...
- Mom! Kevin!
- Hey. -What's up, buddy?
What do you say?
Get me up high.
There it is.
Stay the hell
away from my wife.
She is her daddy's world.
I want more for her
than you can offer her.
I will do everything I can
to stop this.
I did have a really nice time
tonight.
Okay.
- You can come inside for a water.
- All right.
- A water.
- Uh-huh.
Every part of my body aches
like death right now.
Do you want to have sex?
And I'm cured.
You're a witch.
All right.
Okay, you can look.
Schwing.
Stop. That's my spot.
Stop.
Okay, what's the safe word?
Uh, spatula?
Oh!
Mm.
Wait.
Promise me we'll always be hot
for each other.
Easiest promise
I'll ever make.
Not even
if you paid me in gold.
*THIS IS US*
Season 04 Episode 06
Episode Title: "The Club"
You are... insatiable.
- Only for you.
- Mm.
I really want to.
But I promised my mom
I would have brunch with her.
Oh...
Killed the mood.
- Sorry.
- Killed the mood.
Do you think
you could maybe drop me off
at my parents'?
'Cause Jenny has my car.
Please?
Come on. It's 20 minutes away.
Yeah, no, it...
No, it's fine.
It's not that. I just, um...
I don't think your parents
really approve of me
after that first dinner
at the club.
- What?
- I just...
Think I was talking about myself
too much.
Jack, you never talk
about yourself.
I loved it.
Okay.
Okay, okay, fine,
I'll give you a ride.
But I just want you to know,
there is no such thing
as a free brunch.
Dad, come on. Let's go.
Whoa! Randall,
you're-you're like a ninja.
- Get dressed. I got to go to school.
- Oh.
It's 6:00 a.m., bud.
I want to get there early
to talk to Mr. Lawrence.
- He gave me a book to read.
- Mr. Lawrence again. -Oh, yeah?
Mr. Lawrence give you the book about the
tickle monster? - Stop. Dad, stop! Stop.
- Tickle monster is...
- Oh, my God.
Something died in your mouth.
- Oh, did it?
- Go brush your teeth.
- Come on. Let's go.
- You know what,
I think, uh...
I think I want to meet
this Mr. Lawrence.
He's made quite an impression
on you.
Parent-teacher conferences
are next month.
Or today.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Mr. Lawrence.
Randall.
This is the latest
you've ever been early.
Uh, Korey Lawrence,
Randall's English teacher.
Jack Pearson, Randall's father.
I've heard a lot of great things
about you.
Oh. Well, uh,
your son is
a very curious young man.
He asks a lot of questions,
yeah.
So, how's Notes of a Native Son
going?
Great.
When James Baldwin was ten,
he wrote a play
his teacher directed.
Hey. You got a director.
Now you just need
to write a play, right?
- Hey, it was really nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
You have a very special kid
here.
I agree.
Randall, your mom's
gonna pick you up today.
Okay.
Love you.
So...
..how far did you get?
- "The Harlem Ghetto."
- Ah, yeah.
Wilkins is freezing me out.
Yeah, well,
you did cancel on him twice.
Screw it.
I'm going over there.
- To say what?
- I'm gonna ask him
if I vote for his housing bill...
with revisions...
Whether he'll support my grocery
store in the food desert.
Actually, no.
I'm gonna tell him.
- Yeah, you are.
- Yeah.
- Yeah...
- Come on.
- Mm.
No, no, no.
I'm telling you, I'm up
five after nine, right,
and then the back tightens.
And I still had to swi...
Morning, gentlemen.
Sorry to interrupt
the golf banter.
Councilman, if this conversation
is gonna start or end
with the words "affordable
groceries" or "food desert,"
you can keep walking.
Actually, um, Councilman, no.
Uh...
I know I had to cancel
on you twice,
and I wanted
to make it up to you.
So, um,
if you ever wanted
to get onto Stillbrooke,
I have an in.
- Stillbrooke?
- Two-month wait for a tee time.
And, of course,
Pearson has an in.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yes, 'cause I'm a carpetbagger
with rich friends,
and you men of principle
don't want any part of that.
My offer stands.
It was nice talking to you.
Well, what about today?
Today?
- I'll make a call.
- Hmm.
We could use a fourth.
Thanks, but, uh,
golf's not really my bag.
Golf. Bag.
Um, do you still want me?
Oh, we do now.
Ours is a money game.
All right.
Oh, God.
Just...
Uh...
Eh.
Mm...
Okay, what's wrong?
Eh. Aw, I'm just...
I'm creeping on my ex.
Ugh.
What's that even mean?
Oh. Uh...
I'm Internet stalking her.
God, you're old.
It's my-my ex, Zoe.
Uh, her documentary won a prize
at this Rome film festival,
and she's posted
all these photos.
And every single one,
she's with this hot guy.
See that?
- What do you think of that?
- Just friends?
- Yeah. Oh, yeah, definitely.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
But they're also having sex.
Aw.
- What is this...
- What are... Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- No, no, no. What are you doing?
- I'm trying to make
- the picture bigger. What...
- Well, you didn't make it bigger.
You touched the heart, man.
You touched the heart.
- Now she knows I'm stalking her.
- What's your problem?
- I look like an... What's my problem?
- Yeah.
Everything here sucks.
That's my problem.
You know,
you don't need to stick around
here for my court hearing.
Yeah, no, I really do need
to stick around here
for your court hearing.
I told your vet counselor
that I would.
Which means...
a few more weeks.
Let's do something though.
You know?
You want to go in...
You want to go for a hike?
I've had more than enough hikes with
you, kid. - Okay.
Here we go.
Go to a meeting, Kevin.
Yeah, thanks.
Just went to a meeting.
Go to another one.
Oh.
Relax. It's okay.
Hey, Mr. Malone.
You, uh...
going out to play some golf?
No, no. I'm just gonna go
hit some balls.
Do you play?
Not really.
I mean,
sometimes I'll do a twilight
round over at Swenson.
Oh. You want to join me?
You know what,
I got a lot of errands today.
Thank you, though, sir.
All right. Some other time.
Are you sure?
I think it's really sweet
that my dad wants
to get to know you more.
Uh, Mr. Malone.
Maybe I will join you.
Come on!
Thank you.
It'll be fun.
- Tobe.
- Yeah.
You left the onesies
in the washer too long.
Huh?
They sat in the washer too long,
and now they're all mildewy.
Okay, I'm-I'm sorry.
I-I'm operating
on-on two hours of sleep.
I can't be good at laundry
and also work enough
to save money
for Jack's college tuition,
which, accounting for inflation,
will be $6 million a year
by the time
he's ready to go to school.
Okay, well, I'm operating
on two hours of sleep, too.
And I know I don't have a job,
but at least your nipples
don't feel like chew toys.
Wait, are you getting rid
of those?
They're so nice.
Um, these are way too big
for me now.
So I am donating them, yes.
I thought
they were your favorite.
Don't get rid of 'em.
Okay.
Okay. What?
Uh, nothing.
Never mind.
I'll keep 'em.
Tobe, what is going on?
We've been snippy with each
other for the past two weeks.
Yeah, well, I'll tell you
what hasn't been going on.
I'll tell you what hasn't
been going on for nine months
and 23 days.
We're tired.
And Jack is sleeping
right next to us.
I know. But he can't, like...
can't see us.
Um, he can hear us.
You.
So, y-you know what, we...
we need to get out of here.
All right?
We need to...
We need to find a...
an environment
that is more conducive to...
lovemaking.
Okay.
And when are we gonna do that?
I don't know. Today?
How 'bout today?
I already took the day off.
Huh? We can get your mom
and Miggy Stardust to come over.
They've been dying to babysit.
They've been begging us
to go out more.
Tobe, I don't know.
No, you do know.
You know we have to do this.
We need to do this.
For the sake of our sex life,
call your mother.
- Okay.
- Please call her.
- I'm going to.
- Please start dialing.
Okay.
Oh, oh, you got it,
you got it, you got it. - Oh.
Okay. Ooh.
- Oh.
- Hey.
- Thanks. I had that, by the way.
- Yeah.
Yeah, it's just, rep 99 and 100
are typically the hardest ones.
- Sure. You're back.
- Yeah.
I'm just trying to stay out
of trouble, you know,
not that you could actually get
into any trouble in this town.
- Mind if I, uh...?
- You're gonna do some pull-ups?
- Yeah.
- You want a boost? Wha...?
Okay. She's got it.
She has got it.
Wow. That's...
impressive.
- Here you go, Kevin.
- Hey.
- The usual.
- Thank you.
That's... You don't have
to deliver my...
Oxi-Protein PB Energy Spike?
- And did you add the...?
- Chia.
- Yes.
- Wow.
You're like my phone
anticipating my...
- Words.
- Okay.
Technically, you're not supposed
to have drinks
around the workout stations,
but I'll let it go this time.
Well, thank you
for letting it go this time.
- I appreciate it.
- Mm-hmm.
Ah.
The service here's amazing.
Yeah. She wrote her number
on your cup.
What?
Hey! Look at that.
No. No.
You know, AA discourages
romantic relationships
in the first year.
- And drinking.
- Wow. You really sold that.
Talk to your husband?
Not since the hockey game.
Really?
Divorce is on the table, right?
You don't have all this time.
Plus, you know what?
He could just meet someone else.
Like, take my ex,
for instance... Zoe, right?
It's only been, like, six months,
but yet, here she is,
jet-setting around the planet
with some
sandwich artist guy.
What do you think?
Huh? She into him?
Well, 20 bucks says
they had bathroom sex
right before
they took this picture.
She's gorgeous.
- Yeah.
- Why'd you guys break up?
She didn't want kids.
And you do?
Well, yeah, I want kid...
Why do you act all skeptical
and, like, surprised?
I don't know.
You don't seem... motivated.
You just moved
to the middle of nowhere,
and you spend all your time
with your grumpy uncle, and...
Yeah, to help him out.
It's temporary. Trust me,
I'll get back in the saddle.
I'm just saying,
you're not getting any younger.
I'm not getting any younger?
I'm 30, like, something.
I'm sorry. I missed that.
You're 30...?
- Can you enunciate a little?
- I'll enunciate, okay?
- Just enunciate.
- Okay, here it goes. You are very
annoying.
All right? Come on.
Spot me. Grab the 45s
if you can lift them.
What you want is
what you get at McDonald's today.
- That swing...
- Hey, bud.
- Hey.
- That fantastic touch around the green.
- That smile.
- His name is Tiger Woods.
Mr. Lawrence said he's gonna
change the game of golf.
Yeah, I've heard of him.
Tiger Woods has won the world
junior title six times.
In fact, Tiger has won
so many trophies,
his mother says they can't
all fit in the house.
Some of his are stashed
in the garage.
Hey, how about tomorrow
after school,
you and me, we...
we go play some?
Golf?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we'll go hit some balls
at the range first,
and then we'll go par three.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Sure. Sure!
Okay. Cool.
But I thought
you didn't like golf.
It wasn't the right fit for me,
and my ball always seemed
to find the water, but...
I think
you might be cut out for it.
Okay, gents, dollar a hole,
two dollar Nassau,
50 cent skins.
Pearson, you're up.
Oh.
Okay.
I'll say it again, gentlemen.
I don't have a very good history
with this game.
As in, I have only played
one time.
Fore!
Sorry!
- Oh, boy.
- Bubba.
Yeah.
- You're in the wrong cart.
- I sure am.
Sure as hell am.
Ou est le métro, madame?
Ooh, la, la.
What did you just say?
I said, "Where can I find
the subway, miss?"
It's the only French I remember
after backpacking
through Europe.
Um, can we dim the lights just
so it's a little more romantic?
As you wish.
Setting the mood...
- Oh.
- Wow.
My God, you are so hunky.
♪ I don't need what you need,
I'm so unbothered by you... ♪
Oh.
Mmm. Mm-hmm,
yeah, I remember.
Like riding a bike.
Oh.
It's okay.
Oh, it's not...
I just have...
I just have a lot on my mind.
It's...
Like what, babe?
I just need a minute
to clear my brain, you know?
Just...
empty my mind. Um...
Okay.
Want to watch Turner Classics?
It's a great idea.
Yup, Turner Classic Movies.
TCM... that'll, uh,
get me going.
- Well, here we are again.
- Yes.
You are gonna need
to find the right clothes.
What? I thought we were just
gonna hit some balls.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Uh, you need
to wear a collared shirt
here at the club and no jeans.
Uh, you know what?
I forgot my credit card.
No, no, no, it's on me.
What size shoes do you wear?
No, sir, I don't feel
comfortable you buying me...
Hey, Dave?
I'm playing with Johnson.
You want to join?
Uh, sure. Sure.
Yeah, no.
We'll meet you right outside.
Okay.
Yeah.
Gonna take a lot more
than lowering the speed limit
to 55
to reduce our dependency on gas.
Yeah, what's your take
on OPEC, Jack?
Well, I know the lines are long
where I work.
You work at a gas station?
Yeah. Part-time mechanic
at Vine Auto
when I'm not helping my buddy
frame houses.
Well, you hear that, Merrick?
Jack frames houses.
Doesn't your insurance company
specialize in construction?
Yeah, mostly umbrella liability.
Well, you must need smart guys.
Give Jack your card, Merrick.
Maybe he can come in
next week for an informational.
- Sure.
- Oh, it's-it's not necessary.
- No, no.
- Hey.
Thank you for that.
There's hope for you yet.
- Bam!
- Oh.
You didn't win the Masters,
Bill.
I mean, come on.
You triple-bogeyed
the second hole.
- Well... are you sure?
- Four.
Yeah, I am sure.
- Okay.
- Ask my caddy.
- Yeah.
- There's a hundred in it for you.
- Oh, I'm sure there is.
- Better be sure...
- Gin and tonic.
- Double.
- Double or triple?
Oh, I try.
- Triple.
- Can you back it up?
Wow. Look at us, huh?
Yeah.
We should play for $1,000.
A grand? Really?
That's what Michael Jordan bets.
Okay, M.J., you're up.
Okay.
Mr. Lawrence says Tiger Woods is
gonna break barriers in golf.
Great putt.
Mr. Lawrence says I'm breaking
barriers at Hanes Academy, too.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
'Cause they never had
a black kid on the debate team.
- I didn't know that.
- Mm.
Look at you.
Nice!
Yeah, I'm not saying it'll be as hard
for me as it was for Jackie
Robinson and Muhammad Ali, but
it'll still be hard for me,
you know?
Oh, you're gonna do just fine,
Randall.
You are insanely smart
and charming, and you're gonna
do just fine wherever
you want to go in life.
Thanks.
You know, when I was younger,
I never felt welcome
at country clubs.
People thought I...
I didn't... make enough money
or have the right job.
Probably why I stopped playing.
I let those people get to me.
That's not what I'm saying, Dad.
No, I...
I know what you're saying.
I do, and I'm gonna
do everything in my power
to make sure
that nobody gets in your way
or holds you back.
Okay.
Thanks.
Ooh.
Oh, right in the drink.
Dave, you should buy the kid
a lake house.
He loves the water.
You're up, Dave.
Show us the way.
Mm.
- Thank you, Sam.
- Sometime today.
He liked it so much, right,
that now every time we go
over to the mayor's house,
my wife has to make him
potato salad.
You know, the one thing
about potato salad...
Uh, they're off the green.
You can hit.
Oh, right on.
I'll walk.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Slow everything down.
You're too fast.
Look.
It's just back... and through.
Tempo.
Okay.
Slowing down really helps.
Thanks for the tip.
I also ran track.
- Ah.
- Now I think
I'm gonna go back
to grad school and maybe
get a degree in kinesiology
or nutrition.
Yeah. I am very much
into nutrition.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
Like, uh, take now
for instance.
I'm starving, you know?
And we've been sitting here
for 20 minutes
and I've yet to see a menu.
I'm starting
to realize that, uh,
people from small towns
are never in a hurry.
♪ She's living in I.A. ♪
Small towns aren't for everyone.
- Mm.
- But I remind myself
of something Richard Russo
once said.
- Yeah.
- "People in small towns,
"more than in big cities,
share a destiny."
Well, I like that.
- ♪ They say it goes... ♪
- Share a destiny.
I feel like, uh,
destiny sort of brought me here,
actually.
Yeah.
But do-do you see yourself
settling down
in a town like Bradford
after grad school?
I suppose if I met
the right person
and he wanted to live here,
I would.
It's a perfect town
to raise kids.
I love kids.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
See? There,
we have something in common.
- Yeah.
Charlie, I've changed my mind.
I'll go with the ribeye.
- How would you like that, sir?
- Rare.
Just knock off the horns
and wipe its ass.
Hey, seriously, Jack,
call me if you want to come in
for an interview.
Yeah, you two should set up
a time for next week.
Well, that, uh,
won't be necessary,
but thank you, Merrick.
Okay.
You okay, bud?
Yeah.
You sure?
I mean, you barely said a word
in the last couple of holes.
I don't think I want
to play anymore.
Randall, c-come on.
We got four more holes to go.
You know we don't quit
what we started.
We quit the dojo.
Do you remember that dojo
we went to a few years ago
with all the other
black families?
Yeah.
We went a few times,
but then we stopped.
W... You said you didn't want
to learn karate anymore.
Yeah, but you won't let me quit
soccer or baseball.
You don't want me
to quit golf.
I ju... I-I don't quite follow
you here, Randall.
Forget it.
Can we please
- just go home?
- H-Hold on a second.
Where is this coming from?
Is this Mr. Lawrence again?
N-No.
No. You just, y...
You just don't get it.
What don't I get?
What you said before...
about feeling weird at some
country club golf course.
Okay?
You felt uncomfortable
at a golf course
and I probably wouldn't have
even been allowed on it.
Kiddo, I am sorry, okay?
That was a stupid thing to say.
I just... I-I don't...
I don't look at you
and see color.
I see my son.
Then you don't see me, Dad.
Now, remember,
you pull it back in one piece,
slowly... and let it go.
Oh, that was a good one.
And you were right
about the grip, too.
- Thank you very much. Thank you.
- All right.
- Book them the honeymoon suite.
- Yeah, no doubt about that.
Carl, why don't you grab
your clubs,
go look for your ball
with Lester.
Randall, hop on in.
Thank you so much
for the meal.
You are more than welcome.
So, um...
what else is there
to do in this town?
And, um,
please don't say
the Zippo factory.
To be honest, there's nothing
really to do here,
- Mm.
- Except get high and have sex.
And I don't do drugs.
Uh, I know what you're thinking.
Even the tunnel's getting laid.
Is it me?
Hmm?
Are you still attracted to me?
Are you kidding?
I don't know.
You have a whole new body.
- And...
- Kate, really.
I swear, I just have
a lot on my mind.
Okay?
Okay.
It is the pants.
- What?
- What you said to me
about keeping my old pants
in case I put
the weight back on.
Along with the pressure
of knowing
that if I didn't perform,
you would think it was because
I wasn't attracted to you.
Add stress and exhaustion
and...
- Toby...
- Look, why-why-why did you say it?
You know,
is it because you-you doubt
that I can keep the weight off,
or because you're hoping
that I put the weight back on?
Okay, Tobe.
Let's just go home.
Well, I'm glad I'm driving.
You really put back
those G and Ts.
Oh, no. I'm... I'm fine.
Thank you, though,
for the, uh...
drinks and the round.
Jack, you really should
have taken that interview.
I appreciate the gesture,
but I don't need any help, sir.
Look, my father...
was a pipe-fitter.
He worked hard
to put me through college.
And after I graduated,
I wasn't too proud
to take a job as a runner
at a brokerage house.
I rose up the ranks,
met the woman I'd marry.
I bought a house,
raised a family.
Yeah, I...
I joined a nice country club.
And-And this club is where
we are gonna celebrate
Rebecca's wedding.
I see myself
walking her down the aisle
at St. Michael's,
and afterwards,
coming over here,
and raising a toast to her
and her husband
at the reception.
I see it all so clearly.
Question.
Do you see yourself here?
Randall said all that?
Yeah.
Well... he's getting older
- and figuring out his place in the world.
- Mm.
Hey, did we let him quit
the dojo too easily?
I mean...
were we threatened by it?
No.
It was a long drive.
And he wasn't excited about it.
It just...
- It fizzled out.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, not a minute too soon.
Thank you, Lisa.
- Okay.
- There you go.
Could have been a lot worse
without the councilman's
lessons.
How'd you grow up
with a white father
and not know how to golf?
Tell me about it.
Hey, how did you guys
find the game?
Well, when I-I said
I wanted to learn,
my father painted
a golf pro's house
for free in exchange
for lessons.
Really? All right.
- Tiger winning at Augusta in '97.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, my Aunt Lizzie.
She taught me
to putt like Lee Elder
and cuss like Red Foxx.
Well, thank you, gentlemen,
for dragging my sorry ass
around the course today.
Here is to fathers,
to Tiger,
and to Lester's foul-mouthed
Aunt Lizzie.
- Yeah.
- Hear, hear.
- If they could see us now.
- Mm.
Listen...
Why don't you find some time
to stop by the office,
we'll talk about your grocery store.
After we talk about
my housing bill.
- Yes, sir.
- Mm.
That's a sure shot.
That wasn't my shot.
I told you...
- You parked so far away.
- I'm sorry.
My uncle lives right here
so we got to kind of be quiet.
- I'll try.
- Okay.
- But I make no promises.
- You are trouble.
Hey.
Sorry.
Thought you'd be alone.
You didn't have
to send her away.
Sorry I interrupted.
That's all right.
You interviewing mothers
to bear your children?
Really? 'Cause I can catch up
with Donna.
I saw Ryan.
And?
Total fubar.
It started out okay, and then...
he got critical,
and I got defensive,
and then we started arguing,
and I lost my temper.
I'm sorry.
I told you it was a bad idea.
I don't blame Ryan.
I wouldn't want to be
with someone
as screwed up as me.
Hey, come on.
You've seen things.
You-you have seen things
that 99% of us,
we can't even imagine.
And yeah, you made
some mistakes
along the way,
but you're trying.
That doesn't make you
unlovable.
It makes you human.
I'm sorry.
- Hello? Anybody home?
- Oh, no.
They're, um, heading back
from The Grove now with Jack.
Oh.
I'm gonna unpack.
Okay.
Kate?
Do you forgive me?
For what you said
or for cutting up
the wrong pair of pants?
Both?
Baby,
I believe in you.
I always have.
I always will.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
Do you believe me when I say
that you still fuel the furnace
that is my loins?
Well, I could use
some convincing.
My attraction to you...
- Mm-hmm.
- Is purely primal, Kate Pearson.
You are nothing more to me
than a vessel for my feral lust.
And the rest of it,
the emotional stuff,
I cast aside with contempt.
Now,
do you want to take Toby 2.0
for a spin?
I will drive you down
to the rims.
- Safe word?
- Mom and Miguel.
- Weird, but I like it.
- No, they're gonna be back
- in, like, five minutes.
- Good.
That gives us four minutes
to put ourselves back together.
- Oh? Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna marry
your daughter, Dave.
I'm... I'm gonna marry her.
I'm gonna get a good job.
Buy a real nice house.
A happy one.
With kids
running around the yard.
So...
let me ask you.
Do you see yourself there?
You're never gonna be
good enough for her, Jack.
Say again?
- Why don't you say that again?
- Oh, there he is.
There's the guy
I've been waiting for, huh?
Say it again.
Uh-huh.
Jack?
Hey, Bec.
- I... Oh!
- Oh.
- You okay?
- Yeah, no.
- I'm fine.
- It was hot
out there,
and he just had a few too many.
I'm fine. You good? You okay?
- You, uh, you good?
- Hey.
Why don't we get you home?
- Yeah, okay.
- Yeah, I'll take you home.
Jesus, Nick.
You scared the hell out of me.
Why can't you just stay
at your own place?
You have fresh cold cuts.
Yeah. Well, okay.
Well, you know, help yourself.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
We should've taken
that hike today.
- Night.
- Good night, Uncle Nicky.
Wait.
- Mr. Lawrence.
- Randall, my man.
Mr. Lawrence,
can I, uh, talk to you a sec?
Sure.
Go on. I'll be right in.
Okay.
Thank you for taking
a special interest in my son.
He really looks up to you.
Uh, still, he's a...
12-year-old kid,
and if my son is asking
complicated, heavy questions
about his place in this world,
a simple heads-up to his parents
couldn't hurt.
Don't you think?
- A heads-up.
- Mm.
Okay. Anything else?
No.
Actually, would, uh...
you and your wife like
to come to the house
this weekend for dinner?
We'd love to.
Great. Saturday at 7:00?
- Hey, nice job, Randall.
- Thanks.
I'll do better next time,
I promise.
Randall, hold on a second.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
All right? I will...
listen better and lecture less.
Okay?
You are gonna be
a very important man, Randall.
And a lot
of important relationships
happen on a golf course.
Me, I... I hit a ceiling.
But for you,
there is only sky.
So don't get caught
on the outside looking in.
Sometimes you'll have
to play up to the competition,
sometimes you'll have
to play down.
But play the game.
Like father, like son.
What you want...
is to have a routine.
First,
you got to line your shot up.
And then you line your feet up
to the target.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Good.
Again.
This one's for you, Pop.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Sync corrections by srjanapala