Previously on This Is Us...
You know,
you don't need to stick around
here for my court hearing.
Yeah, no, I really do need
to stick around here
for your court hearing. I told
your vet counselor that I would.
Mr. and Mrs. Hodges,
I'm sorry for skipping school
with Malik, but I am not sorry
for yesterday because that was
the best day of my life.
Okay. Pick a letter.
- Any letter.
. Um...
"Z."
- "Z." I got it.
- Yeah, thanks.
Zachary.
Okay.
Zeke.
Zeppelin.
Ooh. But what if
they're all girls?
Zoe?
Zophie.
-Zusan.
-No, you can't just put Zs
on "S" names.
I'm telling you, Jack,
we can never go back there.
Kevin bit the librarian.
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
He bit her on her face
with intent.
Okay, so, the kids
are never gonna learn how
to read. It's no big deal.
-Parachute! Parachute!
-What?
-Parachute!
-Okay, okay.
Parachute it is.
There you go. And...
parachute!
- Ooh!
- Parachute.
I dropped Kevin at Sophie's,
Randall at the library,
Kate at the mall,
and I fixed that annoying rattle
in the Wagoneer,
and all before lunch.
I mean, it's a bird.
It's a plane. It's Super Dad.
Well, look at you,
man of the year.
Couldn't do it without you.
Well, you'll never have to.
Yeah.
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By Hisoka Oni
I think the spray arm is broken.
So I don't need
a whole new dishwasher?
Thank God.
That is the last thing
I need right now.
I got it!
Don't get it. I'll get it.
Hey.
I missed you, babe.
Yeah? Prove it.
Hey.
-What's up, Randy?
-What's up?
How you doing, man?
Hey, Rebecca.
- Hi, Marc.
- How's it going?
Damn, college boy.
What, back for more laundry?
You're here, like,
every weekend.
-Hey, Bug, that's not lunch.
-I know.
I'll get something
at the movies.
Beth and I just saw
Practical Magic.
The one with Sandra Bullock
and Nicole Kidman together.
- I've been dying
to see that.
But we're not 12-year-old girls.
- You ready?
Good to go? All right.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Rebecca, good to see you.
Bye, guys.
-Have fun.
-Randy, good to see you.
What does Kate see in that guy?
Honestly, I'm just happy
that she's happy.
And you, Mom? How you doing?
These mortgage payments
are eating away
at what's left
of the insurance money,
and I really need to get a job,
but I'm not...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I-I...
I don't want you to worry.
Since I'm already here,
you know,
we could look at your résumé.
That is a very sweet
but unnecessary offer.
And I'm sure you have a ton of
schoolwork you have to work on.
I already knocked out
next week's reading,
Mom, I'm a huge nerd.
Résumés are my jam.
Like, I live for them.
Look, um, Cassidy...
We're both adults.
You're single. I'm separated.
Nobody did anything wrong.
You're okay, though?
Because the last thing
I want to do
is make your life
more complicated.
I'm fine.
- I'll...
- You'll what?
You'll call me?
Probably not.
You slept with her, didn't you?
That's why Cassidy hasn't been
at AA all week?
Not gonna talk about that
with you.
Let me ask you something.
Just out of curiosity here.
What's wrong with you?
I mean,
I thought you were trying
to help the poor kid fix
her marriage, not destroy it.
You're like
a human wrecking ball.
Yeah.
Yeah, thanks for the pep talk.
- No, I'm serious.
- Explain it to me.
What kind of person
does that?
Shame on you.
I'm so glad
I could make it out early
for Thanksgiving.
The house is gorgeous.
Miguel is gonna love
all these period details.
How's his visit
with his kids going?
It's good.
He is gonna take the train down
from New York
in time for dinner, though.
Okay.
Mom and I are off
for our tour of Philly.
Tess, Annie, let's go, girls.
The playdate express
is leaving the station.
Can't wait for some quality
"R" and "R" time.
That's,
that's Randall and Rebecca.
-I know, baby. I know.
-See what I'm saying?
- Hey.
- What?
That is for Deja
and Malik's movie date.
It's not a date.
A date is when
you go out somewhere alone.
Well, them's the rules.
Chaperoned dates only.
We all agreed.
Besides,
you won't even know I'm here.
You'll be in the living room.
I'll stay in the kitchen.
The kitchen and the living room
are the same room.
I just want him to take
one bite of the banana.
He should've tried solid food
at least two weeks ago.
Here's a theory.
Maybe baby doesn't like banana.
Everybody likes banana.
It's the healthy snack
-that comes in its own wrapper.
-Well,
-maybe we could try
something else.
-Well, no.
We can't, because you can only
introduce one food at a time
in case there's
an allergic reaction.
That's why I made
the baby food chart
to match the daddy food chart.
Right.
Well, then, Jack,
it's boob juice until dinner.
I got to squeeze in a gym sesh
before my staff meeting,
so maybe we'll try again later.
You know what? I really want
-to keep trying now.
-No, babe, babe, babe.
Please wait for me, all right?
I already missed first rollover
and first sit up.
I don't want to miss
first solid food.
- But I'll try to leave work
early, okay?-
-I love you, Kate.
-Love you.
Jack.
Mwah. Okay, bye.
Did you feel Daddy's kiss?
Wakey, wakey, eggs and bakey.
I don't have bacon.
I don't have eggs.
But I got coffee.
Hey.
Kevin, look,
you know, my...
my court hearing's
this afternoon.
I'm sorry if I was rough on you
the other day,
but you've beaten yourself up
enough. I'm coming in.
Yeah?
Hey, it's Nicky.
Um, is the kid with you?
No, we haven't spoken all week.
Well, he's just...
He's locked himself
in the trailer
since you morons slept together.
But now he's gone,
and he left his phone here.
It's not like him
to just take off.
Nicky, I've got my own crap
going on over here.
I mean, I just... I just signed
the divorce papers.
Cassidy, how many times
have I ever picked up the phone
and called you?
Yeah. Right, okay.
I'm on my way.
I think I overdressed
for this interview.
Kaufmann's would be lucky
to have you.
Thank you for all your help,
sweetheart.
I really appreciate it.
But you don't have to worry
about me, okay?
Ever.
So, if you could,
picture me grocery shopping
with three toddlers,
you'll understand
I know all about multitasking.
I'm sure you do.
- Yeah.
- Triplets. Wow.
- You're familiar
with our purchasing
and scheduling software?
If I'm honest, I-I'm not.
But I am computer proficient,
and I type 85 words a minute,
so...
I'm sure I can handle
whatever software you use.
Mr. Simons,
-thank you so much
for your time.
-Sure.
-How'd it go?
-Okay.
I think I sweat out
all the liquid in my body.
I'm gonna go freshen up
for a second.
Do you want to grab the car?
Okay, thanks.
- I'll need to see
some more applicants.
No, I didn't, so we...
Rebecca Pearson is here!
Mrs. Pearson,
so good to see you again.
- Hi. A hug. Ooh!
- Hi. Welcome.
You know, Randall tells
a lot of stories
about his family,
like, a lot a lot.
Like, more than anyone, ever,
in human history.
Okay, let's give her
some space, please.
You guys are very sweet.
I am just...
I'm very proud of Randall.
My son, the congressman.
It's, councilman, Mom.
- I'm a councilman.
- Congressman, no.
-Councilman.
-Hey, I... I like
-the sound of that.
-Hey, one job at a time,
Jae-Dubs.
- Now, is it okay
if I take pictures?
Of course.
Yeah? You don't mind?
- No.
- All right. Maybe...
-You want to see
the rest of the office?
-the two of you. Ready?
One, two, three.
- Nice.
- Jae-Won. Nice.
- Randall Pearson.
- Yeah.
-There's more to it, Mom.
-No, I know.
I just want to take pictures
along the way. All right.
Wow.
I like these maps, too.
This carpet is really...
I just want to make sure
I get every angle here.
-Let me see.
This is your office?
-Yes, ma'am.
Right here.
Wow, look at the desk.
Hi. Are you okay?
It's time for our walk.
I'm having a bad morning.
Join the club.
No. Seriously.
Bad mornings are worse for
people who had massive strokes.
I've got muscle spasms.
Maybe tomorrow.
Do you need help?
All right, well,
don't just stand there.
You're letting the bugs in.
-Hey.
Hey.
Hey-hey!
Hey, Mrs....
Mrs. Pearson. Um,
thank you so much
for having me over.
What's that, popcorn?
Okay, you two,
just pretend I'm not here.
But also remember,
I will be here the whole time.
Neh!
You gonna take it?
Neh! You got to be fast.
All right, just take it.
Have fun, y'all.
So, I told you what
happened when I took my wife
out to Pittsburgh
to do some shopping last week.
Okay, so, we found this...
So, as he comes by us,
Crosby bumps our table,
knocks over her glass,
gets red wine
all down her dress.
So I sucker-punch him.
You sucker-punched
Sidney Crosby?
It was a new dress.
Another club soda?
Yeah.
Just so we're clear,
you're telling a story
about how you sucker-punched
Pittsburgh Penguins captain
Sidney Crosby
for accidentally spilling wine
on your wife's dress?
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean,
there's no way that happened.
But... but okay.
Buddy...
you looking for trouble?
No, no, I don't have
to look for trouble.
Trouble always finds me.
Like a human wrecking ball,
actually.
Aren't you that actor that's
been hanging around town?
Let me ask you a question.
Do you love your wife?
-Yeah.
She love you?
Of course.
I bet you a hundred bucks I can
get her to take her clothes off
within 20 minutes
of meeting her.
What did you say?
Actually, you know what,
I might have overshot.
I'll tell you what I'll do.
Here, I'll bet you ten dollars
that I can get your wife
out of that wine-stained dress
within five minutes
of meeting her.
What do you think?
There it is. Come on.
Can I help you?
I'm Rebecca Pearson's son.
Sh-she was just in here.
She and my father adopted me
when I was left
at a fire station
and raised me as their own.
That's the kind
of person she is.
Did she tell you that?
No.
That's also the kind
of person she is.
Did she tell you
my father died last year,
saving our lives
in a house fire?
Jesus.
-No.
-Of course not.
Because...
she's not the type of person
to tell you a sob story
to try to get a job.
But you are?
Absolutely.
Your mom's lucky to have you.
I can barely get my son
to return my calls.
She seems like a great person.
She certainly raised
a great kid.
But she doesn't know how
to use the software,
and I don't have the time
to train her.
Sir, I graduated
top of my class.
I have a full scholarship
with Carnegie Mellon.
I'll teach her any software
you need by Monday morning.
Please.
Sh-She just needs a chance.
Hey.
I was just grabbing my bag.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Everybody's all about
the Philly cheesesteak...
...but my money's
on the roast pork from DiNic's
as the best sandwich
in Philadelphia.
I ordered these in special.
- It's delicious.
- Right?
All right, so...
...tell me about life in L.A.
Um...
it's-it's lovely.
That's it?
-Any celebrity sightings?
-No.
Don't you want to complain
about the traffic
- or how there's no weather?
. No.
I want to show you pictures
of the baby.
Okay.
Where is my phone?
I just had it.
-Mom, it's okay.
-Come on. No,
it was really expensive.
And Miguel splurged
when I told him not to.
I'm sure it's in here. Hey.
Where could it be?
I mean, I just had it.
-Are you kidding me?
-Mom, it's okay.
-I'll just call it.
-I really need
to find my phone,
though, Randall.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Okay? Can you help me, please?
Yes, ma'am. Hey, guys.
- Has anybody seen
my mom's phone?
No, I hear it.
- Is it this?
- Hey!
! Okay.
-Crisis averted, Mrs. Pearson.
-There it is. Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
Um, okay, now I'm gonna show you
pictures of your nephew.
-Come on, sweetheart.
-Yes.
Look at this picture.
Look at that one.
Look at his little face.
I'm not talking
about this anymore.
I thought you said
you wanted to.
I told you...
it's just the way it is.
Okay, so you can't even
talk to them about it? I mean,
I don't get why you won't
just have the conversation.
And I don't get why you
can't take no for an answer.
Deja.
-Anything you want
to talk about?
-Just...
please tell him to leave.
Hey, Malik?
I think it's best
if you go home.
Yeah. Yeah, no, it was...
completely my fault.
I pushed her too hard, so...
Yeah.
You pushed her too hard.
And what... what was it,
exactly?
It's not my place.
I'm sorry.
Malik,
if you push my daughter
on something that makes her
uncomfortable,
I have the right
to know what's up.
Deja wants to see her mom.
Her birth mom.
That's what's up.
- Okay.
- Now, this is service.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
I'm happy you came by. Really.
Are you?
'Cause you don't act like it.
Yeah, I know.
Ever since the stroke,
I have trouble making
my voice and face
express empathy and gratitude.
Doesn't mean I don't have any.
Hey.
We've been looking for you.
Hey, come on.
Wha...?
It's a funny story.
Did you win?
Did you drink?
No.
I thought about it, but no.
Come on.
Let's go.
Well...
I better go get changed.
Why, you got a hot date?
It's Wednesday.
You actually forgot.
No, your hearing.
Of course. Yes.
I...
I'm sorry.
You're sorry.
Well, I'm sure that'll be
a big help with the judge,
that my character witness
looks like he went 12 rounds
with Mike Tyson.
But you know what?
Just forget it.
I mean, I'm the idiot who threw
the chair through the window.
"I'm sorry" is like a...
It's like a magic word
when you're a kid.
Doesn't matter what you did.
Say you're sorry
and it all goes away.
Then you grow up, and it just...
doesn't work anymore, does it?
No, it doesn't.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
See what I mean?
Yeah.
A little concealer
should do the trick.
I will say, for a Marine,
you've got
a pretty gentle touch.
Well, whoever busted up
your face was an amateur.
You wouldn't want to see what
a professional can do to you.
Growing up,
my dad,
he-he flew a Cessna 150.
He called it
The Screaming Eagle.
Named it after
the 101st Airborne Division.
He was so proud
to be in the 101st.
I didn't know your dad served.
You never mentioned that.
Well, not all of us have to talk
about our dead dads
all the time.
Okay.
I never found what my dad did
in the military, though.
Bravery. Heroism.
I kept chasing it.
I enlisted again and again,
thinking...
"This time I'll feel it."
I tried and I tried until...
I just ended up destroying
everything I had back home.
It wasn't you who destroyed
my marriage, Kevin.
I did that all by myself,
way before I met you.
All right.
I did my best.
There's only so much I can do
to fix a face like yours.
You know, Cassidy,
it's not too late
to put your family
back together.
I signed the divorce papers
yesterday.
Today is Wednesday.
Matty has swimming lessons
every Wednesday.
And, afterwards,
Ryan takes him to the diner
on Hawthorne for dinner.
Every Wednesday night, I park
across the street and I watch
and I try to work up the courage
to walk in and join them.
And I can't do it anymore.
I'm gonna call it a day.
Okay, kids.
time to face the music.
Could you cut an avocado in half
for me?
-Yeah.
-If I try it myself,
it's fifty-fifty
I lose a finger.
And I've only got five left
that work.
Thank you.
Jack, what do you think?
- You want to try some?
- You can try,
but this kid
does not eat anything.
Open up. Here it comes.
It's like guacamole.
There you go.
Wait, what?
Buddy, you did it!
Look at you.
My-- This is...
Well, this is terrible timing.
Sh-She wants to see
her birth mom.
But she doesn't feel like she
can talk to you guys about it.
She really did not like it
when I pushed her on it,
which... again, I did,
like an idiot.
God. What if I blew it?
What if she's over me?
I mean, the-the best girl
-in the world and...
-Hey, Malik,
-I need you to focus, okay?
-Yeah.
Deja knows that she can talk
to us about anything.
Okay.
"Okay"?
What's-what's that
supposed to mean?
Well, she did...
talk to you guys about it.
A while ago.
I guess you just
kind of let it slide.
No, we didn't.
Did you take her to see her mom?
No, but that's because
everything just got so busy.
Okay.
Malik, you "okay" me
one more time...
Off the record.
Yeah?
Just say it.
Well, Randall ran
for city council.
You guys moved to Philly.
You opened a dance studio.
I mean, you weren't too busy
for any of that stuff.
*
Hey.
Yo.
Dude.
-What?
-Well, your tie is a disaster.
-What-what is this?
-What? I...
I haven't worn one of these
since the prom.
Okay, I got you.
Look at that.
That's sharp.
Uncle Nicky.
Hey.
You got this.
We got this.
All rise.
Uncle Nicky.
Miguel's train is on time.
There's a very persistent
young man downstairs
who won't leave
until you come talk to him.
Then he'll be waiting
a long time.
Deja, I'm sorry we haven't taken
you to see Shauna.
What, he told you?
No, Beth,
he shouldn't have said that.
-It's no big deal.
-Hey. Yes, it is.
It's a very big deal.
I don't want you
to think that...
I'm ungrateful
for everything you and Randall
do for me.
That-That's why I didn't want
to say anything.
That's why I got so mad
at Malik.
Hey.
We're gonna look at a calendar
and find a good time to visit.
I promise.
Beth.
Um...
I'd actually like
to invite her here.
For Thanksgiving.
If that's okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
I got a bunch
of mushy, nutritious stuff.
All right, we ready?
I'm sorry I ran out
this morning,
but now I'm here, I'm all in,
and I brought a smorgasbord
of solid food options.
Wait, what are those?
Are these
perfectly ripe avocados?
Um...
Yeah, they're
from Gregory's tree next door.
All of the avos at Trader Joe's
were hard and green,
like the Hulk's calf muscles.
These are
quintessentially California
first solid food.
This is gonna be great.
Thank you, Gregory.
All right.
Let me get my phone. Hold
on, let me get my phone. Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Baby Jack Damon.
First solid food.
Can you hear the spoon?
You hear it?
- Here comes a spoonful
of ripe avocado.
He did it.
Kate, he did it, he's eating it.
First solid food, buddy.
Today was the day!
You want a little more, buddy?
Here you go.
Mr. Pearson,
I've reviewed your case,
and I'm willing to consider
the pretrial diversion
advocated by the prosecution.
But I have one question.
Do you feel remorse
for what you did?
Not really.
I mean, throwing that chair...
...was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
If I didn't throw that chair
through the window,
I wouldn't have stopped
drinking,
wouldn't have joined AA
or stuck with therapy.
When I threw that chair,
my-my nephew came back
into my life.
No matter
how much I told him to scram,
he just stuck around.
For 40 years,
I have pushed people away.
Not because I-I thought
they would hurt me
but because I thought
I would hurt them.
I told myself I was doing it
for their own good,
yeah, 'cause I'm broken.
But...
but I was wrong.
I wasn't broken.
I was sick.
And when you're sick,
you...
you got to let the people
who care about you help.
*
No matter what that judge says,
he did it.
He turned his life around,
forgave himself.
Puts things in perspective,
doesn't it?
Mr. Pearson.
I will sign off
on the diversion.
As long as you remain
in treatment
and don't re-offend
for two years,
all charges will be expunged
from your record.
Look, I'm sorry about before.
Nah, no matter how sorry
you think you are,
- I'm definitely more sorry.
- No.
I'm, like, the sorriest dude
in the history of sorry dudes.
I'm going to the pantry.
You'll be unsupervised
for the next 30 seconds.
Okay, that's enough!
You get on out of here, Malik.
I have a feeling that your
little performance at dinner
has more to do about me
than Andre.
Hey, guys.
-Hey.
-Hello.
-Hi.
Well, how was R & R time?
It was lovely.
Randall was the perfect
tour guide, of course.
-Hi.
-And I took about a million
pictures on my phone.
She was glued to that phone
all day,
except when she lost it.
What? Again?
I had to buy her
that new phone
'cause she lost the last one.
Now, the two of you
just leave me be.
I did not lose it, Randall.
Can I talk to you
about Thanksgiving?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Here we are.
What are you gonna say?
If he won't even let me
sit down and join them,
I'll just...
give him the divorce papers
and walk out.
If he does...?
I'll think of something.
Well, don't be me, Cassidy.
Don't let it take 40 years
to get better.
You're the best cautionary tale
a girl could ask for.
When do you leave town?
I'm going to Philly
for Thanksgiving,
and then I'm back to L.A.
You know, the thing I did find
in the Marine Corps
was the thing
I wasn't looking for.
Friendship.
Community.
Over there, those guys
were my family, you know?
Then I got back here
and it was like I...
moved to another country
without a map.
Thanks for helping me
find my way home.
*
Hey.
I hope you find
your happy ending, Kevin.
I hope you find yours, too.
*
Now, of course I will.
Yes.
That is very kind of you.
Thank you so much.
Okay, bye-bye.
I got it.
Hey, Mom.
That's awesome.
-I knew you nailed it.
-Well.
So, now that I actually
got the job,
were you gonna tell me
what you said to Mr. Simons?
-What?
-Randall.
You just seemed so down
on yourself.
I just want people to see you
the way I do.
You...
You're so much like your father.
You know that?
It makes me... very proud.
Very proud.
I cannot believe I'm starting
an entry-level position
at my age.
I never would have seen
this coming.
Not in a million years.
-Sorry, I'm sorry...
-Mom, it's okay.
Shouldn't be putting any
of this on you, sweetheart.
I mean...
I am the parent
and you're the kid.
You know, you should be out
there having fun with Beth.
I don't need you
to worry about me. I promise.
I'm just happy that you need
to come here to do your laundry.
Mom, they have laundry
at the dorms.
I come back for R & R time.
Randall, Rebecca.
God, that was
one of the lamest things
-I've ever said, wasn't it?
-It was pretty lame. Yes.
Yeah, it was.
But I loved it.
Hi.
Hey.
You don't seem
like yourself today.
You had a few, mix-ups.
Yeah.
Miguel calls them
"senior moments."
Yeah, I get it.
But this felt like,
a little more than that.
The whole thing with the phone.
I'm fine, Randall.
I'm fine.
I'm just... getting older.
-I don't recommend it.
-I know.
I'm sure it's nothing.
I was just wondering
if you've seen a doctor lately.
You know, I could call around,
set something up for you
while you're in town.
I'm only here for a few days
and I barely get to see
my granddaughters.
I'm not, I'm not gonna
go see some doctor
just because
you're overreacting.
I'm just worried
that there could...
-I said I'm fine.
-Mom.
Randall, enough.
Okay?
I'm still the parent here
and you're still the son,
in case you've forgotten.
Okay.
Okay, what?
- Forget it, it's all good.
- No, no, no, no.
If you want to say something,
go ahead and say it.
Mom, the only thing that I want
to say is that I love you.
And I'm concerned.
You're acting
extremely defensive
over absolutely nothing
right now,
and that's only making me
more concerned.
And for you to say that you're
the mother and I'm the son
after 20 years of...
- Of what?
- Nothing.
I didn't say anything.
Yeah, you did.
You said something very clearly.
And it was cruel.
And it was beneath you.
You know what? I'm tired.
I think I need to lay down
for a minute,
so could you... please leave?
Yeah.
*
Man.
Hey, you should come
to Philly with me.
For Thanksgiving.
I know the family
would love to see you.
I could do that.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Hey.
You're a good kid.
*
Who's my good boy?
Me.
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By Hisoka Oni
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH