Previously on This Is Us...
Do you want to go on a drive?
Where do you want to go?
Los Angeles.
My mom says I'm nuts for doing
this with a guy I barely know.
- We've known each other a whole week.
- (GIGGLES)
- LABEL EXEC: So, keep in touch.
- _
Definitely keep us posted
on what you're up to.
REBECCA: He said that I
was "Pittsburgh good",
which I've decided to
take as a compliment.
♪♪
Let's go home.
- ♪♪
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SHUTS OFF ENGINE)
(QUIETLY): Hey.
Hey.
REBECCA: Mm?
- (GROANS SOFTLY)
- We're home.
Oh, wow.
(EXHALES)
How long have I been out?
Just a little while.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(EXHALES) So...
great third date.
I thought so.
(REBECCA CHUCKLES)
Isn't it crazy?
- Hmm?
- How, just a couple weeks ago,
I was a girl singing at a bar and...
I locked eyes with a cute guy...
No. No, no, not you.
There was another guy
there, and then he left.
- Ah.
- And I saw you
and I was like, "He'll do".
Okay, yeah. No, I got it.
(CHUCKLES)
It's so strange, isn't it?
How, just like that,
a complete stranger can become
such a big part of your story.
♪♪
It's actually kind of
terrifying, you know?
How a single cross with one person
you've never met can change...
everything.
Yo.
- What's up?
- Malik. What's up, man?
- What's up, man?
- You good?
- Come on in here. Come on.
- I see you, I see you.
Let's go.
(INHALES) All right,
I'm stalling. (CHUCKLES)
'Cause I don't want
to get out of this car.
Which is odd for me,
'cause it's usually the...
bad-boy musicians I like
when it comes to
life-changing strangers.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
(EXHALES)
Okay.
Uh, just so you know,
I am gonna play it cool here,
so don't expect to get a phone call
- from me right away.
- Oh, yeah.
Same here.
Yeah, I-I got a pretty full plate,
to be honest.
I got to find a job,
- couch to crash on, so I...
- Yeah.
I wouldn't expect you to hear from me
- anytime soon.
- Mm.
Or maybe ever again.
- It's quite possible.
- Yeah.
♪♪
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(EXHALES)
I'm not calling you first.
♪♪
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
(PAPER RUSTLING)
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello?
I called you first.
Couldn't play it cool, huh?
No, that's never really been
- my thing.
- (CHUCKLES)
Hey, can I see you tomorrow?
Yes.
That's... that's never really been
- my thing either.
- (CHUCKLES)
Oh, shoot. Tomorrow.
I'm supposed to have
dinner with my parents
and their friends tomorrow.
They want... (CHUCKLES)
proof of life.
But you could come.
I mean, it's at their country club,
- so I don't know if you'd want to...
- Yeah.
No, I'll... I'll be there.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Great.
Uh, you do have to wear a sport coat,
but they have a few there
if you want to just borrow one.
Mm, no. Nah, I'm... I'm set.
Um, hold on one second.
I'm gonna go find the address for you.
Okay.
♪♪
(EXHALES)
_
Cass.
- Hey. Hey, guys.
- Cassidy?
Hey. Hey, Matty?
It-It's just me. Matty
couldn't stay up any longer.
He's got school in the
morning. But I pinky swore
I'd ask if you got
his Lightning McQueen.
Yeah, I did. I did. You can
tell him I did. (CHUCKLES)
Sorry I haven't called.
Ah...
(EXHALES) Ryan,
I miss you guys like crazy.
First thing I want to
do when this is over
is make breakfast with you and Matty.
We can have breakfast for dinner.
Remember when we used
to do that all the time?
I think about that all the time lately.
You know that, right? You
know that... (SNIFFLES)
... even when we're not talking,
I think about you both all the time.
Every minute. Every day.
I know.
MAN: Sharp.
Hey, babe, I got to go, okay?
(EXHALES)
Okay.
Big kiss.
All right.
Bye.
♪♪
(CREAKING)
(WHINES)
(BARKS)
(CHUCKLES) All right, fine.
It's your waistline.
Oh, Sammy.
Crap. No. Sammy, get back, get back.
Just stay.
Can I help you?
Sir? Can I help you?
- Oh, my God!
- Oh!
- I'm so sorry.
- Oh, my God, why did you do that?
- Oh, I'm so...
- Why would you touch me?
I'm so sorry. I-I
was just trying to get
- your attention. I-I...
- (LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES): O-Oh, my God.
- That scared me.
- I'm totally kidding.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Yeah.
But I'm starving.
So if you could, like,
show me to a table,
that would be really, really cool.
- Of course. (CHUCKLES)
- Yeah.
- Right this way.
- Can you just...
- Yeah.
- Can you just... Yeah.
Yeah. Thank you.
ANDRE: Bro,
20 minutes is too long for homeroom.
That's all I'm saying.
It's got no purpose.
- JONNY: They take roll in homeroom.
- Roll?
Roll? Hey, Malik, you here?
- Here.
- That took one second.
And we're going into junior year
still losing 20 minutes to homeroom?
That's all I'm saying.
Oh, that's all
you're saying? Promise?
'Cause you say one more word,
you're giving me a dollar.
- (SNORTS)
- That's cool.
(LAUGHS)
- Here, fool.
- Give me that money.
You got it.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Come on, man. Put the phone down.
You're obsessed with her.
If she was your girl,
you'd be obsessed, too.
ANDRE: All right, guys, look,
last kickback before
school at my place tomorrow.
Malik, you coming?
My mom said we can invite girls,
and I got you on grill duty.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Maybe.
Maybe. I'll see, I'll see, I'll see.
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
No promises on the kickback.
But I got to get home.
- All right.
- Told Moms that I'd bring home
some food, so...
- Okay.
- Catch y'all later.
(LOCK CLICKING)
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Hey, Ma.
- Got you a burger.
- Mmm.
No, no. Go away.
Mmm.
Not as good as yours, baby,
- but mmm!
- Oh, yeah. I know. (LAUGHS)
- I'm going to go head upstairs...
- Mm-mm.
(QUIETLY): Don't wake that baby.
Can't hear you. Too
much food in your mouth.
(BABY COOING)
(MALIK LAUGHS SOFTLY)
What you doing up?
(COOING CONTINUES)
Hey, Janelle.
Hey. Hey.
I was watching you on my phone today.
Hey, look. Look.
- That's you. (CHUCKLES)
- (COOING)
Aw. Aw, Janelle.
Come here.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, you're getting heavy.
Long way from that NICU, huh?
You know, Grandma said not
to wake you up, but, uh...
Daddy trumps Grandma, doesn't he?
Doesn't he? Doesn't he?
(CHUCKLES)
(COOING)
♪♪
Can I help you?
Yeah. Um...
I'm looking for a suit.
Can I get you anything else? Coffee... ?
- No. I'm good, thanks.
- Okay.
Wait. Come. Sit.
- Join me.
- Oh, I, um...
Your shift is over, Lucy.
I heard you say that to the other lady.
Mm. Also heard her call you Lucy,
just so you know I'm not a stalker.
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- Come sit.
- Mmm.
- (EXHALES)
This is amazing bacon here.
This is great for a hangover.
Why are you hungover?
I'm hungover, 'cause, last night,
I was writing a song
and...
I realized I completely suck
and I'm gonna be
playing cocktail lounges
and country clubs for
the rest of my life.
You're a musician?
I'm trying.
It's bright in here.
How do you...
I can see some light.
Just a little. And, um...
and really, really blurry shapes
but nothing clearly.
- Mm.
- I've been here a few times,
but never for breakfast.
Can you describe it for me?
The restaurant?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's, uh...
... it's one of those diners
that will... never change.
It's not what I would open.
I'm a chef.
Or... I want to be a chef, I should say.
But it's...
warm here, you know? It's...
The food is warm, the people are warm,
the room is literally always warm,
even when it's super cold out.
- Yeah.
- (LAUGHS)
May I?
Sure.
♪♪
(EXHALES)
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Damn.
I think I'll have another cup of coffee.
Okay.
She sleep through the night?
- (CHUCKLES): Not really.
- 'Cause you woke her.
(SINGSONGY): Told you
not to, and you woke her.
- Would you leave him alone, woman?
- "Woman"?
(LAUGHS): I'm sorry,
you plan on kissing me
with that mouth today?
That is definitely the plan, yeah.
Grandma and Grandpa are cheesy as hell.
We've earned our
cheese, thank you kindly.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm working the night shift
at the hotel tonight, Malik.
Be home by 5:00.
- 5:00?
- Mm-hmm.
Yes, I know all about Andre's barbecue.
You're watching the baby.
Welcome to responsibility.
Don't start. Now, go to work.
Both of you.
Hey.
Promise to shine that
beautiful light of yours
onto the world today?
What about you, husband?
For you?
I'll give it everything I got.
Yeah, cheesy as hell.
KELLY (CHUCKLES): Hmm...
♪♪
You don't need a suit
for a country club.
Navy sports coat is a much better play.
It'll get you anywhere.
Yeah. Mark my words,
you will be sleeping in this.
Looks good. Fits you perfect.
You know, I... I just
got back from 'Nam,
and...
haven't quite landed a job yet, so...
Oh, uh, yeah, I get it.
Yeah. Somehow my number
didn't get called.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Puerto Rican kid whose
number doesn't get called.
- You ever hear of something so crazy?
- (CHUCKLES)
Look, we're not, uh...
we're not tailoring this thing, right?
So why don't you take it,
tuck the tag up in the sleeve
when you wear it, and
bring it back next week.
Really?
This girl, she's worth it?
Oh, man, she's like no
one you've ever seen.
♪♪
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
- Lasher.
- Roger that.
- Waters. You're with me.
- I got it.
LASHER: All right, guys, listen up.
Go ahead and set up a
cordon around the building.
As-salaam alaikum.
Wa-alaikum-salaam.
Dalta rasha.
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
Lasher.
What's up?
- Put a guy at the door.
- Ortiz!
Post up here.
We're losing daylight.
I'm not gonna have my guys in a row
in the middle of the
night in IED country.
You got five minutes.
Asmaan, you promised me
a photo of Mohammad Nadir.
- (BABY CRYING)
- I haven't received anything.
I haven't even heard from you.
(TRANSLATING)
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
She says she's nervous.
People are watching her.
- She's scared.
- I know. You need to think about your child.
(TRANSLATING)
Tell her to look at me,
not you, when she speaks.
Nadir, the bomb maker,
I need his photo. The
longer we are here,
the more danger we are all in.
(WATERS TRANSLATING)
(DOG BARKING)
If this dog keeps barking,
I'm gonna shoot it.
You're not gonna do anything
till I tell you to, Marine.
- (BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
- We had a deal.
An immigrant visa and
an expedited process.
If I leave here without that photo,
you get nothing.
(BARKING CONTINUES)
- ORTIZ: Sergeant.
- LASHER: I see 'em.
(OVER RADIO): One Bravo, Echo Main.
Echo Main, this is One Bravo.
Be advised ISR spotted
12 military-age males
moving towards your
location, possibly enemy QRF.
How copy?
CASSIDY: Asmaan.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
She's asking for water for the village.
That's more than fair. I can
get water for the village.
All right, Asmaan, I need
you to calm down that baby.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
Hey, Sharp! Wrap it up!
(BABY CRYING, DOG BARKING)
Asmaan, there's no more time.
- (WATERS TRANSLATING)
- I'm a mother, too.
I have a son... I would
do anything to protect him.
Anything. Just like you.
Your patients here, they are
mothers and they are children.
Nadir is a murderer.
- (SNIFFLING)
- He is hiding amongst you.
You give me that photo,
or the entire village pays,
including you and your child.
- (WATERS TRANSLATING)
- Look at me. Stay with me.
Hey, look at me!
Do you think I'm playing?
Do you hear me?
You have five seconds.
Five.
(WATERS TRANSLATING)
Four.
Three.
Two.
(SPEAKS ARABIC)
Okay, give it to me.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
We'll be in touch about the visa.
- Water?
- And the water.
Let's go.
LASHER: All right!
Let's mount up!
♪♪
(PIANO PLAYING MELLOW JAZZ)
Thank you.
- (QUIETLY) Oh! He's here.
- Oh! He's here.
Hi.
- Hey.
- (LAUGHS)
Um, I want to,
(WHISPERS): but there
are eyes everywhere.
- Okay, got it.
- Okay,
so, it's my parents
and their best friends.
My mom is... tough,
I'm not gonna lie, but my dad
saves all, and he's
gonna absolutely love you.
Okay.
I like your jacket, by the way.
Oh, this old thing?
Oh, and I did tell them,
under no circumstances
are they to bring up
anything about Vietnam, so...
- Thanks.
- (QUIETLY) Okay.
Everyone...
this is the famous Jack.
Famous or infamous?
Taking my daughter across the country
just a week after meeting
her seems to land...
squarely in the infamous territory.
DAVE: Well, now, honey, he took her
for two weeks, but he
brought her back in one piece,
so he can't be all bad. (CHUCKLES)
Very nice to meet you,
Jack. Sit, sit, please.
- Make yourself at home.
- Thank you.
(DAVE CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS): So...
I heard you just returned from Vietnam.
(ELECTRIC TOOL WHIRRING)
It was just a little fender bender.
I can't... I don't know
- how I'm going to pay.
- Let me see what I can do.
You pay what you can when you can.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Yo.
Haven't you seen by
the spot in a minute.
Yeah, I been busy.
Man, you're a Boy Scout now.
It's all good.
The kid has your car in the back.
Custom work's his department.
- All right. Good seeing you.
- You, too.
- (KNOCKING)
- Yeah?
- GUNNY: Sharp?
- (DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
Nadir came back to the
village a few hours ago.
- Predator drone took him out.
- What?
I-I... thought the point
was ID him, take him quietly.
He's just gonna be replaced in a week.
Yeah. Well, headquarters seems
to like to play Whac-A-Mole.
How many civilian deaths?
Eight dead, 12 or more so wounded.
Strike caught the back
side of a building.
We think bags of fertilizer were inside,
because the blast radius
wasn't supposed to be so big.
Your asset survived.
We're working on a visa
for her and her kid.
Gunny.
I promised her water for the village.
There's no more village, Sharp.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SAM WHINING)
Hey, buddy.
(SETS KEYS DOWN)
(PIECES OF PLATE CLINKING)
♪ Mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
- ♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
- (PLAYS NOTE)
- ♪ Mm, mm, mm ♪
- (PLAYS DESCENDING NOTES)
♪ Could a stranger ♪
♪ Ever end up ♪
♪ Being you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ In the quiet way ♪
♪ You caught my eye ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Caught enough to get you ♪
♪ Memorized ♪
♪ Can one wrong turn ♪
♪ Give me new direction? ♪
(MUTED CHEERING, WHOOPING)
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ Could a stranger ♪
♪ Ever end up being you? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ In the quiet way ♪
♪ You caught my eye ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Caught enough to get you memorized ♪
♪ I found my way, I found my way ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ I told the story ♪
♪ Before I knew the ending ♪
♪ I got an answer ♪
♪ Before I heard the question ♪
- (BARKING)
- ♪ How could a stranger ♪
♪ Ever end up being you? ♪
♪ And oh ♪
(SIGHS)
♪ In the quiet way... ♪
Sam wants to ask you something.
Oh, wait. Sorry. No.
I want to ask you something.
♪ Enough to get you memorized ♪
♪ I found my way, I found my way ♪
- ♪ To you ♪
- (GIGGLING)
♪ Found my way ♪
♪ I found my way ♪
♪ To you. ♪
Well, I will bet you
anything that South Vietnam,
Laos and Cambodia will all fall
to the communists just
like Ike said they would.
I don't recall hearing any
congressional declaration.
Wasn't even a real war.
- JANET: Honey? Stop.
- DAVE: Well...
Enough. Enough war.
- Uh...
- Yuck.
Happier topics.
So, Jack, it must be nice for you
to just take off cross-country
at a moment's notice.
You must come from a wealthy family
to fund all that wanderlust.
What do your parents do?
Um...
(WHISPERING): I'm sorry.
Was that inappropriate?
Jack, looks like you
took a little fire there.
Um, I should probably go clean this up.
Mm. The restroom is to the left.
- Do you need me to come show... ?
- No, no, no, no. I'm-I'm okay.
Excuse me.
(SOFT JAZZ PLAYING)
Dad? What the hell?
It's good work, kid.
Damn good.
(SIGHS) Thank you.
Um, M-Mr. Castillo,
look, I-I know you, um...
I know you have a business
of your own, right, and, uh,
look, if you ever need anything...
Whoa. You're Darnell's kid.
And Darnell's kid and my
business are not a fit.
Hey, look.
Yeah, yeah, I'm... I'm
Darnell's kid, but, uh...
man, um...
I'm-I'm also raising a
kid of my own, and, um...
(SIGHS)
... she's special.
I-I've been looking up the best schools.
And it's like ten K,
ten K for pre-K.
I mean, my-my parents
do fine, but, come on.
Even you know they don't do that fine.
I need to earn real money
for her.
I got your number.
I'll call you when you
can grow a mustache.
(SIGHS)
(TOOL WHIRRS)
(WHIRRING)
(PIANO PLAYS SOFT JAZZ)
(SIGHS)
Breathe.
Breathe, Jack.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Oh, so many...
- Didn't you work here once?
I did.
Sorry. Sorry about that.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
To be honest, I've never had lobster.
- Oh.
- Kind of got the best of me.
(JACK CHUCKLES)
My parents don't do much, ma'am,
in answer to your question.
I mean, my dad...
he-he's in door-to-door sales,
but mostly what my folks do is fight.
He hits, she cries.
That's... that's what they do.
I had, uh...
a little brother.
Um...
Basically raised him myself.
When he was l-little,
he had this two-year phase
where he was convinced
there was a monster
living in his closet.
I couldn't convince him
that there was no monster,
so instead, I would sit in
front of his closet door,
and I'd tell the monster stories.
(REBECCA LAUGHS SOFTLY)
I'd tell it bedtime stories
until Nicky was convinced
that the monster had gone to sleep,
and it wasn't gonna bother him anymore.
Yeah.
Of course, the monster wasn't real,
but my brother's fear...
that was real.
The sweat on his forehead was real.
My brother's experience was real.
I lost my brother in Vietnam.
People died.
People that I loved.
So, due respect,
it may not seem like
a real war back here,
but I promise you, that
war was very real
for those of us who were there.
I know...
a stranger taking your
daughter cross-country
might not have been your favorite thing.
And I'm sorry that was your
first impression of me, but...
don't worry.
You'll get to know me.
I'm not going anywhere.
Oh, I got to say,
I think I might be a lobster guy, Bec.
(LAUGHS)
(BIRDS SINGING)
RYAN: Hey.
Hey.
Been drinking?
I needed a few after another
day of looking for jobs.
Needed more than a few, actually.
Well, hey,
at least you're finally out, huh?
Yay for me.
(RYAN SIGHS)
Did you drive home drunk?
I don't need a lecture.
Well, hey, don't have one prepared.
Somehow I missed the last
credit card statement.
We're gonna have to pay a late fee.
Well, that's because you keep
piling the mail on the counter
even though I keep telling you not to.
(RYAN SIGHS)
I'm doing the best I can here, Cass.
I'm-I'm... I'm taking
care of everything,
I'm practically raising Matty alone.
Must be nice to have it so easy.
- Do you have any idea... ?
- No, no. I don't.
I don't because you won't talk to me.
MATTY: Mom? Mom, come here!
I made a car out of Legos!
Matty, give me a second.
Mommy just got home.
Oh, and the, uh... the hot
water heater broke again.
- Again?
- MATTY: Mom, come on!
- Come on, Mom!
- Matty, please, come on.
I asked about getting it
replaced, but it's expensive.
It's 12 hundred bucks.
(LAUGHS) Can you believe that?
$1,200 for a water heater?
(BARKING)
MATTY: Mom? Mom?!
Mommy? Mommy? Mom! Mom.
(BARKING)
- Mom?
- Stop!
Sor...
Matty.
- Matty, I'm so sorry. I...
- Um... no, no.
Get out.
- I didn't... I didn't...
- Just get out of this house.
- (PIANO PLAYS SOFT MUSIC)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I'm gonna go to the restroom,
I'll be right back.
- I'll get the coats.
- (QUIETLY) Okay.
Young man,
you know, you walked in here
tonight a bit of an underdog,
- to put it mildly.
- (CHUCKLES)
But you had yourself quite an evening.
You made a bunch of fans.
Thank you, sir. Just need the one.
Ah.
You know, first year of her life,
she only stopped crying if I held her.
Not her mother, not her sister.
Just me.
And everyone would say
"Oh, she's a Daddy's girl."
And I said, "No.
She is her daddy's world."
Oh, and she still is.
You're a good man, Jack.
I can see that.
I can also see a man who
is carrying things with him.
And I can see a man
who is far more haunted
than he wants to let on.
I don't follow.
I want more for her
than you can offer, Jack.
I will do everything I can to stop this.
And make no mistake about this, son.
I'm a lot harder to beat than
an imaginary monster in a closet.
REBECCA: Oh, goodness, I
barely ate, I was so nervous.
- Daddy, thank you.
- Oh, you're welcome.
- Yeah.
- Oh, thank you for dinner. I love you to death,
but Jack, can you take me
to go get a burger, please?
- Absolutely.
- Okay. Good night, Dad.
Good night.
♪ You were waiting outside ♪
♪ For me, in the sun ♪
♪ Laying down to soak it all in ♪
♪ Before we had to run... ♪
Thanks for coming tonight.
I-I know how boring
this is for you, but...
No, of course.
Sorry. I'm just... tired.
Well, yeah. I mean...
we knew getting the
restaurant off the ground
would be the hardest part, but
now that it's up and running...
I'm pregnant.
♪ Oh, the glory of... ♪
I'm-I'm sorry. My brain
just short-circuited. Did... ?
I'm six weeks pregnant.
♪ Was lost on me ♪
♪ Till I saw how hard... ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ It'd be to reach you... ♪
Lucy.
(CHUCKLES): Lucy, oh, my God.
♪ Light-years away... ♪
I wanted to get my
career sorted before...
How the hell is this gonna work?
♪ Light-years away... ♪
Look at me.
Are you looking at me? I'm blind.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I'm looking at you.
♪ In the shadows alone ♪
♪ You could've been right
there next to me ♪
♪ And I'd have never known ♪
♪ Oh, the glory ♪
♪ Of it all ♪
♪ Was lost on me ♪
♪ Till I saw how hard
it'd be to reach you ♪
♪ And I would always be light-years ♪
♪ Light-years away from you ♪
_
♪ Light-years ♪
♪ Light-years away from you. ♪
(DARNELL GROANING SOFTLY)
What, you feeling your age, old man?
- (CHUCKLES) Watch it.
- (CHUCKLES)
I see you roll your eyes
every time your moms gets
on you about responsibility.
I get it.
Responsibility.
For me, it was always
a pain in the ass word.
When I was young, it meant doing chores.
As I got older, it
meant not getting to do
the stuff I really wanted to do.
I was going down a wrong path in my 20s.
Then your mom got pregnant.
And being responsible,
setting the right example for you,
it saved me.
That's when I realized
"responsibility" didn't have
to be a pain in the ass word.
Son.
Hey.
Don't even think about it.
A'ight?
Yeah.
A'ight.
I'll watch the baby.
I'll talk to your mother.
But you're going to Andre's barbecue.
No, no, no, I-I...
Son, your life is not over.
You're still a young man,
you still have friends
that have barbecues,
and, on occasion, your
wonderful father...
I'm down to babysit.
Get some QT with my granddaughter.
W-Wait, are you sure?
- You're making breakfast tomorrow.
- (LAUGHS)
And you better not half-ass it, either.
I want the full deal.
Western omelets and hash browns.
- Yeah? All right.
- (LAUGHS): Yeah, okay. Okay.
Yeah.
I used to sing here all the time,
and they basically paid me in burgers.
♪ Send me ♪
♪ Never-ending words of love... ♪
- Rebecca?
- (GASPS) Hi, Gerry.
- Oh, we've missed you, kid.
- Aw.
You know, it's open Mic tonight.
Place is pretty dead, so...
You want to dust off an old one for us?
No, no, no, I'm okay.
- We're actually just gonna...
- Yes.
It's-it's been a day.
I could use a song
from my favorite singer.
CASSIDY: So...
the drinking's become a thing.
It started a few years ago.
It's only gotten worse since
I've been out of the Corps.
My husband and I are...
separated, I guess.
My life's at a standstill.
Actually, that's a lie. It's...
moving in reverse.
I went from working
in classified settings
to driving around college students
on a Saturday night for Uber.
(CHUCKLES): No offense to Uber drivers.
I...
I can't... feel anything.
I can't feel sadness.
I certainly can't feel joy.
And I hate throwing
around the term PTSD,
and I know you guys
will probably tell me
that that's what this is, but...
But when I hit him...
When I hit my son,
I can't blame PTSD or alcohol or Uber.
It was the cost of a water heater.
Just brought me right back.
On behalf of the U.S. government,
we'd like to present to you
these condolence payments
for every civilian that
was killed yesterday.
$1,200 U.S. per person.
(BABY CRYING)
CASSIDY: You guys
know we do that, right?
Dead civilian.
Dead kids.
$1,200 per person.
That's the price of a
life over there. That's...
a price of a water heater.
So when I think about that...
Don't know where Toby
and Kate put their dishes.
- They've barely even unpacked.
- I will find them.
- (REBECCA GASPS)
- KEVIN: Guess whose birthday
- it is, huh?
- Hi.
- Birthday cake.
- No, no, no, no.
Don't touch the cake.
- We're waiting for your sister and Toby.
- Yeah?
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you, Mom.
- (PHONE BUZZING)
- You know, I came out first. I feel like
I should be able to eat the cake first.
REBECCA: No one's eating any cake yet.
We're waiting for your sister.
Hello?
Yeah.
Uh, no. Yeah.
Okay. Uh, no. No, of course. Yeah.
Um... I...
H-Hold on one second.
It's Uncle Nicky. He got in trouble
in Pennsylvania, he's being arrested
and he gave them my
number for the bail money.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MALIK: What's up, what's up, what's up?
Hey, man.
(CHUCKLES): Hey. Hey.
Hey, yo, Malik.
Hey, Malik.
Hey, Sky. What's up?
Yo, I heard you got into honors bio.
That's what's up. (CHUCKLES)
Hey, I want to introduce you to someone.
This is my friend Deja.
She just moved here.
She's starting school tomorrow.
Uh... Hi, hi, hi, Deja.
- Um, Malik. Nice to meet you.
- (DEJA CHUCKLES)
Um, Sky says you make a good burger.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh, I-I make a...
I make a decent, decent burger.
(CHUCKLES): But-but for you,
I'll give it everything I got.
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Dej.
Hmm?
What's happening with your face?
What? Um, nothing.
All right, here's the plan.
I'll take a break and
stay home with him.
- Or her.
- Okay.
Tobe, no matter what he says,
he's gonna have an
amazing, incredible life.
Yes, he will, because he has
an amazing, incredible
mother who's going to give him
all of her amazing, incredible traits.
His dad's not so bad.
- Is he? Huh?
- Yeah.
Well, maybe his dad will
give him his sense of humor.
But please, God, please,
please, please, God,
not his hairline.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Grow some hair, please.
You crush it at the restaurant,
and if you can make it home
every once in a while to see him...
- Or her.
- Okay.
Well, that's great,
but it's not required.
- Okay, guys.
- (JACK FUSSING)
So...
Nothing's really changed
since the last procedure.
Jack is still not following
cues or responding to tests.
I know it's been a long three months,
but now it's time to move forward.
Jack's retinopathy will not be reversed.
His eyesight will not return.
Okay, we're here.
DOCTOR: The good news is
it's not total stage V.
He will be able to see some light,
maybe some shapes.
Am I lined up?
You're perfect.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and gentlemen,
Jack Damon.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Hi.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE CONTINUE)
Good evening. Hello. Sorry to interrupt.
Um... (CLEARS THROAT)
I would like to dedicate this song
to a man who was a total stranger
just a few weeks ago.
I may be only Pittsburgh good,
but, my God,
he makes me feel like one day,
I will stand
on the biggest stage in the world.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
♪ Can one wrong turn ♪
♪ Give me new direction? ♪
♪ Can one false move ♪
♪ Bring me one true friend? ♪
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE CONTINUE)
♪ Could a stranger ♪
♪ Ever end up being you? ♪
(SINGING INAUDIBLE)
♪ We took it back ♪
♪ In all directions ♪
♪ Reaching out ♪
♪ Towards the door ♪
♪ Is there a message ♪
♪ A pathway to something more ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ In the quiet way you caught my eye ♪
♪ I got enough to get you ♪
♪ Memorized ♪
♪ I found my way ♪
♪ I found my way to you ♪
♪ I told a story ♪
♪ Before I knew ♪
♪ The ending ♪
♪ I got an answer ♪
♪ Before I heard the question ♪
♪ How did a stranger ♪
♪ Ever end up being you? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ In the quiet way you caught my eye ♪
♪ Got enough to get you ♪
♪ Memorized ♪
♪ I found my way ♪
♪ I found my way to you ♪
♪ I found my way... ♪