Previously, on
"This Is Us"...
I take office
in the next few weeks,
and God only knows
what kind of effect
that's gonna have
on my family.
We're moving to Philadelphia.
This is my friend Deja.
Hi, hi, hi, Deja.
Um, Malik.
Nice to meet you.
I think I might like girls.
We love you.
No matter what, okay?
Hello?
All right, um,
hold on one second.
It's Uncle Nicky.
He got in trouble
in Pennsylvania.
He's being arrested
and he gave them my number
for the bail money.
Nothing's really changed
since the last procedure.
Jack's retinopathy
will not be reversed.
His eyesight will not return.
*THIS IS US*
Season 04  Episode 02
Episode Title: "The Pool (Part 2)"
Happy end
of summer vacation,
- Ah.
- Babe. Thank you.
- Good morning.
Next week,
those irritable
prepubescent monsters
are no longer our problem
between the hours
- of 8:00 a.m. and 3:00 p.m.
- Ugh. Right?
- Hmm...
- Mmm, I actually hated that high five.
Me, too.
Hey, babe, can we please
just do something fun today?
I feel like we haven't even seen
the kids all summer.
Yeah, that's because they're
going into seventh grade.
They want nothing
to do with us anymore.
You know, they actually think
we're dorks.
Like, me, a dork.
- I know.
- Me.
Okay.
Hey, kids?
Get in here!
Hey, why don't we go
to the pool?
We haven't been to the pool
in forever.
Well, I could do,
I could do a pool day.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- Good morning.
- Hey, you two, eyes up here.
- Take those off for a second.
- Hey!
Hey yourself.
Exciting announcement:
we're doing a Pearson family
fun day.
We're gonna go
to the Greenview pool.
Do we have to?
There's a 90210 marathon on.
Yeah, I'm good to stay here.
I want to knock out two more
books to make sure that I win
this summer's library
read-a-thon.
Can we go
to the Greenview pool?
- Please.
- You big mope, don't hold out on us.
- Please. Please.
- Please.
Okay.
Hey, Nicky, it's Kevin,
uh, again.
Listen, I-I left you,
like, five voice mails, man.
Um, I'm just trying to make sure
you're okay.
And I-I know you texted me last week
saying that you were okay,
which was a little urprising,
actually,
'cause I didn't realize texting
was in your wheelhouse.
But, um...
Listen, man, I guess I'm looking
for a little more detail,
you know?
Uh, seeing as I did wire you
all that money for bail.
So...
Would you please call me
back?
Just want to make sure
you're okay.
Bye.
So, good news: my houseplant
finally grew a new branch.
So... which, for those of you
who aren't regulars here,
uh, my sponsor suggested
that I get something simple
to take care of.
Said it would keep me
focused.
So I got a ficus.
A Ficus benjamina, to be exact.
And good on my sponsor,
because that plant
is basically the only thing
in my life
that I feel in control of
right now.
Yeah?
- Ready for you, Kevin.
- Okay.
I've been just sort
of going through the motions
on this new movie
that I just finished.
All right, Kev.
Last take.
Mind if we try
something different?
You just tell me what to do
and I'll do it.
All right,
don't let this guy hide.
He's alone. Let him not be okay
for a second.
- Sound good?
- Great idea.
Okay, all right, here we go.
Everybody to one.
Let's go.
Set!
- And... background.
- Background.
- Action!
- Go, guys, go, cops.
And cut.
- Fantastic.
- That's a cut!
Great.
- Hey, man.
- Hi. Thanks for the opportunity.
I really appreciate it.
That was fun.
And, uh, thanks
for being a good sport
about all
the "I see dead people" jokes.
Yeah, that never gets old.
- I bet.
- Yeah.
All right.
- You know, when... Sit down.
- Yeah.
You know, when you strip away
all the artifice,
all those tricks you use
to make yourself seem
appealing and charming
and handsome...
When you let all that crap go,
you're absolutely
incredible.
And I am...
...way in over my head
with my sister
and her new son.
He was born premature,
and we just found out
that he's blind.
So I go to all the doctor's
appointments with them,
but I never know
what to say.
I never know what to do.
So...
there's that.
Hey.
Just saw
the new windows going in
over at the community center.
Yeah.
Got some real nice
double-paned beauties.
Almost as beautiful as
my wife.
Did you just compare me
to rec center windows?
They're double-paned windows.
It's the sexiest kind
of windows.
- Okay. All right.
- All right, all right.
So these are
the paint options
for my dance studio. - - Mm.
- Right? Which one do you like?
- Hmm.
Silver Whisper,
of course.
But no studio today.
I got big things planned
for the last day
of summer break.
Everybody's been
so busy getting
settled in
these past few weeks,
so I'm thinking
a classic Pearson
family fun day.
I'm down.
But good luck
getting these girls on board.
I don't know
if it's the hormones
or the stress
of going to new schools,
but they are definitely
getting meaner by the day.
Stop it. They are not
getting meaner by...
Hey! There they are.
The flyest females in Philly.
You don't need to give us
nicknames every morning.
No, sometimes,
you could just be like,
"Good morning, Tess.
Good morning, Deja."
- Meaner by the day.
- Mom,
can you take me
to get my hair cut?
Yeah, I would,
but your dad has a classic
- Pearson family fun day planned.
- Ooh!
It's gonna be epic.
I'm talking Liberty Bell.
I'm talking gorging
on cheesesteaks
- till you get meat sweats.
- Mmm!
Mom promised that I can get my
hair cut before school starts.
That's why I've been
growing it out all summer.
And you promised me
that we could ride the bus
together so you could decide
if I can take it to school
by myself.
Even though
I've been taking the bus
by myself
since I was eight years old.
All right.
All right, how about this?
Dej, you and I
will do a trial run
of the bus route to school.
Beth, you take Tess
to the salon.
And then we'll meet up
for a classic
- Pearson family fun afternoon.
- Ooh.
Unless something horrible
happens on the bus.
- Ooh.
- Would you stop? Do you hear this?
Annie, my favorite child,
is there anything
that you'd like to do today?
I'm good with whatever.
Bless your soul.
♪ Baby Jack,
doo, doo, doo, doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Baby Jack, doo, doo,
doo, doo, doo, doo ♪
♪ Just went to town,
♪ On Mommy's boob. ♪
Okay, that was creepy.
There's my hungry dude.
Yes.
Is he done? 'Cause I got
to squish that little face.
Yes, he is.
Okay, Jack,
I'm gonna hand you
to your dad now, okay?
- Okay. Okay.
- Here comes Daddy.
- Got him?
- Yeah, I got him.
- Okay.
There you go. You're okay.
You want to come up here? Hey.
- Aw.
- Hey, buddy. It's me, your dad.
All you have to remember
is that I am the hairy one.
Huh?
There... Yeah, see?
There it is.
Now...
how are you feeling?
- Good.
- About today?
Yeah, I'm excited.
I mean, according to Dr. Dorsey,
this woman is amazing.
And Yelp.
There are specialists
who teach you how to raise
a blind baby on Yelp?
Oh, there's everything on Yelp.
But I cannot wait to learn
- some pro tips. I need 'em.
- Yeah.
- Right, Baby Jack?
Can you feel Mommy smiling?
She's so excited
to learn pro tips.
She's so excited.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Uh...
A week ago, we found out
that there is nothing we can do
about his vision,
and you haven't missed a beat.
Now, don't get me wrong.
That... I think that's awesome.
I'm just...
I'm just checking in.
- That's all.
- I'm so good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And I appreciate it.
Thank you.
- Okay.
- Thank you. How are you feeling?
Uh... I'm hanging
in there, I guess.
- Good. Good.
- All right.
- Okay.
I love you.
♪ All I wanna do is
zoom-a-zoom-zoom-zoom ♪
♪ And a poom-poom,
just shake ya rump ♪
♪ All I wanna do ♪
♪ Is zoom-a-zoom-zoom-zoom ♪
♪ And a poom-poom,
just shake ya rump... ♪
Oh, hey, Stewart.
- Read-a-thon?
- Book number 64.
Well, good luck.
You don't stand a chance,
Stewart.
Hey, Kev?
Kev.
Sunscreen. Come here.
Take that.
- Your shoulders.
- Hey!
Gross.
- What?
- I can do it myself.
♪ All I wanna do... ♪
I...
Hey, Kev,
don't forget your back.
♪ All I wanna do ♪
♪ Is zoom-a-zoom-zoom-zoom
and a poom-poom. ♪ - Dad!
- Stop. There's people around.
- Hey, I got five chairs.
Five chairs.
- That is a pool day miracle.
- Nice.
Keith, Renard,
you guys made it.
Come on, we're going
to get Firecracker pops.
What are you listening to?
Wreckx-n-Effect.
Oh, cool.
We brought our boombox.
- You want to put it on?
- Sure.
Hey. Hey, g... I...
- I got five chairs, guys.
- Hey, Bug,
do you want to go play a game?
Mom, stop talking right now.
Hey, Carrie.
Hey, Jessica P.
- Cool cover-up.
- Oh, thanks.
- Want to come hang out with us?
- Sure.
Hey, Katie girl,
- I-I got five chairs.
- Uh...
Do you know who that is?
Carrie and Jessica P.?
Yeah, the most popular girls
in school.
I don't think they've ever
talked to Kate
a day in her life.
Come on, you heard them,
they-they like her cover-up.
Yeah. I don't trust that.
Hey, babe?
- Hmm?
- You know, there is an upside...
Why don't you lay back...
To kids that want
nothing to do with us. Ah.
- Hey, Kev.
- Yeah?
If your uncle wants to talk,
he knows how to find you.
Right.
I... I think that you should be
staying focused
on your sobriety.
Working and keeping busy has
been a really good thing
for you, maybe you should try
looking for your next job.
Yeah, maybe.
Now, we did read
in The Hollywood Reporter
that you're on some short list
for that new movie
with, um... What's...
- Uh, Spike Jonze.
- Spike Jonze.
Okay, hold on a second,
you two are reading
The Hollywood Reporter?
Oh, yeah, we got a subscription
- when we moved here.
- Wow,
that's terrifying.
Yeah.
Anyway, um, the movie shoots
in Chicago, right,
so I'd have to leave,
then I'm thinking
it might be best for me
to just stay here and
- help Kate with the baby, you know?
- Yeah, I...
I just think it would be good
for you to stay busy,
is all I'm saying.
All right,
- are we ready for this?
- Yeah.
- All right. Here we come.
Hello?
Hi.
- Hi.
- There's my grandson.
Hi. - Hi. -Hey.
- There you go.
- Wow. This place is really
- coming together.
- Thank you. -Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Hey, Toby, every time
I see you,
I-I swear you're skinnier.
Oh. Yeah. Thanks.
You doing paleo or aikido or,
yeah, are you
intermittent fasting?
More like, uh,
intermittent stressing.
You know, what-what you do is,
for 22 hours a day,
you stress, uh, uh,
over your baby,
and you stress
about your mortgage, and then,
you just sleep
for the other two hours.
- Hmm.
- Yeah, the weight just falls off.
Too bad
it doesn't work for me.
I keep telling you,
you have to stress harder.
Ooh, I think that's Anna.
Come on.
Let's all go wash our hands.
- Yeah. - Oh, hey.
- Hey.
- How are you doing?
Good. Madison,
please don't do the voice.
- Okay.
- Listen,
I... I'm great, Jack is great.
Today, we're just gonna
keep things very light.
- Right? And positive.
- Okay. Okay.
- Okay.
- I am... I am so your girl.
I was head cheerleader
in high school,
and I was one
of those bar mitzvah
party starters in college.
If there's anyone
who can keep things peppy,
you're looking at her.
I know you guys have been
through a lot
over the last couple months, but
today is about the next chapter.
Today, we're going to go over
the basics of how to care
for your blind infant,
to make sure
he has everything he needs
physically and developmentally.
Great. Great. Right?
We're so eager to learn.
What? Oh, you want
to take notes, Jack?
Oh.
He wants us to take the notes.
He's just gonna listen.
He's just gonna listen, right?
Ha! Too funny.
Okay.
Uh, so, first question.
- I know this is a new house.
- Mm.
Are you happy
with the furniture
- and where everything is?
- Uh...
Why? Are you
an interior designer, too?
I ask
because Jack is already starting
to absorb the layout
of the new home.
So, if the furniture stays put,
then it makes it easier
for him to learn each room.
- Mm.
- Different floor textures help, too.
Uh, carpeting in one room,
tile in the next.
That's smart.
Okay, so, I'd like
to start with an activity.
We will all take a notepad,
choose a room, and write down
anything you think
might be dangerous
or of concern to Baby Jack
once he starts to crawl.
What are we doing for you today?
I was thinking
something like this.
Oh, bold! I love it!
Here. Let me clean up my station,
and I'll come grab you?
Hey.
Are you sure about this?
Yup.
Okay.
As long as you're sure.
I mean, I-I want you
to express yourself,
you know, I really do, but this is...
this is a big decision.
I know, which is why you've made
me think about this all summer.
Can you just...?
So, this is what a bus is like.
I've been on a bus before, Dej.
I know this is important to you.
I'm just trying
to wrap my head around it.
- So, humor me here, okay?
- Okay.
Well, how about
we don't sit together
so you can see what it'll really
be like for me riding it alone?
It's a good idea.
Mm-hmm.
I told you all the good stuff.
I told you
all the good stuff, Grayson.
People get buried
in their phones.
When I was growing up,
if you weren't home,
they didn't get a hold of you.
Frankly, I think people
get a hold of you
too easily nowadays.
I'd like to disappear
every now and then.
Excuse me.
Can I sit next to my daughter?
Yeah. All right.
What was he talking to you
about?
The Democratic primary.
I don't know.
Randall, he was a weirdo.
The bus is full of weirdos.
But I can handle myself.
Why do you even care
about riding the bus so much?
It's faster if I drive you.
You moved us here.
You wanted me
to live in Philadelphia,
so let me live in Philadelphia.
I am letting you live, Deja,
but I am also your father.
Okay, you're right,
but I also had a whole life
before I met you.
We grew up real different,
Randall.
The stuff
that makes you uncomfortable
reminds me
of where I'm from.
I get it.
But it is my job
to worry about you.
And you're only in
the ninth grade, and I'm just
not comfortable with it yet,
so maybe next year, okay?
Unbelievable.
M.C. Hammer is mad old.
Okay, I got one.
Which member of Kris Kross
do y'all think is cooler?
Definitely Kross.
Neither of them
are named "Kross," Randall.
I know.
I was making a joke.
- Sure you were.
- Hey, guys, check this out.
♪ Booties of the cuties
steady shakin' but relaxin' ♪
♪ The action, is packed
in a jam like a closet ♪
♪ Beats bound to get you up,
cold flowin' like a faucet ♪
♪ Not mean to make you sit, not
mean to make you jump, but ♪
♪ Yup, make the hotties
in the party shake your rump. ♪
It was nice, man.
- Thanks.
- ♪ And a poom-poom... ♪
Hey, Randall,
take the next part.
Yeah, come on.
You got this, Ray.
Yeah, come on,
show us your stuff!
♪ And a poom-poom,
just shake ya rump ♪
♪ All I want to do
is zoom-zoom-zoom ♪
- ♪ And a poom-poom ♪
- ♪ With a poom-poom ♪
♪ I like the way
you comb your hair ♪
- ♪ Uh, I like stylish clothes you wear ♪
- ♪ Clothes and... ♪
♪ It's just the little things you
do, uh ♪ - ♪ Wear with ♪
♪ Uh, that makes me want to ♪
- ♪ Get with you ♪
♪ All I want to do is... ♪
How is your brother
blacker than you, Randall?
Randall's an Oreo!
I don't know what that is.
- Hey, is that your mom?
- Hi, ladies.
How are you?
Hi!
I just... I wanted
to see if maybe
you wanted to go swimming
with Dad and I?
Or play a little Marco Polo?
Um, I'm gonna stay here.
Okay.
Hey, Bug, um...
Have those girls ever wanted to
hang out with you before today?
I mean, I just want to make sure
that you're having fun, and...
Can you just go back
to Dad, please?
Yes.
You are looking very trim, Toby.
Yeah. Breastfeeding.
Burns calories.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
How are you holding up?
Honestly?
Hanging on by a thread.
Yeah.
I have... I've just...
I've never worried
about so many things
all at once.
Is one of those things Kate?
You know, a few months ago...
...when we found out
that, uh, something was wrong,
I remember
the new eye doctor coming in
and telling us that...
Jack wasn't responding
- to visual cues.
- Mm.
I remember him saying the word
"retina."
And then,
everything just kind of went,
"Wah-wah, wah-wah,
wah-wah."
You know, Charlie Brown's
mother, just noise.
And I look over,
and Kate is sitting up
real straight.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, like when she...
when she really locks in
on something,
and she is nodding.
My amazing wife just...
nodding her head
as if someone is giving her
a bad weather report.
And she's, uh...
She has been that way
every single day since.
You know, just steady.
To be honest,
I'm kind of in awe of her.
So I shouldn't be concerned?
She's overeating, Rebecca.
And I know that
that is just a way of...
dealing with difficult emotions.
But of all of the things that
I am worried about right now...
she's at the top of my list.
You know?
I know.
Yeah, I do know.
Hey, pretty lady.
What you sitting out here for?
Oh. Hey, guys.
How was the...
bus?
I was gonna say,
"How was the bus?"
Yeah.
I'm gonna go out
on a limb here
and say the bus ride
did not go well.
A man sat next to her,
I freaked out
and forbade the bus.
- Oh.
- So...
Deja's not too thrilled with me.
I'm gonna go out
on that same limb
and say that the haircut
didn't go so great, either.
- It did not.
- Mm.
She's just gonna look
so different, you know?
My little girl.
I love her hair.
I love when people say
that we look alike.
But, I don't know,
first it's the new haircut,
and then it's clothes, and...
before long the little girl
I knew like the back of my hand
is someone completely new,
and it just...
makes me so sad.
They're changing so fast.
I remember
when I was their age.
There was so much going on
in my brain.
And I'm talking real,
complicated adult stuff.
I hope moving to Philadelphia
was a good idea.
I know it's gonna be.
Hey, guys.
I-I know it's really different.
You know, I couldn't...
really picture it before,
but now that I see it...
baby, you never looked
more beautiful.
Really?
I love it.
- I love it.
- Me, too.
All right, come on,
we gotta get
our classic Pearson
family fun afternoon on.
All day today!
Hey! You ruined it!
You embarrassed me
in front of my friends.
- That's why!
- No!
- I'm not!
- Hey! - Yes, you are!
- No, I'm not!
- Hey, stop! Stop!
Both of you, stop!
- What's going on, huh?
- Nothing.
Nothing?
We were just roughhousing.
- So you're good?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we're fine.
All right.
You embarrassed me
in front of my friends,
and you liked doing it.
You're supposed to be
my brother.
Hey. What's up?
Oh, they want to meet with me?
Oh, well, that's great.
That's great.
Tomorrow?
Uh, well, tomorrow,
that means I'd have to get
on a flight tonight.
Uh...
just let me think about it,
okay?
Thank you.
...53 sharp corners
and four electric cords.
Mm.
♪ And two turtledoves... ♪
And a partridge in...
a pear tree, hmm?
Okay.
Any hanging cords
that a baby can pull down,
we also want to avoid.
Yeah, we are all over
the electrical cords.
And we have someone coming
to, uh,
wall-mount that bad boy
next week.
I know we splurged a little.
We just wanted a great TV.
You know, have little Jack
starting to watch the Steelers
really young.
Yeah, and you'll
just explain to him
everything that's happening...
like you did with me.
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'll just, uh,
narrate, and then he'll...
understand.
I'm sorry. I promised myself
that I wouldn't do this.
- It's okay.
- Oh, I'm really sorry.
Just give me a second.
Please don't follow me.
Okay.
Hey.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay. Look, it's...
Relax, man, I'm trying
to have a moment with you, okay?
Am I a good person?
You know you're
187 days old today, Jack.
So, you know,
it's pretty important.
You know
how I know that?
Because I am
187 days sober today.
Which...
seems like an absolute eternity
when you're trying not to drink,
but I look at you, and...
it doesn't seem
like any time at all.
You're so...
new.
Not me.
I'm a year away from 40...
40 years old, and the most
successful relationship
I have in my life is
with a frickin' house plant.
Yeah, of course I think
you're a good person, Kev.
Why?
I do so many bad things.
Look...
you and me...
we come from a long line
of Pearson men
who've got a lot of...
mixed-up stuff
inside of us.
I should just take
that movie in Chicago.
Just take another movie,
you know, stay busy.
Focus on being clean.
That's...
the important thing.
And it's much easier on set,
anyway.
I mean, the director tells me
to do something, and I do it.
He says, "Smile," and I smile.
He says, "Laugh," and I laugh.
He says, "Cry," and I cry.
And then he yells, "Cut!" and...
...and it's just me again.
I think that's the problem.
Hey, you want to know
what worked for me?
Hmm?
Having people
you care about.
People you want
to take care of.
That will turn you into the man
that you want to be.
But the fact that
you're already asking
these kind of questions...
that's a good sign.
Okay.
Thanks.
Hey.
How long were you, uh...?
Just for a few seconds.
- Oh.
- But I heard
everything else
on the baby monitor.
Aw, come on.
Are you okay?
Everyone's worried about you.
Mm-hmm.
I know.
You know,
so many doctors warned me.
So many doctors told me
not to have a baby.
Told me...
...about the risks,
but I decided to...
do it anyway.
It's hard not to feel
like it's my fault.
- Kate, come on...
- No.
Let me wallow.
Why does he cry every time
I go to pick him up?
Am I doing something wrong?
No.
- No.
- He, like, loses his mind
every time
I go to pick him up. I...
- Oh.
- I don't think he likes me.
No, no, no, no, no.
He likes you fine.
You just,
you have to warn him first.
Right? Because he can't see you,
so you have to...
You got to brace him
for what's coming.
Right? So then you just,
- you narrate what's happening.
- Okay.
Right? So all the baby stuff
- that you normally do with your face...
- Mm-hmm.
...it's with your voice
and with your touch.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Right? Okay.
Hey, buddy, it's your mama.
Can you feel my hand?
Okay, I'm gonna pick you up now,
okay?
Okay, bud?
Okay.
Oh, my goodness. Hi.
Come here.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna give you
to Uncle Kev, okay?
You're gonna love him.
And he always smells
really expensive.
I got you.
So I'm your Uncle Kevin.
Yeah.
I'm gonna teach you
how to pick up girls.
We're gonna do that.
Or boys.
Or robots, if that's what people
are into in the future.
Oh, this is great.
Hey. Hey.
Oh, he's perfect.
Cliff really said
he wanted to kiss me?
Yes. Just go behind
the snack shack
and he'll meet you
back there.
Okay.
Hey, Kate.
Stewart?
Oh, Stewart.
Who did you think
it was gonna be?
Cliff Ward.
Who did you think
I was gonna be?
You.
We can just stand here
for a minute
and they'll all leave.
Okay.
You know what?
No.
Okay, so tell me about this
movie offer in Chicago.
Yeah, I don't think I'm gonna
take it, though, you know?
I think I'm gonna... I'm gonna
stay here with you guys.
'Cause I'm so helpful.
I wish that you would have
as much compassion for yourself
as you do for me.
Go to Chicago.
Do this movie.
Focus on your sobriety.
You're gonna be Jack's uncle
for your entire life.
And he's gonna need you
at your best.
He's the luckiest kid
in the world
to have you as a mom,
you know that?
Aren't you?
Do you know that?
Let me look at you.
Ah.
Oh, you're gorgeous.
You're gorgeous.
Okay.
So here's what's up.
I know this is all new
and I know
that everyone is worried
about us and about me.
Jack can't see,
but he can hear, he can sense,
he can feel.
And I don't want worry
to be the prevailing feeling
in this home.
I want it to be hope.
I mean, we spent the entire day
being worried about
what we have to limit around
here in order to protect him.
That's just not how we roll
in this house.
No... No offense, Anna,
I'm sorry.
I know that's like
- a monster part of your job.
- It's all good.
Okay.
My son is gonna live
a life without limits.
I know my family
can't give him sight,
but they can damn sure
give him that.
So... who's in?
Well, you had me at,
"Okay, so here's what's up."
Mom?
Of course I'm in.
Of course.
I know that w-we're all
trying to have a family moment,
but he... this is a... his, uh,
pants are a disaster right now.
He's... That's foul.
Oh.
Did he just laugh?
Did you just laugh?
- We really have to do this?
- Yes, we have to.
And we're gonna do
a thing first,
so settle in.
Uh, there's no denying it.
You three are getting old.
Old as dirt.
So I think it's time,
uh, we let you girls in
on a little game
your mother and I play.
It's called
"Worst Case Scenario."
- No.
- Ah.
Now, the rules are simple.
We all go around and we say
"worst case scenario,"
and then our biggest fears
as to the worst possible way
our lives could go
from this move.
Now, if you don't want to go,
you don't have to, but...
Worst case scenario:
Randall never gets over himself
and I have to spend
the next four years
trapped in my room
like Rapunzel.
Wow. That was good.
I'm a fast learner.
My turn.
Worst case scenario:
Tomorrow when Deja takes
the bus to school, she forgets
to text me the moment
she arrives,
and then I'm forced to ground
her until she turns 18.
W-W-Wait.
You're gonna let me...
A text the moment
you get to school.
Every single day.
Yes, sir.
All right, worst case scenario.
Um, that I project
my own stuff
on to you girls,
making you feel
anything less than your
wonderful, beautiful,
wildly unique selves.
Tess.
I don't have one.
Nothing?
Nope.
Philly looks good on me.
Worst case scenario:
All of my friends back home
forget about me.
Wow, babe. Have you been worried
about that?
Why didn't you say
anything sooner?
I'm just messing with you.
All right.
So...
We ready to do this?
Last one up the steps is
- buying cheese steaks.
- Wait! - Wait! - Wait!
Go!
♪ I love my father
and I love him well ♪
♪ I hope to see him
someday soon ♪
♪ I love my father
and I love him well... ♪
- Hey.
- Hi.
Nacho?
Yes. Thanks.
- What happened?
- Ugh.
I'm just eating my worries
about Kate.
Don't judge. Okay?
Mm.
Kevin asked me if I think
he's a good person.
- What?
- Yeah.
What did you tell him?
Something... Something about
complicated men.
Did he feel better?
I have no idea.
- ♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
- Hmm.
Hey. Do you remember
when we used to come here
- way back when?
- Mm-hmm.
And our biggest problem
was getting the kids
to put their floaties on?
Yeah.
♪ I love my father
and I love him well ♪
What airline?
American, please.
♪ Someday soon ♪
♪ I love my father
and I love him well ♪
♪ I hope to see him
someday soon ♪
♪ 'Cause where I live
it gets dark at night ♪
♪ The kind of dark
eats up the light ♪
♪ And where I live
it gets dark at night ♪
♪ The kind of dark ♪
♪ Eats up the light ♪
♪ And you know that, Mother ♪
♪ I'd be lying ♪
♪ If I didn't tell you
I'm afraid of night ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm... ♪
Hey.
All right, I'll be back
in a little bit.
Babe, are you sure
that you want
to go to the grocery store now?
I mean, we-we have stuff
for breakfast.
Yeah, I like going when
the store's not so crowded.
- Mm. Okay.
- All right.
- Love you guys.
- Love you.
♪ And as I dream
I'm falling down ♪
♪ The world moves
without a sound ♪
♪ I'm lost as sure
as I was found ♪
♪ The sun comes up
without a sound... ♪
Hey, Bug.
How was it hanging
with your new friends?
Good. Thanks.
♪ So I'll up and face
another day ♪
♪ And I hope that kindness
comes your way ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll up and face
another day ♪
♪ And I hope that kindness
comes your way ♪
I didn't need you to come.
I know.
♪ I pray for you today... ♪
You guys have a good
end-of-summer pool day?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ And in the morning
I'll be gone ♪
♪ Wherefore and to
cannot be told ♪
♪ A mind filled
with memories ♪
♪ Weigh me down like gold ♪
♪ I love my father
and I love him well ♪
♪ I hope to see him
someday soon. ♪
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Sync corrections by srjanapala