Previously on "This Is Us"...
You want your husband back?
Yes.
Well, then we should get him back.
I think it's time we got
out of this place, you know?
Get into a home.
And start a new chapter.
Hey, Mom, it's Kevin.
I got married, uh, to Sophie, yeah.
Got married to Sophie.
Babe?
I can't find it.
Hey, what about this? Will this do?
We can't have our first dinner
in our first house on terrycloth.
Found it.
See? This is perfect.
It's gonna look so good on our table...
- Where's our table?
- Finding table.
- Hey.
- Morning. How'd you sleep?
Weird. I kept waking up
and forgetting where I was.
Me, too. I mean, we only
moved in a month ago.
I feel like it's gonna take some time
for it to feel like home.
Can you grab me that other chair?
Please, Bug?
Do you really think a fancy
dinner is gonna make it
less bizarre that Kevin got married
five years after puberty?
He doesn't even understand
how a checking account works.
Kate, we've talked about this.
What's done is done. Now we
just have to support them.
I actually think it'll be fun
to have something to celebrate.
Randall's bringing his new girlfriend,
Miguel's gonna bring some
fancy bottle of wine...
And a sleeping bag.
What? He's here all the time.
He also talked the Realtor
down and fixed the gutters.
So I think that at least
deserves a dinner invitation.
I'm off to work.
Hey, how is work, by the way?
You seem to really be liking it.
Yeah, it's okay. A little boring.
Hey, does anyone actually work here?
- Go.
- I know, I'm gonna go.
Hello.
Yeah. Coming.
Baby, slow down.
I have to go over my
science presentation,
proof my English essay,
and review my Spanish vocab
before school.
All right, well, what's
Spanish for "chew"?
- Masticar.
- Then do that.
Good morning, my breakfast beauties.
Who's ready to own this day?
Hey, you were out early this morning.
- I didn't even see you.
- I did.
That's right. 'Cause we're early birds.
Getting that worm.
Ten miles. Best time. No big deal.
Ten miles? What are you,
training for a marathon?
I just felt good and I kept going.
Hey, Dej. Cereal?
One-third Corn Flakes,
two-thirds Cheerios,
just like you like it.
You think cereal is gonna make me forget
you treat me like a child who
can't make her own decisions
about who to date?
That was the plan.
Okay.
You're gonna need a better plan, man.
Yeah.
Hey, Kate.
Okay, you have to tell
me what the baby gift is.
I don't. It'll ruin the surprise.
Oh, is it a pony?
Huh, Randall? I'd love a pony.
Or a, or a hot tub.
For a baby?
Look, I don't know.
The Pearson men are known
for their grand gestures.
It could be literally anything.
- Yeah.
- In the meantime, listen, I got to go.
I'm off to the gun show. All right.
Love you. Bye, Randall.
It's not a pony or a hot tub.
But it is from me and Kevin.
He made me promise I'd tell you that.
Even though it was my
idea, and I did everything
while he did nothing. So you call
me first when it gets there.
Okay. Hey, um...
I'm worried about Kev.
I mean, he bought a trailer?
In Pennsylvania?
Quiet's nice, huh?
It was.
So... what was it like
growing up with my dad?
Hmm? Tell me a story
about his childhood.
He liked ice cream.
Yeah. That's a good story.
That's-that's a great story. Uh,
I'm gonna expand on that a bit.
I remember when I was a kid,
my dad used to come home,
sometimes he'd bring these,
uh, these cartons of ice cream.
You know, the, the ones
with the cardboard sides
that you'd fold down,
leaving just a brick of ice cream?
Anyway, he'd, um...
- Right there?
- Right there.
He'd cut it like it was a cake.
Big old cut, oh!
God, I really loved that.
Nothing. Okay, great.
Mm. You, uh, you looking forward
- to the hockey game today?
- Yeah, I was.
- Yeah.
- But then I remembered
I don't really want to go, so...
Listen, they're honoring
vets at tonight's game.
They're inviting
Cassidy down on the ice,
it's a whole thing.
Plus I might have told her
I'd help her win her husband back.
You... have
strange relationships with people.
Might be the nicest
thing you ever said to me.
Councilman.
Ah... there's the man that
stood me up for drinks.
Thank you for meeting me.
I'm really sorry about the other night.
I hate missing a good Scotch
and a healthy debate on gentrification.
Well, it didn't sit too
well with a few councilmen
that you obviously had
better things to do, but we
consoled ourselves with steaks
at Del Frisco's afterward.
Yeah...
Ah, excuse me, this is
my daughter's school.
Hello. Yes.
So, did you talk to my wife? She didn't?
Okay. Um, I will be right there.
Councilman, I'm so sorry, I have to go.
Um... my daughter had a panic attack.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Okay. Two of the legs are now
officially attached. We
just have to find the others.
Where is the big pot?
I can't make lasagna
without the big pot.
Oh, baby, that's a problem,
because I-I'm starving.
And I think, I think
I might have forgotten
to pack the big pot.
How about an hors d'oeuvre
to tide you over, good sir?
- Thanks.
- Hmm?
Bon appétit.
Aw.
I hope the salmon's not chewy.
- No, it's good.
- Uh, it's okay if you don't like salmon,
you know, or are allergic.
I totally forgot to ask
about dietary restrictions.
Uh, I-I like salmon.
What do you think, guys?
Should I, uh, open the wine
and let it breathe before
Kev and Sophie get here?
Yeah. I'll open the
wine and let it breathe.
I forgot the dill garnish. Hold on.
Ah, yes. Because a garnish
will make it less crazy
that Kevin got married.
- Kate, come on.
- It's true.
I keep a list of things
to fix around the house
'cause my mom needs help
now that she's alone.
Oh, actually, she's not alone.
I'm here all the time.
All right, I got the garnish.
Oh, that reminds me.
I brought a housewarming present.
What?
Tonight.
Um, there's a story behind it.
Don't worry. It's...
What, d-does everybody hate hot sauce,
- or... ?
- No, no, no. Um...
It's just that, uh...
Jack used to put hot sauce
on everything.
Uh, my dad loved hot sauce, too.
So much so
that he brought a bottle
of it wherever he went.
Um, as a gift, but it
wasn't actually a gift.
He just wanted to make sure
he always had hot sauce.
Um, yeah, he put it on-on eggs
and put it on burgers.
Um, one time, he even put it on Froyo.
Yeah, after he died,
I started bringing it as a gift, too.
- Well, thank you.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Oh, that must be them.
Hey. This is weird, right?
- Hi, Mom.
- Look at you guys.
Let's try to be supportive for Mom.
There they are.
Oh, my goodness!
Come on in. Come in.
Uh, wife, would you like to enter?
Yes, husband.
Okay.
This is how we enter buildings now.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Now, that's weird.
Thank you.
You want to talk about it?
- 'Cause I know a thing or two about...
- Please, no.
You know, it's okay.
Happens to me, too.
Sometimes it just comes out of nowhere.
Like when I have a lot of
stuff going on in my life.
I won't even know that
I'm feeling that way,
and then it just catches
up to me all of a sudden.
Hey, baby.
I left the studio right away.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, she's okay.
The nurse said she had a
little trouble breathing
and a rapid heart rate.
Probably brought on by some anxiety.
Is that what's going on? Huh?
- Feeling a little anxious?
- I don't know.
- I guess.
- It makes sense.
There's a lot happening.
New school, friends.
You put a lot of pressure
on yourself with your grades.
- I think you get that from me.
- S-Stop.
Stop saying I'm like you.
I don't want to be anything like you.
Hey, don't you, uh, don't
you have one of those
Vietnam baseball hats you
could wear or something?
You know?
You know, it's not like it's a-a
concert we all went to, Kevin.
No, no, it's, it's... I'm just
saying, like, it would be nice
if other people could
recognize you for your service.
You know what I mean?
That's sort of what this whole thing
is all about.
- You know what would be nice?
- What's that?
If I could just drink,
like, ten beers in a row,
you know, just to get through this.
Relax. I'm kidding.
I prefer whiskey.
- You made it.
- Hey!
Hey, congrats on the whole,
uh, you know, your whole thing.
- Oh. I guess.
- Yeah.
Um, Matty's dad's coming
to the ceremony, so...
Oh, okay.
Shut up.
He's just being a good
dad. He's bringing his son
- to see people clap for his mom.
- Mom!
- Hey.
- Kevin!
- What's up, buddy?
- Hi, bud.
What do you say? Get me up high.
There it is. Nice vertical.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Dad!
Dad, this is Kevin. Isn't he cool
- like I said he was?
- Nah, come on. You know what?
You buy a kid one Kit Kat.
Good to meet you, Ryan.
Ah, glad to finally meet the adult man
that my nine-year-old son keeps saying
is one of his best friends.
- Okay. Come on.
- Okay.
You really do have the strangest
relationships with people.
I couldn't find the fourth table leg,
so we're just gonna have
to eat on the strong corner.
Babe, you're already
cooking three babies
in your belly, okay? You
don't have to do this.
It's our first night in our new home,
and I want everything to be just right.
- Okay.
- Here.
- Start on your salad.
- Huh.
Hey, Kev.
You recognize the salad recipe?
It's Emeril Lagasse.
- Who?
- Emeril Lagasse, you know,
the chef that goes "Bam".
We watched him together
all last year.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Bam.
- Yeah. This is him.
- Yeah, totally.
Awesome.
So how come you guys got married?
Mm. It was a sign.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm. Tell them.
So, I'm walking down
the street in New York.
- Mm-hmm.
- Beautiful day.
I'm thinking about how
lucky I am to be with Sophie,
and I look up and I happen
to be in front of a theater
playing The Princess Bride.
- Oh.
- Our favorite movie.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, so, then, that was the sign...
No, not all of it.
No, no, no. Um, across the
street, there's a church
that starts ringing its bells
and, like, two seconds later,
- a street vendor walks up selling...
- Rings.
- Bracelets, but definitely jewelry.
- Yes.
Yeah. Um, and, yeah.
In that moment, I
just realized that, um,
I couldn't wait another second
to start our lives together.
So...
And how could I say no to that?
Aw.
You want to see the wedding photos?
Yes. Please.
Of course.
I picked up the camera at a Duane Reade
on the way to the courthouse.
Uh...
- Oh, Polaroids.
- Ooh, I want to see.
We did a lot of 'em.
Oh, I'll pass them around.
- I'll get it.
- Wow.
Hey.
Hi. What are you doing here?
Well, I didn't want you to have
to go through tonight alone.
So, just got your address off
your application and I, uh,
picked your neighbor's daisies
and, uh, here I am, so...
Oh. That's so romantic.
- Yeah.
- And a little creepy.
That's me, just all together.
Hey, Bug? Who is it?
You sure you want to do this?
Bug? Oh, absolutely. Yeah.
- Okay. Come on.
- Definitely.
Everyone, um, this is
my friend from work.
- Hi.
Oh, I'm Marc.
I'm... Kate's boyfriend.
Uh... yeah.
You, uh, you and Cassidy
go to a lot of games?
She must be fun at
the hockey games, huh?
- I've never been. I hate hockey.
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Hockey sucks.
Just awful.
I'm out of here.
What do you mean? You're
not... the ceremony
hasn't even started yet.
Uncle Nicky. Hey.
- I don't feel good here, Kevin.
- Pardon me. Hey.
Where are you, where are you
gonna go? You gonna go to a bar?
No, I just need to be somewhere else.
- Well, let me go with you.
- No, alone.
I'm fine. Please.
Randall, you have to
call me back and tell me
when this present is getting here. Okay?
I'm trapped in my house
with a tiny sleeping baby
and a dog who has to pee.
There's just no way
that this grand gesture
is going to be worth it.
Call me back. Bye.
It's here? Oh, my gosh.
Okay.
Hi.
Are you my present?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Oh...
- No, I came to see the baby.
Okay.
- Very cool.
- So, your favorite band
is called Modest Mouse?
- Mm-hmm.
- Now, wait a minute, is-is that a band
or a shy cartoon character?
No, it's actually from
- a Virginia Woolf short story.
- Uh, yeah. And, um,
and so, like, the lead singer,
uh, like, he got started
by recording just, like,
these crazy experimental songs
with a distortion pedal
on his answering machine
and stuff like that, so, you know...
- Uh-huh. Very cool.
- ... it's pretty cool.
- So cool.
- Yeah.
So, what do you guys think of Marc?
Oh, he seems like he's really
into obscure music facts.
That's kind of his job. Kevin?
Uh, yeah, he's too old for you.
- Definitely too old for you.
- Uh, he's 23.
Dad was six years older than Mom.
How do you guys not like him?
Okay? He was nothing but nice to you.
- I personally don't have a problem...
- I don't know, it's just a feeling.
Like that time Grandma
wanted us to try escargot.
You know, we didn't need to try
it to know we didn't like it.
Marc is escargot.
- What do you guys think about Beth?
- She's great.
- Yeah? Cool.
- No, actually, she's perfect.
She even has a beauty mark
on her eye. Didn't know
that was a thing until
now, but it's adorable.
- Unlike Marc.
- Kate, come on.
You want me to lie? I love Marc.
- He's my new favorite.
- You... no, no. You know,
I don't even care about that, Kevin.
You got married without
telling me. Okay?
- I'm supposed to be your person.
- You know what?
- It was spontaneous.
- I'm with Kate here.
- Polaroids?
- Hey. What's going on in here?
Kate's freaking out.
No, Kev, I'm not freaking out.
I'm just, I'm not gonna sit here
and pretend that your
ridiculous marriage is real.
Man, so, who are you, again?
I don't know, Kate,
what are we supposed to do?
- Stay here and be sad all the time?
- Hey, bro, come on.
- What? We're being honest, right?
- Guys, stop.
You are so selfish!
- Enough. Enough!
- We should have been at your wedding, Kevin.
It is our first night
as a family together
in our new house, and I have spent weeks
getting this place together
so that it would be perfect.
Because this is where we move forward.
This is where we sit around a table
with napkins and placemats
and laugh and celebrate
and eat Cornish game hens.
And so help me, God, that
is what we are gonna do:
move forward.
And it doesn't matter that I
didn't have the right size pan
and that the hens are
all squished together
and they're burnt on the
top and raw on the bottom.
It doesn't even matter that
Kevin doesn't remember Emeril,
or that I have four whole
Polaroids of your wedding.
So pull yourselves together,
pretend you like burnt raw food,
get your whiny little asses
back out in those seats,
and enjoy my damn dinner.
Babe.
Oh, no, no, no. Wait
for it, wait for it.
You're a genius.
Yeah. I know.
Here. I can help.
There we go. Look how nice that is. Huh?
What's that smell?
Did you clean the oven out?
I thought that you did.
What?
- Oh, God.
- Oh. Okay.
Jack.
Oh, man.
Wow, baby.
Still looks good.
Okay?
Can we get sick from this?
So good.
Ladies and gentlemen, please stand
as we honor Bradford
County's Heroes of the Game.
Please give a round of applause
for U.S. Air Force Second
Lieutenant Alan Ellis.
And U.S. Marine Corps Staff
Sergeant Cassidy Sharp.
Yeah!
And finally, let's show our support
for U.S. Navy Chief Petty Officer
Jon Gutierrez.
Hey, can you tell
Cassidy I had to take off?
She can bring Matty home whenever.
We thank you for your
service and dedication
to our nation's freedom.
Yeah, she's been in
her room for an hour.
We got to go talk to her.
Let me see if grilled
cheese can get her to talk.
You know, she loves my grilled cheese.
_
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Growing up, I never
shared genetic traits
with anyone I knew.
And when you and I had kids,
I couldn't wait to see
what they got from me.
Would they have cute ears,
be able to roll their tongues?
Having anxiety and panic attacks
is the thing about myself
that I like the least,
and I passed it on to her.
I hate that I gave this to her.
What did the doctors say?
They want to keep him another night.
Um, see how he adjusts
to the medication.
This must have been
building for a while.
He feels things getting away from him,
and then he...
works really hard to rein 'em in.
Like more time at the
office, more time at the gym.
And then he just pushes himself
harder and further and...
I should have saw the signs.
I had a tell when I was young.
Really? You had anxiety, too?
Back then they didn't
have a name for it.
They said I was
"fragile" and "sensitive".
But when it was happening to
me, I thought I was gonna die.
My mother would help
me through it, though.
She'd fill a glass with
seltzer water and tell me
the inside of my mind was like
the bubbles bouncing around,
trying to get out.
And we'd watch together
until those bubbles settled.
Eventually, I would settle, too.
Beth, out of all the things
I could have passed down,
I hate to think that it was that.
Babe, come on, it's gonna be
perfect, it's gonna be perfect.
- All right?
- Mm.
All right? You know, I think the smoke
gave it a nice hickory flavor.
- Hickory lasagna.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, are, uh...
are you okay?
Am I trying too hard?
Are we...
are we unfixable?
Maybe this loss is just...
Too big.
You know?
Uh, you know, those...
those sound like questions
that can only be answered
by the wine that I brought.
No.
I've barely had a drink in ten years.
Well, lucky for you, over the course
of the many, many boring
dates that I've been on,
I have learned a lot about wine.
Okay, fine.
Okay. Uh, this...
is a bottle of Brunello di Montalcino.
They call it the King of Italian wines.
It's a hundred percent Sangiovese grapes
grown only around the
Tuscan town of Montalcino.
- Montalcino.
Very good. Now, the region is so small
that they can't produce
a top vintage every year.
The ripening season has to be perfect.
And there's nothing they
can do if the weather...
won't cooperate.
Maybe this year is too
hot. This year's too cold.
They, uh...
... they have to be patient.
They have to wait out the bad years...
believing that there
is a better year coming.
And it always is.
Thank you.
- Now give me that wine.
- Okay.
Thanks for the ride.
- Yeah.
- I thought we'd be...
having dinner together
afterwards as a family.
I'm so stupid.
You can't just wish a
marriage into working out.
The truth is,
I don't think there's much to save.
Forget love.
I don't even think he likes me.
Hey. Come with me.
Mom, I don't want
- to talk about...
- Come on.
Hey.
- Hmm?
- I need you downstairs.
- Can it wait for just a s... ?
- Nope.
You two don't like this
thing you have in common.
And I get that.
It's scary.
But it also made three
of my most favorite people
in the world who they are.
William would also get
anxious about things.
He was...
sensitive and artistic and caring.
But there's a fine line
between caring and worrying,
and sometimes that line gets blurry.
From the moment I met your father,
he was obsessed with
making everything okay
for everybody else.
And that took some getting used to,
but I loved him for it.
'Cause it meant he cared deeply.
Now, there's some things
you get from your dad
that you're gonna have
to navigate around,
but there are some gifts, too.
You give everything your all.
You're an amazing sister
and daughter and friend and student.
Now, look, we're gonna
get whatever this is
under control, okay? Believe that.
But I will not have you talking ill
about three of my most
favorite people in the world.
No way, no how.
Are you hearing me?
And if it ever gets to be too much...
Mm-mm.
Just take a minute...
... and wait for the bubbles to settle.
William.
Um...
last week Ashley wanted to know
if I thought DeShaun was hot.
I should have just come out then,
like I'd planned to,
but...
instead, I said yes.
And now it's gonna be a whole thing.
That's a lot.
But we can figure it out.
Thanks.
So, the night your father
and I moved into our house,
I made a fancy dinner, too.
And, of course, I ended
up burning the lasagna.
So we had to open the window
to let all the smoke out of the kitchen.
And just as we were sitting down to eat,
a bird flies in through the window.
Oh.
- Okay.
- Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Now, the important detail
of this story is that your dad was
- terrified of birds, terrified.
- Terrified. Yeah, he was.
So...
he runs out of the room...
- Hey, Jack?
- and he runs back in
with a tennis racket
and a pillow case, and he goes...
Don't worry, I'll catch it.
He must have
freaked the bird out, because
then the bird starts...
diving at him and chasing
him around the room.
And your father made the
most ridiculous squealing sound
I've ever heard.
So he's trying to get away from the bird
and protect me, I guess,
with the tennis racket...
- Wait, where did it go? Where did it go?
- Right there. Look, look, look.
Jack...
And somehow we knock over the lasagna.
Bec?
And we just started laughing.
And that's when it
became the perfect night.
When we just let it be what it was.
We need to be able to think
about him and not only be sad.
We need to be able to
talk about the hot sauce.
Right?
He was perfect the way
that dinner was perfect.
He made us... so happy.
And that's all I want for you guys,
is just for you to be happy.
Then, let's have a toast.
- Please.
- To happiness.
Oh, and to Kevin and Sophie.
Yes.
- Congratulations.
To Kevin and Sophie, cheers to that.
Salud.
All right, this meal was
disgusting. I admit it.
- Who's still hungry?
- Me.
Me, too. I am tru...
You can keep the change.
Thank you.
Pizza...
- I'll get his, uh, stuff.
- Thank you.
You got it.
- Hey.
Here you go.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
You know, your wife was, uh,
she was being honored tonight
for her service at that hockey game.
Man, she was excited when she
found out you were showing up.
If you were gonna stand there
and stare at your phone all day,
why'd you bother coming?
Okay.
That's good stuff, man.
I met her when I was 15.
I smashed into her in the hallway
As I was walking into biology class.
And I knew,
I knew before her books
even hit the floor,
I had just met my favorite person.
That, uh, that ceremony
that you're talking about
honored the thing that broke
my favorite person in the world.
I was staring at my
phone because otherwise
I would have started openly
weeping in front of my son,
and that's not what he
needs from me right now.
I'm sorry, man. I-I... I didn't know.
Stay the hell away from my wife.
He's out. I'll be back
for him on Thursday.
Yeah.
What?
He still likes you.
It's all right. I'm sober.
Okay.
I'm not a storyteller.
And I don't like people.
I-I don't even like
you very much, and, uh,
you're the closest person I've
been to in the last 20 years.
You know, your father wasn't the, uh,
first person to do this.
Uh, he learned that
trick from his father,
uh, your grandfather.
That man was a bastard,
but every now and then...
he could be kind of fun.
Yeah. What he'd do was...
... he would fold down
the sides of the carton...
hmm... so that it looked
like a, like a big cake.
And then he'd then get a knife
and just wave it over the ice cream.
And he'd, he'd ask, uh,
"How-how good a boy were you today?
Were you kind of good?
Or were you real good?"
And depending on the answer,
that was how big a slice you got.
So...
How good were you today, Kevin?
Um...
I think I annoyed my uncle today.
Other than that, I think I
was pretty good.
Well, then, you get
a pretty good slice of ice cream.
I've been very good.
Uh, I need to give you your wedding gift.
- I hope it's an air popper.
- Oh. I-I hope it's cash.
- Kevin.
- Excuse me.
- Oh.
- No, it is a song.
For the newlyweds.
From a little movie called
The Princess Bride.
- Ooh.
- Mm-hmm.
♪ Come, my love, I'll tell you a tale ♪
♪ Of a boy and girl ♪
♪ And their love story ♪
♪ And how he loved her ♪
♪ Oh, so much ♪
♪ And all the charms she did possess ♪
♪ Now, this did happen... ♪
- Just... careful.
- Is that our old piano?
♪ Things were not so complex... ♪
The Pearson men nail
another grand gesture.
♪ She walked ♪
♪ When he looked in her eyes ♪
♪ He became obsessed ♪
- ♪ My love is like a storybook story... ♪
- That's middle C.
Yeah, that's your home base.
You know where that
is, you can go anywhere.
Yeah.
♪ My love is like ♪
♪ A storybook story ♪
♪ It's as real as the feelings I feel ♪
♪ It's as real as the feelings ♪
♪ I feel... ♪
- I found a therapist for Tess.
- Good.
I think that'll be
really helpful for her.
And... I found one for you, too.
I don't need a therapist.
I'm good. Best I've been in years.
But you've been working crazy hours
and running ten miles a day and
constantly bouncing that knee.
You know, you don't have to wait
for it all to come
crashing down to get help.
Glad to know you think I'm gonna crash.
You know, when you had
your first breakdown,
you thought that was
gonna be the only one.
All these years of just managing
it and making lists, babe...
We have resources now
and people who are trained
to deal with this kind of stuff.
I appreciate your concern.
- But I'm fine.
- Okay, I am worried
that we are just one big
emotional thing from this...
Beth, I'm fine.
♪ My love is like a storybook story ♪
♪ But it's as real
as the feelings I feel ♪
♪ My love is like a storybook story ♪
♪ It's as real as the feelings I feel ♪
♪ It's as real as
the feelings I feel... ♪
What's wrong, Bug?
What?
I was trying so hard to hold it together
that year after your father died.
And I wanted to believe so
badly that you kids were happy.
I'm so sorry I didn't
see what was happening.
I didn't see it, either.