Previously on This Is Us...
I didn't need you to come.
I'm your brother's son.
And I have come here for you.
You want to go to jail?
Because that's what
your future holds if you don't
start taking this seriously.
How do I know you?
Oh, you were on a television show.
Jack can't see, but...
my son is gonna live
a life without limits.
Okay, look, Randall,
you're a very nice guy,
but please don't call me again.
I'm gonna marry her.
Huh. Check out these babies.
Goodbye, stakes. Hello, flying fatality.
- What can I shoot?
- Oh, nothing.
Are you sure you don't
want to go with me
to visit Randall at college?
... the basic tools of combat...
Mom, it's Parents' Weekend,
not Parent and Loser Sister Weekend.
Well, what are you gonna do today?
I don't know.
Maybe sit around and
listen to our one CD.
You know what?
I have an idea.
Why don't you...
... go to the record store in the mall
and buy some new albums?
- Hey, Kate?
- Hmm?
Promise me you're not just
gonna sit around all day, okay?
Please?
Okay.
That was a good walk, wasn't it, Jack?
Are you excited for
your music class today?
- Huh?
- So with everything
that kid's been through,
his first big outing,
and you're taking him to the Valley?
Yeah. Miss Mindy's Music Makers
is the best baby music class in L.A.
I mean, there's a wait list.
How about I give the
kid a pot and a pan to bang on,
and you pay me 40 bucks
an hour instead, huh? Yeah?
- Huh?
- Hey, Gregory.
- Hey, man.
- Hey, listen.
You know, he's so tiny here.
You sure it's not too early to
be taking him to music class?
Yes, it is.
Sorry. I'm slow.
- Thanks.
- The website said
for newborns and up. Plus, you know,
music is good for his development.
- That's what everybody says.
- Okay, but...
- I-I was just, you know...
- Tobe,
this is something that Jack
can do like every other kid.
He's gonna be tapping on
the drum, hitting the cymbal.
It's gonna be like a
little baby symphony.
Okay, then. We shall
go, and he shall jam.
All right. Come on, buddy.
Do we have everything?
Just want to get there early
so he's comfortable with the space.
Yeah, I've got extra diapers and wipes,
both pacifiers, two changes of clothes,
a UV blanket, a stylish
hat, a practical hat,
a cooler full of backup milk.
- How did the cavemen do this?
- Oh, did you get Monkey?
Monkey! Yeah. No, I didn't.
We never go anywhere without Monkey.
I'll be right back.
Monkey?!
Hey, you about ready?
Ready for this AA meeting, huh?
Ready to go? It starts in 15 minutes.
Rather not get kicked out
of this group, too. You know,
they got almond milk over
there, which I'm excited about.
Not easy to come by out here.
Not ready. Haven't had coffee yet.
Your roof's leaking again, huh?
Yeah.
Man, you sure you don't want
to just come stay with me at the hotel?
Very.
Well, I'll tell you
what. Why don't you...
why don't you at least let
me buy you a new trailer?
All right? Brand-new trailer.
I got all this Hollywood
douchebag money to throw around.
I could put it toward a good cause.
I'm not a cause. And no.
Right.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Uh...
"Gee, Kevin, what is it?
I'd like to know, too. I'm concerned.
Can I help you in any way?"
They canceled The Manny.
That show was still on?
Yeah, it's still on.
They-they replaced me
with Morris Chestnut after I left.
I can't believe it's finally over.
I... shot that pilot, like, uh...
eight years ago.
Kev, this is really happening.
Yeah.
You are the star of a
huge network TV show.
It's just a pilot, you know?
Who knows if it'll actually be on TV.
What's going on? Are you freaking out?
Uh, maybe, you know,
a little bit, you know?
- It just, it just sort of feels like...
- Mr. Pearson?
- Yes. Okay.
- They're ready for you.
They're ready for me.
Mr. Pearson.
I never saw the show.
Saw a commercial once, though.
You were drinking out
of a baby's bottle,
and you weren't wearing a shirt.
Come on, Hollywood douchebag.
I know I'm forgetting something.
- Check your list.
- Okay.
What if I forgot to put
something on the list?
What if nobody shows up?
- Okay, what if when we get there...
- Wife of mine,
- apple of my eye...
- Get to the meat, baby.
- Get to the...
- You have been prepping
for the opening of your dance studio...
your very own dance studio,
what? For three months.
There's gonna be delicious food.
- There's gonna be dancing.
- Mm-hmm.
You are Footloose in Philadelphia.
Mwah.
Okay, well done.
- My meat is always well done.
- Don't ruin it.
Might your, um, stress level have to do
with a certain regal,
yet intimidating individual
who will be in attendance?
I am happy my mom is coming.
I really am.
But you know she always
thought this was a crazy idea.
- Yeah.
- And she's just so judgy.
Oh, she is Supreme Court-level judgy.
Look, you just focus on your opening.
I'll take care of your mom.
I'll be your firewall.
You handle my mom?
- I will.
- Okay.
Yeah, historically, she's
been a scootch tough on me.
Hasn't necessarily been
my biggest fan since, uh...
well, since we met, but
does any of that phase me?
Not today, Carol. Not today.
Um, can I go to the movies tonight
after the opening with some friends?
What friends?
New friends.
Might one of these new friends
happen to be a gentleman friend
that your mom saw you all... mmm?
Okay. Malik is a friend, and he's a boy,
and he invited me,
but it's a group thing.
- Okay.
- We need to meet him first.
We have to meet him first.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Your sister
has me worried because she
barely leaves the house.
Kevin likes New York. He
just hasn't figured out
the whole subway system yet.
And I...
need to think about getting a job, too.
I'm thinking about
becoming an astronaut.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Hi, Mama C!
- Hi, Mama C!
- Hi.
- Mm. Mm.
- Hi, Mama C.
Hi.
Mama C.
Hello, Randall.
That's a nice shirt.
Thank you.
- It's a big day.
- Big day.
We are so, so happy you are here.
Is that the space?
- Yeah, this is it.
- Oh, very nice.
Well, looks like you'll have
more than enough parking.
Hold on. Hey.
- Your hip.
- My hip what?
Uh, I got it, ma'am.
Thank you, Deja.
All right, follow me.
We are so happy you are here.
Beth's been working really hard,
and, uh, I think we have to remember
how much pressure she's under, you know,
and to take great care not
to... exacerbate said pressure.
You're trying to tell me
how to speak to my daughter?
No, ma'am. No. I-I... Mm, mm, mm.
All right, so here we are.
It's not huge, but, uh,
you know, we've been
working really hard, and...
Okay.
- What?
- Oh, my God, that smell.
What is that?
I can't breathe.
I'm, like, tasting it.
But the website said that the
AA meeting was at 10:00 a.m.
I know. We haven't
updated that website since,
- gosh, at least last winter.
- You can't do that. You can't
say that there's a meeting,
and then, there isn't a meeting.
- That's... deception.
- What's going on?
The meeting isn't till
3:00 p.m., and she's saying
that the website hasn't
been updated since...
What's happening to her face?
- I know you!
- Hi.
- You're the Manny.
- How you doing?
Kevin Pearson. It's
really good to meet you.
Oh, excuse me one second.
- Hey. Hey, you okay?
- I had breakfast
with my husband this morning,
and he says he thinks
we should proceed with the divorce.
I'm sorry. What'd you say?
I said nothing.
I put down my five bucks for my eggs,
and I left, so I need a meeting now.
We got, like, five hours
until the meeting starts.
What you need is to stay occupied, okay?
Um, you know what? Come on, both of you.
Where are we going?
I'm an actor, right?
I'm great at filling
up free time. Let's go.
Come on. It'll be fun.
Come on.
Road trip.
♪ A, B, C, D, E, F, G ♪
♪ H... ♪
Hi. Sorry we're late.
Monkey business.
Uh, I'm Kate, this is my husband Toby.
- Hi.
- And this is Jack.
Welcome! We haven't even started yet.
Yeah. Come on.
We're gonna sit down.
- All right.
- Gonna sit down.
We're gonna sit down.
♪ Hello, Jack ♪
♪ Welcome to class... ♪
- Oh, he's just surprised, um...
- Yeah.
- It's okay.
- He's blind,
- so...
- Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't realize.
We should have given
you a heads-up. Sorry.
- Just grab a drum set and play along.
- Okay.
Good morning, friends!
Good morning!
We have a new musician joining us today.
Let's everyone give a
musical hello to Jack!
♪ The itsy bitsy spider
went up the water spout ♪
♪ Down came the rain
and washed the spider out ♪
♪ Out came the sun ♪
- ♪ And dried up all the... ♪
- Yeah, this is a drum.
♪ Rows and rows of houses ♪
♪ With windows painted blue ♪
You guys are out of Nevermind.
You don't already own Nevermind?
Oh, come on. Who doesn't own Nevermind?
Someone whose house burned down.
♪ Running parallel to you ♪
Uh,
Neil Diamond?
Oh.
I know.
My dad loved him.
Mm-hmm.
♪ Rumored to be ♪
He died last winter.
Oh.
He had a very
questionable musical taste,
okay, but...
he was, like, my favorite person.
Him and my mom actually
danced to "Sweet Caroline"
at their wedding, I think.
So cheesy.
Well, I don't know.
I think, uh,
wedding songs are the one time
people are just actively
allowed to be cheesy,
- I think.
- Mm.
How long were they married for?
22 years.
Wow.
That is a long time to love somebody.
Yeah.
♪ With you ♪
I think I like Death Cab for Cutie.
But I have no idea what Ben
Gibbard is talking about.
Yeah.
But I also think that's why I like him?
I don't know. Maybe his songs are less
about the lyrics and more about, like,
the feeling of the lyrics?
♪ I'd try to fold it over ♪
Hey, you know, you're
getting a lot of stuff.
And, uh...
an employee discount would
really save you a lot of money.
Are you offering me
your employee discount?
No. No, no, no.
Um, I mean, I'm offering you a job.
♪ Roll over... ♪
What do you think about this
one right here, Uncle Nicky?
This is nice. It says
a 65-inch television.
Right? It's got a queen-size bed,
heated bathroom floors
and it sleeps up to...
How many more of these
do we have to look at
- before you give up?
- Oh, come on, man.
We've got three more hours to kill.
At least let's see if we
can get a good deal. Right?
Cassidy, you were a military
intelligence officer, right?
You're probably great at negotiating.
Yeah, that's exactly what
the military teaches you,
how to negotiate with an RV salesman.
Hey, you negotiate all you want.
I'm gonna... get out of the sun.
Hi. Can I help you?
- Hey.
- Oh, my goodness. The Manny.
What are you doing there? I mean, here?
You're beautiful!
Oh, thank you. We're just...
We're checking out some of your
beautiful RVs here, actually.
You think you could hook
us up with a discount?
Are you kidding?
Of course.
Come on.
Jesus, you're tall.
My wife and I loved you on that show.
That final scene in the first episode.
You and the baby?
We cried.
That's what everyone says.
Okay! Here we go!
Final bell! Last scene.
Well, don't you want your...
Come on, don't you want
your milk? It's good.
It tastes good. I should know.
I accidentally put some
in my coffee this morning.
Cut!
That's a cut!
Kev,
you're killing it out there.
The pilot's no good.
- Wait, what?
- No one's laughing.
I can't tell if it's because
they can't hear me
because the baby won't stop crying
or maybe the jokes
aren't funny, you know?
- Or maybe I'm not funny.
- You are very funny.
Well, maybe. Maybe I'm
funny for a hot person,
- not actually funny, you know?
- No. You are funny.
I have waited ten years for this, okay?
And now the pilot's no good.
It's probably not gonna get picked up,
which really doesn't
matter because the baby
will probably never stop crying anyway.
Okay, well, that I can't help you with,
'cause I'm so not a baby person.
That was terrible, Tobe.
Yeah, I guess we should've
e-mailed them ahead of time,
let them know about Jack.
Their website said
babies with all abilities.
But we also can't ignore the
fact that he's blind, all right?
There was too much stimulus
there. We overloaded him.
I mean, can you imagine
what it would be like
if a cymbal crashed in
your face out of nowhere?
Yeah. That's why I wanted
to get there early...
so he could adjust to the environment.
Instead, we're spending 20
minutes looking for Monkey.
Okay! I had Monkey, I went to get milk,
and I left Monkey in the refrigerator.
It happens.
- To who?
- To me!
Why didn't you just pack Monkey first?
- He needs Monkey to function.
- No, no, no, no.
He would've... he would've been
just fine with Other Monkey.
No. No, he wouldn't.
He turned on Other Monkey.
That would've made it worse, but...
you don't know that because
you've been spending
all your time at the gym, so...
Nice.
Wow.
Okay. All right, don't go home.
When he's all worked up like this,
it's the only thing that
calms him, is to be in the car.
Okay. Well, where do
you want me to drive?
Till the road ends. Follow
the yellow brick road.
Toby, I don't care.
Randall, you've looked over
there about a hundred times.
I'm guessing that's Beth,
that girl you went on a date with.
What?
Uh...
- Yeah.
Okay. All right.
We're doing this.
- No.
- Yeah.
- Mom, Mom, no, no, no, no.
- Come on, it's okay. Let's go. Follow me.
Hi.
Sorry. Excuse me.
I'm-I'm Rebecca Pearson.
This is my son, Randall.
Oh. Rebecca, Randall, I'm Carol Clarke,
- and this is my daughter, Bethany.
- Yeah,
I-I think Beth and Randall
already know each other.
Do you mind if we sit,
- join you for a minute?
- I actually have
to get to class. Five...
Please sit down.
Thank you.
So,
how do you two know each other?
- Uh, econ class.
- We went on a date.
Econ class.
And what's your major?
Uh, maybe econ.
Or poli-sci.
Or potentially math,
although multivariable calculus
is kicking my butt right now.
The z-axis is...
ooh... throwing me for a loop.
I should, uh, really get to class.
Yeah, me, too.
Yeah, we can walk together.
I have class in the same building.
Um, okay.
Uh, well, Mom,
maybe you can go for a walk in the park
or I could give you the keys to my dorm.
Or I could just sit here and
chat, if Rebecca wants to stay.
- Oh, that won't be necessary.
- Oh, that would be lovely.
Yeah.
Have a good class, guys.
I had to guess, it's a dead possum.
Could be a dead rat or
a family of dead rats.
A family?
Ronny, uh, I know it's a Saturday.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
- You probably have other appointments...
- We have 30 minutes
before people start showing up,
and we can't have an opening
with this horrible smell.
Can you get rid of it?
I'll try.
Be tricky if it's a dead family.
Please stop saying that.
You got the keys to the crawl space?
Come on. I'll show you.
I'll come with you.
Oh, actually, Carol...
I mean, Mama C, maybe you should...
- What's that smell?
- Uh, air freshener
and dead animal thing.
Look, uh, Randall,
he's-he's a really nice guy,
- but sometimes our jokes are...
- Hey, hey, hey.
It's all good.
Okay.
Mr. Pearson!
Hey.
Uh, Randall, this is Malik.
Malik, this is my dad, Randall.
- Randall, please don't do anything weird.
- The famous Malik!
My man.
How's, uh...
- Ni-Nice to meet you, sir.
- Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to... nice to...
Got you.
So, uh...
what-what grade are you in, Malik?
Oh, I-I'm a junior. I'm a junior.
Um, but-but Deja's in my math class,
'cause she's, uh... 'cause
she's kind of a genius,
so...
Shut up.
- Yeah, we're in agreement on that one.
- Yeah.
You live nearby?
Not too far. Not too far.
My-my dad, he owns a
body shop over on 29th.
And, uh, Mom's a manager
down at the Marriott, so...
Ah, the Marriott!
- Yeah.
- I'm a rewards member.
- Yeah?
- Yes, sir.
Okay. Okay, yeah. I'm sure
my folks would love to meet you.
You know, after Deja
told me who you were,
I read up on you, and... I-I really love
the work you're doing
down at the rec center.
Really important stuff. Really.
All right, listen, man.
I'm gonna level with you, Malik.
We're new to town and
Deja's making new friends,
including a boy who is
two grades older than her,
and it's all a bit overwhelming
for my wife and me.
But, um...
but it means a lot that
you came down to say hi.
And I like the firm handshake
and the way you looked me
in the eye and the fact that I feel
confident that I could
physically squash you like a bug
if I needed to.
Do you feel me?
Yeah.
Yeah. No, no, no, man.
No, I get it. Really.
Man, when my daughter gets old enough,
I plan on installing a
tracking device on her.
So...
- Right. Right. Yeah.
- No, really. Like, my daughter,
she created this little
flirty smile the other day.
Gave it to the mailman.
Yo, I was freaking out.
Uh...
I'm sorry, when you say "my daughter",
what do you mean by those words?
I thought...
I just assumed she told you.
Mr. Pearson, I have a daughter.
Six months old.
Janelle. Janelle.
I have full custody, and
my-my parents help out
with her sometimes.
He thinks it's just one
dead possum, baby, not a dead family.
You know the dude's wasting your time.
He's just in there
calling everyone he knows
and saying that the
Manny is in his office.
It's all right.
My uncle's probably not gonna let me
buy him one of these things anyway.
But what about you?
I mean, I know you really needed
that meeting this morning, huh?
Tell you what, I feel like I
needed a meeting this morning
after finding out that
my show got canceled.
Don't try to relate to me.
Talking about a television
show... a television show
you're not even on
anymore getting canceled.
My marriage is getting canceled.
Can't imagine why, you're
so pleasant to be around.
No. Wait. You know what? No.
Here's the thing. Maybe
I didn't fight in a war
but I'm allowed to have a crappy day
just like everyone else, okay?
Something that was really
important to me ended.
And, yeah, I know it
was a little goofy, okay?
But it was a big part of my life,
and when big things end,
it's hard not to imagine
how they started, so, please,
if you could just ease
up for maybe two seconds.
Oh, my God, it is you.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry.
My husband works here and
he texted me at the gym,
and I just... you know.
My God, can-can I have a hug?
Well, yes, of cour...
Oh, you're coming in. All right.
Hey.
There you go.
What's your name?
- Gina.
My husband and I, we just
loved you on that show.
- Thank you.
- You were wonderful.
Thank you.
Would it be okay to get a selfie?
Well, yes, of course. Yeah, no.
I was actually, I was just
gonna ask you if I could get one.
This is gonna work out great.
- There you go. Oh.
- Uh-oh.
- My hand's a little...
- You know what? Check this out.
Watch this. Here we go, Gina.
I got long arms, right?
And...
You tell me if you
think that looks good.
I think you look gorgeous in that.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah. You like it?
I love it.
Oh, thank you so much.
You're welcome.
- Oh...
- Ooh, watch your back there, Gina. All right.
- Thank you.
- Good to meet you, Gina.
Good to meet you.
You have a weird life.
Don't we all?
I've been a dick.
Yeah, well, you know, it's...
I-I haven't fought in a war, but
I have been through a divorce.
You know? And I'm not
trying to relate to you,
it's just...
it's a fact.
It really sucks.
We got engaged in Spain.
I'd just finished my first tour,
fixing helicopters overseas, and...
I knew-I knew he was gonna propose,
'cause he insisted on meeting me there
when my ship came into port at Rota.
And I saw his phone
when his bonehead buddy
Triconi texted him saying,
"Did you put that ring on it yet?"
And he knew. He saw that I saw it,
but we both pretended like I didn't.
So... I got a manicure.
And then for four days,
he just messed with me.
You know, he'd point out, like,
these old couples and be like,
"Oh, God. I want to
be like them someday.
They're so cute and in love."
And he'd get real serious
again and be like...
"Do you want to get a beer?"
He did this for four days.
He messed with me for four days.
- But eventually... Yeah.
- He did it.
You know, on a bridge
where his grandparents met,
yada yada. Nailed it.
I just can't picture you in a manicure.
I know, right?
Yeah.
Uh, it was the first and last.
So now we're just living
in this little rental condo
until I can figure out what to do.
My God. You lost your
husband and your home.
I cannot imagine.
And Randall was supposed
to go to Howard University,
but he decided to stay closer to home.
He's had a tough year.
We've all had a tough year.
Oh, I understand.
I lost my husband last year.
What?
I had no idea.
I was just blabbing on.
I am so sorry.
H-How is your family coping?
Well, they are a tough bunch.
Although, Bethany was Daddy's girl.
They were inseparable.
Are we supposed to take
off our wedding rings?
No, ma'am.
I'm not taking off mine.
Yeah, I'm not either. I don't want to.
No, no, no. Not unless Harry
Belafonte comes knocking.
How do you seem so together?
'Cause I just feel like
at a moment's notice
I-I could completely break.
Well, I've got a job that I love.
Mm.
A classroom full of wonderful students
who are counting on
me showing up every day
to make them love books.
My husband loved books.
You know, we used to read in bed.
Although, usually, he
would only get a page in
before he was snoring.
And I would lie there for hours reading,
listening to him snore.
It was about a couple
of months ago I realized
that I haven't read a book
before bed since he passed
and I wondered how he would...
well, what he would think.
What he would think about me
if he knew I'd stopped reading.
So I picked up a book
and started a new chapter
in every sense of the phrase.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, hell no. She's 14.
She is not seeing a boy
who puts babies in people.
We are in lockstep.
Okay, so we have taped up
the dryer sheets to the vent
and that is helping with the smell.
S-Sort of... What's wrong?
It's nothing to be
concerned about, just...
- Deja likes a boy who has a baby.
- It's that.
But we're gonna put
an end to it tonight,
so don't worry about it now, okay?
Everything is gonna be just fine.
So there's no way to
get rid of the carcass
without opening up the entire wall.
You just gotta let it decompose.
The smell will fade away
in about a week or two.
- A week or two?
- Sorry.
They're actually wonderful animals.
They're kinda cute, too.
This is an unmitigated disaster.
Mm, no. We-we will figure it out.
Who the hell's gonna want to sign up
for dance classes in a rat cemetery?
- It's a possum cemete... it's not the time.
- Oh, this some...
And I know what you're
probably thinking, Mom,
that this is some stupid pipe dream
that I'm so not
equipped to handle, so...
What are you talking about?
This isn't anyone's fault.
- You just have to reschedule.
- Mm-mm. We're not rescheduling.
Randall.
You can't have people coming...
Okay, this is what we're going to do.
You're going to tell
people you are very sorry.
You're going to ask them
to come next Saturday.
You will double down on promotions.
- It's a shame.
- Don't tell me what I can
and can't do, Carol.
This is important to my
wife and I'm gonna fix it.
So we're not rescheduling. Am I clear?
And I apologize for
speaking to you in that tone.
But the content... holds.
I am not loving this
B-minus in poli-sci, Bethany.
Was that awkward, having
lunch with his mom?
No.
She was lovely.
What's the story with him?
We went on a date.
But it's probably not gonna work out.
It's probably for the best.
What does that mean?
He's nice.
Very nice.
And grieving; his whole family is.
There are only two ways to
deal with a loss like that.
You hold your head up
high and move forward,
like we have, or you fold inwards.
Randall and his family
are still very broken.
You don't need broken
right now, Bethany.
You need strength.
You deserve it.
You deserve someone who sees you.
Stop.
He's still out.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I just...
I just want him to be
able to do everything
that all the other kids do.
He can.
He will. He just...
he has to take it one sound at a time.
That's all.
One step at a time.
Baby steps.
Let's go to the beach.
Hey, everybody!
I just wanted to thank you
for your patience in dealing
with our little switcheroo.
- Yay!
- Thank you.
I'm gonna do a short demo for you all.
And then I'm gonna invite you up
and I'm gonna teach you, right?
All right. Hit it, baby.
Oh, it's very nice
putting this together.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry...
for the way I spoke to you.
You've always seemed to
have a problem with me.
You haven't liked me
since the day you met me.
Randall, I have always liked you.
True, I didn't want you
to go out with Bethany
because I didn't think
you were right for her.
And I was wrong.
When I met you...
... I didn't see the strong partner,
father and man you would become.
You know, Uncle Nicky, I am so sorry
for pushing that trailer on you.
I mean, I thought it
was pretty cool, but...
different strokes.
Your trailer has a certain...
... rustic charm to it.
It was originally for someone else.
The trailer.
Uh...
Sally.
We, uh, started dating
before I got drafted.
I was too chicken to ask her out,
so Jack did it for me.
We wrote letters during the war.
We were gonna drive across
country when I got back,
but after a while,
I-I just stopped writing.
And I, uh...
I got back, I was in
Walter Reed, and, uh...
I lost Jack.
And I lost my family, and...
I was pretty broken.
But I decided
I was gonna go for it.
One shot at a life.
And so I got the, uh...
'68 Boles Aero.
Practically took up all my savings.
And I... and I hitched it to my car,
and I drove to Sally's house.
I didn't tell her I was coming.
I just drove.
But she wasn't home.
Then what happened?
That was it.
I realized...
it wasn't meant to be.
I drove off.
You didn't wait?
I mean, maybe...
maybe she comes back in 20 minutes,
and-and, you know, you'd
have a whole nother life, man.
I just knew.
You know? It...
was one of those moments.
Almost ready to shoot the final scene.
Just waiting on the baby to calm down.
- Yeah.
- Again.
I'm so not having kids.
You know, look, I mean, maybe, uh...
maybe it's good if
this pilot doesn't go.
You know, maybe I don't
even want it to go.
Okay, don't spiral.
I'm not. Hey, listen,
I-I've been in L.A. for
what, like, ten years now?
I'm not even sure if I like it.
Yeah, and-and you know
what? I don't even know
If I really like doing this.
This what?
Acting.
Kev, this is what you've always wanted.
Is it, though?
I started acting
when Dad died because I
needed something to do.
And now I'm so close to it,
and I'm not sure if it's
actually what I want, you know?
I mean, what would you
do? Where would you go?
Someplace simpler, you know?
I-I would... I would...
Small town somewhere.
I don't know. Find a good woman.
Have a couple of kids.
Okay. Don't think about it.
We're just gonna flip a coin.
Do you want the pilot to go or not?
- I don't.
- Mr. Pearson?
We're ready for you.
You want your husband back?
What?
You want your husband back? Just...
- I'm not sure that's an option.
- Don't think about it.
Just flip a coin. Do
you want him back or not?
Yes.
Well, then, we should get him back.
That's very presumptuous of you. "We"?
"We". Yeah. I'm a very
presumptuous person.
You know that, right?
Hey.
I know that...
the show was a big chapter in your life,
and I'm sure that it
getting canceled was...
Yeah, sorry. No, I can't
do it. I can't care.
- Well, you did a little bit.
- Nah.
- Eh. Felt like it. Just a smidge.
- I don't. No.
- Hello?
- Hey.
I picked up a few things
for you at Jerry's.
Bug, thank you.
Carole King.
Oh, I didn't even know you
knew who Carole King was.
♪ I feel the earth move ♪
♪ Under my feet ♪
♪ I feel the sky tumbling down ♪
I missed this.
♪ I feel my heart start to trembling ♪
♪ Whenever you're around ♪
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
♪ When I see your face ♪
- ♪ Mellow as the month of May ♪
- I got a job today.
At the record store.
I'm sorry, what?
- You did? Bug! Congratulations.
- Mm-hmm.
That is... that is the
perfect job for you.
- Wow.
- Thanks.
I'm so proud of you.
♪ I feel the sky tumbling down ♪
- Okay, Mom. All right.
- What?
Dance with me.
Dance with you?
- Dance with me.
- Dance with you?
How do you want to dance to that?
♪ Ooh, darling ♪
♪ When you're near me ♪
♪ And you tenderly call my name ♪
♪ I know that ♪
Oh, Kate.
I think it's time we got
out of this place, you know?
Get into a home.
A place that has more light.
Start a new chapter.
Yeah?
Yeah.
♪ Under my feet. ♪
All right, I'll give.
What is this final scene of The Manny
everyone's asking you about?
Oh, well, well, well,
look who's all of a sudden
interested in The Manny.
Oh, okay. Never mind.
Okay, if-if you must know,
it was, uh... it was the last scene
of this terrible pilot, right?
And the baby just...
it won't stop crying.
So I'm bouncing the baby,
I'm making faces at the baby.
Okay, c-can we get a different baby?
You know, d-don't
cut. Please, don't cut.
Let me just, uh, let me
try something here, okay?
Be my guest.
What is that? Huh? What is that?
Huh? What is that? Huh?
And all of a sudden,
he just calmed down.
So they kept the cameras rolling, right?
And this angry baby and I just...
We connected.
And suddenly, the-the stupid Manny,
this stupid character
on this stupid show
with a stupid premise,
- became a real person.
- Peekaboo!
Hey, you did it.
Hey, that may work. We go with sweet
- instead of funny.
- Yeah.
He wasn't a joke anymore.
Oh, plus, they played this
really awesome Pink ballad
- underneath. Oh, yeah.
- Love Pink.
So acrobatic.
I've been thinking
about that day all day.
I didn't know what I wanted.
I made a baby laugh, and...
my life changed.
It's overwhelming if you think about it,
the power of these little decisions.
Hey.
Um...
Why'd you give me that lemon?
What?
Today at lunch,
you, um, passed me a lemon.
You didn't even say anything.
Oh, um...
When we were on our date,
you ordered a Coke with lemon.
And at lunch, you had a Coke, so...
You noticed that?
Beth, if you knew how much
I've noticed about you...
Do you hear that, Jack?
The world is making music for you.
Do you hear the waves?
The wind?
Can you hear the seagulls?
Do you hear that? Water!
Ooh!
Howdy, neighbor.
I told you, I don't want a new trailer.
Oh, I heard all that. It's
not for you. It's for me.
I was sick of staying
at the hotel, anyway.
Such an amazing view.
Did you see?
We have a message.
Hey, Mom, it's Kevin.
Uh, thanks for the brownies you sent.
I'm good. It's-it's raining a lot.
Uh, I actually might have
an audition next week
- for a SunnyD commercial.
- Hmm.
Oh, and I got married. Uh, to Sophie.
Yeah, got married to Sophie.
Um, can you send me some money?