- You guys ready for a good day?
- Ready!
In southeast Alaska’s
remote wilderness,
Mckinley creek...
Alright, he's going in.
- Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
Halfway through a season.
Shortened by
the covid pandemic...
- Can you see anything at all?
- Yeah, I can see fine.
Dustin and his crew.
Are pulling up thousands
of dollars of nuggets.
The old-timers
could never access.
Holy crap!
What the hell, Dustin?
Yeah, yeah, you're welcome.
This boulder's heavy.
The more boulders
that's coming out of there.
Means good things.
More boulders, more gold.
That's funny how that works.
I like it.
Last week, the crew
cleaned up 14.2 ounces...
- Whoa!
- This place is a mess down here.
I got plenty of work to do.
More gold than they've ever had.
At this point of the season.
What the.
Well, I'll be damned.
There's a granite boulder rock
down here.
17 around.
- Really?
- Yeah.
A rock this size
can weigh over 10,000 pounds.
We have to find a different way
to deal with that.
I'm not sure our skyline
will handle a rock that big.
- The colossal boulder.
- The Jurassic boulder.
You guys and your names.
- Hippo rock.
- Hippo?
- I like that.
- That's a perfect name.
That thing is like a
hippo, and it wants to kill you.
You know what I mean?
So it's not one of those.
Purple hippos that, like,
Frickin' sing and dance
kind of deal.
It's a purple hippo
that wants to kill you.
Aaaah!
What the are you doing?
Stupid-ass rock.
Aaah! Not gonna work.
I think I'm done, dude.
Copy that.
I got you. I got you. Okay.
I don't know what to do
because that's bigger.
Than any boulder
we've ever moved ever.
Not only are we way behind,
We need to be hustling
to get things done.
Figure out where
that gold is hiding.
Losers talk about their best.
Winners just do it.
Just do it.
Into the abyss.
This current's kicking my ass.
- We're doing something different.
- We've never done this before.
So no mistakes.
Got a lot riding on this.
Three, two, one!
What do you got?
That's gold.
We're about to have
a big payday.
Holy crap!
That's the pocket! Whoo!
Everywhere.
I'll remember today
for the rest of my life.
Captions by vitac...
www.Vitac.Com.
Captions paid for by
discovery communications.
That's the thing
about this place...
Just when you think
you got your together.
And things are going good,
Mother nature kicks you
in the teeth.
In porcupine creek, Alaska...
Dustin's best-ever season
has hit a roadblock.
A gigantic boulder at the bottom
of rockfall ravine.
Is blocking his path
to what could be.
A life-changing pile of gold.
- Hey, mark.
- Dustin, how's it going?
It's going pretty good, man.
Good to see you.
I'm glad we found you.
Four miles from dustin's claim,
The mining legend known
as "the pirate," mark sebens,
Has been pulling gold out
of the ground for over 20 years.
How come you're not
in the water?
Well, we're having
a little bit of a problem.
We got a rock sitting
at the bottom of a hole,
Sitting on bedrock,
and we can't move it.
That's a tough one.
It's more than my gear
is rated for.
So I don't think I can move it.
And we're not gonna try.
Because I'll break every last
thing I put on it, basically.
What about Carlos? He's tough.
I don't think he's that tough.
But what I do have... I've got
something called rock blasters.
Okay. Drill down into a boulder.
Or a large rock, you set...
These are small charges.
It sends a shock wave down and
will crack good-size boulders.
So if you want to try that,
I've got it here with me.
That sounds great, man.
It's somewhere in here.
I'm very well organized.
Not!
Let's see. Give me a sec.
Wait. Here we go.
I thought it was gonna be
a huge kit.
Pretty compact
so you guys can get it.
Up to where you're working at.
That's pretty cool, man.
And if you set
several of them in a row,
You can split any size boulder
that you want.
Figured it'd be more than that,
but that'll work.
That should take care
of your problem.
Okay.
Got to get more food for Carlos.
Absolutely.
Well, hell, yeah, man. Thanks.
We'll get them back to you.
Take care.
If these things actually work,
This is gonna be
a huge game-changer for us.
There's not gonna
be a single rock.
We can't move or get under.
We got a lot riding on this.
This doesn't work, I don't know
what we're gonna do.
Hey, Ryan, what the hell's wrong
with your leg?
My leg's hurting me pretty bad.
You got to be
in the water today.
Higher up the mountain,
With less than an ounce of gold
so far,
Fred hurt and his crew are
having their worst season yet.
Well, to tell you the truth,
Fred, man,
My hip is killing me, man.
It's only getting worse
walking down this height.
Well, let's go on
up to the tent.
We'll talk about it. Alright.
The corona pandemic cost them.
The first four weeks
of their season.
His right-hand man,
Paul Richardson,
Upped and left three weeks ago
and is yet to return.
He's coming.
And the double dive duty
has taken its toll on Ryan.
What the hell?
It's been bothering me
for a couple of days.
But today, coming down the hill
there, it got really bad.
I got some really bad grinding
going on in there.
Believe it or not, Dustin is
a therapeutic masseuse.
Yeah?
He makes you lay down
flat on your face.
And bend your leg backwards.
It hurts like
I bet.
Well, I'm willing
to try anything.
Yeah.
You know, I know it's my turn
to dove today,
But I can't see
how I'm gonna put on.
A 50-pound weight belt
and move anywhere.
Wow.
If it continues like this,
My diving days
might be over out here.
Well, let's just go ahead
and get me in the water.
And we'll do it.
Fred's already dived twice
in the last five days,
But as Scott took
the most recent dive,
The 77-year-old maverick...
Must step up once more
for him to have any chance.
To get down
to the gold on bedrock.
Into the abyss.
How's your visibility
down there?
Got about a foot,
foot and a half.
The water is ice...
Did you say the water's too hot?
- No.
- Okay.
Fred is 14 feet deep,
Following the vertical face
of an ancient waterfall.
But Fred believes
they're only halfway down.
And every day must count.
If they are to get down
to the pile of gold on bedrock.
Alright, I got
two or three large rocks.
And I'm throwing...
Rocks out of the way
so I can put the sled down.
Might be possible to be able
to roll it right there.
Copy that.
Right here at all.
Rocks. Nothing but rocks.
Copy.
Alright.
Alright, y'all bring up
the basket.
Nice rock, boss. Nice rock.
Yeah, looking good.
Mineral rock there.
Fred's first basket of the day,
that was a damn good basket.
Nice big rocks.
Get those out of the way.
Getting ugly a little bit
on that water.
The water's horrible, man.
Water's definitely
coming up quick.
You know, hopefully Fred
can get through it okay.
It's gonna be rough, though.
Are you out of the way
of the basket?
Not yet, but just a minute.
Alright, I got to go sit down.
I really hate seeing
Ryan suffer this way.
He's in a lot of pain.
With Paul being gone, it's
the never-ending saga this year.
Of stuff breaking
and people getting hurt.
Well, if Ryan has to take off.
For a couple of days
'cause of his back,
I don't know what the hell
we're gonna do.
I don't think we can dive.
That's got a big question mark
for our season.
With Paul being gone,
it's just inevitable.
That somebody's
gonna get injured.
You know, this site definitely
can't be run by two people,
Especially when
one of the guys is new.
And it would make it really,
really difficult.
For them
to run this place alone.
So we're all hoping Paul
gets back here quickly.
I just don't know
what's going on.
But I know, you know,
if I leave,
These guys are in some deep.
Alright, I think
I'm ready to come up.
Fred will use the gold blaster.
To cut through the hard pack
he's uncovered.
Fred's down there calling
for the gold blaster.
That means he's ready
to dig deeper.
So, hopefully,
we can fire this thing up.
And he can get
a couple of feet today.
Because we really need
to hit bedrock.
Power. I'm gonna crank her up.
Alright, here we go.
The gold blaster breaks up.
The compacted gravel fred's hit.
Opening up new real estate.
And potentially
gold-rich material.
- How's it going down there?
- Well.
Fred's a hell
of a trooper for 77.
Amazing, every day,
what I see him do.
Fred's making
a lot of progress today.
He's got some good rocks
out there.
He's got the gold blaster,
And now he's got a lot of
material to suck up down there.
So, fred's having
a damn good dive today.
The current's
pretty damn strong.
This water is really raging.
Elements in the chilkat
mountains can flip on a dime,
And the heavy rain now thunders
through the trifecta.
This current's kicking my ass.
After four hours in the water,
Fred calls it a day.
Coming up.
Copy that. Diver coming up.
Diver coming up.
He's got two feet
closer to bedrock.
I'm so tired right now
that I can hardly stand up.
But the broken crew
really needs to catch a break.
Another day
with no gold showing.
Did anybody look?
No gold.
Well, this area just doesn't
have gold in the over burden.
Yeah.
We'll get to the bottom
eventually,
Figure out where that gold
is hiding.
We're on a marsh
down to the bottom.
And we're looking
for the real gold.
If we find that nice little "v"
full of gold down there.
In the bottom of this,
freddy's fortune.
Up ahead...
We know there's gold down here.
So this is my only option
right now.
You got it.
What do you got?
Look at that! That's gold.
3... 2... 1...
You want to have
Dustin try to look at it?
I don't know if I want
to stretch me all out right now.
Dustin is a licensed
therapeutic masseur,
So maybe he can help him out,
maybe he can't.
Ryan has completed the steep
hike back to Mckinley camp.
Despite debilitating pain.
What's going on, man?
Lost that option. Sorry.
What you did? I don't know, man.
I got a real, real bad pain
right in my hip joint.
On a mine site, this remote,
An injury can end
the miner's season.
Why don't you
let me help you out?
I don't know if I could stand
the pain, man.
It's a trade off... now with me.
Or all night
or maybe even all week.
I don't know. It's up to you.
Let's do it.
Yeah? Yeah.
If Ryan can't dive,
then fred's entire operation.
Will once again
come to a standstill.
We'll fix you up, man.
Don't worry about it.
Have a seat. Just lay down.
I'm going to press right here.
This hurts.
Well, you're out of the rain.
Best to leave the place
to just him and Ryan.
Up about two inches.
I know.
I think it's a torture chamber.
Yeah, it is.
Hey, y'all doing
alright in there?
Yeah, let me work on him
for a minute, Fred.
Alright.
It's mid-July,
But this far north, signs
of winter are fast approaching.
I'm predicting August 31st,
first snow.
I put five bucks on it.
Anybody bet me?
I bet October 15th. Ho, ho, ho!
I'm going... October 20th.
I'm probably wrong.
You guys are so far off.
Should I put this down
on a calendar or something?
Walk around for just a second.
It feels about 80 times better.
- How you feel, bro?
- Hey, man.
- You look good.
- You want to race?
Look like you got tears
in your eyes, man.
Yeah, I cried just a little bit.
I know, dude.
You couldn't do that before.
No, not really.
- Thanks, Dustin.
- Yeah, thanks a lot, man.
I appreciate it.
Miracle worker here.
The last thing you need
is a diver out of the rotation.
You need all hands on deck.
- Doctor Dustin.
- Doctor hurt.
Take it easy. Get some rest.
Ryan must stay on light duty.
To avoid further injury,
Meaning he cannot dive
for a week.
It was super, super painful,
but I'm just thankful.
That he is around and, you know,
was willing to do that for me.
Kind of need you.
Yeah, and I want to be there.
I don't want to be away.
Damn right. We got gold to get.
I'm down to two helpers.
We need everybody
in the world out here.
I mean, we got so much
to do right now.
We're not only way behind,
We need to be hustling
to get things done.
In all the years that we worked
out here, never had to move.
A boulder this big.
Dustin's crew
is mining the most gold-rich.
Dive site of their lives.
But the gold trail is now
blocked by a gargantuan boulder.
It is a big, big boulder,
So we're going to take it slow
and no mistakes.
You're not in a hurry, alright?
You're doing
something different.
We've never done this before,
so no mistakes.
Everybody take the damn time
and focus on what they're doing.
Try my best.
Losers talk about their best.
Winners just do it.
Just do it. Just do it.
We don't have enough winch power
or cable power or skyline.
To pull this boulder around.
We're having to bring
in new techniques.
We're having to
step up our game.
The whole reason we're here.
Is because
we know there's gold down there.
We can't just leave it there,
and we can't move the rock.
So, this is my only option
right now.
Hopefully, we can blow it
to little pieces.
To crack open the boulder,
They will first need to drill
holes for the blaster rods.
So, this is a cordless
underwater drill.
Do you know how they work?
"Pressurize tool
before all underwater work.
"See instructions." which,
we don't have instructions.
They need to set the pressure
inside the hammer drill.
To match the water pressure
at the depth.
James will be working.
Too little pressure,
And water will penetrate
and kill the motor.
Too much pressure,
and the drill will seize up.
So you pump it up
with a bike pump.
See, this is "bar"?
That's the red numbers.
- Okay, the red number.
- That's 6. That's 90 pounds.
- So, six more.
- I guess.
I really,
really don't know, man.
Let's go get him in the water,
shall we? Alright.
James is the least
experienced member of the crew.
But his brute strength is
the reason Dustin selects him.
For this critical mission.
Could be a good day, man.
Yeah, I believe so.
So, you just stay calm.
I want you to do everything
right today.
Can't have any mistakes.
Alright. Maybe you're ready?
We're ready.
You hit bottom? Yeah.
Yeah.
I'm looking at the boulder.
Copy that. We'll get
the underwater cordless drill.
Here we go.
Alright.
Just give me some gas, man.
Be gentle on it, man.
I don't know what the seals
are gonna do down there.
Alright.
Let's see if we can drill.
Right now, we got a brand-new
underwater drill.
That we're testing,
never tested before.
It's going slow!
You've got to really pull
the trigger.
Is it working at all?
Yeah, it is. Okay.
It's just really hard
to pull the trigger.
Yeah, well, then you're man
for the job down there.
Boy... I can't even get it
to sit right.
I don't know what to tell you.
Got it! Got it! I got it.
It's going. It's going.
Boy, that trigger is tough.
Yeah, well, be tougher.
Are you on hole two yet?
Hole two. Awesome.
James needs to drill three holes
for the full set of blasters.
You don't have to go
balls deep with that one.
Just go three quarters,
then go to the next one.
And see what you can get.
It's shutting off.
Alright, bring it back up.
And see. I don't know.
It's so weird.
I think it's cooked.
Without the drill, they
won't be able to blast the rock.
There's a failed attempt.
What do we do now?
That's so weird.
I think it's cooked. Really?
At rock fall ravine,
dustin's attempting to blow up.
The biggest rock
they've ever found.
What do we do now?
They need to drill a third hole
for the blast charges.
Worst-case scenario, there was
water inside the machine.
And it's dead now.
But their underwater drill
has failed.
What the is wrong with that?
Has it got too much pressure
or something?
Maybe.
Carlos, check
the pressure, please.
See, if you put
too much pressure on it,
It can't handle it.
They've pressurized the drill
to 90 psi,
4 times what it should be
for a 10-foot dive.
The increased pressure
on the seal causes friction,
And with it, heat.
When the motor overheats,
it cuts out.
Stand by. Stand by.
Pressure released,
Carlos can now re pressurize.
The drill correctly...
We've got 30 pounds of pressure
with 35 pounds.
It's holding the pressure, man.
And James can get back
to drilling the charge holes.
Hole number 3.
You got it.
Appreciate it.
That's good, dude.
I think it's good enough.
So I've got the charge,
The boosters
onto the power head,
So I've got connectors here,
and this is the blast cord.
They say
they'll blow up underwater,
But we've never done it.
I have no idea.
This is a whole
new system for us.
The blaster's must be
an exact fit.
Inside the drill holes.
Wes will fire a trigger
and send an electrical current.
Down the blast cord.
Onto the power heads,
Detonating the blaster.
The blast needs to be sealed
inside the boulder.
There's a small charge
to crack the monster rock.
From the inside out.
We don't know
if it's going to work.
Underneath the water or not,
But it's really our only option
to get rid of.
This large boulder.
That's got no telling
how much gold underneath it.
I'm giving you
these power heads.
Be very, very careful.
I need you to plant these
in the rock.
And then get the hell
out of there.
Alright, slow down.
All your movement
has to be slow right now.
Okay? Everything
needs to slow down.
Slow and steady, man.
It's gonna make
things easier. So far so good.
Whoa!
Are they in there?
Yeah.
That's what I wanted to hear.
They're sticking out about
roughly 6 inches, 7 inches.
That's almost perfect.
Last one's the toughest one.
Catch your breath
and do it right.
Done now.
Are they in there? Yeah.
Alright, there's
three blasters there.
Good job, man.
That was a tough one.
Yeah, right, man.
Y'all ready? We ready for this?
We're ready!
I'm armed. Here we go!
1...
That hit a lot harder
than I thought it would.
I'm so excited to find out
if it worked!
Wow!
It cracked!
I love it when a plan
comes together.
That was so much fun.
Good job, James.
This thing's completely cracked.
It just cracked it perfectly?
Hell, yeah.
We got a cool new toy
is what we got.
This changes everything, dude.
We don't have to break
no more anchors,
No more breaking guide lines.
Dude, there's
nothing that can stop us.
I mean nothing.
Holy crap!
The boulder split.
The crew works to remove
the smaller chunk.
That right there is about
a third of the rock.
That's sitting down there,
and it's huge.
It's a big rock.
That's less than
a third right there.
Do the dredge where it was.
The gravel beneath
the boulder should be.
Prime nugget territory.
There we go.
This water is way too
freezing cold.
I got to stop.
That's alright, man.
That's cool, man.
It's late.
It's been a long day, man.
Yeah, I'm good. I'm tired, man.
Did a lot of good work.
After five hours in the water,
battling with a new drill.
And new blasters,
James and the crew.
Check out the sluice.
Holy holy moly!
- Is there nuggets in there?
- Look at at all that gold!
My.
- Look at that!
- Holy.
There's ounces, dude!
I just started it!
Holy damn, man.
I only dredged this much
of an area.
That's amazing.
I did not expect that.
That's only a third
of that rock.
Gold. Gold. Gold. Gold.
That is ama...
It was a great day.
We got to use a new toy,
And we got gold.
This is why we're here.
It was the epitome
of why we should be here.
This is what we've been talking
about... pockets of gold.
And it was right
underneath that boulder.
And you see how much more
is in here, right?
I see it, man.
About five ounces
of gold in here.
We broke this big piece
of rock out,
But it's only less than a third.
We got a lot more work to do.
But I love this job.
This is an adventure,
And we're having
a damn good time doing it.
It was a long,
rough night last night,
I woke up this morning,
and my left leg was numb.
Wow. That's not good.
At their porcupine base camp,
Ryan's injury
has worsened overnight.
I don't know
what to say about it.
I'm kind of in
a rough spot here.
Sounds like somebody's
pulling in.
Yeah, it does.
I think that's Paul.
What's going on, man?
Not too much.
Where you been?
I had to go take care
of some personal business.
And get that done
and get back as soon as I could.
Sorry I had to leave you guys,
but I had some stuff.
That needed to take care of.
Alright.
So, how's everything been going?
Actually, it's been
pretty damn rough.
Ryan and I've been doing
double duty.
On the diving and everything.
They have a little bit
of problem.
With his hip or something.
I said, "crap.
What am I going to do now?"
We're making
pretty good progress.
I think Ryan and I are kind of
wearing down a little bit.
So, y'all get any gold at all?
Just a little.
We could use some help out here.
Said I'm all rested up,
so I'm ready to go.
Let's go ahead
and get out there.
Put me in. Alright.
Alright. Let's do it.
Paul's return means the crew
can now get back to diving.
He first mined with
"Dakota" Fred in the glory hole.
Seven years ago.
Over time, he's become
his most trusted crew member.
We did things a little
bit different.
Than when you was here last.
It's looking pretty good.
Y'all moved a lot of rocks.
That's a lot of rock
out of there.
We got a pretty nice sized hole
over there.
It's about 10 feet deep or so.
Not bad. So, about another 10
feet, and we'll hit the bottom.
We hope is before that.
Well, we'll give you
a baptism of fire,
And you're going to go in today.
Perfect.
Straight off the airplane
and straight into the water.
Damn right. Heck, yeah.
Let's go.
Sometimes when you've been away
and kind of hoping.
To kind of ease
back into the thing.
Nah, just throw him
right in water,
Get him orientated right now...
Baptism of fire.
Well, Paul, you know
we're way behind, buddy.
We need some gold
in that box today.
I know.
Good luck. Have a good time.
Alright. Good luck, Paul.
A big weight lifted
off our shoulders.
Now that paul's back
down in the water.
We're going to have
an increase in material moved,
And that's exactly what we need
to get down at the bottom.
Alright, here we go.
Have a good time.
How's your visibility
down there, Paul?
About 3, 4 feet at least.
Hell, yeah.
Two months
into the shortened season,
This is paul's first dive.
Alright, go ahead. Yep.
First, Paul cleans up
the exposed bedrock sidewall.
How's it going down there?
I'm about ready
for the gold blaster.
Copy that.
Let me get some water
going through that thing.
This thing's fun.
It definitely is.
Muddies up the water
down there, doesn't it?
He uses the gold blaster
to punch through the hard pack.
And push closer
to the bedrock below.
I bust right through
that hard pack.
Maybe we're getting on to
something a little different.
When the material changes,
the layers change,
That's always exciting,
Because you never know
what's in the new stuff.
What? Go back.
What do you got?
Look at that!
Alright. That's gold.
That's the real thing, man.
- Yeah, dude!
- Great job, Paul.
After weeks of no
gold, five hours in the water,
Paul has delivered their first
golden nugget of the season.
It'll be good for the morale
of the crew.
It'll be good for my morale.
That's pretty
damn exciting news,
Knowing that we're actually
finding gold again now.
I think that's officially
called paul's crack now.
It's great to have Paul back,
and he absolutely kicked butt.
We don't need a superhero
out here in Paul.
We just need him
to come back out here.
And do what he normally does.
And that's what we're all
out here for, finding that gold.
And today, we found it.
Alright, man, look at that.
That's gold right there.
We got some pickers
in here, Fred.
That one right there is
the one that I saw.
Down there in that crack.
That was in your crack?
That was in my crack.
Alright, man.
Look at that one right there.
- Wow.
- Look at that, man.
That is a sexy piece
of gold right there.
- Alright, good job, Paul.
- Good job, man.
That was my first dive.
Couldn't ask for a better day...
Good, clear water, full team,
Everybody working hard,
and it paid off.
There's nothing better than
seeing gold come out of the box.
The crew, now at full strength,
They are on the gold
and back on track.
It's been a long, long, long,
long summer of no gold.
If we can continue
on this trajectory,
We're going to get
to that bedrock this season.
And not only that, we're about
to have a big pay day.
I'm happy to see
it finally showed up.
I can't wait
to get down there tomorrow.
And get down a little deeper.
Alright, guys.
Either freddy's folly
or freddy's fortune.
Until we get down to the bottom,
we won't know.
It's going to be good!
Up ahead...
You guys ready to pop
some rock?!
We're going to pop
the rest of the hippo.
Holy -my.
Are you alright?
In the wilderness,
Months of living
shoulder-to-shoulder.
With your crew can get to you.
Damn it. You spit
all over my man.
See what I got to deal with?
I pee on that at night, dude.
You do what?!
It's just a fixture, you know?
It's just kind of like
garden gnomes, man.
I piss on those things
all the time.
You're funny man.
You guys ready to pop
some rock?!
At rockfall ravine,
dustin's determined.
To get the crew
back on the gold.
Whoo!
But, first, he has to break up
the rest of the hippo boulder.
That they couldn't remove
on their last dive.
Alright, good to go? Good to go.
My head is freezing.
Wow. There's pieces
of rock everywhere.
Yeah, man, that rock blaster,
man, deal.
It's like rock and roll.
Alright, I think I'm only going
to put two in the center.
Of this thing
and see if it cracks.
Good deal, man.
We got the drill ready.
Alright, gonna put two holes,
no problem.
I'm coming up for the drill.
He's coming up for the drill.
Let's see what happens, man.
Alright.
Gonna do a little bit
of pumpkin carving.
On this leftover hippo rock.
We just need two holes, man.
That's all we need, two holes.
Alright, that's one hole.
They figured out
the correct pressure,
And the underwater drill's
working perfectly.
I think that dustin's
going to use.
Only two blasters on this one.
You know what? I might be able
to get three in this thing.
Now he's talking about three.
No doubt there's going
to be freaking gold underneath.
No doubt!
This is our pay day right here.
This is where we collect
the fricking gold pot.
Alright.
That's two.
I finished one hole.
Alright, I think
I drilled enough.
Cross my fingers
and hope it works.
Alright, wes gots
all your boulder blasters.
Ready for you, man.
Whenever you're ready.
I can't lift my arm that high.
I'm so god dang excited man.
I love it.
Dustin
carefully places the charges.
In the remaining section
of the hippo rock.
Dustin's got
the three holes drilled,
Got our three charges in.
We're ready to pop
this thing off.
We're going to get
everybody out of the water.
We're going to pop
the rest of the hippo.
Yeah, all three are plugged in.
I didn't get them exactly
perfectly up-and-down,
So hopefully they won't shoot
out and kill us all.
Nah, it's not gonna shoot out.
What a good way
to freaking get hurt, though.
Y'all good there?
Alright, let's do this.
Ready?!
I'm armed.
Ready?! Ready!
1...
Nothing but gold down below.
I guarantee it, man.
Wes, good job, brother.
The last of the hippo cracked,
Dustin dives to see
what it has uncovered.
Alright.
It's nasty.
It's in three pieces now.
Alright, got a bunch
of broken-ass rock down here.
Going up.
Okay. He's freaking turned up.
He's showing off.
That's pretty cool, man.
That's funny.
Get the out of here.
Nuggets. Nuggets!
You got a nugget already?
Yeah, I found one. Hell, yeah.
There it is, gentlemen.
We got to get
underneath the rocks.
Yeah!
Dustin popped up a nugget out.
From underneath the rock
he just broke.
My.
Are you alright?
Did he lose his mind?
Are you gonna
bring it up or what?
Holy crap!
Holy man!
We knew it was going to be
down there underneath that rock.
It's paid off.
My gosh! Look at that, wes!
Where there's going to be
so much gold down there, dude.
That's the pocket!
That's the pocket that you was
talking about!
After four seasons
trying and struggling,
Their new underwater
blast system
I just watched a whole pocketful
go up the dredge.
Has allowed Dustin and his crew.
To get to the piles of gold.
The old-timers
could never reach.
We hit the jackpot.
Alright, should I come up
or what?
Yeah, I think we should
leave for Carlos.
Yeah, man! Save some for me!
Can you believe that?!
Great freaking dive, dude.
There will be a lot of gold
in that box.
I guarantee there's
a bunch of gold in there.
I guarantee you, man.
Last hour,
all I could see was gold.
There's ounces in here,
ounces of gold.
- So much gold!
- Like, big pieces.
It's honestly the most gold
I've ever seen in our sluice
since we've been dredging.
Holy!
How awesome is that?
I just was in awe.
I couldn't believe
it just kept coming.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- It's literally everywhere.
- Yeah, it's just everywhere.
The new tools are
a game changer.
No boulder, no matter how big,
Can stop them
on their path to gold.
I've got lots and lots of years.
Under this water right now,
And today, possibly,
was the very best time.
For over an hour,
it was gold constantly.
It was like Christmas forever is
what it felt like.
Time slowed down.
I enjoyed every second of it.
I finally did this.
I'm doing this right.
Today was the most fun
I've ever had in the water ever.
It didn't feel like
a dive anymore.
It felt like an experience.
I laughed like a maniac,
And I'm gonna ride this out
because I love it.
I don't know how long
it will last,
But I'll remember today
for the rest of my life.
The rest of my life.
On the next
"gold rush: White water"...
- Look at all that gold.
- Holy crap.
It's good to be
on the winning team.
We got to clear that rock.
That rock falls on somebody,
it just plants you down there.
There's no way to get you out.
There's a lot of tension
on that rock.
We are here to save the day!
Let me get the story right.
This is where I was born.
Now we're gonna have some fun.
3... 2... 1...