Dustin!
At rockfall ravine,
A month of lifting the biggest
boulders the crew has ever seen.
Has wrecked their
rock pulling system...
There's one of our anchor bolts.
Putting a stop to them.
Dredging for
chunky gold nuggets.
The other one's about to pop.
Yeah, it popped
one bolt at least.
Started pulling
the other one out.
So we have broken anchors?
I guess our mammoth fall
put your anchors to the test?
There's no way we're diving.
Let's work on that skyline.
Fix the broken bolts.
You've gotta make sure
that everything's safe enough.
To really pull on
some gigantic boulders.
Marine veteran Carlos
baynor volunteers to drill.
The new anchor
bolts into the cliff face
30 feet above the
raging creek below.
Why don't you drill some holes?
Make sure they're deep enough.
I need you to set
up a come along,
Put two or three
shackles on that.
Make sure it's all set up.
James, you know what to do?
Yep. Do it.
How's that hole coming, man?
I think I messed it up because
it's just spinning there...
Just spinning in the chuck.
You alright?
I'm not comfortable at all.
Okay. Stop. Stop,
stop, stop, stop.
Yeah don't... leave
that in there, come up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. What are you doing?
Hey. Carlos!
We need to toughen
up and get the job done.
What could possibly go wrong?
I got a spy from fred's team.
Pain in the butt.
It's a big damn rock, man.
I think I'm sliding.
Ooh, that was rough.
If there turns out to be no
gold down there, though,
I guess I'm eating
noodles for a looong time.
Gold can't swim in liquid dirt.
Our nugget day!
Get out of here, man.
Look at that. Wow. This
is gonna be amazing.
Captions by vitac...
www.Vitac.Com.
Captions paid for by
discovery communications.
Don't fall.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa. What are you doing?
Whoa.
Hey. Carlos! Dustin!
How you doing, man?
How do I get the up here?
Alright. Hold on. Hold on. Stop.
Here's what you do...
you grab that one,
And you pull that up.
Yep. All the way.
Now reach up and grab
that rope and take a step.
Whoa.
Man, it's always a
weird feeling, right?
Yeah, it...
Take a break. Come back to it.
I gotta figure this out.
For dustin's crew,
the clock is ticking.
They now have less than
60 days in their season.
Before the Alaskan
winter hits hard.
This is taking forever.
Dustin risked his life
savings buying these claims.
Finally, the gamble
is starting to pay off,
Pulling out nuggets every dive.
But hiding the nuggets
are monster boulders.
That have destroyed
their skyline anchors.
I think we're done with this.
Basically, we just reset our
anchors and tightened it up,
Tightened up our skyline again.
It's tighter now.
Bigger, better bolts.
So now I can get back to
work. Find a big pile of gold.
We're still out in the same box.
Today is the day, fellas.
I can feel it, man.
Upstream at the trifecta,
Fred hurt has staked his season
on finding an ancient waterfall.
With a plunge
pool flush with gold.
But unlike Dustin,
Fred's skeleton crew have
found next to nothing at all.
Well, if there turns out to be
no gold down there, though,
I guess I'm eating
noodles for a looong time.
Fred's newest diver, Scott,
Is unable to dive.
After injuring his
hand last week.
Sliced right through, and
these are down to the bone.
And it's uncertain what his
most experienced diver, Paul,
Will return.
We're already missing Paul,
And it makes it
really, really hard.
With the amount of work
that's on all of our backs.
Down to a two man dive crew,
Fred and Ryan are
on double dive duty.
You can go about
every three days.
And go diving... it's okay.
But, boy, you try to do it
day after day after day...
It's not a good situation.
Ryan took the last dive,
so it's fred's turn today.
Looking good.
How's that?
Feels good.
Go ahead, Fred.
Whooo! My forehead is cold.
It's gonna follow that on
down that bedrock wall.
Until the bedrock flattens out.
And that's what we have
to do to get to the gold.
Fred's theory is
that the trifecta.
Was once the site of
an ancient waterfall,
Creating a 20-foot-deep
plunge pool.
Now at seven feet, Fred
must head straight down.
Through another 13
feet of rock and gravel.
To get to the gold-rich
bedrock floor below.
This gotta be a waterfall.
Got a dip in the bedrock.
You got a dip in the bedrock,
You got a good
place for catching gold.
Hope and pray that
when we get down there,
He's right and there's a
bonanza of gold down there.
Fred's hose sucks the gravel up.
And sends it to the sluice box.
Where the gold should
settle in the riffles.
You see that this is
all jagged right here.
It's all full of little
layers right here.
This is not carved
out by glaciers.
This is carved by water.
Fred believes these
layers in the rock face.
Could be evidence
of his ancient waterfall.
The side that we're
we're dredging,
You can see all the
jagged edges sticking out.
It's like nature's sluice
box right through there.
I agree 100%, man.
We're gonna find
some gold down in there.
I guarantee it.
I hope so, man. We need it.
Yeah, this is good material.
How's it goin', Fred?
After an hour of dredging
good-looking gravel,
Scott and Ryan
check the sluice box.
You know, there should be a
lot more material in this thing.
Yeah, pretty gloomy
looking box today, buddy.
Yeah.
Fred?
What now?
I've got a problem.
What the hell are
y'all doing up there?
We're having some problems.
Fred, this box is empty.
This is not good.
Alright, shut your motors down.
Why don't we just pan it?
See if there's
anything at all in that.
Scott pans a
sample of the tailings.
At the back of the sluice to
check if they're losing gold.
I'm seeing gold in it.
In my mind, it just says that.
You're just letting
the gold right on down.
I guess I just want to set
it up to where we caught.
Every piece of gold that
came through here, period.
I didn't come up here to
run a whole bunch of rocks.
Just because I
wanted them washed.
You know? I came
up here to get gold.
We're gonna have to do
something about this, man.
Ryan gets to work.
I'm gonna grind out
some of these bars.
And I'm gonna
bend the riffles up.
That's gonna give
us less of an angle.
And more of a dead
zone behind the riffle.
So that gold will have a
real nice place to settle.
Right in the
back of the riffles.
As the water and gravel
run through the sluice box,
The heavier gold
should sink to the bottom.
And be caught in the riffles.
But their angle is sending
the water and gold.
Out the back of the box
with the worthless tailings.
Ryan's plan...
Bend the riffles up to
increase the water vortex,
Slowing the flow of
water, trapping more gold.
All your job.
Here... we'll bend them
up a little bit more here.
You can finish them off.
We don't really have
a choice in the matter.
We're just doing the best
we can with what we have.
Good job, there, man. Good job.
The modification to the riffles.
Will finally start
catching all the gold.
On their way down
to the big payday.
They believe is on the bedrock.
By bending those up,
We're gonna be catching
more material, I believe,
Than what we're doing
right now with these riffles.
Can't wait to get in there.
And find out exactly
what we're gonna get.
Deeper we go, more
gold we're gonna get.
Alright. Good. Perfect.
Up ahead
I'm pretty concerned about Fred.
He is 77 years old.
What could possibly go wrong?
Oooh!
The most lucrative
job we've ever had.
I'm diving today, so it's
gonna be a good day.
So I go get suited up or what?
I think it's time.
Water does look good.
As long as it's clear,
we're in good shape.
I'd love to just be able to just
keep digging and getting gold.
After five weeks
of raging melt water,
The worst of the
winter snow has thawed,
Improving the dive
conditions at rockfall ravine.
This is gonna
be a hell of a day.
Were you about six feet here?
Yeah, right there. Right there?
Hey, James, did you take
any weight off that belt?
10 pounds.
Is that hot enough for you?
Feels pretty good.
Hey, you're all
rock and roll, man.
In the water.
I'm goin' down there.
How's the current?
It seems pretty good.
The rockfall ravine dive site.
Is scattered with
buried chunky nuggets.
Dustin's mission is
to hunt them down.
Leaving no boulder unturned,
As one small pocket could
contain life-changing gold.
So I can't see very well.
Should I keep going or not?
Come here, James. Please.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What what the.
What do you got
there? What do you got?
No way! What?!
Look at that!
Is that gold?!
Put him over if that's gold.
I can't tell down here.
You just don't
understand how dark it is.
Holy moly, dude!
That's a good piece.
Is it? Yes!
Wow. Good job!
Whooo!
That's crazy! Are
you kidding' me?
Look at that. Look at that gold.
He wasn't even in the water
not more than 15 minutes.
Lo and behold, he
comes across a nugget.
Can you believe that?
Wow, that's like a
quarter of an ounce!
For now, dustin's crew
are still on the nuggets.
With gold heading
towards $2,000 an ounce.
And nuggets
selling at a premium,
This single find is
worth more than $500.
This is it.
Hopefully it continues to
hand us nuggets every day.
Back to work.
At the trifecta,
Fred's skeleton crew still have
over 13 feet of rock and gravel.
To clear to get down
to the bedrock gold,
And only Fred and
Ryan are able to dive.
You know, I'm pretty
concerned about Fred.
He is 77 years old
busting a hump down there.
So the plan today is to
move a bunch of boulders.
And a bunch of rocks
down there in our deep hole.
You know, if I can move
a lot more boulders today,
Move a lot more material,
It might make it a
little bit lighter on Fred.
Fred's crew have found
barely any gold this season,
But he believes there's a
payday on bedrock 20 feet deep.
They just have to get there.
Are we ready? You're ready.
Let's do it.
But right now, Ryan is just
filling baskets with rock.
And he's dredging.
He's getting a lot of
material out of there.
It's looking pretty nice
on this back slope now.
Yeah. Well, good.
Couple rocks left,
but not too much.
Yeah, just pile them over there.
Ryan's efforts have paid off.
He's deep in the hole by a foot.
And dredged material
up into the sluice.
Ryan, you can probably
just make your way back here.
We're done.
The dredge's working fine.
The winches are working fine.
All the anchors holding up.
What could possibly go wrong?
Fred is staking everything
on the trifecta paying out.
And needs Ryan’s
riffle fix to have worked.
How much have you got in there?
It looks like we're catching
a little bit more material,
That's for sure. Yeah, I mean...
If we clean that
out, say, tomorrow,
Tomorrow afternoon, maybe?
Okay. Good job.
Our box is working
a lot better now,
And I'm pretty confident.
If we suck up any
gold from here on out,
It's gonna stay in the box.
That's music to my ears.
Tomorrow, I'm going down.
I need a knife or
something like that.
At rockfall ravine,
Dustin has been in
the water for four hours.
Hunting every inch of
the dive site for nuggets.
What do you got?
It's another piece, I think.
What?! What?
I found the perfect
little crevice.
I think it's got about a
half-ounce of nugget in it.
I can't tell 'cause it's
buried, so I gotta dig it out.
Hopefully it's as big
as it looks to my eyes,
But everything looks
bigger under water.
Yeah.
Look at... no way, dude!
Nugget, man?
I'm coming up, James.
James, get the gold!
I got it in my pants.
And I can't feel it
'cause of my gloves.
Hold on. It's stuck
in your gl... It fell.
Aaaah!
Okay.
I'll try it again.
You gonna get it this time?
Yeah, I got it.
Take the thing.
That's a nice piece.
Look at that baby.
Look at that!
That's awesome, man.
He's just picking up
nuggets. That's all he's doing.
I like that. That'll work.
So that means
there's gotta be some.
Going to the dredge, too.
Yeah.
Two nugget day for Dustin
hurt. Two nugget day.
We have company. We
got a spy from fred's team.
Scott? Yep.
Good for him. I'd wanna
see this place, too.
Lack of gold at fred's site.
Has pushed new recruit, Scott,
to investigate the opposition.
How's it goin' up there?
It's goin'.
Ryan put in about
three hours today.
We're still on team the box,
But we'll get...
We're just moving a lot
of overburden right now.
Yeah.
I wanted to check
out a rockfall.
Let's see how
varsity does it, man.
This awesome, man.
You're barely 100 feet
over top of this waterfall.
Yeah, this has got
real danger to it.
Yeah, it does.
First was bigger.
Yeah, I can't wait
to go look in the box.
There's gotta be some in there.
Can't touch it, but
you can look at it.
Yeah, that's a piece.
That's all the stuff.
Probably have at least a
quarter-ounce of fines in there.
Check that out, Scott.
Look at that nugget, buddy.
Wow.
Seeing the gold
in their sluice box.
Makes me a little
annoyed at our spot.
You know, somewhere up
creek, there's that mother lode.
And I'm really hoping that
trifecta is that right spot.
Dude, just come
work on our side, man.
I would love to be over
here, brother. I really would.
I would take that opportunity
in a flying heartbeat.
Dustin's crew are
on a winning streak.
Their nugget hunt is paying off.
We're getting really good
nuggets out of this thing.
I hope it continues all
season to tell you the truth.
This is...
This is great.
At Mckinley camp,
Carlos is up early,
hungry for nuggets.
I'm diving today
and my main focus.
Is the competition to get gold.
On his last dive,
Dustin pulled out two
quarter-ounce nuggets.
Worth over $1,000,
And Carlos is determined
to stay on the gold.
Who wouldn't want to have a
day that... dive day like that?
Pulling out gold. You know?
Everybody wants
to pull out gold.
Get the gold!
Gonna be a an awesome
dive today, dude.
Yeah, we can take
things slow and easy.
I am expecting
a lot of gold, man.
'Cause I know you're
good with the gold.
I can't wait to see what
happens when I go in there.
But Dustin wants
Carlos to switch track.
And do some heavy lifting.
Hold on. Hold on. Nope, not yet.
To keep the crew safe,
His plan for Carlos is
more grunt than glory.
You're gonna go down there.
There's gonna be some rocks.
Move those.
Okay. These rocks right
here, I'll move them, man.
No problem. Some
deadly ones here.
I got it, man. I'll
assess the situation.
Diver going in the water.
Ooh.
Oooh, I see you, rock.
This is a boulder, man.
Dude.
That's what's gonna kill us is
those big teetering boulders.
That the current
is hitting so hard,
You just know they're gonna go.
A giant boulder is hanging.
Directly over
dustin's dive site.
Making the area a kill zone.
If the crew continue
to dredge the dirt.
And rocks beneath the boulder,
It could come loose,
crushing anything in its path.
Carlos' mission...
Remove the boulder
from its unstable position.
Using the skyline and clear
the boulder downstream.
Honestly, I didn't anticipate
rocks the size of cars.
This is one of the biggest
boulders we've tried to move.
This three-ton boulder.
Will test the skyline
anchor bolts to their limits.
Am I safe?
You are safe right there.
Okay.
There she goes!
Goin'.
That's just movin', too.
That's a.
That's good. Bring it in.
Holy moly. Holy moly.
- So stressful!
- My
dude.
Holy moly, you're halfway there.
It almost got
stuck in there, man.
Rocks falling!
Look at that.
I can't believe you
get that out of there.
Now that far, dude.
Holy moly, man.
Come on!
There it goes!
Is it moving? Yeah.
There it goes.
Come on, come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on.
Whooooo!
Holy.
You know your
skyline's doing good.
When you can
pop cables like that.
Wow!
Well, that's the biggest
rock we've ever moved here.
There's no doubt of that. It
was enough to break a cable.
Now the boulder
is out of the way,
The dive site is safe.
Carlos has achieved the
mission and gets back to the glory.
Of hunting for more nuggets.
Alright. Show me some gold, man.
Let's see what I got!
Alright, man. I've
got a nugget today.
A nugget. Whoa!
What the
look at that nugget!
My.
That's a pretty nice nugget.
That's a nice nugget.
So Carlos came up with a nugget.
That came out from
underneath that mammoth rock.
Another pretty nice nugget.
He's trying to pull out
another nugget right now.
I can hear him.
It's another day for me.
Man. They're getting better.
That one broke in half!
That's beautiful, man.
I love that you're
getting comfortable.
Bringing up two
nuggets one day, buddy.
Yep. I love it.
That's the norm
for us now, dude.
Yeah, that's the daily norm.
Is at least bring
up two nuggets.
How about that?
Of course, man.
Getting tired, though.
Four hours in.
And having matched
dustin's two nugget dive,
Carlos is low on energy
and ready to call it a day.
Whoa, wait a minute.
It's a three nugget day!
It's a three nugget
day. Three nugget day?
It's a three nugget day!
Carlos, I think you got the
record on this one, buddy.
- Three nugget day.
- Ohhhh.
Damn, man! Look at that?
That is beautiful. Whoo!
My goodness.
Three nugget day!
Three nugget day.
Look at that.
Beauty. Look at this.
What number in my hand?
- What number in my hand?
- My.
This will be number four.
That is awesome.
You're on fire right now, man.
Look at you. What you got?
Ha haaaa!
My.
It's even bigger
than the last one.
Carlos, you are on fire.
Whoo-hoo-hooo!
Nugget!
Look at you, man.
That's number four.
That's number four, man.
It's gonna be real
hard for me to beat this.
You're my hero right now, man.
That's nugget number four
he's brought up by hand.
Alright, man.
Good job today, man. Damn it.
Whoo! I'm free!
Good job, dude.
Awesome dive, man.
- Aah.
- Hey, Carlos.
I don't even have to check, man.
That's the most lucrative
dive we've ever had ever.
That's crazy, right?
Hands down across the board,
The most lucrative dive
we've ever, ever, ever had.
You kept this boy for
two frickin seasons.
Without seeing nothing, man.
Yeah? Yeah?
You pull out three
or four nuggets?
Four. I'm so jealous.
That one boulder, man.
The combined value
of Carlos' four nuggets.
Is over $2,000.
They're onto a bonanza of gold,
Meaning rockfall
ravine is on track.
To become the most
gold-rich ground of their lives.
Carlos found gold right where
we thought we'd find gold.
Underneath one
of the big boulders.
Four nugget day, brother.
Four nugget day, man.
The old timers couldn't
move the big boulders.
I think they skipped
over a lot of stuff.
That was way too hard to dig.
But we had to be stubborn
enough to keep doing it,
Creative enough to
be able to pull this off,
And tough enough
to just keep going.
We did.
And now it's paying off.
I hope it continues all season.
Up ahead...
You just never know
when you're gonna find gold.
I'm so frickin' excited.
You got a big one? What?!
This is the biggest one that
he brought up so far today.
Get out of here, man.
Look at that. Look at that.
I'd like to see some
gold in the box today.
We could sure use it.
At the trifecta, morale is low.
Fred's crew have found
next to no gold this season.
And still have over 12
feet to go to reach bedrock.
I'm thinking that there is.
Some sort of a hole
to catch the gold in.
Anything got in there
could be a bonanza.
It would be good for
the morale of the crew,
And it sure would be
good for my morale.
Down to just a
two-man dive crew,
77-year-old Fred
is forced to dive.
For the second time this
week, and the pressure is on.
It does put us in a bind.
Because it's little more
strenuous on the divers.
And it will be a test.
We need to toughen
up and get the job done.
Hopefully breaking it down
there dredged that material up.
And there'll be some gold in it.
You know, we gotta clean
up at the end of the day.
It'd be nice to have
some gold in the box.
Alright.
Go down there and give her hell.
Good to go.
Well, we'll see
how things go today.
Go get in there, gold hound.
Looking good down
here. Let me look around.
If there ends up being
no gold back there,
I'm gonna be growing my
own vegetables in the backyard
'cause I'm gonna
be broke as hell.
So I hope fred's
right. I really do.
Fred dredges up
small rocks and gravel,
Sending them to the sluice
box and deepening the hole.
What's the material
looking like down there?
Are you seeing any
change in the layer?
Lots of small rocks. A lot
of them go up the dredge.
It's alright. Well, good, man.
You ought to be able to make
a lot of headway today, then.
You got it.
The box is looking
a lot better today.
The change in riffle angle.
Is already showing better
results in their sluice box.
Yeah, I'm down.
I know I'm deeper
than I've been down.
Well, fred's down
in the hole now,
And he's about 8
1/2, 9 foot down.
So he's starting to get
into some new material.
He's running a lot
through the sluice box.
And, you know, we're really
hopeful at the end of the day,
There's gonna be
some gold in the box.
For two seasons,
Fred and Dustin dredged
just 10 feet from here.
And failed to hit it big.
You're coming up on 4 1/2 hours.
But Fred is convinced that they
were diving in the wrong place.
And right now he's directly
above a gold ridge plunge pool.
We're just over eight
feet here, almost nine feet.
So hopefully this next layer.
Is gonna give us
at least something.
It can't get no worse.
Holy crap. The world is
going straight down almost.
The bottom just
doesn't go straight out.
So there's a big area
here that's really deep.
It's a good possibility
this hole is part of the bowl.
On this waterfall. Whooo!
Gosh.
Nine feet into the hole,
Fred has made a
crucial discovery...
A near-vertical wall of bedrock.
Fred believes this is the
face of the ancient waterfall.
That will lead him
into the plunge pool.
And a pile of gold in
the bottom of the bowl.
I'm gonna come up.
I'm so frickin' excited.
This may very well
be that bonanza.
That fred's always
talking about,
This bucket of gold down there,
So there's only
one way to find out.
And that's just get down
there, get to bedrock, and find it.
Whoo!
Good job, Fred.
Fred's discovery
proves to the crew.
That his ancient waterfall
is more than a theory,
And they could be just 11
feet above a giant payday.
Today was a good dive.
The bedrock is coming down,
And then it drops off
20-something-feet deep.
Any time you find a
bedrock that drops off,
It pretty well proves.
That you've got a
plunge pool right there.
You're gonna look for gold in
the bottom of that plunge pool.
Carlos had an
amazing day yesterday.
Just nuggets everywhere.
At Mckinley camp, after
seasons of striking out,
Dustin's crew are onto
the best gold of their lives.
It was crazy what happened.
We're hoping for
the same day today.
Dustin's desperate to
carry on the winning streak.
And beat Carlos'
four nugget record.
With his second
dive of the week.
I'm a little jealous.
I'm not gonna lie.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
That just about
ripped my mask off.
I should have grabbed it.
The material's
never been touched.
And it keeps going down.
Look what I can see.
You gonna bring us some nugget?
I think I got it.
My gosh.
That's good.
Good morning, sir. Yeah.
One nugget. Three more
to go... catch up to me.
As long as we're bringing up
golden nuggets, we're happy.
You still up there,
wes? Yep, I'm here.
It's not as big as
the other one, but...
That doesn't matter.
That still counts.
It's just numbers.
That works.
- Second nugget.
- Got two!
Got two more to go
to catch up with Carlos.
It's coming.
Alright, you can
bring me a basket.
Okay, copy that. Basket's
coming in the water.
Thank you.
Not sure what time it is,
but this has to get done.
Copy that.
Just keeps going down.
Straight, straight down.
That's insane, man. How
deep do you think you are?
I have no idea.
Aw, man, I'm doing a
handstand inside of a hole.
I don't know how you
can see with a vis like this,
But he's been down for
four or five hours now.
Done with this.
Nope. No more gold.
Hold on.
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
You got a big one?
What? What?!!
What?! Whoo! Aw, hell yeah!
They're not too huge
but they're in there.
I can barely stand up, bro.
Oohh!
Oooh!
Aaaah!
Carlos, is that three now?
That's two! Two?
No, that's three. Three!
He's catching up to you!
This is dustin's third nugget.
This is the biggest one that
he brought up so far today.
It's probably close to a
quarter-ounce, just guessing.
Every time we
get under boulders,
Get into deep areas,
there's nuggets.
It's awesome.
And that's gnarly. That
hasn't traveled anywhere.
So there could be a source
right here close to where we're at.
We know for sure that
none of the old timers,
Nobody has been
to this area yet.
This is what we've
been looking for.
There's gold in there?
You gotta shut it off, man.
I think so.
Dustin has been
diving for five hours,
Determined to beat
Carlos' four nugget record.
He digs us up a
grave every time.
When he gets tired, he's
just going after the gold.
What now?
What, what, what?!
What?!
You got a big one?
I think my mind playing
tricks on me right now.
I'm comin' up.
Oooh!
There's a couple of them.
Whoo! Four nugget
day! It's getting' bigger.
- Get it!
- My.
That's like, a quarter
of an ounce, dude.
I... Had a great big
day, and I am exhausted.
Dustin's hard work has paid off.
These four nuggets combined
are worth over $2,000.
Good dive, man.
What a job, what a
job. Four nugget day!
Awesome dive.
You look tired, dude.
You sound like you're
going to pass out.
Ooh, that was rough.
You're gonna carry me out here.
I'll bring you up in the basket.
Right now, we're getting
ready for our first cleanup.
I'm nervous. It can be horrible.
At the trifecta, fred's
crew are having doubts.
Heading into their first
cleanup of the season.
After blowing gold
out of their sluice box.
You just never know
when you're gonna find gold.
You just never know.
And, well, you never know
when you're not gonna find gold.
Fred has discovered
what he believes.
Is the wall of the
ancient waterfall.
But his skeleton
crew need more proof.
That they are on track
for a massive payday,
So Fred is called for the
first cleanup of the season.
It'd be really disappointing
to be doing all this work.
For the last month
or so now and...
Nothing to show for it.
I'm not really looking
forward to this.
I'm a little worried
myself, brother.
All you can do is
hope for the best.
That thing's heavy.
Worth its weight in gold.
Hope so.
What are you seeing in there?
Things are looking pretty
damn good right now.
You know, for overburden,
this is pretty good stuff.
Whooo!
Yeah. There's gold in there.
Every single pan,
I'm seeing gold in it.
Bending those ripples
worked perfectly.
The crew are still 11 feet away.
From the bedrock floor,
But even this small amount
of gold is a promising sign.
That fred's ancient
plunge pool theory is right.
And they could be in
for a monster payday.
It's pretty sweet to see
this from our overburden.
I can't wait to see what we
get when we get to bedrock.
This whole area is
one ancient waterfall.
Deeper we go, the more
gold we're gonna get.
Any time you can
find any gold at all,
It's a good day.
What a dive.
At rock fall ravine,
Dustin has pulled
off a five-hour dive.
And already matched
Carlos' four nugget record.
Now he's banking
on the sluice box.
To break the tie.
Nuggets!
Big nuggets!
Come check it out.
They're glowing.
Look at that.
Man. This is the
best we ever done.
Holy crap!
This is the best I've
ever seen the box.
That one nugget's
at least a half-ounce,
Three or four
quarter-ounce nuggets,
A bunch of smaller nuggets.
So right now, gold is running
pretty close to $2,000 an ounce.
So you look at that right there.
And I've got probably $5 grand
sitting in my hand right there.
Check this out, dude!
What are we talking about, man?
Well, we're talking about a lot.
Get out of here,
man. Look at that.
That is beautiful.
Look at that. That is beautiful.
Talk about a lucrative dive.
I work for that, man. Holy cow.
I was getting changed and I
leaned down to grab my socks.
And started just throwing
up. I'm like, "my god."
Went way past my limits.
Well, you overworked
yourself today. That's for sure.
That is the definition
of gold fever...
Pushing your body till you
about to pass out underwater.
I never, ever seen that
much gold ever, bro.
This pile of chunky nuggets.
Is a breakthrough for Dustin
and is worth more than $8,000.
We're trying to find places
the old timers didn't get,
And I'm pretty sure this
nugget ball at rockfall ravine.
Is one of those places.
I went broke
getting these claims.
And basically didn't
know if it was worth it.
Well, it's worth it.
Dustin's gamble
is finally paying off.
The crew are on the
richest ground of their lives.
If they can stay on the goal,
They're in for their
best season ever.
It's been a long time coming,
but it's finally paying off.
Handfuls of nuggets every
day. This is gonna be amazing.
Feels pretty good.
On the next "gold
rush: White water"...
First dive. I'm excited
but I'm nervous.
If you mess up, it could
cost you your life, man.
He'll make it. His ego
won't let him not make it.
If that thing pops up,
It just smacks you
right in your mouth.
!!
Gotta be careful, man.
We can see quite a few
boulders overhanging.
Scott, have you got a copy?
That's a big mother lode.
We all know how much work.
It took to get that.
Finally doing it, guys.