- Last season on "The X-Files":
- We have the complete corpus
of an extraterrestrial biological entity.
The ice-core samples I took can't be faked.
(Mulder) I refuse to believe it's not true.
- So you're saying it's all been a hoax.
- Which you've been used to perpetuate.
- (gunshot)
- He said that the men behind this hoax
gave me this disease to make you believe.
Early this morning,
I got a call from the police, asking me
to come to Agent Mulder's apartment.
The detective asked me...
He needed me to identify a body.
Agent Scully...
Agent Mulder died late last night
from an apparent self-inflicted
gunshot wound to the head.
(man) When we speak of life beyond Earth,
what we generally mean is intelligent life,
something resembling our noble selves.
It is highly probable
that there are such intelligent forms
of life in other galaxies in the universe.
And it is even more probable
that many of these forms
are vastly more intelligent than we.
(Mulder) I have held a torch in the
darkness to glance upon a truth unknown.
An act of faith begun
with an ineloquent certainty
that my journey promised the chance
not just of understanding but of recovery,
that the disappearance of my sister
23 years ago would come to be explained,
and that the pursuit of these greater
truths about extraterrestrial life
might even reunite us.
A belief which I now know to be false,
and uninformed in the extreme.
My folly revealed by facts which illuminate
both my arrogance and self-deception.
If only the tragedy had been mine alone,
it might have been more easy tonight
to bring this journey to its end.
(Phone)
(man) Agent Mulder?
Agent Mulder?
Yeah.
There's a matter of security I hadn't
anticipated. Just after I left your...
- Who are you?
- Just after our last conversation I was...
- Are you listening? Are you hearing me?
We can't speak right now. I believe...
Did they give Agent Scully this disease?
Did they do this to her because of me?
They may be listening, Agent Mulder.
They may be watching
everything you do and say.
Are you listening, Agent Mulder?
Agent Mulder?
Put that out! Back away!
Get away.
(gunshot)
(Dew)
You have no new messages.
(man) Keep going, FBI woman.
Mulder? What are you doing? Why are
you sitting in my bedroom in the dark?
It was too crowded in my
apartment. I couldn't sleep.
- I'm not kidding, Mulder.
- Good, cos neither am l.
There's a dead man in my apartment.
It's only a matter of time
before he stinks the place up.
What are you talking about,
Mulder? What's going on?
Somebody thinks my life
is interesting enough to video.
My apartment's been under surveillance
for at least two months. Look at this.
Courtesy of the US government.
- That's the dead man in your apartment?
- Yeah. He works...
He worked for the Department of Defense.
How did he die, Mulder?
Gunshot wound to the face.
Have you contacted anybody at the Bureau?
I can't do that. I can't go to the authorities.
- What are you talking about?
- This man Ostelhoff worked for the military.
Are you getting the picture?
Do you see what's happening here?
That the hoax is connected to the military.
This hoax, your cancer, everything.
It just doesn't lead back to the military,
it leads right back to the FBI.
What?
This man Ostelhoff was set up
in the apartment directly above mine.
I caught him destroying phone records
on which the same number
was called 17 times.
This is a PBX operator at the Bureau.
Yeah.
- Who would he be calling at the FBI?
- I don't know.
- Mulder, how long has this been going on?
- Maybe since you joined me on the X-Files.
That would mean that for four years
we've been pawns in a game,
that it was a lie from the beginning.
Mulder, these men...
You give them your faith,
and you're supposed
to trust them with your life.
There are those who can be trusted. What
I need to know is who among them is not.
I will not allow this treason to prosper,
not if they've done this to you.
We can't go to the Bureau
making these accusations.
No. But as they lie to us, we can lie to them.
A lie to find the truth.
(Mulder) Let the truth be known
though the heavens fall.
The web of lies entangling us
can now be connected back
to the very institution
which brought us together.
The facts supported by a Byzantine plot,
executed by someone inside the FBI,
who, if named, could be tied
to the hoax meant to destroy me...
and to the terminal disease
inflicted on Scully.
In four years I have shared my
partner's passionate search for the truth,
and if my part has been a deception,
I have never seen her integrity waver
or her honour compromised.
But now, I ask her to lie...
to the people lying to us.
A dangerous lie to find the truth,
to find the man who would be
revealed as its enemy, as our enemy...
as the enemy within.
Agent Scully,
is it true?
Yes, sir.
- Are you all right?
- I'm, uh...
I don't know what to say. They asked
me to come down and identify the body.
Well, how'd you make the ID?
The word from Alexandria PD is it was
self-inflicted. A shotgun blast to the face.
I saw Mulder earlier this morning.
He was wearing the same clothes.
Well, I'm very sorry.
Agent Scully.
Section Chief Blevins
wants you in for questioning.
He believes you have information
that you haven't come forward with.
(Mulder) The military connection to the
conspiracy we had pierced was undeniable.
The man in my apartment worked
for the Department of Defense,
at its Advanced Research Facility.
What I might find here I was uncertain of,
but my crime had provided me access.
As long as they believed Scully's lie,
that it was me lying on that floor,
I might learn truths here.
But if our lies were discovered, both
Scully and I would be discovered with them.
(Dew)
Agent Scully. Please have a seat.
Some time has passed
since you were first here.
Four years.
From our reports, your work on the X-Files
brought you very close to Agent Mulder.
- Yes, sir.
- We're all sorry about what's happened.
- But that's not why I'm here.
- We've been informed by the DOD
that prior to Agent Mulder's accident
you may have been contacted
by a DOD employee.
Yes. That's right.
And that he gave you classified information.
He had information about the discovery of
what Mulder believed to be an alien corpse.
He, uh... he said the body
was part of a hoax.
He provided evidence of this?
No hard evidence, no.
Agent Scully, I suggest you
tell us everything you know.
If you have any knowledge of this man,
you should speak up now.
- What knowledge?
- His name.
Whatever you're withholding,
you'll be asked to explain yourself tonight
at a joint FBI panel I've asked
assembled on this matter.
Is this the man? Michael Kritschgau?
Yes.
Hey.
- How'd you get in here?
- Through the front door.
- You can't bypass security.
- You can when you have the card.
Put that away. Put it away.
You knew my apartment
was being surveilled. How?
Come with me.
I was followed from your apartment
the night we spoke.
Someone at the FBI is involved.
This man Ostelhoff was the contact...
How did you get his card?
I found it on a dead man.
You know what that is?
What you have in your hand?
It gives you level-four clearance.
Level-four clearance? I get
to dine at the Officers' Club?
You have access to everything.
Things that I can only tell you about.
- I need to know who did this to Scully.
- Which you can have.
- What you may find is much more than that.
- What?
What you want most desperately of all.
The cure for Scully's cancer?
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
- Communication Center, please.
- One moment.
- Communications. Holly.
- It's Dana Scully.
Dana, I'm so sorry about
what's happened. I just heard.
I need your help on something. I was hoping
that you could help with some information.
- Sure. What do you need?
- I have some calls placed to the Bureau,
on the sixth, seventh, eighth,
ninth and tenth.
They came in to the PBX operator.
The first was at 11:21.
The next at 11:14, 3:07,
2202 and 5212.
They would have all gone
to the same extension.
- And you're looking for that extension?
- Yes.
I got five calls matching the times and dates
transferred to an executive-level extension.
- Whose?
- It could be anyone at that level.
Would Assistant Director Skinner
be at that extension?
Yes.
- Thank you.
- OK. You take care now, Dana.
(Phone)
Yes?
- (man) Special Agent Scully?
- Yes.
This is Dr Vitagliano at the Paleoclimatology
Department at American University.
You'd asked me to look into
these ice-core samples for you.
Right. I'm sorry that I
haven't gotten back to you.
You might wanna come down to the lab.
There's something I know you're
gonna want to see for yourself.
- What am I looking for?
- Level four is a biological quarantine wing.
It houses a series of labs
and medical facilities
in an elaborate system for the
storage of vast quantities of DNA.
- DNA from whom?
- Virtually every American born since 1945.
Every immigrant, every indigenous person
who's given blood to a government doctor.
This is what I told you. This is the
hoax into which you've been drawn.
The roots go back 50 years
to the end of World War ll.
Playing on a national
appetite for bogus revelation
and a public newly fearful
of the atom bomb,
the US military command fanned the flames
of what were called "flying saucer" stories.
There are truths which can kill a nation.
The military needed something to deflect
attention away from its arms strategy:
global domination through the
capability of total enemy annihilation.
The nuclear card was fine
if we alone could play it,
but the generals knew they could
not win a public-relations war.
Those photos from Hiroshima were not
faces Americans wanted to see in a mirror.
Oppenheimer knew it,
but we silenced him.
When the Russians developed the bomb,
the fear in the military was for armistice.
The business of America
isn't business, it's war.
Since Antietam nothing has
driven the economy faster.
We needed a reason
to keep spending money.
If there wasn't a war,
we called it war anyway.
The Cold War was essentially
a 50-year public-relations battle,
a pitched game of chicken against
an enemy we only called names.
The Communists called us
a few names, too.
"We will bury you", Khrushchev said.
The public believed it. After what McCarthy
had done, they ate it with a big spoon.
We squared off a few times,
in Cuba, Korea and Vietnam.
- Nobody dropped the bomb. Nobody dared.
- What has this to do with flying saucers?
The US military saw a good thing
in '47 when the Roswell story broke.
The more we denied it, the more people
believed it was true. Aliens had landed:
a made-to-order cover story for generals
looking to develop the national war chest.
They opened investigations called Grudge,
Twinkle, Project "Blue Book", Majestic 12.
They brought in professors, congressmen,
fed them enough bogus facts, fuzzy photos
and eyewitnesses that they believed it, too.
They'd even hooked
Doug MacArthur, for God's sake.
I can't tell you how fortuitous
the timing was.
You know when the first
supersonic flight was? 1947.
Soon every experimental aircraft
being flown was a UFO sighting.
When the abduction stories
started up, it was too perfect.
We'd almost gotten caught in Korea,
a misstep. China and the Soviets knew it.
The UN got heated up.
Germ warfare. We were
accused of using it on the Koreans.
It was developmental, nothing like
what we and the Russians have now.
The bio-weapons used in the Gulf War were
so ingenious as to be almost undetectable.
- Developed right in this very building.
- And these abductions, they've been lies?
Not lies, exactly. But citizens
taken unsuspecting and tested.
A classified military project
above top-secret and still ongoing.
You've heard the recent denials about
Roswell by the military and the CIA?
What's been the effect? Even
wilder and more widespread belief.
The American appetite
for bogus revelation.
But I've seen aliens.
I've witnessed these things.
You've seen what they wanted you to see.
The line between science and science fiction
doesn't exist. This is about control,
of the very elements of life - DNA.
Yours, mine, everyone's.
Then why a hoax?
Why create hard evidence,
an alien body that could be disproved?
The body you found
was so good, so believable,
that only a scientific examination
would have proven the fraud.
Scully would have known.
The hoax was planned so that Agent Scully
wouldn't be alive to do an examination.
You went along with all this.
You let them do this to Scully.
I paid the price, Agent Mulder.
When my son came back sick from
the Gulf War, that was my retribution.
I'm helping you now, but not unselfishly.
Do you believe there's
a cure for him in here, too?
I have to think there is.
(Dew)
Michael Kritschgau, may we talk to you?
- What about?
- DOD is detaining you for questioning.
Would you come with us, Mr Kritschgau?
Sir?
I was told that you needed to see me.
That there was some urgency.
- It seems I've been left out of the loop.
- Left out?
You were watching Mulder.
You had a man on him.
No one bothered to inform me of this.
I know nothing about a man.
I will not be cut out like this!
You need my expertise.
Is this being run from DOD?
If it is, I'm unaware of it.
I've always kept Mulder in check.
I put this whole thing together.
I created Mulder.
Agent Mulder is dead.
Our FBI source confirmed it this morning.
Mulder killed himself.
Mulder was an asset. Without his partner,
we may have underestimated his fragility.
I've never underestimated Mulder.
I still don't.
As you'd asked, I've tested
some of the cellular material
found in the ice-core sample.
Because we couldn't identify it
as either plant or animal,
only as some kind of chimeric hybrid,
I put some of the cells in media
containing foetal bovine serum.
The cells began to divide.
Then they were animal cells that you found.
- They are not classifiable.
- You said there was mitotic cell division.
When the cells began to divide
they didn't just multiply.
They began to go through the
stages of morula, blastula, gastrula.
- They began somatic development?
- The beginning of a life form.
Growing into what... I don't know.
(Mulder) I had come here
looking for answers,
hoping not only to lay bare this conspiracy
against the country and the men behind it,
but to finally learn the truth about the
possibility of intelligent extraterrestrial life.
Now, with what I've heard, my beliefs
seem more and more improbable.
The possibility of a cure for Scully
somewhere inside these walls,
my only hope.
But if I might find it and somehow save her,
the very existence of this cure
would mean with certainty
that I have believed in a lie from the start.
(Click)
(Scully) I had no way to reach Agent Mulder,
to tell him what I had discovered:
an unidentified microscopic life form,
whose very existence held
the possibility of revelation.
Was this organism, extracted from the ice
which had entombed the alien corpse,
the germ cell that might give
proof of extraterrestrial life?
Or was it just the opposite: the scientifically
engineered creation of a chimera,
an unclassifiable biological product
designed to set up a hoax,
manufactured to create the false beliefs
that have long driven Agent Mulder?
I now began to realise
that the answer to this question
might exist within the life form itself.
Biological proof of its connection
to the cancer invading my body,
to a virus living inside this organism
to which I had been exposed
during my abduction three years ago.
- I'm not sure what you hope to find.
- I need to do a Southern blot,
to run the culture that you
showed me against my own DNA.
You said that the unclassified cells
you saw were full of virus.
Right. What are you looking for?
A match. And I need it before seven.
Tonight?
Not gonna happen. Not unless
we have a blazing-hot probe.
It's got to happen.
Everything in my life depends on it.
- What are you doing?
- I was gonna ask you the same.
No, you weren't. You followed me here.
Why are you following me? Is this more
dirty work you're doing for the DOD?
Why don't you tell me
what you're doing here?
- I want an answer from you.
- I want an answer from you!
- This isn't your job!
- My job is to direct the agents under me.
To question their motives when
they're lying about investigations.
To take steps to cease
or censure those actions.
- Your lying is on record.
- And what about yours?
I have the pathology and forensics reports
for the body found in Mulder's apartment.
Now, you have to answer
for yourself in five hours.
As you compound the lies, you
compound the consequences for them.
All lies lead to the truth. Isn't that right?
And what about your lie, Agent Scully?
What does it lead to?
The truth. About the men
behind what happened to me.
About my abduction and the tests.
About being exposed to
something against my will.
About being put on a table and
having something implanted in me,
then having my memory stolen,
only to have it returned along with
a disease I was given.
Is that yourjustification? Is that
what you'll tell the joint panel tonight?
- Are you afraid of that?
- Well, considering the dead man
was murdered in cold blood and you
wilfully misidentified him, yes, I am afraid.
- But I'm only afraid for you.
- You're gonna use that against me.
You're gonna use me as I've been
used all along, to preserve the lies.
Where is Agent Mulder?
Your silence won't save you.
Not with these people. And if you lie,
I don't know if anything can.
Except proof.
(Scully) The cruellest ironies are those
consecrated by the passage of time,
chanced and occasioned
by shocking discovery.
I had joined Mulder on the X-Files because
of my background in the medical sciences.
My assignment was to question his work,
to debunk his investigations and
rein him back into the FBI mainstream.
Now, as fate would have it,
I am calling on these very same skills
to prove that he has been
the target of a scheme
orchestrated by someone
close to us in the FBI.
Someone we have trusted above all others,
involved in a highly organised plot to keep
a dangerous secret from the light of day.
I could only guess at what Agent Mulder
may have uncovered on his own,
what he may have found to confirm or deny
what he has long held to be a conspiracy
to control the public inquiry
into the government's knowledge
and contact with an alien race or races.
If he had hoped, as I do,
to learn the identity of those
who sought to destroy us,
I had, with the discovery of
this unidentified microorganism,
what could amount to forensic evidence.
Hard and undeniable genetic evidence
of a connection between the conspirators
and the cancer which has now
metastasised in my bloodstream.
(Dew)
I have few short hours
to conduct these tests
before I must appear before
an FBI panel to explain myself.
And as I am ready to lie to them
about Agent Mulder,
I am also ready to confront them with proof.
Proof extracted from this tiny organism
that could blow open a conspiracy
of global consequence.
(Mulder) If Scully and I were led to believe
that the conspiracy meant to destroy us
has its roots in the Department of Defense,
that fact seems all but irrefutable now.
I had entered a storage facility by a hallway
connecting underground to the Pentagon.
On hundreds of shelves are materials
that reveal nothing
of the cure for Scully's cancer.
And now, as I have reached
the terminus of this space,
what appears to be an old filing system
seems my only hope of finding what this
man Kritschgau has assured me exists.
If his own desperate hope for
his son's cure has eluded him,
I now share his desperation.
But among these drawers
is a sign, a glimmer,
some small confirmation that
the journey which has brought me here
has not been in vain.
(Phone)
Yes?
I had orders to contact you if
Scott Ostelhoff entered the building.
- Is he there?
- His key card was scanned at level four.
He used the subterranean access
to breach the Pentagon.
- Are you sure it's him?
- I can't ascertain that.
- Do you want me to apprehend him?
- Don't do or say anything.
I'm on my way.
(Scully) If my work with Agent Mulder
has tested the foundation of my beliefs,
science has been, and continues
to be, my guiding light.
Now I am again relying on its familiar and
systematic methods to arrive at a truth,
a fact that might explain
the fate that has befallen me.
An investigation that began without,
now turning within.
Taking cellular material
from the unidentified life form
and isolating a virus contained within it,
then matching the DNA from this virus
against that which I believe
has caused my cancer,
I hope a picture will develop.
A picture that might confirm
my darkest suspicions
about the source of this
disease invading my body,
in hope of providing evidence
that its cause is not without blame,
even though its cure remains unknown.
If science serves me to these ends,
it is not lost on me that the tool which
I have come to depend on absolutely
cannot save or protect me,
but only bring into focus
the darkness that lies ahead.
There it is.
I don't understand.
My DNA hybridised with the
viral DNA from the cell culture.
But that means the material
from the ice-core sample...
You'd have to have DNA from the
unclassified chimera cells in your own body.
- I know.
- But how? And how did you know?
I believe that I was exposed to this material
and it is responsible for giving me an illness.
What kind of illness?
One which cannot be cured.
(Mulder) If I had the cure for Scully's cancer,
I was now as dependent
on her as she was on me.
As I had breached this facility,
I needed to find my way out to safety,
depending on Scully to weave her story,
to tell her tale, to make them believe the lie.
- (Blevins) Agent Scully, please have a seat.
- Thank you.
Agent Scully, we've had a brief discussion,
but will you restate the matter
we're here to put to rest?
Yes, sir.
Four years ago,
Section Chief Blevins assigned me
to a project you all know as the X-Files.
As I am a medical doctor,
with a background in hard science,
my job was to provide
an analytical perspective
on the work of Special Agent Fox Mulder,
whose investigations into the paranormal
were fuelled by a personal belief
that his sister had been abducted
by aliens when he was 12.
I come here today, four years later...
to report on the illegitimacy
of Agent Mulder's work.
That it is my scientific opinion
that he became, through the
course of these years, a victim...
a victim of his own false hopes
and of his belief in the biggest of lies.
You were contacted by a man who claimed
he worked for the Department of Defense,
a Michael Kritschgau, who told you
that Mulder had been taken in by a hoax.
Yes, sir.
He told me a story
which detailed, point by point,
the systematic way in which Agent Mulder
had been deceived and used.
And how I, as his partner,
had been led down the same path,
losing a family member
due to my allegiance
and contracting a fatal disease,
which I was being told was engineered by
the men responsible for Mulder's deception.
(Blevins) Could you
convince Mulder of this?
What I couldn't tell Agent Mulder,
what I had only just learned myself,
was that the cancer, diagnosed in me
several months earlier, had metastasised.
And the doctors told me, short of a miracle,
it would continue to
aggressively invade my body,
advancing faster each day
towards the inevitable.
(door opens)
(Dew)
- I'll have Security stop him at the entrance.
- No, it's OK. Let him go.
Early this morning,
I got a call from the police, asking me
to come to Agent Mulder's apartment.
The detective asked me...
He needed me to identify a body.
Agent Scully...
Agent Mulder died late last night
from an apparent self-inflicted
gunshot wound to the head.
(door opens)
(Blevins) Agent Scully, these
accusations that you've made...
- You've been given a disease...
- Yes, sir.
They're extremely serious charges.
Yes, sir, but I have proof...
against the men behind this,
of the lies that I believed.
What I have here is proof undeniable
that the men who gave me this disease
were also behind the hoax:
a plot designed to lead to
Agent Mulder's demise, and to my own,
planned and executed
by someone in this room.
What I have here
is scientific evidence...
You.
Somebody get a doctor.
What? What is it?
It's de-ionised water.
It's nothing more than that.
Visiontext Subtitles: Adrian Isaac
(Child) I made this!