Can you help me?
I'm looking for a woman...
Excuse“.
Excuse me, I'm looking for a Dana Scully.
Was a Dana...? Sc...?
Excuse me, I'm looking for Dana Scully.
Is she a patient here? Dana Scully?
Is there an admitting nurse here?
- Can somebody help me?!
- You'll have to calm down, sir.
I will calm down when somebody gives me
a reason to! I'm looking for a patient.
- Dana Scully. I heard you the first time.
- Where is she?
- In the ICU.
- Where is that?
- Tell me who you are.
- Where is she?!
Agent Mulder.
- Where are you going?
- ICU.
- You move good for a dead man.
- I'm half dead.
You got a lot to answer for, Agent Mulder!
- You guys hold here.
- Yes, sir.
What happened to her?
She went into hypovolemic shock.
She's lost a lot of blood.
Due to what?
- Due to what?
- She's dying.
- Let's go.
- Let go of me.
- There's nothing you...
- Get off!
Don't do this! Don't make me
put you under arrest! Don't!
I'm somewhat at a loss here
in going forward.
This situation developing unexpectedly
during a formal inquiry
into your reported death, Agent Mulder -
the fact of your being here today,
very much alive, gives the effect
of reshaping this investigation
into something altogether different,
as we are now put upon
to verify the identity of this body
found in your apartment
and the circumstances which led to this.
Care to enlighten us
on these circumstances?
Are you suggesting I can?
Agent Mulder, we're here informally
to give you the chance to help yourself.
Help myself how?
By allowing any facts or details
which might serve to let us go forward
with this inquiry
in a more informed manner.
- That helps you. How does that help me?
- Agent Mulder,
this is going to become
a murder investigation.
Criminal charges are going to be made.
We have only one other suspect.
She may no longer be able to testify
on her own behalf.
Agent Scully lied to us. Why?
Who's protecting whom, Agent Mulder?
Your choice is your own but your failure
to answer will reflect poorly on the record.
Are we finished, then?
Word of advice from a friend.
Keep playing it the way you are.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Now you need all the help you can get.
Should have mentioned that
when you hauled my ass off.
I saved your ass, Agent Mulder.
I've withheld forensic evidence
about the body found on your floor.
Until you showed up I was
the one keeping your secret.
I had no choice but to bring you in.
Scully'll verify all of that.
That's a good place to lay it
considering her condition.
You want me to lay it
where it belongs, Agent Mulder?
Pathology turned up two
gunshot wounds to the dead man,
one fired point-blank
through the left temple,
the second a postmortem wound to
the face to remove the man's identity.
Now, I'd be happy to verify
the ballistics on that first shot.
How can you help me?
Tell me why Scully lied for you.
The disease she has was given to her
by somebody connected to the FBI.
To a mole working here.
Who?
I failed to find that out, sir.
You don't want to forget who
your friends are, Agent Mulder,
to remember who you can trust.
(man) What are the appropriate
limits of human knowledge?
(2nd man) I don't think there are any
appropriate limits to human knowledge.
As long as science is done
openly and with free will,
then I don't think there are any limits.
- Senator Kennedy.
- Dr Beaumont,
you've stated that the cloning of humans
would be ill-considered
and difficult to accomplish.
Can you expand on
what you see as the biggest
technical obstacle to human cloning?
I trust you've heard.
Mulder is alive.
As I said, he's not to be underestimated.
Yes, as you said.
Though I hear he has you to thank
in some part for his new freedom.
Using a stolen ID,
Mulder was able to get into
the Advanced Research Projects Facility.
- And you allowed him to escape.
- Yes.
We're too vulnerable.
Our man in the FBI is exposed.
What Mulder may have seen
could expose our plans.
What Mulder's seen only serves us.
Serves to insure our plans.
Mulder is in trouble.
He needs help. We can give it to him.
In exchange for...?
His new loyalty. To us.
As I've said all along, Mulder's
much more valuable to us alive.
You can proceed now.
What are you doing here?
I heard you were being moved out of ICU
and you were feeling better.
- Somebody's gonna see you.
- It's OK.
I'm officially among the undead.
What happened?
I didn't come here to talk about that.
Mulder, don't try and protect me.
- I need to know.
- There's not much to talk about anyway.
I'm gonna testify everything I know
in front of the FBI assembly.
The conspiracy, the men behind it,
what I believe is its purpose.
- Did you find out who in the FBI is involved?
- No. But that doesn't matter now.
- Yes, it does.
- Hey, Scully. How about those Yankees?
Mulder, Skinner has evidence against you.
He knows you killed that man
they found in your apartment.
Yeah. Skinner is withholding it.
Mulder, Skinner's dirty. He's not your friend.
I'm almost certain that
he's the man inside on this.
- I don't believe that.
- If you testify he will use it to ruin you.
No, not Skinner.
He's been in a position to know everything
that we've done over the past four years.
But if I don't testify now
they'll start to bury the truth.
Well, then you have to lay it on me.
You have to tell them
I was the one who killed that man.
I can't. I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
Mulder, if I can save you, let me.
Let me at least give some meaning
to what's happened to me.
- Dana? Hi, Fox.
- Hi, Mrs Scully.
- I hope I'm not interrupting.
- No, I was just on my way out.
Hi, I'm Fox Mulder.
I don't think we've ever met.
I'm Bill Scully.
I'm sorry about your sister.
- Mr Mulder?
- Yeah?
I know something about you.
About what Dana's been through with you.
So let's leave the work away from here, OK?
Let her die with dignity.
Please tell me you're here
with severe chest pains.
You should be glad for why I'm here.
To pay you some respect.
- Go to hell.
- For your cleverness and your resource.
- What you've managed to do for Scully.
- What are you talking about?
Well, breaching the security
at the Defense Department facility.
- Finding a cure for her disease.
- What I found was useless.
On the contrary.
It's essential to her survival.
If you like, we could step outside
and I might explain myself.
I'm here tonight as a friend, Agent Mulder.
He promised me that it'd be in here.
(Frohike) I'll be damned.
I never thought what
the de-ionised water might be for.
Who knew we were looking for a microchip?
This is a cure for cancer?
It may be for Scully's.
- How?
- Shortly after she was abducted
she discovered a small metallic chip
implanted subcutaneously in her neck.
It was just a short time after she had
it removed that she developed cancer.
- It's unreal.
- Too freakin' amazing.
Watch your language, Frohike.
Grab me some tweezers.
Mr Kritschgau, thank you for being here
and for cooperating with this investigation.
We hope you can provide information
that will allow us to make formal charges
for the murder of Defense
employee Scott Ostelhoff.
Mr Kritschgau, we have learned
that you were in contact
with Agents Mulder and Scully
just prior to this man's death.
That's correct.
And that you may have given
them classified information.
What motivated this?
My knowledge of government involvement
in a conspiracy against
the American people.
Now, before... before we go
into any specifics on that subject,
I'd like to ask you a more pointed question.
Do you know who killed Scott Ostelhoff?
No, I don't.
Do you know of any connection between
his death and Agents Mulder or Scully?
No.
I'm aware of one death
in connection, though.
My son, who died early this morning.
Mr Kritschgau, you are employed by
the Department of Defense. Is that correct?
Technically.
Part of my remuneration
has come from another source.
A congressional lobbying firm.
Something called Roush.
Roush. Any idea what that is?
No, sir.
This is crazy. Just crazy.
In what sense? In that it might
save your sister's life?
You're not a doctor. You have no place
even suggesting this science fiction.
- It's not science fiction.
- He's never heard of it!
Bill.
Have you?
No, I haven't.
I think there's an obvious
difference of opinion here.
I think... that everybody here
has their heart in the right place.
- But I need it to be my decision.
- Dana...
I know you're only looking out for me, Bill.
But I don't think you have all the facts.
Shouldn't you listen to your doctor?
Yes. I am.
Would she have to stop
the conventional treatment?
To be honest, at this point,
the only approach I have left with her
particular cancer is quite unconventional.
I'd like to try this.
You really believe this crap, don't you?
Yes, I do.
See, she's your big defender
but... I think the truth is,
she just doesn't want to disappoint you.
If it works, I don't care
what you think she thinks.
You're a real piece of work. You know that?
Why's that? Because I don't
think the way you think?
Because I won't just sit passively back
and watch the family tragedy unfold?
You're the reason for it.
And I've already lost one sister
to this quest you're on.
Now I'm losing another.
Has it been worth it?
To you, I mean. Have you found
what you've been looking for?
- No.
You know how that makes me feel?
In a way, I think I do.
I lost someone very close to me.
I lost a sister. I lost my father.
All because of this thing I'm looking for.
These what? Little green aliens?
Yeah.
Little green aliens.
You're one sorry son of a bitch.
Not a whole lot more to say.
(phone rings)
One sorry son of a bitch speaking.
How's our patient?
You did find the chip,
didn't you, Agent Mulder?
Yes.
I can imagine there was some question
as to its medical value.
Well, there still is.
And so I have yet to earn your trust,
in spite of my gesture.
You could say that, yeah.
I have something else to offer you.
I've arranged a meeting I think
you'll want to attend, Mr Mulder.
Tabasco. Cures anything.
I'll keep that in mind.
You know him or something?
I think that's my sister.
Samantha?
I was afraid I'd never see you again.
He always told me something
had happened to you that night.
Who? Who told you that?
My father.
I never really knew what happened.
I could never put the...
memories all back together.
But as much as I tried to remember,
I tried more to forget.
- Why?
- I was eight years old
and frightened to death...
and they told me that I was an orphan.
But you call that man your father.
Some time later - I don't know how long -
my foster parents took me to a hotel room
and said that I was gonna see my father.
- But you knew who your father was.
- I thought I knew.
But... he told me that it had all been a secret
and that he and Mom hadn't
told anyone, to protect the family.
- And you believe that?
- He was so kind to me.
And he was the only one I could
remember from before what happened.
You don't remember
anything about that night?
I remember... you.
I remember something...
Men and... and then nothing.
I can help you.
You were abducted, Samantha.
I can help you to remember.
I don't want to, Fox.
I don't.
Then why come here at all?
My father told me that he'd found you
and you wanted to see me very badly.
That you'd been looking
for me for a long time.
Is that true?
I'm so sorry, Fox.
And I wish that I'd known how to find you.
What you've been told...
I want you to listen to me, OK?
What you've been told by
that man... may not be true.
Why do you say that?
Because the man that brought you here has
known where I've been for a very long time.
I don't understand.
- Why wouldn't he tell me?
- I don't know.
But I think he's kept a lot of things from you.
I don't believe you.
He's been a good father to me.
He's given me a life and he cared
for me when there was no one else.
I want you to come with me.
Come with me to see Mom.
- Mom is alive?
- Yes.
And I know she'd like
to see you very, very much.
- I can't.
- Why not?
This is too much.
I didn't wanna come here at all, Fox.
I was afraid to see you.
- I have another life now. I have children.
- No. Please don't go.
- I can't stay here.
- Tell me how I can find you.
- I need some time.
- Tell me where to find you.
Please don't, Fox.
We will do this on your time. Just...
Then please...
please let me go.
I promise you I'll think about it.
You doing OK?
Mm. Either it's my head
or I'm a long way from med school
but I can't remember what
you're injecting me with.
Fluorodeoxyglucose.
Deoxyglucose.
If you're making any progress I'm hoping
it might show up first in a PET scan.
You're not holding your breath, are you?
I'm going after your cancer
as aggressively as I know how, Dana.
If I can jump-start your immune system,
if I can get your cytolytic cells to recognise
your tumour as something to attack,
then there's a chance.
Have you ever witnessed
a miracle, Dr Zuckerman?
I don't know that I have.
But I have seen people make recoveries,
come back from so far gone
I can't explain it.
Isn't that a miracle?
Maybe they are miracles,
but I don't dare call them that.
Thank you.
My apologies for the... rather
hasty departure last night.
- What do you want from me?
- Want from you?
You give me these things,
the only things I ever wanted
and I can't think of any
reason for you to do so.
That's true. No act is completely selfless.
But I've come today not to ask but to offer.
To offer you the truth that
you've so desperately sought.
About the project and about the men
who've conspired to protect it.
I know the truth.
- Do you?
- I spoke to one of your men.
- You know he's not lying?
- I've seen enough to know he's not.
- You've seen but scant pieces of the whole.
- What more can you show me?
This man you spoke to,
Michael Kritschgau...
He has deceived you with beautiful lies.
He's told you everything you believe
about the existence of extraterrestrial life
is untrue.
And what are you saying?
As I said, I'm offering you
a chance to know the truth.
- In exchange for what?
- Quit the FBI. Come work for me.
I can make your problems go away.
No deal.
After all I've given you.
What have you given me?
A claim of a cure for Scully?
Is she cured? You show me
my sister only to take her back.
- You've given me nothing.
- I intend to keep my promises.
- I just need something from you.
- You murdered my father.
You killed Scully's sister
and if Scully dies I will kill you.
I don't care whose father you are.
I will put you down.
You're certainly capable, so I've been told.
I understand you have a hearing tomorrow
where you'll have to testify to
these murderous impulses of yours.
When you reconsider, the offer still stands.
Dana?
Dr Zuckerman called. He...
he said that you wanted to see me.
What is it?
I'm so sorry.
I fight and I fight and I fight
but I've been so stupid.
What? What is it?
I've come so far in my life on simple faith.
And now when I need it
the most I just push it away.
I mean, why... why do I wear this?
Why do I wear this, Mom?
I put something that I don't even know
or understand under the skin of my neck.
I will subject myself
to these crazy treatments
and I keep telling myself that I'm doing
everything I can but it's a lie.
You have not lost your faith, Dana.
But I have, in a way.
When you asked... when you asked Father
McCue to dinner to minister to my faith
I just closed off to him.
What's important now...
is that you save your energy.
I'm not getting better, Mom.
You don't know that yet.
The PET scan showed no improvement.
I know you're afraid.
I know you're afraid to tell me
but you have to tell someone.
I'll make a statement right here.
Cloning will continue.
The human mind will continue
to inquire into this.
Human cloning will take place
and it'll take place in my lifetime.
I think it's right and proper
that we continue this kind of inquiry.
I think there will be untold benefits
for humankind in the future.
Turn on your television.
Are you watching the hearings?
Do you see who's there? He's
gathering information for who?
I just wanna make that statement.
I came to ask a question.
Our colleague was supposed
to have fixed the FBI problem.
He will fix it now. Do you understand me?
Then I will fix it for good.
Agent Mulder, please take a seat.
Something urgently important
has come to the fore.
As you're set to testify
on your own behalf later,
I have received alarming forensic evidence
from the body found in your apartment.
I have in my hand ballistic data matching
your service weapon, Agent Mulder.
- Where did you get that?
- I'm not at liberty to say.
But unless you can offer up someone else
who might have fired the kill shot
everything points to you
as this man's murderer.
Are you prepared to give testimony
you're not the man who fired the shot?
Why am I here?
The man worked for
the Department of Defense.
The man was spying on me.
Do you know for whom?
Agent Scully was prepared
to name the man at the FBI
who was involved in this plot
against you and her.
We believe she was going
to name Assistant Director Skinner,
whom we have learned has been working
inside the FBI with a secret agenda.
I refuse to believe that.
We've accumulated substantial
evidence against him.
- Can you show it to me?
- Agent Mulder,
if you name this man today in your
testimony, we can file charges against him.
Charges which may very well
exonerate you.
Name Skinner and save myself.
That's what I called you here
to recommend, as a friend.
I'll see you at the hearing.
Morning.
What are you doing here?
You have a hearing.
Yeah. I came by last night but
I didn't have the heart to wake you.
Came by for what?
Mulder, what is it?
I was lost last night.
But as I stood here
I thought I'd found my way.
I've been, uh...
I've been offered a deal. A deal
that could save my life, in a way.
Though I'd refused the deal earlier,
I left here last night with my mind
made up to take it.
A deal with who?
It doesn't matter. I'm not taking
the deal. I'm not taking any deal.
Not after what happened this morning.
What happened this morning?
Section Chief Blevins directed me
to implicate Skinner.
To name him as the man inside at the FBI
who may have deceived us both.
And if I name him they'll protect me.
Are you going to name him?
No.
Then they'll prosecute you.
Yeah. They have evidence against me.
They know I killed that man.
Even with the ballistics evidence,
I can still be the...
Scully, I can't let you take the blame.
Because of your brother,
because of your mother,
and because I couldn't live with it.
To live the lie, you have to believe it,
like these men who deceive us,
who gave you this disease.
We all have our faith
and mine is in the truth.
Then, why did you come here if
you'd already made up your mind?
Because I knew you'd talk me out
of it if I was making a mistake.
You'll be in my prayers.
Have your father say
a few Hail Mulders for me, OK?
If he's a no-show I'm gonna
ask for a bench warrant.
Sorry I'm late.
Agent Mulder,
the members of this review panel first
convened to address your reported death
only to find shortly
that this report had been a lie,
that you were indeed very much alive
and that the body found in your apartment,
believed to be yours, was a murder victim,
killed with a weapon issued by
the FBI and registered to you.
Respectfully, sir, I have come
to set the record straight
so that this process you've begun can be
completed and the guilty parties named.
I'd like to ask for a short break.
I'm ready to proceed, please, sir.
Go on, Agent Mulder.
Four years ago, while working on an
assignment outside the FBI mainstream,
I was paired
with Special Agent Dana Scully,
who I believed was sent to spy on me,
to debunk my investigations
into the paranormal.
That she did not follow these orders
is a testament to her integrity
as an investigator,
a scientist and a human being.
She has paid dearly for this integrity.
Agent Mulder,
Agent Scully lied straight-faced
to this panel about your death.
She lied because I asked her to,
because I had evidence of a conspiracy.
A conspiracy against the American people.
We've heard testimony to these allegations.
A conspiracy intended to destroy the lives
of those who would reveal its true purpose:
to conduct experiments on unwitting
victims to further a secret agenda
for someone within government operating
at levels without restraint or responsibility,
without morals or conscience, men who
pretend to honour as they deceive,
the price of this betrayal - the lives
and reputations of those deceived.
Agent Scully... is lying in a hospital bed
right now diagnosed with terminal cancer,
a victim of these same tests, conducted
without her knowledge or consent
by these men who, as they try
to cover their tracks,
who suborn and persecute the people
they've used in their plot,
I will now call by name.
Agent Mulder, did you or did you not shoot
the man found dead in your apartment?
I will answer that question.
Did you shoot Scott Ostelhoff,
employee of the Department of Defense?
I will answer that question, sir.
(Senior Agent) Answer the question.
- I will answer after I name the man.
- Agent Mulder.
I will answer that question
after I name the man
who is responsible for Agent Scully,
the man who directed that my
apartment be surveilled by the DOD,
a man I want to see prosecuted for his
crimes, who is sitting in this very room.
The section chief has asked you
a question. You are going to answer.
- I can't do that, sir.
- You can and you will.
I can't do that, sir, because the section chief
is the man I'm about to name.
The Smoking Man is dead.
- How?
- Shot through his window.
Forensics found it at the scene.
- We're assuming it's his blood.
- Assuming?
No body was found,
though there was too much blood loss
for anyone to have survived.
This afternoon when you named
Blevins... how did you know?
- I didn't. I just guessed.
- That's a hell of a guess.
Blevins had been paid for four years by
a biotechnology company called Roush,
which is somehow connected to all this.
I'm sure whatever connections
there were are being erased.
They're cleaning up,
taking everything away.
Not everything.
Scully's cancer's gone into remission.
That's unbelievable news.
- It's the best news I could have ever heard.
- What turned it around?
I don't know. I don't think we'll ever know.
- Can I see her?
- Yeah. She's with her family.
But I'm sure she'd love to see you.
Visiontext Subtitles: Abigail Smith