[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[DISTANT ENGINES WHIRRING]
[DOORBELL BEEPS]
[DOOR BUZZES]
[DISTANT ENGINES ROARING]
[DOOR HINGE SQUEAKS]
- How ya goin', mate?
- Good, mate. Yourself?
Good. Come in.
- You know Gaz.
- Hey, mate. How are ya?
- How's it going?
- Hey, yeah. Good.
[DOOR THUDS]
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER SPEAKING]
So, ah, what's going on?
How do you feel about
doin' a bit of drivin'?
Sure, what's the deal?
There's a bloke out at Cabramatta.
Vietnamese bloke.
Drug dealer.
He's got a shitload of drugs
and cash lying around and
we're gonna relieve him of it.
Cool. Whereabouts?
You know the old commission
flats on Church Street?
Yeah. So...
what's the plan?
Well, me and Gaz are gonna go and
rip him off.
You're gonna drive.
[CHUCKLES]
Cool.
- In and out.
- Cool.
You want a beer?
Yeah, love one.
- You want another one?
- Bloody oath.
Oh yeah, of course.
Hey, ah, where's your dunny?
- Straight through, mate.
- Cheers, mate.
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER SPEAKING]
[LIGHT CLICKS]
[DOOR THUDS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[PHONE KEYPAD BEEPS]
Beautiful!
Gold!
[SINISTER MUSIC]
[LOUD SPLASH]
Fuck.
[SLOSHING, DRIPPING]
[INDISTINCT]
Yes!
Fuckin' good goal!
Good goal.
[PHONE SNAPS SHUT]
[TOILET FLUSHING]
Hey, ah, I might get some smokes.
You guys want anything?
Yeah, grab some chewy.
What kind?
Juicy Fruit.
Ray?
You hungry?
Yeah.
- Dimmies?
- Dimmies.
How many dimmies?
Half a dozen?
Half a dozen. Six.
Mm-hmm.
Easy.
- Beautiful.
- Half a dozen.
Be right back.
- All right.
- Righto.
[DOOR THUDS]
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[COINS JINGLING]
[DIAL TONE RINGING]
[DIAL TONE TRILLING]
Detective Roberts.
Hello?
Mm.
So.
Jack, or a dog?
Jack.
How'd you know?
I didn't.
I just wanted to make sure
you got soya sauce for the dimmies.
[DOOR HINGE SQUEAKS]
[SPORTS ANNOUNCER SPEAKING]
What's going on?
We got a problem.
[DOOR THUDS]
One of us is a cop.
I fuckin' knew it.
I...
What's the matter, mate?
You look a bit worried.
Hmm?
You should be fucking worried.
What are we gonna do?
Go for a drive.
Good idea.
[HINGE SQUEAKS]
After you, mate.
[DOOR THUDS]
[GARAGE DOOR CREAKS]
[ENGINE HUMS]
I got nothing on you guys.
I haven't got nothing on you.
You let me go now,
and nothing'll happen to you.
I swear to God.
[DOOR THUDS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[AMBIENT MUSIC SWELLS]
♪ ♪
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
[TIRES CRUNCHING GRAVEL]
Mate, my guys know I'm with you.
So where are they?
Well, I didn't have a car on me
but if I go missing,
they're gonna come looking for you.
So what's your real name?
It's Nick.
Get out.
Get... out.
[DOOR THUDS]
The fuck you doing, Ray?
For what it's worth, I don't feel great
- about this...
- Just fuck off, will you?
[DOOR THUDS]
We can't just let him go.
You wanna kill him?
I think we should.
Yeah, and then we got the
cops up both our arses,
mate, no thanks.
Just try and get it on the side.
Yeah, that was the center, but, anyway,
- good try.
- Nearly.
- Ray.
- What's going on, mate?
Not much.
How are ya, girls?
- Hey.
You wanna give us a second?
- Mm-hmm.
- Sure.
[BALLS CLATTER]
Mate. Beautiful.
You haven't seen Nick, have you?
No, I haven't been able to get onto him.
Hmm?
Yeah, he's probably just busy.
With his other job.
Being a cop.
What are you talking about?
Me and a mate were going to
do a job with him last night
and we caught him trying
to tip off his buddies.
Oh, get the fuck out of here.
Are you fucking kidding me?
He's a cop?
Yes. He's a cop.
Oh, Jesus Christ. What did you do?
We let him go.
What's he got on you?
Oh...
fuck all, really, but, you know.
- Huh?
- Ah.
Think yourself lucky.
I...
Thank you. Thank you.
I owe you big time, my friend.
Yep.
And you still owe me money, too.
Yeah, I do, I do still
owe you that money,
but I'll, ah, have that
to you in another week.
Sure.
- Catch ya, Phil.
- Yeah, see you, mate.
Oi!
Get across. Quick, quick, quick, quick!
Move, move, move! Get over!
Get over. Hurry the fuck up, get across!
Right, bring your hands
over here so I can cuff ya.
Other one, other one, other one.
[ENGINE TURNING OVER]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[ROCK MUSIC RINGTONE PLAYS]
♪ ♪
I'll hang onto that.
So how much would it take for
you to let me go, you reckon?
More than you got.
Well, how much you got, Ray?
More than you're making
on this fuckin' job,
- I'll tell you that much, mate.
- Is that right?
Yeah.
Well, how much more?
162,000 bucks.
Fuck off.
Fair enough.
- Bullshit.
- Alright.
What the fuck are you doing
with that kind of money?
I'm a hard worker.
And where is it, then?
You know who Glen Davis is?
Other side of the Blue Mountains there?
So what's it doing there?
Well, it's not doing much at
the moment, mate, so uh...
might as well go get it, eh?
So what, we go get the money
and then we let you go, Ray.
Is that it?
Yep.
Keep your fucking head down, Ray.
Bobby, get out of the car.
[DOOR THUDS]
- Put your gun away.
- Right.
Not in there, you fucking moron.
So what do you reckon?
[FAINTLY] About what?
You heard what he said.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, so?
So you wanna go and get the money.
Yeah, I wanna go get the fucking money.
Yeah, but we gotta
meet like Davos first.
- And...
- Davros.
- Yeah.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
We'll still do that
after we get the money.
We get the money first,
we drop him off to Davros,
everyone's fucking happy.
Yeah, but... but we gotta...
- to be there, so...
- You just tell Davros
that we run out of fucking petrol.
- He'll be fucking pissed, though, Dave...
- Yeah, no, no,
we'll just tell him it's a fuckin'...
wasn't our fault that the
fuel gauge is fucked.
Yeah, no. I don't know, man.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
It's $160,000. You don't want 80 grand?
Of course. Like...
like 80 grand could come in handy.
- Oh, you fucking think so?
- Yeah.
Imagine the shit you
can buy for 80 grand.
Yeah, a new car would be nice, hey.
Wouldn't it be fucking nice?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
What do you like? You
like Holdens or Fords?
- Holden, mate. Holden.
- Holden?
Yeah.
For 80 grand you could buy a
really fucking nice Holden,
right? A Commodore.
HSV, club sport,
all the bells and whistles.
[MIMICS CAR ENGINE REVVING]
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Are we good?
- So we'll go get the money, eh?
- Yeah.
- Get in the fucking car.
- Right.
[CAR DOORS POPPING]
All right, Ray. This is
what's gonna happen.
We're gonna go get this money.
And then we're gonna let you go.
If that money ain't there,
I don't give a fuck
if it's $20 less than you said it is,
then I'll put a fucking hole in you.
- Fair enough.
Mm-hmm.
[ENGINE ROARS]
Yeah, nah, nah, she's eating
all kinds of crazy shit.
How far along is she?
Eight months.
Boy or a girl?
Boy, thank fuck.
What's wrong with girls?
I got a girl.
Yeah, well, fucking you know.
Better you than me.
So what's the problem?
- So how old's your little girl?
- Eight.
Okay, so, she's eight years of age.
Right now she's really sweet
and she's innocent and all that
but anyway, one day she's gonna grow up,
like she's not gonna be so
fucking sweet and
innocent, you understand?
Well, she's not innocent all the time...
Well, okay.
Most of the time she's
sweet and innocent.
- Right.
- But at some point,
like I said, she's gonna grow up,
and she's gonna...
mate, she's gonna be...
she's gonna be sucking a cock.
Okay?
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Where I'm coming from?
Yeah, I understand where
you're coming from.
And I'll probably kill her first couple
of fucking boyfriends, but...
you get over it, mate.
No, I don't think you
fucking get over it.
- You get over it, mate.
- Yeah.
- Jesus Christ.
- Anyway, fuck,
you can have the girls,
I'll have the boys.
Okay. So what are you going
to call him, anyway?
Quentin James.
[CHUCKLES]
What the fuck is... what is that?
You're worried about
your kid sucking dicks
and you're gonna call the kid Quentin?
Mate, Quentin's a good name.
That was my grandfather's name.
You don't like Quentin?
Yeah, your granddad's name. Was he gay?
No, he wasn't fucking gay.
[LAUGHING]
Why don't you call him
John or something?
Give him a fucking bloke's name.
Quentin is a bloke's name.
A gay bloke's name. Yeah.
- Good one.
- Get fucked.
- [LAUGHS]
- Fuck you.
Name one bloke that you
know called Quentin
who's a blokey bloke.
I don't know any Quentins, all right?
I don't know any Quentins
except my grandfather.
That's one of the reasons I...
it's an original name.
- It's an original, strong fucking name.
- Yeah, right.
Okay, one man from history,
one bloke, in history,
who's a blokey bloke, called Quentin.
[SIGHING] Ah, fuck.
See?
Okay, all right.
Remember... okay, probably
not a blokey bloke
but if you're gonna talk
about, like, courage...
remember that little
fucking Quentin from...
from Willesee? He was in his...
you know, he was
fucking all crumpled up
and fucking the little
blond-haired kid, used
to come on Willesee,
make the fucking cunt cry.
That poor little bastard
couldn't eat a fucking Tim Tam
without breaking his fucking fingers.
- Not a blokey bloke, though...
- Not a blokey bloke, but,
mate, was in a movie, wrote a book,
he fucking... mate,
one year they put him
in a fucking... in a celebrity car race.
They propped him up on
some books and he raced
the fucking car, like
at fucking good speeds.
Hmm. Yeah, no, ah, you know.
I mean he's not a blokey bloke.
I mean you got a point but, yeah.
Yeah, I absolutely got a fucking point.
It's a fucking good, strong name.
Yeah.
- This it here, Ray?
- Hurry up.
Yeah?
- Yeah, back door.
- All right.
Ah, fuck ya.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Yeah, I'm going the best I can, mate.
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOOR THUDS]
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS, BEEPS]
Hey.
Where is it, Ray?
[PANEL THUDS]
We ran out of petrol.
'Cause the fuel gauge
on this car's fucked.
[WHISPERING] Sneaky fuck.
Yeah, so, we...
ah, we're walking into town now,
but I don't know what the town is,
so, yeah.
But as soon as we get some, uh...
So what's the combo, Ray?
Don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
I've got it written down, but...
Where?
At home.
Well, how am I supposed to
open the fucking thing, Ray?
Oxy cutter?
Oxy cutter.
I'll just, what,
pull one out of my arse, will I?
[THUD]
Come here, you.
Come on.
You know, you should have
said something, Ray.
'Cause it's starting to feel like
you're trying to pull some funny shit.
Mate, all you gotta do is
cut the fucking thing open.
I don't know what
you're whingeing about.
No, no, I'm not whingeing, cunt.
Well, it sounds like it.
You gotta go fucking ten
minutes up the road,
go to a hardware store,
get an oxy cutter,
job's done.
Yeah, all I'm telling
you is this, all right?
You better not be trying
to fuck me around.
- That's all I'm saying.
- Yeah, mate, yeah.
I came out and put the
box in the fucking house
just to fuck you around.
Get in.
- You want me to get in there?
- Yep.
Who's whingeing now?
Come on.
Stay in the car.
[DOOR THUDS]
Just that, thanks, mate.
You got eye protection?
No, I'll be all right.
You used one of these before?
No. I'll try not to burn meself.
At least wear a pair of sunnies.
Yeah, all right, mate,
I'll wear sunnies.
- How much, how much?
- 119.
Right. Keep the change.
- You want a receipt?
- No, all good.
Thank you, brother.
What?
Where's the car, Dave?
What did I tell you?
- I just went and got...
- I told you to stay
in the car.
I just went to get smokes.
I just went in to get...
smokes. I run out.
Oh, fuck.
Hey, brother.
- You're back.
- Yeah.
Mate, where are your, ah,
your steel rulers?
- They're in aisle two.
- Thank you.
Scan that, brother.
All right, thank you. Keep
the change, thank you.
Come on, come on. Fuck.
Get the, get the oxy.
Fuckin' moron.
So what are we gonna do, Dave?
Hurry up, fuck ya!
Come on, ya fu...
Get in the car!
- All right.
- Get in the fucking car.
[ENGINE ROARS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Well, how do you reckon
he got out of the boot?
What?
Where do you think he went?
Mate, maybe he's hiding somewhere, eh?
Just shut the fuck up, okay, Bobby?
Just do me a favor and shut up.
- Well, how...
- Shut up.
["HOPING FOR" BY BAD//DREEMS PLAYS]
♪ When my mind's at ease ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When I show up at your door ♪
♪ When I'm not strung out ♪
♪ I can give you what you need ♪
♪ It's what I'm hoping for ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When you lay me out ♪
♪ When I wake up on your floor ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When I'm not strung out ♪
♪ Dead fly's buzzing round my eyes ♪
♪ It's what I'm hoping for ♪