[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
We there yet?
No...
you impatient cunt.
So what's the surprise?
Not telling.
Why not?
'Cause it's a fucking surprise.
That's the whole point of a surprise.
You don't tell the other
person 'cause then it just...
it ruins the surprise.
But I don't like surprises.
Well, you'll fucking like this one.
- Yeah, we'll see.
- You'll like this one.
Yeah, we'll see.
Look the other way.
I didn't come out this far
for you to fuck it up.
Close your eyes. Look the other way.
This better be fucking
good, mate, I tell you.
Just close your eyes.
They're closed.
Put your hands out.
Get fucked.
- Hey?
- Fuck off.
Hey, you like surprises now, hey?
- That's a Sterling.
- No, that's a Patchett.
Patchett?
Better than a Sterling.
Better than the Sten.
Pretty much won us World War II
and it'll blow your fucking head off.
What are you doing with them?
Gonna make some fruit salad.
Stay.
Stay too.
[COUGHING]
You ready?
This is it, mate.
Merry fucking Christmas.
[WATER RUNNING]
All right, I've got another one for you.
Yeah.
Would you rather have
great sex or great food?
- Great food.
- Oh, that's boring.
Well, you gotta eat.
Yeah, but if you're going
to have the great food,
then you gotta have bad sex.
What's bad sex?
Oh, that's the sex I have with you.
Oh... very funny.
All right, if you're gonna
have the great food,
then you've gotta have...
bad sex with like some
stinky, crusty old granny.
I'll have the great sex, then.
Okay, but then you're
gonna have the bad food.
What's bad food?
I don't know. What's a
food you don't like?
Sandwiches.
What do you... who
doesn't like sandwiches?
- I don't fucking like sandwiches.
- What do you mean?
I mean, toasted's all right
but not fucking raw ones.
Well, what is a raw sandwich?
Well, not toasted.
A bit of bread with some shit in it.
Yeah, all right, fine. Okay...
If you're gonna have the great sex then
you have to eat raw sandwiches
for the rest of forever.
How about I eat the sandwiches
while I'm having the great sex?
Yeah, if you want. Sure, why not?
All right, I'll do that then.
Won't even notice.
[LAUGHS]
[HIP HOP MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT RAPPING]
Bobby.
- How you doing?
- Hey.
♪ ♪
- How you doing?
- Yeah, good.
- Ray, Davros.
- How you going, mate?
♪ ♪
So, Ray...
did Freddy explain why
I wanted to see you?
Yeah.
♪ ♪
So how is your friend?
- He's been better.
- Yeah?
Right.
I heard he was in a coma.
♪ ♪
That's the way it goes, eh?
No hard feelings.
[CHUCKLING SOFTLY]
Well, I'm afraid there
are hard feelings.
Quite a lot of hard feelings, actually.
Are there?
That's why we're having this chat.
[CHUCKLES]
♪ ♪
You can't go around bashing my guys.
But your guys can go around
bashing my friends, can they?
♪ ♪
Look, we had no idea you were friends
with the guy that got bashed.
I know you and Freddy are friends.
And out of respect for Freddy,
my guys wouldn't have done
what they did had they known.
If they did...
♪ ♪
I would have put them
in the hospital myself.
♪ ♪
Did you know Freddy and I are family?
He does now.
♪ ♪
Good.
Well...
we all know where we stand now, so...
we're good.
Right?
♪ ♪
Come on. Get up.
Get up there.
In the future...
if there is a problem...
you won't go off half cocked.
You just keep your guys
in line, mate, okay?
And then I won't have to do it for you.
♪ ♪
Nice to meet you.
[SIGHS] Jesus Christ.
Don't even think about it.
Trust me. Don't even think about it.
♪ ♪
[KIDS YELLING]
Pass it to me!
Go, go, go. Keep it moving.
Come out, come out.
Bella, Bella, over here.
Hey, Britt. Brittany.
Corey.
But even though there are lots
of different types of stag beetles,
many are facing a loss of
habitat that is threatening...
- What's that?
- Bug Versus Bug.
I'm obsessed with it.
Last night they had two spiders.
They had this like, jumping spider
and this spitting spider.
And the jumping spider, he
attacks the other one...
- and jumps on him, but he misses.
- Mm.
And the spitting spider,
he then shoots out this kind of like...
What are these idiots doing?
Having a good old fucking chit-chat.
[HORN HONKS]
Oh, fuck, here we go.
- What's your problem, dick head?
- What's my problem...
- Ah!
- I'll fucking give you one of those,
- you fucking little turd.
- Ray!
Yeah, you better run,
you fucking cocksucker.
Hey? Hey?
Ah!
Yeah, fucking run, you little bitch.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- What?
- What the fuck?
Just get in the car, love. Get in.
♪ ♪
[TOILET FLUSHES]
You want a cuppa?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Hey, can we talk?
Yeah, what's up?
What happened today with those guys...
it's kind of really bothering me.
Mm.
Um...
I mean, I know they were
being assholes but...
Mm.
Like, you were really violent...
and it bothers me.
What was I supposed to do?
I just...
feel like you could have...
you could have at least
tried to talk to the guy,
you know?
Maybe tried to...
defuse the situation.
Yeah.
That would have given his partner
time to get out of the car.
And then I'm dealing with two
assholes instead of one.
I mean, one on one...
yeah, sure. But, uh...
two on one, it's just too risky.
And you were there, I don't
want you getting hurt, so...
Sure. Right, yeah.
Okay?
Yep.
Yeah, well, thank you, Max. Thank you.
Um...
Ray.
How many, uh...
how many people, if you had to guess,
how many people would you
say that you've assaulted?
Heaps.
And how do you feel about that?
Fine. They had it coming, so...
And what did they do?
Oh, it depends. Uh...
I mean, I'm pretty big
on, just respect, so...
like, if you respect me, I respect you.
You know, if you don't,
we got a problem.
Well, let's talk about
the most recent assault.
The one with the two youths.
No, well, I only bashed one of them...
and um...
they weren't youths. They
were, like, in their 20s.
Well, let's call them young men then.
Ah, yeah, so...
I was walking down the street
with me daughter and...
these two guys come
along, bumped into her,
and she had an ice cream, and...
you know, dropped her ice cream and...
So you assaulted him?
Well...
no, they started... then
they started swearing...
and she's only eight, so...
So you bashed him...
while your daughter was
just standing there?
No, not while she was standing there.
I bashed him later.
Okay, well, how did you feel afterwards?
After it was... after it all happened?
Fine.
Do you enjoy hitting people?
I wouldn't say I enjoy hitting people.
You know, if I hit somebody
I generally got a pretty good reason.
And you think you had a good reason?
Didn't I just say that?
So can you remind me again
what that reason was?
Well, they were being assholes.
The world is full of assholes, Ray,
you do realize that?
Yeah and you know why?
Why?
'Cause people let them get away with it.
See, if you were in jail, right?
And you fucked with somebody,
you disrespect somebody,
you can end up dead.
There's consequences.
But out here in the real world...
There's no consequences.
Right?
So next time these two pricks
are walking down the street
and they start thinking,
"Oh, we might go
and fuck with somebody."
They're gonna think twice about it...
which is good for everybody.
So in your mind...
you've done society a favor.
Yeah.
Well, I guess on behalf of society,
I should say thank you.
[ALL LAUGH]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Steve, how are, uh...
how're things at home
since we last spoke?
[SIRENS WAIL]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING, YELLING]
[CHUCKLES]
- Here you go.
- It's about time.
- [LAUGHS]
- Oh, sorry.
- Hey.
- Bruce, Ally.
Gidday, mate.
- Nice to meet you.
- How you going, love?
Yeah, good. Good, thanks.
Britt, you wanna...
- Hi.
- Hello, Brittany.
- I'm Ally.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Your dad tells me you're
a bit of a legend
- on the netball court.
- I'm okay.
Okay? I'm sure you're better than okay.
Do you wanna come see my room?
Sure, I'd love to. Lead the way.
- It's over here.
- Okay.
Top shelf.
How'd she end up with you?
- She must be desperate.
- Mm-hmm.
- Did you do that?
- Yeah.
That is awesome.
- This is Patrick.
- Oh, hello, Patrick.
Oh, he's got a lovely mane.
He's very beautiful.
Are you gonna marry my dad?
Um...
Uh...
Do you know what?
Actually, I don't know.
- Okay.
Did you know that my dad's
seen a real unicorn before?
- Has he?
- Mm-hmm.
He said he saw it in the Blue Mountains.
Okay. Wow.
We're gonna go to look for one.
Right.
Do you wanna come?
Yes, I would love to come.
That would be great.
Okay, cool.
Okay, cool. [LAUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
[DOG BARKS]
[DOGS BARKING]
[CAR APPROACHING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
[TURN SIGNAL CLICKING]
♪ ♪
[ENGINE REVVING]
[EXHALES]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CAR HORN BLARES]
[EXHALES]
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
♪ ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Where have you been?
Run out of smokes.
Mm.
What's that smell?
What smell?
I don't know, it's like a...
it's like a burning sort of...
chemically sort of smell.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
["RECKLESS (DON'T BE SO)"
BY AUSTRALIAN CRAWL PLAYS]
♪ I miss our early morning wrestle ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Not a very happy ♪
♪ Way to start the day ♪
♪ ♪
♪ She don't like ♪
♪ That kind of behavior ♪
♪ ♪
♪ She don't like ♪
♪ That kind of behavior ♪
♪ So... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Throw down your guns ♪
♪ Don't be so reckless ♪
[LIGHTNING CRACKLES]
[DRAMATIC TONES]
[DRUMMING]