[BUZZING, HUMMING]
[HEART RATE MONITOR BEEPING]
[CHATTER ON INTERCOM]
_
Ray.
Who let you in?
Your mum.
Hmm.
How ya feeling, all right?
Not bad.
For a bloke who's been
in a fucking coma.
Went and saw that
brother-in-law of yours.
He fucking set me up.
Uh-huh.
What'd you do to him?
Bit of this.
Bit of that.
And the other pricks?
They'll live.
[SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
I fucking owe you one.
I'll add it to the list.
[BUZZING, HUMMING]
Nah, it gives me the shits.
And what's with the fucking cowboy hats?
Even the old country days,
fucking hardly anybody
- wore a cowboy hat.
- Mm.
Especially inside.
Johnny Cash never wore one.
Fuck, Johnny Cash never wore one.
Now, every cunt's wearing a cowboy hat.
- Aye.
- Yeah, I think...
I think their record company
tells 'em to wear the hat.
You know, like it's... like
it's fucking advertising.
- Probably.
- World's gone to shit, mate.
Everything's just money, money, money.
That's it.
Fuck.
[COUNTRY MUSIC]
So you still moving jewelry?
Yeah. What do you need?
Girlfriend's got a
birthday coming up, so...
How much you wanna spend?
200, 300.
Yeah, I'll see what I can do.
♪ ♪
Bewdy.
[HONKS HORN]
Here's trouble.
[SIGHS]
- What's going on?
- Hey.
Did you tell Brittany there's
no such thing as Jesus?
No, she asked me if Santa was real...
I don't care about Santa.
Do you want me to tell you
what happened or not?
- Sorry, okay, yeah.
- Okay.
So she asked me if Jesus was real,
and I said, um, I don't
know for sure, 100%,
if he was real, but I said
he could've been real.
You know Quentin and I are
raising your daughter
as a Christian, right?
Yeah, I know that, yeah.
So why would you tell her
something like that?
'Cause I don't wanna lie to her.
You don't wanna lie to her,
but you tell her unicorns exist?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
- Bye.
- Love you.
[ORCHESTRAL MUSIC ON TV]
♪ ♪
Color suits you.
Matches your eyes.
[MOUTHS "FUCK YOU"]
- What'd you say?
- You heard.
- Did you hear that, Britt?
- No. Finished.
Beautiful.
Can you paint my nails, please, Dad?
Mm...
- Please?
- All right, here.
[SNIFFLES]
[GRUNTS]
[ZAPPING, GRUNTING ON TV]
Tsk.
[THUMP, RATTLING]
- Jeez, mate.
- Fuck.
- You all right?
- [MUMBLING]
Careful, Britt.
Stay away from that glass there.
Nothing fucking works anymore.
Sit up, sit up, sit up. All right.
I'm gonna lift you up. All right?
[GRUNTS]
Lean against here, buddy.
I'm fucking over this.
I know you are, mate, I know you are.
You all right?
I'm sorry, Britt.
Looks like I owe you a dollar.
It's okay.
But yes, you owe me three
dollars, actually.
She's onto it.
She certainly is, mate. All right.
I'm gonna get you out of here, mate,
so I can clean this up.
- All right?
- Yeah.
You all right?
Feeling is of power, of empowerment.
Hi. Come in, come in.
- It's Ray, is it?
- Yeah.
- I'm Peter.
- How ya goin', mate?
- I'm good.
- Good to meet you.
Yeah, you too. This is Steve,
Bob, Carlo,
and, uh, this is Max.
- Take a seat.
- Cheers, mate.
All right, so now... now we're all here,
we can get started. Um...
Uh, the first thing we'll
do is we'll, uh...
We'll go around the room,
introduce ourselves,
and, uh, you know, just
tell us a little bit
about why you're here.
Ray, do you wanna...
You wanna get us... get us started?
So... so what do you want me to do?
Well, introduce yourself first,
and then tell us why you're here.
Okay. My name is Ray.
Um, I'm 40.
Divorced.
Got a kid.
Um, work security.
That's about it.
And why are you here?
Oh, I bashed a bloke.
And you've been ordered
to be here by the court.
Mm.
Do you think that you've
got an anger problem?
No.
Okay.
Carlo, do you wanna go next?
Um, yeah. Um...
So, I'm 43. Um...
Got a young son, and... and daughter.
Work in the building industry, and, uh,
been married, uh, 12 years.
And I'm here 'cause, um,
'cause my wife said
she'd divorce me if I,
mm, didn't attend, so...
And why does your wife
want you to be here?
Uh, she reckons I'm angry.
What do you reckon?
Sometimes.
And when you... when you
get angry, what do you do?
Sort of, um...
Sort of lash out sometimes.
At who?
My wife.
Kids.
You lash out physically?
Yeah.
Thanks, Carlo. Uh, Steve.
Yeah, uh...
Hey, I'm 38. Uh, married.
No kids.
Uh, we're separated at the moment,
wife and I.
Um...
I'm not working at the moment,
so it's pretty tough, you know.
Reason I'm here, I just
wanna patch things up
with the missus, about it.
And your... your separation,
is that something to do
with anger-related issues?
Yeah.
I just lose my temper.
And how does that manifest itself?
What?
How does, uh... how does
your anger show itself?
Sometimes I hit her and stuff.
[SIGHS]
Is everything okay, Ray?
I think I'm in the wrong room.
What makes you say that?
Well, the person I bashed was a bloke.
Not a child or a woman.
And what's your point?
Well, no offense, but I
don't really wanna sit here
with a bunch of fucking
wife-bashers and child-beaters,
you know what I mean?
- What the fuck did you say?
- You heard what I said.
- Time out, time out.
- Hey.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- Come on, tough boy.
You're dead.
I can fuck you up, you little fucking...
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Get the fuck off me, man.
- Outside, outside, please.
- Are you all right, mate?
I'm good, mate.
Fuck's sake. Fuck!
Look, if you can't take this seriously,
then I'll be recommending
jail time instead.
Okay? Do you wanna do jail time?
Not particularly, no.
Well, then, I expect you
to behave yourself.
If you're gonna cause trouble,
then we'll have to come to
some other arrangement.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Okay, next order of business.
Did a mate of yours get bashed recently?
A gun deal?
- Why do you wanna know?
- I just need to know.
Just... just...
tell me.
Maybe.
I'm gonna ask you,
did you bash the guys that...
that ripped off your mate?
Yeah.
Right, so those guys,
the ones you bashed,
they belong to a crew run
by a guy called Davros.
And Davros is my son-in-law's brother.
- Oops.
- Yeah.
- Hilarious.
So,
I need you to go sit down with him.
What for?
- 'Cause he's fucking pissed.
- [CHUCKLES] So?
Mate, this guy's family, okay?
I'm asking you a favor here, please.
Just sit down with him.
[SLOT MACHINE MUSIC]
[GLASSES CLINKING]
Why don't you shove a
bit more in your gob?
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
A-ha.
Ah, very nice, mate.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Really good.
- What do I owe you?
- Don't worry about it.
- No, I'll give you some money.
- Nah.
Just buy us a beer.
Done.
- Easy.
- Appreciate it.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
Yeah.
All right, what about these ones?
♪ ♪
No.
Oh.
There you go.
Those.
I thought you wanted to
buy me some sexy undies.
Yeah, they're sexy.
They're plain cotton.
They're sexier than those ones.
What do you mean? Guys
love the lacy ones.
No, we don't. You guys like 'em.
- Go with the cotton ones.
- Oh.
I don't want 'em.
Well, you've gotta pay for them.
No, give 'em me card.
Why don't you wanna do it?
'Cause.
Are you worried they're gonna
think they're for you?
Possibly.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, yeah, shot in 4K.
[INDISTINCT SPEECH ON TV]
Oh.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
That's it.
[MOANING]
Mmm.
[DOOR OPENS]
Fuck.
[TV TURNS OFF]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Jesus fucking Christ.
Vasilli? What the fuck?
- Where's safe?
- Is safe?
- Is it safe?
Yes.
Is it safe where?
Safe, where?
What the fuck are you talking... ah!
Safe. Safe. Money, money, safe.
Yes, okay, okay, okay.
It's in the fucking garage.
- Garage?
- Yes.
Go. Go, go, go.
[SPARSE AMBIENT MUSIC]
[CELL PHONE CLICKING]
♪ ♪
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
_
♪ ♪
[SPARSE AMBIENT MUSIC]
[SNAPS FINGERS]
♪ ♪
Open it.
I don't have the combination.
What?
I wrote it down somewhere.
Where?
Don't know. It's... upstairs.
You better no fucking me.
Mate, why would I be fucking you?
Let's go. Let's go.
♪ ♪
[WATER BUBBLING]
- Come on.
- All right.
Fuckin' hell.
Ah, fuck.
Come on.
Well, if it's not there then...
I'm positive it was up in the top one,
but she moves things
around all the time.
- What we do?
- If it's not there, I don't...
I don't know what she's done with it.
I'm just gonna have to give it a crack.
Okay, go, go.
- Hurry.
- 'Ey.
I just got out of hospital, mate.
Just calm down.
♪ ♪
Hurry up.
Yeah.
I have to be able to hear the click.
I don't know the
combination. You're just
gonna have to give me about
five minutes, all right?
Okay. In five minutes,
if not open, I shoot you in face.
Uh-huh.
You don't believe me?
No, I believe you.
[GROANS]
- How much longer?
- Two minutes, tops.
I'm nearly there.
Hurry up!
Mate, I almost had it there.
Now I gotta fucking
start all over again.
- Well, start then.
- Well, fuck, just be quiet.
- Stop talking.
- I gotta listen to the fucking click.
- You stop talking.
- No, you stop talking.
I can't hear the clicks.
You know how this works?
[COCKS GUN]
Ten seconds I shoot. Ten,
nine,
eight,
six...
Skipped seven. Ten,
nine,
eight, seven,
six, five,
four, three,
- two...
- Bingo.
[SAFE CLICKS OPEN]
Ah.
Ha-ha, good, good, good.
Where bag?
- What?
- Bag, you know, put shit in.
You didn't bring a bag?
Where bag?
There's plastic bags up in the kitchen.
No, no, no, no plastic bag.
What're you, stupid? Big bag.
I got a big bag up in the cupboard.
Let's go. Fuck.
Go, go, go.
You know, generally
when you rob somebody,
you bring your own bag.
Shut fuck up.
♪ ♪
There. There you go.
Nice big bag.
Good.
Go, go.
- Go.
- Fucking right-o.
♪ ♪
What?
Fill.
Don't look at me. Fill.
♪ ♪
Ah, ah, ah, careful with gun.
Careful with gun.
- Hurry up. Come on.
- All right,
I'm going as fast as I can.
[ZIPS BAG]
Happy?
Well, brother, I rough with you,
but I need money, so,
no bad feeling. Hmm?
[RUNNING UPSTAIRS]
What fuck? [THUMP]
[GROANS]
[PANTING, HISSING]
- [GRUNTS]
- You took your bloody time.
Lucky I fucking came at all.
Shoot the prick, will you?
I'm not doing it.
What's your problem?
Well, he's your fucking brother-in-law.
Yeah, I know, that's why
I don't wanna do it.
No.
Where's your car?
He's not going in my car.
Well, you gotta. Tat's got the Falcon.
Nah, I just had it
detailed, mate, forget it.
Well, I'll get a fucking tarp.
Cool?
Gotta get rid of him.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
Get him inside.
Right, roll him.
[GRUNTING]
There we go.
'Ey.
- Good?
- Right.
[GRUNTING]
Right.
I'm gonna get the car.
I'm gonna back it up.
I knock.
Door opens. He goes in the boot, right?
- Yeah.
- Got it?
Yeah, cool. Okay, good.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Ah, fuck, Tat's home.
Fuck.
Ah, just... just fucking just stay here.
[SIGHS]
Come on, you fucking cunt.
Hey.
What's this?
- Huh?
- What happened to the glass?
Ah, a bird...
- flew into it.
- When?
- Just before.
- Is the bird okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he just flew away.
He just hit the glass, flew away.
Why you have knife?
'Cause I couldn't find the broom.
So I was just gonna use that.
It's in the kitchen cupboard.
Ah.
- Didn't look.
- [GIGGLES]
- What an idiot.
- [SPEAKS FOREIGN LANGUAGE] _
Yeah.
Go and take a bath, or you're
gonna get a cold there.
- Da.
- How was the gym?
- All right?
- Good.
Yeah? [SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE] _
Fuck.
Here. Here.
What?
- Chop him up.
- Fuck off.
Why not?
He's your fucking brother-in-law.
- You do it.
- Why do you keep saying that?
Who gives a fuck whose
brother-in-law he is?
- Come on.
- Fucking chop him up later.
I can't chop him up later.
We gotta chop him up now.
He'll be easier to get
out in smaller pieces.
- Fuck, man, I'll owe ya.
- Keep fucking saying that.
Hold on, we gotta get
him up on the table.
Okay, okay. Come on, quick.
Can't lift the fat cunt me self.
- Okay.
- I got him.
- All right, got him.
- Ready?
Okay, one...
BOTH: Two, three.
Fucking get that shit off the table.
Okay.
[GRUNTING]
Okay, good.
Hold on, we gotta get his
fucking clothes off, man.
Fuck. Okay, get him up, get him up.
- Hang on. Got it.
- Good.
Shoes gonna...
Yeah, yeah. Good?
- Yeah.
- All right, good, good.
[LOUD EXHALE]
- Babe, what're you doing?
- Da?
What're you doing?
Cleaning up.
Ah!
- What's that?
- What?
Fuck me!
- Tatia.
- Vasya?
- [RUNNING, SCREAMING]
- Vasya.
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE] _
What fuck goes on?
Your fucking brother tried to rob us.
- Vasya.
- Yeah, he held a gun to my head,
and he said empty the safe downstairs
or he was gonna kill me.
If Ray hadn't come over,
he would've fucking shot me.
- You know that?
- [SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE] _
_
- Fuck you, Gary, fuck you.
- Stop it, stop it.
- _
- Get out of here.
Get out of here.
Get out!
BOTH: [SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Fuck you, Gary.
- What the fuck happened?
- Fuck you, Gary.
Wasn't dead.
Well, thanks, Captain Obvious.
Bullet...
Bullet must've ricocheted off his skull.
You couldn't tell when
you were cutting him?
You couldn't tell he
was still breathing?
No?
Well, you didn't fucking
recognize him breathing,
did ya? You were down there.
Where you going?
Fucking going home.
Ray.
[SPARSE AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[CAR BEEPS]
[ENGINE STARTING]
[CAR DRIVING OFF]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Ow! Fuck!
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
[THE LOVED ONES' "THE
LOVED ONE" PLAYING]
♪ ♪
♪ Yonder she's walkin' ♪
♪ She comes my way ♪
♪ Her red dress on ♪
♪ Her long black hair ♪
♪ Talking like ♪
♪ Walking like ♪
♪ Wanting like ♪
♪ She comes to me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh, baby, I love you so ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ I want you back ♪
♪ I can't go on ♪