Hello and welcome to Top Gear.
On tonight's show,
we've got a world exclusive
on four wheels and on two wheels.
That's right, we're doing a bike.
But first, if you like
huge horsepower hypercars,
and if you're watching this
it's safe to assume that you do,
now is a great time to be alive.
There's not a week that goes by
without another 1,000 horsepower,
million-pound monster
appearing on the scene,
but where did it all begin?
Well, here's Chris Harris,
with a quick history lesson.
Once upon a time, there was
a car called the Bugatti Veyron.
Volkswagen's passion project,
it launched in 2005
and promptly rewrote the rule book.
Not only was it the world's fastest,
most powerful production car,
it cost an unprecedented
one million euros.
This was hypercar 1.0 and,
without it, we might never
have seen the likes
of the McLaren P1, the LaFerrari
or the Porsche 918 Spyder.
But now it's gone -
and been replaced by this.
The new £2 million Bugatti Chiron.
Like the Veyron,
it has an eight-litre, 16-cylinder
engine, with four turbochargers.
And because this is the car
to replace the Veyron,
you would expect it to pack some
sort of extra futuristic shove.
But you'd be wrong, because this
is basically a very modified Veyron.
The same huge petrol engine,
four-wheel-drive system, gearbox -
it's all been tinkered and improved,
but this is the old formula.
So, if the Veyron was revolutionary,
the Chiron, I'm afraid, isn't.
But it does have...
..1,500 horsepower.
And that...
Well, that's a really long runway.
I'm quite nervous.
I don't really know how you
prepare yourself for this,
so I think you just go, don't you?
Oh, my God!
60. That's 100.
That's 125, that took six seconds.
That's 190. That's 200.
215. I'm trying to read
the speed and look ahead.
225. 228.
231. 233.
236 and that's the limit to there.
That is absolutely mind-bending.
I'm sorry, but that...
..needs another go.
This is looking insane.
You can almost hear it
gulping down the fuel.
The Veyron could empty its
100-litre fuel tank in 12 minutes.
This thing can do it in nine!
And the force
on those tyres - 3,800Gs!
Which means at this speed,
the 12mg valve caps weigh 13.5kg.
This is the edge of physics!
At this speed,
this Chiron is gulping
1,000 litres of air a second.
Drink in, Mr Chiron!
Get it down you!
That's a drug. That's a drug.
I know it's just going fast
in a straight line, but...
just the motive force required
to smash you through the air!
Now, if you're thinking, hang on,
the Veyron goes quicker than 236,
well, you'd be right,
but so does the Chiron.
You see, the Chiron
is a two-key vehicle.
The first key nestles in the
dashboard here and that gives
you 236mph, but down here, there's
another one, if I can find it.
There you go. Look at that.
Put that and turn it down there
and you're allowed 261mph.
And because Bugatti
is still testing the tyres,
even that speed is still limited.
How fast will it go?
270? Maybe 280?
I think we can speculate that,
at some point during its life,
the Chiron might well do 300mph.
300mph.
It goes like
a £2 million car should, then.
But what about the way it looks?
When I first saw pictures of the
Chiron, I was totally underwhelmed.
It looked too much like a Veyron,
but now I'm here with it in the raw,
I can get a sense of proportion and
the details, and it really works.
This lovely C that houses the air
intakes, then round the back here,
to this floating light bar,
massive diffuser and huge wing.
It's a stunning-looking thing.
The only problem is this
rather nasty 3 door handle,
but otherwise, well, it looks
every inch the £2 million car.
As does the interior.
It isn't complicated by
huge screens or rows of unfathomable
buttons and switches.
Bugatti intends the Chiron
to be timeless...elegant.
Then again, no-one ever criticised
the old Veyron for feeling cheap.
But they did criticise it
for being a bit, well, dull.
You see, it was admired,
but never really adored.
It was so competent, so stable,
it all felt a bit joyless.
With the Chiron though, Bugatti
has started to have some fun.
To start with, it's got
adaptive dampers all round,
so they can slacken off
and make the car comfortable
when it needs to be, and firm
and responsive when it needs to be.
And the steering is
a different world to the Veyron.
It's now electromechanical,
it's into the wrists.
The car now feels so much more
agile, but easier to place as well.
It's got a front end
you can lean on.
And with the four-wheel-drive
system revised, as well,
there's even mention of the D word.
Yes,
Bugatti says this thing will drift,
so I suppose we'd better
find out, hadn't we?
This is my
"BLEEP don't crash it" face.
It's like wrestling a shark.
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
The traction is mega.
All the power goes to the back
wheels, then it goes all
to the front and you have
to just grab armfuls of lock.
Rail breaker bit, get the rear
to rotate, then follow the gas on.
Yeah. You can drift the Chiron.
Now, of course, I'm not saying
Bugatti has gone and built
some P1 918 LaFerrari
baiting trap weapon.
The truth is, the more time
you spend with the Chiron, the more
you get the impression those
three upstarts don't even feature
on its radar.
What Bugatti has built here is
a car with a different purpose.
Above all else, the Chiron
is about straightforward speed.
And when it comes to speed,
it has no equals.
You can talk about
which one of the McLaren,
the Ferrari and the Porsche
you would buy, but you don't
with the Chiron.
You either buy a Chiron or no
Chiron. There is no competition.
A class apart, then.
Well, the Chiron isn't the Veyron.
It doesn't rewrite any rule
books or change the way we look
at the automobile,
but there's something
oddly appealing about that.
This is no longer the Volkswagen
group trying to demonstrate
its technological superiority.
It just wanted
to go really, really fast.
It wants to win at car
Top Trumps and that's
a pleasingly,
pig-headed aim in my book.
And talking
of going very, very fast...
Come on. If you were me,
you would, wouldn't you?
I'll never tire of this!
Amazing.
Amazing!
I'm a very, very lucky boy.
That's the fastest
I've ever been in a car.
- OK, now, you hit the limiter
at 236mph, right? - Yeah.
OK, so I've got to ask you,
you had the second key,
why didn't you use the second key
and hit the limiter at 261?
- I knew you'd ask that. - Of course
I'm going to ask you that.
Look, this car
isn't quite finished yet.
Bugatti's still working on it.
That's the reason it can't go
- around our lap, by the way.
It's not quite finished. - OK.
It's so complicated,
it's a leap into the unknown.
They're still developing it
and I was, sort of, part of that
- development process, actually.
- You are so selfless.
Risking your life for
the millionaires of the world.
- I mean, it's amazing.
- It's not a millionaire's game,
- this is a billionaire's game.
- Yeah! - Let me give you some stats.
- Bugatti tells us the average
Chiron owner has 42 cars. - OK.
Two yachts and 1.6 helicopters.
OK, which 0.6 of that second
helicopter do they have, though?
- The expensive bit. - OK.
Anyhow, of all
the mind-bending stats,
I think the tyres might be the
most mind-bending part of this car,
because when Bugatti
developed this machine,
it had to go faster than anything
else had gone before, so it
went to Michelin and said,
"We need a new tyre,"
and Michelin said, "OK."
But they'd never tested
a tyre to 300mph before,
so they had to test it on their
aircraft rig to get the tech right
and that's how you have
to think of this car.
- It's not so much a car, it's like
a land-based jet. - Yeah. All right,
let's think of it that way.
And we're not done with the Chiron,
because later in the show,
this car is taking part in a very,
very special race. Trust me,
you don't want to miss that one.
- Rory! - That's right.
This has the most horsepower
of any Top Gear film ever
and that's not all, because,
and I don't think I'm giving away
too much when I say that tonight's
show also features an exclusive
appearance from the Smart Fortwo.
Yeah. - That's right.
Now it's time to welcome
this week's guest. I love this guy.
This is great. OK.
He is the platinum-selling,
Brit Award-winning, chart-topping
megastar who loves to go low.
Ladies and gentlemen, Tinie Tempah!
Girls Like
by Tinie Tempah
You all right? Yeah.
- How's it going? - Pretty good.
- Where do you want me, here?
Yeah, right there is good. So glad
to have you here, right? Come on.
Finally! Finally!
- Yeah, yeah. This isn't your first
time here. - No, it isn't, actually.
So, basically, I was supposed
to shoot the video for the song
Girls Like in Dunsfold,
I was supposed to shoot it here.
And as soon as I got here,
it was rainy, rainy as hell.
The light went by, like, 3pm or
4pm, so we couldn't do anything
and then, by 6pm,
the director said it was a wrap.
I watched the video back
and it was absolutely BLEEP.
It's the worst video
I've ever seen.
The worst video I've ever seen
in my life, so then we had to rush
over to South Africa, to do
Top Gear, where we met. Yeah. Right.
And then,
after we finished doing that,
then I got to reshoot the video
in South Africa, so actually,
Top Gear and Girls Like have a lot
of synergy, there's just a lot
- there. - Speaking of Girls Like,
- that kind of became an unofficial
Top Gear anthem. - Oh, yes.
On shoots, everywhere we go,
you can always guarantee
this man is playing Girls Like.
- You are in his head 24/7.
- I think he just likes to...
I'm not sure he even likes the song,
he just likes, "Go low,
go low. Everybody get low."
That's what he likes. I love it.
- You're a bigger part of the show
than you think. - I appreciate that.
- That's on the new album?
- Yeah, it's on the new album, Youth,
coming out pretty soon
and I'm excited.
I've been working
on it for two years.
I'm like a Londoner,
it's an artist from the UK,
born and bred in London
and I wanted to be
a rapper when I was growing up
and everybody said it was naff.
You could never be a rapper.
A rapper would never get on the
radio or get on a show like this
and times have changed. Youth
is basically a celebration of that,
you know, just doing
something that wasn't really
a thing before and it's a thing now.
Speaking of growing up,
what was your first car?
- Oh, OK, so my first car
was a Vauxhall Corsa. - Yes. - 1.1.
- Humble beginnings. - Yes.
Y Reg, I remember
that very vividly and I used to...
Outside my mum and dad's house there
was a driveway and I'd, literally,
because I wanted to listen
to my music loud and stuff,
I'd just keep
the car in the driveway,
invite all my friends, technically,
to my house, but to the car,
so they'd get, "No, no,
don't go in there. Come in here."
And it was, literally, like,
my little, kind of,
like, domain for a while.
- What do you drive now? - At the moment
I'm driving the Lamborghini Huracan.
- Nice. - We talked about this.
I thought
you were going to get a Porsche?
Yeah, I kind of...
I don't know, we spent a week
together and I realised that you was
talking a lot, bro, and I was
listening to everything
you was saying.
You know you're with, like, Matt
LeBlanc, it's like, he's a legend.
I'm just like, "Yes, Matt.
Of course, Matt. I will, Matt."
And I got home and I was like,
"No, I don't want the Porsche."
- "Screw what he said."
- Yeah, "Screw his advice."
- And how do you like it?
- It's good, yeah. It's a good car.
I'm quite glad he wasn't the guest
two weeks ago, when I was...
less than kind
about the Lamborghini Huracan.
What did you say about it, bruv?
I said it was a wonderful car
for wonderful people.
And I went
and got it matted as well,
so I got MATT black colour.
Oh, thank you.
OK, what do you think?
Let's see how you did
in your training lap with Chris,
who just finished his Tamsin
Greig school of social etiquette.
- How did it go out there
with him? Good? - It was good, man.
I've heard a lot
of bad things about you, bro.
of bad things about Chris,
so I wasn't looking forward to it.
It was raining. It was raining,
then we started getting a bit
of sunlight, but too much,
so there was glare in the
windshield and I was thinking,
"This is probably all
because of Chris, somehow."
Like, he's just got...
There's just something about him.
He brings misery to the role.
Yeah, he brings misery,
but then I started to get upset
and then, after that, I started
to realise that he has got a soft...
quite a soft, sentimental side.
Because as I started
to get quite worked up,
he was immediately there,
to be like, "Don't worry, T..."
- Who has a soft, sentimental side?
- Chris. This guy over here, yeah.
I'm very giving.
Just watch the film.
Whatever! OK, let's take a look.
- Right, first gear, please. - Right.
- First gear, please, Tinie. - Cool.
- Handbrake off, please.
- Nice and positive.
- See, you like that? - I love it.
- Now just get on with it, come on.
- It's really slippery. - Yeah.
And we both want to go home
with all of our limbs, don't we?
Yeah, nice and safe.
- Feel that understeer, baby.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Now feel that oversteer
on the exit. - Yeah.
- Whoa! - Got it, got it, got it.
Now you're alive. Got to
go left here at the blue line.
To the left of the tyres.
Brake, brake, brake.
- Remember, look for the red line
now on your right-hand side. - Yes.
- It's there. It's there,
it's there. - Oh, spinning out.
- Understeer, understeer, understeer.
- There we go. Am I within the line?
- Is that cool? - That's good,
that's brilliant. Up here.
- Let's go.
- Admittedly, begrudgingly...
Come on! Come on!
It's time for some tunes, man.
Brake, brake, brake, brake,
or we're off. Brake or we're off.
You know, Toyota make an offroader,
as well. It's called a Land Cruiser.
- Is it? - It's not
this one, though. - Oh, OK.
I'll bear
that in mind for next time.
- Good Lord! - I've got it.
- And over the line.
- Over the line! - Yes!
- You nearly braked before the line!
- The pressure's too much, man.
I don't know
if I can deal with this.
I'm going to get
high blood pressure. Come on.
How did you do it?
Teach me the dance move.
Look at this one. Do this one.
Just a slow one. Just a slow one.
This is about my Lamborghini.
Yeah, just have
to dance like a grandad now.
- That's all you have to do. - Your
Lamborghini looks like a shark?
Yeah,
my Lamborghini looks like Jaws.
What was that dance
you were doing in the car?
I don't really understand.
I was taking some lessons
from Tinie about how I should dance
and he said, very reassuringly,
"Dance as you want to. Be a
grandpa." So I thought, OK, I would.
I mean, obviously,
when my children see that,
that's just going to be appalling,
but I tried my hardest.
Look, he dealt very well with the
conditions, because it was so wet
it was flooded. The tyre
wouldn't deal with the water,
so we were aquaplaning,
and then, the sun came out, so
he couldn't see where the line was.
- It was just like a glass surface,
wasn't it? - It wasn't easy, bro.
- It was tough. - Yeah, that was wet.
We'll see how you did
in your timed lap.
- We'll check
that out later on. - Cool.
Now, usually these two get to
hoon about in Ferraris and Lambos
and such,
but a couple of months ago,
the producers told me
there was a new rear engine,
rear-wheel drive sports car
that I should take a look at.
Maybe a rival for the Porsche 911.
So, I went to check it out.
And this is that rear-engined,
rear-wheel drive sports car. Yeah.
I've been stitched
up here, haven't I?
It's called the Renault Twingo GT.
And, yeah, like the Porsche 911,
it does have
the engine in the back.
And, like the Porsche 911,
that engine
does drive the rear wheel.
But I'm calling foul on the
whole sports car thing, I'm sorry.
What sport?
What is sporty about this?
Well, right now, not a lot.
Even on a dry day, 0-60 takes
over 9.5 seconds and it's got
a top speed of just 113mph.
Those are not numbers
to worry Porsche.
They're not numbers to worry anyone.
But according to Renault,
this really is a sports car.
Compared to the standard Twingo,
the one driven by your nan,
the GT has bigger alloys,
firmer suspension
and twin tailpipes.
And, on the left-hand side only,
a small intake, which feeds
cool air into the three-cylinder,
turbo-charged engine,
which makes 20% more power.
All right, that still
only gives it 108 horsepower.
But that doesn't actually matter,
because this Twingo is
a different kind of sports car.
It doesn't need power. It weighs
less than a ton. It's light.
And the GT costs
under £14,000, so it's cheap.
This is a baby hot hatch.
And that is a very good thing.
Because unlike a big hot hatch...
..you're not paying
for anything you can't use.
Ha-ha!
Your Ford Focus RSes
and your Golf Rs and the like,
great cars,
but they're so damn fast.
In Britain at least,
you can only use a fraction of their
firepower a fraction of the time.
Not in the Twingo, though.
You can keep your foot
buried for 20, 30 seconds,
safe in the knowledge
that it's not going to kill you.
It's one of those cars
that encourages you to drive
like an absolute hooligan
and, yet, you always stay
on the right side of the law.
It's just a really
rewarding car to drive.
OK, it's not a Porsche,
but it is good.
So, yes, if your name's
Chris Harris and you commute to work
sideways over empty,
sweeping moorland B-roads,
the Twingo IS going
to leave you a bit cold.
But because you're not Chris Harris,
and, thank God, neither am I,
we don't commute to work over
empty, sweeping moorland B-roads.
We spend most of our time...
..in the city.
And that is what
the Twingo is all about.
Because there's no oily,
petrolly, motory stuff jammed in
by the front wheels, I can
get an insane amount of lock on.
That means it's a cinch to park.
It also means I'm agile, I'm nippy.
I'm like a big,
orange hummingbird on wheels.
What I'm saying is,
you don't need loads of horsepower
to have a good time.
Remember the Peugeot 205 GTi
from the '80s?
One of the best
hot hatches of all time.
And yet, the Twingo GT
has almost exactly the same power
and performance.
This car is retro.
And I do love a bit of retro.
The thing is, if you're
after a playful little city car
with that old school appeal,
the Twingo does have its rivals.
And helping find
the right car for you
is something we take very seriously.
Oh, yes.
Welcome to what, for legal reasons,
I'm obliged to refer to as
the Top Gear arcade-based
maze re-creation challenge.
Yes, like all classic arcade games,
here, the rules are simple.
There's a big maze covered in dots
and me and the Twingo
have three lives to drive
around eating said dots
without getting got by the ghosts.
And by ghosts, I do mean
similarly-priced city car rivals.
Ghost number one
is the Brabus ForTwo.
It has the same engine
and performance as the Twingo
but only has
two doors, two seats and,
for tonight at least,
is being driven by a speedy German.
I see you, man pack.
No, it's not man pack,
it's... Never mind.
Ghost number two
is the new Volkswagen Up!
Yes, it might be five years old,
but the king of modern city cars
now comes with a turbocharger,
to give it more zip -
especially in the hands
of Mr Happy here.
Rory, do you know what
corrugated steel tastes like?
I'm sorry, did they have arcade
games when you were growing up?
Or were you part of
the stick and hoop generation?
Less talky, more smashy.
'Right, three lives
to eat up all the dots
'and one handy sat nav map,
to help me find them.'
Get ready
for an arcade masterclass.
See you later, suckers!
He's going left! Follow, Harris!
Catch me if you can, losers!
Give me them dots,
give me them tasty dots.
Yummy, yummy, yummy, come on.
This is good fun!
One thing I've got on my side
is that this is the most
manoeuvrable car of the bunch.
A little car.
Such a tiny little thing.
And for this job, just perfect.
Now, officially,
the Up! is the cheapest car here,
but it has the highest top speed.
'Which is of no use
in an arcade maze.'
Handbrake!
Yes! Whoo!
- That was - BLEEP - great.
Oh, yes.
This is the best
city car, bar none.
Oh, no, no, no! Come on!
Come on!
I'm dead. Already!
OK, two lives left, and with nearly
a third of the maze cleared,
lots of dots still to eat.
Rory,
be a bit less rubbish this time.
We're off. Here we go, here we go.
Don't let them beat you, man.
Don't let them beat you!
I'm right behind you.
Right behind you!
Oh, Harris is quick!
- He's quick! - Go, Harris!
'Immediately, the ghosts
were closing in again.'
Go, go, go!
'But no retro arcade game would
be complete without the odd...'
Here we go! '..power up.'
- Ha-ha! - Whoo!
- You hit me! - What are you doing?
What's the red light thing?
The red light means stop, Grandad.
'And that gave me
ten whole seconds...
'Of ghost-free dot-munching.'
I am on a dot spree now, baby.
I think you'll find
they're called biscuits.
Literally,
nobody calls them biscuits.
Well, except old people.
- Oh, we can go again.
- Let's go! - Now we're blocked in.
Whoa!
Oh, the turning circle!
The turning circle!
I haven't quite got the turning
circle of a Twingo, have I?
Oh, delicious dots.
Delicious dots! Mine!
'And with Harris still halfway
through his million-point turn...'
I'm not going to catch
anyone at this rate, am I?
'..I tried a new tactic. Stealth.'
Stay under the radar.
- Off the grid.
- Ah, we're away. Right, come on.
Where is he?
Think stealth. Think ninja.
Rory! Where are you?
He's hiding. We'll find him.
I'm right behind him.
He doesn't even know.
'Yep, my awesome ninja
stealth skills let me sneak in
'a few more dots before...'
I got him, I got him!
Yeah, I can see him.
Run away! Run away!
'The city car ghosts
were back in the hunt.'
I'm going to catch you, Reid.
Which way? Which way?
Which way? Which way? Which way?
- Got him! - No, no, no!
Oh!
Mate!
Dude, it's a brand-new Twingo!
'You're better than this, Reid.
'Right, still a load of dots left.
'Last life, no continues.'
Rory, just give up.
You're not going to win.
Come on, Twingo, help me
out here. Please, please, please.
You can do this, you can do this!
'Game time.
Hunting out the last of the dots.'
You're not supposed
to wreck all the lights, Reid.
'The Twingo and I were using
every trick in the arcade manual...'
Dots, dots, I need dots. Come on.
'..which isn't even a thing..
Oops.
All right, we've got to stop him
getting these last biscuits.
I have an idea.
Come on, Twingo!
Come on! Yes, yes!
The last dots! Come on!
'We were nearly there, but with the
last dots almost within reach...'
That's them.
The last dots. Let's go.
Argh!
'..Sabine had set up a dot block.'
Sneaky German ghost!
Oh, no, you don't,
Mr French shopping trolley.
Ha-ha! Ken Block who?
Good skills.
Ah, yes!
- Oh, no! - Here we go, here we go!
Yes! Nearly there, Twingo!
That's them - the last dots!
Yes! Yes!
Go!
We did it! We did it!
Oh, look,
he's doing a victory doughnut.
In your face!
It's not really a doughnut, is it?
More of a kind of crap teacake.
In your face!
- Victory for the Twingo!
- Victory for the Twingo.
That was... That was great.
That was great.
You know, not a day goes
by where I don't find myself
trapped in a maze of shipping
containers and wonder,
"What would be the best car
to help me escape?"
- Yeah, exactly. - Now I know.
- Exactly, exactly.
You know what I like
about the Twingo, right?
It's the fact that all city cars
were, kind of, all becoming the
same, they were becoming clones,
but the Twingo is a different way
of answering the question.
It's not the front-wheel drive,
it's not, kind of, boxy.
All right, it's not perfect
but it's got character.
And when you want to go somewhere,
you just pop it in the boot
of your real car and off you go.
OK, now it's time to find
out which of these teeny, tiny cars
is fastest around our track,
and that means handing
them over for testing.
Not by The Stig,
but by The Stig's teenage cousins.
So, there they all are,
standing around Snapchatting,
photo bombing, looking for
Pokemon Go...
And off the line, the Twingo,
rear-engine traction,
has got a little bit
of a march there.
There's no room up the inside for
that particular adolescent lunatic.
Oh, my God. Imagine what's inside
that helmet - all the acne.
Right, turning in, there's not
enough room for you there.
Oh, dangerous - headphones on.
What are they listening to?
Tinie Tempah, maybe.
Some cool tunes.
OK, this is worrying now because
there's not room for two of them
going in here.
The Up looking a bit sneaky
at the back there.
A tighter line... This is clever.
..and he's going
to get the march on the Smart
coming down the back straight.
They don't look very fast, do
they? No, not in a straight line.
What's he doing there?
I don't know, talking to his
pals on Face Chat thing...
OK, breaking hard
down into the Hammerhead.
What's going to happen here?
Well, the Up has got
a massive advantage because...
I think because it's front-engined,
it looked better.
But look at that sneaky
git on the inside there.
Three abreast.
I don't how this is going to end.
This looks like a massive insurance
claim in waiting, doesn't it?
So let's go through
the Follow-Through...
Oh, that's rude! That's rude!
He's cut him right
off at the nose there.
And that Smart just looks
unstable to me... It looks so short.
So short. OK...
Oh, that's a
buttock-clenching moment there.
But the Smart's
got the run on the Twingo
heading down towards second-to-last.
Really unstable under breaks -
I don't know what
they're playing at here.
I think the
Twingo's got this wrapped up.
Second-to-last, Twingo runs wide.
Carry... That's just rude!
OK, that's rude! So effectively,
a moral victory to the Renault
because he had
to get out of the way,
otherwise he'd
have crashed into that Stig.
All right, now, because
that got a bit out of hand,
we also got The Stig himself
to lap all three cars.
Now, only the fastest one of the
three earns a place
on the leaderboard, and that
was the Smart in 1.49.1.
Which is...
a way down there. OK...
- I told you. - All right, now...
Hold on, hold on. I want to
talk about the internet
- for a second... - Yes.
..because I hear that you
and Chris Harris have the same
favourite website, which I've got
to say, I find hard to believe
because I know Chris
and he's disgusting!
Oh, we definitely do, then.
No, I'm joking!
No, my favourite website
is actually Auto Trader, bro.
- I love it. Do you love Auto Trader?
- Yeah, I'm addicted.
I love it.
Ever since I've been a kid...
For me, I grew up in, like,
a council estate, south-east London,
didn't have much, so being able to
go online and look at all these cars
at all these ridiculous prices...
I used to type in
"£200,000, £1 million,
"let's see what cars come up."
And you'd see all these rare
cars, and I just...
I was obsessed with it. So, yeah,
it's my favourite website.
- OK. And that's your favourite
website, too? - It is, yes.
To avoid any confusion,
that is my favourite website.
What's you second...?
No, never mind! Let's not do that.
Tinie, I heard you enjoy an
Aston Martin.
Yeah, bro. I... Oh, God!
So I... Luckily, when
they launched the One-77
they invited me down
to be factory.
So they said to me, "Do you want
to borrow one for a week?"
So I borrowed the
Aston Martin Virage
and I remember rolling around like
just the coolest kid in the world.
I was like 23 years old at the time
and I was dating this girl
at the time,
and so when she saw the car,
and she was in the car,
she got really, really giddy
and excited.
And she said, "We should celebrate.
We should..."
- Should what? - Yeah. - Should what?
- What? What? What?
Don't make this harder
than it already is, please.
- But, yeah...
- Is that what you said to her?
Choose your words more carefully.
That Aston Martin badge, I told you.
Yeah, I felt like James Bond for,
like, 20 seconds, which was great.
20 seconds?
The good thing is, they don't make
the Virage any more
because I don't want to borrow one.
Yeah, don't ever buy... Like,
if you see used one floating around,
don't get that one.
What do you think?
I think it's time to take a look
at Tinie's lap around the track.
- Who wants to see that?
- Yeah!
Let's do it. Yeah? How do you think
it went? How did you think you did?
I think it was cool. I mean,
I don't really know how I did.
And it was a swamp out there.
Yeah, the conditions were horrible,
but I'm not going to be a moaner.
I'm not going to make excuses.
All right, let's take a look.
Off the line.
It's time to make the family proud.
It's a freezing day in England,
but I'm actually sweating.
It's nerves, I've got gas today.
OK, well, you're using most
of the circuit, that's good.
Third gear...
Look, at the flooding there!
- Wetter than...
What was going on there? - Whoa!
That was properly lairy. A bit of
understeer here. Get on the gas.
- A bit of oversteer
on the exit. - Come on, son!
You're letting it just dance
around, aren't you?
- Braking hard now into Hammerhead.
- It's started to rain again.
You're really not...
Really trying to rain
on my parade.
Oi, oi! It's all about
the smoothness, T.
It's all about the smoothness.
Smoother than a baby's bottom.
Come on.
OK, coming down now
to the Follow-Through.
This is going to be tough.
I think I've just
farted out of nervousness.
I don't know what to say about that.
That is a massive moment!
Do you know what that face is?
That the new underwear face.
So we're going to roll
into Second-to-last.
It's slippery here.
You got that one right that time.
Breaking hard, keeping it tight.
Do you know what?
I think that was the toughest
conditions so far
for any of our drivers
over the line.
- That face! - Are you happy with that?
What do you think?
It's weird because it feels a lot
faster than it looked on the screen.
- Yeah, always. - So while I was
driving, it felt way faster
and there it didn't really look
that fast, but, I don't know.
Who knows, bro? I don't know.
Yeah, the same thing happens
to me in performances.
It always looks a lot
better when I'm doing it
then what it actually looks like.
You watch it back and you're like...
All right, now, the top of our
leaderboard is still Max Whitlock,
the iconic gymnast.
You give that guy a foam horse
covered in suede and he just gives
you poetry. Is it not nice...?
Incredible. But, because it was
so wet, you have a wet time,
so you have to beat
James McAvoy's time of 1.47.1.
Don't say it like,
"You only have to beat..."
Don't say that.
OK, Tinie Tempah,
you went around the track...
in one minute...
- 50... - Oh!
- Point four. - Good effort.
That's a good effort.
Considerably wetter.
Considerably...
..three seconds slower out
there for you. Yes, it was.
Yeah, that's solid.
That's solid for those conditions.
Ladies and gentlemen, Tinie Tempah!
What a hero.
OK, now, earlier on you
remember Chris was driving
the 1,500 horsepower Bugatti Chiron.
Which, so long as you have more
money than Mark Zuckerberg,
- is pretty much as fast as you
can go in a car. - Yes, that's true.
But, of course, if you have more
money than Mark Zuckerberg,
you're not limited to just cars.
So, since we had
a day to kill with the Chiron,
we decided to have a little race.
It's the age-old question
we've all pondered -
you're a billionaire oil mogul
based in downtown Dubai,
you knock off work at lunch
on a Friday,
or a Thursday as they do here,
so what's the fastest way
to reach your luxury weekend
retreat in the Omani mountains?
Car or not car?
- Hello. - Well, I'm what they call
suitably equipped, Matthew. - Yeah.
I can't help noticing
you have no transport.
Are you planning
on walking to Oman?
No, no, no. Don't worry.
Off you go.
I'll be the guy at the hotel bar
with all the empty drinks
- in front of him.
- No, you're going to lose.
It's not possible to get anywhere
faster than in this car.
Yeah, and what a car!
Does come in men's?
You're better than that,
you know you are.
- And, also, what's in that rucksack?
Why's it so big? - This?
My lunch.
Three, two, one, go.
- Oh, hang... - You're going to lose.
- Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
- You're going to lose.
- I'm already in front of you!
Now, the winner of this
billionaire's commute-off
would be the first to get
from the heart of Dubai
to a luxury five-star retreat,
perched high in the mountains
of neighbouring Oman.
And with Chris driving the Chiron,
I would have
to travel by other means.
No driving.
I won't be driving.
Not one bit of driving.
I have a plan.
I think I can safely say
I'm the only Chiron driving around
on the public highway
in the world at the moment.
One of us is currently winning...
and it's not Joey!
Anyone can take a car.
A billionaire doesn't take a car.
So you are actually
walking to Oman.
- Very luxurious. - You're wasting
time you don't have, keep going.
An angry small man in Dubai,
rocks up in his Chiron,
says, "Hi," What a...
Unfortunately, I quickly encountered
a problem unfamiliar to most
billionaires, rush hour.
There's about 19 lanes and yet
everyone's stuck stationary.
Oh, come on!
Don't drive into me.
This is worth 2 million quid.
'Silly Harris, you see,
traffic was not something
'I needed to worry about.'
That's right, it's a boat.
'And this was just stage one
of my four stage master plan.'
This is the
frustrating part of the race
because we have to adhere
to this five-knot speed limit.
Once we get out on the
open water, we can pin it.
The Riva Rivarma is 44 feet long,
costs £1 million -
half the price of Harris's car,
which is only a third the length
of this boat, and he doesn't
even have an onboard ice-maker.
Or a toilet.
He's in trouble.
Well, not quite...
Because when you're
a billionaire for the day,
you can call in the odd favour.
Yes, yes, yes!
Now, this is what I call a plan.
I'm being escorted out of Dubai
at speed
behind a Dubai police i8.
There's a McLaren 570 ahead,
behind me, a Nissan-GTR -
and to my left
is an Audi R8 V10 Plus.
It has 610 horsepower.
That's 900 less than
the one I'm in. 900 less!
This is cool!
'Whatever.
See, I was now clear of the marina.
'Fast as you like.'
Oh, yeah, baby!
That's the stuff right there.
- Hello! - Have you located
some proper transport yet?
I can't really hear you too good.
It's a little windy
out here on the sea.
- What are you on, a boat? - Yeah.
Just having a
good old time racing you.
I've got through the Dubai traffic
by using a police escort
and I'm now heading
towards the border.
I can't possibly see how
you can win.
Yes, an hour in and with Admiral
LeBlanc bobbing around in his boat,
I was well on my way to Oman.
Frankly, this wasn't
much of a race after all.
Maybe I could just spend the next
hour conjugating the verb "to win."
I win, you win,
he, she or it wins...
we win, you win, they win...
Or you're Matt LeBlanc,
and you lose.
What has Matthew got planned?
Well, since he asked, it was time
for the second stage of my commute.
OK, here she is!
Now, that is the
Bentley Mulsanne EWB.
Extended wheelbase.
Now, of course, I'm not driving.
'No, no. Like any good billionaire,
I have a chauffeur -
'The Stig's Emirati cousin.'
OK, vamos!
Andiamo!
Allez?
Go!
Meanwhile, basking
in my comfortable lead,
I had time to consider
some of the Chiron's utter madness.
Remember when you were a kid
and you'd get into cars
and always look how fast
the speedometer read to?
And you'd assume that
if a speedometer said 140,
the car could do 140?
Ha-ha!
In the Chiron, the game is over.
This reads
to 500 kilometres per hour.
That's 300 miles an hour.
How do you out-Chiron a Chiron?
What do you do?
Come on.
Now, I had hit some traffic,
but to be honest,
in the Mulsanne,
it was hard to care.
Oh... Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it gives you a massage...
Oh... That is maybe the nicest
car seat that was ever made.
Let's give him a call,
see how old Chris is doing.
Hello?
Well, well, well, how are you?
Pretend you're not going
to hear this...
- Super, please. - Super? - Super.
How many fuel stops have you made so
far? Is this your second or third?
It's my first, don't be stupid.
'Where are you?'
I, my friend,
am sitting in the back of
a beautiful Bentley Mulsanne EWB.
So, you've taken a boat
to get in the back of a Bentley
that you know is slower
than my car, and now you're
just going to drive
all the way to Oman?
'I had you down as a clever man.'
I didn't say anything about driving
all the way to Oman.
OK.
Oh, do you want some money?
Do you want money?
'Yeah, you have to pay
for that fuel.'
Hey, listen...
Oh, he's gone.
A small, angry man in Dubai
Rocks up in his Chiron,
says, "Hi..."
With his mad little grin
Cos he thinks he'll win...
OK, my plan to avoid all of Dubai's
traffic with the speedboat
had backfired,
and after two hours of racing,
I was still stuck downtown,
while Chris was approaching Oman,
100 miles ahead of me.
Ah. The border.
Which looks strangely similar
to the Mound Stand at Lord's.
What's going to happen here?
Don't we just go through?
He's got a gun.
He's got a gun as well, actually,
I didn't notice him.
What's going on here?
Come on, let me through...
Yes! I'm liking the look of this!
You see...?
The Bugatti Chiron improves
international relations -
just smile and look as if you are
comfortable with what you're doing.
What's he doing?
He wants me to wait here?
Or what? Wait here?
Good, OK, OK.
So...
They're all tweeting
and taking photos of the car.
- Hashtag - can I please get on
with it? - How are you, sir?
- Hello, how are you? - Welcome back.
- Thank you. Hello.
- Sir, I've got to change
this number. - What?
So they're re-registering the car
cos we've entered Oman.
This is a disaster,
I've been here 30 minutes now.
Matt LeSmuggins is going to be...
I don't know where he is.
Well, I had finally reached
stage three of my plan...
Thanks, Stig!
'..and really had
some catching up to do.'
How are you?
Nice to see you. Hello.
OK. Did not plan on
that much traffic.
Worse still, Chris had crossed
the border into Oman.
'Luckily, stage three...
was a good one.'
Ho-ho! There it is.
The Honda Jet,
as in a jet made by Honda.
Howdy, boys. Let's go!
This thing's quick!
Oh, that's a steep climb.
Yeah, baby.
That's what I'm talking about.
Hey, how fast are we going?
About 480mph. Maxed out, boom!
It's like we're rolling up here.
You know, somewhere down there
there's a very small man
in a very fast car,
and though that very small man
is still talking a very big game...
..deep down, deep, deep down,
that very small man knows very well
that he is going to lose.
It's very sad.
That border check situation...
That lost me a lot of time.
Come on, Mr Bugatti... We might just
have to deploy a bit of your speed.
Meanwhile...at 15,000 feet...
The Honda Jet, £3.6 million,
20 years in the making.
Its ground-breaking
overwing engine design
maximises performance
and efficiency.
It comes with snacks too.
But what it all really adds up to
is a great way to overtake a Chiron.
You're what...? You're in a Honda?
No, it's not a Civic.
No, it's not an Accord.
It's not the NSX either.
It's the Honda Jet.
Git! Utter git!
I can't even boast that I've got
the fastest, most expensive
toy now, can I?
'The Honda had definitely
put me back in the game.'
Making time, making time...
'But my one-hour flight would
touch me down in Muscat,
'which was still a good 100 miles
'from the mountaintop finish line.
'So, Chris was technically
still in the lead...'
Speed's dropping again.
'..for now.'
We're coming into another town...
It's becoming a pain, this.
You know when your brain tells you
you just have to keep moving
when the traffic stops, so you
dive off and take another route
and think that keeping moving
is the thing...?
But it turns out to be rubbish?
Yeah, that's where I am now.
Matt's going to be quivering
when he finds out how fast
I'm driving through here.
This is ridiculous.
No, no, no, no, no...
This thing is two metres wide!
I hate this!
A-a-a-a-nd...touchdown.
Thanks a lot, take care.
'Stage four, it was time to open up
the backpack.'
Excuse me one second,
I'll be right back.
I've got to take care of something.
So, the rules said no driving...
Nobody said anything about riding.
This is the new
Ducati 1299 Superleggera.
Hey, Chris, I don't know where
you are or what you're doing,
but I'm pretty confident
I'm going to win.
Now, I know what you're thinking,
and, no,
your average billionaire
probably wouldn't finish
their commute on a bike,
but that's probably because
they haven't tried THIS bike.
The Superleggera will do 0-60
in about two and a half seconds,
which is the same as the Chiron.
The only difference is I don't need
1,500 horsepower to do it,
just a bit of bravery.
The top speed is
190-something miles an hour.
Now, some people will look at that
and say,
"Well, that's just stupid,
"that's more speed than anyone
would ever need."
To which I say, "Exactly."
The small, angry man in Dubai
Rocked up in his Chiron, said, "Hi"
With a mad little grin
He thought he could win
But at the bar in the mountains
he'll cry.
That's it, that's the rhyme.
But as I made short work of
my 100-mile ride from Muscat,
Chris had found his way
back onto the open road.
Are you off the plane?
- Yeah, I'm on a bike.
- What do you mean, you're on a bike?
What bike?
Ducati 1299 Superleggera.
- You what?!
- Yeah, you better stand on it, buddy.
That bike is basically
a personal teleportation device.
Thankfully, so is the Chiron.
Let's get a move on.
Now we're talking.
A little bit of open road here.
Come on, push, push!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Foot down.
- This thing's - BLEEP - fast!
Approaching the mountains
from opposite sides,
we were entering the final stage
of the race.
With no way of telling
who was in front,
there was just one road up
to the finish line...
Oh, look at that.
..and it was a good one.
This is about to get fun.
Wow!
Now this is a proper road!
Look at it, fantastic!
Now we're talking.
This is nice!
God, it goes left to right so good.
It just holds the line perfect.
And I know this is a car show...
so you probably want the Chiron
to win, but if it doesn't...
I mean, when...
When it doesn't...
..don't blame the car...
blame Harris.
I don't know if I'm hunting him down
and catching him
or maybe he's catching me.
I don't see that big gold Bugatti
in my mirror.
Got to be in front. He's got to be.
- Come on! Come on! Come on!
- Please let me be ahead of him!
Please let me be ahead of him!
Come on, push, push!
Push, LeBlanc!
Come on, Mr Chiron!
We have to win this!
This is it, this is it.
OK, thanks, buddy.
Where is he?
That's it, that's the spot.
He's small, but he's not that small,
I don't see him.
I think we have a winner!
Oh, yes, that's what I'm
talking about, look at that view!
Harris is going to be so mad.
I can't wait to see the look
on his little...
..bald face.
There you go...
Have a Chiron. And no-one there.
I think we've got this, boys.
I think we've got...
Oh, come on, no.
Welcome to Oman!
- No! - How are you, my friend?
Why so slow...bro?
I haven't even thought of my line!
Oh...
What was your line?
It's like you're always stuck
in second gear,
which looking at it now
wasn't very funny, was it?
- I was stuck in top gear, my friend.
- Yes, well done. Well done.
Oh! - Oh, yeah.
I can't believe I lost.
You didn't lose.
If you say I just came second,
I'll throw you off that balcony.
- No, no, no. - OK.
No, you lost.
No! Just get me off of here!
Cheers.
That's a good beer.
It never tastes as good as
a winning beer, though, does it?
- You want to try that one? - Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah, that's better.
Oh!
You just missed the sunset,
it was beautiful.
We could have held hands
and everything.
So close. So, so close.
That was so close.
You know, I think if it wasn't
for that border crossing,
you would have had me.
Well, the border crossing and
the fact that I had my own jet.
- Look, I'm gutted, but I made the
Chiron look good value. - What?!
Well, add up the cost of the boat,
the limo and then the plane
and the bike... How much is that?
- About £5 million. - OK.
Double the price of the Chiron and
I only lost by a couple of minutes.
- You still lost. - Mm. - Or, or...
I maximised my time in the most
extraordinary car of the millennium.
Ah! No, you lost.
On next week's show,
a motorsport battle
as we find out who's quickest...
Chris Harris or Sabine Schmitz?
And an American man drives
an American car in America.
Yes, he does, the Ford GT.
Whoo!
That's right.
- We will see you then. Good night.
- Night.