Hello, and welcome to Top Gear.
On tonight's show, we go supercar
hunting in a Volkswagen Golf,
and discover the perfect
run about for the fashion
conscious Bond villain.
But fist, let's talk about Aston Martin.
Now, Aston Martin, they've
always made beautiful cars,
but the truth is, in recent years,
Aston's been a bit left behind.
You know when we first saw this DB9?
2003.
In car years, that's ancient, right?
But now the DB9 has been replaced
by a new car, promising to bring
Aston right up-to-date.
This is the all-new DB11.
Aston Martin says it's
the most important model
in its 100 year history.
No pressure there, then!
Thankfully, it still looks great.
But look beneath the body work
and there are a few surprises.
Aston's given the DB11 a smaller
motor than the old DB9,
and for the first time
ever, accessorises it with
a pair of turbo chargers.
Now this - this is controversial.
The free revving, naturally
aspirated Aston Martin V12
is a British institution, like
the Royal Family - or crumpets.
Aston Martin going turbo is big news.
So, have they ruined it?
Well - no.
Not at all.
In fact, this might just be
the best all-round Aston
in the last 20 years.
Or 40 years.
Or...
Damn, I'm old.
The engine might be smaller, but
those controversial new turbo
chargers means Aston's V12
now produces 600 horsepower,
which is, you know, enough.
Enough, in fact, to make
this the first DB car that
will do over 200mph.
It goes like hell!
Sounds like hell, too.
Woo-hoo!
And hey, it's still rear wheel
drive, the gearbox is still out
the back for better weight
distribution, and now there's even
proper multilink rear suspension.
So if you do happen to accidentally
end up in a massive power slide...
Then, yeah, it'll do that too.
Oops, there it goes again.
I'm so careless.
Now, some might complain that
this British icon has sourced
all of its electronic computery
stuff from Mercedes.
Frankly, I don't care if the stuff
behind the scenes is programmed
by German guys in wire-rimmed
glasses, it doesn't bother me at all,
mostly because, unlike old Astons,
it actually works.
Besides, all the tactile stuff
is still just as it should be.
There's leather.
It's very leathery.
And this metal is very metally.
And this wood is very - ooh!
I'm just kidding, that's nice wood.
Now the armrest.
You don't have to go through
all that effort of manually
sliding it back to get to the little
bit of storage underneath there.
No, there's a switch here
that does that for you.
I cannot believe that I
have been manually sliding
armrests all these years, like an ape.
That is time I cannot get back.
So it's great to drive.
Great to spend time in.
But it should be.
The DB11 is 155 grand.
Which does raise that old debate.
For about half the money, you
could have a Nissan GTR,
which has about the same
power, and four wheel drive,
and will annihilate this Aston
around any circuit on earth.
But come on, that's not
the point of the DB11.
This is a luxury yacht.
Not a speed boat.
It's a private jet.
Not a jet fighter.
It's about understated elegance.
Sophisticated, effortless, cool.
Yeah.
Which means this race track is not
where the DB11 was meant to live.
However, we've installed a useful
new feature on this race track.
Narnia had its wardrobe, Bill
and Ted had their phone booth
and Stargate had its...
its Stargate.
Top Gear now has its left at hammer head.
That's right.
Left turn at hammer head.
OK.
First time for everything.
Let's do this.
Oh, yeah!
Now we're talking.
Sweet!
Yeah.
Just call me...
Le Bond.
Matt Le Bond.
Would have been nice if
it came with the pants.
Of course, every hero needs a villain.
Introducing...
The Mercedes S63 AMG coupe, a
two door with an evil streak.
It's huge, it is ostentatious.
I mean, I've got cameras that
scan the road ahead for bumps,
and for some reason I have Swarovski
crystals in the headlights.
I'm coming to get you, Le Bond.
Who the hell is that?
Oh...
Hey.
I get it.
Bond villain?
Let me guess, Dr No-hair?
You're loving this, aren't you?
You've got the car, you've got the suit.
Oh, hey, listen, Hillary Clinton
called - she wants her jacket back.
Look, I didn't even choose this!
Oi!
That's a V8, right?
Well, a twin turbo V8, yes.
V12.
Twin turbo V12.
Horsepower?
580.
You?
Only 600.
OK, look, pretend Mercedes, real
Mercedes, more talk and let's
face it, it's a better driver.
It's on.
Bulldozer, bulldozer!
That's actually an articulating loader.
Get out of the way.
I've got a smug American to kill.
Let's see how you cope with this, Le Bond!
Full beam, is there no limit to his evil?
Where's he going?
Decision, decisions.
He's lost!
Here's good.
Such a picturesque country.
Ooh.
Sorry.
Enjoy your lunch!
130...
140...
150...
Wow, this car's quick.
Live with this, Le Bond.
You see, the thing about that
Merc is, it's limited to 155.
This DB11 isn't.
Later, Harris.
Whoa.
That was a New Holland TN90 F.
Classic.
Did you see the police?
Of course I saw the police,
and I think they saw us.
Ooh!
What kind of police cars
are those, Dr No-hair?
They are Vauxhall Astras, Le Bond.
We can outrun those, right?
Absolutely.
This is cool.
Oh, yes.
Police.
Police everywhere.
We're surrounded, Le Bond.
We're surrounded.
Oh, it's very bad.
It's very, very bad.
Where are your trousers?
Don't draw attention to it.
That was fun, that was really fun.
Yeah.
Thank you.
So, left at hammer head.
Yes, I think it opens up a
whole new world of opportunities, right?
You just have to pack
an extra pair of pants.
That would be wise.
OK, let's talk about the cars.
You love this Mercedes, right?
It is fantastic, it's 20 grand
cheaper than the Aston Martin.
It's the best GT car I have ever driven.
I mean, I arrive at places feeling
more relaxed than when I started.
Double glazing, best hi-fi I've ever heard.
Best GT car you've ever driven?
It's wonderful, just a great car to be in.
It is very subtle.
I like that.
Yeah, yeah, it's not overstated,
and you say you really like it.
But it does miss one thing.
There is one important
thing it doesn't have.
Are you ready?
It doesn't have THIS.
This badge, right here.
It doesn't have that.
You're so vain!
This badge here was founded
by Karl Benz in 1885.
He invented the motor car.
This thing has provenance.
But it doesn't have THIS badge.
This one right here.
THIS badge.
And do you want to know
why that's relevant?
I'll show you.
Who here would take the Mercedes?
That woman over there.
OK.
And who here...
OK, let me finish.
Who here would have the Aston?
Ouch!
I am disappointed in each
and every one of you.
You've let yourselves down.
It's a great car, it's a great
car, but it's not an Aston Martin.
Fair enough.
Right, OK.
Now there's one thing to do.
Find out how fast the DB11
went round our test track.
You know what that means -
it's time for the Stig!
Here he is then, on the line in the DB11.
600 horsepower, twin turbo V12.
Pretty good traction off the line.
Howling up past the heli-shot.
Braking zone, looks heavy,
doesn't it, look at the roll
on the car straight away.
Stig, very relaxed in there,
very leathery and woody.
A bit of tyre smoke coming out.
This has got so much power.
Braking hard, look at the pitch,
look at the weight moving around.
Hammerhead.
Managed to hold his line, but
watch the oversteer on the exit.
Managing it all the way.
That was sexy driving.
Over to the right-hand side now.
Braking hard into Hammerhead.
Again, it stops well,
but it does look heavy.
Look at the lean, a bit
of understeer to start with,
then Stig gets on the
throttle, neutralises it.
What happens on the exit?
Here we go.
That's just showboating.
Super slick oversteer.
Look at the smoke there,
the diff opening up a bit.
Maybe the diff isn't that tight.
Through the follow-through.
That's really fast and
skilful through there.
Bang, that was aggressive.
Braking hard into second to last.
What's it like here?
Looks very, very stable to me.
But it doesn't look that grippy.
That was using all the track.
Now left into Gambon and over the line.
That looked fast.
OK, the new Aston Martin DB11 went
around the track in one minute 21.5.
Right there.
It's ahead of the M3.
Before you ask, before you
even ask, we had the Stig take
the S 63 around as well.
What do you think?
It's perfect.
Yeah, right, absolutely.
So the Mercedes AMG S 63 did
it in one minute 24 flat.
Oooh, that goes there.
Well, it's totally irrelevant.
What?
Hold on, you, Chris Harris,
pro racing driver, car guru,
is going to tell me that in the
context of comparing two cars
that the lap time between those
two cars is totally irrelevant?
It's totally irrelevant!
This is a comfort game.
This is a comfortable car.
I can sometimes be, you know, rational.
You can also sometimes be a sore loser.
Rory.
And a bit later on in the show,
I'll be proving you don't need
to spend supercar money to
keep up with supercars.
You just need the right machinery.
And the right driver.
Yeah. Not you!
All right, now it is time
to meet this week's guest.
Star of Green Wing, Friday Night Dinner
and Episodes.
Great show.
Please welcome Tamsin Greig.
Wow.
All right?
How are you?
So glad to see you. So glad you're here.
Tamsin and I have been
friends for a long time.
We do the other show together, obviously.
And we have kissed on camera.
- On camera.
- I vomited on you.
- Yeah.
- On camera.
- You did.
And you kicked and punched me
repeatedly on and off camera.
Yeah.
But we never have had the chat.
The what?
The chat, you know?
The chat, what chat?
Tamsin Greig...
We want to know about your first one.
Oh. Because this is a car show, right?
Yeah, your first car, what did
you think I was talking about?
Your first car, come on.
A Fiat Uno.
Oooooo!
Yeah, guys!
And it gave me this kind of exultant
feeling of liberty
and I was very, very happy in that car.
An exultant feeling of liberty?
You don't get a lot of that.
That's the first poetry
ever induced by a Fiat Uno.
But the Fiat Uno became a, kind
of like, gangster car after that.
- Did it?
- It did.
No, no.
In Chipping Norton.
In Kilburn, where I grew up.
And, yeah, it became...
The souped up version.
The Turbo IE.
Thank you.
Is that the one you had?
No, I had the basic one
that sounded like a fridge.
The door made that really satisfying noise.
And did things move up after that car?
After that car, then I got
a Citroen AX, which...
Yeah, guys!
Aren't you glad you've got me on your show?
- I have a Citroen AX now.
- What, still?
- I still have one.
- How old is it?
It is 1988.
They were famously unreliable,
though, so did you ever
break down in it?
Yeah, I did. I did break down once.
There's a tiny little road that
goes over the Lake District
called Rhino's Pass.
And I was on my own with a dog.
And I thought to myself,
this would be a really bad
place to break down.
At which point my gear
stick came off in my hand,
and this was before mobile phones.
And so I got out of the car
with the dog, at sundown,
so I'm walking down the
mountain of this little road,
and managed to find a little house.
And there was a house
there, a couple there,
and I used their phone and
phoned the breakdown services
and they found me.
I said to the AA guy...
Are we allowed to say AA?
- Can we say that?
- Is that advertising?
Yeah, you can.
The man from Alcoholics
Anonymous came, and he said...
I said, it's so brilliant to see
you, I was really, really worried.
I'm here on my own, and
I'm female, I'm female!
And it could have been a nightmare.
And the guy, without blinking,
said to me, "It's not a nightmare."
"It would have been a nightmare
if I'd had a knife."
That's horrid!
That's what the recovering alcoholic said.
The recovering alcoholic
said, hiding his weapons.
Can we stop the horror stories,
because that's frankly harrowing.
Can we talk about Episodes,
because I'm a big fan.
You've just filmed the last season.
Why does it have to end?
Tamsin didn't want to do it any more.
Well, boo to you.
Awwwww, well I'm glad we're
leaving you on a high.
I think it's really good to
know when to end stories.
Yeah. Don't you?
It's great to just know when you're done.
I kind of feel like we've told our story.
Leave them wanting more.
We have tried to get a clip of this.
It was quite difficult
to get a pre-watershed,
friendly clip, but here we go.
You want to loosen up, don't
hunch your shoulders.
Still hunching...
Still hunching!
Those are my shoulders.
Really?
Both hands tight on the grip.
It's loud!
Holy crap!
Well done, darling.
That was no bloody car door.
I'm never doing this again,
because it was loud!
All right, my turn.
What?!
Well done, well done.
Great wrist action.
Thanks, did that look like...
Yeah, what was that? Was it a .357?
No, no.
No!
It was a Smith Wesson .44.
It's a big cannon.
Yes.
I mean, I stood there for a long time.
That's why my arms look so toned.
Because it was the whole day
I was stood there like that.
OK, I want to show you something
very special now, OK.
A couple of years ago, Renault
thought they had spotted
a gap in the market place, and
they have just created this.
Have a look at this.
This is delicious.
The Alpine 110.
Al-peen?
"Al-peen", yeah.
It's a fast Renault.
Not Al-pine?
It's an Al-peen.
OK, now, the Porsche Cayman
is worth 40,000 pounds and up, so Renault
thought, we can offer a cheaper car.
So it's about 250 horsepower, 1250 kg.
It's mid-engined, it's sexy as hell.
Look at that, it's just perfect.
And it's developed by the guys
at Renault Sport, and they know
a thing or two about
making great, fast cars.
Except there's one problem.
It's not cheaper than a Porsche Cayman.
Is it?
It's about 60,000 pounds.
That is the slight issue.
They identified the gap in the
market and then they totally
missed the gap in the market!
And it's actually more expensive
than a Porsche Cayman.
Yeah.
And it's also named after a toilet cleaner.
Alpine? Al-peen.
Al-peen.
Alpine, it's Alpine fresh.
Does he look like a man who
buys his own toilet cleaner?
Yeah, he doesn't know
what we're talking about!
Why can't I buy my own toilet cleaner?
Do you go to the shops
and buy toilet cleaner?
Whoa, why is everybody
talking like this to me?
Ask him, Rory. Do it
from that side as well.
Name one brand of toilet cleaner.
Al-peen.
Ermmmm...
Fairy liquid! Fairy liquid!
Toilet.
You wash your...
Fairy liquid.
You wash your toilet with fairy liquid?
After doing the dishes. OK.
409.
That's in the States.
That's a car.
It's the stuff with the funny neck
on it, so you can get under the rim.
Duck. Duck.
All right, time to see how
your training session
went with the loving, caring, kind, tender,
gentle Chris Harris.
Let's take a look.
What's the fastest you've been in a car?
- I think about 90 miles an hour.
- 19?!
Or 90? 90!
90, OK, this could be interesting.
Let's go.
Just be nice, all right?
No, nothing gets done if you're not nice.
OK, I'll try. OK, full power.
You've got 7000 revs, use them! Louder.
Second, third gear now.
Whoa, it's in there somewhere.
Sorry. Fourth gear.
You know the bit on the show where
you have to set the fast lap?
That's this bit.
You are aware of that, aren't you?
Is this it?
Fourth gear.
Keep going.
We need a sundial to time
this, not a stopwatch.
Be clear.
Down here, straight. Braking
hard now, right, right.
No, left of the... You said right!
Just say every bit.
Round there, round there, to the right.
This is the famous Hammerhead.
Don't get it wrong.
Left, left, left, left.
Right.
That's no bloody good, is it.
What are you...? What are you doing?
I'm really glad you're here.
You've been very helpful in many ways.
But I'm feeling a kind of...
A wave of anger coming from you.
I'm just interested in
what that's all about.
I'm angry because we're trying to go
fast and you're not going fast yet.
I just want to go fast.
I am going fast, faster than I was.
You think you're going fast.
OK, you're a teacher.
If you get angry when I can't quite
do what you're asking me to do,
that's going to reflect badly on you.
Not on me.
So I think you just need to calm down.
And maybe we can just
start by saying please.
Or, and, thank you.
But if I use those pleasantries,
will you go faster.
Yes.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I will.
All right, are we ready? Yeah.
Teach me.
Don't point.
Can we go, can we please
move the steering wheel
in a rightward direction.
Now, before we're driving? Now, please.
Before we go.
Let's go.
Now accelerate and use the throttle
and into second gear, please.
Thank you.
And into third gear, please,
if you feel like it.
Thank you.
Now four. Thank you.
Now over to the left but
avoid the cameraman,
because that would be bad.
Now down the end here. Come on!
Get on... Please hurry up.
Where am I going?
Left, left is good. Over there.
Maybe just also say...
OK, OK, OK. Come on, Tamsin!
I know you've got it in you, come on!
And can you please, please, brake
between the 100 and the 50.
Brake, brake!
Don't shout. Third gear, please.
Left, left.
I feel like we've been
through something there.
How do you feel?
I feel that you have improved as a driver,
and that I have improved as a human being.
Win, win, win.
Now get out the fucking car!
And just think about how
you've been behaving.
That was great. You see what you get?
I can't help it.
No, she was very, very good.
She really was.
Yeah.
It looked pretty slippery out there, too.
It's the worst conditions there have
ever been experienced on Top Gear.
In three episodes?
No, ever. Ever?
Wasn't it?
I'm not sure I agree with that,
but sure, whatever you say.
I can't wait to see your time now.
But we'll do that little bit later.
Now, I want to talk about
ancient history, the 1970s.
You see, 40 years ago, if you
lived in Britain and wanted
a fast car that wasn't a pain
to live with, you were stuck
with something like this.
The Triumph Dolomite Sprint.
Yeah, the 70s kind of sucked.
But one humble hatchback
was about to change
all of that forever.
1977.
The original Volkswagen
Golf GTI lands in the UK.
Its mission, to prove you can have
practicality and proper performance.
Mission successful.
The GTI was quicker than most sports cars.
0-60 took barely eight seconds.
By 70s standards, that was warp speed.
The GTI was a game-changer.
And in the mid-1980s, with
the rest of the world
running to catch up, VW dropped this.
The second-generation Golf GTI.
Big bumpers, and big attitude.
Damn, this thing's good!
But then came the 1990s, and the
GTI became heavier and uglier.
The Mark 4 was so porky, it
was actually slower to 60
than the 70s original.
But VW wasn't done yet.
Argh!
That is more I like it.
Yes, the Mark 5.
Loads more power, way more nimble.
This was a hot hatch for the noughties.
And by 2009, with the Mark 6, VW had
officially rediscovered its mojo.
The GTi was back.
That brings us, 40 years after
the original GTi landed
in the UK, to this - the
Volkswagen Golf GTi Clubsport S.
The most powerful production Golf ever.
306 horses, nearly three
times as many as that
original GTi from the '70s.
And that's the kind of inflation
I think we can all get behind.
And because it's a proper old school
Golf, all the power heads that way.
By rights, front wheel drive
cars like should understeer,
but the Clubsport S doesn't, it
just grips and grips and grips.
How is it doing this?
That just makes no sense!
This is a fast, fast car.
Woo-hoo!
Yes, yes, yes!
You can almost smell the
engineering quality.
It feels like 40 years of
perfecting the hot hatch formula.
It feels sophisticated.
It feels expensive.
Which, I'm afraid, it is.
In fact, this Clubsport S model cost 34,000 pounds.
That's nearly three grand
more than a Ford Focus RS,
which has more power, four
wheel drive and rear seats.
Did I not mention that?
Well, yes, as part of their weight
saving measures, Volkswagen has
chopped out the rear bench
and replaced it with a pole
and some garden netting.
The rear parcel shelf has also gone,
along with most of the insulation.
They've even ditched the floor mats.
And there's no armrest.
And guess how much that crash diet saves?
30 kilos.
I mean, you can put that
back on after a big kebab!
The Clubsport has all the
performance, but almost none
of the practicality.
It's like it's forgotten
what hot hatches stand for.
I'd argue this isn't
really a hot hatch at all.
So, if it's not a hot hatch, what is it?
Well, ask Volkswagen and
they will tell you it's
a two seater sports car, with
an appetite for race tracks.
One race track in particular.
The Nurburgring.
The scariest circuit on the planet.
13 miles and 73 corners of twisting.
Terrifying tarmac.
And the spiritual home of the Clubsport S.
This is officially the fastest
front wheel drive car
ever to lap this track.
It was developed here, tested here.
Every detail has been tweaked
to make this go as fast
as possible, out there.
It even has sticky tyres, fade
resistant brakes and proper
functional spoilers.
So what's this track
ready Golf really like?
To find out, I've turned up to
a typical German track day,
to see if the Clubsport S can
keep up with the locals, who,
let's face it, seem to take
things pretty seriously.
Yes, getting the very best out
of the Golf in this field
was going to take some real driving talent.
Right.
Let's do this.
Hi Rory, welcome.
Yes, why don't you show me round?
For you, I've got a special present.
A map of the track and then you
know where we are exactly.
You think we can keep up?
No problem!
With Sabine in confident
mood, we headed out to see
what the Golf was made of.
It's like a little go-kart.
A front wheel drive go-kart - so much fun.
OK.
I love the carousel.
OK, now I'm scared.
I love it.
Argh!
Your name is Rory Reid, not Rory Worried.
I'm very worried right now.
Oh my God.
Now I was keen to really
drill down into the merits
of the Golf's chassis dynamics.
Sorry!
But then Sabine spotted some prey.
They're our enemies.
OK, we have some cars up ahead.
So we went hunting.
Come on, little Golf.
What is it?
That's a 3 Series BMW.
Later!
I wonder how he feels,
being overtaken by a Golf?
I think we need another victim.
I can see a Porsche.
That looks like a - it's a Cayman R.
Cayman R.
The quick one.
Bye, bye, baby.
It's a Cayman GT4.
We're just giant killing right now.
I'm going to start writing these down.
Oh yes.
In the hands of Sabine, the
Golf wasn't just keeping
up with the locals...
Loser, loser!
It was owning them.
Come on, little Golf.
Coming closer.
Look at this!
That was a Carrera 4 GTS.
That is a 90,000 pound car.
Oh, cool.
Which made me wonder
while we were out here,
could the Golf overtake
a million quid's worth?
OK.
Only one way to find out.
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on, come on!
What's that?
That's a Corvette.
That's the C6.
Seriously?
It's 90 grand.
There's a Golf GTA on your tail!
Bye!
Sabine, I'm trying to write here!
But Sabine was in the zone.
She was braking later.
On the power earlier.
Woo!
That's a GT3.
They're 100 grand.
The Golf was astonishing.
Nissan GTR.
80 grand.
Now past the half million pound mark.
We need more.
Sabine wasn't done yet.
Come on, come on, come on.
What is it?
That looks like a Porsche 911 Turbo.
I'll catch you, my friend.
You are on it, you are on it.
No brakes.
We're catching him.
Get out of my way.
911 Turbo.
Destroyed.
How much is it?
That's 130k!
Wow.
Woo-hoo!
With 700 grands-worth of overtakes
now in the bag, nothing was safe
from our little hatch back.
What is that?
That's a Lamborghini.
A Lamborghini!
That's a 570 Superleggera!
And I mean nothing.
Oh my God.
Oh my God!
Then, around the next corner...
One more, one more.
Yes.
911 GT3 RX.
If you get this, you've done it.
Get him.
Come on, little Golf.
Are we going to get the GT3?
Are we going to get it?
Can we overtake it?
We've got him, we got him!
We got him!
Have some of that!
You are not human.
This car...
I love my job!
Very nice.
Great driving, Sabine.
Great driving, you crossed everything.
Yeah, even him.
No, the car was really great.
Yes.
Good handling, like a little
go-kart, so I had so much fun.
I think you had a little
bit fun as well, Rory?
I was having fun up to a point,
and then, you know, my stomach
was churning around a little bit.
But we got there.
How bad?
Not too bad?
It was touch-and-go.
Touch-and-go?
Not that we don't trust Rory's
math, but we added it all up back
at the office, and you
passed?1.1 million worth
of cars out there.
Way to go!
But I must say, I could have done two
million, but I had the heavy fat
oak in my passenger seat.
I thought we were friends!
Down hill, yes, but uphill, no.
Can we just take a minute to
appreciate the Clubsport S.
34 grand is a lot for a hot hatch,
but that's cheap for something that
can annihilate six figure supercars.
Yes, if you have a Sabine driving it.
If it's you or me driving
it, it's just an expensive
Golf with no back seat.
I take your point.
Sabine, we will talk more about that
lap over in Extra Gear later on, OK?
We'll do that.
That's right.
Check it out.
Ladies and gentlemen, Sabine Schmitz.
So no pressure then.
What, so I have to follow that?
Yes.
Is that deliberate?
Well, yes.
How cool was that?
That was really, really brilliant.
Yes.
All right.
Now, it's dream garage, OK.
You have?100,000 to spend,
you want something exciting,
but just a little bit scary.
Something that will get the blood
pumping, but not too much, you know.
What do you get?
OK, I could go BAC Mono.
The car that looks like an F1 car.
Oh yes.
Superb engine, a Chevy
Corvette, maybe, Stingray.
What is it with you and Corvette Stingrays?
Cayman GT4, with shaved down rear
tyres for a bit of slidy slidy.
Perfect.
OK.
Both good answers, both wrong answers.
Because if you want to
spend?100,000 on something
exciting but a bit scary,
you want one of these.
Huh?
That is the Bunning
Lowlander, Widebody 380HD.
That's what you want.
What the hell is that?
That's a rear end muck spreader, obviously.
HD stands for high-definition.
How do you know that?
Everybody knows that.
I don't know that.
These people all know that.
You know that?
Yes.
Yes, thanks, cheers.
So that thing just spreads poo?
Well, yes, it spreads poo, but
that's not all it spreads.
Oh no!
Want to know what else it spread?
What else does it spread?
A melon, a shed and a Volvo.
Check this out.
This is the Bunning Lowlander
Widebody 380HD and it spreads muck.
Really well.
Check this out.
OK, I got my trusty
assistant with me today.
She's super competent.
Her name's Tamsin Greig.
Let's rock and roll.
Mind my melons!
I think this is going to be fun, Tam.
Oh, it's a melon storm.
Wow!
What a mess!
Next is the shed.
OK, Tam, he's all loaded.
That is a shed in the chute.
Let's make some matchsticks.
Ooh!
Are you having fun?
There is still one side of it
left, being a bit stubborn.
OK, Tam, I got the perfect
thing to get rid of that
last piece of wood.
Our scrap Volvo.
OK, this is the big one, Tam.
We're going to need full power, I think.
There goes the bonnet.
Oh, the poor Volvo.
I've never you so excited!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, there goes the wheel.
There's a lot of leg room in that car now!
So there you have it.
That is the Bunning
Lowlander Widebody 380HD.
It spreads stuff.
All over the place.
Hold on - that's a poo spreader.
What kind of animal produces
the kind of poo that needs
a machine like that?
It doesn't matter.
Any animal.
It'll spread anything, anywhere, any time.
I have never seen you look so happy.
I think you enjoyed yourself
too, in the big tractor.
That was good, because I was
the one making the things
and the things and the...
But I knew you'd know about this
stuff, because you play a farmer
in The Archers, don't you.
I play a farmer on Radio 4's,
you don't know about this
because you never ask me any
questions, on a programme
called The Archers.
The Archers?
The Archers.
Is that an archery show, what is that?
Tell him.
The Archers is a long-running
radio show on Radio 4.
It started in 1951, I think. Mm-hm.
And it's about a made up
a place called Ambridge.
You've been on a radio show since 1951?!
Not that long. '91.
Yeah. That long?
Yeah, I let them warm up for
30 years before I joined it.
How did I not know this?
Because you don't ask me any questions.
That's right.
I've done a lot of stuff with muck
spreading and my character drives
a huge combine harvester, which is
kind of the size of a bungalow.
What kind of combine harvester?
A big one.
The size of a bungalow.
Is it an International
Harvester, a John Deere?
What is it?
It's like a chair in a radio studio.
But I stand on the chair to
get height differential.
Why?
Because then you can hear the
difference in height when I'm up
there and someone is shouting
to me from down there.
So it sounds like a tall machine.
So you record your pieces
standing on a chair?
Yeah, and shouting down
to the person who's not
in the combine harvester.
You should see me when I'm riding a horse!
All right, now it's time to see how
you went around our test track.
Are you ready?
The big moment. Yeah.
How do you think you did? Well...
I was really afraid. Great.
Really afraid. Great.
And I was most afraid of the weather.
And being in the car on my own.
Was it fun, did you enjoy it?
I did.
It was kind of like, you
know when you've just
had too much coffee... Yeah.
And you remember each coffee,
but then you're left with this
feeling that you don't
know what to do with.
Yeah.
So if that's enjoyment, then yes.
What do you think? Do you
think she had a good time?
Definitely not.
All right, well, shall we take a look?
Before we watch the lap,
though, it needs to be said,
it was really, really slippery.
Almost flooding conditions.
It was horrendous out there.
Just shy of ice.
Let's take a look. OK, here we go.
Tamsin Greig, GT 86.
Pretty good off the line.
Slick gear up into third.
Don't know if I should change
gear, should I change gear?
It's telling me to change gear.
Well, it's too late.
Look at this, good speed, look how
wet it is with puddles everywhere.
Third gear.
Not quite on the line.
Grass!
That's the grass there, Tamsin.
You must have...
You were a bit scared there, weren't you?
You went on the grass.
Here we go, third gear.
I think you're in second there.
I think you're being cautious,
that's the word there, cautious.
Whoa, sorry, I'll pay for that.
Matt will pay for that.
Was that the gearbox again?
Third gear, down the
straight and breaking out.
Look how wet it is.
I do feel sorry for you. It's properly wet.
Get on the power.
Sorry, I'll pay for that one.
Matt will pay for the first.
Down the back straight.
Breathe, come on breathe.
You weren't breathing
in training, were you?
No, you weren't.
There's the follow-through.
Safely navigated.
It's really brilliant when
you go fast around corners!
Through the tyres.
You can actually accelerate around corners!
I've never been able to do
that in north-west London.
Look at your line, it was always
really good into that corner.
That was the one.
Was it?
That's the most unsighted
corner on the circuit,
but you always nailed it.
OK, Gambon.
Pfft! It's not...
It's what we call controlled driving.
Yeah! Yeah.
OK, now considering it was
a swimming pool out there,
are you happy with that?
It looks a lot slower than it felt.
It was like an old lady going to the shops.
Chris, how do you think she did?
I'm confident.
I think we've got a good solid time,
and we've got someone that's alive.
OK, are you ready?
The time to beat is still
1:39.5 set by Max Whitlock,
the Olympic demigod.
Have you ever seen his scissor
work on the pommel horse?
Fantastic. Calm down.
Tamsin Greig...
You went around our track in one minute...
Yes!
58.7.
Yes! That's a wet time.
That is a wet time.
You're OK.
Look at that.
That's the second-fastest wet time.
And the last wet time we had
was not nearly that wet.
It wasn't. That's a good wet time.
We are here, we are alive, and
I haven't brought too much
shame on the family.
No shame. We all win.
I did really, really secretly enjoy it.
You should be proud of yourself.
That was great.
Ladies and gentlemen, Tamsin Greig.
You were great, fantastic.
Thanks. Thank you, well done.
You're still alive, so we're all good.
OK, now I want to talk sports cars.
Not big, intimidating,
fire-breathing supercar
monsters, but affordable,
adorable, attainable cars.
Cars with romance, you know?
The thing about sports cars
like that, there's only
one place that springs to mind, right?
Italy.
There's just something
about it, isn't there?
Especially if you're in a classic
Italian sports car, like this.
The Fiat 124 Spider.
Bella, huh?
Born in 1966, the 124 Spider
was designed by Pininfarina.
It had a sparkling twin cam
engine, a cutting edge
5-speed manual gearbox.
And it weighed about as
much as an actual spider.
And it was bellissima to drive.
It still is.
Still is...
The 124 Spider was so good, so
timeless, that Fiat kept building
it for nearly two decades.
But that was 30 years ago.
And ever since, fans of simple,
sensibly-priced Italian two seaters
have been left kind of hungry.
But now, Fiat has a new dish on the menu.
This is the Fiat 124 Spider Abarth.
A classic name, classic recipe.
Small, lightweight,
brilliantly back to basics.
It's stick shift, rear-wheel
drive, and the roof is not some
complicated, Transformer
robot of metal and motors.
It's just a little scrap of fabric
you operate using one of these.
Just pop it up and pop it down.
Simple as that.
And when you get it out on the road,
you can really start to appreciate
that beautiful simplicity.
Hello, parmigiana, panna cotta.
Oh right, the car...
See, this 124 is a throwback
to a less complicated age.
Sure, sometimes you want a
state-of-the-art sports car
with your torque vectoring and
your magnetic adaptive damping
and a double clutch gearbox and
a Wi-Fi enabled milk frother.
But sometimes you just want
to keep it simple, right?
So, after a 30 year absence, is
this finally the genuine Italian
sports car we've been waiting for?
Buongiorno.
Une caffe espresso si prega?
Well, here's the problem.
I'm not really in Italy...
Hiya!
I'm in Los Angeles, and this is a film set.
And this waiter, he's not
called Alessandro or Giuseppe.
His name is Hunter.
Hey.
Can you read my film script?
Oh, sure.
And this 124 is not an Italian car.
Sure, it's got a Fiat badge
on it and a few bits
of it come from Italy, but
underneath, this is Japanese.
Specifically, it's one of these.
A Mazda Miata, or MX-5,
as you guys call it.
And while pretty much every
car in the world shares
something with another car,
these two share pretty
much everything.
Check out the Mazda's cabin.
And now check out the Fiat's cabin.
Mazda.
Fiat.
Wait, hang on, which is which?
The 124 is even built in Japan, on the same
production line as the MX-5.
Now, if you're going to borrow
from a little sports car,
the MX-5 is definitely
where you want to start.
However, the stuff the Italians have
added seems to have made it worse.
You see, where as the Mazda uses
a naturally aspirated motor,
this 124 uses a turbo motor.
Yeah, you get a bit of extra power,
168 horsepower, to be exact.
And this 124 goes 0-60 in 6.8 seconds
and has a top speed of 144 miles an hour
Quick enough to leave a Mazda its dust.
But, and this may sound picky,
but that's kind of my job,
these kind of cars are meant to be
all about instant throttle response
and high revs and keeping you
connected to the chassis.
But here, when you put your foot
down, there's just a little bit
of turbo lag, a slight hesitation
before things get going.
Just enough to break the connection.
It's like trying to tie your
shoelaces with boxing gloves on.
It's a pain in the ass.
So the Mazda has the Fiat beaten on feel.
But at least the 124 is cheap, right?
Well, no.
This one cost nearly 30
grand, almost nine grand more
than the fastest MX-5.
Mamma Mia.
Don't get me wrong, this
isn't an awful car.
But this was Fiat's chance to summon
the ghost of all those classic
Italian sports cars to
revive that 60s spirit.
Yeah, it's a fun car to flick
around on a winding canyon road,
but to call it the 124...
I don't know.
That name feels like it
should have that 60s spirit,
and this car, it just doesn't.
It's like, the way it looks,
all 21st-century retro.
It's just a bit... Fake.
So if you want a two seat
Italian sports car that takes
you back to the golden age,
and come on, who doesn't?
I'm afraid I can't recommend the Fiat 124.
I can, however, recommend the Fiat 124.
Seriously.
If you want to live out all
those 60s Italy fantasies,
and I really don't blame you
if you do, then why not do it
in a car from 60s Italy?
Molto bene.
Bonasera.
Pappa da pupeda.
♪ On days like these
♪ I wonder what became of you
♪ Maybe today you're singing
songs with someone new...
I tried, I wanted to like it.
I really did, I really wanted to like it.
Yeah, you're right.
It's a let down.
I just can't get on board with the styling.
To me it's kind of, I don't
know, a little droopy.
Such a disappointment.
And the worst thing is, it doesn't
even feel rear-wheel drive,
because it's got so much grip.
Yeah. This is a beautiful moment.
What? What?
We agree!
We all hate it!
On next week's show, I'm
the first person ever
to review the Bugatti Chiron.
Yeah.
And I'm the first person ever
to review the new Ducati
1299 Superleggera.
And they gave me a Renault Twingo.
It's a big, big show.
We'll see you then.
Good night.