Hope
you're ready to howl.
On this show,
we're bringing you
more of the hysterical
animal clips you love,
including a crazy catastrophe,
a fast food freeloader,
and improbable punk quick guard,
and a daughter-doggy dance.
You're watching "World's
Funniest Animals."
Hey, and welcome
to another episode
of "World's Funniest Animals."
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton.
Today I'm joined by
my trusty psychics,
Hank and Ruby,
and a few friends,
and panelists,
as well as our celebrity guest,
Jennifer Veal.
- Hi, everyone.
Happy to be here.
I cannot wait to see what
we have in store tonight.
- Thanks for being
here, Jennifer.
On tonight's show,
we've got more of the
stuff you love the most.
Silly animal videos that
are sure to make you laugh.
Plus plenty of animals
that are just plain cute.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelists,
actor Carmen Hodson.
- Hey, Liz.
- This next part features some
adorable animal affection.
- This sounds really good.
This is so adorable.
- Our next panelist is
the amazing comedian,
Brian Cooper.
- Hey Liz.
- We have some animal
cuddling in this clip.
- I do not think
I can handle this.
And this was when they started
as best friends for life.
- Now we are joined by
actor, writer, producer,
Noah Matthews.
- Hey, Liz.
- We have some animals
cuddling in this clip.
- I love these kinds of videos.
The most comfortable
pillow in the room
is your brother's head.
- For our final panelist,
we have singer, actor,
comedian, radio host,
Mikalah Gordon.
- Hi, Liz.
- Are you ready for an animal
who just wants to
give some love?
- What?
I need to see this.
Look at his butt.
Look at him trying to get out.
- We're back with a fan favorite
"Hidden Talent."
- Another slam dog,
I am on fire!
- Okay, I've never
done this before.
Is this how you stand on it?
It's getting bro, move over,
I'm gonna ride.
Look mom, no hands!
- This dog is better
balanced than me.
- She just couldn't find
another dance
partner her height.
- It's that time again,
where we visit a celebrity
guest in their home
and get to know their pet.
Tonight's celebrity
guest is my good friend,
Jennifer Veal.
from "Jessie" and "This Just In"
Hey, Jenny.
Thanks for being here.
- Hey, Liz.
- I see you have
someone there with you.
Tell us about them.
- This is called Melina,
also known as Lilly for sure.
And she is quite a diva,
but she's my best
little friend.
Aren't you?
- Have you ever worked
with any animals on set?
- Lizzie, I don't know how we...
I haven't thought this before,
but you and I have had
an animal encounter.
When we were in India,
we went to the Monkey Temple.
And I was on the
impression that maybe
like one, two, three monkeys.
No, that wasn't,
was that, Lizzie?
There was about 5,000 monkeys
climbing on top of my head.
Picking things out of my hair.
I think I have a picture of
one on my head somewhere,
but I mean, it was an
amazing experience.
- Hey Jenny, can your
dog do any tricks for us?
- Yes, Lizzie.
She does Lizzie,
and I'm so glad he loves.
Lilly,
do as you please.
See, she's really good
at doing if she pleases.
That's whatever she wants.
Oh, Lilly, of course
you're very cute.
- Thanks so much for
stopping by, Jenny.
Coming up,
we have pets who are
clearly the jealous type.
That's not me.
Next on "World's
Funniest Animals."
They can't talk,
but if they could,
these next pets can
definitely be saying,
"Hey, that's not me."
- Okay, this dog is like,
"I'm the only one freaked out.
Guys, it's a tiger!"
- Wait for it.
Peekaboo.
- Just a little closer.
Oh, come on, I dare you.
Oh, you're lucky,
I can't reach you.
Oh, okay, too close.
- To be young and in love.
Here's our absolutely
adorable segment,
"Puppy Love."
- Oh, this is so cute.
But little do we know,
they were playing
with glue before this.
Super glue.
This is cuteness overload.
- I can't tell if this bear
is nice or this guy is insane.
- See, this is always
one of those videos
they show after the fact.
- I have no idea
what's going on here,
but I just know it's cute.
And just
in case you cat lovers
are feeling left out,
we present for your enjoyment,
a montage of cozy kitties.
- Oh, little
baby kittens!
He's hugging her arm.
Not yet, you're not
done petting me.
I will tell you
when you're done.
- Coming up,
these pets have been
caught red handed, guilty.
Next on "World's
Funniest Animals."
Do you guys have
a good poker face
or can someone usually
tell when you're lying?
Well, while some may be
good at hiding their shame,
others wear it right
on their faces,
like the animals in our
next segment, "Guilty."
- Yeah, I was wondering
why the housekeeping
at this hotel was so bad.
- Yeah he ran out of the
little mince an hour ago,
now he's just eating soap.
He stole it.
- When he can't eat just one.
The only way to
show you what just happened
is by video.
Charlie got the yogurt
and ran with it,
and the yogurt was.
- Man, this guy's
house is a pig sty.
Oh my God, what a mess!
- That I think is,
this guy has four pigs
that live with him,
and he's surprised
they made a mess.
- Do you think this
has happened before,
or does this person just always
wanna keep an eye on his fridge?
- I don't know what's weird.
The fact that this man was
gonna swallow a whole fish,
or that the bird instead
went for the fries.
- To our pets, we
are the whole world.
We feed them, walk
them, take care of them.
So naturally,
they can be a bit possessive.
- There can be only one.
- Oh, not sure which is worse.
The fact that this cat
is jealous of everything
or that this woman
pets household items.
- Think about it this way,
if your girlfriend met
an exact puppet of you
and started going
on dates with it,
how would you feel?
- Puppy giving kisses.
Hi, puppy.
Give me a kiss.
Give Annie a kiss now.
You are not a person.
He's not a person,
but he does have feelings,
like jealousy.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey,
don't eat the camera.
- Really?
Really.
That's my camera.
That's not funny.
It's expensive.
Hey, Riches, Riches.
- Really?
Really.
- You won't believe some
of the amazing tricks
people's pets can do.
"Mad Skillz" next on
"World's Funniest Animals."
Welcome back.
You're just in time for one
of my favorite segments,
where we get a close look at
some pretty, skilled critters.
I mean, very skilled,
"Mad Skillz."
- This is taking bobbing for
apples to a whole new level.
More like launching for apples.
- Oh yes, you guessed it.
The downward dog.
- I feel so relaxed.
Beer me.
Good, shut the door.
Shut the door.
Can you give me a crizy?
Good boy.
Here, throw this away.
Throw it away.
Good, here.
Go throw it away.
Throw it away.
Oh, good, throw it away.
Good, shut this door.
Shut it.
Good boy.
- This is every man's dream dog.
- Now it just needs to
learn to order pizza.
- Okay, my favorite
part about this
is when the other dog
whites out on a surf board,
and then so he jumps
onto his friend's board.
- These next pets
have been caught
red handed.
- I told you the toilet
paper goes over not under.
- Well, next time
you get the creamer.
- Yoink!
Oh, snap!
- This seems pretty calm
until the other monkey
jumped on the camera.
- How many bananas
does this guy have?
- Oh my God!
Wait for it.
- I told you not to
vlog while driving.
Now that's what you get.
- Teddy.
- Teddy,
what did you do?
What did you do?
- Teddy, come on.
- You bad girl.
Hey, what happened here?
What happened here?
- What happened?
- Who did it?
Who did it?
- Well, that's almost ii for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here's a quick recap of
all the funniest moments.
Possessive pooches,
a resentful reptile,
cuddling cats,
a swindling seagull,
a Yogi Yorkie,
a monkey misappropriating
room service,
a dancing dog,
and a German shepherd
who can just about fly.
That's it for this episode of
"World's Funniest Animals."
A special thanks to our panel
and to our celebrity
guest, Jennifer Veal,
for joining us and talking
all things animals.
- Oh, and thanks Liz.
It was our pleasure.
- I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton,
and I'll be back with
more hilarious videos
on "World's Funniest Animals."
See you then.