- Get ready for more
hilarious animal antics.
We've got a bad to the
bone bulldog, a hind leg
hopping hound, and a kitty
who doesn't want to be caught.
You're watching World's
Funniest Animals.
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton.
Welcome back to World's
Funniest Animals.
Today, I'm joined by my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby.
And a few friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guests Bradford Anderson,
Hi Liz!
We're so happy to be
here, right buddy?
- And Breille Barbusca.
- Hey everyone, We're
super happy to be here
and excited to watch all
of the videos tonight.
- Thanks guys.
Hank, Ruby, and I are excited
to introduce you to some of
the best clips of some
of your favorite animals
that we could find.
If your pet is
anything like mine,
they don't think there's
anywhere that they can't go.
These next animals don't have
a sense of boundaries either.
Let's take a look.
Wild
Animals at Home.
Brought to you with
commentary from our first
panelists, actor Carmen Hodgson.
- What's up Liz.
- Are you ready for
some animals who have
snuck into places
they don't belong?
- Ooh, Awesome. Let's see it.
- Okay, This is so crazy.
The fact that everything
is just so calm before,
and then BAM!
Oh my God, I think I
have the wrong house.
- Our next panelist is the
amazing comedian Brian Cooper.
- Hi, Liz.
- This next clip features
an animal who is not
in their natural habitat.
- Now I've got to see this.
Wow!
- Ah, ha!
- Bro!
Oh my God, what are you doing?
- Narration is the best.
Wow!
Now we are joined by
actor, writer, producer,
Noah Matthews.
- Hey, Liz.
Show me what you got.
We have an animal who
has managed to get
into a pretty sticky situation.
- Oh, yhis should
be interesting.
Slowly open it.
Okay, open it up dear.
There you go.
- We got two big ways
for him to get out
and he just won't go either way.
Okay, mind if I
snap a picture or two as well?
Yeah.
We didn't want
him coming down this way,
so I've kind of
guarded this area.
- Okay.
He's almost
there, come on.
Go for it, man.
- That turkey is like
"Okay, only one of you
tell me which way."
I am getting confused.
It's right there. You
know.
There he goes.
There he goes!
- For our final panelist,
we have singer, actor,
comedian, radio
host, Mikalah Gordon.
Hi Liz.
- Are you ready for
some wild animals
in a not so wild setting?
- What?
I need to see this.
Ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Get down!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Come on!
Prose.
Prose!
Go on out!
- It seems like
this has happened
enough times where they've
now named the bear.
Prose!
Go on out!
Ah!
Go on out.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Come on!
- Did you know that brown bats
have been known to hibernate
for up to a year at a time?
That's a napping talent I
really wish I have myself.
But the animal skills
we're about to see
will really make you envious in
our next segment, Hidden
Talent.
- Did that dog just catch
a bucket, and then catch
balls in the bucket?
Wait a second.
- Such a good and patient pup.
- This is how
champions are trained.
Horse yoga.
- It's time for my favorite
segment of the show,
where a celebrity
guest and their pets
come to us from their home.
From Modern Family
and The Starter Wife,
the amazing Brielle Barbusca.
Hey Brielle, thanks
for joining us.
So who
do we have here?
Hey Liz, this is my dog Lola.
She's my best friend.
Even though she doesn't want
to stay here with me right now.
- Do you think
Lola has any tricks
that can make her go viral?
- Now, Lola does
not have many tricks
that would make her
an internet star.
Besides stealing my snacks.
- Brielle, I hear you
had an experience on set
that turned into a bit
of a dog and pony show.
Tell us about that.
- I worked on a movie last
year called The Adventures
of Dally and Spanky, and onset
there was a pony and a dog.
And the dog would literally
ride the pony around set.
I think they became
internet stars.
- Thanks again for
joining us Brielle.
Some of the
best train pets coming up
next on World's
Funniest Animals.
- I used to have
a coach who said
"perfect practice
makes perfect."
If that's the case, the
animals in our next segment
have been practicing
perfectly for a long time.
Let's check out their
insane abilities
in Training Day.
- I got to work on my moves
and my dog's moves
at this point.
- Yay!
The jump
is the best part.
- Yay!
Up.
- Not sure who's better
- the dog jumping
on his hind legs, or his friends
that trust him and don't move.
Up.
- Oh, Okay, he's
just a big baby.
That's adorable!
- I'm excited to introduce
our celebrity guests
to World's Funniest Animals.
And I'm even more excited
that they brought their pet.
From General
Hospital, it's Bradford Anderson
Bradford, who do you have here?
- This is Dublin,
our 15 week old
Cavalier King Charles Spaniel.
Can you say hey, bud?
- I have to ask, even though
Dublin is just a puppy,
does he know any tricks?
- He's got many talents.
Some of his favorite things
to do are to chew shoes,
especially little
kids water shoes.
Right?
That smell good?
And then of course
mommy's nice shoes.
Oh, very exciting.
But, beyond shoe
chewing and waking us up
three times a night, he's
an incredible soccer player.
- These are some pretty
serious defense skills he has.
Thanks so much for
sharing with us Bradford.
- Thank you so much, Liz.
It was such a blast
being here with you.
Right, bud?
Yes.
Yes, yes.
They say that
imitation is the most
sincere form of flattery.
If that's the case,
these next animals are
really working it to
try and compliment their
human counterparts.
In our next segment,
Just Like Us.
- That's about as cute
as it gets right there.
- Oh my God, hey!
It's Elton John's dog!
- Did they have to
hand-make that outfit?
Where do you even
buy one of those?
- Obviously trust fund kids.
Am I right?
- I'm telling you, I only
doggy paddle with my shades on.
- Some of the cutest
clips I've ever seen,
coming up next on
World's Funniest Animals.
- These next animals
aren't all bark.
They have the skills
to back it up.
Mad Skillz.
- This little dog is
having so much fun.
- This is the way that
I want to walk my dog
on the beach every time.
- Hey guys, this is
what you look like.
Here we go.
- This puppy's amazing!
Good job!
Come on.
- Most of the time, wild
animals belong in two places:
out in nature to be
admired from afar,
and on our televisions
making us laugh.
But these next critters
stuck their noses, and their
antlers and trunks
where they shouldn't be.
And it's pretty great.
Animals Where They Don't Belong.
- Oh, this video is so deer.
- It's a bear.
- Holy...
It's a bear.
It's a bear!
What are you doing?
- This bear is like
"yeah, I'm not interested
in that kind of party."
I've never
seen a bear in a hotel.
seen a bear.
There's a raccoon.
- Can you imagine declaring
that on your insurance?
Yes, the dent came
when I was attacked
by a group of bison.
- More unbelievable
animals to come on
World's Funniest Animals.
- They say that
imitation is the most
sincere form of flattery.
If that's the case, these
next animals are really
working it to try and compliment
their human counterparts.
In our next segment,
You Look Familiar.
- Yeah, I just like to swing.
- I'm just waiting for this
cat to bite his own fingers.
That is what I want to see.
- I got the car, I
got the clothes,
the hat, and the shades.
What else do you need ladies?
- This looks like every couple
that's been married
over 20 years.
Harry, Harry!
Yes, dear.
- Crack open the notepad,
because these expert
trainers are going
to show you some amazing tricks
they've taught their pet.
Pets Have Talent.
- Nothing funny here,
just impressive.
- Okay, this is
just one of those...
wow videos.
I'm speechless.
- I do this every Saturday,
with double dutch.
- Want to do some tricks?
Go under.
Good boy.
Lay down.
Roll over.
Oh, so fast.
High five.
- I think it would make
my absolute day if my
dog high five me.
Like, it would make me so happy.
- Go around.
Can you go under?
Can you jump over?
Ooh, good boy!
- Okay, I will do
all these things
if I got a treat every time.
Come on, someone
give me some candy!
- Can you do some dancing?
Give me kisses.
Thank you.
Oh!
Good job, Poop.
- I balanced on the
beam, and then the stick,
and you keep
putting stuff on me.
What is next?
I just want to be a dog.
Speak.
Whisper.
Whisper
- I have a few neighborhood
dogs that can learn how
to whisper
Speak.
Whisper.
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case you missed
anything, here's a quick recap
of all of the funniest moments.
A defrauding deer, a bevy of
bison, an encroaching elephant
munching monkeys, driving
dogs, a horse doing yoga,
and a bear who has
decided he wanted to
take a load off indoors.
Well, that's it
for this episode of
World's Funniest Animals.
A special thanks
to our panel and
to our celebrity
guests for joining us.
- My pleasure, thanks Liz.
- Thanks for having us, Liz.
Off to play.
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton,
and I'll be back with
more hilarious videos
on World's Funniest Animals.
Until next time.
Oh, God!
There we goes!