You won't want
to miss what we've got in store
because today on the show we
have a piano tuning pooch,
a cat who loves camo,
and one of the cheekiest
chipmunks you've ever seen
all on this episode of
World's Funniest Animals.
You're watching World's
Funniest Animals.
I'm your host, Elizabeth Stanton
and these are my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby.
Joined today with a few of
my friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest, Dee Wallace.
- Hey Elizabeth.
Hey everybody.
- Animals are the absolute best.
They greet us when we come home,
they can sense when we're
sad, and every now and then
they can give us those big eyes
and tuck their tails
back between their legs
and let us know they've
done something guilty.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist
actor, writer, director,
and musician, Maiara Walsh.
- Hey Liz, thank you
so much for having me.
I'm so excited to
watch these clips.
- This clip features a dog
who may have gotten their head
stuck in the trashcan.
Module, did
you go in the garbage?
Let me see, the laundry basket.
The garbage, you are so naughty.
- Oh, just look at this dog,
he knows he's been caught.
Was it delicious?
- For our next clip,
singer, actor, comedian,
radio host, extraordinaire
Mikalah Gordon.
- Hey Liz.
- This clip has a monkey
who has decided to
take a selfie or two
for this lucky tourist.
- So excited.
Oh my God, did he
just knock the camera
out of the person's hand?
Oh yeah baby, yes, he
knows he looks good.
- Oh, he still has that
camera to this day.
His social media
content is fire.
- We are now joined
by the hilarious
comedian, Brian Cooper.
- Hey Liz, I'm happy to be here.
Ready for some funny
clips, let's do this.
- We have a chipmunk who may
or may not have found his way
to an all you can eat
buffet at the bird feeder.
What are
you doing mister?
- Who me?
I don't have
anything in my cheek.
That's kind of gross.
- And for our final panelist,
we have musician, singer
songwriter, Brandon Rogers.
- Hey Liz, so nice to see you.
Let's do this.
- Hey, Brandon, what
do you think of dogs
chewing holes in walls?
Come here.
Did you do this?
I think you did.
I think you did it,
I think you're giving
the clues away.
I think we know the culprit.
Here, come here.
This is all about you, isn't it?
You don't
have to shame me.
The wall just jumped
in front of me.
It's the wall's fault.
So now I ask you
who took the cookie
off the counter?
- I think it's crazy
how people keep talking
to these animals
like they speak English.
I ask you again guys
who stole the cookie
off the counter?
These two
raccoons are up to no good.
Busted.
Oh, just a normal
day at the weight room.
Everybody getting some workout
in and boom in jumps up a,
what was that, a kangaroo?
I don't even know what that was.
- Wait, let's see
that in slow-mo.
Yup, it's a deer all right.
You know, some pets
hate being left alone
and need more
attention than others.
They bark or whine
or paw at your leg,
but every now and then
animals break out the big guns
when they really want
to get our attention.
In this segment, we take a
look at eye grabbing animals,
hidden talents.
- Oh no!
- We need to see
that in slow mo.
- This escalator sucks.
- Wee!
Okay, get it girl.
Yeah.
- Aw yeah, that's my jam.
He's not gonna make
it, he's not gonna make it,
he's not gonna make it.
Does he clear that?
Let's go!
- I have to see that again.
- You know, I can't even
walk through a doorway
that gracefully.
- I love this part of the show
where we visit celebrities
and meet their furry friends.
You'll recognize our next
guest from her roles in films,
ET and Cujo, Dee Wallace,
welcome to our show.
- I'm really excited to be
here because I love animals
and I really love funny,
silly, stupid animals.
- What furry friends do
you have with you today?
- This is my Freedom.
She's a rescue, all my
dogs have been rescues.
Yes.
- Dee, I know you have some
experience working with animals.
Tell us about your time on
the set of the new Lassie.
- Actually, we
did the new Lassie
because the producers happened
to find an actual ancestor
of the original Lassie.
This dog had not been trained.
We got on the set to
do the first shoot
and it was this complicated
story of these smelly old socks.
We bring Lassie and
the attorney goes,
"Oh no, you can't throw
socks to him or anything
because he's too scared."
So working with animals, you
have to have a lot of patience.
- Wow Dee, I can only imagine.
Coming up, we're joined by some
aspiring musicians for pets
sing along next on
World's Funniest Animals.
- We'll be right back with
- These days, karaoke has
become a pretty popular activity
for people to do
with their friends.
But it's not just humans who
are getting in on the act,
animals like to strut
their stuff to, sing along.
♪ I've got a lovely
bunch of coconuts ♪
Okay, I'm done.
Okay, I'm back.
♪ Dilly D, they they
are standing in ♪
- At first I thought
he was whistling,
now it looks like he's DJ-ing.
- I don't care what this
dog plays, it's so cute
he can literally do
whatever he wants.
A little bit off key though.
Translation, please
stop playing the harmonica.
They're both
such great performers.
Just walking by, I would assume
they are a professional duo.
Let's take a look
at some animals
who belong in the doghouse
in our next segment,
caught red handed.
Hey, didn't
I just say no more?
- Meredith, if you are
hiding my bananas in this bag
so help me.
All right, are
you allowed in that bag?
- I swear my monkey
ate my homework.
- Babe!
- Your eyeliner
still looks great.
You've
done it this time.
- What's the big deal?
You have a Rumba.
Hey babe, I got
the new memory foam.
You want two pillows or one?
- I can't believe this
guy is letting me do this.
What did you do?
Come here.
- Who uses that
much toilet paper?
Especially these days.
Coming up
there are purring, crying,
and inquiring
animals, curious cats
next on World's
Funniest Animals.
Now, I'm not really
a fan of the saying
curiosity killed the cat.
So in this segment, we checked
out what really happens
when curiosity gets the
best of our animal friends.
Spoiler alert, it's
usually hilarious.
Check out some of these
clips of curious pets.
- Doesn't that cat
know how to knock?
That is me, yeah
I'm fine, let me kiss myself.
Do not play
this cat for money.
Oh no, what happened?
- That looks like my
hair without a blowout.
- Yeah, I'm the same
way in the morning,
that dog has not
had his coffee yet.
- These next animals
aren't just all bark.
They really have the
skills to back it up.
Let's jump into our next
segment, pets have talent.
Welcome everybody
to the handball finals
where Tabby the cat
still has the lead.
- Who put this
dog in that truck?
My dog never
does chores, I'm jealous.
Oh yeah, I like the moves.
- This dog is friends
with everybody.
- This dog has the whole
neighborhood trained.
You should see when
they play against the lions.
- What about you Dee,
does your dog have
any tricks to show us?
- Her best trick I think,
is we go out and
play balls every day
and I flip the ball and I
don't know how she does it,
but she tracks it and
she catches it in midair.
Good catch!
Good girl.
- Thanks for coming and bringing
your pet to see us today.
Coming up, it's time
to join the band.
Grab a snack and your
pet's favorite treat,
and I'll grab some more
hilarious animal clips for you
when we return to
World's Funniest Animals.
Sometimes I like to just
play my favorite songs
and sing along.
I just wish my
pets would join in.
In this next segment, these
animals are doing exactly that.
Join the band.
- That's literally
me annoying anybody
while they're doing
anything at all.
♪ If you're hungry and
you know it say meow ♪
♪ If you're hungry
and you know it ♪
♪ And you really wanna show it ♪
♪ If you're hungry and
you know it say meow ♪
Are you hungry?
- Lady, I'm hungry.
How many times do
I have to say it?
- And now the
Portuguese version.
- This is taking
singing for your dinner
to a whole new level.
- What, this is how we pay rent.
He ain't nothing
but a hound dog, howling.
Do you want to sing?
So is anyone not
impressed how big that dog is?
That's easily a queen size bed.
Why is
this so impressive?
You can obviously
see he's cheating.
You can see the keys light up.
- Do you have a pet who
sticks their nose in the room
every time you
open a bag of chips
or chases after a sound when
it hears an unfamiliar noise?
These next clips feature animals
who are just as
inquisitive as your pets,
and maybe even a little
more in our segment,
investigative animals.
Huh?
Where did, where did he go?
Oh, you
wanted that there?
Well, I wanted it on the floor.
Hey neighbor.
Hi.
What you doing?
Hey.
Hi.
You want to hang out?
- Yeah, yeah, don't mind them.
- Just a couple
of nosy neighbors.
You're not from
around these parts are ya?
I mean, that's no way
to greet a stranger.
Hey.
Bear get out of there!
He's taking the
Legos, he's taking the Legos!
- Forget the food.
Do you know how
expensive Legos are?
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here's a quick recap of all
of the funniest moments,
a dancing cat with sombrero,
a piano playing pug,
a cat who has found
his new favorite toy,
a chipmunk who has
hit the jackpot,
a monkey with a new backpack
to show off to all
of his friends,
a deer who was trying to
get some reps in at the gym
and a couple of dogs on
the neighborhood watch
jumping at the bet.
Thanks so much to our panel
and our celebrity
guest, Dee Wallace,
for hanging out with us today
on World's Funniest Animals.
- It's so great to be
with you guys, thank you.
Thank you for letting
me share Freedom
and our love with you.
- Until next time, I'm your
host Elizabeth Stanton.
I'll be back soon with
more hilarious clips
of your favorite creatures
right here on World's
Funniest Animals.
You got
food in the car?
He's taking the Legos!
- Babe!
Was it delicious?
What did you do?