- Get ready to laugh.
Because on this episode,
we have a confused canine,
bear cub birth bath, pull puppy,
and a foam soaked feline..
All this and more, on
World's Funniest Animals.
Hey there, I'm your
host Elizabeth Stanton,
and these are my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby.
Joined today with a few of
my friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guests, Garrett Clayton.
- Thanks for having
me Liz, hey everybody.
- Thanks for being
here, Garrett.
We all love to pamper
our pets, treats, baths,
the occasional bow tie.
But how far is too
far when it comes to
cuddling our best friends.
Spoiled.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist,
musician singer song
writer, Brandon Rogers.
- Hey Liz.
- Are you ready for an animal
who was just blamed spoiled?
- Ooh, now this sounds
like a good one.
Yes, that's right everyone, I
come with a builtin snorkel.
Nope, I don't wanna to
open my eyes because,
then I have to go back
to my normal life.
- Our next panelist is the
amazing comedian, Brian Cooper.
- Hi Liz.
- Are you ready for an animal
who is having a very lazy day?
- Even animals need to take
time to just chill out.
What?
This cat likes baths.
Yea get in there.
I thought cats hated water,
he is having a
whole bubble bath.
- Now we are joined by
singer actor, comedian,
radio host, Mikalah Gordon.
- My girl, hey Liz.
- We have an animal
engaging in a little RNR.
- Okay, I need to see this one.
Ooh, yeah, a little belly
rub, that's the stuff.
Do I need to start asking
my friends when I go over,
if that's the monkey toothbrush?
- For our final panelist, we
have an actor, writer, director
and musician, Maiara Walsh.
- Hey Liz.
- we have an animal who has
decided to take the day off.
- I think I might be jealous.
When's my day off?
- Someone said,
curiosity is one of
the great secrets to happiness.
That's sure seems to be the case
with the animals in
our next segment.
Who seemed pretty thrilled at
all of their new discoveries.
Curious pets.
- Does anyone know
how these things work?
The funny thing is, this
cat has the same reaction
as all of us, when
those first came out.
- That's right, Fado
you've been replaced.
He also doesn't need to be fed,
and, he cleans up after himself.
Don't worry everyone, I have
this situation taken care of.
- What is it with
cats and cucumbers?
- Okay, first things first,
this cat is adorable.
The cat reaches its little
paw out and does like,
a little tiny lick.
- What in the world,
where'd he go?
This guy is a magician.
- You might know,
today's celebrity guest
from Disney's Teen Beach
movie and Hairspray Live,
Garrett Clayton.
Thanks for being with
us today, Garrett.
Oh, I see you have your dogs
with you, what are their names?
- This is Dart, or
Dartagnan is his full name.
Named after the hot
musketeer and that Dash.
He, dash, is the very timid,
scared one and Dart...
They know theirs
treats in my pocket.
Dart is very confident
and outgoing.
Dash is very timid and
scared all the time.
Good boys, good boys.
Thank you for the
kisses, thank you.
- Hey Garrett, can your
dogs do any cool tricks?
- Do you just want
to go do some tricks?
Let's go.
And jump!
Oh ooh
- Wow, he can nearly
jump over you.
- Oh, Oh, Oh.
Oh, this isn't a trick, but
he likes a belly scratch.
- Thanks for coming on
with your pups Garrett.
Coming up, what would you do
if you came face to
face, a wild bear?
- Animals where
they don't belong.
Next on World's
Funniest Animals.
We're back with one of
my favorite segments,
Animals, Where
They Don't Belong.
I can't wait to show
you what antiques,
these wild animals
have been up to.
- I'm telling you honey,.
They said this was a two
person tub, I promise.
All right,
that's far enough, buddy.
Come on, get outta here.
Go on, get out, come
on, get outta here.
The bear spaced
when he heard the guy,
and he stopped on dime.
All right, that is
Far enough, buddy, come on.
- Yeah, so the resorts
are all inclusive,
food and drinks for free.
Don't you hate
when you go down to the pool,
and it's just full
of rowdy kids?
- Canning ball!
- Donkeys are known as
some of the most stubborn
creatures in the animal kingdom,
but the animals we're
about to show you,
give them a run for
their money, trust me.
Nothing you could say would
make these animals move.
They are just Too Lazy.
- After a dog's day at
work this guy is exhausted.
- Okay, seriously guys,
you knew where I was
when you dropped the toy,
and now you expect me
to reach, not cool.
- Okay, move me over to my bowl.
No, I said my bowl,
no, not the door.
Ah great, now we're
just going in circles.
- What?
Okay, am not sure
what sales us more?
The Baggy t-shirt,
the cheese puffs,
or the fact that this dog looks
so normal in this position.
This dog thinks
shopping is a real drag.
Oh I know,
what a good boy.
- Coming up, there
are peering, crying,
and inquiring animals.
Grab a snack and your
pet spirit retreat,
and all grab some more
hilarious animal clips for you.
When we return to
World's Funniest Animals.
Do you have a pet who sticks
their nose in the room
every time you open
a bag of chips?
Or chases after a sound, when
it hears an unfamiliar noise?
These next clips feature
animals who are just as curious
and maybe even a little
more in our segment,
Investigative Animals.
- This is like those ships
in a bottle, but it's a cat.
This gives me anxiety, how
is he going to get out?
- Let's get out
here, what is that?
An alien, it is an alien, run.
There's four of them,
and I still think
the toy is gonna win.
- I am a dog.
For a walk, for
a long walk.
- Look at these videos of
animals, living their best life,
in our segment called, Pampered
Pooches and Fancy Felines.
- This is the
calmest cat in water
I've ever seen in my life.
Are these puppies
in the hammocks?
It's the cutest thing ever.
I smelled treats in the package,
are you going to open them?
Are you going to open them?
No? I'll open them myself.
What have you found?
- Yea it is for me baby.
Yummy.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- The little dog is like,
"I'll come to the party,
but I'm not wearing that hat."
- Coming up. We see some animals
who've decided they
cannot be bothered.
I don't wanna, next on
World's Funniest Animals.
After a long week, sometimes
you just can't be bothered
to get out of bed or off the
couch and do your daily chores.
Our pets have one thing
they have to do each day.
Go for a walk.
Here's some clips with
animals who are too lazy
to even do that, I Don't Wanna.
Betty your
supposed to be walking.
- Wait, wait,
I have to get something
from the back.
Okay, that's what I
needed to get, a seat.
- Okay, this is the guy who
inspired the phrase, Cool Cat.
- Come on, you guys
all know it's so nice
jumping into fresh sheets.
I mean, you can make that bed,
but I am not moving a muscle.
- No, no, I'm now
working out today.
I am not doing it, no.
Gerry, no.
No, I am not doing it.
- Most of the time wild
animals belong in two places,
out in nature to be
admired from a far,
and on our televisions
making us laugh.
But these next critters
stuck their noses,
and their antlers and trunks
where they shouldn't be.
And it's pretty great.
Wild Animals at Home.
Oh my God, it's
It's in the room!
- I like how in
today's day and age,
everyone's reaction is,
"Well, better take a selfie."
- No kids, we're
just looking today.
No one's getting anything.
Nothing says
summer days like
jumping through a sprinkler
on the front lawn.
That's some serious refreshment.
Oh no, it's breaking.
It is breaking.
don't do that.
- It is an elephant pool party.
they are really thirsty,
look at them.
You guys better
get outta here man.
what?
- Don't you just hate
it when party guests
don't get the hint.
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here is a quick recap of
all of the funniest moments.
A curious cat, peach primates,
a lackadaisical Lassie,
a baboon break in, relaxing
rottweilers, puzzle pug,
a cat discovering ice cream,
and a dog who was convinced
their owner is a magician.
Great show.
That's it for our show, a
special thanks to our panel,
and to our wonderful celebrity
guests, Garrett Clayton,
and his pups, Dart and Dash.
- Anytime Liz.
- I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton.
And Ruby, Hank, and I
will be back next week
with more World's
Funniest Animals.
Until then, pamper those pets
like there's no tomorrow.
They are really
thirsty look at them.