Get
your friends together.
The show is about to start.
We're bringing you,
some running rovers,
a few fidgeting felines,
some peeking pooches,
and laugh inducing laughs.
All this and more
on "World's Funniest Animals".
Welcome back to "World's
Funniest Animals",
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton.
And these are my
curators Ruby and Hank.
They are great at their job.
Which is good news for you
because tonight's
episode features
loads of new hilarious clips
that you won't want to miss.
Today I'm joined by a
few friends and panelists
as well as our celebrity
guest Dan Sperry.
- Hey Liz thanks for having me.
Hi everyone I'm shock
illusionist Dan Sperry
coming to you from Las Vegas
with my best friend Spike.
- Thanks guys.
So let's get right into it.
Is it just me or is there
a lot of pressure to
stay in shape these days?
Every where we turn there's
a new work out routine,
or supplement that
we've got to have.
But it turns out
the animal kingdom
is no different.
And our furry friends
strive to stay in shape too.
Animals Exercising
brought to you
with commentary from
our first panelist
the hilarious
comedian Neel Ghosh.
- Hey Liz happy to be here.
- Are you ready for a
little animal exercise?
- Well don't keep me
waiting for this long,
the suspense is killing me!
Ah hey man can you
check on my delts?
You might be getting a workout,
I just really don't
like this tire.
- Our next panelist is
actor Carmen Hodgson.
- Ooh what clips do you
have for me tonight Liz?
I'm so excited!
- This next clip features
an animal work out partner.
I need a furry friend
for my work outs.
- I can't!
- Push up.
I can't!
Yes you can.
Yes you can see look at that.
Look at you!
That's one.
- Is this considered
resistance training?
- Now we are joined by
Actor-Writer-Director-Musician
Maiara Walsh.
- Happy to be here Liz.
- Are you ready for
some exercising animals?
- Talk about motivation!
Burpees to the extreme!
- For our final panelist
we have top notch
comedian Brian Cooper.
- Happy to be here Liz!
Can't wait to see
what we've got today.
- We have an owner working out
with their pet in
this next clip.
- This has got to be good.
You think you can outstretch me?
You will be sorely mistaken.
- Even though this is
World's Funniest Animals,
while we were searching the
web for hilarious videos
to bring you, there were a
few that were just too cute
to pass up.
No laughs about it,
this segment is Just Plain Cute.
- This cat has skills.
- Aw so cute!
- This dog just expects
pets at every moment.
Get the water!
Oh is this a little pencil case?
Go back to school shopping?
- That is a fast kitten.
- I'm excited to introduce
our celebrity guest,
to "World's Funniest Animals".
And I'm even more excited
that they brought their pet.
In this case Las Vegas
magician Dan Sperry,
has a pet who is also
a lifelong coworker.
- Spike is a 16 year
old umbrella cockatoo
and I've had him since he
was about five months old.
And he can live to be
upwards of 60 years old.
And over the years we've
traveled all over the world
and met a lot of people,
encountered a lot
of crazy things.
So we've got plenty
of road stories,
isn't that right?
- Pets, performers or not,
always love attention.
Does Spike know any tricks?
- He likes to give kisses.
He does a couple tricks.
You gonna play dead?
Okay ready?
Bang!
Oh and then he's dead?
Can you come back to life?
Okay now he's back to life,
he's come back to life.
That's a big boy!
Good job buddy!
- So I hear that Spike is
a big fan of rock music.
You'll have to show us!
- He likes to listen
to Rob Zombie,
especially when we're
driving in the car.
When I'm backstage I usually
set up two folding chairs
and let him fly the lengths
of the hallways backstage.
And we have, we
have a lot of fun.
- Thanks for stopping
by and joining us Dan.
- Thanks for having me.
Thanks everybody.
We'll see you guys later.
- Pets working to get
their owners' attention.
Coming up next on
World's Funniest Animals.
No one likes to be ignored,
but these animals in our
segment insist that you pay
attention to them at all times.
Some of these videos are
absolutely hysterical.
Check them out.
Play with me.
- This new cat hat will
keep you warm year round.
If we're going to continue
to play this game,
we're going to definitely have
to get you some deodorant.
- Aw, this is the
sweetest alarm clock.
It looks so much fun.
Can I play?
Can I?
Come on, move over.
Never mind, I don't
want to play anymore.
- I can't tell if this
guy's the world's best gamer
who just really
can't be distracted,
or the world's meanest owner.
Play with him!
- You want to go for a walk?
You want to go for a walk?
- You better have taken
that dog on a walk.
- It's time for one of
my favorite segments,
curious pets, where we
see animals discovering
the world for the first time,
and it's pretty dang cute.
Curious pets.
- Ah, cat's favorite
pastime, hitting stuff.
- Here I am.
Now I'm not.
Oh, Hey, I'm back.
Peekaboo!
- This is how I would be,
if I worked in a cubicle
at an office, hey guys.
What's for lunch?
We're out of creamer.
Hire me.
- Hey guys, guys, give
you a little help in here.
- Smells good in here though.
- Some of the cutest
clips I've ever seen,
coming up next, on
World's Funniest Animals.
Are you ready for some animals
who just want to give some love?
These clips are
just too precious.
- Yay a snow day!
- This is every dog's dream.
Sit.
Sit, sit.
- Well at least
the boy's trained.
Sit.
- That's not fair, the kid
didn't even get a treat.
- This dog knows what he wants.
- This is the most
adorable wrestling match.
Look at that flow
between each other.
Each know each other's moves.
- That is what you
call a euphoric meal.
- Hank and Ruby are
my best friends.
We do everything together.
However, I'm surprised I
never thought of working out
with them.
These pets and their owners
have figured it all out.
- I need to limber up, I have
a walk plan for later on so.
- This is the only way I can
get this woman to exercise.
- No we're gonna get
there someday, I promise.
Oh never mind.
- And that pose earns
you a kitty kiss.
- It almost looks like there's
one dog and one person,
but just double.
- Are you feeling
like you're all fluff?
Well we're gonna take
you to the next step
and make you an alpha dog.
- Okay, this dog is like,
ah, I told you I
wanted the blue one.
And one and two and three,
come on, let's keep it going.
Now this is the kind of
workout partner I want.
- It's very dangerous to do
lunges on a wood floor in socks.
- Didn't say I wanted
to kiss, all right?
I'm just lazy.
- The world's most curious
pets coming up next,
on World's Funniest Animals.
Welcome back let's jump right
into the fan favorite segment,
Investigative animals,
- DJ kitty scribble
kibble into his house.
- Yes, that last song
was Cat Scratch Fever.
One of my favorites.
- Hey mom, how do I have
cat fur in my water?
- The cat's just
like, hey, come on in.
It's warm in here,
you can trust me.
- Now that is a
thorough carwash.
- Yeah you gotta pay a lot
extra for the cow tongue wash,
it's a delicacy.
- No matter how much tug
of war or fetch you play,
it'll never be
enough for some pets.
These clips are a
prime example of that.
I will not be ignored.
- This kitten is like
stay away from my woman,
I'll blend
in with the cabinets.
So maybe he won't
see me, if I..
Oh!
That's right, I got ya.
- Okay.
Oh my god!
- Oh my god!
- This goes from super cute
to super scary real quick.
- Um, a little problem here.
- Well that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here's a quick recap of all
of the funniest moments.
A collapsing cat, a curious
cow, a workout drill dog,
rollicking red pandas,
a devious Dalmatian,
a robbing retriever, and
a couple who has managed
to turn their pets
into workout equipment.
That's a new one.
Well that's it for this episode
of World's Funniest Animals.
A special thanks to our panel,
and to our celebrity
guests for joining us.
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton.
And I'll be back with
more hilarious videos
on World's Funniest Animals.