Grab your
favorite furry friend
and take a seat.
We'll be checking out,
a fish feeding frenzy,
a bread loving bear,
a slippery swine,
and a canine carousel.
Stay tuned for
this and much more
on "World's Funnies Animals."
- Welcome back, I'm your
host Elizabeth Stanton.
And these are my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby
joined today with a few
friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest, Danielle Nicolet.
- Hey everyone.
I'm so excited to be here
and I am super excited
to see what we have
in store tonight.
What do you think Biggie?
Are you excited?
Oh, he's excited.
- Thanks for being
here, Danielle.
Getting excited to eat
is definitely something
I can relate to, but
these animals take
it to another level.
The hunger is real
in a segment we call,
"Dinner Time,"
brought to you with commentary
from our first panelists,
the hilarious
comedian, Neel Ghosh.
- Hey Liz.
- This next clip
features an animal
getting ready to
dig into their meal.
- Ah, perfect.
I haven't eaten all
day, so let's get to it.
This isn't coffee!
What is he making, it looks
like a power, smoothie?
Okay, I'm not
eating any of that.
First of all, the monkey
sniffs everything,
and second, he scratches his
butt with that same hand.
Ugh!
- Our next panelist is
actor Carmen Hodgson.
- I'm happy to be here Liz.
- This next clip features
a very hungry animal.
- Ohm, can't wait to
see what we got tonight.
Seriously, again?
I'm gonna film you eating and
see how great you look, okay.
- Now, we are joined by actor,
writer, director,
musician, Maiara Walsh.
- Hi Liz.
- We have an animal
who can't wait to eat.
- Let's see how this pans out.
Ooh!
And he shoots, and he scores.
- For our final panelist.
We have top notch,
comedian Brian Cooper.
- Hi, Liz.
- Are you ready for some animals
digging into their dinner?
- This sounds interesting.
Hello.
Hey guys, this is the place.
Trust me.
You just knock and
they bring food.
This bread better
be gluten free.
- This is horrifying.
This man has lost his mind.
What happens when
he runs out of food?
Fish just swarm him and
start eating his body?
♪ Ring around the Rosie ♪
♪ 'Cause this food
is delicious ♪
- After watching so many
of these animal videos
I kinda know what
they're thinking
when I look into their eyes,
and these next animals are
all thinking the same thing.
Don't mess with me.
- This is the dog's
version of shotgun.
I thought we settle this.
I get it for 10 minutes
and then you get
it for 10 minutes.
- Get your hands off my man.
This is one hangry dog.
- This cat wants
to go on vacation.
I can be a carry on.
Just put the zipper on.
- I love this part of the show,
where we visit celebrities
and meet their furry friends.
Our celebrity guest is the
amazing Danielle Nicolet
from "The Flash" and
"Central Intelligence."
Hey Danielle, I see you
have someone there with you.
Tell us about them.
- This is the one and
only Biggie Smalls.
I know there's
another Biggie Smalls,
but don't tell him
he doesn't know.
He's very sensitive.
As I was saying,
the one and only Biggie Smalls.
He is the love of my life.
My greatest hangout
partner, my travel buddy,
and also my snuggle pal.
- Hey Danielle, can your
dog do any tricks us?
- I'm gonna to say that I
think Biggie is the best pug
in the whole entire world
because he's the only pug
I've ever known that will do
what you ask him to do.
For example, Biggie, lips.
Lips.
Yes.
Biggie's also very
good at other things.
For example,
should I ever remove
my sock from my foot,
he will promptly
take it and eat it.
- Coming up, we take a
trip down to the rodeo.
Next on the, "World's
Funniest Animals."
Yeehaw, it's time for a
new segment on this episode
of "World's Funniest Animals."
Our animal rodeo.
Lucky us these animals
have been practicing
long before their
day in the arena.
Take a look.
Rodeo.
- Ah, man, I know I'm
gonna regret this picture
when I grow up.
Stay, stay, whoa.
Stay.
I can't tell who the
woman is talking to,
because the horse stopped,
but the dog was like "No."
Stay.
- Look how cute.
I want baby goats
as my step trackers.
Get your steps in.
- Heehaw, little doggie.
- Even animals get
annoyed sometimes.
Whether it's personal space,
or they're trying to rest,
if they don't want attention,
they will be sure
to let you know.
Get ready for our next segment,
"I don't think so."
- You still haven't
got me my milk?
♪ I've got a peanut ♪
♪ I've got a peanut and
you can't have none ♪
♪ And you can't ♪
Dang it.
- I'm wondering who likes
it more the dude or the cat?
- What this woman doesn't know,
this the leg of the
last person who tried
to touch him when he was eating.
- Getting my work out for the
day.
Now here's the training center.
Lave me alone.
- Okay, this is my side
and so is that side.
- Our celebrity guest is the
amazing Danielle Nicolet,
from "The Flash" and
"Central Intelligence."
Hey Danielle,
have you ever worked
with any animals on set?
- Yes, I have actually worked
with animals, quite a few.
I seem to have the biggest
issue with goats, though.
I was doing an episode of
"Real Husbands of Hollywood"
with Kevin Hart, when
a goat was in the scene
and that goat pooped on my foot.
And I thought that
would be the last time
that a goat ever pooped on me,
but it turns out no.
Last year I was doing an episode
of my friend, Katee
Sackhoff show,
and we did goat yoga on the show
and the goats helped
stretch my back
and then he pooped on
my foot and on my back.
Go goat go!
Oh, no.
- Why's it me?
It's the poop.
- Well, I think we
know we won't see you
at the State Fair Petting Zoo.
- I don't know why
goats don't like me?
I'm a vegan.
- Well, thanks for
stopping in Danielle
and introducing
us all to Biggie.
- It's been my pleasure.
Our pleasure.
Thank you so much Liz.
- Coming up, we find out that
animals are just like us?
Next on "World's
Funniest Animals."
- Did you know that 90%
of human genes are similar
to those found in domestic cats?
It's pretty crazy how similar
we are to our animal friends.
I mean, some even sing,
dance and enjoy fine dining,
just like us.
- Do a stare.
- People have way too
much time on their hands.
There's a person underneath
this goat right now.
We need to understand this.
There's a human being with
feelings and thoughts underneath
the shirt, hand
feeding a goat wine.
You want something?
- I think the woman's
actually talking to the man.
- I asked for a lap pool.
This is not a lap pool.
- They lure you in
the bathtub with wine,
and duckies and then bam,
they turn on the water.
- I absolutely love to eat
and I know my pets do too.
Get ready for our next
segment, "Supper Club."
- Well, I thought
that was for me.
Give me that.
Get your kid out of here.
The time to play with
you, dinner time.
- Sir, please chew
with your mouth closed.
I mean, this guy's
tables manners
are utterly unbelievable.
- Hey, mine was
good, but I wonder.
Oh, yeah, yours is
definitely better.
This little guy
had a rough night,
but a sunflower seed
is just the right cure.
This is the ultimate supper
club, a turtle an iguana,
a bunch of bunnies and a
chicken all at the same buffet
That is an epic fail, love it.
- Don't go anywhere more
amazing animals after this.
"World's Funniest Animals,"
we'll be right back.
You know, they
always say how pets
and their owners
start to look alike
after a certain amount of time.
Well, in this next segment,
it seems like they even
start to act the same,
"Two of a Kind."
You and
Bruno are literally
exactly the same right now.
- This impression is uncanny.
An odd case of twins
separated at birth.
- And one, and two, after
this we'll cool down
with a downward dog.
- Okay, that's
what you look like.
Maybe I should have
gotten glasses,
before I decided to move in.
- Yo, what's up?
Catch you on the flip side.
- A boy and his
dog, two of a kind.
- The rodeo is synonymous
with bull riding,
horse tricks and farm animals.
Let's saddle up,
"Home on the Range."
- And the world keeps
going round and round,
round and round.
- And he's a good guy.
He probably--
One time.
Did you get it?
I've got you.
I'll get you.
- Sure, just go get the mail.
It's easy, you said.
Ha-ha, very funny.
And I'll lick, and will
lick your house down.
- How far are you going?
About two feet.
Fine with me.
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here is a quick recap of
all of the funniest moments,
A bull riding boxer, slippery
swine, galloping goat,
a berating bird,
a displeased dog,
filching foul, a pup
who's not yet mastered
the art of catching,
and a monkey who can
make their own lunch.
Wow, that's really impressive.
Well, that's all the time
we have on this episode
of "World's Funniest Animals."
Thanks to our panel
for guiding us
through these crazy clips.
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton,
and I'll be back with
more hilarious videos,
on "World's Funniest Animals."