Time to cozy up
with your very best friend.
Because on the show,
we've got a dancing ostrich,
an elephant who clearly doesn't
understand personal space,
and the Tony Hawk of monkeys,
plus the most talented
dogs you've ever seen.
Don't forget about the cats.
Hold on tight for
a stunning display
of aerobic skill.
And if that's not enough,
we take to the skies and
also learn new tricks
with our feathered friends.
All this and a lot more
on "World's Funniest Animals".
- Welcome to World's
Funniest Animals,
your one stop shop
for the most hilarious
animal clips out there.
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton.
And these are my
trusty sidekicks Hank
and Ruby joined today with a few
of my friends and panelists as
well as two celebrity guests.
Tom Arnold.
- Hey everybody.
- And our next guest,
Natalie Lander.
- Hey, thanks for
having us, Liz.
- While some animals are content
to cozy up in a comfy dog bed.
Others prefer to stretch
their legs in their natural
or not so natural habitats.
It's a wildlife.
- Brought to you with commentary
by our first panelist,
singer, actor, comedian,
radio host extraordinaire
Mikalah Gordon.
- Hey, Liz.
- Hey Mikalah, check out
this clip of this fat seal
and the unusual
way it gets around.
- Oh my gosh, I'm so ready.
Oh, that was sad feels
like me at the beach.
- For our next clip,
actor, writer, producer,
Noah Matthews breaks it down.
- Hey Liz.
Yes, so ready let's get started.
This husband has
designed a prank destined
to have him sleeping
on the couch tonight.
He has a live snake
that he's about
to sneak up on his wife with.
If someone did this to me,
I would have some
serious trust issues.
- Oo ooh, these wild animal
clips you never know.
- Top-notch comedian Brian
Cooper is also on our panel.
- Hey, Liz,
I'm happy to be
here and I'm ready
for some funny clips.
- Hey Brian, what do you think
of these girls wrestling
a baby elephant?
- Elephants never forget people.
So three to four years from now
these girls might be ready
for the heavyweight rematch.
It's
feeding time at the zoo
for these adorable lemurs.
I'm kinda jealous at
this guy right now.
Wait a second.
Does he even work there?
How do I get to feed lemurs?
- Our fourth and final
panelist is a rising star up
and coming actress
Carmen Hodgson.
- Hey, Liz.
Yes, animal videos are my
favorite, favorite videos.
- Well perfect then
I've got one for you.
Let's see if you can tell
what's happening here.
♪ I'm so tired of
the same thing ♪
♪ Nothing all right ♪
♪ It's still good ♪
- Oh please mom, can
I please just go play
with my friends?
♪ No where to escape ♪
♪ It tasted good ♪
- And I'm excited to jump right
into our category,
hidden talents.
Where you'll probably
be pretty jealous
after checking out the
skills shown up by man
and woman's best friend.
I know I was.
Hidden talents.
- I'm gonna hire this
guy for my next gig.
I've been getting it wrong.
- I play for treats.
- Don't you hate it when
you get crumbs in your keys?
Arthur, can
you go play the piano?
Ah, now singing too.
Very nice.
Very good boy playing piano.
- Is it still considered
a layup if you're
on all fours.
Let's go.
Load up.
- Wait.
Let's see that in slow mo.
I
would never be late
to anything if I could
jump in the car that fast.
They must be going to the park.
- Why is this dog 10 times
more coordinated than me.
- Imagining getting your
waves stolen by a dog?
- I can't believe I'm
considering asking a dog
for surfing lesson.
On your
marks, get set, go.
What a top
of the line security dog.
He's scanning the
perimeter like a pro.
- I'm really excited
for this part
of the show where
we bring you right
into the homes of
celebrities and their pets.
- Hey Liz.
Happy to be here.
- With all you've done
in TV and film.
Do you have a
story about working
with animals on set?
- I worked with
a famous elephant
on the set of "Saving Flora"
and this elephant had
better credits with me
and she was in a
ton of great movies.
"Water for Elephants" and
"Operation Dumbo Drop"
and I noticed that
she was always
on the right spot
better prepared
than me to do all of her lines.
I can't even explain it
just this gentle, beautiful,
40 year old elephant.
- It's crazy to think
that some animals
are career actors themselves.
You don't wanna
miss what's coming next,
some of the craziest antics
of animals ever caught
on tape, and later,
the show's gone to the birds.
- We'll be right back
with more "World's
Funniest Animals".
- Cats usually sleep
anywhere from 12
to 16 hours a day,
lounging around all
afternoon stretched out
in the sun.
Sounds pretty nice, doesn't it?
Well, since cats are
known to be so relaxed,
this next segment
might surprise you.
Check out some of
these crazy felines.
Flipping out!
- Honey, I think
we broke the cat.
- My money is on him in the
feline Olympics definitely.
- Maple leafs are
just Canadian cat nip.
- Touchdown house gangs.
- We are back with one
of my favorite
segments wild animals.
I can't wait to
show you what antics
these wild ones have been up to.
- Okay, this has to be one
of the best bucket list
things I've ever seen.
Oh, I'm so jealous.
- Wow, wow, wow, come
on one bear per hammock,
you know the rules.
Can you just relax for once?
It's supposed to be peaceful.
Don't stand why
are you standing?
Oh no.
Corny,
corny, corny pick.
There you go.
Oh my god.
Imagine
going on safari
with your family with the hopes
of relaxing seeing a
few animals and bam,
bird food everywhere.
They merely lost
the whole bucket.
This photographer is trying
to be as still as possible.
You can't outrun a cheetah
so your best bet is
to just not move.
Are you eating the bouquet?
Are you guys here for
Johnny Kelly's wedding?
- We were told it was cool
to take the centerpieces
or is that not cool?
I don't remember this
level in Tony Hawk.
- Is that parkour?
Up
next, the show's gone
to the birds.
- Don't go away "World's
Funniest Animals"
will be right back.
Did you know there are
around 18,000 species
of birds in the world,
and over 1100 of them live
in the United States.
Not only is that pretty crazy,
but it means that some have
to work a lot harder than others
to get attention.
If pumping up their feathers
isn't enough birds can resort
to some pretty
bizarre behaviors.
Watch me.
- Hey, Bill.
Hey Bill.
Look, I'm upside down.
Ah, a
nice trip to the farm.
This chicken is not having it.
- Wait is it playing in tune.
- I took guitar
lessons for two years.
I'm not kidding you
and this bird is
still better than me.
- So are they flying?
This is actually cool.
- Please get on the bike,
please get on the bike.
He's on the bike.
- These next animals
aren't just all bark.
They really have the skills
to back it up.
Let's jump into
our next segment.
Pets have talent.
- Yes, people it's all
about the matching outfit.
Ah, that was brutal.
- We need to see
that in slow mo.
- No the dog is not
putting itself to bed.
This cat just
might have a better memory
than I do.
He is a total pro
with this game.
See if you can play
along it's tough.
Now that is difficult.
- On his way to steal yo girl.
Good job buddy.
Good job.
- This dog is on my team
for any board game please.
- Natalie, what about your pup?
Can Billy do any tricks?
- Yes.
Billy can do one trick.
Ready?
Billy stare.
You're a star.
- Hey Tom, can your pet
do any tricks like that?
- My pet is good at
running in circles.
- Hold on a minute
A dog.
What kinda pet do
you have there?
- I'm very proud of these guys.
But they seem to get in
this low pair of sight
and just making noise.
- Wow, impressive.
- Guys, you wanna get
in there do some loops
for the people at home.
Gonna wanna do a little get
to do though.
Okay, they don't
like to show off.
- I get it Tom no one wants
to flaunt their
talents too much.
It's rude.
Coming up,
these animals are
absolutely losing it.
Next on "World's
Funniest Animals".
- Grab a snack and your
pet's favorite tree
and I'll grab some more
hilarious animal clips for you.
When we return to "World's
Funniest Animals".
There are certain phrases
like walk or treat
that can cause our
pet to totally freak.
These clips show
those exact moments
where animals are losing it.
- I wanna swing
from the chandelier he
loves Sia makes sense.
- That's a good cat.
That's a strong cat.
That's a real cat.
- Honestly I just feel bad
for the Roomba at this point.
I mean, how is it ever
supposed to finish it's job?
- That's mission
impossible I can tell.
- Aww, it's so sad.
I love the moment where
the cat realizes mid air
that they haven't
made the catch.
- We are joining the
rest of the flock
as we start our next
segment feathered friends.
- Alexa Christmas lights on.
Okay.
- Dude half the time I use talk
to text it comes out
as just gibberish.
But this bird can work
the Christmas lights
with voice recognition.
- Alexa Christmas lights on.
Okay.
- And here we are ladies
and gentlemen at the first
annual parakeet dunking contest.
- Flamingo with the
dance fever I like it.
And
there goes your hat.
- For your dining entertainment
we bring you Marty
with his mating dance.
- Imagine trying to eat dinner
and some guy is doing this
right in front of you.
- She's just not into you.
No what is it like a
carnival for chickens?
- I have a weird
feeling about chickens.
I don't trust them.
- Well, that's almost it for us.
But just in case
you missed anything,
here's a quick recap of all
of the funniest
moments, rolling seals,
a cat spinning out of control,
an aspiring dog pianist,
a cat who has turned
their owner's table
into jungle gym,
a dog who is a pro on a scooter
and let's not forget
that amazing dress,
an Olympic gymnast hopeful cat,
a BMX bird,
a thrill seeking monkey,
a burrito enthusiast pup
and an owner who bite
off more than they could
chew with their dog
on a skateboard.
Whoa.
That's all the time we
have on this episode
of "World's Funniest Animals".
Thanks so much to our panel and
to our special guests,
Tom Arnold and Natalie
Lander for joining us
and checking out some of
these crazy animal clips.
- Anytime Liz.
- It was our pleasure.
Thank you for having us, Liz.
- Until next time,
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton.
I'll be back soon with
more hilarious clips
of your favorite
creatures right here
on "World's Funniest Animals".