Take a seat
and make sure to buckle in,
because on this show,
we've got a buffet fit
for a group of geckos,
grand buffet,
street-crossing salmon,
a seat-stealing seal,
and a pig who loves parkour.
You're tuned in to
World's Funniest Animals.
Here at World's
Funniest Animals,
humans take a back seat for once
and we put the spotlight on
some of the best animal clips
the internet has to offer.
I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton,
and these are my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby,
joined today with a few of
my friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity guests,
Ace Young and Diana DeGarmo.
- Hey, Liz!
We're so excited to
get this started!
- I'm so excited to show you
some compilations of
our favorite home videos
of animals being
absolutely hilarious.
Let's dive in.
Dinner time!
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist,
the hilarious
comedian, Neel Ghosh.
- Hey, Liz.
- Are you ready for
some hungry animals?
- I'm feeling a
little hungry myself.
I should start doing this.
This would make eating and
watching TV super convenient.
It's like half
eating, half grooming.
- Our next panelist is
actor, Carmen Hodgson.
- What's up, Liz?
- This next clip features
a very hungry animal.
- So I could definitely
relate to this.
Yeah, sure, everyone gets a
knife and a piece of bread,
but no, I have to lick the jar.
This is degrading!
- Now we're joined
by actor, writer,
director, musician,
Maiara Walsh.
- Hey, Liz.
- We have an animal
who can't wait to eat.
- Perfect.
I got this.
I don't need your
help, I got it.
Okay, help me.
- For our final panelist,
we have top-notch comedian,
Brian Cooper.
- Hi, Liz!
- Are you ready for some animals
digging into their dinner?
- Sounds like I came
here at the perfect time.
Bring on the food!
Yeah, really funny, Mom.
Can we just get two bowls?
- Birds of a feather
flock together,
or so the saying goes,
but some of the best
friendships come
when we meet people, or animals,
that are completely
different from us.
Let's check out some
unexpected pairings
in our segment,
Opposites Attract.
Animal friendship.
- If this is a Mortal Kombat
between Bambi and a puppy,
I'm sorry, I'm going
Bambi every time.
The best part of this
is the kid's commentary.
That is the
cutest thing I ever saw.
- Baby cows are so adorable.
- Oh, this is "Lion
King" part four,
they replaced Timon.
Yeah, I know this.
Hakuna matata, everyone!
- This dog is so chill.
- I'm so excited for this
next part of our show
where we talk to a celebrity
guest and their pet,
and today, I'm even more excited
because we have on
a celebrity couple.
From "American Idol," welcome
Diana DeGarmo and Ace Young.
- Hey, Liz!
- How are you?
This is our foster puppy, Amber.
- She's very sleepy right now,
it's hard being a puppy.
- I get it, Amber,
I can only imagine
what being a puppy must be like.
Sounds exhausting.
Diana, I hear you have a
pretty interesting story
about working with
a horse in a movie.
That, I have to hear.
- Okay, so this one time, I was
on a set for a western film.
We're in Southern California,
we're atop this beautiful hill
overlooking the countryside,
my human co-star
is on his horse, I'm on mine,
and then the poor horse
had gastric distress.
For hours.
Needless to say,
what should've taken
maybe 30 minutes to film
took all day.
But I think he was
feeling better at the end.
Coming
up, we have some pets
who have definitely
had better days.
Don't Mess With Me, next on
World's Funniest Animals.
Sometimes, you just
want to be left alone.
Everyone needs to recharge
every once in a while,
and our pets are no exception.
Take a look at these grumpy
animals in our segment,
Don't Mess With Me.
- Uh oh, torpedo cat.
Engage.
Three, two, one.
Bang!
I love the ending where
the cat just stares.
Like, "I almost had you."
- That's how I sound
in the morning.
I would be yelling too
if that guy kept
tapping me on the head.
- Wow, he is so gentle,
he's so majestic, just
look at his proud stride.
Roll the windows
up, roll them up!
- Wait a minute, one
more time on that.
- Who did it better?
- You know when you just judo
chop your cat in the forehead?
Yeah, that's what you deserve.
- If you're like me, you
probably have a doggy gate
set up where you live.
For my pets, it works.
For these next animals,
that could hardly
hold them back.
Here's Jailbreak.
'Sup, little guy?
- Squirrels do not mess around.
- Okay, this is
definitely pig parkour.
- And here we are at the
200 meter hurdle race
and oops, he's
immediately disqualified.
- Okay, one thing I've learned
from all of these clips
is that you have to
put a roof on stuff.
- Hey guys, excited to
chat with you today.
So I know Amber is pretty tired,
but does she happen to
know any tricks we can see?
- Is being cute a trick?
'Cause she is incredible
at being cute,
and she's really
good at sitting,
and jumping, we think she
might be part kangaroo.
We're waiting on
the DNA results.
- We'll wake her up, we'll
try some tricks for you.
Come here!
Come here, Amber!
Yeah!
There's our girl!
- Well, after all that,
I can definitely see
why she is so tired.
Coming up, we have
some friendships
that go against everything
cartoons taught us.
- We'll be right back with
more World's Funniest Animals.
- Dogs and cats, cats and birds,
cats and pretty much any animal,
now that I think about it,
conventionally, are not
supposed to get along.
These next clips break
all the stereotypes.
A World of Difference.
- This is the cutest
thing in the world.
"Are you my mother?"
- "Yeah, man, come on,
"I'm gonna show you
right where the oats are.
"Yep, just follow me, I got you.
"You know I always take care
of my boys, come on, let's go."
"Yeah, yeah, so dude came
at me and I was just like,
"and then
he was like,
"and then I was like 'whoa!'"
And the duck's just like,
"Man, get out of here!"
- The dog's face when he turns
around and looks at the cat.
Like, did he not know
who was doing that?
- This bed's too soft.
This bed's too hard.
This one's just right.
- Now one of my
favorite segments,
because I absolutely love to
eat and I know my pets do too,
get ready for our next segment,
Supper Club.
- This chinchilla looks
really deep in thought.
I wonder what it's thinking.
"If this woman
doesn't stop filming me
"eat every meal, I'm
gonna freak out!"
Man, don't you
hate going into a restaurant
with your friends and
there's the one person
who eats way too slow?
This is that person.
- Try some of that.
Oh, no.
Whatever you say.
- This Crocodile Dundee son
having lunch with animals
and letting the animals
eat off of his plate, okay.
- Wanna try some of that?
Good, right?
Come up here if
you want the rest.
Cereal and
a bottle of wine.
It's always nice to have a
sit-down dinner with the family.
"Jerry, that's mine.
"Dude, quit licking my food.
"Come on, Dave, you too?"
- Coming up, some pets
just can't be contained.
We have some escape
artists in these next clips
on World's Funniest Animals.
Did you know that Houdini
one staged a harrowing escape
from inside a sea monster?
Really!
This next segment may
not be as cool as that,
but I bet even Houdini
could've learned something
from these canine jail breakers.
Planned Escape.
Why do we even
take dogs to the park anymore?
Do they even really need us?
You can just give them
the car keys by now.
Good boy!
"See,
Barry, the key to
"opening up doors
without thumbs is simple.
"You gotta proportion
your weight.
"Yeah, there we go.
"Ah, yep, see, it's
in your weight."
Wow.
The one thing a horse
is supposed to do
is jump over a fence.
Run, Forrest, run!
- Why did the fish
cross the road?
Because the river
ran through it.
- Finally, I can take
my fish for a walk!
I could be a
wish-walker!
- Everyone has their good
days and their bad days.
These next animals
are definitely not
having a good day.
Up The Wall.
- Yeah, this dog is
not being subtle,
he does not want
to share his bed.
Which one's the robot?
I can't even tell.
- Actually, this really
isn't a good time,
he takes his meal
time very seriously.
No,
you've had enough.
Your breakfast is gone, move on.
No, you'll get more tonight
at supper, you are not starving.
No, you're not,
you're on a diet.
No--
No more breakfast!
Listen--
Oh, my--
What just happened,
did he hit you?
- Oh man, he hit
me really strong!
Are you okay?
- We need to see
that in slow-mo.
- That had to hurt.
- Permission to approach
the bench, denied.
- Yeah, I would get right up
if a seal growled
at me like that.
Have you seen their teeth?
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here is a quick recap of
all of the funniest moments.
A haywire horse, a daring dog,
a clip that took the
term "dog and pony show"
to a whole new level,
an exasperated elephant,
a tourist who was rudely
kicked out of his seat
by a local sea lion,
and a cowboy who must
really enjoy his family dinners.
We've really covered a lot!
Our time's up on
this week's episode
of World's Funniest Animals.
A huge thanks to
our fantastic panel
and to our celebrity guests,
Diana DeGarmo and Ace Young,
for bringing their
pet on the show.
- Thank you, our pleasure.
- Amber's, too.
- I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton,
and Ruby and I
are off to uncover
some more interesting
animal clips.
See you next time!
Can you wave bye?
Wave bye-bye?
'Sup, little guy?