- Get the game together,
you're not gonna wanna
miss, a minute of the show.
Where we have, a silly spinner,
a bobby leaving bad boy,
an utterly clean otter,
and these babysitting buddies,
right here on, "World's
Funniest Animals."
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton,
and you're watching
"World's Funniest Animals."
Today, I'm joined by my
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby,
and a few friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest, Stephen Kramer Glickman.
- Hey everyone,
happy to be here,
and excited to see what
we have in store tonight.
- Thanks for being here,
Stephen, these next animals,
well, there are no words
just get your ohs and ahs ready,
because these critters,
are just plain cute.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist,
the hilarious
comedian, Neel Ghosh.
- Hey Liz, happy to be here.
- We have one of the cutest
clips, I've ever seen right now.
- These cute segments
are too much for me.
What are you guys
trying to do here?
I kinda like these gloves?
Anyone else have a problem?
- Our next panelist, is the
amazing comedian, Brian Cooper.
- Hi Liz.
- This next clip features,
a very hyperactive animal.
- This is gonna be good.
And from that moment on,
Timmy believed that
he too, was a dog.
- Now you're joined
by actor, writer,
director, and
musician, Maiara Walsh.
- Happy to be here, Liz.
- Are you ready for something
that is just too cute to handle?
- I can't wait for this one.
That was some pretty good form.
- And now, our final panelist,
actress, Carmen Hodgson.
- Oh my God, I'm so
ready for tonight.
What clips do we have?
- Are you ready for the
cutest animal I've ever seen?
- Awesome, let's see it.
Oh man, I hate it when
I get shampoo in my eye.
- There's certain phrases,
like walk or treat, that can
cause our pets to totally freak.
These next clips show
that exact moment,
where animals are "Losing It".
- Parkour cats.
Yeah, that's a thing.
- This cat learned how to do
this from the Caddyshack gopher.
- That dog just turned that
hammock, into a seesaw.
- Catch a rabbit, no problem,
catch his tail, a lot harder.
- Hey, what's up dog?
I don't know, but I don't
think that was Decaf coffee
they just gave me.
Are ball pits the equivalent
of catnip for dogs?
- From the television
series, "Big Time Rush,"
we've got Stephen Kramer
Glickman with us here tonight,
is that a pug I see?
What's their name?
- Hey Liz, this is Jelly Donut.
She's like a member
of our family
and she's a pillow
with eyeballs.
- Jelly Donut?
What a fun name?
Jelly Donut looks
pretty adorable,
does she happen to
know any tricks?
- Liz, she doesn't do
the trick on demand,
because she has
performance anxiety,
but she does sleep
70% of the day.
So, she's basically a magician.
- So, we talked to James
Maslow in a previous episode,
where he had a run-in with
a Boa constrictor on set.
Did you have any scenes
with animals on that show?
- Well, Elizabeth,
on Big Time Rush,
we got to work
with a chimpanzee,
we got to work with a skunk,
and when I played "The Pigeon",
in the movie, "Storks,"
my mom bought me
an actual pigeon.
It was pretty crazy.
- Thanks again for coming
on the show, Stephen,
I guess we'll just
leave Jelly Donut
to do her, favorite trick.
Some of the most playful pets
coming up next, on,
World's Funniest Animals.
Every now and then I
have a lot of work to do
and Ruby here, just
won't stop pestering me.
Even though it may make
me fall behind a bit,
I can't resist that
cute little face.
Check out these other animals
who just wanna have fun,
on our next segment,
"Play With Me".
- Come on mom, hold still honey,
have a colic and
something on your face.
- What did I say about
too much Red bull?
- Don't feel like studying?
Need a distraction?
Bingo.
- You know honey, if you keep
getting that ball for him,
he's never gonna learn
how to fetch on his own.
- Yeah, he can set,
but can't he spike?
- Just make sure
that you feel good.
About you, it is
about you today.
- Crack open the notepad,
because these expert trainers,
are going to show you
some amazing tricks,
they have taught their pets.
Here's training day.
- And you grab your
partner and Dosey-doe.
- Come on let's go.
Through, wait, come
on get up, okay.
- Okay, is it like a school,
to teach dogs these
stuff or something?
- Oh, that is so cool,
a hand stand on a hand.
- That's incredible!
- Emma wants to
know, what's going on.
- Poop!
- Yeah, Jerry good job!
- Make sure you go downstairs.
Ready?
Bring me that ball back..
- He
brought it back, huh?
- I've never seen a cat
play catch
and actually bring it back.
- Coming up, we
have some animals,
who just about had enough,
"Flipping Out,"
next on World's
Funniest Animals.
Did you know, that a
hummingbird can beat its wings
up to 88 times per second?
You heard me right, per second!
While these animals may
not have that much energy,
it's clear that something's
driving them crazy.
Flipping out.
- Spinning butt attack,
can't defend it.
- Now I've heard of a Tasmanian
devil, but the
Tasmanian Pitbull?
- Sign that dog up for the NFL!
- Every day, it's another bill,
a piece of junk mail
or collection notice.
Where's that mail
order bone I ordered?
- Please rip-up
all my bills too.
- And then he just went crazy.
- But he's having so much
fun, you can't get mad.
- Somebidy's gonna
attack somebody
soon, I can feel
it, I can feel it.
Don't just sit there, videotape
me for all your friends!
Help me get up!
- What to do when there's no TV.
Stick something on the wall
and watch your cat for hours.
- Even though this is
World's Funniest Animals,
while we were searching the
web for hilarious videos
to bring you,
there were a few that were
just too cute to pass up.
No laughs about it, these
clips are too adorable.
Hi,
spin, turn!
- Good gril, wave, wave.
Are you sad?
Be sad!
Good girl, can you hi-five?
Good job, can you pray?
Put your paws out,
put your paws out
Can you pray?
Good girl, goodbye!
- Okay, my dog has poops,
that are bigger than this dog.
- 5% dog, 95% fluff.
- Man, if only someone could
keep me occupied like this.
- Patty cake, Patty cake,
baker's man, bake me a
cake, as fast as you can
so pat it and roll
it, good girl!
- Does this dog take double
A or triple A batteries?
- Pat a cake, pat a cake
as fast as you can.
- Patty cake, Patty
cake, producer man,
get me this dog as
fast as you can!
- Don't go away, World's
Funniest Animals,
will be right back.
Don't you hate when you're stuck
at home with nothing to do?
I know I do.
Sometimes, you just gotta
escape, and get some fresh air.
Turns out, animals
feel the same way,
as we found out, in this next
segment, "Planned Escape".
Jump over the fence.
That is too crazy, oh man!
- That was perfect timing,
when he said to jump.
- Jump over the fence.
- This giraffe, has had enough
of being a tourist attraction.
I think
we've reinforced this,
locked off the windows, so,
he can't break through that,
extended the door,
double locked,
I think, now I may
be speaking too soon,
but I think, we found a
way to keep stinky in.
Don't think you can
break through those,
Yep, all the way to
the ceiling, bud.
No jumping on the...
Are you kidding me?
- I have to see that again.
No jumping on the...
Are you kidding me?
Alright, is that
how you do it, huh?
Perfect.
- This dog has definitely
done this before.
- If you have a pet,
you know how sometimes
they just can't stop
begging for attention.
These next clips feature
animals asking for attention,
in some unconventional ways.
"I will not be ignored."
- Okay, big deal, your
tail is longer than mine,
you don't have to keep
whacking into my face.
- Spin around.
- This is one of
my favorite things
that dogs do with the hose.
- Washing two hogs and a dog.
- Wow, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here is a quick recap of
all of our funniest moments.
fetching furballs,
dizzy dogs a berserk
parker, a cat who refuses to be
beat on the green
a frisky feline, the smallest
puppy I have ever seen,
and a Patty cake,
playing kitten.Aww!
Well, that's all the time we
have for you on this episode
of World's Funniest Animals,
a special thanks to our panel,
and to our celebrity guest,
Stephen Kramer Glickman,
for joining us.
- My pleasure, thanks Liz.
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton,
and I'll be back with
more hilarious videos
on World's Funniest Animals.
- Can you pray?
- Jump over the
fence, jump, jump,
oh, wow, that was too crazy.