- The show is about to start.
You won't wanna miss this.
A five finger female feeding
these dooling deer
a tail biting tagalong
or this crazy
kangaroo knockout.
These hilarious
animal clips and more
next on "World's
Funniest Animals".
Welcome back to "World's
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton.
Today I'm joined by
my trusty sidekicks,
Hank and Ruby, and a few friends
and panelists as well as our
celebrity guests, Toby Rand.
- Hi everyone, I'm
really looking forward
to getting stuck into
tonight's festivities.
- Thanks for being here Toby.
Hank, Ruby and I are
excited to introduce you
to some of the best clips of
some of your favorite animals
that we could find.
Trust us you're not gonna
wanna miss what's coming up.
Why is it that the smallest pets
tend to be the most scrappy?
In our next segment,
"Mighty Mini",
we get to root for
the little guy.
"Mighty Mini" brought
to you with commentary
by our first panelist
singer, actor,
comedian, radio host
extraordinaire, Mikalah Gordon.
- Hi Liz.
- Are you ready for a little guy
to finally stand
up for themselves?
- The suspense is killing
me, play the clip.
This duck is like
come back here,
you have not paid the bill.
- Now we are joined
by actor, writer,
director, musician,
Maiara Walsh.
- Hi Liz.
- Are you ready for a
clip with this animal
who I am convinced has
a Napoleon complex?
- Let's see it.
Yeah, buster I might be
small, but I have a big roar.
- Our next panelist is the
amazing comedian, Brian Cooper.
Hi Liz.
- This next clip
shows us some animals
who just wanna play.
- Let's see it.
Two dogs, one toy.
- Now we have musician, singer,
songwriter, Brandon Rogers.
- So happy to be here Liz.
Nice to see you.
- We have a little guy
whose bite is just as big
as his bark in this clip.
- I gotta see this.
This is crazy.
I'm more impressed how the
other dog doesn't even move.
- This puppy is so cute.
He just wants to
play or is he hungry?
I can't tell.
- Oh, so cute.
- That is utterly adorable.
- For some reason
my little Ruby here
thinks it's funny
to hide from me
whenever I'm looking
for her in the house.
But there's one thing that
always works, dinner time.
- That one dog is
just watching them,
like, "What are you guys doing?"
- This is the kind of
competition I've
been waiting for.
- Honestly, this is how I feel
when I'm waiting for
everyone else's food
to get to the table.
- This dog is so excited to
eat, but he's being so good.
- I think at this point
you just got to invest
in a lock and key.
- Today on "World's
Funniest Animals",
we're excited to bring a
special celebrity guest
to chat with us about their pet.
Please welcome
rockstar, Toby Rand.
Thanks for being here Toby.
I see you brought your
cat with you today.
- This is Tripp.
He's having a bad day.
He's like a part of
furniture, aren't you buddy?
But he doesn't leave
any hair anywhere.
So we're pretty
happy about that.
- I mean, no cat hair
is definitely a plus.
Have you ever worked with
any animals professionally?
- As you can see, I have
a real affinity with cats.
And this amazing thing
happened on scent once
when we were in
a line enclosure,
the line turned around lifted
its tail and peed all over me.
You heard that, didn't you?
- Thanks Toby and
Tripp for stopping by.
Great to see you both.
- Say goodbye Tripp, yeah
go and get lost somewhere.
Go on off you go, see ya.
- Some of the most playful pets
coming up next on "World's
Funniest Animals".
Remember that one toy
you couldn't let go of
when you were a kid,
also to these animals,
let's take a look at
some of these cuties
at play in our next
segment "Playtime Pooches".
- Girl, just put the
cushions wherever you want.
Feel free to
redecorate, whatever.
This puppy has
some new friends, Guinea pigs.
Hi there are, how are you?
Hello again?
Hi, nice to meet you.
What you doing?
Hi, wanna play?
- How would you be
able to pick just one?
- This is why our
pets need pets.
- Can we play back
the part when the dog
actually rolls over the balloon.
- We are back with one
of my favorite
segments, wild animals.
I can't wait to
show you what antics
these wild ones have been up to.
It's a wildlife.
- Wow, this family
has some skills.
Where do I sign up for this?
- What did I just watch?
Did he just flip
over on purpose?
- This guys are
really going at it.
- I mean, come on.
Who doesn't want to be a
part of this wrestling match?
Sometimes it's
tough to get comfortable.
Looks like he's just giving up.
- Definitely don't see
those in my backyard.
- A buck and a doe
ran into a carwash.
Well actually only one of
them ran into the carwash.
The other ran through it.
Thank you, come again.
You're watching "World's
Funniest Animals".
We'll be right back.
I absolutely love to eat
and I know my pets do too.
Get ready for our next segment,
it's time to "Chow Down".
I don't know if I've seen
a dog eat a watermelon.
- He's on a diet.
He only has fruits and
veggies for treats.
- Who's down to cover my
full body in peanut butter
so I can do this?
- You know, when your
partner makes annoying noises
when they eat?
Once you pop the fun,
don't stop y'all.
- As cute as many of the animals
in our next segment may be.
Their behaviors remind
us that sometimes
it's best to leave
them in the wild.
Check out some of
these untamed beast
in "Rumble in the Jungle".
- This golf course takes playing
in the rough to a
whole another level.
- Help I'm falling I can't
get up, oh I'm good.
- This is amazing, imagine
seeing this in person.
- The people on this
whale watching tour
definitely got
their money's worth.
- Remember size matters
not small but strong.
Coming up next on "World's
Funniest Animals".
Sometimes it doesn't matter
how small you are.
If you have a big enough
bark, that could be enough.
Small but strong.
This goat is like
a boxing trainer.
Like come on, Rocky
hit me, hit me harder.
Is that all you got?
- Cats are so evil.
- Okay, remember the rules.
No face hits, that's
my money maker.
Hey, I said not the face.
This dog is like, "Thanks
mom I love my new toy."
- Okay, hear the
rule, we can play.
But the minute you get too
close, you got to close.
- This puppy is like, "Okay,
so if I win the tug of war,
"What do I get?
"A treat?"
All right a treat it is.
- Okay, I said you can play
with my toy for a minute.
It is now getting out of hand.
Let go, let go.
- Sometimes the best playmate
for your pet is another pet.
Get ready to "Party
All The Time".
- Got to love
community pool day.
- Pool party.
- Something tells me
that they're not sticking
to the no peeing
in the pool rule.
- These beers are
having so much fun
but look at their reactions.
They know they
don't belong there.
- Well, that's almost it for us
but just in case
you missed anything
here is a quick recap of
all of the funniest moments.
Squeaking swine, silly Sloss,
daring dogs, friendly foxes
courageous Courtneys,
tight tigers.
Somebody's heads
on the golf course
and an owner who had an eating
competition with his dogs.
Maybe I should try
that, probably not.
Well that's all we have
time for on this episode
of "World's Funniest Animals".
A special thanks to our panel
and to our celebrity
guest, Toby Rand.
Thanks for joining us.
- Bye everyone, thank you
so much for having me.
Be safe
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton
check back in with us
soon for more insane
animal antics, right here on
"World's Funniest Animals".