I hope
you're ready to laugh.
Because on this episode,
we're bringing you a head
banging doggo,
an excitable elephant,
cross walking
cows,
and a raccoon who's
way too relaxed.
This and more on today's episode
of world's funniest animals.
- Hey and welcome to
world's funniest animals,
where we've curated some of
the most hilarious animal clips
just for you.
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton.
And these are my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby.
Joined today with a few of
my friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest Brittany Underwood.
- Hey everyone,
thanks for having me.
- Thanks for being
here, Brittany.
Some animals are content
with just chilling out
and relaxing all day.
But the animals I'm about to
show you are not the calm type.
In fact, they're pretty crazy.
Let's take a look
at some animals,
expanding energy in our
next segment, flipping out.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist,
actor, writer, director,
and musician, Maiara Walsh.
- Hey Liz.
- Are you ready for a dog
who will not stop trying to
get their owner's attention?
- This sounds adorable.
I can't wait.
What you doing'?
Dog, stop it.
- Well, you know, at least
they have a free window washer.
Could
you please not?
Okay, and there's drool
all over the window.
- Our next panelist is the
amazing comedian, Brian Cooper.
- Can't wait to see
what we got tonight.
You think I can't fly?
Are you serious?
You guys haven't seen Dumbo?
I got this, watch this, hold
on, wait a second, I got this.
I got this, watch this.
- Now we have musician singer
songwriter, Brandon Rogers.
- Hey Liz.
- Are you ready for
a very rowdy animal?
- Show me what you got.
what's the opposite
of spring cleaning?
- For our final panelist.
We have singer actor, comedian,
radio host, Mikalah Gordon.
- Hey Liz, what clips do
you have for me tonight?
- We have an animal who
is just a little excited.
- I can't wait.
- I mean, come on.
Who doesn't like to
play in the snow.
- Let's take a look
at some of the animals
who belong in the dog house.
In our next segment, guilty.
Hi.
- There's no way I'm
not losing my mind,
because if see this monkey,
you will see he has
LeBron's wingspan.
He can slap everybody in
that room from that balcony.
- So do you think he has
a favorite candy bar?
Or does he just grab
the first one he sees?
Look at that
bear, it's huge.
It's in the trash.
- This gas station's
prices are too high.
So I'm gonna take a
snack from in here.
- I have one of these
contraptions at home
and if I walk in and my
pet is drinking like this,
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I'm gonna be terrified
and also impressed.
- I'm always excited for
this part of the show,
where we introduce you
to a celebrity guest
and their pet.
Today bringing us
her fuzzy friend,
we have Brittany
Underwood from "The Bay"
and "One life to live."
- Just chilling here
with my buddy Skeeter.
He's already passed out.
He was like, "mom,
I'm exhausted."
Already it's mid-afternoon.
- Brittany I heard you
had a pretty funny story
about working with
an animal on set.
Do you mind sharing it with us?
- I worked with a
dog on this show.
I think it was an
English bulldog
and we're in the
middle of a scene
and he starts snoring
and we were like,
"Oh, okay."
But we just used it in
the scene and we laughed
and it ended up being fine.
So it wasn't like
a horror story.
Although I can imagine
that on any type of set,
working with animals,
there's always an option
and a possibility of
like terribly gone wrong.
But I've been lucky,
I've been lucky,
animals are, they've been
good with me I guess.
Right?
- Not every dog is a
consummate professional,
like Skeeter over there.
- Okay, sure.
- I can't to show you what
else we have in store.
A howling hound, a curious
cat, a mischievous monkey,
a rowdy raccoon and a dog who
just really wants some pizza.
All this and more next on
world's funniest animals.
Music is an art form.
It requires dedication,
rhythm and focus.
And I'm absolutely not promising
you'll get any of that
in these next clips
of animals jamming out.
Or at least
attempting to jam out.
Sing along.
- Looks like someone's had
one too many at the piano bar.
- I have to see that again.
- Yes, I prefer music
with my massage.
Thank you.
- Do you know how
to play the piano?
"Oh, well I just pick
at the keys a bit."
- Look it's Travis Barker.
Get it?
It's a dog.
- Nothing like a night
out at the opera huh?
- The funny thing
is that the bird
is much better than the guy.
Try that one,
try.
You beat me on that one.
- Do you have a pet who
sticks their nose in the room
every time you open
a bag of chips?
Or chases after a sound when
it hears an unfamiliar noise?
These next clips feature animals
who are just as
inquisitive as your pets,
and maybe even a little more
in our segment, curious pets.
- Nice birdie.
Must not eat, nice birdie.
- This is great.
Look how careful
that cat is being
it's like he doesn't
want a murder rap.
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
- When a ferret thinks he's
a better cook than you,
you was not be very good.
Oh very funny guys,
who greased the pole?
- Hey Brittany.
- Okay. Skeeter.
Don't you wanna come
say hi to everybody?
Come say hi Skeets.
He's got bedhead, couchhead.
Is that a thing?
- Well, Skeeter may have
couchhead, but he's adorable.
Does he know any tricks?
- Yes, Skeeter can
do some tricks.
Right Skeeter?
- It's Skeeters world,
we're all just living in it.
- Go get it.
Or he just watches me throw
it and looks back at me like,
"Are you gonna get that?"
He's like, "I
can't be bothered."
Cool, thanks Skeeter,
you're embarrassing me.
- It's okay, buddy.
It's mom's job to be
in front of the camera.
You keep doing what
you're best at.
- I feel like after this, I've
realized how slacking I am
on teaching Skeeter tricks.
I feel like I wanna teach
him the ones like bang!
And then the dogs go aah.
Are you scared?
Bang!
I'm sorry, I didn't meet it.
He just looked at me like,
"mom, did you just kill me?"
Oh my God, his face
is like of betrayal.
I'm so sorry, I don't
wanna teach you that trick.
I love you.
We're good, I promise.
- Thanks for coming and bringing
your pet to see us today.
- Well, thanks so
much for having me.
This was so much fun.
- Coming up, we have some
critters who are up to no good,
caught red handed.
Next on world's
funniest animals.
Pets are infamous for chewing
up important documents,
hiding socks and stealing
food off the dinner table.
These next furry guys have
been caught doing all that
and taken it even a step
further, caught red handed.
Okay, so
it's 7:30 in the morning,
I woke up and my
bedroom door was shut,
which my love left so
I could get some sleep.
But that's a very
dangerous combination.
And so I came out
to the living room,
where my dogs came
running to me.
it looked like this.
- I promise you, this was
like that when we woke up.
Well, I
did have two pillows,
see it over there,
that's the last one.
- Raccoon videos are
confusing, right?
Is this their pet?
Or are they going to have
to call animal services?
Who knows.
- Why pay for an expensive
shredder, when you have Max.
- These monkeys are
like velociraptor,
they work in teams.
Like stealing candy from a baby.
- Some dogs can sit,
stay and rollover,
but these next animals are
more musically inclined
with their tricks.
Join the band.
- I mean, I think everyone
has done this right?
Spin around and then
try to walk straight.
- The bird is like,
okay, I'll sing with you,
just quit spitting on me.
- Tonight we have the
two-cat duo playing,
"who even knows at this point."
- Don't go away just yet.
You'll be just as curious as
these animals in our next clip.
These next clips feature
animals who are just as curious
and maybe even a little more,
in our segment,
investigative animals.
- And now the new toy, kitty
in a bottle, hours of fun.
- Aww, so cute.
- In between teacup and
miniature I unveil to you,
Mason Jar Kittens.
- Safety first, you must
always hold the handrail.
- When you can't
kick the craving,
but you just started your diet.
What are you doing?
- Forget expensive water
jets, just get a pet.
- There are certain
phrases like walk or treat,
that can cause our
pet to totally freak.
These clips show
those exact moments
where animals are losing it.
- So is this a follow
the leader thing?
Or do they know something
that we don't know?
- Simon says,
"jump, jump, jump."
Oh yeah we got this.
Hey, daddy's home.
Its been a long eight months.
- Now that is true love.
Why can't my roommate
do that when I get home.
- This is me growing up trying
to make sure everybody knows
that I'm not ticklish,
but in all actuality,
I'm very ticklish and
I hate being tickled.
- This dog's face is hilarious.
He knows it's coming,
but he can't stop it.
- What like you've never
had an existential crisis
on the couch with your family.
- This dog really loves
world's funniest animals.
- That's it, I'm drafting
him for very obstacle course
known to man.
Water's not slowing
him down, nothing.
- Ahhh, an open air mud bath.
- That's an impressive strike.
- Wait a minute, one
more time on that.
Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything.
Here is a quick recap of
all of the funniest moments,
a cooped up cat,
a DIY dog jacuzzi,
a kleptomaniac squirrel.
I still wanna know
what candy bar he took.
Oh, and man's best
feathered friend,
a fatigued feline
trying to relax
during its owner's
piano practice.
A drumming dog and a
cockatoo has decided
he prefers his toys on the
ground instead of in the bin.
I might pass out.
That's all the time we
have for our show today.
Thanks to our fantastic panel
and to our celebrity guest,
Brittany Underwood, and
her pup for joining us.
- Look, good bye everybody.
- I'm your host,
Elizabeth Stanton,
that pizza made Ruby
and I both hungry.
So we're gonna place an order.
Come on, girl,
see you next time.
Right here on world's
funniest animals.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
You're always hungry.
What are you doing?
But he's hungry
though look at him go.