- Get ready to laugh
because today on the show,
we have a hopping husky,
a doting duck, a canine
with cowboy aspirations
and a photogenic flamingo.
These clips and
much more to come
here on World's
Funniest Animals.
Hey there and welcome to
World's Funniest Animals.
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton
and these are my trusty
sidekicks, Hank and Ruby.
Joined today with a few of
my friends and panelists,
as well as a celebrity
guest, James Maslow.
- Hey everybody?
Blue and I are happy to be here.
And we're excited to see
what is in store tonight.
- Thanks for being here, James.
Our pets are so cute
that we just wanna
kiss and squeeze them
because we can't stand
at how cuddly they are,
but sometimes they just
wanna be left alone.
Let's take a look
at what happens
when animals feel like
their personal space
has been invaded,
Don't mess with me.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist
actor, writer, director
and musician Maiara Walsh.
- Hey Liz.
Thank you so much for having me,
I'm so excited to
watch these clips.
- This video shows us a
dog owner taking a selfie
with their less
than pleased pet.
- Now if an animal is angry,
I'm making a 180 and getting
out of there immediately.
- Hey selfie ready?
Go!
- I mean, what could go wrong?
- For your next clip we
have the hilarious comedian,
Brian Cooper.
- Hey Liz.
I'm happy to be here ready
for some funny clips.
Let's do this!
Play stupid games,
win stupid prizes.
- Now we are joined with one
of my favorite comedians,
Neel Ghosh.
- Hey Liz?
- We have a video
with an angry goat
and a girl trying to
take a video with him.
- Angry goat, brave girl.
Can't wait to see
how this turns out.
- It's trying to
head pat me bro.
- That's a concussion.
- It's trying to
head pat me bro.
- And now our final panelist,
actress, Carmen Hodgson.
- Hey Liz?
Yes, I'm so excited for these
because animal videos are
seriously my favorite videos.
Next time bring the carrots!
When this guy
is asked how he relaxes,
he pets his little dog
who is clearly not a
fan of being touched.
- You see petting your dog
is one of the most relaxing
things you can possibly do.
It releases a hormone called
oxytocin, which reduces stress.
Also it lowers your heart rate
and it lowers your
blood pressure.
Plus people who pet their dogs
are five times more likely
to live longer than
people who just have cats.
Plus--
- Some of my favorite movies
feature a great escape,
with the main character
against all odds
manages to sneak away.
These animals must have similar
tastes in entertainment.
Here is Jailbreak.
Okay, can we get a freeze
frame on that face?
Cats are pretty genius!
Easy.
He does this every day.
- Where there's a
will there's a way.
- Not even a thank
you from the dog.
- So the myth that
cats don't have bones
obviously it's true,
there's no way.
- On today's episode,
we've got James Maslow
from Big Time Rush.
We love animals,
you love animals
tell me, have you ever worked
with any animals on set?
- You remember a
film with a snake?
It was an episode
of Big Time Rush
it had this huge
yellow boa constrictor
something around there.
- A boa constrictor?
You're braver than I am James.
- I'm not a huge fan of snakes.
And they're like, oh
always cool I'm like okay,
I'll take one for the
team and I'll do it.
We did like three or four takes
and he started
tightening a little more.
Eventually I just had to stop
it honestly freaked me out.
It was a nice snake, but like
there's still wild reptiles,
I don't know, I just don't need
a, eight foot snake murder.
- If you think that's funny,
just wait for what's coming up.
We have a robotic cat
feeder, a dumbfounded dog
and a horse who has decided
it's time to leave the stable.
All these and more, next on
World's Funniest Animals.
Getting excited to eat
is definitely something
I can relate to,
but these animals take
it to another level.
The hunger is real
in this next segment
when it's Dinner time.
- You know what would
make this clip better?
Skates.
Hello?
I would like to speak
to your manager.
- Wow!
Way too much time on your hands?
How the cat clearly
terrified clearly horrified,
please why don't
you just feed me?
- Variety is the spice of life.
These next animals would
have to agree in our segment,
Opposites attract.
- Okay, this has to be
one of the cutest things
I've ever seen.
No offense Blue you are
out there too but you saw it.
- No, that is a baby goat.
Hey look, it's Tom Brady's son.
When did this scene of
Harry Potter come out?
- Aaaw cute!
- How's it going James?
- All right Blue?
Or just say hi, wave, hi.
- Blue seems like a good boy.
Does he know any tricks?
- He didn't learn a
whole lot of obedience
wherever he was before this.
Blue is good though
at walks and runs,
we do like six or
seven miles a day
'cause he is a gigantic beast.
He's also good at eating things,
whether it's food in his
bowl or food on your plate,
or your socks or your hands
when you give him
out for a snack,
he might just eat
those, kidding, kidding
but also not kidding.
What else is he good at?
Annoying Dad!
He's so good at annoying me.
- Even more surprises
from the animal kingdom
when we come with
World's Funniest Animals.
Don't you hate when you're stuck
at home with nothing to do?
I know I do.
Sometimes you just gotta
escape and get some fresh air,
turns out animals
feel the same way
as we found out in this next
segment, Planned escape.
- Oh, that's flexible!
That's how you know
yoga is paying off.
- The stable door is securely
locked because otherwise
the horse would just,
nevermind.
- That's a high fence!
I know humans that
couldn't climb that.
- If this dog jumps,
I'm gonna flip out.
Don't do it!
Don't jump.
Owh, okay.
- And he clears it, okay.
If I can just squeeze.
There's gotta be a way
to get out of here.
Hold on wait a second.
There it is!
I knew I shouldn't
have that last snack.
Cats can open doors,
escape through windows.
If you have a cat,
you just need to be
contained with them
going where they want.
- Sometimes you just
wanna be left alone.
Everyone needs to recharge
every once in a while
and our pets are no exception.
Take a look at
these grumpy animals
in our segment, Up the wall.
- Trying to get a
selfie with you.
- Flamingo slap!
- We need to see
that in slow mo.
- Just a five foot tall bird
what's the worst
that could happen?
- It's what you get,
trying to outdo a flamingo
at the beach.
- It's not a horror
movie that's like
an espionage film.
'Cause like the
ocean sent the seal
to remove its oxygen source.
- Oh, the cat's a
vegetarian that's it.
- Duck duck, you're gonna
get stumped, I can tell.
- That cat is more
patient than I am.
Eat your vegetables, eat up.
- Oh my God!
Me and this dog are the same,
we don't like
housekeeping chores.
Just a good Samaritan
trying to help a baby goose
off the curb.
They gonna peck you.
Mama goose
is not having it.
At least that little guy is
safe and off the streets.
- Play with me Mom, play
with me, play with me.
Huh?
Why can't you just stick
your head out of the window
like a normal dog?
A kitty
slap from the stairs?
- Owh!
That's what you
get for taking a selfie.
- Just like hey man, can I
chill on the couch with you?
It's a nice chair, can we hang?
No!
- Coming up on World's
Funniest Animals,
unlikely animal friendships.
- We'll be right back with more
of World's Funniest Animals!
- Cats and dogs are
like oil and water,
they don't usually mix well,
at least that's what cartoons
I used to watch taught me.
But we found some pretty
cool animal pairings.
I know I was surprised what we
discovered for this segment,
A world of difference.
- Hey, this ain't no
dog and pony show.
- Nevermind that's
exactly what it is.
That dog seems so happy.
Could it be the fact
that he's riding a horse?
Or it could be because
he has an amazing outfit.
- That's real love right there.
- Oh my gosh!
My heart melts when I see
the dog kiss the cow back.
- Oh yeah that's the spot,
you get in there bestie,
you get in there,
like a massage.
- I wish I made friends at the
beach as easily as that dog.
Now I wanna know
what the plans to do
if he does catch the dog.
- It's about the thrill
of the chase sometimes.
And you can stop hogging
all the attention.
- I absolutely love to eat
and I know my pets do too.
Get ready for our next
segment, Supper club.
- People put actual
vegetables on their snowman?
Hair noses and stuff?
- You see the other deer runaway
like oh man, get outta here.
- If someone asks me if I
want a snack and I say no,
I always regret it and
look exactly like this dog.
- This dog is like
the Oprah of carrots.
You get a carrot, you get a
carrot, everyone gets a carrot.
- I just love the salad bar.
Always fresh, always organic.
Me too Mich
but the early bird special
is getting out of
control these days.
- All right and the
test results are in.
You appear to be 70% fluff
and 30% celery, healthy.
- My doctor told me I have to
chew up to 30 times per bite.
- Oh my goodness!
What is this stuff?
- Give me food, give me food!
Must eat food!
- I'm not sure if she
realizes she's a bird.
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything.
Here's a quick recap of all
of the funniest moments,
a bouncing sibling rivalry,
an interesting pairing,
a wild west woofer, a flamingo
who is totally over tourists,
a dog who has no
time for chores,
some bunnies with
their very own butler
and a horse who has decided
it's finally time to move
out of their parents' house.
That's all the time
we have on our show.
Thanks again to our panel
and to our celebrity
guest, James Maslow
for bringing his pup
by to chat with us
on World's Funniest Animals.
- Thank you so much,
Liz it was our pleasure.
Blue has had a good
time being on the couch,
which he's not
usually allowed to be.
So say thank you
and say bye, bye.
- I'm Elizabeth Stanton
we'll see you again soon
with more crazy animal
clips, until next time.