Are you
ready to leap in action?
Because today on the show
we have a goose with
an attitude problem,
a map-stealing monkey,
and a reluctant retriever.
This and more on today's episode
of "Worlds Funniest Animals."
Welcome back to "World's
Funniest Animals,"
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton,
and these are my trustee
sidekicks Hank and Ruby.
Joined today with a few of
my friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest, Murray SawChuck.
- Hey Liz, thank you so much
for having me on your show.
I'm just absolutely excited
to be on this type of show
'cause I love animals.
- Thanks, Murray.
If you're anything
like me and Ruby here,
and love a good funny animal
video, you're in luck.
We've hunted the web for the
wildest animal clips out there,
and I can't wait to show
you what we've found.
Ever have one of those lazy days
where you don't feel like
doing anything at all,
even when you actually
have a ton to do?
Turns out animals can be just
as stubborn as us humans.
Check out how
stubborn they can be
in the segment,
"You Can't Make Me,"
brought to you with commentary
from our first panelist,
the amazing comedian,
Brian Cooper.
- Hey, Liz.
- Are you ready for this clip?
- Show me what ya got.
Sometimes you lose
motivation mid-sprint
- Now we joined by
by singer, actor,
comedian, radio
host Mikalah Gordon.
- Hi, happy to be here, Liz.
- This next clip features an
animal who is not very patient.
- So excited.
Oh no!
After long day of
dealing with tourists,
sometimes you gotta just
give one a good toss.
- Our next panelist is rising
star, actor, Carmen Hodgson.
- Hey, Liz, I'm so
happy to be here.
- This next clip
features some lazy dogs.
- Ooh, okay, this I have to see.
Come on.
Let's go, come on,
come on, let's go.
- I said I don't wanna go.
- For our final panelist,
we have actor, writer,
producer, Noah Matthews.
- Hey, Liz.
- We have an animal who
does not wanna be bothered
in this clip.
- Let's get into it.
Noga, you're so lazy.
Look, I'm glad you're
on this fitness journey,
but I've taken five walks
today, and I'm over it.
I only agreed on
you going on a walk,
I didn't say I would.
- Even animals get
annoyed sometimes.
whether it's personal space
or they are trying to rest,
if the don't want attention
they will be sure
to let you know.
Get ready for our next
segment, "I Don't Think So."
Is
she squishing you?
Tilly, you're
squashing the baby.
Tilly!
- She looks terrified,
but he looks so cozy.
Matilda!
He's as
happy as he looks.
It's me and my wife, guys.
We
got witnesses, boy.
- I understand why
chickens are so aggressive.
Everyone's trying to eat 'em.
Okay, now remember,
when getting attacked
by a vicious goose, just
call for some school children
to come and save you.
- Oh, okay.
- Unfortunately though,
they won't be able to save
your dignity but.
- This is what it feels
like sharing a plate
of nachos with someone.
Stop stealing all the good chips
- Here's a thought.
When you have a giant thieving
bird in the neighborhood,
maybe not such a great idea
to leave the kitchen
door wide open.
- Hey Murray, who
do we have here?
- I have long hair chihuahuas.
They are all rescues.
This is Smudge, yes, it is.
And this is Kahlua,
and this is Bailey.
- Do you ever use these
little guys in your magic act?
- I am always asked if I use
them in my magic show
here in Las Vegas and I don't.
I have brought them on
stage 'cause every year
I do a charity show
that raises money
for rescue dogs and animals,
and it's our 8th year this year
and I call it
"Begging for Magic."
And we have all sorts
of entertainments
here in Las Vegas,
and we were about on stage
just to show everybody the pups
and they got to meet them
and get pictures with them,
but that's all we do with them.
We don't usually use
them in any magic tricks.
- Wow, magic for
an amazing cause.
So do your dogs know any tricks?
- Yes, they do some tricks.
They're not ridiculous tricks.
Actually, Smudge does
have ridiculous tricks.
Smudge is actually the only
chihuahua bowling ball.
She runs up to me, falls on
her back and you push her away,
she slides on her back,
gets up and runs right back
and she absolutely loves it,
so we'll demonstrate
that for you.
Smudge, come here!
We can do it, come here!
That's my little girl, ready?
And away she goes!
Come on!
Oh wait, one, two,
three, and away she goes.
Come here, baby,
and one more time.
Away you go!
Come here.
That's my girl, that's
my girl!
That's our Smudge.
Bailey and Kaluha they're
great at rolling over,
shaking a paw, sitting up.
Sit, sit!
Good girl! That's funny.
Roll over, let's roll.
Good girl!
Such a good girl.
Also they actually
do a training course
which I take them every week.
They go up and down
different partitions
and through tubes
and all that stuff.
They've been all doing it
for a couple of years now.
- Wow, that is quite
the agility course
I'll have to bring
Hank and Ruby someday,
and we can have one
big pet play date.
Coming up, we have a
gregarious giraffe,
a gruff goat, a monkey
stealing a bus driver's lunch,
and a dog dancing
their heart out
in the middle of the pet store.
All this and more next on
"World's Funniest Animals."
Did you know that butterflies
can taste with their feet?
Pretty cool, but
not exactly a talent
I think I'd want myself, yuck.
But there are few that
I wouldn't mind having
in the segment "Hidden Talents."
- A dog that does laundry?
I've never been more jealous,
Oh, now he's taking
them out of the dryer.
He does laundry better
than me, and I have thumbs.
- Okay, here is
the real question.
Shouldn't the dog's sneakers
be on the front paws?
This is the same
way Rocky trained
when he beat Clubber Lang.
- We get it, you're cool,
and your dog's cool too.
Meanwhile, I can't
even can't let my dog
off leash at the beach.
- One, two!
- Come on down, chest
down, elbows out.
- One, two, one, two, one!
- The real question
here, who's training who?
- One, two!
Wow, this
cat is seriously shredded.
He's Olympic material for sure.
Watch out, Shaun White.
No one likes being
ignored, even animals.
In fact, some will
go out of their way
to get your attention and end
up hilarious when they do.
Check out these
attention-hungry animals
in the segment, "Look at Me."
Why are seals so cute?
I think I want one.
Boom, that thing is long.
Hello, I
look good, look at me.
Ooh, yeah gimme a kiss.
Yeah, you haven't had
enough love.
- Wait, did that bat just wave?
- You're gonna get
up and feed me,
even if I have to
take it all off.
Welcome back to the
little pug's camera view.
So far this camera
strap is holding up.
Why are
small dogs so brave?
Coming
up, we see some animals
who've decided they cannot
be bothered, not today.
Next on "World's
Funniest Animals."
The animal kingdom can
be an unforgiving place
and sometimes it's
survival of the fittest
or at least the bossiest
to survive and prove
that you are the
alpha, "Not Today."
You call that a bark?
This is a bark.
Never mind.
She doesn't
see that one coming.
Boo!
- It's a sneak attack!
- Don't drop it on the floor.
What's wrong with you?
Say bye to everyone.
- Bye!
Say goodbye to everyone.
- He just stole his lunch.
- I have to see that again.
- So that's how dogs learn
how to swim, it's by ducks.
It's your turn to chase me.
Guess you guys are
gonna leave now?
Okay, the dog
is doing the dog paddle
and the ducks are doing fly
the heck out of this place.
Oh, you think you
are so cool with the toy.
I'll show you.
Here I come!
- You'll be left in awe by
some of these furry feats.
Coming back to part two
of the fan favorite,
"Pets Have Talents."
- Five, six, seven eight.
So am just picturing
them in their living room
going over these steps.
It's not weird at all.
Seriously, do
I have to do everything
myself around here?
He's just a delivery guy
bringing in some lunch
to some lazy cows
on Moober Eats.
I'm doing
an obstacle course
and the only obstacles are
all the other darn cats.
Move!
- Oh my God, it's like
ninja warrior cats style.
Well,
now I've seen it all.
and he's actually riding the
bike around the neighborhood.
- Mischief, can you say hello?
- Hello.
- Good bird.
He does all sorts of voices.
Can you say hi?
- Hi.
Good job.
And sometimes he hears people
who have a cold.
Good job, Mischief.
Can you say hello?
No, hello.
He's all excited.
- I mean, he's
technically saying hello.
- Hello.
Hi, hi.
- Hi.
- This isn't working
out too well.
- Quoth the raven, just
give me the treat, lady.
Coming up,
some animals just want
all the attention,
"Hogging the Limelight,"
next on "World's
Funniest Animals."
What would the internet
be if it wasn't for people
constantly seeking attention?
Well, it's not just people
and lucky for us sometimes
it's even caught on camera.
"Hogging the Limelight."
- Smile for the camera.
Guess what, I'm not taking a
picture, I'm taking a video.
Yeah, got you, ha.
Still smiling though.
Good job.
- Don't you hate it when
someone takes a picture
of you when you're eating?
- No, insurance lady,
I said goat prints.
What you mean, I'm not covered?
It's not showing
off when you have talent.
Absolutely amazing.
- Oh, whoa, cool
guy with my shades.
Okay, they
reversed this video, right?
This cannot be real.
Good girl, good girl.
Seriously, mom?
You're a good girl.
This
is a joke, right?
Gimme that.
- Hey! Sadie!
- Some days you just can't
be bothered to do anything.
These pets are having
one of those days
in our segment "I Don't Wanna."
This dog is taking a nap
and falling ever so slowly.
Great, now the cat's awake too.
- Went down, collapse
on the ground.
Works for me when I
don't wanna do something.
Now it's
time to come home.
- This cat has dug her
claws into this decision,
and she ain't moving.
Hey try picking up
the rock instead.
- He flipped him over like he
was a barbecue piece of meat.
These millennial
dogs are so spoiled,
wants everything done for them.
- Well, that's almost it for us
but just in case you missed
anything, here is quick recap
of all the funniest moments.
A not so scary goose,
a poking primate,
a canine workout
partner, sneaky lion cub
and a snowboarding cat.
I totally think it might
just make the pros.
Thanks so much for tuning
in and checking out
some of the world's
funniest animals.
And a special
thanks to our panel
and our celebrity
guest Murray SawChuck
for checking in and chatting
with us about your pets.
- Hey, Liz, thanks so much
for having me on your show.
Smudge, Bailey, and Kaluha
had such a great time.
Thank you.
- Until next time, I'm
your host Elizabeth Stanton.
I'll be back soon with
more hilarious clips
of your favorite
creatures right here
on "World's Funniest Animals."
You're
squishing the baby.
- Say bye to everyone.
Bye!