- Time to plop down
after a long day
because today on the show,
we have karate kicking cats,
a helicoptery hamster,
a turtle taxi,
and a floor sweeping fowl.
Settle in for a good laugh,
because you're watching
World's Funniest Animals.
Welcome back to World's
Funniest Animals,
I'm your host Elizabeth Stanton.
Today I'm joined by
my trusty sidekicks,
Hank and Ruby
and a few friends and panelists
as well as our celebrity
guest, Kelli Goss.
- Hi guys, we're so
happy to be here.
We're excited to see
what you have in store tonight.
- Thanks for being here Kelli.
We're bringing you
some of the best
animal bloopers you've
ever laid eyes on,
but enough talking about
them let's get started.
You know while it's always
nice to have friends
with things in common,
sometimes it's nice
to learn from others
who come from
different backgrounds.
I'm not sure if that's
what these animals
had in mind,
but check out these odd pairings
on this segment
opposites attract.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first
panelist actor, writer,
director and musician,
Maiara Walsh.
- Hey Liz, show me what you got.
- Are you writing
for some animals
you would not expect
to be friends?
- Sounds like my
new favorite clip.
This could be seen as cute
or the cat version
of me falling asleep
with a bag of chips on my lap.
- For your next clip
we have the hilarious
comedian, Brian Cooper.
- Hi Liz, this is gonna be good.
This cat is a dog whisper.
- Now we have musician,
singer songwriter,
Brandon Rogers.
- I'm so pumped
I cannot wait to see
what we have tonight.
- Are you ready
for some interspecies
friendships?
- Well don't keep me
waiting, this I have to see.
when you cuddle with
your best friend.
I can't tell who's
enjoying this more,
the dog or the cat.
- For our final panelist
we have singer actor comedian
radio host, Mikalah Gordon.
- What's going on, Liz?
What clips do you
have for me tonight?
Ah love is love, no
matter what species.
- Who doesn't love nestling
with a little kitten.
This taxi service is so slow.
- At this rate, I'll
reach my food bowl
by next week.
- I'm pretty amazed
that so many animals
seem to be skilled
escape artists.
Uh-oh, someone sound the alarm,
we've got another set
of jailbreak videos.
- Good boy.
- Not sure why this
guy left me a ladder.
- No, I can
fit it, you're wrong.
I just need to
move a little more
and there you go, like a glove.
- Now this is an
actual jailbreak.
Not exactly a high
speed pursuit.
- It's that time again
where we visit a celebrity
guest in their home
and get to know their pet.
From The Ranch and The
Young and the Restless
Kelli Goss. Hey Kelly,
who do you have there with you?
- Yeah, this is Teddie Sue,
this is my little rescue dog,
she's about a year old
and she's still a pup,
so she's got lots
and lots of energies,
you can see, she can
barely sit still,
but she is the light of my life.
- Hey, in your
time as an actress,
have you ever worked
with an animal on set?
- Working on the ranch,
we had animals on
set all the time,
every type, every size,
and one time I had a
scene with Sam Elliott
who I love and a cow,
and it was supposed
to be a really
sentimental scene
and really sweet.
But the entire time, the cow,
I guess had taken a liking
to the shirt tied
around my waist
and was nighing on
it the whole scene.
So, I'm trying to be all
sweet and into the scene
and I just feel this
cow tugging on me,
and then after every tape
we'd have to replace the shirt
because it had just been
chewing on the shirt
and getting it sopping wet.
- Hey Kelli, does Teddie Sue
have any cool tricks to show us?
- She's kind of a wild child
but here look, wanna
show them a trick,
can you sit?
Hey Teddie, can you
give me both paws?
Can you give me both paws?
Oh, give me both
yeah, good girl.
- That's awesome. Thanks
for coming on Kelli,
and thank you Teddie Sue.
We have some animals
going along for the ride
coming up on World's
Funniest Animals.
You know how your pet
never wants you to
leave the house,
well, this next segment
is full of clips
that show how they might
try to catch up with us
when we do.
You'll see what I mean
in along for the ride.
- Bird on a wire, no bird
on a windshield wiper.
Does this count as
distracted driving?
- Housework is so tiring.
- Don't you hate when
the plane just circles
the tarmac? Land already.
- Some pets are just
big balls of energy.
And these next clips
showcase exactly that,
here's flipping out.
- Men, this cat gets some air.
- Be quite, they will
notice we are here
telling you be quiet.
- This kitten was waiting
for the perfect
moment to strike.
- We need to see
that in slow mo.
- Oh my Gog, that
was a bad move.
- Okay, this dolphin
is totally showing
off these surfers.
- Sneak attack.
- Stay tuned, you
don't wanna miss
the hilarious pets coming up.
- We'll be right back
with more World's
Funniest Animals.
- They may be worlds apart
but these interspecies
relationships
are thriving. Here's
a world of difference.
- This dog will not give
up on hitting this bird.
Stand up for yourself.
- What are you
doing with a kitten
- I'm not sure if we
should be concerned or not
- Dog riding a horse,
what's weird about that.
- I love him and squeeze him
and pet him so gently.
- When your normal stylist
is booked you adapt.
- This monkey loves this kitten.
- Our pets may be domesticated,
but that doesn't mean
they won't always try
and run wild, planned escape.
- Those metal
squares are so small
who would guess that?
- Okay, as soon
as he steps in
I pull the string,
almost, one more step
and I'll pull it, the rope broke
I'm out of here.
- Never try to trap
a flying squirrel.
- It's mostly fur weight.
- Trust me man.
This gate is made
from stainless steel.
Nothing can penetrate this cage.
- We've one of my
favorite categories
up next on World's
Funniest Animals.
Imagine if you lived in a world
where you couldn't communicate
how you felt to
anyone around you
how would you act?
The animals in
this next segment,
give us a few good
options. Losing it.
- I got it, I got it,
I don't got it.
- Look mom, did you see it?
Okay, I'll do it again.
Are you watching?
Okay, oh, okay. I'm
starting to get dizzy.
- I've been excited to relax
but this dog is taking
it to the extreme.
- But you won't escape
my signature move.
The jump in land.
- Ride sharing is so
popular these days
even our pets are car pooling.
- Let your tongue hang loose.
- Okay, go forward.
Now right, now head
over to the sun.
Yeah, yeah that's the spot.
- We agreed, you do the dishes
and I do the floor.
- Okay, now I want a hamster.
I had no clue they
had pilot licenses.
- The hamster is
the double threat.
He's cute, he's a pilot,
it sounds like all
my girlfriends list
of their perfect guy.
- Oh guys, you know those days
you just can't seem
to get anything done
and it feels like you have
a monkey on your back.
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything
here's a quick recap
of all of our funniest moments,
a breakout bunny,
a dastardly dog,
two adorable best friends,
a good old fashioned
dog and pony show,
a hovering hamster,
calisthenic cats,
daring dolphins, and a bird
who has decided to
hitchhike their way
into their final destination,
wherever that is.
That's all for now, a
special thanks to our panel
and our celebrity
guest Kelli Goss
for joining us on
World's Funniest Animals.
- Thanks so much for having us,
bye guys, say bye Teddie.
- I'm your host
Elizabeth Stanton,
and I'll see you back here
as soon as I can come up
with some more
hilarious animal clips.
Thanks for watching
World's Funniest Animals.