Prepare
to be amazed.
Or at least amused.
Because today on the show,
we found a sandwich stealing
seagull, a deer who
dines and dashes,
and a cat who thinks,
he's computer savvy.
Give it back to me.
- All, right here,
on this episode,
of World's Funniest Animals.
- I'm your host Elizabeth
Stanton, and I'm here with,
my two best friends,
Ruby and Hank,
and welcome to World's
Funniest Animals.
I'm joined today, with a
few friends, and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest, Jennifer Taylor.
- Hey Liz.
- Thanks for being
here, Jennifer.
Did you know the phrase,
"flipping out", began because,
when people, would get
really excited or upset,
their wigs would flip right off?
Well, the animals in
this segment
aren't wearing hairpieces,
but if they were, they'd be
flying all over the place,
flipping out.
Brought to you with commentary,
from our first panelist,
actor, Carmen Hodgson.
- I can't wait to see
what we've got today.
- This next clip features,
a very hyperactive animal.
- That's my favorite.
This cat, has great cardio.
- Our next panelist, is the
amazing comedian, Brian Cooper.
- Let's see it.
- When I get real excited,
for food, I dance too.
- Now we are joined by,
actor, writer,
producer, Noah Matthews.
- Happy to be here, Liz,
You know, when you
think you're alone,
and you're not, that's as bad.
He's going at it.
- For our final panelist,
we have singer, after-comedian
radio host, Mikalah Gordon.
- Liz!
- Are you ready, for
a wild animal clip?
- So excited!
- This deer, really
did not enjoy its meal.
- We all need a
little RNR sometimes,
but these animals, can't seem
to get enough of playing,
no matter what!
check out, what I'm talking
about, in our next segment.
Play With Me.
- This poor puppy, this
cat is obviously skilled,
in grappling. It's not fair.
- I don't know why
this kid is so excited,
his shot just got blocked.
- We need to see
that in slow-mo.
- They seemed so proud,
once they finally find her.
- How many times, does this
happen with your sibling?
They never want to play.
- Over here, now
here, and then there,
You missed a spot.
- I'm always
excited, to introduce
this next segment of our show,
where we go into a home,
of a celebrity guest,
and their pet, for a chat.
Today on World's Funniest
Animals, you may know,
our celebrity guest, from
shows like, Two and a Half Men,
Shameless, and The
Young and the Restless.
It's Jennifer Taylor.
Thanks for being here
with us today, Jennifer.
I see, you have your
dog, here with you.
At least, I think I do.
- Okay. So, this
is Buddy. Buddy!
Come on up. He's
a little shy, too,
come on, come up, and say
hi to Liz.Say hi, Liz?
Buddy?
Oh, he's being shy, shy boy.
- It's okay, Buddy.
It's mom's, job to be
in front of the camera,
you keep doing,
what you're best at.
- Buddy, does do some tricks.
He has the trick of trying to
disappear.
Were are you going? No,
Buddy, Come here, come
on, give me some sugar.
Who's my good boy!
- Coming up, we have
some very stubborn pets,
in our segment,
I Don't Think So.
Next on World's
Funniest Animals.
When we think of animals,
usually we think about them,
living in packs or herds.
But sometimes, they just
want to be left alone.
A feeling, we can all relate
to. Well, I can anyways,
check out our segment,
I don't think So.
- What a nice day,
to be at the beach,
with a nice view, what a nice
sandwich, and, there it goes!
- I told you, this is my space,
and you need to find another
place for your stuff.
- Alright guys, single
file line, Come on.
Let's go. Single file.
Jamal. Get back in line.
Move it, or lose it, ladies.
You got a lagger back
here. Let's go. Come on.
If you don't get your tail in
line, what's wrong with you?
Holding everybody up.
Let's go, come on,
Stop pushing the mail out.
- And this mailman is having
a blast, with his job,
- There are certain
phrases, like walk or treat,
that can cause our
pet, to totally freak.
These clips, show those exact
moments, where animals are,
losing it.
- Don't be sheepish.
Come on down the road,
you can trust me.
- This is so cute,
but I think it's fake.
- My question is what
happened to the first dog?
- Somebody needs to help me,
there was this bird
on my driveway.
There was a bird in my driveway,
so I thought it was dying,
so I picked it up,
- Why would you bring a
bird, into your bathroom?
This doesn't feel
totally thought out.
- I was going to the
bathroom, then it flew
and I can't get a hold of it.
- Thanks for being
with us Jennifer,
we know, you have a
ton of experience,
working with animals on
set. What's that like?
- Yes, Liz, I have worked
with animals on sets.
I've worked with, dogs and cats
and horses, and even a pig.
I worked on this one movie,
where we had this little,
baby pig.And he was so cute.
Now, pigs, they actually
mature rather quickly.
So during the time
of this movie,
the pig started going
through adolescence.
And when they go
through
adolescence, they
get this smell,
so, that cute little piggy,
left the smell, everywhere.
- So, I'm not so surprised
by that pig story.
- My character on Two and a
Half Men, actually had a cat.
You know very well,
that's Sir Lancelot's
litter box.
I'm highly allergic to cats.
Of course I didn't tell them
that, cause I didn't think,
it was pertinent information.
My allergies just went
like, off the charts.
I ended up having to
borrow, somebody's inhaler.
- Thanks for sharing
with us, Jennifer.
So, glad you were
able to join us.
- All my pleasure, thanks Liz.
- Coming up, these days,
everyone is fairly tech savvy.
Even our pets, Pet Tech,
Next on World's
Funniest Animals.
Look, we love our pets,
and we love our tech.
But most of the time,
these two things don't mix well.
At all. You'll see, what I
mean, in this next segment,
Pet Tech.
- Even birds, Know we need
to reduce our screen time.
- I don't even have a tablet,
and they're giving
one to their dog,
Must be nice.
- Okay, hold still,
I just wanna to talk.
- Let it go. Drop it, drop it.
Good boy, I'm going to
put it back. Don't do it.
Hey, give it back to me.
It's mine.
- Sometimes, you just
want to be left alone.
Everyone needs to recharge,
every once in a while,
and our pets, are no exception.
Take a look at these grumpy,
animals in our segment,
Don't Mess With Me.
- I would smack her too if
she kept blowing in my face,
Oh my gosh!
- What's up behind that fence?
Just wait till I jump over.
- Thirsty?
- No good deed, goes unpunished.
- Okay, these two are
the worst singers,
in the entire animal kingdom
- Coming up, It's
not just us humans,
that are attention
hogs, pet can be too.
Play With Me, next on
World's Funniest Animals.
- If you have a pet,
you know how sometimes,
they just can't stop
begging for attention.
These next clips, feature
animals asking for attention,
in some unconventional
ways. Hogging The Limelight.
- I need him for
a workout partner,
- Honestly, dogs can
motivate you to do anything.
Trust me. I wouldn't
even leave my house,
If it wasn't for my dogs.
Apparently, they have
to walk, outside,
This dog keeps throwing,
its toy over the
fence, look at this,
I'll pick it up, and throw
it over, get to leave. Right?
In your home,
no. Drops it again.
- This dog knows how
to get what it wants.
I
Can't just leave, the toy.
He's got me trapped I'm
gonna be here forever.
Stop it.
- Look at that little sea
otter, I love sea otters.Hi?
I never, ever,
- Is it illegal to
have them as a pet?
Can I have one?
- I just think he needs to
hold hands, and calm down.
- Okay, this dog's
whole demeanor changes,
so, much after he gets
attention. I'm the same way.
- He not only hit the camera,
but he missed the treat.
- These days, everyone is fairly
tech savvy. Even our pets.
Wild Electronics.
- What, what do you
want? I am working.
- Okay, if this was my dog, I
could never get any work done.
- Something fishy
is going on here.
- I'm tired of you working
like, a dog all day,
- Well, that's
almost, it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything,
here is a quick recap of
all the funniest moments,
a slippery Schnauzer,
some choir cats
a stealing seagull.
A dog who has outsmarted
the neighborhood,
a FIFA inspired feline,
hyperactive horses,
and a puppy who shrinks
right before our eyes.
Well that's all the
time, we have for you,
on World's Funniest Animals.
Thanks to our panel,
for guiding us through
these crazy, clips,
and a special thanks
to our celebrity guest,
Jennifer Taylor.
For dropping in, and
bringing her pet pal, along.
- Oh, Liz, It was my pleasure.
Now, I think it's time
to take a nap with Buddy.
- I'm your host
Elizabeth Stanton.
I should probably, go hide
all my chargers from my dogs.
I mean, they're
usually pretty good,
but some of those videos
made me pretty nervous.
Well, see you next time, on
World's Funniest Animals.
There we go, good baby.