- Are you ready to
leap into action?
Because today on the show,
we've got a monkey,
who just wants to be left alone,
a virtual driving dog,
a very casual cat,
and a cup full of cute.
All this and more,
on this episode of
world's funniest animals.
- I'm your host
Elizabeth Stanton,
and we've got some
special treats,
in store for you tonight,
on world's funniest animals.
Tonight I'm joined by my trusty
side kicks Hank and Ruby,
and a few friends and panelists,
as well as our celebrity
guest Griffin Gluck.
- Hey everyone, I'm
really happy to be here,
and let's get to it.
- Thanks for being here Griffin,
if you love watching
hilarious glimpse of animals,
well you've come
to the right place.
Stay tuned and I'm sure,
you'll be laughing at
this fantastic episode.
Which also has the
cutest creatures ever.
Brought to you with commentary
from our first panelists,
Actor Carmen Hodgson.
- What's up Liz.
- Are you ready for one,
and the most adorable
clips I've ever seen?
- I can't wait to see this.
- That's what best
friends are for.
- Now we are joined by,
actor, writer,
producer, Noah Matthews.
- Hey Liz.
- This next one features,
just about the cutest
little guy ever.
- All right I have to see this.
- Yeah I'll have a glass of the
incredibly cute kitten please.
- Now we are joined by,
singer, actor, comedian,
radio host, Mikalah Gordon.
- What's going on Liz?
- We have one of my
favorite clips right here.
- Sounds like a blast,
I'd love to join in.
- I mean that's one
way to get belly rubs.
- For our final panelist,
We have top-notch
comedian Brian Cooper.
- Hey Liz,
- Are you ready for your
new favorite furry friend?
- Oh this sounds
like a good one.
- Cuteness overload.
- Some animals
are best observed,
in their own habitats.
Where they can stretch out,
and just live their lives.
Take a look at these clips,
showcasing animals in
their natural habitats.
Well, most of them
anyway, it's a wild life.
- You're not getting my good
angle.
- Let me see that thing.
- Oh no don't mind my tiger,
he's just thirsty.
He's fine with tap.
- Actually this is an
inter-species bathroom.
- That's honestly
exactly how my parents,
would react when my brother,
and I would be throwing
each other around the house.
- Kids, enough now
your parents are trying to tan.
- I'm so excited for
this part of the show,
where we get to visit
celebrity's homes,
and meet their pets.
You might recognize
tonight's guests,
from shows like Lock and Key,
an American Vandal,
Griffin Gluck.
Just who all do we have here?
- So this butt belongs to Petie.
We've got Poe down
here to my left.
We've got Bear sitting
over there in the corner.
This one's Mochi,
and that's Max over there,
and then can't forget
Lulu right here,
and Bubba right here.
These two are their babies too.
That's their mom and dad.
- That's quite a few pets,
You obviously have a ton,
of experience with
animals at home,
but my question is,
have you ever worked
with animals on set?
- Yeah, one of my first jobs,
"Just Go With It",
I've got to swim with a dolphin,
and one of the
world's only wolfins,
which is killer whale
mixed with a dolphin,
and that was I mean the
coolest, that was the best.
- Swimming with dolphins is
definitely a bucket list item.
- Also on "Why Him,"
there were a bunch
of farm animals,
and so during breaks,
I would go and hang out,
with like two pigs,
peacock, a sheep.
I was hanging out
with those guys,
like every second of the day.
- Thanks so much for coming by,
and sharing your
pets with us Griffin.
- Up next take a deep dive,
with this to discover
some fishy situations.
Don't go away,
more World's funniest
animals coming right up.
- There's something about
the calmness of the ocean,
that really makes
you feel at peace.
It's also just really cool.
Take a look at the
fishy situations,
We've compiled in
this next segment.
Fishy situations.
- Hey, you got any snacks,
in that thank of yours
care to share.
- Whale slap.
- I hope you have
insurance, life insurance.
- I consider myself
pretty tech savvy,
but you know,
I'm also human.
Check out the ways,
some of these amazing
pets use technology,
in our next segment, Pet Tech.
- Oh what,
did the cat just come
out the TV screen.
- Did you see what
Karen posted last week?
I can't believe her.
- I think the dog thinks,
that it's voice activated.
- What is wrong with you?
- I wanna go fast,
I wanna go fast
- We take a trip
to the wild side,
coming up next on,
world's funniest animals.
- We're back with one
of my favorite segments,
I can't wait to show
you what antics,
these wild ones have been up to.
Let's take a walk
on the wild side.
- Do you think they
know each other?
- Here comes a bear hug.
- This wildbeest has been
hanging out with the Honey
badger, he just does not care.
- To be fair,
they kind of deserve that
for spraying him, okay
- Well he was thirsty.
- This one is a
little bit funny,
a little bit terrifying,
and a whole lot of amazing.
- Okay this cheetah
is really debating,
whether or not this
woman is a snack.
- These next animals,
well, there are no words.
These creatures are
just plain cute.
- Okay, I have so
many questions,
where can I get one?
What is he all dressed up for?
How does something
look this cute,
and is missing
most of its shirt?
Like what is going on?
- Is the bow tie what
makes him a French
bulldog?
- Bear cubs are so cute.
- Oh my goodness,
you can't even tell these are
bears they look like puppies.
- Witnessing his first
climb, it melts my heart.
- So much focus, look him go,
- Now if kittens stay this
cute I would have 80 of them,
- Somebody wants sushi?
- We have some animals,
going along for the ride,
coming up on world's
funniest animals.
- Ride sharing is so
popular these days,
even our pets are carpooling
along for the ride.
- This is how I now go to
the kitchen for snacks.
- These duo is the
definition of cool.
- Yeah, cats know
how to ride in style,
but dogs know how
to ride for fun.
- He's like trying not to get
on video, he's really trying.
Oh My God!
- And don't forget our monkey
friends.
- Prepare yourself for the
ultimate military machine,
and it's adorable driver.
- Now that's one
cute commando kitty.
- Turning radius on
this thing is carp
That's a type of fish!
- Little did they know you
head down the highway that
night, and never looked back.
- Brace yourselves for visiting
our friends from the ocean.
It's time to go under the sea.
- No one else is worried about,
the giant fish
circling around them.
They are heavily outnumbered.
- Surfers and dolphins,
what could possibly go wrong?
- Great idea let's go
diving with sharks,
they said it'll
be cool they said.
- Yeah, I'll just
watch those from here.
- Come on dad,
Can I join them?
- All that little
dog wants to do,
is check swimming with dolphins,
off his bucket list.
Let him live.
- Well, that's almost it for us,
but just in case
you missed anything.
Here's a quick recap of all
of our funniest moments.
Mirthful monkeys, drifting dogs,
thirsty tigers, crying pug,
a careless cat, a baby
and a dog on a road trip,
and a fish tank
that drives itself.
Well, I guess there's
a market for that.
- Well that's all
the time we have,
on world's funniest animals,
a special thanks to our panel,
and to our celebrity
guests, Griffin Gluck,
for joining us.
- Of course, thank you
for having me, Liz.
- I'm your host
Elizabeth Stanton,
and I'll be back with
more hilarious videos,
on world's funniest animals.
See you then