Take them straight to the wagonette.
The inventory, Mr Carson.
Oh. Thank you.
Mrs Hughes. Oh. Thank you, Mr Barrow.
How can we get it up to London?
Don't worry. We'll have plenty of time to make repairs.
I must say, you're a real artist.
Well, it's as much Daisy's work as mine.
Now, how much should we take and what can we buy when we get there?
I'm happy to tell you that most things you can buy in Ripon
are also available in London.
But you don't trust them quite the same.
Well, YOU don't.
Why is she coming to London? Haven't they replaced Mrs Bute?
Oh no, no, they're not going to.
There'll be no permanent housekeeper at Grantham House in future.
Another clang in the march of time.
- Ta dah!
- Oh, that's lovely.
- You don't think it's a bit mumsy?
- No!
It's very chic. Can we see it with the hat?
Are you looking forward to London? I am.
Mr Bates and I need to inspect our house,
so the timing couldn't be better.
I'm sorry Susan's missing all this. She doesn't care about clothes.
I still don't understand why they didn't come two months ago.
The Government changed the date for the hand-over. They were stuck.
I'd have come back if it were my daughter's wedding.
I do not suggest a career in the Diplomatic.
- Will they be there before us?
- No.
They're spending the night in Southampton.
We'll all arrive in St James's on the same day.
Are we to pretend they're a happy couple?
Yes, we jolly well are. Why cast a shadow?
I quite agree. I'm sorry it can't be here.
I don't think a registry office wedding and a church blessing
would be what the county expects,
and London makes more sense for Susan and Shrimpie.
And I want a blessing in a synagogue.
Would you find a synagogue in Ripon?
I do admire the way you just take it all in your stride.
It would make it easier for Lord Sinderby.
Oh, I'm not sure Lord Sinderby deserves your concern.
Atticus loves him and I love Atticus.
Love may not conquer all, but it can conquer quite a lot.
I worried about her ladyship having to face the traitor,
but Miss O'Brien's got herself taken on by the new Governor's wife.
Typical, but I've been told they've neither maid nor valet,
which seems odd for a Marquess and Marchioness.
I don't think they have two pennies to rub together. It's all gone.
So, the Sinderby millions must be a cheering thought.
I wonder. Lady Flintshire's not the
most liberal being on the planet.
No. Then again...
Madge says Lord Sinderby's none too keen. So I gather.
Hurrah for intolerance on both sides.
I'm worried about running it with only Messrs Barrow and Molesley.
You think we'll look a bit dingy? Don't you?
Could we borrow a spare footman? I don't know.
Borrowing footmen sounds like something out of the last century.
Even to me!
Hire a lad for the week. It wouldn't cost much.
That's to be it for the Big Parade?
The Big Parade's passed, Mr Carson.
We're just trying to keep up as best we can.
My turn.
What would my father say?
That you were building a very solid
friendship with your granddaughter.
No, darling. You've landed on a snake
so you have to go back to there.
No!
Don't be so mean. Let her stay where she is.
It won't be very helpful later on if we don't teach her how to lose.
Go ahead and cry, darling.
Make Donk feel guilty. Don't call me Donk!
Oh hurry up, Donk! It's your turn.
What's that? It's from my cousin in Boston.
He sells cars but he wants to expand into farm machinery.
Well, you know about both.
Exactly. He'd like me to come in with him.
Oh, is he opening a branch over here?
No. He's asked me to join him in Massachusetts.
As a partner. Oh, I see.
How's Lord Sinderby? I think he dreams of my changing my mind.
You'd think with a father like that
Atticus would have a more Jewish name.
His real name is Ephraim Atticus,
but his mother called him Atticus as a baby and it stuck.
She's your ally.
Yes, but not because she thinks it's all unimportant,
just that she thinks her son's happiness is more important.
Thank you!
I like the sound of that.
Mr and Mrs Bates. Might I take up a moment of your time?
I had a call earlier from Sergeant Willis.
Mr Vyner is back up here and wants to come by in the morning.
To see me. To see both of you.
I don't understand. Why?
I dare say it will become clearer after he's been.
We hoped this was over.
So did I, Mr Bates. So did I.
I'm going up.
Good night.
I'll check on the children so you don't have to.
She's keen. I'll give her that.
Why does she have to carry on as if she'd invented motherhood?
I'm going to bed, too.
Before you do, have you thought about the work in the village?
Those cottages are in quite a state and we ought to get on with it.
I know, I know, but how are we going to find the money?
Let's think about it while we're in London and make a decision.
Is it true that London Inspector is coming back tomorrow?
How do you know that?
Just remember I'd be happy to swear I saw that ticket in one piece.
Her ladyship's on her way to bed. Right. Thank you.
I hope Miss Baxter's not all we've got between us and trouble.
I want to use London this time because I always resolve
to visit theatres and galleries and museums.
Then I get home and I've not done anything.
I'll join you.
We'll go together. I'll hold you to that.
Ah. The date of the unveiling. Of the memorial? When is it?
On the 25th, so we'll just be back from the wedding.
Everyone, we will be unveiling the war memorial in the village
at twelve noon on the 25th.
I'd like the house to be well represented.
I hope you won't object if I don't come, Mr Carson.
Oh? You'd be missed.
I don't want to drag it up again, but it would be painful.
Mr Carson understands.
Yes, that's as may be.
Poor woman.
You heard her. Let's not drag it up again.
Have you quite finished, m'lady? Yes, thank you, Denker.
Who was that at the door?
A gentleman called Prince Kuragin, m'lady.
He's in the drawing room.
I told him you weren't downstairs but he said he'd wait.
He was most insistent. Yes I...
I don't think I'll wear what I chose last night.
I suspected that might be the case
so I put out the lavender day dress.
Goes very well with your ladyship's colouring.
The Prince is an old friend, Denker, nothing more.
Oh, I'm sure, m'lady, but it never hurts to look your best, does it?
No. I don't believe it does.
We'll need representatives of the regiments involved and a band,
but I dare say that's all under control.
I dare say it is, m'lord.
Oh, I'd like William Mason's father to have a good place.
William left this house to give his life for his country.
I feel that very deeply. We all do, m'lord.
Will you tell the staff? Already done.
We should have a good turnout.
Mrs Patmore has asked to be excused but that's understandable.
I'm sorry, but not surprised.
M'lord.
I don't know what you mean by "our last chance".
We left any chance we had behind us, many years ago.
I don't accept that. And what about the Princess?
They haven't found her yet.
We've been apart for a long time.
Are you proposing to divorce?
Why? Do you want more children?
I wish to spend my final years with you.
As a friend, as a lover.
I don't seek scandal, only love.
The last years have been ugly.
I don't want what remains to be ugly.
No.
So...
...what do you say?
You want an answer just like that?
I know my own feelings. You do too.
I can't make a decision now!
I won't change.
Don't proclaim your intransigence as if it were a virtue.
Things have advanced a little.
It seems Mr Green was not quite the
sunny soul that Mr Carson depicted.
He appears to have carried out a series of attacks on women.
They were too nervous to come forward before now,
but with a little encouragement some of them have spoken out.
We've formed a picture of his behaviour.
But nothing happened here!
His victims were generally small, slight women,
who'd given little or no encouragement.
How very unpleasant. It is rather 'unpleasant'.
Wouldn't you agree, Mrs Bates? Yes.
We also have news which may put Mr Bates in the clear.
A second witness has come forward.
His evidence suggests whoever was arguing with Green on the pavement
was shorter than him.
Shorter than yourself, Mr Bates.
What do you think, Mrs Hughes? I don't know a thing about it.
We'll leave it there.
If we need Mrs Bates to come to London, could that be arranged?
We'll be in London next week for Lady Rose's wedding.
Could you pop in to Scotland Yard on Tuesday at ten o'clock?
If she comes, I'll be with her. As you wish. Now I'll say goodbye.
What on earth was that about?
He's trying to bully it out,
but it's best not to stand in his way.
Bully what out?
You're required upstairs, Mr Carson.
Mr Evans. It's good of you to come. I'm pleased to, m'lord.
Your father carved many stones for our dogs over the years.
I'm glad you're prepared to go on with it.
These are like the ones we've made for you in the past.
Is this a book of pets' tombstones? A parallel universe.
No, m'lord. You've examples of everything we do.
Oh, I see. What's this?
A memorial, m'lord.
We made it for a garden in Hinckley.
Near Leicester? You do get about.
There you are! You took your time.
I thought you'd rung by accident.
How would you like to be summoned, by Joshua's trumpet?
I prefer not to be "summoned" at all.
At any rate, not by you.
Take these down to the car.
I'm going to fetch her galoshes and umbrella.
I've been thinking.
Should I tell them everything when
we get there and have done with it?
No. I'm not one to give up my secrets unless I have to.
They have nothing if the man who killed him can't have been you.
Even so.
Daisy?
Yes, Mr Carson.
Before we go, his lordship wants to extend an invitation to Mr Mason
for the unveiling, which will include you as William's widow.
Thank you, Mr Carson. I'll write to him as Chairman.
It might be nice if you were to mention it in your next letter.
Of course. Right.
Well, we'd better get up to the cars.
I hope you can manage a few days without Denker, Spratt.
A hope that will be fulfilled and gladly, m'lady.
Are these all the cases, Denker?
Your ladyship is very sharp-eyed.
We are missing one.
Since Mr Spratt was given the task of bringing them down,
no doubt he's put it somewhere for safe keeping.
Oh, how very considerate of you, Spratt.
Fetch it now, please. But your ladyship, I don't...
Fetch the case, Spratt.
I feel so guilty, leaving Marigold on her own.
Oh, she's surrounded by nannies and children!
I know. She'll have a whale of a time.
Edith is obsessed with that child.
She's a dear little thing. So she is.
But as a matter of fact, there is something about her.
About Marigold? What? I don't know. A sense of deja vu.
I can't quite put my finger on it.
All of you, Andy will be an extra footman while we're in London.
Please be helpful to him.
Starting at dinner tonight? That's the idea.
How did Mr Carson find you? I was working as a hall boy.
Mr Carson rang my old butler.
It's only a week's work. Will he take you back?
I don't want to go back as a hall boy.
I want to be a footman now and this is the first step.
I think that's brave. You've got to be brave these days.
Do you know London well? Not here. I grew up in the East End.
I've only ever worked in Bayswater. Bayswater?
North of the park. Oh yes, I know where it is.
So you're not known round here then? No.
You're just with us 'til after the wedding?
That's it. I dare say you enjoy a bit of fun.
I s'pose so. As much as the next man.
There's fun to be had round here if you know where to look for it.
You know this area, then? Oh, yes. I've come home.
I spent many a year in St James's Square.
Before we get drawn into Miss Denker's past adventures,
why don't you come with me and I'll show you how it all works?
Chop, chop.
Welcome the hunter, home from the hill.
How are you both? Worn out!
The train from Southampton
was almost as bad as the voyage from Bombay.
You must lie down before you change.
Do you remember Carson?
I gather you haven't brought any personal attendants, m'lord.
Those days are done for us. We needn't tell the world.
You will have Lady Mary's maid Anna, to help you, m'lady.
His lordship will have Mr Molesley. Now I'll show you to your room.
We're not in one room? Together?
The thing is, we're very squashed. I'm not sharing a room.
I'll go to an hotel. Come on...
Don't worry m'lady, we'll manage. If you'd like to come this way.
Maybe Lady Rose could share with Lady Edith?
Thank you, Mrs Hughes.
I knew she'd be trouble.
Mummy.
They said you'd arrived. Yes. What a journey.
I seem to have been travelling for as long as I can remember.
Well, you're here now.
Won't you give your poor old mother a kiss?
Of course.
This is quite a choice you've made. I hope you'll like him.
They're all coming for dinner tonight.
And you're quite, quite sure?
Absolutely.
Well then, that's all I needed to hear.
Has Mr Carson announced dinner? They're not all here yet.
I found a letter from Mr Vyner when we arrived,
confirming I'm to be at Scotland Yard in the morning.
Try not to worry about it.
Why not go to see your house afterwards? You'd enjoy that.
Now, in London, we supervise,
but they help themselves to coffee and drinks from a side table.
Once they settle, we leave them to it.
In my last place, the footmen stayed 'til they went to bed.
If they want a second drink, it's up to them.
There we are.
I hope Anna was helpful.
She will be, I'm sure.
Where are the Sinderbys?
Oh?! We thought you might be Lord and Lady Sinderby.
'Fraid not.
Hello.
What are they like? She's very nice and fond of Rose.
He's less convinced. Rose is more than a match for him.
It does make me smile that they should be the ones objecting.
They have as much right as we do. Mummy, Daddy...
Can you try to behave like a happy couple?
Wouldn't that be rather dishonest? You haven't separated yet.
We separated the moment we walked down the gangway at Southampton.
It won't kill us to put on a show for a few more days.
The thing is, I don't want to give Lord Sinderby any ammunition.
So, Lady Rose MacClare is a mesalliance.
I'm not sure that's helpful, Granny.
Lord and Lady Sinderby and Mr Atticus Aldridge.
Do come in. How lovely to see you.
Daddy, Mummy. This is Atticus.
How do you do? What a peculiar name.
How's it going?
Lady Flintshire is not a push-over. I told you that.
I must ask, because I can't get it out of my mind,
why has the Inspector summoned Mrs Bates?
Would it help if I swore neither of them has done anything wrong?
I never doubted it, but it's a relief to hear.
I'd better go up.
What made you choose Yorkshire? Was it a historic reason?
Not really. I used to go there as a
girl and of course it's beautiful.
Do you have any English blood?
We only date from the 1850s,
but Lady Sinderby's family arrived in the reign of King Richard Ill.
Really? I think of you as nomads, drifting around the world.
Talking of drifting round, is it true you're starting your honeymoon
at the Melfords' in Coningsby?
Oh yes. Lady Melford is Mother's cousin.
Is she? I never knew that.
You wanted a synagogue blessing? I'd like to respect both sides.
You don't understand our customs. Then again, why should you?
So it won't be possible? No. He should have told you.
I thought we could have a dinner on Wednesday night
so you could meet some of the relations.
And show them how lucky they are!
Have you got many staying? We're crammed to the gunwales.
Atticus has had to move into the Halnaby Hotel.
I love the Halnaby.
It makes sense and he can have his... What do they call it now?
His stag party there, without disturbing us.
- Will you be going, Lord Sinderby?
- Hardly.
Stag parties are high on Father's disapproval list.
Is it a long list, Lord Sinderby, the things you disapprove of?
No, as long as I can steer clear of
card sharps and undercooked fish,
and divorce, I think I'm fairly easy.
Is divorce so terrible? Is it worse
to stay together and be miserable?
I am clearly old-fashioned but to me divorce signifies weakness.
Degradation, scandal and failure.
Are you glad to be in London again?
I will be when I get the house back.
When do the tenants go? Next week in theory.
I need to pull the real pictures out of storage. What a palaver!
I know, but think of the relief
when I can shut the door at last and be alone in my own home.
Won't Lord Flintshire be with you? Of course he will.
Of course I will. What a funny thing to say, Susan.
Funny is one word for it.
Well, I want you to know that you'll
always be welcome at Canningford.
How kind.
Tell me, do you find it difficult these days to get staff?
Not very.
But then we're Jewish, so we pay well.
If I don't get an early night, I'll never make it through the week.
Is Dicky Merton coming to the wedding?
I don't think so.
Oh, oh I'm sorry.
You've changed your tune.
I've been reminded recently that one
is not given many chances in life
and if you miss them,
they may not necessarily be repeated.
Sinderby's as stiff as a board. What more can I do?
May I ask, do you two worry about
Sybbie and George when you're away?
Why should we?
No reason, but I think about Marigold all the time.
What are you going to be like when you have your own?
I intend to leave it all to Nanny. You say that.
I'm used to the way the children live at Downton, but it seems odd.
Will it be different in America? He isn't going and that's flat.
Mary... Stop!
This is my wedding and I'm not having it spoiled.
Quite right. I tell you what.
Why don't the four of us go for lunch on Wednesday? Even you, Edith.
To mark Rose's last days of freedom and the end of an era.
Let's go to Rules. My treat.
Yes. Why not?
Sinderby's going to be quite a challenge for Rose.
No doubt about that.
And what possessed Susan? "Do you have any English blood?"
Really! She speaks without thinking.
Did you know Bates and Anna are going
to Scotland Yard tomorrow morning?
Certainly not! Why? Bates didn't really give a reason.
Do they want character testimonials? I offered,
but he said no. Not yet.
The stone mason has sent his bill. Is Mrs Patmore downstairs?
I believe so, m'lord.
And is Bates back? Not yet, m'lord.
A strange business, Carson.
Can I help? I'm trying to find the letter box.
It's through there, but the post may have gone.
Is it crucial? A bit crucial.
I hate saying, "the cheque's in the post" when it isn't.
I'll walk up to Jermyn Street.
Here's Carson. Is Lady Flintshire too late to give you a letter?
No, m'lord. I'm collecting them now.
Thank you, Carson.
Miss Baxter and Mr Molesley have asked me
to see the Wallace Collection with them tomorrow.
Daisy, the wedding is on Friday! That's what I said.
But, it's only Tuesday now and we've done most of it
apart from the stuff we can't do before the day.
I don't know. Is this a kitchen or a holiday resort?
Oh, go but...
If you're not back by teatime, I'll call the police.
Oh, my God!
I do apologise for interrupting your work, Mrs Patmore.
That's quite all right, m'lord. I'm afraid I'm a bit of a mess.
Not at all, please.
I just wanted to ask you if you might reconsider
coming to the unveiling of the memorial.
I don't mean to be rude, m'lord... I know that.
But, it's important reconciliation is the spirit of the day.
I should feel I had failed if you
were to be absent from the ceremony.
Please. I ask it as a favour.
Very well. If it means that much to your lordship.
It does. Thank you.
If you'll come this way, Mrs Bates. I'm staying with her.
Suit yourself. Through here please.
Take your place in the line.
But why? What have I done? This is madness.
Come along.
Hold the cards in front of you.
Thank you very much. You may go.
What is this about?
She had nothing to do with it. You know that!
Calm yourself. You must be aware that
most of this stuff is just routine?
So we can cross people off our lists.
Let's go. We have some business to attend to, while we're here.
You'll want to get on with it, then.
Have you got the hang of it now?
I think so. Dinner's done and dusted without incident.
I'll take you for a walk later, show you the sights.
What about Lady Grantham? She'll be in bed before then.
Would you mind taking the coffee up while it's still hot?
Or is that too much to ask?
I hope you're not planning to lead him into bad ways, Miss Denker.
No. Andy isn't a country lad, is he?
I expect he knows his way around better than I do.
I doubt that.
She's got a plan in mind, that one,
a plan to her own advantage and I'd like to know...
Daisy? Are you listening? London's full of possibilities.
Life's full of possibilities.
Really? Sometimes I think my life has no possibilities at all.
Where's Aunt Violet?
MY Aunt Violet has gone up. So has Mrs Crawley.
And Atticus? Where is the lovelorn swain tonight?
Don't you remember? He's got his bachelor party.
Do you like him, Daddy? Please say you do.
Certainly I do. Very much.
Did you get to Bond Street?
The chap I need to see was busy. I'm going tomorrow afternoon.
Please don't make us late for Lady Sinderby's dinner.
What are you doing in Bond Street?
It's an idea I've had, that's all.
An idea he is clearly not going to share with us.
That's it. I'm going to bed.
You said we'd have one more drink and I've had one more.
So now I'm off to bed.
You can stay as long as you want. Put it on my bill.
Champagne!
No, not tonight.
I'm sorry if I misled you, but it's not going to happen.
- Who is it?
- Your tea, sir.
But I didn't order any tea.
What on earth?
Is this a joke? Did Mr Ryecart pay you to come up?
Just wait, one moment...
Bye.
Andy? How was last night?
Did you go for your walk with Miss Denker?
Yes, I bloody well did, the more fool me.
Is everything all right, Mr Barrow? Just fine,
Mrs Hughes, thank you.
Michael and I had luncheon here on our very first date.
One day you'll be glad to think of the times you spent together.
You're the only member of the family that seems to understand.
Sorry we're late.
How did you get on? So well!
If I show you, the women here will be too jealous to eat.
Oh. Er, this came for you by messenger.
Carson asked me give it to you. Thank you.
Who's it from?
It's not signed. There's just a note that says "Last night".
What is it? Atticus.
Picking up a tart of some kind and letting her into his room.
What?!
Oh, God. Have some water.
Are you ready to order? May we have a few more moments?
What are you going to do? I'm not sure.
Maybe I'll chuck tonight, but what should I do about the wedding?
I'll tell you what you'll do.
Go and telephone Atticus now. Arrange to see him this afternoon.
Mary, go with her.
This is classic stag party stuff.
You mean they got him drunk, set him up,
and booked a photographer to maximise his embarrassment?
I'm sure he's regretting it bitterly this morning.
But is "regretting it" enough? It wouldn't be for me.
There is a man who'd rather this marriage didn't take place
and his name's Lord Sinderby.
Would he do something so grubby?
You'd be surprised what people can sink to, to get their own way.
They're talking now. He'll meet her in St James's Park at three.
This is to confirm there'll be no upstairs dinner tonight.
The family is dining with Lady Sinderby.
I can't see why we bothered to get an extra footman.
We should've just hired some help
for the wedding and left it at that.
It's unusual for a bridegroom's parents
to entertain just before a marriage.
It feels quite foreign. Maybe that sort do it differently.
Oh, don't you start! I am not prejudiced, Mrs Hughes.
There are many things you could accuse me of, but not that.
How about lack of self knowledge?
Mr Carson, could Andy have some time off tonight?
If the family don't need him?
He's only been here a couple of days
and he's asking for extra time off?
He wants me to show him a bit of the town.
And the Dowager?
I'll be back in time to put her to bed.
I want everyone here until the family leaves,
and make sure you're back by ten o'clock.
What were you going to show him that you didn't show him last night?
Why? What did he tell you?
Only that he didn't enjoy himself. Oh poor Diddums.
I hope he's made of sterner stuff than that.
I never even knew it existed. Oh, I like these smaller museums.
The Wallace Collection or the Mauritshuis near the Hague.
Have you been to Holland? No, I've just read about it.
It's as if the intimacy, being near the paintings,
makes them more powerful.
I feel the same. Do you, Daisy?
I feel as if I've been down a coal hole
and someone's opened the lid and brought me into the sunlight.
Well, that's very gratifying. Is it, though?
I feel so resentful, so discontented.
It's as if my old life were a prison I have to go back to.
Don't say that! I don't want to think I've made things worse.
Isn't that Lady Rose?
This doesn't even make any sense! Stop!
Let's leave them to it.
I don't know. You're never safe 'til the ring's on your finger.
Do you want to be safe, Miss Baxter?
I might.
You really believe I would stoop so low?
You think that of me? I am satisfied it was not a prank.
Rather a plan to induce Lady Rose to withdraw from the marriage?
Call her Rose, for heaven's sake.
And you think I am the perpetrator?
You are opposed to my marrying her,
much more so than I have confessed to Rose or her family.
Very well. Let us be honest.
I am against it.
Our family has achieved a great deal since we came to this country
and not just for ourselves, for our people.
We have a proud history
and we've taken our place among the leaders in this land.
And now, you want to throw all that away for this little shiksa.
Don't call her that! I'm sorry.
I don't mean to insult the girl. She seems decent enough.
But she is English and Anglican and so will her children be...
She's Scottish. British, then.
The second Lord Sinderby may be Jewish, but the third will not.
Soon our family will be one more British dynasty
with all the same prejudices as everyone else who shops at Harrods!
Any children will be brought up to
know both sides of their heritage.
Your children will not be Jewish! Don't you understand that?
Their mother will not be Jewish and neither will they!
They may choose to convert.
Or are you implacably opposed to giving anyone a free choice?
How easy you make it sound,
and how little you've had to fight.
You must come.
They're here.
I need your word it wasn't you.
Of course it wasn't me!
Don't you know me at all?
Atticus says it must have been a practical joke.
Do you believe him? I don't think it was a joke.
It was either true and he's lying,
or someone is trying to stop the wedding.
I'd like to know which. Preferably before Friday.
Rose, may I introduce you to my cousin, Sir John?
Come.
Edith, darling! Excuse me.
We'd better act fast before it all hits the rocks.
Everything seems to be hitting the rocks at the moment.
That's a bit sad. I mean it.
Sybil was my ally and she's gone. Now Rose.
You're about to leave and take Sybbie with you.
It's too much to bear. Mary, I must live my life.
What? And leave me alone with Edith?
When you read I'm on trial for murder, it'll be your fault.
Maybe you're right and it wasn't a joke,
but all I care about is you should believe me.
Of course I do, but it's almost worse
to know there's someone out there
who hates us enough to concoct such a lie.
Tell us more about British India. It's a wonderful country.
Bombay is a marvellous city.
I'm not sure how long British India has to go.
We heard about that terrible Amritsar business.
Amritsar was a very unfortunate incident,
ordered by a foolish man.
I can't agree. General Dyer was just doing his duty.
You haven't got that quite right. We're entitled to our own opinion.
Are we? I hesitate to remind you that
Shrimpie knows India and you don't.
You look very serious.
Granny, do you think Lord Sinderby
would try anything horrible to prevent the wedding?
He'd certainly like it stopped.
But he does love Atticus.
My dear, love is a far more dangerous motive than dislike.
Go on. It's no fun on my own.
You never talked to me from the time
we got there. Go and get changed.
Why are you bullying him, Miss Denker?
Can't you pick on someone your own age?
He'll have fun when he gets there.
Maybe, but I suspect you're a bad influence all the same.
Then I suspect we have something in common, Mr Barrow.
Cheeky.
If it was so lovely, why have you
been in a gloom since you got back?
It showed me what I've been missing.
Before I started studying I thought history, art or 'owt like that
were only for the family, not for us.
Surely it's a good thing, if your horizons have expanded?
In a way, but it's shown me how empty my life's been until now.
You've learned a trade. You're skilled.
You're an artist yourself. Look at this wedding cake.
What for? So I can skivvy in a kitchen that isn't even mine?
Wasn't it your plan to study so you could help run Mr Mason's farm?
But even if I do that in the end,
wouldn't I be better studying here,
with galleries and libraries and theatres all around me?
I could get a job in London, I know I could.
I'm sure you could. Then that's it.
I've made my mind up. I'm handing in my notice.
Oh... Oh, Daisy.
You've been very good to me, Mrs Patmore,
and I'll be sad to say goodbye, but I think it's right.
Hasn't she brushed it off as a malicious trap?
Yes, she has, but who would do it?
Granny thinks it might be Lord Sinderby.
Ought we to challenge him?
Can I give you a nightcap? Yes, please.
Not for me. I'm tired.
Ah, and you?
No, but I'll look in to say good night.
Where are Miss Denker and Andrew? Not back yet, Mr Carson.
I said I wanted everyone in by ten o'clock.
I'm sure they won't be long. Hmm!
Where have they got to? God knows. It's hard for Mr Carson.
Miss Denker's not under his jurisdiction.
Andy won't be round long enough to mind a black mark.
She's using him in some way, that lad, to her own benefit.
Which I do not like to see.
Cocoa if anyone wants it?
Thank you, Mrs Patmore.
You should have let me do that.
I shall have to manage without you. I may as well get used to it.
Don't be like that.
I'm not 'like' anything. I'm just facing facts.
What are you doing in here?
Waiting for you. I can't think why.
Did you enjoy this evening?
Not really, no. In fact, I hated it.
Having to play act in front of those people is so degrading.
It's not for much longer.
Did you know that Anne Melford was Jewish?
I neither knew nor didn't know. What difference does it make?
No need to parade your pseudo-tolerance here.
We are quite alone. I don't feel as you do about it.
Or about anything else.
I want no more of your tricks. Is that clear?
I don't know what you mean.
Yes, you do, and if you don't promise to behave,
I will tell Rose and we'll see what she makes of it.
You're talking in riddles. You set up Atticus.
The whole cheap, dirty episode began and ended with you.
Just because Rose was too clever to be taken in,
doesn't mean she'd forgive you.
Are you ill?
I was curious to know about the payment you spoke of.
I read the chequebook stub and telephoned the firm.
Get down, you cat!
Doesn't it mean anything to you?
That we have lost our money...
...that we have lost our position
that we have lost everything the children have grown up
expecting as their right.
And now you want Rose to be an outcast?
I'm not saying everything will be easy for them,
but who has a life where everything is easy?
Not us. And God knows not her.
Don't mention the divorce until after she's tied the knot.
Do you think he'd put his foot down at the eleventh hour?
I'm warning you, if this marriage does not go ahead,
Rose will know the part you played.
Since we're all here, I've decided what to do about the cottages.
I'm going to sell the Della Francesca.
I've been to Sotheby's and we'll get a good price.
Are you sure? You've always been so proud of it.
I don't enjoy it as I did.
My Papa always said one should only sell for a purpose and I agree.
The good of the village can be that purpose.
I'm pleased. Now we can get on with the work as soon as we're home.
Shall we?
I've spoiled the painting for you, haven't I, with Mr Bricker?
That's why you're selling.
Yes.
But not in the way you think.
Every time I look at it, I am reminded that I didn't trust you
and I feel so angry with myself, I want to be rid of it.
Oh, that is a horrid trick!
Whoever thought it up has a nasty mind.
What shocks me most is that anyone could want me to be so unhappy.
Excuse me.
This is what troubles me, would I be right to marry Dickie
when I know his sons would hate us to be happy?
That's all very well, but let them cheat you of your future?
I am sorry to disturb you, m'lady, but Miss Denker is not well,
so Miss Baxter will look after you tonight.
Will she be all right? It's nothing serious, m'lady.
Thank you.
At last I have a plan, start the work in the village,
find the new agent and set off for America.
But won't all that take months?
Why don't we say I'll stay for Christmas then go?
It's a dagger in my heart.
I don't know what I'll do without you.
Did you ever think you'd say that when I drove you to your fittings?
And Sybil got her to make evening pyjamas and Granny almost fainted.
We have our memories, you and I.
But now you'll take them away with you to Boston.
And I'll cherish them when I get there.
It's a long way to Tipperary. I think you need to calm down.
You need to calm down, Miss Denker. To go...
Go and get Mrs Hughes.
To Tipperary...
Oh, I must get up to my lady. No, I'm doing it.
Mr Carson's told her you're ill. Ill?
Really, Miss Denker. And in front of the maids, too!
Well, who gives a tinker's curse about the maids?
Right. That's quite enough of that.
And as for you, where have you been? You don't want to know.
Put on your livery and get to the drawing room.
Maybe if I made her coffee, it might sober her up.
Anything's worth a try.
Mrs Patmore? Whatever's the matter? Don't mind me.
Tell me! No. It wouldn't be fair.
Fair to who?
To you, you daft ha'porth. I don't understand.
I'm crying because I don't want you to leave.
I'll miss you.
Don't... don't concern yourself. I'll get over it.
I'll work out a month's notice.
I have to come back for the memorial ceremony,
and I haven't got another job yet.
Forget the coffee. She's gone up, thank the Lord.
We should go, too. You're right.
Has something happened? No. Not yet.
Ah, you've come back, then? We thought you'd run away to sea.
I'm very sorry, Mr Carson, but Miss Denker was taken ill.
Never mind "taken ill," I wish she'd been taken away.
By the men in white coats.
Go down, Mr Carson. We'll manage.
What happened?
She took me to this horrible club somewhere off Shaftesbury Avenue.
And I suppose you gambled. I lost the lot.
I paid for it on the note but it'll take all my savings.
I bet she didn't lose a thing? Hmm.
One question, she's not made a play for you?
Done anything improper?
No! God no. No, nothing like that. She just sat and drank.
They gave her whatever she wanted. I see.
At least, I think I see. Next time I'm coming with you.
Does there have to be a next time? Yes. just one more.
I'm fairly sure you're gonna enjoy it.
I dare say this is a first for you, Granny,
to sample the joys of a registry office.
You'd be quite wrong, no, in 1878
I attended the wedding of Lord Rosebery and Hannah Rothschild
held in the Board of Guardians, very much the same.
It seems almost sad in a way.
But in marrying a Rothschild, there are certain compensations.
Is Lady Flintshire all right?
Cora, would you go and help Susan? She seems in rather a queer way.
There is something that you must know
and I feel most uncomfortable not having told you before now.
We don't want any deathbed confessions, Susan.
Remember, this is not your day!
I'm sorry, Aunt Violet. I think it's time.
In fact, it's long overdue.
What is? No, please.
Shrimpie and I are in the process of getting a divorce.
What?!
I'm afraid it is going to be all
over the papers and as things stand,
it must involve you and your family.
God if I... Thank you, Lady Flintshire.
Or may I call you Susan?
We are forewarned and so now we will be forearmed.
You can't mean... Father, I beg you...
Do anything to stop this marriage,
anything at all, I will leave you,
and then you will have a scandal worthy of the name!
Oh, I doubt you expected to take your beloved child
through the portals of Caxton Hall Registry Office.
There are lots of things in my life I never anticipated,
but if you're sure, I'm sure.
By the way, Atticus was blameless.
I'm ashamed now that I wobbled.
I know he was blameless. How can you know?
Well I do, beyond a trace of doubt.
Who did my enemy turn out to be?
Never mind about that. You don't know him. Not properly.
Then I don't want to know.
I don't want to hate anyone today.
You do realise this is my real wedding?
Not the blessing this afternoon? This is where I become his wife.
And I hope you will be very, very happy, my dearest darling.
I don't believe it. Is that it?
Am I just expected to be a good loser?
It's too late for that, my dear, far too late.
Please stand.
Er, listen everyone, as soon as they've finished lunch,
they'll get ready for the blessing at half past two.
Those going to the Savoy Chapel,
there'll be a coach to bring you for the reception.
What about dinner, Mr Carson? Just family.
Her ladyship wants a buffet of what's left over.
I might add some hot soup.
I should go. I'm helping Lady Rose to change.
I don't think it's right to put on a wedding dress
when it's only a blessing.
She won't wear a veil. You're right. We should get on.
So, we should be able to get away later on if you're up for it.
After her ladyship's gone to bed. You mean you want to come?
You've been having lots of fun, Miss Denker.
Unless you feel the worse for wear? I don't know what you mean.
I had a headache, that's all.
If he's coming, you needn't bother. No! We want Andy with us.
With you for what? Nothing, Mrs Hughes.
Andy, you take your life in your hands
if you throw in your lot with these two.
Lord Sinderby, please believe that I love your son very much
and whatever I can do to make him happy, I will do.
We know that, my dear, and we wish every blessing on your head.
Well, well, the thing is done. Let us go forward in hope.
Ah, look who's coming your way.
Hello, Tony. How lovely to see you. And you of course, Mabel.
Welcome. Are we welcome? I hope so.
You're as welcome here as I trust I will be at your wedding.
Is it just me who's embarrassed? I'm not embarrassed.
We're getting married in December.
We'd be delighted to see you there.
Oh, I am so pleased. Truly. It'll be in London.
Country weddings in the winter can be such muddy affairs.
I don't suppose we'll ever know who did it now but who cares?
It wasn't my father. Oh, I never thought it was.
I mean, I know he's against me,
but that sort of thing's not his style.
You see? She already knows you better than he does.
I'm not sure it's what she really wanted,
a registry office and the Savoy chapel.
But, I think she'll be very happy. I agree. They're well matched.
When are you going home? First thing. I can't wait.
The call of young Marigold. You sound as if you don't approve.
Oh, it's not that...
Oh, look. It's Tony and Mary. They make a handsome couple.
Give it up, Papa. It's a pipe dream.
So, it turned out as you planned.
You were just what I needed when I needed it.
I hope you know that. Well, I know a lot of things.
One of them is not to mess with Lady Mary Crawley.
But everything's come right?
Hmm, it has for me. I hope it does for you, too.
Good luck, Mary.
Lord Sinderby has taken Brancaster Castle for the grouse this year.
In Northumberland?
Yes, and we wondered if you might like to join us there?
That's very kind. All of you. It would give us great pleasure.
All of us? I wonder if you know what you're taking on!
I'll telephone Lady Grantham and we'll talk dates.
I look forward to it.
That wasn't too hard, was it?
Not hard for me, since I was allowed
no say in the matter. None at all.
He seems like a wonderful boy. Thank you, that's very kind.
I heard about your declaration at the registry office.
All I want is your happiness, my darling.
Whatever I said or did was done from love.
I'm afraid we must have different definitions of the word.
Hmm.
How are you two bearing up?
Well, thank you, Lady Manville.
I do feel for you.
It must be very trying,
but I so admire you for putting on a good face.
I wonder if you remember that my father was Jewish?
Oh.
I'm afraid I...
That is... How interesting...
Ah, Louise, I wasn't expecting to find you here.
Is everything all right, m'lady? I thought I'd sneak away.
I don't think I'll be missed. Oh, I wouldn't say that.
I feel as if our household is breaking up, Carson,
but I suppose that's what happens.
People grow up and move away and things change.
I hope Lord Gillingham hasn't upset you?
Oh, no.
He's happy with Miss Lane Fox and I'm happy for them.
Because if I might be permitted to say so?
He wasn't good enough for you, m'lady, not by half.
I don't think anyone else would agree with you.
But the difference is that you agree with me.
I watched you realise it as time went on.
Reluctantly perhaps,
but you came to see that he wasn't up to the mark.
I'm not sure if that's alarming or reassuring
coming from someone who knows me so well.
Reassuring I hope, for I'm confident
that you will triumph in the end.
Thank you, Carson. That means more to me than you know.
Oh no, it was a funny marriage.
No proper service, no veil!
You'd have thought one of them was divorced.
I wish them well. I don't mind Lady Rose, me.
Is this it? Welcome to the Velvet Violin.
Thank you.
We'll go in separately.
Don't talk to me 'til we're at the tables.
Back again, Miss Denker?
I've brought two with me. The new boy and another one.
So I see. Give yourself a drink and help 'em find the tables.
Thank you.
What's his name? The one she was talking to.
Erm, Basil Shute. Why?
You'll see.
Are you going 1:0 play?
I might have a go. Pontoon's my game.
But don't you. Right?
That was quite a marathon, but I think a happy one.
Oh, yes. They're well suited.
They were bound to find out in the end about Lady Rose's parents.
At least it's out in the open. They'll have to lump it.
Now that Lord Sinderby and Lady Flintshire both have a reason
to look down on the other, that should keep them quiet.
Yes?
I beg your pardon, m'lady, but Anna's wanted downstairs.
What do you mean, Mrs Hughes? I haven't dismissed her.
I know, m'lady and I feel most uncomfortable but...
What is it? What's happened? Mr Vyner's downstairs.
What? But he hasn't...
He says he's come to arrest you.
Does that always happen? Not always, no.
Right. Cash them in and pay your bill.
I couldn't let you do that. Why not?
You want to get out of here alive? I'd have to pay you back.
We'll argue later. Off you go while I see to Mr Shute.
What do you mean? Go.
Excuse me,
can you tell me which of these knuckleheads is a Mr Basil Shute?
Why?
There's a woman who's boasting of a
trick she's played on him all week.
Oh, yeah? What's that, then?
Yeah, she erm, she waits outside until someone's coming in,
then she enters with them
and claims free drinks all night for bringing in new punters.
Oh, she does, does she?
It's the woman I arrived with.
Bye!
No! Wait!
Bye.
She chose me because she thought
I was too young and stupid to see what she was at.
And she was right, wasn't she? So, next time, ask your Uncle Thomas.
Right, let's go.
Oh, thank you.
Haven't you forgotten something?
What?
Your bill for three nights' worth of drinking, Miss Denker.
That'll be four pounds and ten shillings.
I must wait for Mr Bates. I can't go without telling him!
It might be kinder if you let him hear the news
when he can't say anything he'll regret.
I forbid you to take her! Correct forms have been observed.
What is this? What's happening? Don't make trouble, Mr Bates.
You can't do this! Try to keep calm.
Can't I stand surety for her? I'm afraid not, sir.
Mrs Hughes, will you fetch her coat? No! I can't let her go.
A witness has identified Mrs Bates
being on the pavement near Mr Green before he fell.
I insist on telephoning our lawyer! Telephone all you like, Miss.
He'll find Mrs Bates at Gerald Row Police Station.
I suggest you leave it 'til the morning.
I will ring him now because she is innocent and I am not "Miss"!
I am Lady Mary Crawley!
I don't care if you're the Queen of the Upper Nile.
I'm going and she's coming with me.
NOW!
Bates!
"They fell with their faces to the fold.
"They shall grow not old, as we that are left grow old.
"Age shall not weary them, nor the years condemn.
"At the going down of the sun and in the morning.
"We will remember them. "
We will remember them.
Stand at ease.
Stand easy.
Before you disperse, I would beg your indulgence for a moment.
Can I draw your attention to one more gallant chap
who volunteered to fight?
He wasn't local to Downton and so his
name does not appear on the memorial,
but his memory is cherished by some here,
and so it seems right to us to mark his passing.
Mrs Patmore?
Oh!
"Sacrifice" is right.
I think that's lovely, Mrs Patmore. I'm so pleased for you.
It's just as it should be.
I believe so.
I'd like to see William's name now. If you've a moment, Daisy?
My sister's going to find it a real comfort.
It'll be nice for you too, Daisy, to have the memorial so near.
I thought I'd feel sad when I read William's name, and so I did.
But I felt proud, too.
Very proud. Of course.
Daisy may not be here forever,
but that won't mean she's any the less proud of our William.
What? Are you going away, Daisy? Well no, there's nothing wrong.
She's got a taste for London,
so we'll have to learn to manage without her.
At her age, it's right she should have a new adventure, isn't it?
Is this true, Daisy? No, she's just teasing!
At least, I did think about it,
but I've decided I'm not going anywhere,
or not until after I've passed my exams.
I'm glad.
I hate it when people who love each other must be far apart.
I know what you're thinking.
It is not hard to guess, m'lady.
She won't be convicted. I don't even think she'll be tried.
They have nothing to go on. Nothing they're sharing with us.
But you're right, m'lady, she will not be convicted.
Now we're back, do you really think
I should put up a fight for Dickie?
You said you wouldn't do anything 'til after Rose's wedding.
But, it's over, so it's time for action.
Fighting talk, indeed.
And will you put up a fight for Prince Kuragin?
Well, you forget, you hold the winning card.
Lord Merton's wife is dead.
I always forget how much I enjoy London.
You should go up more often, take an interest in your publishing.
You should get involved in the running of the business.
You're clever and a good writer. They're lucky to have you.
Mary always talks like she's the only one
who'll miss you when you go, but you know I will, too.
And I'll miss you.
Poor Mr Bates. They locked him up when he was innocent.
Why shouldn't they do the same with his wife?
I have faith in British justice. Mr Bates was released in the end.
After he'd served time.
Sorrow seems to shadow them both and in their wake, it shadows us.
Come, Mrs Hughes. This isn't like you.
Take courage for their sake. We must always travel in hope.
I realised what it is about Marigold that keeps catching my eye.
Oh, yes? What's that?
She reminds me of Michael Gregson.
Just tell me if I'm wrong.
You're not wrong.
Don't tell Edith you've guessed. Why not?
It makes things a good deal clearer than they were.
Just don't. Not yet. Mary doesn't know either, nor Tom.
Let it be Edith's secret a little while longer.
Very well.
I must admit it's an unusual sensation
to learn there's a secret in this house I'm actually privy to.
But, I'll be silent if you wish.
And you'll love her? Your new granddaughter?
As a matter of fact, and perhaps to my surprise,
I rather think I will.