-♪
-[gobbling]
[folk music playing]
[gobbles]
[crunching, gulps]
♪
D'oh!
-[buzzer sounding]
-huh?
Our first thanksgiving
since homer passed away.
-More turkey, please.
-Aw.
Thank god we still have
his hologram.
[clanking]
All right, everyone.
Get out
your remembrance candles.
Granny lisa,
why do we light a candle
Every thanksgiving?
In remembrance of
the great blackout
That almost destroyed our town
When we actually had to
write things down by hand.
(gasping, whimpering)
It started on
a cold November day.
Back when you could actually see
snow outside of a museum.
[wind howling]
[kent] goodbye, autumn,
hello, novem-brrr.
A powerful winter storm
is headed our way.
-Homie.
-♪ aloha 'oe ♪
Homie, wake up.
♪ aloha 'oe... ♪ [groans]
This isn't hawaii.
It's never hawaii.
It's just stupid america.
There's a winter storm
coming in.
[scoffs] winter storm.
I refuse to be scared
Unless there's
some terrifying new term for it.
It's an arctic blast
with a bomb cyclone
And a chance of firenado,
Or as we in the news business
call it,
-And "arcticonado."
-[homer screams]
None of us call it that, kent.
Pipe down, arnie.
I'm selling hoodies.
[homer humming]
-Homer, this is important.
-Hmm?
Did you put up the storm windows
like you promised?
[lisa]
there are two things I've leaned
are completely worthless:
Scented toilet paper and
a promise from homer simpsons.
-[wind whistles]
-[ralph whimpering]
I'll put 'em up
right after work.
You're going to work in that?
It's hawaiian day,
and the guys elected me
King kamehameha.
Let the goofing off at work
commence.
[toots]
-[wind whistles]
-[homer groans]
Ew, bacon.
Mmm.
-[wind whistles]
-[gasps]
[grunting]
[exhales]
Now, kids, I know the forecast
says it's triple-mitten weather,
But the good news is, it's less
than one week till turkey day.
Mom! Can we please not
call it "turkey day"?
You're celebrating
the slaughter of a living thing.
Lisa, you always
slaughter the mood.
You know, there are some amazing
faux turkeys to eat now.
Said no one, ever.
Right now,
they're perfecting the taste,
But in the future, faux turkeys
will taste really good.
[munching] hmm.
Nope. Still sucks.
[groans, coughs]
But for this year, my menu
is already up on the fridge.
And it really means a lot to me.
It's our first thanksgiving
with maggie.
I'm finally not pregnant,
so I can drink.
I call a drumstick.
Nice try, boy,
But we agreed I'd get
both drumsticks
Every thanksgiving
on the day you were born.
Aw, no fair.
I was too young to sign that.
I believe this is
your foot, is it not?
-And I had it notarized.
-Why you giant...
-[grunting]
-[chocking]
[sighs]
[lisa]
but the worst was yet to come.
That thanksgiving would surpass
christmas and my birthday
As the saddest day of the year.
[hawaiian music playing]
[slurping]
Welcome, or as they say
in hawaii: Welcome.
You're probably wondering
why we chose this special day
To have this celebration of you,
my workers
And dear, dear friends.
[chuckles]
Smithers, I need a distraction
so those unionized money-sucks
Don't see the new
cheaper replacements
I'm bringing in
to take their jobs.
Why don't we throw
a hawaiian day?
Aloha-ha-ha-ha.
Now enjoy, relax, mahalo,
Knowing your jobs are secure
and I could never replace you.
[cheering, laughing]
Nothing ulterior
about that statement.
We love you!
That's the last
we'll see of them.
Welcome, nonunion workers.
In an older era,
they'd call you scabs.
Now you're just friends
without benefits.
[chuckles]
[machines whirring rhythmically]
♪
♪ see here, smithers,
here's my theory ♪
♪ of how to cut down
what people earn ♪
♪ every worker
should be nonunion ♪
♪ that's the genius
of monty burns ♪
[tap dancing]
♪ they've got no health care,
they've got no dental ♪
♪ there's just one bathroom,
so they take turns ♪
♪ and all the money
and all the power ♪
♪ are in the clutches
of monty burns ♪
♪ hallelujah ♪
♪ make us grovel ♪
♪ for your energy ♪
♪ speed up the core,
speed up the core, man ♪
♪ speed up the core, speed up
the core, man ♪
♪ speed up the, speed up the,
speed up the, speed up ♪
♪ the core ♪
♪ rig detectors
and bribe inspectors ♪
♪ skip the training
'cause no one learns ♪
♪ even people
who ain't too clever ♪
♪ can work for minimum wage
forever ♪
♪ broken parts can be
glued together ♪
♪ for monty burns ♪
♪ monty burns, monty burns ♪
♪ monty burns. ♪
[cheering]
Smithers, how do these nonunion
avocado toasts sing so well?
Oh, they're all graduates of
Prestigious college
theater programs.
-Ah.
-That entire section
is julliard.
[harmonizing]
♪ it's this or teach. ♪
♪
Somebody should clean these up.
I nominate king kamehameha.
I'm starting to think
this king thing is just a trick
To get me to do all the work.
No, no. It's a very great honor,
your gullibility.
[laughter]
[grunting]
Hmm. [grunts]
Mm, mm.
Whew! Not gonna make
that mistake.
[automated voice]
waste disposed safely.
Thank you.
Now to call
jeff bezos and elon musk
And reclaim my title of
The world's most
self-serving billionaire.
Where can I plug in my phone?
[electrical crackling]
Uh, sir, I'm afraid we already
over-amped on that outlet.
I'll over-amp you.
[crackling]
[whooshing]
Put it out! Put it out!
♪ we don't know how. ♪
But we can dance stravinsky's
"firebird" around it.
["the firebird" playing]
[alarm blaring]
[panicked shouting]
[squealing]
Homer, what did you do in there?
I did exactly
what I was supposed to do.
[automated voice over speakers]
attention, plant employees.
See? She'll tell you.
Plant meltdown imminent.
Please take this time
to get right with your god.
♪
Now please put your name tag
inside your mouth
For the easy identification
of your skull.
[panicked shouting]
[alarm continues blaring]
Where are you going?
Uh, to get help.
Don't leave me, uncle monty!
-Smithers,
did you grease the struts?
-Yes, sir.
[screaming]
Yarr... You kidding me?!
[automated voice]
fire extinguished.
Plant ruined,
And you are all now out of work.
-Happy thanksgiving.
-[toots]
[lisa]
we had no power
and no prospects of getting any.
[crowd cheering]
[crowd gasping]
-What is it? What is it?
-We'll never know!
[lisa]
but whenever there's
a threat to civilization,
Good people always
set aside their differences
And blame a scapegoat.
All right, so,
who screwed up here?
Homer?
[chanting]
homer. Homer. Homer.
I agree.
We should find a scapegoat,
but who?
[chanting]
you. You. You.
I can't believe this.
I love you guys,
And now you want to
throw me under the bus?
Great idea.
Hey!
"throwing someone under the bus"
is a figure of speech.
Like, "I'll start my diet
tomorrow,"
Or "I love my children equally."
Okay, homer. Fair enough.
Ten-second head start!
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
You could've at least
done mississippi!
[wind whistling]
-[door rattles]
-[gasps] who's there?
♪
Watch it. I have pepper spray.
[homer]
mmm... Pepper spray.
[salivating]
Homer?
I put in all the storm windows,
And I bought brand-new batteries
for all the flashlights.
-Huh? Huh?
-[gasps]
[lisa]
there was nothing
that alarmed my mother more
Than a helpful homer.
Homer simpson,
did you have anything to do
With the blackout?
Everybody thinks I did,
but I didn't.
But I don't care because
you believe, marge, don't you?
I'm trying.
Eh. Could've been worse.
[cries out]
Once again,
the whole town is mad at dad.
Bart, do you know
how many furious mobs
The average family
has to contend with?
Hmm, six?
Zero. Zero!
You did do this.
Marge, in every marriage,
a spouse gets to say one time,
"you have got to believe me."
Yes, and you've done it
18 times.
Look in my eyes.
You've said that before.
Hold my hand
and look in my eyes.
You've said that before.
Hold my hand, look in my eyes
and feel my heart.
Also, if you can
examine my prostate...
All right, all right.
[grunting]
I don't know.
Mom!
I was aiming for his eye.
Mom, dad, please give us hope.
It's what parents do.
Don't worry, kids.
The government will help.
The government cannot
help itself,
Let alone you.
I have just been authorized
to commission a study
On whether or not a study
should be commissioned.
Finally. Thank you.
So, to take your minds
off your troubles,
I propose some kind of games.
Either "hunger" or "squid."
With that in mind,
tomorrow we will begin
With everyone attempting
to kill milhouse.
I finally got picked first.
Boo-yeah!
-[tires screeching]
-[man grunting]
[woman] take this.
[people talking angrily
outside]
No laptop, no kindle.
What do I do?
[gasps] I'll read a book.
Hmm.
I might learn something.
This pioneer girl was happy.
I'm not happy.
This is a nightmare.
My pa moved us out of wisconsin
Because he thought
it was too fancy.
Wisconsin?
And before you want to be me,
Answer this:
Did you ever kill a chicken?
Sorry, I'm a vegetarian.
So was I.
[lisa]
that as the moment
I began my remembrance book.
[in frontier accent]
and in my memory,
I sound like this.
People were made of
stronger stuff in pioneer days,
Until they died of agony at 39.
[wind whistling]
Well, if nothing else,
I can try to save thanksgiving.
[gasps] the food is gone.
Homer, is there an explanation?
Yes, there is.
-I--
-no more explanations.
I can't take it. [sobbing]
Dad, I'm really sad.
What do I do?
I don't know. Go outside.
-Build a snowman.
-I can't bring another life
Into this awful world.
-Shoo!
-[moans]
I have a little juice.
I can call tech support.
[ropes creaking]
[groans]
[grunts]
You think you miss the internet?
[bell clanging]
Hear ye, hear ye.
The latest matrix movie
was severely disappointing.
Do not take the red pill
or the blue pill.
You need no dose for this one.
End of "tweet."
Hey, like.
In fact,
I'm going to "follow" you.
-[scatting]
-yes, mute.
-♪ giving you likes
and following you ♪
-mute, mute.
[scatting]
[ragtime piano playing]
[piano music stops]
You! How dare you show your face
in here.
Moe, it's me.
And beneath all the drinking
and the jokes,
We have a real relationship.
And that means something.
What are you getting at?
Come on, man.
Deep down, we kind of
love each other.
Love you, too.
[homer moans]
It's hopeless.
Everyone in this town hates us.
But some not as much.
I brought firewood.
Whoa, grampa.
How'd you score that?
For your information, I grew up
in a cruel world like this,
Back in the '30s or '50s,
or whatever makes sense now.
[laughs] now let me get
that fire going for you.
[all]
ah!
Grampa, you saved us!
[chuckles] well, old people
have a lot of wisdom
If you take the time to--
She said thank you.
[jaunty tune playing
[lisa, in frontier accent]
we were more than happy.
We were a family again.
♪
[thumping]
Oh, what was that?
Go back to sleep, sweetie.
Tomorrow's Sunday.
You don't have to start
your chores till 4:00 a.M.
[yawns] thanks, grampa.
[truck engine starting]
We'll finally be rid of that
homer simpson once and for all.
And then I'll be the town idiot.
[chuckles] mm.
♪
[creaking]
Oh, my god! "city celebrates
explosion of the simpsons."
[marge groaning]
That's "expulsion"
of the simpsons.
Oh, whew.
Which means they
kicked us out forever.
Damn it!
Why won't people
believe I'm innocent?
-[creaking]
-oh, it's hopeless.
-[yowling]
-whoa, cool!
[playing jaunty tune]
[sighs] I guess there's
one good thing.
At least there's
no more stupid--
Howdy, neighbor.
I asked them to move my house
right next to yours.
[homer groans]
Well, at least you
believe me, flanders.
Yes, but I also believe in
a holy ghost no one can see.
In the name of the father and
the son and the spooky plus one.
[groans] I haven't slept
for two nights.
Because my choice is either to
be furious at you for the lie,
Or to believe you
and feel like a fool.
[groans]
Okay, okay,
I'm going to believe it.
[gulps]
Ugh. Now I'm actually in pain.
No pain, no gain.
I can't go on faith anymore.
I have to have a reason
to believe you. [groans]
There is. Oh, my god.
Do you remember when you thought
I ate the food in the fridge?
Yes?
Well, I didn't.
I put it under the snow
to keep it fresh.
Like in lisa's
stupid pioneer book.
Oh, my god.
[gasps]
you're telling the truth.
And if you're telling
the truth about that,
-Then you're telling the truth
about everything!
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh. [laughing]
-mm.
-Ooh, homie.
-[chuckling]
But if you're an innocent idiot,
Instead of a guilty nitwit,
How do we prove it?
By finding the person
who was behind it.
And there's only one man
who it could be.
The town villain.
Luigi!
No! Burns!
Smithers, I've eluded justice
yet again.
May my uppance never come.
[marge]
not so fast!
Gah!
We know what you did.
Yes, but you're also standing
on top of my trap door.
It, uh, doesn't work
without power, sir.
Fine. Smithers, do it manually.
[clicking]
[burns cackles]
You can't move.
That's cheating.
Take him away, boys.
Get the kiddie cuffs, lou.
Curses!
I have to take responsibility
for something I did?
[chuckles] ridiculous.
Montgomery burns, we will give
you the stiffest punishment
Any billionaire ever gets.
A fine you can easily pay.
I make more than that
in the time
It took me to say
"I make more than that." ha!
I'm so glad you guys
love me again.
We're still a little mad.
This brought back
a lot of memories
Of stuff you actually did do.
Remember, homer, I was
gonna be an orthodontist.
But no more, thanks to you.
What if you all have
thanksgiving dinner with us?
All you have to do is put
our house back where it was.
It's never just dinner.
There's always something.
♪
[lisa, in frontier accent]
and in the years that followed,
There would be other blackouts
and other mobs.
But they never blamed
my father again.
-Bart?
-Your story was so long
I died of boredom.
Also, I finally got a drumstick.
Mine now.
♪
[homer groaning]
"pa had walked back
after 23 miles
"with an orange for christmas.
"poor becca didn't get
to taste it
"because she passed that morning
from scarlet fever.
So they zested
the rind over her grave."
[sobbing]
[yawns] that's great, dad.
Maybe we should stop here.
No, I have to see if euchariah
sold the pelts in town
To those untrustworthy
canadians.
They didn't pay him
for last time!
Okay, you just tell me
what happens later.
"and in the spring, an orange
tree grew over her grave."
[sobbing]
[fiddle playing jaunty tune]
Captioning sponsored by
20th century fox television
And fox broadcasting company
And toyota.
Captioned by
media access group at wgbh
access.Wgbh.Org
-[lisa] enough!
-[grampa] okay!
[turkey gobbling]