Isn't it a big bonfire?
Yes.
Hastings, my friend, tell me,
to blow up
the English Parliament --
was it a sin or a noble deed?
Oh, it's no good
asking me, old son.
I was never much of a one
for politics.
Where's Mrs. Japp tonight, then?
She can't abide fireworks.
Ah, the noise disturbs
the delicate sensibilities
of many ladies.
Maybe, maybe.
I think it's more
that she doesn't like to see
people enjoying themselves.
Tell you what, though, what
a good night for a murder, eh?
I mean, if somebody
wanted to kill anybody,
nobody would know if it was
a gunshot or a firework.
Mm.
But not so good, my friend,
if your chosen method
is strangulation.
No, that's true. No.
Or poisoning, come to that.
Yes.
You're pulling my leg.
Yes, Hastings,
we pull ever so gently the leg.
Well, I still think it's a jolly
good night for a murder.
Anyway,
I'm going to leave you here.
-This is where I garaged my car.
-Ah.
Good night, Chief Inspector.
Good night, Poirot.
Good night, Captain Hastings.
A demain.
Good night!
Steady on, lads.
You won't forget your dental
appointment at 11:00,
will you, Mr. Poirot?
Hercule Poirot does not need to
go to the dentist, Miss Lemon.
You've put it off once already.
My teeth are perfection.
It is sacrilege
to tamper with them.
But why do we not do something
constructive about my collars,
Miss Lemon, hmm?
That laundry is in the pay
of my enemies.
Hercule Poirot's residence.
-Poirot, please.
-Oh.
-Japp here.
-Yes.
Chief Inspector Japp.
He's here.
Good morning,
Chief Inspector Japp.
Here's a strange thing, Poirot.
You remember how we stopped
at the end of Bardsley Garden
Mews last night,
where your friend Hastings
keeps his car,
and Hastings was saying
about how the sound of a shot
could be covered
by the noise of a firework?
Yes.
Well, someone did it.
Really?
Not murder.
It looks like suicide.
But they're not entirely happy
about it.
Hmm.
I'll meet you there in one hour.
Cancel all my appointments
for this morning, Miss Lemon.
But I've --
Good of you to spare the time,
Poirot.
No, no, no, no, no, not at all.
But I hope you appreciate,
my friend,
the urgent business I have
had to cancel to be here.
-Oh, really?
-Oh, yes.
The dead woman is a Mrs. Allen.
She shared the house
with a friend,
Miss Plenderleith, who is
a professional photographer
or something along those lines.
Miss Plenderleith was away
in the country.
But when she came home
this morning,
she finds
her friend's door locked.
She knocks and calls
but can't get any answer.
In the end, she gets really
alarmed and calls the police.
10:45,
our lads break the door down,
and there's Mrs. Allen lying
in a heap on the floor,
shot through the head.
Right, Brett.
What's the trouble?
Well, the position's all right.
If she'd shot herself,
she'd probably have slipped
from the chair
into just that position.
But?
The prints on the gun,
sir -- they're the problem.
Bit of a thumbprint
and a forefinger,
and that's all.
Just what you'd get
from someone trying to press the
dead woman's fingers on the gun
and not doing it very well.
Mm.
Gun in left hand,
wound on the left side.
Presumably she was left-handed.
It looks as though
she's holding the gun,
but, in fact, she isn't.
It's just sort of lying
in her hand.
Anything else?
The window was closed
and bolted,
and the door was locked.
We haven't been able to find
the key.
What's this, then?
It might mean something.
Anything strike you?
I was looking at her watch.
Hmm.
Expensive, by the look of it.
Tuesday, November 5th.
How long she been dead?
She died at about 11:30
last night.
No sign of any note
having been written.
No.
Seems to me all we've got
to go on at the moment
is the missing key.
If the key was here,
we wouldn't hesitate.
Suicide, we'd say.
This must be a terrible shock
to you, Miss Plenderleith.
I still can't believe it.
We'll be as brief as possible.
Now, you've already told
Inspector Jameson
how you found the body
when you came in this morning.
You were away for the weekend,
I take it.
Yes, since Friday noon.
Uh, pardon, mademoiselle.
When you found the door locked,
you called the police.
Did it not occur to you
that she might have gone away
and locked the door
before leaving?
Why should she lock it?
In any case, she would have left
a note for me.
And she did not leave any note?
Of course she didn't.
Ah.
Tell me about Mrs. Allen,
Miss Plenderleith.
I met her abroad.
She was on her way back
from India.
I was looking for someone
to share a flat with me.
We decided we liked each other.
What about the husband?
Nothing to write home about,
apparently.
He drank, I think.
Died a year or two
after the marriage.
Do you know if Mrs. Allen was in
any financial difficulties?
No, I'm sure she wasn't.
Did she have any particular
man friend or men friends?
She was engaged to be married
again,
if that answers your question.
What's the name of the man
she was engaged to?
Oh, my God.
I haven't told Charles.
Who is Charles, miss?
The man Barbara
was engaged to --
Charles Laverton West.
He's M.P. for someplace
in Hampshire.
I should have phoned him.
We'll go 'round and see him.
But there would be no quarrel
between them,
as far as you know?
I'd be very surprised.
Barbara wasn't
the quarreling kind.
What is your own opinion
of M. Laverton West,
mademoiselle?
He's young, ambitious,
a good public speaker,
means to get on in the world.
And on the debit side?
Well, in my opinion, he's
commonplace and rather pompous.
Those are not very serious
faults, mademoiselle.
Oh.
You don't think so?
Well, they might be to you,
but to Mrs. Allen... no.
She would not notice them.
You were fond of your friend?
Yes, very.
I know this must be
upsetting for you,
Miss Plenderleith,
but there are just
one or two more questions
I'd like to ask you.
Mrs. Allen was left-handed,
wasn't she?
Left-handed?
No, I don't think so.
No, I'm sure she wasn't.
Really?
You see, Mrs. Allen was shot
in the left temple,
and the gun was in
her left hand.
Didn't you notice that
when you found the body?
No, I didn't.
It was so horrible.
I didn't notice anything.
That's understandable, miss,
but it seems highly unlikely
that a normally
right-handed person
would shoot themselves
left-handed.
Have you ever seen this before?
No.
It's not yours,
nor Mrs. Allen's?
It's not the kind of thing
normally worn by our sex, is it?
Oh, so, you recognize it.
I don't recognize it.
I recognize what it is, though.
It's half of a man's cuff link.
Hastings!
Once we've got
this filter screwed down good...
Hastings?
...and tight,
we can put the new oil in,
and she will run
like a well-oiled clock.
Hastings?
Hello?
What are you doing, Hastings?
Well, I thought I'd just do
some work on the car.
But you were to ask questions,
Hastings,
to sound out local opinion.
Oh, I've done that.
Freddie?
Freddie's helping
with the oil filter.
That'll hold her.
Should be tight for now.
We'll put the spanner to it,
then put in a new gasket.
Right. This is Mr. Poirot.
How are you, gov?
I'm Fred Hogg.
You can call me Freddie.
Hello, Freddie.
Freddie's got the goods.
Did you see something
last night?
Well, Mrs. Allen -- she went
to the post box about 6:00.
About half-9:00, though,
a car pulled up.
Standard Swallow Saloon.
Rubbish, really,
but it looked smart.
A man got out.
He was about -- about 45,
well set up.
Military-looking gent.
You've seen him before?
Yeah, a couple of times.
Dark blue overcoat,
toothbrush mustache.
He was in there
for about an hour.
I saw them come out together.
So you saw him leave?
I don't miss much, gov.
Then you heard
what they said, of course.
Yeah, he said, "Think it over
and let me know,"
and she said something
and then he said, "So long."
And the way they talked --
they were friendly, yes?
Can't always tell with toffs,
can you,
but they seemed all right.
You didn't hear
what Mrs. Allen said?
Nah, she was sort of 'round
behind the door.
Now, look here, my boy,
I want you to answer my next
question very carefully.
If you don't know the answer or
can't remember, you just say so.
That clear?
Ask the question.
Which of them shut the door --
Mrs. Allen or the gentleman?
I think the lady did.
No, she never.
It was him.
He pulled it to with a big bang
and then got into the car
really quick.
Ah.
Here you are, my boy.
You seem a bright
kind of shaver.
Here's sixpence for you.
Oh, that's very kind of you,
sir,
but you couldn't see a way
to making it a shilling,
could you?
Go on.
Clear off.
Chief Inspector Japp
and Mr. Poirot, sir.
Good day, gentlemen.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
No great pleasure, sir,
I'm afraid.
Oh?
We've brought some bad news.
Go on.
It's about Mrs. Allen,
Mrs. Barbara Allen.
What about her?
Get on with it, man.
She's dead, sir.
Dead?
I don't believe it.
What's happened?
Apparently suicide, sir.
Was there anything worrying
Mrs. Allen, do you know?
No, not a thing.
We were engaged to be married.
Yes, quite so.
I can't believe it.
Dead?
How?
Shot, sir.
Shot?
Good God, I hope the newspapers
haven't got ahold of this.
I couldn't say, sir.
I wonder if I could just ask --
Hello?
Ah, yes.
Yes, thank you.
I'll hold on.
It's the prime minister.
I will have some questions, sir.
Just make an appointment
with my secretary at the house.
Yes, I'm still here.
Very good, sir.
We'll do that.
I'm sorry to be the bearer
of such bad news.
Pardon, monsieur.
Allow me to express my deepest
sympathy at your loss.
Yes, right, thank you.
Um, stiff upper lip, you know.
That's the British way.
Magnifique.
By the way, sir,
was Mrs. Allen left-handed?
Left-handed?
No, I don't think so.
Can't say I ever --
No, she was right-handed,
I'm sure.
Ah, Prime Minister.
No, not at all, Prime Minister.
Yes.
Yes, everything's ready for you.
What a stuffed fish.
No, not a stuffed fish.
A boiled owl.
As you say, Japp.
More concerned
about the newspapers
than his fiancée being dead.
The Plenderleith girl
was quite right about him.
Mind you,
he's a good-looking chap.
Might go down well
with some women.
Perhaps, but it would not do,
I think,
for them to have
a sense of humor.
The important thing is,
everyone seems agreed that
Mrs. Allen was right-handed.
Yes.
Of course, one must not jump
to conclusions, mon ami.
Never mind about jumping
to conclusions, Poirot.
This is a murder
we're dealing with.
To the Bulldog Breed Laundry --
Dear sirs...
once again...
I am obliged...
to communicate to you...
the dissatisfaction I have...
...for your starching...
of my collars.
I refer...
to my instructions...
of the 2nd of March, 1935,
and subsequent letters.
And you look them up
in the file, Miss Lemon,
and enumerate them.
All of them, Mr. Poirot?
All of them, Miss Lemon.
It has become serious.
The trouble is, Mr. Poirot,
they just don't understand
the letters.
Why not?
They're Chinese, Mr. Poirot.
The Bulldog Breed Laundry
is Chinese?
Yes, Mr. Poirot.
What is the world coming to,
Miss Lemon?
I'm sure I couldn't say, sir,
but when the boy brings
your laundry back,
he brings the letters back, too,
for me to explain to him.
And you do?
No.
Why not?
I don't speak Chinese.
So, what do you say to him?
Well, I -- I say, "Him collar
no velly good, starchy."
I show him the collars
and say it.
Hastings, my friend,
you spent some years in China,
did you not?
Oh, absolutely.
Fine fellows, fine fellows.
Did you ever have any trouble
with your laundry?
Yes, I did, as a matter of fact.
And what did you say to them?
Well, I said, "Him collar
no velly good, starchy."
That's where I got it from, sir.
I asked the captain,
knowing he'd been in the East.
But, Hastings, my collars,
they do not get any better.
No, mine didn't, either,
now I come to think about it.
Miss Lemon.
Why don't you get yourself some
turned-down collars, Poirot?
They're much more the thing,
you know.
"The thing," Hastings?
Do you think Poirot concerns
himself with mere "thingness"?
-Uh, no, no.
-No.
No, I-I-I see that, Poirot.
The turned-down collar
is the first symptom of decay
of the gray cells.
It's Chief Inspector Japp,
Mr. Poirot.
Well, she's out of it.
Good morning,
Chief Inspector Japp.
Yes, well, good morning.
Now, who is out of it?
Plenderleith.
She was playing bridge in Essex
up till midnight.
We've got to give up any idea
of her being concerned
in the business.
A disappointment, Japp?
You are still convinced we are
dealing here with a murder?
No doubts about it.
Something I've been meaning
to ask you, Poirot.
Hmm?
What was that
you were sniffing at in the room
when we first examined the body?
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
-You got a cold, have you?
-No.
I always thought
the little gray cells
were in your brain.
Don't tell me your nose cells
are superior to everyone else's,
too.
By no means.
It was merely cigarette smoke.
I didn't smell cigarette smoke.
No more did I, my friend.
There were nine cigarette ends
in the ashtray,
six of them gaspers,
three Turkish.
Exactly.
Your wonderful nose cells knew
that without looking, I suppose.
I assure you my nose
does not enter into the matter.
My nose registered nothing.
But the brain cells
registered a lot?
Well, there were
certain indications.
Did you not think so?
Now, am I wrong,
or are we going to talk further
with the beautiful
Miss Plenderleith?
Yes.
You know, there was something
missing from that room,
Chief Inspector...
but also something added,
I think.
You know what's
worrying me, Poirot?
Yes.
"Yes"?
What do you mean, "yes"?
I saw you looking
at Mrs. Allen's checkbook stubs
yesterday.
You're too clever for your own
good, you are, Poirot.
And you noticed, as I did,
that Mrs. Allen drew out
£200 in cash from her bank
on Monday morning.
And three months ago, on the 6th
of August, another £200.
-Truly?
-Truly.
And there's no £200 in this
house that my lads could find.
I'm afraid, Miss Plenderleith,
that we are no longer treating
this as a case of suicide.
Not suicide?
You see,
being as how your friend
was in no way, shape, or form
likely to commit suicide,
we have to consider
the alternative -- murder.
Murder?
Are you sure?
How horrible.
Horrible, perhaps, mademoiselle,
but impossible?
I suppose it's possible.
And if there was a murder,
there would have to be a motive.
Ask me any questions you like.
But I don't see
how I can help you.
On Monday night,
Mrs. Allen had a visitor.
He's described as a man of 45,
military bearing,
toothbrush mustache,
smartly dressed,
and driving
a Standard Swallow Saloon car.
Do you know who that is?
It sounds like Major Eustace.
Who's Major Eustace?
He was a man
Barbara had known in India.
He turned up about a year ago,
and we've seen him on and off
since.
He was a friend of Mrs. Allen's?
He behaved like one.
Would it surprise you,
Miss Plenderleith,
if I suggested that this man
was blackmailing Mrs. Allen?
Of course!
So that was it.
You find the suggestion
feasible, mademoiselle?
I was a fool not to think of it.
Oh, I wish she'd told me.
I'd have told him
to go to the devil.
But he might have gone,
might he not,
to M. Laverton West?
Yes.
Yes, that's true.
Which room do you think
Mrs. Allen would have received
her visitor in?
Oh, probably in here.
On the other hand,
if she wanted to write a check
or anything of that kind,
she'd probably take him
upstairs.
There's no question of a check.
Mrs. Allen drew out £200 in cash
on Monday.
So far, we've not been able
to find any trace of it
in the house.
But I'd like to have just
one more look 'round, if I may.
Look anywhere you like.
Thank you.
Would you like to sit down?
Cigarette?
You are most kind.
This cupboard under the stairs,
Miss Plenderleith.
It's locked.
Yes, I've already
found that out.
Could I have the key, please?
Um... I don't know where it is.
Oh. That's too bad.
Don't want to have to break
the lock.
No.
Um... it might be upstairs.
I managed to find it.
Good.
We keep it locked.
Otherwise, one's umbrellas
and things
have a habit of getting pinched.
Very sensible.
Right.
That's mine.
It came back with me
yesterday morning,
so there can't be
anything there.
Just as well to be
on the safe side.
Nothing much there.
No, well, there couldn't
have been, could there?
Sorry to bother you again,
Mr. Laverton West.
Couldn't it have waited?
This sort of inquiry
is often inconvenient, sir.
I don't mind the inconvenience
if I see the results.
Have you any idea yet,
Chief Inspector,
what caused Mrs. Allen
to take her own life?
Well, perhaps it will be
more understandable, sir,
if I tell you that it was
not suicide, but murder.
What are you talking about?
Have you any idea,
Mr. Laverton West,
who might have
any conceivable motive?
No. It's bizarre.
The mere idea is unimaginable.
She never mentioned any enemies,
anyone who might bear a grudge
against her?
Never.
Do you know a Major Eustace?
Eustace?
Oh, yes, I remember.
I met him once at Barbara's.
Mrs. Allen's.
Rather a doubtful type,
in my opinion.
I said as much to Mrs. Allen.
He wasn't the sort of man
I should have encouraged
to come to the house
after we were married.
Look, I've got to get dressed.
What did Mrs. Allen say to that?
She quite agreed.
She trusted my judgment
implicitly.
And naturally, as my wife,
she would have found a good many
of her old associates,
well, unsuitable, shall we say?
Quite.
What can you tell me
about your own movements
on the night of November 5th,
sir?
My movements?
Purely a matter of routine, sir.
We have to ask everybody.
I should have thought a man
in my position
might have been exempt.
It doesn't work quite like that,
sir.
Very well.
Let me see.
I was at the House of Commons,
left about half past 10:00,
went for a walk
along the embankment,
watched some of the fireworks.
Lucky there aren't any plots
like that nowadays.
Then I walked home.
What time did you arrive?
Somewhere about 11:15, 11:30.
Perhaps someone let you in.
No.
Did you meet anyone
whilst walking?
No.
What an alibi.
It's so feeble,
it must be genuine.
No, I'm not bothered about him.
It's the Plenderleith girl
that worries me.
I'd still like to know
why she got so hot and bothered
about that briefcase.
That's something in your line,
Poirot.
You like chasing about
after the kind of triviality
that leads nowhere --
the mystery
of the perambulating briefcase.
Sounds quite promising.
No, you got to work south
a little.
No, you got to work east now,
boys.
Nunca, nunca.
Major Eustace in the club?
Major Eustace?
Yes.
Chief Inspector Japp,
Scotland Yard.
Oh, yes?
Drink?
No, thank you, sir.
Might we have a word?
Uh, yes.
Shall we go over here?
Well, well, well.
Take a pew.
It's not often I get honored
by a big gun
like a chief inspector.
No, thank you.
Ah.
You smoke Turkish, I see.
Yes.
Would you prefer a gasper?
I've got some.
Somewhere.
No, no, this'll do fine, thanks.
I think you knew Mrs. Barbara
Allen, Major Eustace.
Ah, yes.
Very sad business.
Saw it in the paper last night.
You met her out in India,
I believe.
Yes.
That's some years ago now.
Did you also know her husband?
No, as a matter of fact,
I never came across Allen.
But you know something
about him.
I heard he was by way
of being a bad hat.
Of course, that was, uh,
only hearsay.
Mrs. Allen never spoke
about him?
Never.
What I want to know is
did you see Mrs. Allen on
the night of November the 5th?
Indeed I did.
You called at her house,
I think.
That's right.
She asked me to advise her
about some investments.
She gave no hint about
contemplating suicide?
Not the least in the world.
As a matter of fact,
when we said goodbye,
I said I'd ring her up soon
and we'd do a show together.
You said you'd ring her up?
Those were your last words?
Yes.
Curious.
I have information that you said
something quite different.
My information is that
what you actually said was,
"Well, think it over
and let me know."
Not quite the same thing, is it?
Well, I -- I-I think what I said
was that she should let me know
when she was free.
I mean, you can't expect a man
to remember word for word.
Excuse me, Major.
Deirdre says we need some more
gin from the cupboard.
Ah.
Get a couple of bottles out,
will you, Trevor?
Right.
You own this place,
do you, Major Eustace?
Wish I did.
Little gold mine, this.
You say that Mrs. Allen
asked you to advise her
about investments.
Did she, by any chance,
entrust you with a sum of £200?
What the devil
do you mean by that?
Well, Mrs. Allen drew out
the sum of £200 in cash
from her bank.
Some of the money
was in £5 notes.
They can be traced
by their numbers, of course.
Well, trace them, then,
and be damned to you!
Trace them.
I don't care.
Was the money for investment,
Major Eustace,
or was it blackmail?
That's a preposterous
suggestion.
How dare you?
Look -- Look --
what happened was this --
I went 'round to the house.
I mean, I-I telephoned first --
What time did you get there?
Um... about half past 9:00.
We sat and talked.
And smoked.
Yes, and smoked.
Anything wrong with that?
Where did this talk take place?
In the sitting room.
As I said, we sat and talked
quite amicably.
And then I left, uh, just before
about half past 10:00.
You stayed in the sitting room
throughout your visit?
Yes.
You didn't go upstairs
to Mrs. Allen's own room?
No.
Could I just look at your
cuff links, Major Eustace?
Cuff links?
You can refuse if you wish,
of course.
I've got nothing to hide.
When did that happen?
-What?
-One of them's broken.
Oh, I know.
I, uh -- I noticed it
this morning.
It doesn't show if I put
that end on the inside.
Would it surprise you to learn
that it happened when you were
visiting Mrs. Allen?
Well, I've not denied
I was there.
Yes, but that piece of cuff link
was found not downstairs
in the sitting room,
but upstairs
in Mrs. Allen's own room,
there in the same room
where she was murdered.
Murdered?
Yes, and where a man sat smoking
the same kind of cigarettes
that you smoke.
Are you trying to frame me?
I never went near the house
again that night.
You didn't need to.
She was dead when you left.
No.
No, now, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
You've got someone who heard me
talking to Barbara
on the doorstep.
You said --
They heard you talk to her,
then pretend to wait for her
to answer, and then talk again.
That's an old trick.
Oh, my God, it isn't true.
Robert Erskine Eustace,
I must ask you to accompany me
to the police station.
Oh, my God.
Oh, hello.
Yes, dear?
Could I please speak
to Miss Plenderleith?
Well, you could, dear,
if she was here.
She's gone off playing
that golf.
Golf?
If you please.
And that poor Mrs. Allen still
lying cold down at the mortuary.
Indeed.
This is most difficult.
I'm sorry.
Missus...
Pierce, dear.
Ah.
My name is Hercule Poirot,
Mrs. Pierce.
Ooh!
I've heard of you, dear.
Well, I am most flattered.
Mrs. Pierce, I am in something
of a difficulty.
Oh.
I came here yesterday
with a Chief Inspector Japp,
and we omitted to search
for clues
in one particular place
in the house.
So, I was wondering if --
Oh, come on in, dear.
Help yourself.
You are most kind.
Thank you.
My old man will be
ever so tickled
when I tell him you was here,
dear.
Always reading your exploits
in the paper, he is.
That's very nice, Mrs. Pierce.
May I?
Yes, go on.
Drive you to drink, he would,
reading all that rubbish
in the newspapers.
Mrs. Pierce,
where does Miss Plenderleith go
to play the golf?
Are you sure he's all right,
Captain Hastings?
The name of Poirot is feared
on golf courses
all over the continent.
You don't happen to have
a handicap certificate on you,
do you, sir?
No, no, I'm fine.
Now, there should be
a little hole somewhere,
and I have to push the ball
into it.
You see that flag there?
No.
In front of the big tree,
a little patch of red.
Ah, yes, good.
That's where the little hole is.
No.
Won't keep you a moment.
Now, all you have to do
is hit it with that.
Go ahead.
Easy does it.
Am I allowed to hit the flag?
Oh, yes, yes, that'll be fine.
No, it will not hit the flag,
I think.
Oh.
Bad luck.
Hastings, how will we ever
catch up with Miss Plenderleith
if you take so many hits
each time?
Well, we can't.
She started out
an hour and a half ago.
We might see her coming back
on one of the parallel holes.
I do wish you'd stop rummaging
around in the dustbins.
Ha.
Not another one.
Number three, Hastings.
Someone's having a bad day.
People do break clubs, you know.
But three clubs in three holes?
Well, what, then?
Our Miss Plenderleith is getting
rid of some golf clubs
in a place where she thought
they would never be noticed.
Major Eustace is not guilty
of murder, Hastings.
Lost your ball again, Poirot?
Shh!
Keep out of sight.
Look.
Have you seen enough, Hastings?
I must regretfully abandon
our most interesting game
and go and telephone
the Chief Inspector Japp.
Come on.
Why?
Why would a presumably sane
young woman
want to throw an expensive case
into a lake
with just two magazines in it
and a couple of stones
to make sure it sank?
You need worry no longer.
The answer is coming.
And why break up a perfectly
good set of golf clubs?
I don't mind telling you
I lay awake last night
worrying about it.
Mon pauvre Japp.
Miss Plenderleith, Mr. Poirot.
Thank you, Miss Lemon.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've just come
from Barbara's funeral.
It was so good of you to come.
Please sit down, mademoiselle.
I have certain news to give you.
I read it in the papers.
Major Eustace has been arrested.
It was murder, then?
Oh, yes, the willful destruction
of one human being
by another human being.
And now, mademoiselle,
I am going to tell you
just how I arrived at the truth
in this matter.
He has his methods.
I humor him, you know.
To begin with, there was the
smell of the cigarette smoke.
Which I didn't smell.
Precisely.
And yet the ashtray had in it
no fewer than the stubs
of nine cigarettes.
So it was very odd, eh, very odd
that the room should smell
as it did -- perfectly fresh.
Oh, so that's what
you were getting at.
Hmm?
The next thing
that attracted my attention
was the wristwatch worn
by the dead woman.
What about it?
It was worn on the right wrist.
In my experience,
it is more usual
for the wristwatch to be worn
on the left wrist.
But now, my friends,
I come to the writing bureau.
Yes, I thought we'd come
to that.
You know the blotting pad
had on top
a clean, untouched
piece of blotting paper?
The sheet was clean
because Barbara hadn't written
any letters that day.
Yes, she had.
Freddie saw her post
some letters at 6:00.
Well done, Hastings.
So, what, then,
happened to the piece of paper
on which she had blotted
her letters?
But there was a second curious
detail about the writing desk.
Perhaps you, Japp, can remember
the arrangement of it.
Allow me.
Ink stand and blotting pad
in the center,
the pen tray to the left,
the calendar and the quill pen
to the right.
Eh bien?
Yes.
Ah, you do not see?
The pens for use were in
the pen tray on the left.
Is it not more usual to find
the pen tray on the right
more convenient
for the right hand?
So I made myself a picture,
Japp.
A picture of Miss Plenderleith
arriving home
after the weekend.
A picture of Miss Plenderleith
opening the door
and finding her friend
lying dead,
with the pistol clasped
in her hand.
Barbara?
Her left hand, naturally,
since her friend was
left-handed,
in spite of everything
Miss Plenderleith has done
to convince us that her friend
was right-handed.
There is also a note addressed
to you, mademoiselle.
It was, I fancy,
a very moving letter
about a young, gentle,
unhappy woman...
driven by blackmail
to take her own life.
I think almost at once the idea
flashed into your head --
"Let him be punished."
You take up the note, and the
top sheet of blotting paper.
Then you go downstairs
and light the fire...
...and drop both
into the flames.
You take the ashtray upstairs
to further the illusion
that there were two people
sat up there talking.
You also have a lucky break.
You discover a fragment
of Major Eustace's cuff link
in the sitting room.
You take that upstairs, too.
You expect that
to clinch the matter.
You take the pistol
from her left hand.
You wipe it clean and put it
back in her left hand.
You bolt the window
and lock the door.
There must be no suspicion that
you have tampered with the room.
And so it goes on.
Oh, yes, mademoiselle,
it was clever,
a very clever murder.
For that is what it was.
The attempted murder
of Major Eustace.
It wasn't murder.
It was justice.
That man hounded Barbara
to her death -- poor kid --
just because she got involved
with some married man in India
and had a baby.
When the child died,
she came back to England.
She met Charles
and fell in love with him.
God knows why,
the pompous little tick.
And then that devil Eustace
turned up from India.
If you'd read that letter
she left me,
you'd understand
why I did what I did.
She loved Charles, she said.
She couldn't live without him,
but for his own sake,
she mustn't marry him.
She was taking the best way out.
I wish you'd seen that letter.
And you call it murder!
Because it is murder.
The man you wish to trap
is already in prison.
Do you really wish
to destroy him?
Do you really wish to destroy
the life,
the mind of any human being?
No.
No, I don't.
I wish I did.
But I don't.
Well, I'm jiggered.
Not murder disguised as suicide,
but suicide made to look
like murder.
And cleverly done, too.
Nothing overemphasized.
Wait a minute.
What about the briefcase?
And what about the golf clubs?
Ah.
Well, they were Mrs. Allen's.
You see, Jane Plenderleith
had to convince us that
her friend was right-handed
if we were to believe
she had been murdered.
But the golf clubs --
they were the left-handed.
Of course!
And when she opened
the cupboard,
she tried to focus our attention
on the wrong object.
So she used the briefcase
as a --
What is it, a bloater?
Kipper?
Red herring.
Absolutely.
And now, my friends,
it is time for me to take you
to lunch.