Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
- Are you enjoying yourself?
- Yes.
Hastings, my expensive one, says to me.
To destroy the English Parliament,
was it a crime or a noble act?
It is not worthwhile to ask about me.
I never realized a lot of of politics.
Where you are. Japp?
It does not support fireworks.
The noise injures the sensibility
of many ladies.
Perhaps, perhaps.
It seems to me that the fact is that she does not like
of seeing the persons enjoying oneself.
He would say that it is a beautiful night
to commit a crime.
If someone wanted to kill someone,
a shot was not heard by the fire.
It is already not possible to say the same thing
if the option was the estrangulamento.
No. In fact, no.
- Or poisoning, already now.
- Yes.
Be getting involved with me!
It is true, Hastings.
We am alone putting us with you.
I keep on thinking that it is
a beautiful night to commit a crime.
I am going to leave them here.
It is here that I stay.
In the good-night, Inspector Chief.
In the good-night, Poirot.
- In the good-night.
- Up to tomorrow.
Good night!
Continue, boys.
It is not going to forget
of his consultation in the dentist to 11:00?
Hercule Poirot
it does not need to go to a dentist.
It postponed already once.
My teeth are completed.
It is a sacrilege to adulterate them!
Because we do not do anything of constructive one
for my collars, Mrs. D. Lemon?
That laundry must be
on account of my enemies...
- Residence of the Mr. Poirot.
- You. Poirot, please.
Yes.
Inspector-chief Japp.
He is here.
- Good-day, Inspector-chief Japp...
- This is strange, Poirot.
One remembers of we stop
in the Stables Garden last night
where his friend Hastings
it guards the automobile
and to say that the noise of the fire
was it stifling a shot?
- Yes.
- So someone fired.
- To serious?
- It is not a murder, it seems a suicide.
But the case is not very clear...
I will be in there of an hour.
Cancel all my promises
for this morning, Beauty queen Lemon.
But...
- I thank to have come, Poirot.
- Of all.
I wait for them to myself what values while having
when an urgent promise was canceled.
- Had you had to?
- Do not doubt.
The dead woman is called a Mrs. Allen.
It was sharing the house with a friend,
Beauty queen Plenderleith,
photographer or something of the type.
The Beauty queen Plenderleith
it was out in the field,
and when it returned this morning
it found the shut door.
Rice seed, but it does not obtain answer.
Be preoccupied and it calls the police officer.
To 10:45,
our colleagues break the door down
and they find you. AIIen in the ground,
with a shot in the cabeca.
Ç
- Then, Brett, what the problem is?
- The position is normal.
If she was giving a shot in the head,
it had to slip for this position.
- But ...?
- The problem they are the impressions.
A thing to that of light one
of the thumb and of the index finger.
The same thing that would be obtained while trying
to put the weapon in her hand, and badly.
It arms in the left hand,
injured in the left side...
It had to be left-handed.
It seems that it is holding the weapon,
but it is only with her in the hand.
- More something?
- The window was closed and locked.
The door was locked,
but we did not find the key.
What is this?
It can mean something.
- Does anything take place to him?
- It was looking at the clock.
It seems that be expensive.
" It mixes, 5 of November ".
- Is there how much time is killed?
- It died around the 23.30 of yesterday.
- There is no sign of a written note.
- No.
It seems to me that completely what we have
it is the lost key...
If we had the key,
we would not hesitate.
We would say that it was a suicide.
It is necessary to have been a terrible shock,
Beauty queen Plenderleith.
I still do not manage to believe.
We are going to try to be abbreviations.
It counted already to an Inspector Jameson
since it found the body this morning.
Was it out in weekend?
- Yes. From Friday in the afternoon.
- Excuse, my lady.
When it found the shut door,
it called the police officer.
His friend did not take place to him what
could it have gone out and closed the door?
Is it why because it would do it?
Be that as it may,
a note would have left me.
- And did not it leave any?
- Clear what not!
Talk to me on you. Allen.
I knew it abroad.
She was returning of the Indian.
He wanted someone to share the seat
and we sympathized one with other one.
And the husband?
Not noteworthy at all, apparently.
It was drinking, I find. It died one year
or two after marrying.
If you know. Allen
did it have financial problems?
No, I am sure that not.
It had some friend or friends
closer men?
It was that he gets engaged to return marrying,
if that responds to his question.
What the name of the man is
with whom does it link was he going to marry?
- My God, the Charles did not say to.
- The one who is it Chatter?
The fiance, Charles Loverton-West.
It is delegated of the government in Hampshire.
It must to him have phoned.
We are going to speak with him.
Did not he know them to me about any anger?
It would be very much surprised.
To Pipe it was not given to discussions.
What his opinion is
on you. Laverton-West?
It is young, ambitious,
speak well in public, it is made a list well.
And in another side of the balance?
- Not much banal ... and quite pompous.
- They are not very big defects.
- Does not it find?
- Perhaps for you.
But for you. Allen, no.
She would not notice them.
- Was it liking his friend?
- Yes. Very much.
I know that this must be annoyed,
I me need to ask more two questions.
- You. was Allen left-handed?
- Left-handed? No, I think that not.
- No. I am sure that not.
- To serious?
The fact is that the shot was in the left temple
and the weapon was in the left hand.
- Did not it notice when he saw the body?
- No.
I ... it was so awful
what I did not repair in anything.
We understand.
But it is highly unlikely
what a skilful person
it was firing with the left hand.
- Sometime did he see this?
- No.
It is not his not even of the Mrs. Allen?
- A woman does not use these things.
- Then does it recognize it?
I do not recognize it.
I recognize them to myself what is.
It is a half
of a button of man's fist.
This filter is spoilt.
We put a new and he is going to work
like a clock certinho.
Hastings!
Hello!
- What it is doing, Hastings?
- A few arrangements in the car.
You had to be asking questions.
Probing the local opinion.
- Oh, already I did that!
- Freddie!
Freddie is helping me
with the filter of the oil.
This is going to maintain it held tight
up to having the piece of news anilha.
- Right. This is you. Poirot.
- How it is, boss?
I am Fred Hogg.
- Hello, Freddie.
- Freddie has the news.
- Did you see anything last night?
- You. Allen went to the mail to the six.
But there to 21:30, a car appeared...
A Standard Swallow.
It swims of special one,
but it was looking good.
A man left, there of approximately 45...
quite established, soldier's aspect.
- Had you already seen it?
- Yes, sometimes.
Dark overcoat, moustache to the little brush.
It was there more or one less hour.
- I saw them leaving joined.
- Then did you see it?
It me does not escape very much, boss.
- You heard what they said, clearly.
- Yes.
He said
" Think well and then he speaks with me ".
Then she said any thing
and he said " Up to abbreviation ".
And speaking, did they seem friendly?
One never knows with fine people,
I am them that yes.
You did not hear what you said. Allen?
No, she was average behind the door.
Now he hears, boy, I want that you answer
with much taken care to this question.
If you will not know the answer
or not to remind of you, he says. Combined?
- Ask the question.
- Did which you erase close the door?
I think that it went to lady.
No, link not! It was he!
He opened it a bit with strength
and it got involved in the car quickly.
It prays well. It seems to you to be a good informer.
Here you have six pence.
Very much thank you, man.
And does it manage to stretch them up to 1 shilling?
Go, go away!
- Inspector Chefe Japp and Mr. Poirot.
- Good morning. What I owe this pleasure?
- It is not any pleasure, unfortunately.
- To serious?
- We bring bad news.
- Continue.
It is on you. Allen.
You. Barbara Allen.
What is that it goes on?
Say, man!
It died, man.
Did it die?
I do not believe. What happened?
Apparently, it was a suicide.
Does he know if something was preoccupying it?
No, not even for shadows.
We were going away to marry.
We knew already.
I do not believe. Killed?
How?
With a shot.
With a shot? Good Lord!
Will it be that the newspapers know already of this?
I cannot say to him.
It will be that I can ask about him...
Is it? Obliged...
Yes, I wait.
He is the Prime minister.
I have some questions what...
Yes, make one's mark with my secretary.
Yes, yes, I am.
Very well, man. We will do that.
I lament to have brought so bad news.
Allow to me what it expresses
my condolences.
Yes. Thank you.
Be necessary to maintain the composure, he knows already.
Magnify!
Already now ... you. was Allen left-handed?
Left-handed? No, it does not look to me.
I cannot say what ... no.
She was skilful, I am sure.
Mr. Prime minister...
Of all, Mr. Prime minister.
Yes, yes, it is completely ready.
What a peacock! No, a peacock not.
A known fox.
It is how he says, Japp. More preoccupied
with the newspapers what with the fiancee.
It is the Plenderleith that was certain.
Even so, well similar.
It must be pleasing to some women.
Perhaps.
I find them to myself what would not see this
with sense of mood.
What it matters the fact is that they all agree
what you. Allen was skilful.
Yes. We do not owe them to me
to draw hasty conclusions.
Do not be preoccupied by that.
We are talking about a murder.
For the Laundry Bulldog Breed.
Expensive Sirs,
Again
I am obliged
communicating them
my dissatisfaction
in spite of pressing of
my collars.
I refer to my educations
of 2 of March of 1935
and subsequent letters of...
Look for them and enumerate them.
- All, Mr. Poirot?
- All, Beauty queen Lemon.
The subject is becoming serious.
The problem, Mr. Poirot,
the fact is that they do not realize the letters.
- For what not?
- They are Chinese, Mr. Poirot.
- Is the laundry a Chinese?
- It is, Mr. Poirot.
- Is it where that the world is going to stop?
- I do not do idea.
But when the boy brings the clothes,
it brings the letters in order that I explain them to him.
- And does it explain him?
- No.
- Why?
- I do not speak Chinese.
- Then what he says to him?
- Well, I say to him...
" Collar erases badly pressed ".
I catch the collars and show him.
You spent a few times in China,
was not he Hastings?
It is true. Excellent types.
Did it have any problem with the laundry?
- By chance, I had.
- And what he said to them?
Well ... he said...
" collar erases badly pressed ".
Exactamente. I knew that the Captain
it had been in the Orient and I asked.
- But the collars did not improve!
- Thinking well ... mine also not.
Because it does not arrange other collars?
Of what they are in use more.
Of what they are in use? Billet what Poirot
does it use any thing?
- He is not that, Poirot...
- A common collar
it is the first symptom
of decadence of the grey mass.
- He is the Inspector Chief Japp.
- Good, she is out.
- Good morning, Inspector Chief Japp.
- So, well... Good morning.
- Who is out?
- The Plenderleith.
It was playing bridge in the Essex
even to the midnight.
We will set aside the idea
of what she was wrapped.
What disillusionment.
It is still convinced
what one treats as a murder?
I have no doubts.
It wanted to ask about him a thing.
Because it was walking smelling
when we were in the room?
- Snif, snif. Is not it with a cold?
- No.
I always thought that you sweat them
grey cells were in the brain.
There does not say to me what in the nose, also!
Of all. It was only a smoke of cigarette.
- I did not smell cigarette.
- I also not, my expensive one.
There were nine pious women in the ashtray.
Six common ones, three Turks.
- Exactamente.
- Did it detect for the smell, without looking?
My nose is not relevant.
My nose did not register anything.
But the cells of the brain
did they register enough?
There were some signs,
does not it find?
We are going to speak again
with the Beauty queen Plenderleith, right?
Yes.
He knows, Inspector Chief,
any thing was lacking in that room.
But also there was something to more.
- Does he know what it is preoccupying me?
- I know.
- Does he know? How so?
- I saw it consulting
the check book of the Mrs. Allen.
You are very clever, Poirot.
And it noticed that you. Allen stood up
200 pounds in cash in the second one?
- And three months before, other 200.
- To serious?
Yes. But it was not
money none at the home.
I am afraid that one does not negotiate of
a case of suicide.
Was not it a suicide?
It is not possible to conclude for the position
what his friend if it committed suicide
we will consider
the hypothesis of ... murder.
Murder? Does it find?
What horror!
Awful, perhaps...
But ... impossible?
I suppose what is possible.
And murder is dug,
there would be a motive.
One asks about what he will want.
But I am not seeing how it could help.
In the second one at night,
you. Allen had a sight.
A 45-year-old man, military type,
moustache to the little brush, quite dressed
and guiding a Standard Swallow.
Does he know who is?
He seems to be Major Eustace.
- Who is Major Eustace?
- To Pipe it knew it in India.
It turned that there is one year
and we it were seeing turn and a half.
- He was a friend of the Mrs. Allen?
- It was held how if it was.
It would be surprised if he was saying to him
what he was blackmailing you. Allen?
Clear! Then it was that!
Clear!
Does it think that it is a hypothesis credível?
I was foolish in not having thought about that!
That it grieves it not to have called myself at all!
It had ordered it for the Devil!
But perhaps he has gone...
to have with you. Laverton-West?
Yes ... yes, it is true.
In which room will you have. Allen
when his visit was received?
Probably here.
But she wanted to pass a cheque,
it is natural what was taking it there up.
Cheque was not necessary any.
She lifted 200 pounds in cash.
We still did not find money any
at the home.
But was he liking was seeing again, it can be?
- See to the will.
- Thank you.
- Does not it want to sit down?
- A cigarette?
- It is very gentle.
This cupboard under the staircases...
It is closed.
Yes, already I noted.
Can it give me the key?
I ... I do not know where it is.
That it suffers!
It did not want to spoil the lock.
It must be up there.
I managed to find it.
The best!
It uses to be closed,
to protect the things.
Quite thought.
That is mine!
It brought it yesterday morning,
therefore it has not there anything.
It is not lost at all in certifying.
- It seems that it has not anything.
- No. Could it not even, it is not?
- Excuse to bother it again.
- Could not it wait?
This type of interrogation
it has his drawbacks.
I do not mind drawbacks,
one will have resulted.
It has some idea
of what you got a beating. Allen to the suicide?
Perhaps understand better
it will be said to him what was a murder.
- What he is saying?
- It has some idea
of whom it would have a presumable motive...
No! It is estranhíssimo!
The mere idea is ... inconceivable!
Does she ever speak in enemies?
Someone who had something against her?
Never.
- Does it know Major Eustace?
- Eustace?
Oh, yes ... I saw it once
at home of Barbara ... of the Mrs. Allen.
A doubtful type, as for me.
As a matter of fact, I commented with you. Allen.
It was not the man's type what I
it wanted to come to receive at home.
- Excuse, I have to dress myself.
- What you said. Allen?
It agreed.
It trusted my judgement.
And like my woman, it was natural
what was coming to consider
a great deal of the friends ... unsuitable.
Undoubtedly.
What he says to me of his movements
in the night of 5 of November?
Movements?
My movements?
It is only a question of routine.
We will ask everyone.
He was thinking that in my position
it was dispensed of these questions.
It is not quite so that it works.
Very well.
Let me think...
I was in the Chamber of the Common ones.
I left about 22:30.
I went for a walk near the Docks.
- I was seeing the fireworks.
- Be already no arguments of this!
- Then I walked up to house.
- To which hours did it arrive?
Between them 23:15 and them 23:30.
- Did anybody open the door?
- No.
- Did it find anybody in the way?
- What an alibi!
- It is so weak which debit to be true.
I am not preoccupied by him,
but with the Beauty queen Plenderleith.
It was liking realizing
that preoccupation with the suitcase.
This is more his type, Poirot:
To examine the trivialities in detail.
" The Mystery of the Walking Suitcase ".
It promises.
Is Major Eustace here?
- Major Eustace?
- Yes?
Inspector Chief Japp, Scotland Yard.
- Does it accept a drink?
- No, thank you. can We talk?
Yes. We go for there.
One feels, please.
It is not every day what I receive
someone at the level of an Inspector Chief.
- It smokes Turkish cigarettes.
- Yes.
Does it prefer of others? I have someone there...
No, so it is well. Thank you.
I suppose what you knew. Allen,
is not it so?
Yes, it knew.
A very sad history.
He knew yesterday for the newspapers.
- Do I believe what knew it in India?
- Yes. That was already that there are a few years.
- Also did it know the husband?
- No, by chance I never knew.
Does anything know them to me about him?
I heard that it was a bad type.
- It is clear what are only noises.
- You. does Allen ever speak on that?
Never.
He wanted to know if you saw. Allen
in the night of 5 of November.
I saw, yes.
- Was it up to her house?
- Exactamente.
She asked for me advices
on a few investments.
It did not give anyone signs
of what one was going to commit suicide?
Absolutely none.
When we say goodbye,
even I combined to phone to speak
on a show joined.
- Were last words his?
- Yes.
Snooper.
I have a different information.
To what I know, you said:
" Think about that, and then he talks to me. "
It is not well the same thing, is not it?
I must have said to him to call myself
it is when that I him could phone.
It is not to the wait that reminds of me
of each word that he said.
Excuse, Major...
We need more gin of the cupboard.
- Take away a few bottles, favor is done.
- Right.
- Is this Club his, Major Eustace?
- Who had given to me. It is a mine.
You. Allen asked for him opinion
on a few investments, was not it?
By chance did not she give him 200 pounds?
- What it means with that?
- You. Allen lifted 200 pounds.
Part erases in notes for five pounds.
They can be found by the numbers.
What a devil! Then find them!
- Find them ... I want to know there!
- The money was to invest,
or does it the question be blackmail?
- What a more insulting insinuation!
Ear, which happened was this...
I was up to her house.
It means, I phoned first...
- To which hours did it arrive there?
- Around 21:30.
- We sat down talking...
- And do they fume?
Yes ... we smoked.
What hardly has that?
- Where this conversation had place?
- In the living room.
As he was saying, we sat down
and we talked friendly
and I left about 22:30.
- Was it in the room during the whole visit?
- Yes.
- It did not rise to the room of the Mrs. Allen?
- No.
- Can I see his buttons of fist?
- The buttons of fist?
- It can refuse, is clear.
- I have not anything hiding.
- Is it when that that happened?
- What?
- One of them is broken.
- I know.
I noticed that this morning.
He does not see himself if I will put for inside.
It would be surprised if he was saying to him
what happened at home of the Mrs. Allen?
- I did not deny what I was there.
- Yes, but this piece of the button
it was not found in the room,
but yes in the room of the Mrs. Allen.
In the same siege where it was murdered.
And where a man was seated
smoking the same cigarettes than you.
Is it trying to incriminate me?
I did not return any more to the house in that night.
It was not necessary.
She was killed when it went out.
No! Wait there!
You said that someone me heard
with It to Had begun to have a beard in the entry...
They heard him speaking with her.
And to pretend that it was obtaining answer
and he was speaking again.
It is an ancient, expensive trick of mine.
Good Lord! it is not true.
I need of asking for him
what accompanies me even to the squad.
Good Lord!
- Favor is done.
- Say.
- I can speak with you. Plenderleith?
- It could, if she was.
- It played golf.
- Golf?
Between. And to think that you. Allen
it still lies frozen in that morgue.
It is true.
Is this very painful, Sra...?
- Pierce, darling.
- My name is Hercule Poirot.
Oh, already I heard of you.
I am very much flattered.
Mrs. Pierce, I am with a problem...
- Do not say.
- I came here yesterday with the Inspector Japp
and we forget of looking for traces
in a specific siege of the house.
- It will be that it might...
- Between, make itself at home.
It is very kind.
Thank you.
My old man is going to be green with envy
when he will know that it was here.
- It is always reading it in the newspapers.
- It is very kind.
- Do I can?
- Clear, continue!
It was offering soon a drink,
he was going to talk about the nonsenses in the newspapers...
Mrs. Pierce,
it is where that the Beauty queen Plenderleith
does it usually play golf?
He is sure that this is allowed,
Captain Hastings?
The name of Poirot is feared in
any golf course of the continent.
- Has not it been certifying of handicap?
- No, no. I am well.
There had to be somewhere a hole
for where to throw the ball...
Does he see that flag?
No.
- In front of the big tree ... I redden.
- I am seeing!
- It is where the hole is.
- No...
We wait.
Promptly. Only it has to beat him with this.
Go.
- Can I be right in the flag?
- Yes, it is not important.
It does not look to me
what is going to be right in the flag.
Little luck!
With so many shots of every time,
we do not catch the Beauty queen Plenderleith!
It is not possible.
She began that there is hour and a half.
We can see it to the turn
in the parallel holes.
It was liking what was stopping
of rummaging through the garbage.
- More not!
- Number three, Hastings!
Someone is having a bad day.
It is normal cues leave.
- Three cues in three holes?
- Well then?
The Beauty queen Plenderleith
it is being free of the cues
in a siege where it was judging
what nobody would notice.
Major Eustace is not blamed,
Hastings.
- Did it lose the ball again?
- Be hidden!
See.
We already saw the sufficient thing.
We will leave
this so interesting play
and to phone to an Inspector Japp.
Because there would be a normal young person
of throwing an expensive suitcase for a lake
with only two magazines and stones
to guarantee what was sunk?
Do not be preoccupied any more.
We already have the answer.
And why to leave
a set of perfect cues?
I am not going to lie they.
I passed the night woken thinking.
My poor person Japp.
- The Beauty queen Plenderleith.
- Thank you, Beauty queen Lemon.
Excuse the delay.
I had just come from the funeral one of the Pipe.
It was very kind in having come.
One feels, please.
- I have news for you.
- I read in the newspaper.
Major Eustace was imprisoned.
Was always it a murder?
Yes. The destruction of a human being
for work of other.
And now I am going to say to him
since I reached the truth.
He has his methods.
I do not contradict it.
To begin,
the smell of the smoke of cigarette.
- What I did not smell.
- Precisely!
And however the ashtray
it had at least nine cigarettes.
It was strange what the room was smelling
as fresh as it was smelling.
Then it was that!
Then it was the watch
what the dead woman was using.
- Are it what what had?
- It was in the right wrist.
For my experience,
it is more worn-out in the left wrist.
But now, my men
we go to the part of the writing.
It was already to the wait.
The block of letter was how
one had not written in him.
To Pipe it did not write anything in this day,
therefore the leaf was clean.
It had, yes. Freddie saw it
to go to the mail in this day to 18:00.
Very well, Hastings!
Then what happened to the leaf
where she had written the letters?
But there was another curious detail
about the writing desk.
Perhaps one remembers, Japp,
of the arrangement of the things?
Allow me.
Paint and block of letter to the centre,
inkwell on the left,
calendar
and pen of feather on the right.
- Eh bien!
- Yes?
Is not he seeing?
The inkwell was on the left.
Is not it more common to be on the right?
More to the hand of the right hand?
Then I imagined the next thing, Japp.
I imagined the Beauty queen Plenderleith
reaching house after weekend.
I saw it reaching house
and finding the friend
lying in the ground
with the pistol in the hand.
In the left hand, clear.
She was left-handed.
In spite of the Beauty queen Plenderleith
in trying to convince otherwise.
Also there was a note gone to you.
For right, a very moving letter,
on a young victim of blackmail,
what took it committing suicide.
I think that it robbed the idea
in the same instant.
He will be punished!
It withdraws the note and the leaf in the top
of the block of letter.
Go down the staircase, it lights the bonfire,
and it launches them to the flames.
It takes the ashtray to the room,
simulating the conversation
of two persons.
It has a blow of luck.
It discovers
a bit of the button of fist in the room.
It takes it also to the room.
And wait that that puts the question in order.
It takes from him the pistol of the left hand.
Clean it and it places it in the left hand.
Lock the window and it closes the door.
There must not be tracks
of what you altered things in the room.
And it was so.
It was very intelligent, mademoiselle.
A very intelligent murder.
So it was that that it the question was...
Of the attempt of murder
of Major Eustace.
It was not a murder...
It was a justice!
That man pursued to Pipe
even to the death! Poor girl ...!
Completely because she became involved with one
man married in India and it had a baby.
When the child died,
it returned for England.
It knew it Chatter
and he fell in love with him...
One has no idea why, pompous that one...
And then that swindler of Eustace
he returns of India.
There was read the letter what it links it wrote to me,
it was realizing because I did what I did.
She was loving it Chatter, it wrote it.
He was not managing to live without him.
But for his good,
he was not going to marry with him.
It was going to take the most right decision.
It would of read that letter!
And still call him a murder!
And it was a murder! The man
what it tried to incriminate, is in the prison.
Want even I destroyed it?
It wants to destroy even the life...
the mind...
... of a human being?
No ... I do not want.
He was liking wanting, I do not want them to myself.
It is not possible!
Disguised suicide of murder
and not the opposite.
And quite thought.
Not too at all affected.
Wait there!
Then and the suitcase? And the cues?
They were of the Mrs. Allen. Jane
Plenderleith was having to convince us
what his friendly skilful era
to believe in murder.
- But the cues were for stubs!
- Clear!
When she opened the cupboard... It tried
at what we were looking for another object...
It used the suitcase like...
How he calls himself? How I bait?
- To throw off the scent.
- That itself!
And now, my friends,
it is a height of we go to have lunch.
Translation and Legendagem
Maria John Santos / CRISTBET, Lda.
Synchronized and Revised for: Chicharro [NaN]