Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
POIROT
The ADVENTURE OF JOHNNIE WAVERLY
- 50.000 Pounds?
- Yes.
- The last letter was saying 30.000.
- And the previous one was asking 25.000.
You did not tell me that there was more.
I did not take them to serious.
Rays, Add, we are in England!
Here children are not kidnapped!
Go, car, one more effort.
When it took care, mother, it looks at the car.
- Beauty queen Lemon?
- Yes, Mr. Poirot?
They are almost 11:00H.
- I need the tisane punctually.
- Clear, Mr. Poirot.
It is already almost ended,
my system.
All his successful cases
and with crossed references,
in five different forms.
- Five?
- Yes.
Here, witnesses' names.
Here, criminals' names.
Activity or profession
of the victim, type of case.
Kidnapping, dependence,
adultery,
to consult also " marriage ".
Bigamy, to consult " marriage ",
bombs...
To consult in " marriage ".
You. Waverly is here
to speak with you.
- Monsieur Waverly, good morning.
- How it has been passing?
Thank you, Beauty queen Lemon.
It can keep on filing things.
Beauty queen Lemon dreams with
the perfect system of filing,
what it will leave backwards
all the other systems.
This morning,
it is ready doing an innovation.
Call, which brings it consulting
Hercule Poirot?
- I was accepted.
- Acceptance?
In It Reads Mans. one remembers
that I applied the Lagonda?
I received the form of inscription,
I do not realize them to myself anything.
- What entusiasmante!
- The Branston also has a Lagonda.
- Did you already participate in races?
- Not, in fact, not.
- Who is with the Poirot?
- Such a Mr. Waverly. It is a case.
This morning I received this.
" He did not pay. His son him will be
taken away ás 12:00H of tomorrow,
" day 29. His redemption
it will cost to him 50 thousand pounds. "
- 50 thousand?
- What impertinence!
You dispose of 50 thousand pounds,
Monsieur, Waverly?
Well, I dare saying
that I can bring together them.
I understand.
- Does it think even that they will kidnap it?
- Clear! I have not because to doubt.
Holy God!
I introduce to him the Captain Hastings,
my partner. You. Waverly, a client.
Pleasure.
You. Waverly received letters
in what they threaten to kidnap the son.
To serious? In England?
He can be a group of foreigners.
These letters do not charge
that the author is foreign.
- It suspects someone, Mr. Waverly?
- Saint Deus, no.
- Is not it a target of resentments?
- I find that not. No.
Very well. Poirot will intervene.
It already showed this letter
to the Scotland Yard?
No, I came straightly for here.
It does not advance anything.
- They never appeared interested.
- I understand what it feels.
But now we will will speak again
with the Inspector-chief Japp.
I do not want to be much time
far from house.
I delay five minutes, at most,
packing
and we will catch the near train
after speaking with the Inspector.
- I can take you.
- No, I do not want to bother it.
He needs of going round.
It does not the question be a dog.
We are there this afternoon.
Beauty queen Lemon, we are going to be out
up to tomorrow. Guard the castle.
The Inspector-chief Japp
it is going to receive them, gentlemen.
- It prays well...
- Good morning, Inspector-chief.
But what unexpected pleasure,
Mr. Poirot. Mr. Waverly.
You. Waverly received another letter.
He thinks that the Police officer is not
convinced about the gravity of the case.
Therefore did it resort to you, Poirot?
You. Waverly is a man
of discernment and intelligence.
- Perhaps the case is serious.
- Billet what yes?
I think that preventing is better
of what to put right, Inspector-chief.
It is right, Mr. Poirot,
if we had many people operational.
We have hundreds of these cases all
the days. If we were investigating all...
Hundreds, Inspector-chief?
Well, he would not say hundreds,
it is not possible to take everything literally.
- Every day?
- At least, every week.
It the question is a discontented employee,
an envious neighbor.
- We are wasting time, Mr. Poirot.
- It is not necessary to be hurt.
I am a rural nobleman. I pay mine
imposed and I wait for something in exchange.
- Now I know that it is not of use.
- There are many taxpayers.
There are also many rural noblemen.
If we...
Not only it does not cooperate,
since it also is very offensive.
Since you highlighted, you pay to me
to exercise my discernment
as for what it can threaten
the public order and this does not threaten.
- His superior will know of this.
- What I amuse so much all that.
- That police officer is a fool.
- No, the Japp is a good police officer.
The police officers cannot prevent.
An agent would be necessary for
always to accompany each citizen.
Fortunately for the human race,
most of us have a police officer here.
This kidnapper has not any police officer.
Thank you.
C'est magnifies.
This is the new house. It was built
for an ancestor of mine in 1 760,
when the old mansion
it was destroyed by a fire.
Is it increasing the work of his relative?
No, we began a restoration
there are five years.
We would stop,
I wait for them to myself to retake it soon.
From there are 400 years
what my family here survives.
- And is this land completely his?
- No, already it is not.
It was already, how far the sight was reaching.
But it is already not.
- Marcus, you returned!
- Hello. This is you. Hercules Poirot.
Enchantee, Lady. Hercule.
' - Say?
- And Hercule and not Hercules.
- Yes. He is the famous detective.
- I know.
Just as well what came, Mr. Poirot.
We did not know to whom resorting.
The Police officer does not do anything.
We will pay the peace of spirit
with our money.
But the Captain said to me
what his honorary are reasonable.
- Oh yes?
- I did not specify anything.
It arrived quite fast.
I delayed 75 minutes.
I reached 120 km for hour.
The Captain Hastings
it is delirious with cars.
It had the kindness to talk to me
of the race in which it is going to participate.
This subject is serious, Hastings.
We cannot amuse oneself.
The question of the kidnapping?
I spoke with you. Waverly on that.
We should not have worried.
The letters are a work of a crazy one.
I am more calm, Hastings.
Thank you.
But let's not put the car
at the front of the oxen. I am going to see the house.
Do favor.
This is the living room.
It gives for the terrace
through these carried ones.
- Is this the south side of the house?
- Exactamente.
- And does this division give for where?
- For the library.
Bon.
Thank you, Mr. Poirot. Thank you.
Everything will run well, Lady.
- The kidnapping is an easy crime.
- Easy?
Clear!
The child could have been kidnapped
in any height since it was born.
- There are four years.
- And of what that advances us?
On the contrary,
it advances us very much. It does not even imagine.
Because it will be
that the kidnappers make difficult the kidnapping
warning the family?
Some cases are simple,
someone are trés complicate.
But they all are interesting,
so they all depend on the character
of the intervenient ones.
Clear.
Excuse, it costs to me to speak normally
I eat if tomorrow...
He is ready went to sleep,
Mrs. Waverly. dismisses you, Johnnie.
- This is the famous Johnnie Waverly.
- Good night, I adopt.
- My car.
- What rich machine.
Is he seeing, Hastings?
Another enthusiast.
- It comes to ensconce myself in the bed.
- I do not delay anything, love.
- Thank you, Mrs. Withers.
- Good night.
Good night.
Darling!
Promptly, wanted. It is going to run everything well.
Clear what everything is going to run well.
Tomorrow, to I halve it,
the Johnnie will be gone by friends,
for his mother, his father, Hastings...
... for Poirot!
Nobody will kidnap the Johnnie Waverly.
She is my wife, it is ill.
It woke up with intestinal cramps.
The doctor is already with her.
- Cramps?
- It is necessary to have been something that she ate.
- I lament.
- Excuse if we woke it.
Bonjour, mon ami.
Did it sleep well?
Best.
Excellent. Now we are going to taste
the famous English breakfast.
One serves.
- What he is eating, Hastings?
- I think that he is " Kedgeree ".
It is a rice, nothing has them to me any more.
But, Hastings, who is done
of the famous English breakfast?
Did not it notice the dinner of yesterday?
A small potato for each one.
- A chop...
- But the English dinners are so.
- But the breakfast...
- Will it be that they are badly of finances?
They did not light the hearth
last night in my room.
Call them to all!
lmediatamente!
- All of them, Tredwell!
- Certainly.
- Good morning.
- Bonjour, Monsieur Waverly.
- How his wife is?
- Be still weak, it is not going to get up.
But I have worse news.
See.
In my room itself!
I had a bath,
I did not delay any more than ten minutes.
While returning, it had that in the cushion.
- Only two words: " To I halve it. "
- But that it barks!
Precisely!
One of my employees
he is a traitor.
- But I know how to take revenge.
- What it intends to do?
I am going to dismiss them, to all they!
Unless one of them is accused.
The Tredwell will be, it works here
since my childhood.
- As well as Beauty queen Collins.
- Beauty queen Collins?
The secretary of my wife,
it is of confidence.
Skies, I do not support traitors!
- The people is brought together.
- Thank you, Tredwell.
Mr. Waverly,
I ask him to reconsider.
The more it discharges the house it will be,
better the scoundrel will be moved.
Stupidities.
Do his work and I do mine
and everything will run well.
But to empty the house
some hours before the kidnapping
it is an illogical attitude.
How does it dare?
Is it calling me crazy?
I do what I consider to be better
to defend my son.
- Allow me to value that.
- I cannot obstruct it.
It is right.
This is obstinate, Hastings.
Mon Dieu! The surprises do not cease.
The Inspector-chief Japp.
- Did it change of ideas, Inspector?
- Yes, one can say that yes.
Or he can call oneself
what a worried amateur did not want to see.
It is very kind, an Inspector-chief.
His heart will be his disgrace.
It is true. Call,
where the simple rural nobleman is?
It is in the hall,
dismissing the employees.
Skies.
Did it wake up with the feet out of the bed?
Perhaps. Bonne chance!
One of you is responsible.
I am waiting for an answer.
Then? I am to the wait.
- Do not go very fast.
- No, I do not pass of the 80.
- Kilometers?
- Miles.
Happen what will happen,
we will return ás 12:00H.
- I will not be treated in this way!
- There is any more nothing saying.
There is still very much to say it,
Mr. Waverly. I not...
Pack and Beauty queen Collins
he will pay to him his salary.
- And what the Johnnie says to?
- He does not say anything to him.
He now is with Beauty queen Collins.
It is dispensed, Mrs. Withers.
- What it does here?
- Good morning, Mr. Waverly.
It brought some agents with me.
Does it allow to me that it spreads them for the house?
It walked recovering
the mansion of Waverly?
We will return soon,
according to him he says to me.
Only I believe when he will see.
She does not mind very much the house.
- Oh yes?
- No.
For her, the house can fall of rotten one.
It is her that has money,
but for her conduct, it is not noticed.
I want an agent in the way
what is going to give to the cowsheds.
Beacher, for the cowsheds.
- One near the principal entry.
- Osborne, in the principal entry.
- Two in the perimeter.
- George, Smith.
- Someone here near...
- Quarters of the employees.
- And scrambled eggs?
- Clear! And small sausages?
- Yes, clear.
- Seasoned kidneys?
Kidneys, yes. And bacon?
- Estaladiço?
- Clear. And tea?
- Or a beautiful beer?
- Beer? To the breakfast?
- Two mugs, please.
- We will return ás 12:00H.
We have much time.
Certainly, men.
But what admirable young person.
Hastings, the restoration
of Waverly it is going to continue.
I did not trust the builder.
It seems to me that it does not like the Waverly.
Perhaps.
Very well!
The Johnnie will keep me
and you are a joined ás you keep at the window.
- The best.
- The Poirot is near that door.
I do not know if it does well.
If there will be physical confrontation,
you. Poirot is not the best choice.
It works well with the brain,
but badly with the body...
- And his colleague, Hastings?
- So it is well.
Does he know what I think?
I think that they touched the car.
They touched the car
to be released of us.
Since the fact is that they knew
that we were going to use the car?
When it took care. With knack, Johnnie.
It makes him festive very slowly.
She likes.
She likes you.
- How you are now, wanted?
- I am much better.
It is necessary to have been something that I ate.
Let you be in the bed, it rests.
I am going to take the Johnnie down.
- Because it cannot be here?
- Down there he is better.
Beauty queen Collins keeps you.
- Goodbye, wanted.
- We go.
- Does not it need even me?
- No, keep my wife.
- During half an hour only.
- Goodbye, mother.
Goodbye.
- Well, it is not the carburator.
- It is not that that I want to hear.
I want to know what it is
and not what is not.
Better still,
I want to hear the motor!
Whistle two times
if someone will be captured.
- Are they all in his positions?
- Yes.
- Where the Poirot hid?
- They went out from car when I arrived.
Sergeant,
maintain the agents in alert.
Of car? Does he know for where they were?
They did not say to me, unfortunately.
We caught it!
It was in the middle of the shrubs.
It had the whole material with him.
See, Inspector.
- Does it know this man?
- I never saw it before.
What beautiful order.
A bottle of chloroform, cotton,
and an addressed letter
to you, Mr. Waverly.
I do not know of anything,
they asked for me to hand over him.
- Who?
- A man.
A man whom I found,
on the road.
" He must have paid. The redemption
of his son thousand starts to belong of 70.
" In spite of his precautions,
he was kidnapped ás 12:00H of the day 29,
" such as I promised. "
Must he have paid? It finds what can...
Johnnie.
I halve it!
Mon Dieu! What a pain!
Is it going to do anything or not?
When the height to arrive,
the Poirot will act.
But what problemazinho pleasant.
Obscure and enchanting.
We were deceived
thanks to an advanced clock.
Pleasant? Enchanting?
My son was kidnapped!
Yes, me them he is well.
Rest, these scoundrels
they are going to treat very well him.
He is not, for them,
the hen of the golden eggs?
Nobody knows the car.
I gave the description to the Police officer of Surrey,
but he must have exchanged of car.
- Or then it was for in far.
- And is it it brutal what got a beating?
One calls Joe Rogers, according to him.
It maintains his version of the history.
Perhaps the Poirot manages to convince.
With all the respect, if mine
agents him did not go round...
Poirot is going to act.
Captain Hastings,
is the vehicle repaired?
It had no petrol, imagine.
The indicator is damaged.
- We have work. The kid was kidnapped.
- I know, one of the agents told me.
- Bonjour, Monsieur Rogers.
- Look there!
He is greeting it,
his ignorant one.
Tell to me again his history.
Since the fact is that the order
did it him come to stop ás hands?
I already told everything to him.
- But tell me to me.
- Well, it was handed over me by a so-and-so.
- Oh yes?
- Was not it what I said?
And what the so-and-so said to him?
I called myself to hand over the order
at the big home.
In the side door, he said.
It gave me a note of a shilling.
I called myself to hand over it
to 11:50H, in point.
He knows to what hours
did it meet with him?
By chance even I know. They were 10:15H.
And does it manage to describe it?
He had something of stranger.
It was not high, it was of my size.
- And it had " ears ".
- "Do" you "ear"?
Moustache.
And it was bringing a grey uniform,
with gaiters and a hat.
Like a driver?
- Which age did he have?
- I do not know.
But it is curious,
it had a very strange voice.
He knows this type that walks thereabouts
put on as morning suit?
- It of erect nose?
- Erect nose? Morning suit?
Yes, is he a butler?
Well, he had a son,
it would be the accomplished face
of this so-and-so whom I found.
- Like the son of the Mr. Tredwell!
- Do not be filled with enthusiasm, Poirot.
The Tredwell was with you. Waverly
between them 10:00H and them 10:30H.
- You. Waverly it already confirmed me.
- But will it be that he has a son?
Then there will be another explanation.
Thank you, Mr. Japp.
It was of extreme usefulness.
- And you also, Mr. Rogers.
- Well, very much thank you.
Leave there that, man,
I am going to take it to the local squad.
- Accused of what?
- Begging.
- It cannot, I have a shilling.
- Say that to a magistrate.
We go.
I am going for London to organize the search.
The answer is here, I make friends,
it is not in London.
It can be, Mr. Poirot,
but the boy is in London.
Of that I am sure.
To pass well.
Mr. Tredwell, between.
Between and one feels.
- I prefer to be in foot, already now.
- Clear.
- Work here there are many years?
- There is 30.
I began for bass.
In this time, there was more personal.
If someone knows the secrets
of the family, this someone is you.
I guarantee him that this family
it has no secrets.
- Clear what not.
- You. Waverly is very correct.
- Such as his father.
- Clear.
And Lady Waverly?
Do they have a happy marriage?
Certainly,
she is the best woman.
It is right that it did alterations.
She was not educated in this environment,
in spite of being a rich woman.
It is true.
I find them to myself what begins to value
to this way of life.
Beauty queen Collins,
talk to me about the nursemaid of the boy.
- It was here there are six months.
- Was it of confidence?
Of extreme confidence, I deduct.
Me them she was already not here
in the height of the kidnapping.
It is true, it is right.
But it could have accomplices at the home.
She had a stronger friendship
with another employee?
I do not do idea.
I do not take notice of gossip, he knows.
Clear, it was not intending to suggest...
Excuse,
he did not know that they here were still.
It does not do badly, we were finishing.
Beauty queen Collins.
- Is he sure?
- Yes. Very much thank you.
Merci, Mademoiselle.
- Did it discover anything?
- And you?
- You. Tredwell said to me great thing.
- Well then?
- Only I do not understand a thing.
- I do not understand anything.
No, my friend, is simple.
Only there is a detail.
The child was here,
it was in this division,
watched by the father
and for the Inspector-chief Japp.
The false alarm was given
and the Inspector and the Waverly
they went out irreflectidamente,
leaving the undefended child.
Truth?
- Yes.
- Bon.
The kidnapper enters and takes the child.
- For where?
- I do not understand.
They could not go out this way.
The Inspector and the Waverly had gone out
and a police officer was still
her around 20 meters from here.
This way, yes.
But for where it would follow?
The entry of the house was watched,
as well as the rears.
The Rogers was caught from this side
of the house and the agitation it was reigning.
- Is it a problem, no?
- I am understanding.
- The tunnel.
- Comment?
- Which tunnel?
Many catholics' houses
they had passages for priests.
The men were used when
of the King they were looking for the priests.
Where it is the tunnel?
Sacre bleu!
- Where is it going to give?
- To the mausoleum, to 1 km from here.
I need a lampe of poche.
How he calls himself? A battery?
- Lantern of pocket?
- A lantern!
- I have one in the car.
- Bon.
- Who knows of the existence of this?
- I do not know for certain.
Some persons whom they visited
the house, but especially relatives.
- I understand. And the employees?
- One or two, perhaps.
- Beauty queen Collins?
- No, I am sure.
- And the Tredwell?
- Must know, live already here there has much.
- The nursemaid of the child, you. Withers?
- I find that not. No.
- Take, one for each one.
- The best.
Captain, we are going to start
a travel for the darkness.
- I go with you.
- No, we go alone.
It has a few staircases.
In front, mon brave.
- Say, which conclusions it takes away?
- About the darkness I do not manage to think.
But it is in the darkness that the cells
grey better they work.
We always return to the same question.
Because it are what the kidnapper warned
the family?
It was counting to be paid
without kidnap the child.
That does not alter the fact
of what they made difficult a simple thing.
If they did not specify
an hour and a date,
it would be easy the opportunity waits
of taking the child
when she was with the nursemaid.
I find that yes.
I already see light there to the front.
The best. I am full of this tunnel.
Snooper. Very funny.
The car could wait here.
It is already removed of the house.
They could bring the child
for the tunnel even to the car.
The driver whistles
while it comes to the house.
Everything does not pass of a farce!
Everything indicates that there was an accomplice
inside the house.
- The poisoning of the Mrs. Waverly...
- Poisoning?
My poor person Hastings!
And so innocent.
No, it is touching.
It finds them to me same
what was acidentalmente
what you. Waverly was dispatched
in the day of the kidnapping?
- Saint Deus!
- Second question...
Someone of the house put the message
in the cushion of the Waverly.
- Yes, it does sense.
- Third question...
Advancing the clock ten minutes.
Completely done by someone from the house.
There were four persons at the home.
You. Waverly and Beauty queen Collins
they are out of question.
The wife was...
How he calls himself alite?
Arranged in layers, is it that?
It was accompanied by Beauty queen Collins.
- They remain you. Waverly and the Tredwell.
- It is true.
Hastings,
I am already full of this case.
From here to 40 minutes it breaks a train
for London.
- I take it the London...
- No, Hastings, I go of train.
Where does it go?
The Captain volunteered
to take me to the station.
- Then I follow to London.
- And the case? My son?
- It did not do anything!
- On the contrary, already I did everything.
Then, where he is?
I am going to give him the address.
- The leaf is blank.
- I wait what writes the address.
It is going to take me to me and to a Captain
even next to the boy. Now.
Opposite case, his wife
it will be informed of the events
what compose this ignoble crime.
He is well.
- It is treated well.
- Of that I have no doubts.
Jessie!
Father!
The nursemaid of the Johnnie, is clear. Clear!
- She is the daughter of the Mr. Tredwell?
- Niece.
His skill will allow him
to explain the appearance of the boy.
It was not found what, in the bottom,
he is a good father,
it would not be disposed
giving him another opportunity.
I do everything to avoid a scandal.
Precisely.
It is the appearances that count.
Therefore his wife did not tolerate what
it was stopping the restoration of the house.
To have a rich wife
there is not the same thing as to be rich.
Do not be preoccupied.
- I learnt my lesson.
- The best.
It has an ancient and honest name.
Does not put it again at risk.
Then I send to him my count.
We go, Captain Hastings.
Tell to me the secret.
It is how what it discovered?
It was obvious.
Who dismissed the employees?
Who could write the messages?
To drug the wife?
Who could advance the clock?
Who could give an alibi
to his loyal servant, the Tredwell?
Tredwell never liked the mistress,
but it is dedicated to a Mr. Waverly.
Be three wrapped ones:
the Waverly, the Tredwell and the niece,
to Jessie Withers,
what was noisily a farewell,
in way to arrange
a maneuver of amusement, the Rogers,
and then to take the kid of the mausoleum
up to a house in the middle of the forest.
It was obvious, Hastings.
We are in London.
Does not it want to come with me?
Hastings, the train has an advantage
on the cars.
It is not left without coal.
Translation and Legendagem
Maria Ferreira / CRlSTBET LDA.
Synchronized and Revised for: Chicharro [NaN]