Shit!
My name is Walter Blanco.
You can find my personal
details in my wallet.
You'll find my ID there.
To all law-enforcement entities,
this video
is not an admission of guilt.
I'm speaking to my family now.
Honey...
You're the love of my life.
You know that.
Walter Junior... champion...
I'm very proud of you.
You'll come to learn some things
in the next few days...
that may seem very strange.
They'll seem very bad.
But believe me.
I'm doing this for you.
I love you with all my heart.
Goodbye.
- Happy birthday!
- Thanks!
What's this?
It's veggie bacon.
It's zero cholesterol.
My love,
what time will you be home?
I'll go from school
to that other place.
I'll stay the usual four hours.
I'll be back by 6.
Don't work overtime for free anymore,
please.
That job only helps
us to make ends meet.
- That's it.
- I know. Give me your glass.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
Here.
Happy birthday, Walter.
Thank you!
I thought you had forgotten.
Did you take a shower,
young man?
Yes, but very fast.
The water was too cold.
The heater is failing again.
But water isn't cold. It's warm.
You can take a shower.
It's too cold to me.
Did you take the
cough syrup I made?
Yes. In fact, I'm much better.
- What's this pod?
- It isn't a pod?
It's veggie bacon.
It's zero cholesterol.
I want real bacon.
I'm growing up.
But we'll give it a chance.
- Mom!
- We have nothing to lose.
- Mom, the taste...
- Junior? Junior.
Eat it.
Don't be mean with your mother.
It's very tasty.
¿Y qué, Walter?
¿Qué se siente ya estar cuchito?
How does it feel
to be a smart-ass?
It's disgusting.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes, dad.
Hurry up or you'll be late.
- I'm not the only one!
- I have an excuse!
See you.
Lock the car!
Chemistry!
It is the study of what?
Salazar?
Chemicals.
No. Well, technically, chemistry
is the study of matter.
But I prefer to
see it as the study
of change in matter.
That's what it's about.
Just think about this.
Electrons change their orbits.
Molecules change their bonds.
Elements combine and change.
They change into compounds.
Well,
that's how everything in life works.
It's a constant cycle of
solution and dissolution.
Over and over again.
It is growth, then decay,
and then transformation.
It is fascinating, really.
Mr. Giraldo, I remind you
that cell phones are
not allowed in class!
Go back to your place, please.
Ionic bonds.
Are you done?
Ionic bonds. Chapter six.
Two, four,
six... Ten makes fifty.
Thank you.
He's drunk again,
and he won't come back to work.
You have to replace him, Walter.
No! No, no, Ramiro, please!
Wow!
I'll run the register.
Ramiro,
we talked about this many times.
- I'm not here to...
- What am I going to do, Walter?
What am I going to do?
We should all cooperate!
What's up, Mr. Blanco?
Hey, look who's here!
I'll take a picture, okay?
- Smile.
- You can't imagine
what I'm seeing.
Mr. Blanco is
cleaning Diego's car.
- Let's leave him a tip.
- I'll tell you later.
what's going on. Bye!
- Hello!
- Surprise!
Ayayayayay!
Happy birthday, my love!
Where were you?
They've been
waiting for a long time.
- You look awesome!
Thanks.
Your pregnant belly
hasn't shown yet.
Yes, it has.
She looks like a balloon.
Have you met my sister María?
- No. Hi.
- Hi, María.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
If you ask me which
one I would choose?
A 9 mm or this one?
I'd undoubtedly choose this one.
But this gun needs very strong
bases because this
gun tends to recoil,
to kick back.
Unless you want to repeat
your uncle's experience.
It almost hit him in the balls.
- You're right!
- It's all true.
- I'm sorry. Henry.
- What's up?
Isn't it dangerous to have a gun
with Junior around?
Pal, it isn't loaded.
Nobody will blow his
brains out because of me.
Come on, check it out.
Take it. How does it feel?
- It's great, - It is, isn't it?
Come on.
Check this out.
What do you want?
Do you want to feel it?
Take it. Take it.
Do it. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
So?
It's heavy, isn't it?
Sure!
That's why they hire men.
Come on. Hold it tight.
This isn't a piece of china.
Hold it tight like a man.
Put the finger up there.
And the other hand, here.
Well done.
Hey, it's not going to bite you.
Ready?
Everybody, listen up.
Come here, family.
I'm giving a toast to my brother-in-law,
Walter.
We all know that Walter has
one of the brightest
brains in the whole world.
But we're not holding
that against you.
No, that isn't true.
Let's give a toast...
because Walter
has a big heart, doesn't he?
Where is it?
Where's your heart?
Cheers!
To Walter! Cheers!
My love. Turn on the TV.
I'll appear on the news.
The Police
Anti-narcotics Department
dealt a harsh blow to
the newly-formed chain
of methamphetamine
production in Colombia.
¿Metanfetamina?
What's that?
Is it like cocaine
and marijuana?
No, no, no.
It's a new drug.
It started in the USA,
but now it's strong in Mexico.
Then why it is here, too?
We love to imitate the gringos.
Currently, Colombian people are
beginning to produce that drug.
We ask for the contribution
of all the citizens--
Henry, that's a lot of money,
isn't it?
How much is it?
There are 120 million pesos
and 100 thousand dollars.
Are there dollars, too?
Of course!
Mexicans control the business.
That's why we use dollars.
It's interesting, isn't it?
Walter, come here.
You can join me in an operation
whenever you want to.
Get a little
excitement in your life.
You didn't look ten
pounds fatter on TV.
Thank you, my love.
You looked twenty pounds fatter.
What are you doing?
I'm checking the accounts
of the brownie business.
We grew ten per cent this month.
It isn't much more money, but...
Let's take it step by step.
What do you mean it isn't much?
It's very good.
Hey, birthday boy.
I haven't given you my present.
Really?
Don't you want to do it?
Yes. Yes.
I'm thinking of... I
fear for the baby.
No,
let's leave the baby out of it.
Relax and enjoy.
- Really?
- Really.
What's up for Saturday?
Ehmm... Car wash in the morning.
And I was thinking of
going to a science exhibit.
Won't you paint the baby's room?
Of course.
But we still have time
until the baby is born,
so-- Yes, my love.
But if we leave everything
for the last minute,
we'll end up in chaos.
Está bien, yo pinto.
Thank you.
It won't come up, will it?
No.
Good afternoon.
This is for you.
Thanks.
This is so embarrassing.
I'm-- I am fine, honestly.
Don't make such a big deal.
It isn't worth it.
Hey, listen,
can you do me a favor?
Can you just drop me off
at a corner somewhere?
I'm fine.
I'm fine, honestly.
No, sorry.
My insurance isn't the best o--
Take a couple of
deep breaths for me.
Is there anybody you
want me to contact for you?
No.
Lean forward for me, would you?
Mr. Blanco, are you a smoker?
No, I have never smoked.
Why?
Mr. Blanco?
Walter? Walter?
Walter, did you understand
what I've just said to you?
Yes. Lung cancer.
Inoperable.
I'm sorry to insist.
I just need to make
sure you fully understand.
Best-case scenario,
with chemo, you'll live maybe
another couple years.
It's just...
There something on your lapel.
Is it mustard?
My records show
that I paid for it.
I don't owe anything.
Okay.
Well, I'll check with the bank.
Okay. Thanks.
- Hi.
Did you use the
credit card last month?
Thirty thousand
pesos in one payment?
Yes. I needed printer ink.
And did you use the credit card?
Remember it's only
for emergencies.
Okay. I won't do it again.
So how was your day?
It was...
I don't know.
Fine. It was fine.
Walter, there're a lot of
cars, and I'm shorthanded.
I need you to be washing cars.
- What?
- Wash the cars!
You've been standing
there the whole morning!
Are you here to work,
or to stare at the cabinet?
- Go!
- Leave me alone, Ramiro.
What?
- Fuck you!
- You won't-- Fuck you!
I said fuck you,
and all your shit!
I hate your job!
And I hate you
and your damn cap!
And do you know what?
Why don't you wash these?
Wash these!
Hello. Henry?
This is Walter.
I'm sorry for the time.
I've been thinking about
that offer you made me
of taking me to an operation,
remember?
That's the house,
with the colorful windows.
- Green, coffee... What?
- Mahogany.
That color is mahogany.
- Mahogany, don't be silly.
What do you mean?
Are you interior decorator?
Be careful.
That's how they all begin.
And then you end up
using mahogany high hells.
That you don't have a dictionary
doesn't mean words don't exist.
That color is called "mahogany."
Do you want me to tell
you the words that I know?
I can tell you a lot of words,
Gómez.
I don't do it out of
respect for my guest.
Henry,
how do you know there's a meth lab there?
We have an informer.
Do you remember I
told you the Mexicans
are in charge of the business?
The cook has to be Mexican.
Or gringo.
We found a gringo cooking, too.
We found a gringo cooking!
There also are gringos.
I got fifty thousands
that he's a beaner.
Fifty thousand that he's gringo.
Fifty thousand.
What if he's Colombian?
No. Colombians don't know how to make meth,
yet.
At least not alone.
We found one who added coffee.
Coffee to add a personal touch.
"Espresso," they call him.
Chemically,
it doesn't make any difference.
It doesn't make any difference
because they aren't good at it.
They still have a lot to
learn from the Mexicans.
Or the gringos.
Hey, Henry,
how do they produce it?
Here,
they produce paste or powder.
They don't produce crystal,
which is the best.
That's what they want.
They want to produce crystal,
but they couldn't yet.
Do you know why they work here?
Because they know
this is the preferred place
for foreigners who come to...
- Do you understand? Do you?
- Yes. Yes.
There's the bus.
There it comes.
Gómez,
let's wait until the girl gets off the bus.
Yes.
Ready?
Let's do it!
Hold on.
[screeching
Walter,
these labs are very dangerous.
You mix it wrong,
and you get mustard gas.
- Phosphine gas.
No, no, no,
that's how I'd call it.
Do you know why the
use the respirators?
One sniff of that gas,
and it will kill you instantly.
It's clear.
Is the suspect foreign?
No, he's from here.
He's name is Emilio Molina.
He's the one who adds coffee.
He isn't beaner nor gringo.
- Hey! Hold on.
- What, what, what?
At least I said he
was Latin American.
- So?
Take your twenty thousand.
Don't cry. Don't think I'm bad.
- I'll buy you lunch.
- Henry. Henry, Henry.
Can I go inside and
see the actual lab?
Mm-hum. No, you can't.
We're going to
peek our heads in.
We'll check it out first,
and I'll let you know. Okay?
Don't get off if I
don't authorize you.
- Understood?
- Yes, yes.
Let's go.
José Miguel Rosas?
It's me.
I'm alone. Calm down.
How did you find me?
You're still in the
school filing system.
It's your grandmother's house,
isn't it?
Don't worry.
I'm alone, honestly.
- Nobody is looking for you,
José Miguel.
- Jose.
- Jose. They call me "Jose".
- Jose. Jose.
- Why are you here¡
- Jose, calm down.
I'm just curious.
Don't worry.
Sure. It's just...
I remember you.
You were probably
the worst student I had.
But you were financially okay.
Am I right?
You never needed money.
Not at all.
I don't understand
why you're into this.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
There's a lot of money
in the meths business, isn't it?
What?
Don't you know what
I'm talking about?
Not a clue.
It was just a coincidence
that you run away
during the operation?
I have no idea what
you're doing here.
I'll tell you something.
If you're here to
teach me a lesson
about religion or the right path
or my true calling, save it.
I finished high school
a long time ago.
Okay?
Let's do something.
Thank you for coming,
and good luck.
Go away!
Your partner was caught today,
wasn't he?
What's his name?
Emilio.
They seized the money.
The lab was dismantled.
You've got nothing.
Am I wrong?
Jose.
You know the business.
And I know the chemistry.
I'm thinking...
maybe you and I
could partner up.
Do you want to cook?
You and me?
Methamphetamines?
José Miguel, we work together or
I'll tell the police what I saw.
- How is Walter doing?
- He's fine. Why?
I don't know.
He's quieter than usual.
Well, he's just turned fifty.
It's a big deal.
I don't imagine what
I'd look like at his age.
- I still have time.
Not so much.
As long as I don't
become crazy like you.
Then, Walter is in a crisis.
No.
He's like that.
He's quiet.
- How's sex?
María!
What?
I guess the answer is that.
What's up?
Won't you help me?
Be careful.
What's this?
It's a treasure.
Look at this.
Recovery flask, 800 milliliters.
They're scant.
Erlenmeyer flask.
Look at this.
Round bottom flask,
500 milliliters.
Thermo resistant.
I cook in one of those.
In a bigger one.
This is a volumetric flask.
You wouldn't cook
in one of these.
Yes, I do.
Not anymore. This
is for general mixing
and titration.
This boiling flask
is for cooking.
Didn't you learn anything
from my chemistry class?
No.
You flunked me, remember?
No wonder.
Do you know, Mr. Blanco?
This isn't a chemistry class.
This is art.
Cooking is art.
And I'm and artist.
I cook, and I do it very well.
You can ask.
Don't come here to teach me,
okay?
What you did was shit
considering the place
where you've been doing it.
That place was a shit.
You and I will not make garbage.
We will produce a pure and
stable product, José Miguel.
Jose. My name is Jose.
What's this?
That's for protection.
Otherwise we'll have
an ambulance outside.
For your information,
the fumes of these chemicals
are toxic.
Do you know what?
You can dress up like a faggot,
an astronaut or a bullfighter.
I won't wear it.
Well,
these can't remain here more than 24 hours.
What?
We're going to cook here.
Here?
We won't cook here!
I don't shit where I eat. No.
Then where are we going to work?
You tell me.
This is your deal, isn't it?
Do it at your place.
That's what I thought.
Well... I don't know.
What if we rented one
of those warehouses.
No, it won't work.
They are far away from here.
It's ideal to do it at a
different place each time.
A big truck, or a van.
I don't know.
That's it!
That's a good idea.
- Let's prepare a truck.
- Yes, let's prepare a truck.
Where did we get the money?
Let's share the expense equally.
"Let's share the
expense equally."
I don't have any money.
The police took
almost everything.
Almost.
It means you have some.
They owe me some money, but...
But it will take time.
Thanks.
This isn't even half
of what we need.
These are the savings
of my whole life.
At least,
I'm contributing with something.
You're the drug dealer.
Negotiate. See what you can do.
Hey, wait!
Why are you doing this?
Tell me the truth.
Why are you doing it?
I'm doing it for the money,
brother.
Exactly.
No, come on, man.
A straight man like you,
who looks almost like a
priest around his sixties,
all of a sudden
decides to break bad?
- No.
- Fifty. I'm fifty.
Whatever. Fifty, sixty.
It's the same.
I'm just saying, Mr. Blanco.
If you went mad or
if you're depressed,
you have to tell me
because it affects me.
I know exactly what
we're getting into.
If you know how it works,
why are you doing it?
Because I'm finally awake.
What?
I like it.
We can look for another design.
The skinny ones
are in fashion now.
No.
Look at that! Look at that!
"Mom, please,
help me zip my trousers."
"Mom, please."
No, leave them.
Don't pay attention to them.
They aren't worth it.
He's such a silly boy.
Walter...
- What's wrong with him, mom?
- I don't know.
But don't pay attention to them.
They're very stupid.
Those look really good on you.
"Mommy, please."
"Mommy, please, help me."
What's the matter?
Can you get up by yourself?
Come on! Stand up!
Hit me!
What are you waiting for?
Or do you need your mom?
He's a son of a bitch.
What's this shit?
It's a bus.
We said an equipped truck.
This is equipped, too.
It's a school bus!
That needs to be equipped!
You know?
Why don't you take
a look before talking?
Come on.
We removed the seats
to have more room.
I have some windows sealed
to control the air inside.
These storage tanks
provide us with running water.
This tube is for fumes.
And it also has the
connections you asked for.
This is much worse
than I expected.
What did you expected
with the money you gave me?
You didn't waste my money,
did you?
Are we going to start
mistrusting each other?
This is a mess from
the very beginning!
Then why didn't
you do it yourself?
I'm doing this because
I have no choice.
So? What are we going to do?
Let's get the equipment,
and leave.
Ready!
There's nobody here.
Only a bear or a tiger
can attack us here.
A tiger?
Sure. There're tigers here,
aren't they?
Let's cook.
No. What are you doing?
Let's keep straight.
These are my good clothes.
I won't go back home
smelling like methamphetamines.
- Come on!
- After you.
Hello, my friends!
Boys and girls!
This is a new cultural, didactic
and educational program.
- Cooking with--
- What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
Let's get to work.
I have to go back home today.
Be serious or get out of here!
Mr. Blanco,
these... These are crystals
two or three inches long.
This is pure glass!
This is art!
You're an artist!
Well, actually,
it's just basic chemistry.
- But thank you.
- Basic chemistry?
You're the chef.
The best chef ever.
Everybody will want to taste it.
Do you know what?
I have to try this.
No, no, what are you doing?
We produce it, we don't use it.
Since when?
I won't argue with
you about this.
What's next?
Let's cook more.
In the meantime,
I know who will buy this.
Cat! Cat!
What's up, crazy man?
How are you?
It's a nice dog! Tough!
I had one like that.
You should teach him
to go straight to the balls.
Tell me how much you want
and leave the money there.
Listen to me.
I'm not here to buy.
I'm here to sell.
Show me.
Isn't it the finest product
you've seen in your life?
[background
barking and growling]
Try it!
Go ahead! Try it.
[background
barking and growling]
What do you think?
Aaaahhh...
- It's all right.
- It's all right?
It's all right to be
the best in the world.
What do you think?
Are you back in business?
Of course!
I have to make a living.
After all your cousin
and I went through.
Yes, it was terrible.
My cousin is caught,
and you weren't there.
No, no, no, no.
There's nothing wrong in that.
I was there
with some neighbor lady.
When I heard them,
I just reacted.
What happened, Loco?
Emilio and I are like brothers.
Your "brother"
is slightly suspicious.
He thinks you turned him in.
What?
No, that is bullshit!
Calm him down.
Tell him he's crazy.
- I'm not like that.
- Why don't you calm him down?
There's judicial strike.
They can't detain him
for more than 24 hours.
Emilio!
So what, Emilio?
- What's up?
- What?
Okay, okay, okay!
- Hey, Loco!
- You know,
Jose... You aren't that good
to cook something like this.
These are crystals.
They weren't
produced in Colombia.
Where did you get them?
I didn't know this
was a nudist area.
Someone told me that
you've been cooking
something very nice
and I want to do business.
Would you work for me?
I'd be willing to sell it to you
if the price is right.
I know this man, Loco!
He's a cop!
He was there when
the Police caught me!
- Yes or no? Yes or no?
- Run, Mr. Blanco! Run!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- No!
Loco!
I say we cap them both.
Did you really cook that?
It's a damn shame.
You had talent.
No! No, no, please!
Please, don't do it.
Let's make a deal.
Do you want to cook like me?
Let us both live,
and I'll teach you my recipe.
Can't you do it faster?
Hurry up.
Ready?
Where's the little boy?
He's tied down there.
You didn't hurt him, did you?
No, he won't die.
Put that cigarette out.
Tell him to put
the cigarette out.
I know why I say it.
Put it out.
Jose!
What happened, Mr. Blanco?
What did you do to them?
Red phosphorus in
the presence of moisture
and accelerated by heat
yields phosphorus hydride,
phosphine gas or F205 gas.
One good whiff and...
What are we going to do?
We have to clean this up.
Where were you?
Walter, I don't know what's
been going on with you lately.
Nothing. I'm fine.
Whatever it is,
I'll tell you this.
I don't like it when
you don't talk to me.
I don't like your silence.
The worst thing you
can do is shut me out.
Walter!
Walter...
Walter?