KDK-12 here, over.
Have you arrived?
Report your location.
Yes, I'm at 5km,
Verada Las Aguas.
Hey Tovar, were there people
passing through there?
Yes, somebody finally came
to visit the old women.
Ok, I'll go check it out, over.
Hello!
Doris!
Hello.
Hello, Doris.
(swarm of flies buzzing
in distance)
- Guevara?
What is it, Tovar?
Guevara, we've got a homicide.
Get over here
and bring backup, over.
Whoever is inside,
come out now!
Come out, slowly!
Show me your hands.
On your knees!
On your knees, do as I say!
Down, now!
Do as I say!
Slowly.
Hello.
I found the...
divorce papers right
where you left them,
in the crib.
Yes, well, you know best.
It's what you wanted, right?
- Anything else?
- Yes.
Do you have any thoughts about
how we're going to explain
this to Walter?
He'll always be my son.
Well, of course
he's still your son,
but what I mean is, what reason
are we going to give him
when he asks
why I want a divorce?
Well, I think he'll understand.
I mean,
I think he saw it coming.
He realized you weren't happy.
Well, of course he realized
I'm not happy!
He knows I give everyone
a fake smile.
But what are we going
to tell him?
I thought you said
it was for the best, right?
Ok, fine.
One more thing before you go.
On the child support worksheet,
you listed...
medical, dental, education,
transportation,
food, and clothing.
That's right, all of it.
Walter, no.
Cielo, you wanted me out
and I'm out.
But I will provide
for my family.
Not with that money!
You hear me?
You would be making us
your accomplices!
Answer me this,
where do you think
we got the money
to pay our bills
these last six months?
I have to go. Bye.
Yes, sir, I was right.
There are three other houses
available to rent.
If you like,
we can ask for the keys
and go see them immediately.
No, that's not necessary.
I'll take this one.
No, unfortunately,
this one is a model home,
and it would be very difficult
to purchase it.
I like this one, just how it is.
This puts us in a tight spot.
Look, it just can't--
Friend, name one thing
in this world
that is non-negotiable.
Please put the breasts
in the upper tray.
Hand me some glasses, please.
- How many glasses, sir?
- Two.
Sandra, we have to clean
this machine every night.
- Okay.
- To be able to clean it,
you have to go to go
round the back
where there is a valve.
That valve has a red knob.
You have to turn it
to the right.
When the valve is pointing
towards you,
you can clean the machine, okay?
Seriously, José,
you made this, bro?
Yeah.
Heisenberg can suck it.
José sure can cook!
Look man, it's totally clean.
It's not at all cloudy or dirty.
You're the man.
Now I get why women dream about
blue eyed boys.
Yeah.
And the size, man.
If you put a stick on it,
it'd be like a lollipop.
Try it, bro.
- Are you sure, man?
- Try it.
If you want, I can take it home
and do it there,
because I feel kind of bad
with you being in rehab and all.
No, it's alright.
I can watch.
I can cook and I can watch.
Are you sure?
Go for it, man.
I tried it last week,
and I'm still coming down.
But go easy.
In moderation.
Wow, dude.
Wow.
Hey, man, don't go jumping out
of the window, OK?
That's enough, dumbass,
you're getting the floor dirty.
This guy's hair is falling out.
Okay, enough!
Bow to me,
ladies and gentlemen,
for I am the Lord of the Dance!
Wow, it's so good, dude.
- I want more!
- No, you've had enough.
That's all.
Dude, I feel like...
someone took out my brain
and turned it into vapor.
I told you it was the shit, man.
Yeah, it's like anthrax, dude.
Don't be dumb,
that's something else.
Okay, now what?
Are we going to talk business?
What do you mean?
That wasn't the plan.
Look, I know
what you're thinking.
Really, I do.
But it's not going to be
like it was before.
I promise you guys,
it'll never be like that again.
What's so different
this time around?
The difference is
this time we'll sell it safely.
We'll sell it smartly.
We won't get greedy,
or ambitious.
Not this time.
I don't know, man.
I still think about Gordo
from time to time.
That was really rough.
Yeah, but dude...
We have to keep going, right?
What else do we do?
If it's like Jose says,
and we don't get greedy
or anything,
this time around...
I'm in, dude.
What about you?
I don't know, man.
Last time
we started to push our luck.
I'd love to turn back time,
but...
That's exactly the point, dude.
We've done this before.
We're going to do it again,
but this time
we won't make any mistakes.
Look, step one:
we make an inventory of
everything we have.
OK?
You, Mono.
Go see Germán,
so he can fix up the bus.
Change the oil, maintenance,
lights, all of that stuff.
You know the police are
looking for any reason
to stop someone.
This time,
we don't give them anything.
We're going to be cautious
about everything.
On top of that,
we're going to get
one of those noise things,
that goes off when you leave
the key in the switcher,
you know what I mean?
One of those alarms
that go off
at the drop of a pin.
We need to ensure
the bus isn't just left
in the middle of nowhere.
Of course, man,
like what happened last time.
Exactly.
And you, Tripa,
are in charge of supplies.
I'm going to give you
a detailed, step by step list,
of what you need to buy.
OK? What do you say?
Okay.
Are you sure?
Shit, okay,
let's do it.
- Agreed?
- Ready to go, dude.
This time,
we don't need anyone else.
We're going to do it alone,
and we're going to do it well.
Okay, alright, then?
- Alright, dude.
- Hey, man.
Mauricio Mejía.
I know you.
It's a small world.
Do you want to talk about it?
Why?
Do I have a say in the decision?
Look, ironically,
I think from now on,
I'm going to have
a lot more time for you.
- Sure.
- I'm going to buy a car.
I can take you to and from
school every day.
So I don't have a say
in that decision either?
Better yet,
I can't go with Lucho
just because you feel guilty?
Yes, I feel guilty.
I am what I am, Junior.
You know what?
I would love to
change a lot of things,
but I can't. Here I am.
That's all there is to it.
Call me crazy,
or whatever you want.
But you know what?
I have a good feeling
about this.
I'm optimistic
about what's to come.
Good morning.
Combo three is ready.
Combo three,
for table number four.
Half a roasted chicken,
one hamburger...
This will vibrate
when your food is ready,
and then you come
and collect it, OK?
Good morning, Sandra.
Good morning, Don Gustavo,
How are you?
Have you noticed
who's over there?
Yes.
Sir, I don't know,
but frankly I think
we should call the police.
I don't think
that will be necessary, Sandra.
They have done nothing wrong.
This order is for
table number 15.
Yes, sir, I'll take it now.
- Keep the change.
- Thank you very much, sir.
Good luck with your son, sir.
They get used to it eventually.
Good morning.
Professor Walter Blanco,
I presume.
Yes, that's me.
How are you?
- I'll come down.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Guido Bermúdez.
How are you?
- Are you my new
laboratory assistant?
- Yes, sir.
I suppose you want to know
my qualifications?
I printed my resume,
I can give it to you right now.
I printed it
in case you wanted to see it.
I graduated with a degree in
Chemistry from the Scientific
University of Colombia,
a masters in Science from
the same university and...
with an specialization
in Organic Chemistry.
My doctorate thesis is on...
Well... It's all in there.
"X-Ray Crystallography."
- Seriously?
- Yes.
I could talk for hours
about that subject!
I would love that, professor.
But look, what really makes me
curious is this...
This.
No, it's nothing, it's...
It's a pilot project
that I'm developing
in my free time, of course.
I have the theory that
everything has something
to do with the concentration
of chemical acid.
Because it requires
4,800 milligrams per liter,
but if it overheats
in order to get to that point,
the tannin will filter out,
and then what happens?
It's bitter, right?
It has a bad flavor.
For that reason, I've been able
to extract a very mild space,
in order to
to maintain the temperature
to below 92 degrees Celsius.
Do you want to try it?
Yes.
Thanks.
Mm.
This is the best coffee
I've ever had in my life!
It's organic coffee from Nariño.
You've got to give the mill
some credit too, right?
But thank you very much,
Professor.
Call me Walter.
- Guido.
- Yes?
What are we doing making
methamphetamine?
This is really good!
Thank you very much.
So, you say that,
with phenylacetic acid solution,
there are 150 drops per minute
during the first 10 minutes,
and then 90 drops
for the rest of the time, right?
Why is that?
Because diluting the phenol,
makes a layer of water and oil,
therefore...
A better extraction
of the benzene.
Exactly.
Of course, I prefer ether.
Of course.
I'll make sure
we have some tomorrow.
How nice!
Shall we celebrate?
Guido...
I've keep wondering...
how you ended up here.
Well, it's a question
I also ask myself.
It's strange.
Because you and I don't see
ourselves as criminals, right?
No.
Of course, it's a crime.
But I personally
consider myself to be
a libertarian.
I'm someone who thinks
that adults can do whatever
they want,
as long as
they aren't hurting others.
And, if I don't provide them
with what they want,
then someone else will.
The only difference is that,
with me,
they know exactly
what they're buying.
Without toxins.
Without additives.
Have you seen what
they're mixing it with
on the streets?
They're throwing in
fake ecstasy,
scopolamine,
horse tranquilizer,
not to mention brick dust,
- or gasoline that
they add to cocaine.
It's dangerous.
Here, on the other hand,
it's...
guaranteed quality,
and guaranteed purity.
Cheers!
Mm.
It's just...
I love the laboratory,
because the laboratory
is still magic to me.
Do you understand?
Chemistry is still magic.
And I wonder what would happen
if they took that away from us.
I completely agree.
Chemistry is still magic.
But, you didn't answer
my question.
How did you end up here?
It's nothing special.
I was going through
all the necessary steps
when you have a research grant.
Most of the time...
I was doing office work,
in public relations,
resolving all kinds of issues
that have nothing to do
with chemistry.
You must know how it is
in the academic world.
Yes.
What happened was,
they made me a job offer and...
Here I am.
In action.
I think the best way to explain
what happened to me is,
I opened my eyes
thanks to some verses...
by William Blake,
the English poet.
- Recite them.
- No.
No, it'd make me feel
embarrassed and pathetic.
No, please!
Go on!
Basically, they are three verses
of a poem that's called,
"Proverbs of Hell".
It goes like this:
"The road of excess leads
to the palace of wisdom.
Prudence is a rich,
ugly, old maid,
courted by incapacity.
He who desires but acts not
breeds pestilence".
"We are obligated to consumer
our life with strength today".
I have always wondered...
if it's really worth it
to always behave well.
Because in the end,
nobody will praise you for that.
But I believe
that the only way...
to feel true pleasure
is in life.
And it depends on
someone allowing themselves to,
before it's too late.
It's now or never.
Cheers!
Come on, Rosas.
Go commit a crime,
or steal something.
Hey, my love.
Hi, babe.
Are you coming home for dinner?
I'm working, María.
Did you catch that guy
with the bus?
Babe, if I had found him
I would be home already, OK?
- So--
Why don't you just
arrest him and question him?
It's not that easy, María.
There are things called laws
and the constitution.
Blah, blah...
You don't know how much
I want to catch this asshole.
- It's that Rosas kid, isn't it?
- Yes.
I'm sure he has the bus.
But I don't know
where he's put it.
I just have to wait,
because I know he'll take me
to wherever he's hidden the bus.
So, I won't be coming home
any time soon.
I'm trapped here.
Hey, there's something
we had long forgotten,
and I don't want to throw salt
on old wounds, but...
I think I know someone who can
give you information on Rosas.
Who?
Hello, what is it?
What's up, brother?
How's it going?
Good, Henry.
How are you? What's up?
Listen,
I'm sorry to bother you,
but I have a quick question
for you.
Yes, of course, ask me.
Well, before anything,
I want to clarify that
I'm asking you this simply
because I'm in the middle
of a case,
and I'm at a bit of a dead end.
I want you to know that I don't
want to make you uncomfortable,
or get you in trouble...
Ok, Henry,
can you just cut to the chase?
You remember when you got lost,
right?
And I was trying to
track you down through...
Do you remember your
former student,
called José Miguel Rosas?
Okay, well,
you know that I know
that once upon a time
that guy sold you some weed...
- Marijuana.
- Henry.
Easy, brother,
don't worry,
I really don't care about that.
I know he sold you some.
If people start asking me,
"Is your brother-in-law
a pothead?"
I'll tell them,
"No, he hasn't tried it".
Sorry, I'll get to the point,
as you said.
Do you by any chance know
if this José Miguel Rosas...
...has a school bus?
I know that this sounds weird,
but any information you can
give me would really help me out
for the case.
Have you ever seen him driving
a school bus?
The bus is blue and
has a silver band around it.
- No.
- It's one of those buses...
Well, it's not a huge bus,
or a little one,
it's medium size,
old, like from the 80's.
It's not one of those
modern buses we have nowadays.
- Why?
- It's a long story.
But look, I'm absolutely certain
that guy stopped
selling marijuana,
to join the big leagues,
and produce
crystal methamphetamine.
Do you understand?
The guy is so nutty,
that he took
one of those school buses...
and adapted it
to make it into
a mobile laboratory
to cook methamphetamine.
What do you think?
Hello?
Hello Walter?
Dude, I think you've got
a gift for this.
You also know
about tools and all that.
You know what, dude?
You should invent a car
that run's off of water,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, bro.
We would make a killing
in New York.
Are you crazy?
Why is this out in the open?
Don't be stupid!
- Who is this guy?
- He's Heisenberg.
Is it ok?
Can you drive it?
Yes, of course, we changed
the oil and everything.
Good, we'll clean it
and I'll take it to the plain.
Give me a hand.
What's going on here, bro?
What's happening?
The cops are on my tail.
That's what's up!
Narcotics agents.
Surely you've heard
about them, right?
Well, they know
what's inside this bus,
and they're looking for it
right now!
Well, get it out of here, man.
- I don't want anything
to do with this.
- First we have to
destroy the evidence.
We'll burn it later,
but not here.
I'm closing up shop, bro.
Help me get it
out of here, then.
Listen to me.
Are you going to help me?
If I go down, we all go down,
including you.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Okay.
But not right here.
I know a guy that can make
this bus disappear off
the face of the earth.
No questions asked.
Call him.
Hey! What about José?
What about him?
Dude, guess what's going on.
Get me that address, Mono!
No, man...
I don't care,
just get it for me.
Look, this asshole wants to take
the bus and kick us out
of the business.
- I'll see you there.
Finally!
Where are we going?
Why the rush?
Excuse me, are you leaving?
I'm sorry, gentlemen,
but the tables are for
paying customers only.
Sandra, I'll handle this.
Yes, sir, excuse me.
- How can I help you?
- You know how.
I'll see you tonight
when I leave.
One hundred, two hundred,
three hundred,
four hundred,
five hundred.
Beyond recovery.
Do you know what that means?
Of course!
I want you to erase it from
the face of the earth.
When we are done,
nothing will remain.
So calm down, don't worry.
This is a very
gratifying business.
Only the benefactors remain.
Don't worry,
everything is under control.
Do me a favor,
- call me a taxi.
- Okay.
I'm going to go take a quick
look around inside, do you mind?
No, go ahead.
What the hell are you doing?
Me?
No, what are you doing here,
dumbass?
This is just as much mine
as it is yours
and you're not going to take it
away from me just like that!
What are you doing, Walter?
- We're fucked!
- Why, what are you doing?
- He's here!
- Who?
My brother-in-law, dumbass!
Close everything!
- Your bro-- ?
- Close it!
- Like that.
- Close them!
You brought him here!
You guided him right here,
you imbecile!
What do we do?
Be quiet.
He's at the door.
There are holes in the door.
José Miguel Rosas?
Come out!
It's better
if you give up yourself!
Come out now!
This is your last chance
to do it the easy way!
- Come out!
- Should I go out there?
No.
Okay.
Shit, the door!
What are you doing?
Why are you damaging
that vehicle?
Do you want me decapitate you
and bury you right here?
Do you want me to sell your
pick-up truck to pay me back
for the trouble you've caused?
Take it easy, buddy,
I'm a policeman.
Take it easy.
Who are you? Lower the weapon.
What is he doing?
Lower your weapon.
I'm the owner of this lot.
What do you know about this bus?
Better yet,
tell me what you're doing here,
and why you're trespassing
on private property,
and not only trespassing,
but damaging it.
Do you have a warrant?
I don't need a warrant,
because I have probable cause.
If you can see
bullet holes like these,
then a crime was committed
inside this vehicle.
Understood, Mr. Lawyer?
Well, maybe I'm not a lawyer,
but I have three children
who are lawyers,
and who are going to
eat you alive
in a court of law,
if you go even slightly
against regulation.
Also, let me tell you
that I'm willing to go to any
length to testify against you.
You know what?
Save yourself the trouble
and cooperate with me.
No fucking way!
You came here fishing
for something.
But you're disrespecting
my property,
you're disrespecting me,
and you're disrespecting
my business,
the business that
gave my children
their education.
As I already told you
they are lawyers.
You don't have any proof.
You're violating
the required process.
- You're going to leave
empty handed!
- Rosas!
Come out!
Tell him to bring the
warrant and then you'll talk.
- Tell him!
- Bring the warrant and
then we'll talk!
I'm going to count to three,
and you're going to come out.
One!
- Tell him!
- Two!
I already told you;
get the warrant,
then we'll talk!
Imbecile!
- What?
- I'll bring the warrant,
no problem!
I've waited a long time,
I'm not going to wait
any longer.
No, now we're fucked.
He's got us.
What do we do, Walter?
Vicky, get me the boss.
I know!
I say we ram him.
We run over that peace of shit
and then take off with the truck
- and make our escape!
- Shut up!
Stop talking bullshit!
Then what the fuck do we do?
Boss,
I'm going to need a warrant,
let's see if
you can help me with that.
Think of something, Walter,
think up something!
Thanks.
Do you have a plan?
Yes.
Yes, I have a plan.
What are we going to do?
I need your help.
Hello?
Is this Mr. Henry Navarro?
Yes.
Sir, we're calling you
from the Transit Police.
Is your wife's name
María Restrepo?
Yes, why?
Okay,
I'm sorry to inform you,
but she has been
in a car accident.
How is she?
What's her status?
You're going to have to start
paying me more for this, Saul.
I know it's ugly, Panchita,
but it had to be done.
Emergency room?
- Down the hall, to the right.
- That way?
- Where is the emergency room?
- In the back, to the right.
Mrs. María Navarro?
- Hello?
Hey, babe.
I just got home.
Should I make us some dinner?
How are you, babe?
Henry, what's wrong?
Henry...
Babe...
I already told you that
you can't kill Walter Blanco
until I finish my business
with him.
You have to wait.
I know he betrayed
your cousin Tuco.
But he wasn't the one
who killed him.
The one who pulled the trigger
was a narcotics agent.
This is my territory.
I decide who can
and can't be touched.
As a sign of respect
to the cartel,
I have decided that
you can go after him.
His name is Henry Navarro.
I hope his death leaves you
feeling satisfied.