Come on.
Go.
Walter.
Morning.
Afternoon.
- Really?
No.
You shouldn't
have let me sleep.
You needed it.
Terrible...
Sorry.
I don't entirely remember what
happened last night.
If I said something...
Did you know Guido Bermudez?
Who killed him?
Was it the people you work for?
No, no, no, no.
Definitely not.
Was it somebody who
at one point
- might want to do
the same to you?
- Cielo.
Cielo, my head is going to
burst. Don't you have
something?
- Really.
- I think...
I think I know what happened
last night.
I know exactly
what happened last night.
I drank too much wine.
I won't do it again.
I swear!
No.
Last night you told Henry
that the man he was looking for
might still be out there,
that Guido might not be this
Jaisenber after all.
And I was up all night
wondering why you would
say that to him.
Because I was drunk, Cielo.
That's it.
No, but then I was remembering
the black eye
you got from work.
Come on... Cielo...
I don't want to talk about this.
About any of this, ever.
Listen to me.
It's the best for both of us.
No, Cielo, these are two
separate worlds,
they don't have to
touch each other.
- Terrible!
- No.
And then I remembered
the message you left me
the other day.
Remember?
When you said you loved me.
When I heard that,
I thought that maybe--
I thought that maybe
you were regretting
what's happened between us, but
After last night,
I think you're scared.
- No.
- You were very scared!
- No, no, I wasn't.
- Tell me the truth, please.
That was a kind of goodbye,
wasn't it?
Of course not, Cielo.
I think it was a goodbye!
You know what else?
I think some part of you
wants Henry to catch you.
That is it. Exactly, yes.
A brilliant conclusion,
Doctor.
That's exactly what
To get caught,
and spend the rest
of my life in jail.
Great diagnosis!
If he caught you, at least this
would all be over.
Of course this would all be
over!
If they catch me I'll die!
And if I die
this all ends right now.
Finally I understand.
Thank you!
Walter.
I've said it before:
If you are in danger...
- we go to the police!
- What?
I don't want to
hear about the police.
- No!
- Walter,
I do not say that lightly.
I know what it could do
to this family
if we go to the police.
But if it's the only
real choice we have,
I'm willing to take
what comes,
rather than see you dead.
No! Under no circumstances!
Not the police!
You're not some
hardened criminal, Walt.
You're in over your head!
That's what we tell them.
That's the truth.
- That is not the truth.
- Of course it is!
A schoolteacher, cancer,
desperate for money?
You are a victim.
Okay, we're done here.
- This is ridiculous!
- You had nothing
to leave to your family!
It was the circumstances.
You told me that
yourself, Walt.
Let's behave like grownups.
Stop trying to justify this
whole thing and admit
you're in danger.
Who are you talking
to right now?
Who is it you think you see?
I am a fundamental piece.
They need me!
Without me,
there'd be no production.
You clearly don't know
who you're talking to.
- Walter--
- so let me clue you in!
Someone knocks the door.
A guy opens that door,
and gets shot.
Which one do you think
is me?
I am the one who knocks.
I am not in danger.
I am the danger!
Cielo, I think the best thing
is for us to talk--
Cielo.
Cielo?
Let's finish this.
And where is your pretty wife?
She has other business
to attend to.
Well, like I say to her,
place is as is.
- Understand?
- Yes, I understand.
I don't want her coming back
with more demands.
No. The place is as is.
So here's everything you need.
I keep very good files.
- Perfect.
- Well...
So you are the boss now.
You think you're ready,
Walter?
Yes, I think so.
I say this to you,
because running
one of these business,
is really hard.
Being in charge is not easy.
But maybe,
when you are the boss,
you will
just keep your feet up
and relax.
But...
Not everyone knows this is
but the real important thing
is to be tough,
a boss has to be tough.
You have to be tough.
For instance,
has to make cashiers
wipe down cars,
even if they don't want to.
You hear?
Can you be tough, Walter?
I'm sure you can handle,
and if not
you can always
call your wife.
Can I have the office keys?
Who'd have thought someday I
would hand these keys to you?
Ramiro,
that stays.
It's my lucky bill.
- It was the first--
- We said as is.
Thank you, Ramiro!
A pleasure.
Eat something.
No, I'm fine with coffee.
You okay
there?
It's all right.
I'm not using....
I get a...
But I'm fine.
Eat something, man.
That's right.
Hello.
I'm here with him.
Fine.
I have to go.
You want me to call her back?
No, no.
That's fine.
And...
What exactly did she say?
Not much.
She asked if I was okay,
and not to worry.
Did she say at what time
she's coming back?
No, nothing.
It's about
the gambling, right?
It's kind of hard to explain.
It's not like you're
doing this on purpose.
It's no that simple.
You have a disease.
Addiction is like a disease.
She must understand.
It's like you're
an alcoholic.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
I read online.
She's not even allowed
to be mad at you,
and she can't be mad at you
about the cancer.
No, son, these are two
very different things.
- Not really.
- Yes!
what is going on with me
is not about some disease.
It's about choices.
Choices that I have made.
Choices I stand by.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
You're not moving
back in, are you?
No.
You know what?
School can wait. Why don't we
take a little detour?
What kind
of detour?
So?
So...
I think it's time
we got you your own car.
You are doing well in school,
you have a license,
so here we are.
Walter, are you
trying to buy me off?
Maybe.
If you are going to,
then buy me off.
What does that mean?
It's amazing!
I love it!
Uyuy!
- How's that?
- It flies!
- I saw that.
- I don't believe it.
Watch out
for the speed limits.
Thank you!
Really, thank you!
You're welcome, son.
I love it!
Uyuyuy!
So you're here!
Yes, nice to see you too.
What else?
You're actually here?
To work?
You're actually here to work?
Let's just get started.
Come here a second.
What is it?
I need an update.
Update on what?
An update on these little field
trips that you've been taking
with Mario.
I told you already.
We pick up money, check on
things, stuff like that.
And you're his bodyguard,
right?
- Are you making fun of me?
- I'm not making fun!
I just want to know
what's going on.
That's what you said
you did, you defend him.
No, I never said
I defend him.
I said I was backing him up.
Like a second set of eyes.
Everybody needs backup, right?
And this has to be you.
Couldn't it be anyone else?
The new guy. What's his name?
- Mosquera.
Him or any of those muscle heads
he has working for him? No!
It has to be Jose Miguel Rosas.
Why? Is there something about
you that I don't know?
Are you a former Navy SEAL?
Something you haven't told me?
You suddenly aren't that
sensitive boy I once knew?
Leave me alone, ok?
All I'm saying is
that do you
not even question this?
This is strange.
Do you believe you mean anything
to these people?
Do you think they care?
Even a little?
And I'm not trying
to be insulting.
I'm just trying to make you
see things clearly.
See things clearly?
You want to know what I see?
They can't
outright kill me.
They need me alive.
But they don't want me
getting high.
I see this thing probably
started as getting Mario
to babysit me.
No!
I don't think so.
But you know what?
I saved Mario
from getting robbed,
even killed, maybe.
So maybe I'm not
such a loser after all.
I mean, what if it--
What if it's all just a setup?
What do you mean?
Think about it! Your first day
out guarding Mario.
He steps out for one second,
and what happens? You
immediately get robbed.
You are such an asshole.
What a coincidence,
don't you think?
You are crazy.
- Crazy.
- Look.
It's the perfect way to do it.
Gustavo knows it.
Keep your friends close,
keep your enemies closer.
Like you said, Gus can't kill
you because of me. He knows I
won't stand for it.
He needs me, and he hates
the fact that he needs me.
So what does he do?
He goes to work
driving a wedge
between you and me.
It wasn't a setup.
I was there and you weren't.
You know what's the matter
with you?
You can't accept
that I do anything
other than what you order me.
Wait a minute.
How long did those guys chase
you?
Because the way
you describe it, they gave up
pretty damn easy. No.
No, Jose. This whole thing,
it's all about me.
Gustavo is doing this
to screw with me.
You are an egomaniac, Walter.
Hello.
Yes. Hang on.
It's for you.
Hello.
I'll be right up.
- What?
- I got to go.
How so?
Where are you going?
Ey, Jose. Ey.
Am I supposed to
clean all this on my own?
We have to wash the tanks
and clean everything up!
Ey!
Hello.
Ladies, how are you?
- Fine, thanks.
- I'm glad.
I need help to clean up my work
station.
No, we can't.
Help me!
I need a sign.
If this one turns off...
we'll leave.
If that one turns off,
we'll stay.
We'll stay.
What's the deal?
What are we doing here?
The deal is we're
watching that house.
What for?
A little birdie told me
there's some guys in there
that have two kilos of our
product which they're selling,
which they sure as hell
didn't get from us.
Did they steal it?
Looks like it.
So what's the plan?
I just told you. We sit
here and watch that house.
Are we going to stay here for
ages until someone comes out?
- Yes.
- No.
We wait for one of them to pop
out, then we ask questions,
and get our property back.
Simple.
Why don't you just go
break the door down
and pistol whip those bitches
and show them who's boss?
Because a little birdie
also told me these guys
are heavily into the product
and most likely armed.
Now, what you may not
know about meth heads...
They're kind of
unpredictable,
I don't care for
unpredictable.
We don't want a shooting
in this area.
This is going to take forever.
Sorry to burst your bubble, kid,
but that's 90% of the job.
This isn't like the movies.
Get down from that cloud, son.
I could have brought a book.
A book?
All you read is porn
and comic books.
- Are you an intellectual now?
- No...
Here, I brought
some empanadas.
Chicken of beaf?
That's fine.
You'll see.
I know what I'm
going to do.
Where are you
going?
So they're selling, right?
Maybe I'm looking to buy.
Go and see.
What is it?
- Who the hell are you?
- Tato!
- Will you shut the damn door?
- I'm here to buy.
Tato, shut the door!
Not my question.
I asked who you are.
They call me Bolis.
Word on the street is you're
selling the good stuff.
- Tato, I told you!
- The blue one.
Boli, Boli, Boli...
I don't know any Boli.
Just looking for a tenth.
- Help a brother out.
- Tato, close the door!
We don't sell to strangers!
Chao, chao. Come on!
How did it go?
Hand one over.
Empanada?
These are chicken.
Plan B, we wait.
Mario, flip the trunk, will you?
Why?
There's something
in there I need.
And what would that be?
I'm getting those pricks
out of that house.
You may know this whole
P.I. sit-in-the-car business,
but I know meth heads.
They don't teach this in school.
What are you doing?
Digging.
Why?
You know why.
How deep are you going?
Ay!
I don't know.
How deep do you think it is?
Pretty deep.
You mind taking over
for a minute?
Tato!
Who the hell are you?
Easy, come on, now.
- Who the hell are you?
- Easy now.
Just want
to buy some of the blue.
- It's not for sale.
- No, I have money.
- You were
selling it earlier...
- How do you know that?
- Easy, man.
Easy. Tato.
Tato told me.
Tato needs to learn to keep his
damn mouth shut.
Tato!
It's all good.
You going to help me out?
Don't have enough for all
of Tato's asshole friends!
- Tato!
- I think he's outside.
Why don't you go outside.
Let's go find Tato.
Forget it. Okay?
I don't want to start
any trouble.
Trouble? Trouble?
What does that mean, trouble?
- It's all cool.
- Trouble?
We're good.
Don't put thoughts
in my head!
You don't put
thoughts in my head!
There's the bag.
It's our stuff, right?
"Ready to talk"?
What does that mean?
Nothing.
How are you?
Are you all right?
Everything's fine.
Ladies, thank you
very much for everything.
- Thank you, Boss.
- On the contrary.
You can count on me
for whatever you need.
All right, Don
Walter.
Ladies...
- This way, please.
- We are not done--
Come with me.
Mosquera...
please don't hurt them.
Who do you think
you are talking to, Walter?
- What will you do to them?
- Do you want to know?
I'm putting them on a bus
back to the little town
they came from.
No.
Mosquera.
This was my idea.
Don't punish them.
You tell Gus
to blame me, not them.
He does.
Thank you.
Wait for me outside.
We won't be too long.
I'm listening.
The crew that hit our truck
gave away the cargo to a couple
of local nobodies.
Very disciplined, though,
not keeping anything
for themselves.
All we lost
is what those two used.
It's not worth it.
It was all about sending
a message, literally.
It was written on the bucket
"Ready to talk?".
What do you think?
It's the Mexicans, obviously.
They hired people here
to get the job done.
They found good people, tough.
How good are they?
I would need 10 to 15
top notch men,
and we hit them back,
hit them hard.
These men were hired
by the cartel.
Yes.
This war stays cold for now.
We'll see what happens.
What about their message?
What's the answer?
Set up a meeting.
Let's see
what they have to say.
As you wish.
Speaking about
Jose Miguel Rosas.
Does he still think himself a
hero?
He doesn't suspect anything?
I hear you can handle yourself.
I guess.
Good night.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Why me?
I like to think
I see things in people.
There she is.
Don't be nervous.
You know how she gets.
She won't take the car away.
- Good evening.
You wait and see.
Trust in me. You'll see.
Everything's going to be fine.
- Hi, mom.
- Hi.
Did you see
what's in the driveway?
So that's yours?
Yeah. Dad got it for me.
That was very nice of him.
It's a super safe car.
We mustn't think
about appearances.
Appearances?
I promise...
I will always be careful.
- Ajá.
- I will respect
- the rules and speed limit.
So Dad said I can take it
around the block a few times.
That okay?
Just around the block.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're back.
Junior.
Seat belt.
And remember the speed
limit.
Yes, sir.
I guess we should talk.
I think you said
plenty the other day.
Look, about that,
I want to straighten
some things up-- Cielo.
Did you get the
keys?
Yes, here they are.
Thanks.
Hey...
I may have overstated things
earlier...
It got out of hand,
and I'm sorry to be so forward.
I want you to know something,
I need you to understand that
Junior, Valentina,
you are completely safe.
Everything that I do--
I do it to protect this family.
Sure!
So buying that car, that was
protecting your family?
The car...
All right, maybe
it's a little flashy.
I don't know.
But he needed a car,
and I'm his father,
and I should be able
to get what he wants.
It goes back tomorrow.
That car directly
contradicts our story.
Our story!
And if you're so invested
in protecting this family,
it means protecting the story.
What do you think the neighbors
are going to say?
What about Henry or Maria
or the Government?
Did you think about that? No!
What were you thinking?
I wanted to do
something nice for my son.
Cielo, I just worry
that he'll blame you for this.
Don't worry about that.
Once again,
he'll blame his bitch mother
for taking away
what his
loving father has given him.
So thanks for that.
You know why, Walt?
You know why?
- Do you know why?
- Why?
Someone has to protect
this family
from the man
who protects this family.