Methamphetamines are an
increasing tendency in our country,
but we can eliminate it.
And the theft of lab
equipment from your school
made the national
Police alarms go off,
and is also receiving
our highest attention.
This guy you took in was the
one who stole the gear, right?
Our guess is it wasn't him.
That's why we're
questioning all the people
who have access to
the material storage.
Could it have been
someone external?
Maybe while kids
were having class?
Well, ma'am, at this point we
don't have a precise time or date.
But we're investigating.
Anyway, we think this is
not an outsider of the school.
What? So it was
someone who had the key?
Someone close to the school?
We're investigating that at this moment,
so I'm unable to answer.
No, no, no. Wait,
because you always have the same speech,
and then it turns
out you have nothing.
Look, what I think we need here
are drug-sniffing dogs.
I raise dogs like
that. If you want,
I can sell you a couple at a
good price because it's this school.
And we should
get metal detectors,
like schools have in the US.
Yes, I agree with that.
What we need
here is a firm policy.
Please, let's not wait for our
kids to end up smoking crack.
God, they're our children!
Wait, wait, wait.
Do you at least know
what kind of equipment
was taken from the lab,
or you don't you?
There's someone here who
can enlighten us on that matter.
Walter.
Walter!
Yes?
Professor Walter Blanco is
chair of the science department.
And although he is currently on medical
leave he kindly accepted to be here.
Which I appreciate deeply.
Walter, could you please tell us
about the equipment that was taken?
Yes, of course.
Here's the inventory list.
Ten test tubes, one Erlenmeyer,
one 5,000-milliliter
round bottom boiling flask,
one 800-milliliter
Kjeldahl-style recovery flask.
Careful, careful, careful!
- I'm sorry.
What was that?
Why was that so good?
Because it's illegal.
I think this house is
an excellent investment.
If you wish,
the agency can help you manage a loan,
and if you make up your mind,
let me know.
Just give me a call as soon as you're sure,
alright?
- Okay, thank you so much.
- Take care.
- See you later.
Do you have an
appointment to see the house?
There's nobody
else on the schedule.
No, I'm here to see the owner.
He's in the recreational vehicle
parked just around the corner.
Thanks.
What's up, professor?
What's with this shack?
So the buyers don't run away.
You're selling the house?
Right.
You know, it happens.
How do you feel?
I'll live.
- It still hurts when I breathe.
- Right.
What about you? Got a new wig there,
I see.
No,
just for better air circulation.
Tripa told me
you went to the hospital
while I was asleep.
You wanted Tuco. Are
you planning on visiting him?
I also wanted to know
how you were doing.
Right, aha.
You are alive,
so obviously you wised up.
No, I did go see him actually.
Bullshit. Tell me what happened.
There's your money.
Tuco gave you this?
He had it all here,
the 35 grand in cash.
There's your half, plus a bonus.
Are you actually telling
me Tuco gave you this?
I can't believe this.
How did you do it?
We made a deal. We're
doing business with him.
A deal? What do you mean a deal,
professor?
Why would you make a deal
with that scumbag? That's insane!
José, it's good for us.
I think that we can
do business together.
No way,
man! That man's a lunatic, a beast!
Wait a second. Now just
imagine making that every week.
Two pounds a week.
35 grand for each one.
That's more than 17
grand for each of us!
- Two pounds?
- Yes!
You know what that dude could do
to us if we don't make that delivery?
Well,
we just have to get organized
and squeeze a bit
our working hours.
What about pseudo,
man? How are we gonna get that?
The drug stores haven't sold that for ages,
man!
So we get it elsewhere!
I did that already!
I had to get a guy almost up to
Venezuela. And it's running dry there too.
And I got to half a pound maybe.
- Didn't you know that?
- No.
How can you know when
you don't ask me squat?
I'd have told you
if you'd asked me.
Well, here we are again.
Yes, sir.
Cielo,
your pregnancy is looking great!
You must be, what,
six, seven months?
- So how's it going?
- Great.
It's great other than waddling to
the bathroom every five minutes.
Well,
we're having the baby shower soon,
and she'll be the
queen of the night.
Walter,
I see you've committed to the hair loss.
Yes. Well,
one more thing not to worry about.
That's true!
And how are you feeling
Good, pretty good.
Much better than I imagined.
His color is better. You know,
his energy.
He's even got the energy to...
That's got to be a good sign.
Of course!
Couldn't that mean that
the chemo is working?
Realistically, it may just mean
that we've got the
anti-emetics tuned right.
We'll have this chemo
result after it's finished
and we look at a new PET scan.
I was thinking.
Isn't there anything
else we could be doing?
Maybe alternative
medicine. What do you think?
As long as it doesn't
interfere with our treatment,
anything that helps my patient
have a better comfort, is fine by me.
But let's be clear in that we
depend on what we're doing here.
So it doesn't make
any real difference?
It's important that we
manage our expectations.
Alright?
What?
Nothing, man.
- What's with this place?
- What about it?
Don't you like the
spot I chose to meet?
Dude you sure saw a
lot of movies in your life.
What's wrong with it?
It's private, just as we need.
This is the kind of place where
Americans think crossovers are made.
Like when in Bogota people get
dressed with a poncho and hat.
That's exactly it.
So where do you transact your
drug business? Enlighten me.
How about a cafeteria?
Nice and public.
Everyone in their thing.
And you can eat
something along the way.
And since it's public,
psychos like Tuco
think twice before
shooting anybody.
Here they come.
I'm getting a stomach ache and all,
dude.
José.
I absolutely
understand you're afraid.
You don't have to be here,
so you can leave if you want.
But I'm not a coward. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
The doctor... and Chespirito.
What's up?
Sorry about the other day,
It was pure affection.
So why here?
What,
they close the mall or something?
Or do you think we're
in a fucking movie?
Okay, okay.
Enough chatting.
Let's just get to it.
No, man! Come on, break it out.
This is barely
more than a pound.
We had some production problems.
I don't give a shit! This is
not what we agreed upon.
You said two pounds!
Two pounds, asshole!
Give me that...
This is what we agreed on
minus a fine for
wasting my time.
Let's go!
Tuco!
What?
You got something to say?
You're doing business
like a couple little bitches.
Thanks for nothing!
I want all of the money.
What?
Did you hear what I heard?
What did you say?
I said give me all the money.
You like this product,
you know it's prime quality.
Consider it a
capital investment.
An advance. And next week
I'll give you back what I owe you.
Okay.
Three daily,
I'll see you next week, then.
What?
It's the interest,
three percent every day.
Fine.
Okay...
Here's the money for
the two pounds this week.
The rest, plus interest,
when you deliver the
other four next week.
I hope, four pounds.
That's three pounds.
I just gave you one.
Four pounds!
Two pounds for next Friday!
That's what I said!
Tuco.
Can you handle six pounds?
Don't you get smart on me,
Heisenberg.
Owing me money,
that's not good.
Six pounds?
Let's go.
Professor.
What the hell did you just do?
Come on.
Six pounds.
Six pounds, man!
You couldn't get that much
even before they banned pseudo.
We're not going to
need pseudo ephedrine.
What do you mean
we're not using pseudo?
We're going to make
phenylacetone in a tube furnace,
then we're going to use reductive
amination to yield methamphetamine.
So no pseudo?
No pseudo.
My gosh,
professor. I knew you had a plan!
Long live the professor! Long live science,
man!
Here.
- What's this?
- A shopping list.
Getting some of those
items may be challenging.
One autotransformer.
200 ounces of hydrous methyl...
- Methylamine.
Two M&M tube furnaces.
Milliliters.
One 70-millimeter would be fine,
but they're hard to come by.
So 40 grams thorium nitrate...
Thori...
- Thorium.
I can't even
pronounce half this shit.
That's not even English.
You know what? Count
me out. I'm leaving town.
I'm moving to where Hare Krishnas is,
change my name.
- José! José!
- No...
Calm down, man. Come,
listen to me.
We're already involved in this.
From now on,
our life will change for good.
It's up to you the
kind of life you want.
This could be the most important
day of the rest of your life.
- What is it?
- What'll it be?
A life of restrictions
and lack of things?
Or do you chose to trust?
I don't know.
Here's everything we need.
And only you can
get them for us.
You're the man!
Trust yourself!
There, auntie.
You might be wondering who this
pretty lady is. I'm your aunt María.
And after you're born
I'll become your idol
because when you watch this 20 years
from now, I will look exactly the same.
- Auntie!
- Okay.
Welcome to your baby shower,
Esmeralda!
Esmeralda?
Yes, that'll be your name.
And the first one to know is
your big brother, Walter Junior.
Hey, little sister!
You're all tucked up in there!
Look,
your mommy is all round because of you.
Hey, honey, Esmeralda. Relax,
that's not your name, it's Valentina.
We chose that while taking
your aunt to the mental institution.
That's right,
we took her and now she's sedated here.
Daddy's coming! Dad!
Say something to Valentina.
Yes, say something! Something
really funny like those jokes you tell.
Speak like a coast guy!
Coast guy...
Hey, Valentina.
Honey, I'm so proud of you.
And...
I think about you all the time.
Aw! So cute!
Wherever you go,
whatever you do in life,
and wherever you go,
always know that you have a
family who loves you very, very much.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Cheers! Cheers.
To Esmeralda!
Cheers, honey. Valentina,
Valentina!
Valentina, cheers.
You're gorgeous!
Look at that beauty.
Hannah,
I really appreciate it. They're beautiful.
You're very welcome, darling.
Open this one.
- Alejandra's next.
- No, open this one, Cielo.
Well, alright.
Read the card.
From María and Henry, to...
Valentina!
Esmeralda's nicer.
Wow!
Wow. This is...
a...
brag?
It's a tiara. It's called tiara.
Tiara. So it's...?
It's white gold,
with zircon settings.
Wow, thank you!
Wow...
María,
this must have cost a fortune.
You shouldn't have.
Why? You don't like it?
No, I do! I love it! It's so...
sparkly.
Yes.
Thank you, thank you.
Mine now, mine.
No, come, let's not lose it.
Come, I have a surprise.
I don't know what's going on with me,
but...
I just can't stand so
much women talk.
Hey, come, I'll show you.
Look at this beauty.
Look.
Look, buddy.
You can drink this, can you?
Whiskey? Yes.
Especially if it's delicious.
Wow!
Where did you get this?
You don't get this in Colombia.
A friend of mine, customs agent,
did a raid and found this. He owed me,
so he gave it to me.
Nice!
Well, we should make a
toast. To the illegal drink!
Right.
They say the forbidden
fruit is the tastiest one.
In fact, it's hard to set lines.
On what?
Well, what's legal, what's illegal,
what's allowed or not.
Especially, in things like this.
Could you elaborate on that statement,
professor?
This whiskey is wonderful.
Henry,
if we were in the States now,
in prohibition times...
No, no need to go that far.
Saudi Arabia, today...
This is time in jail.
It's an absolute crime.
But no, we're in Colombia.
Not in Colombia, now.
Well, maybe yes,
but just a little bit.
You know what I mean?
I mean there are things
that go from being illegal
to legal, all of a sudden.
Who knows what will
be legal in the future?
What would you like to be legal?
Pot?
Yes. Pot.
I don't know,
maybe some other stuff.
What? Cocaine? Heroin?
No, I guess I'm just saying
drug restrictions are arbitrary.
Yes.
And no.
I think there's stuff that
should never be legal.
Like what?
Methamphetamines.
Did you know methamphetamines
were legal in the US?
They sold it in drugstores.
Just like cocaine before that.
Thank God they came to their
senses on that one. No party anymore.
How about another one?
Why not?
That baby shower,
wasn't bad at all, was it?
Hum...
This will be the baby with
more T-shirts on the block.
Well, at least the first month.
- And the only one with a tiara.
- A what?
A tiara, this crown,
- made of gems, white gold.
- That María gave her.
- Right.
She's nuts! How
could she even think
of getting one of those
things to a newborn?
- It must be trendy.
- No.
I know where they sell them.
I've been to the jewelry store.
I mean,
that thing must have cost around 500 bucks.
What?
I'm not lying. I think
I'm going to return it.
You sure? She's bound to
find out and get really mad.
Well, maybe I can explain to her
that we need a Diaper Genie...
I think diapers are more
important than a tiara.
Honey...
Talking about something else,
remember what you said
about alternative
medicine earlier today?
Yes, I do.
Don't worry. I'm not going to mention
that anymore after seeing your faces.
No, on the contrary.
Look.
Look at this page I found.
It's a place near Bogota.
They do these treatments
with Amazonian plants.
Some kind of vaporizations.
It's supposed to be
good for your lungs.
Do you want to go?
Well, why not?
I'd like to try it.
Dr. It's All Science I
Don't Believe In Anything?
Well, it's not that costly.
And it doesn't
take long. Maybe...
I could leave on Friday
and come back late on Sunday.
How about it?
I think it's great to
have an open mind.
An alternative center
to inhale herb vapor?
Yes. That's exactly
what I told her.
Dude,
I inhaled herb vapor this morning.
I'll help you with that.
Okay, come help me here.
Hydrogen.
Electrolytically produced.
Alright!
Yes, and all this too.
70-milliliter furnace? Congratulations,
good job!
Okay. I got nearly
everything you asked me.
Right, but it wasn't easy.
Or cheap.
I hadn't spent so much
even in the wildest party.
Right, I can imagine.
Where's the methylamine?
Well,
that's why I said I got almost everything.
That's where I ran
into some trouble.
It's hard to buy it. They
got it locked down tight.
Like it were gold or something.
So?
But I did find some pros
who will rip it off for us.
But they want 25 grand.
Well, okay.
No, not okay.
We don't have 25 grand.
I already spent almost
the whole wad on this.
So did they say where they
would be stealing it from?
- I believe down South.
- Aha.
But they got guards and security cameras,
big ass steel doors.
What's this?
What?
This.
That's a toy my grandma
used to hide here.
I'm thinking we can steal
the methylamine ourselves.
But how?
With this.
So what's this
stuff called again?
Thermite.
And that will cut through a lock? Because
this is supposed to be one big ass lock.
Do you not trust chemistry?
No.
Let me tell you a story, Jose.
In World War II, the Germans
had the biggest artillery
piece in the world.
It was called the "Gustav".
It was capable of
firing a 7-ton shell
and hitting a target
accurately 23 miles away.
It was a nightmare
for the Allies.
I mean, you could drop bombs on it every
day for a month without ever disabling it.
But you drop a commando,
one man, with just a bag of this
and he could melt
right through a wall,
maybe six inches
thick of pure iron.
Hey! What's with you, man?
I think it will cut through
any lock we're likely to find.
You'd like to return this?
Yes.
It's very nice, but...
it's not my style
or the baby's.
It is from the store, isn't it?
Yes, of course.
It's from this store. Do you
happen to have a receipt?
No, it was a gift.
A gift, I see.
Javier, could you do me a favor?
I'd like you to watch this
lady while I phone the police.
Excuse me?
You don't have the ticket
because this item was stolen.
No! No, no,
no. That's impossible.
It's possible. Come with us.
No, just a minute.
You have no evidence.
Come on. Sir, please.
Yes, thank you.
And please bring a patrol
unit. I intend to press charges.
Thank you, we'll wait here.
Did you not get this
is a misunderstanding?
I've never stolen
anything in my life!
Do you think I'd return it if
I'd stolen it? I'm not that dumb!
Believe me,
it was a gift for my baby shower!
So who gave it to you, then?
I don't think I have
to tell you that.
You don't have
to tell me anything.
You can talk to the police.
And I can tell them
that there was a woman
who walked right
out the door with it.
Then I can tell the reporters
that without evidence, you illegally
detained an innocent pregnant woman.
And that I'm not getting
enough air back here,
so my baby's health is
surely being compromised.
This is my office.
I don't think I can breathe.
I really can't breathe.
And I'm being held hostage!
I'm being held hostage!
I'm getting sick
and don't feel well.
You know what?
I think my baby
will be born here!
And it'll be premature
because of you!
I'm getting
contractions! I mean it!
My baby will be born here,
and it'll be premature thanks to you!
My water broke! I swear my water
broke! Call an ambulance, damn it!
Call an ambulance,
my baby will be born here!
Voicemail
Leave your message
after the tone.
María, I'm walking out of the
store where you got the tiara.
I think we should talk.
Where's the guard?
I don't know, man!
- You think he already passed?
- I don't know.
How many, one or more?
I was told it was only one.
Put this on.
Really? There weren't anymore.
Wasn't there amen's one?
Can we not discuss
this? Just put it on!
Here.
- Wait, this doesn't look right.
- Here!
Is this really a good idea?
Do you have any other?
What if we get the pseudo?
Well, well. Where can we get it?
Come on!
Sshhhh...
There it is.
Straight. One, two...
Okay, there.
Come on, man.
Wait, we'll put this.
Why did he come
back? I have no idea.
Pavón, how's the night shift?
Okay, Gómez, all nice and quiet.
I'll be waiting on post eight.
Give me five minutes
so I can go to the toilet.
Okay, but light a match!
What do we do?
What are you doing?
Come on.
Hey, what's going on?
Hey, Gómez,
what's going on out there?
Pavón,
how much longer do I have to wait for you?
What's going on? Hey, hey!
Help! Get me out of here!
There.
You're being caught on tape!
Pavón, come in now,
it's my turn for the shift.
Gómez!
Take two straps.
Here, on the sides.
Will that be loud?
Easy,
in five minutes you'll see.
Step back.
Put your gloves on!
Flashlight.
There.
Where are the gallons?
Here they are.
No,
you idiot! Those are 55-liter cans!
Light up!
Here, this one. Come on,
this one!
Come on!
Let's go. One, two...
There's a 3-27 in area four!
I think I got a hernia!
Move it! You're
committing a serious crime,
and there are security cameras!
Our monitoring center is
connected to the National Police!
Pavón, man.
Don't push it so much,
you'll flood it.
you'll flood it!
Just let me, okay?
Let me do it.
Fine, genius. What'll you do?
You sure are stubborn.
Come on.
There! How about it? When you know,
you know.
You should learn
how to handle this.
Shit. What happened?
When you know,
you know. Lesson learned.
No, man. This time it's screwed.
Whatever happens,
we have to cook.
Right, but we can get caught. We
can't be at my neighbors' window.
No, of course not.
Then what?
With the amount of methylamine
that we got we can make eight pounds...
I don't know, maybe for...
enough time for the
foreseeable future.
How long is that going
to be in your case?
I mean in your situation.
How much cash do you need?
Much more.
Well, it's quite clear that
the house needs repairing,
but I must also say it has...
Shit, there are people up there!
Darn it! The people who
were going to sell the house!
I completely forgot
about it! What do we do?
Please consider this. It's a very
large and comfortable house.
Lots of space, as you can see.
Let's step into the dining room,
please.
- Ssshhh...
You can think about it.
And call me tomorrow.
No problem. Or I
can call you back.
How could you forget they
were showing the house?
But you also--
But you also knew they
were showing the house today!
- Me?
- Yes, you!
I could have remembered.
I'm not the only one to blame.
Go up there and get rid of them!
No!
Listen,
maybe they can leave on their own.
Now!
What a man!
You know you can't
duck me forever.
Cielo, hi. What,
you're following me?
No, but you're running away.
When I went to your office,
you snuck out the back way. I called you.
I didn't hear you.
I didn't sneak. I was
just going to lunch.
María, you know what? I have
never been so humiliated in my life.
They accused me of
shoplifting the diadem.
The tiara.
What were you doing over there?
I was going to return it.
Why would you return it?
Didn't you say you liked it?
Okay,
enough already. That's not my point.
What's wrong with you? Why
would you do such a thing?
What are you talking about?
I'm saying I have no idea
what you're talking about.
María.
María, forgive me,
but this is serious.
My God,
we're talking about theft!
You're not going to admit this,
are you?
I can't really
admit to something
when I have no knowledge
of what it is that I'm admitting.
Miss, how much is this?
Hey.
- How was it?
- Thanks.
Good, good,
an interesting experience.
- Really?
- Yes.
What's that smell?
That must be the...
Like a sacred herbal mix
these shamans make. Awful.
So are you okay?
No, not really.
What happened?
You know that diadem,
that tiara that María gave us?
Yes.
She stole it.
What? María?
I practically got arrested
trying to return it at the store.
My God!
Yes.
Well,
it'll be okay. I managed to get out.
But the worst part
is I confronted María,
and she refuses to admit it.
I don't know what to do.
Well. People sometimes
do things for their families.
People sometimes do that
kind of thing for their families?
No.
Those herbs damaged your brain
because nothing justifies crimes.
What would you do if it were me?
What do you mean?
If it were me,
what would you do?
Would you report me?
You don't want to find out.
Do you want something to eat?
- Thanks.
- I do, I'm hungry.
Fuck me!
Why's this one blue?
We used a different ingredient,
but it is every bit as pure.
It may be blue,
but it's the bomb.
My God, what a hit!
I want more of this!
Blue, white, pink,
yellow... Any way you want it.
Okay, how much does it weigh?
It's all there.
Money will start raining!
Thanks.
Just remember who
you're working for!
What did you say?
I'm just saying they got
to know who's boss, Tuco.
Like they don't
already know that?
Are you saying
that they're stupid?
That they know I rule
and that they're mine?
No, no. I'm just saying...
Wait, let me get this straight.
So you're not saying that they're
stupid. Are you saying that I'm stupid?
Because I don't make
myself clear with Colombians?
No, no, Tuco...
You're just speaking for me,
fucker?
Like I ain't got the damn
sense to speak for myself!
Tuco!
Why don't we all just relax?
Heisenberg says relax.
I'm relaxed. I'm relaxed.
Learn how to shut the fuck up,
motherfucker.
Fighting.
Champion.
Gonzo.
Give me that.
Bring him!
See you on Friday, Heisenberg!