Fuck me!
Why's this one blue?
We used a different ingredient,
but it is every bit as pure.
It may be blue,
but it's even better quality.
My God, what a hit!
I want more of this!
Blue, white, pink, yellow,
however you want it.
Okay, how much does it weigh?
It's all there.
Money will start raining!
Thanks.
But don't you forget
who you work for!
What did you say?
I'm just saying they got
to know who's boss, Tuco.
You think they don't know that?
Are you saying
that they're stupid?
That they know I rule
and that they're mine?
No, no. I'm just saying...
Wait, let me get this straight.
If they're not stupid,
are you saying that I'm stupid?
Because I don't make
myself clear with Colombians?
No, no... No,
Tuco. No, not that.
You're just speaking for me,
fucker?
Like I ain't got the damn
sense to speak for myself!
Tuco! Why don't
we all just relax?
Heisenberg says relax. I'm relaxed,
I'm relaxed.
I'm relaxed. I'm relaxed.
Learn how to shut the fuck up,
motherfucker.
Fights. Champion.
Gonzo, give me that.
Bring him! I'll see you on Friday,
Heisenberg!
This money is
my family's future.
I need to make sure my
kids can go to college.
I want them to study abroad.
That should be
around 37 grand a year.
Times five, that's 185 grand...
For both kids, that's 370.
Remaining mortgage on the home,
that's 55 grand.
Cost of living
food, clothing, utilities,
health, that's...
I don't know,
maybe seven grand a month, so...
in a year,
that's 28 grand... Ten years.
For ten years,
that would be 280 grand.
37 grand for college,
so 65 grand
plus 55 for the mortgage...
that's 120... More
or less around that.
That sums up
to around two million dollars.
That's what I need.
Now we're making about...
Maybe two and a
half pounds a week?
If we double the production,
we could make...
I don't know... Maybe
do it in three months?
Three months would be perfect!
But... Let's just say it's six.
Six would be just fine.
That's it! Six months.
And listen,
call it 11 in a public place from now on.
Let's go!
Damn it, what do we do?
What do we do? Tell me.
Hold it! Hold it!
Heisenberg!
What the hell?
What's wrong with him?
You can't take an ass-beating,
bitch?
Tuco, that was too much,
brother.
Shh.
No, he has no pulse.
- Do something, Heisenberg!
- Do something?
He needs an ambulance.
He needs a hospital!
No, no, no! No hospital...
Do that to him.
It's not working.
Breathe into his mouth!
No, Tuco, that's no good!
They don't teach that anymore.
You, come here! Breathe
into his mouth and save him!
God damn it!
This asshole dies out here!
Gonzo, get rid of him..
We can't do him like that, man. Buzzards
and rats and all that. Let's bury him.
Tuco,
that man lying there was Christian.
If we don't bury him, brother.
Don't argue with me, Gonzo.
- Alright, Tuco. Fine.
- You guys help.
Hurry up, asshole!
Are you in a hurry?
I think we're done here, Tuco.
Right.
You're... done.
Walter?
Walter, is that you?
Honey, you scared me.
Hey... I'm talking to you.
Walter!
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Fine... I'm fine.
- New hat?
- Yes.
I got some grilled
chicken. Want some?
Where were you?
Walter...
Honey...
Wait, let me take off...
Let me wash my face, honey...
Calm down. Junior's
about to come. Hey...
Hey!
Walter!
Wait. Wait! No...
Stop it, damn it!
Walter.
I know you're scared,
and you're angry,
and you're frustrated.
And I know none of this is fair.
But you can't take it out on me.
I'm home!
Dead, man! We're done,
we're through!
I'm telling you!
- No! This is conjecture.
- This is conjecture?
Conjecture!
And conjecture
isn't helping at all.
We need simple facts.
- You want facts?
- Yes.
Fact number one:
My phone rang, like, eight times
last night. Hang ups every time.
So what?
Fact number two:
At three in the morning
a truck pulls over.
Just like Tuco's. At my house.
And if it wasn't the same one,
it was another just like it!
- You're being paranoid, José.
- Yes, right...
Okay, if Tuco wanted to kill us,
he would've done it at the junkyard.
What is that?
Are you basing that on that
he's got a normal, healthy brain?
Did you not see him
beat a dude to death?
For nothing!
Please think, remember...
He just kept staring at us.
Remember what he said,
"Yes, you're done."
You want to know
what that means?
That means exactly
how it sounds!
That we're done, screwed.
We were witnesses
of what happened.
We are bait now.
We are loose ends.
Right now, Tuco's thinking,
"Yeah, hey, they cook good meth,
but can I trust them?"
What happens when he decides no?
- No, I don't know!
- It's him or us!
It's him or us, dude!
Alright,
then! How would you do it?
- What do you mean?
- Step by step!
Specifically,
how would you do it?
I don't know. Say we
set up one last sale.
Every time we
bring in a new batch,
he always tests the product,
right?
- Aha...
So, as his head - is down,
you know...
Bam, bam, bam!
Bam, bam, bam.
- Right...
- Three shots?
- Three shots, or, I don't know, two.
- No, no!
- Three or two?
- Alright, then, two shots.
Two. Where? In the head,
on the chest, on the back?
I don't know. I'm
not that experi--
I'm just trying to understand
exactly how this works.
What about Gonzo?
Gonzo will react there and then.
- So what about him?
- Well...
I can turn and shoot him too.
How many shots for
him? He's a big guy.
- Three!
- Three shots. Perfect!
So we got Tuco and Gonzo down.
Now, is there anyone else there?
I mean,
Tuco is usually with someone else, right?
What'll you do then?
No, don't tell me yet!
How many shots have been fired?
- Five, I think...
- Five, no! Five exactly.
How many bullets
does that gun take?
I don't know,
this thing's jammed.
How can you suggest that we kill a man,
when you can't even handle a gun?
It's not that easy, is it?
Well, no, Walter,
but you did it.
Well, aren't you early bird,
up and out already.
I just wanted to tell you
the big lug and I are going
to try a new restaurant.
It's supposed to be amazing.
So let me know if
you guys want to hang.
See there? I said "hang".
Junior would be
proud. I know the lingo.
Okay......
It's Chinese, the restaurant.
I don't know. I just
feel like Chinese.
So it would be great
for you to come with us.
I had this really crazy idea.
Do you think that people in
China ever just feel like Colombian?
You know,
order ajiaco and eat it with chopsticks?
Okay, so call me and tell
me whether you're coming.
Big kiss, Cielo. Call me, chao.
She didn't answer?
How could she pick up?
Obviously she's not home.
- Honey, listen...
- Yes.
What was that about
Chinese? Dinner tonight.
That new place.
I want to try it.
Really? What time are we going?
I don't know, maybe eight.
- Don't you have therapy?
- No, not today.
Honey, you've got therapy--
No, it's on Thursday. Remember,
Thursday.
That was last week,
and then they changed the day.
Remember they called us
Yes, honey, you've got therapy.
Cheer up,
baby you've only got six more sessions.
And I'm doing them, I am.
I can't help it if you got
your days of the week wrong.
That's not helping.
Wait, wait, wait, no...
Honey, this therapy with David,
the therapist,
that's really helping you.
You look much better.
And I think it's
important for you to go.
Okay. Bye.
Shit!
Sorry about that,
kid. It's just that...
my wife's a bit...
Here, take this.
- Come on?
- Chop-chop.
Look, this is a technical issue.
Look,
takes out the ten? And leaves a midfield?
- Gómez!
- The ball gets lost there.
- And then those here... What's up?
- Gómez.
Gómez! I'll see
you in my office.
Good morning.
- That coach is a bomb. A bomb!
- Gómez!
Coming, man, coming.
- Where is this?
- Farmagalería Industrial.
- Just off the highway?
- Right.
Have you noticed
when you go by there
the whole place
smells like feet?
- Careful with that...
- What's this?
It's called thermite.
Excuse me?
So I get up early and
do some research,
so I did this. Burns at
about 5,000 degrees.
The kind of stuff you see
on a James Bond movie.
Remember the one with the bridge? There,
bam.
No,
I didn't see it because I do night shifts.
Nice! Guys who know their trade.
I take that back.
They're rather some
idiots! Hello. Hey!
That's a barrel!
Barrel's roll!
Some jerks these two!
So what did they get in that?
Methylamine.
- 30 gallons.
- Methylamine?
P2P?
I researched that
stuff when meth
was just starting in Colombia.
They're cooking
old-school biker meth.
I mean, chemistry book,
test tube... That's weird.
Who could be cooking in Colombia,
with that method?
Nobody.
I've been researching
with Mexican colleagues,
and all the
old-timers are dead--
Well, that's even weirder,
even weirder still!
Pseudo's in short supply,
so these two make do
by changing up the formula.
That way they stand out in
the market. If that's the case,
and there's this...
What's it called?
- Methylamine. Aha.
- No, no, no, the thermite,
it means these guys,
I'd say these two
know their chemistry.
- To steal?
- To steal. What do you mean?
They'd get beaten in the
Paralympics. You know why?
For being disabled.
They might know
about the periodic table,
manganese, magnesium,
boron, all that stuff,
but they've got no street skills.
Your daughter's saying hi.
Good morning, honey.
- Were you here all night?
- No.
Not all night.
I just got a stomachache,
and since I knew I'd be
up and in bed all the time,
I came down for a while
so I didn't wake you up.
How would he know where I
live? Did you give out my address?
- And my name? To Gonzo?
- No!
- What about the dead guy?
Tuco must've put out,
you know, feelers.
He's got his ways and means,
and he's closing in.
He asks, finds out.
That dude's a bee,
he does whatever he wants.
And what happens when he finds
out that my brother-in-law is a cop
and that he also
works in Anti-narcotics?
That's all there is to it!
No, man, no way!
Look, it's got six bullets.
I finally figured
how to open it.
Say we get a second gun for you. Double
our chances. I mean, mathematically.
Just as you like it,
with precise science.
- We get one for you. How about it?
- No, no, I don't want guns.
I've got a better idea.
Thank God! Let's hear it.
Beans.
No... Beans? That's
your plan? Beans?
Castor beans.
So what are we going to
do with them? We plant them
and hope for a magic
beanstalk to grow
to climb it and escape?
Nice plan, man!
We are going to
process them into ricin.
Rice and beans? Ricin.
It's an extremely
effective poison.
It's highly toxic
in small doses.
Also fairly easy to
overlook during an autopsy.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
- This?
- Don't touch them!
But why? Is it that poisonous?
Too poisonous, man!
Ricin was used to assassinate
a Bulgarian journalist
back in the late '70's.
The KGB modified
the tip of an umbrella
to inject a tiny pellet
into the man's leg.
He died instantly.
And we're talking
about an amount
not much bigger
than the head of a pin.
- But it killed him.
- Now we just need to figure out
a delivery device to
get it into Tuco's body.
Then no more Tuco
or any of our problems.
Ricin it is.
- Hey.
Sorry I had to knock.
You didn't hear the bell?
Come in.
Thanks.
I should've called
first. I'm sorry.
What can I do for you?
Maybe we ought to...
Are we going to
talk about María?
She sent you, didn't she?
No, no, no, no... No,
hell, no. She...
She's barely even talking to me.
That's why I'm here.
Self-preservation.
This is instinctive for me,
you know?
No... No, you don't understand.
Look,
I know you girls have your ups and downs,
and that's okay
because you're sisters.
And believe me,
the last thing I want
is to get between you
two when there's an issue.
But you have no idea how much I'd
appreciate it if you answered her calls.
No. I'm not ready for that yet,
Henry.
What happened to communication,
Cielo?
All that about
the Talking Pillow,
everybody saying what they felt,
you know?
Look, don't do it for her.
Do it for me, okay?
You can yell at her.
Just call her back.
Tell her anything you want,
but just answer the damn phone.
That woman is going
to drive me crazy.
María is a shoplifter.
That's right.
Remember the diadem?
That tiara she gave
me at the shower?
She stole it from
a jewelry shop,
and I almost got arrested
when I went back to return it.
Firstly, she won't admit it.
And then, she won't apologize.
If she'd thought you
were going to return it,
maybe she would have never...
You knew about this?
She's got this therapist.
We're doing all we can
so she can move on with
this. His name's David.
- The therapist. I think you know him.
- I do.
He says it's an ongoing process.
And we have got
to be understanding.
Each and every one of us, you,
me, we have to support her.
- As a family, you know?
- Really?
Right, so that she...
I'm the one who
needs support her.
The almost 40-year-old pregnant woman,
with the surprise baby,
in case you forgot. And the
husband with the lung cancer
who disappears for hours on end,
and I don't know where he goes.
And he barely even speaks to me
anymore when he does show up.
With the moody teenager son
who does the same thing.
And the overdrawn
checking account
that makes me want to cry.
And the lukewarm water heater
that is rotting out the wall,
and we can't even afford to fix it.
But, I see! Now I'm supposed to go,
"Henry, please.
What can I possibly
do to further benefit
my spoiled,
kleptomaniac bitch sister
who always manages to
be the center of attention?".
God knows she's the one with
the really important problems.
Not me!
No, Cielo, come here.
I can help you fix
the heater if you want.
It's okay...
Could that be enough?
Yes, that's enough.
Now what?
Now, we arrange our next meet.
In a quiet public
place this time.
Business as usual.
We take the same
amount as we always do,
and give him this.
"The new meth formula
we've been working on.
Would you care to try it?"
So what does this new
formula have that's special?
If Tuco asks us,
we have to know what to say.
I don't know, anything. That...
It gets the user insanely
high. I don't know.
That degenerate snorts
anything he gets his hands on.
Okay,
we'll just put a pin in that, then.
Anyway, within the next 48 hours,
maybe 72, he'll be dead.
It'll look like natural causes.
That's the good thing about it.
What...
Like a heart attack,
something like that?
like a heart attack?
Nobody will notice.
Not if Tuco kills us first,
that is.
Hey, Henry. What's up, buddy?
Hey, man. You been home yet?
No, why? Something happened?
No, because...
I really screwed up. I...
I apologize in
advance for the earful
you're going to hear from Cielo.
It's just that...
I'm just trying to get her
and María talking again.
You know? Big mistake.
I should have
just kept out of it.
You know me.
Well, that happens,
Henry, Don't worry.
These things happen.
Listen...
Well, thanks,
man. And I'm really sorry.
Who told us to
mess with these girls?
Right, Henry. Look, right now
I'm in a bit of a situation.
Can we talk later?
No, no, no, no, no...
I'm also working here, yes.
What's more, listen,
want me to show you
something really freaky?
Yes, I would, but again,
I'm kind of busy.
No, no, no.
Hold on a second. I'm right here
with Gómez, we're in the middle
of a crime scene.
You have to see this?
Wait, I'll send you a picture.
Okay...
So how do I send
it? With...? There...
There...
Hey, I just sent it to you...
Hello...
Walter... Hello?
Hello?
- What are you doing, man?
- I'm taking it.
No, no! That mine!
I need it,
Jose! You have to get out of here.
Pack your bags now, get lost!
If Tuco killed Gonzo,
we're next on the list.
- I have to stick up for my family!
- No, wait...
Come on!
Hey, may I?
- Do you have the pictures, Fierro?
- Yes, sir, I do.
Let's see...
Just a minute,
I recognize these two.
Gómez...
This is the Mexican's company.
Yes, sir, Mr. Tuco Salamanca.
- Guess he got tired of associating.
- I suppose so.
Alright...
This big one here!
This one's much fresher.
Sure, much fresher!
I'm wondering about one thing,
Gómez.
Why is there so much blood
when there's no bullet hole?
No bullets anywhere.
Petrochelli,
can we take a closer look?
Sure, guys, come around..
Look at that...
This is beautiful!
Now that's poetry! Look.
Come.
This guy wasn't murdered.
You know how this was,
Petrochelli?
The big one was
moving this guy's body,
who was dead,
who knows if it was from over there
or going that way.
When he's this close,
the stack must have
shifted and boom! Look.
Crushed his arm.
Look at his arm here.
Ding! He gets caught,
cuts his trapped arm, bleeds to
death and ends up on the other one.
- Holy justice. Like it should be.
- That must have been...
Here, now, Fierro,
take me a picture with...
- Stop it now! Come on...
I'll light up here
Now with the arm here.
I'll send these to Walter.
This shit is broken.
They're too good!
What do you think,
Gómez? Just look at that.
It's like a poster to
hang in the bathroom.
Cielo?
Cielo!
Junior?
Hi.
Where's Junior?
With Lucho, or so he said.
The house was alone, so...
Where were you? If I may ask...
Walter...
Walter!
Walter, would you talk to me,
please?
Walter Blanco,
I'm talking to you!
Coming!
Talk to me.
I mean it, Walter, talk to me.
I don't know where to begin.
What the hell are
you doing here?
Get in.
Just get in, God damn it!
Let's go.