Look what I found, babe!
Tell me how they look on me.
Well, we've come a long way,
Walt.
We're at the end of round one.
Now I'm going to recommend
cautious optimism.
We'll check back in two months,
see how you've responded
and decide our next move.
That's right around the time
the baby's due, correct?
Yes.
Try to think of this
as good timing,
you'll start feeling better
and your hair
should start to come back.
I got used
to the old cue ball look.
It's a new look!
A lot of people use it.
So, no more confusion?
Nothing?
No.
Absolutely none.
And, Walter,
how are you two holding up?
Fine, fine.
We're busy, but we're good.
Absolutely.
- How are you?
- How are you, Mr. Walter?
So, we're not going through
an insurer, right?
No, but it's okay.
Make the invoice out to me.
Okay. I'll print it out for you.
Here.
I thought we had discussed
a cash discount.
Absolutely. It's included.
See? There it is.
Just a reminder, Walter.
Here at the Institute
we have a payment plan
adapted to the needs
of every patient.
In case you are interested.
Mr. Walter!
The hope pin.
- Thanks.
- God bless you.
Then, what about the MRI?
Then what's the difference
between diagnosis
and treatment?
But his doctor ordered it.
It should be covered.
I'm sorry you couldn't be
of more help, too. Okay.
Thank you very much.
Bitch.
Hey.
Been around someone
who smokes?
No.
The hospital bill came.
That was fast.
Twenty million.
We could pay Junior
a year of college with that.
Is this something that Marcela
and Edgar might cover?
'Cause we've got no money.
I'm sure they will. Don't worry.
I'll handle it.
Okay.
Henry.
Five minutes?
I'll see you in my office.
Bring me up to speed
on Tuco Salamanca.
- Dead.
- Still?
More than yesterday.
Okay, then.
Thanks for stopping by.
That's how the DA spoke!
Okay. All right, then.
What happened?
Let's see, what can I tell you?
Things are suspiciously quiet
out there.
Not a lot of blue crystal
on the streets right now.
That's good.
Although, with Tuco's death
I'm waiting to see who rallies
the roaches now that his turf
is up for grabs.
Yeah, right. No takers so far?
Are there?
We keep hearing a name.
"Jaisenber"
or something like that.
Every dime-bagger we come across
name him.
Jaisenber or Heisenberg?
That one. A gringo.
Heisenberg,
the Nobel Prize in physics.
It must be
some kind of an alias.
Like a smokescreen they use.
Maybe he doesn't even exist.
All I know for sure
is that somebody somewhere
is still cooking
blue crystal meth.
You know why sharks
are at the top
of the food chain?
'Cause they have
three sets of teeth, I guess.
And also because
they pursue their prey
along thousands of miles.
Yeah, I think I heard that.
You, my friend
are a great white.
That's right.
A great white.
That's why we want
to send you to do some training
with the Mexico Border Police.
And with the DEA.
How does it sound?
Well, sir
it's a great opportunity.
Of course it is!
But you deserve it.
It was you who opened our eyes
about all this business
of methamphetamine.
And that's why
we've gone so far.
I am honored, sir.
- Thank you very much.
- My friend
you deserve it.
You already thought
what you gonna do without me?
No?
Come on, Gómez. Gómez.
Are you gonna miss me?
Tell me the truth.
You know what I'm gonna do?
Celebrate.
What? How's that?
Not having to see you every day
is like a reward.
Very funny.
You know why they send me
and not any of you?
Because I did understand
that in this job
what you need is...
Gómez?
- Sensitivity.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- No, no.
This isn't only
about the brains and the brawn.
So you should take your chance
and learn.
I'm surprised his head
still fits through the door.
Hey, listen,
you wanna grab lunch?
Let's have a beer
to celebrate. Nice.
You got promoted,
so it's on you.
Sure, it's on me.
You better not start crying
and writing letters, desideratas
and all that stuff, okay?
All right?
Okay, see you later.
All right.
See you.
Hello.
Mr. Ricardo.
Congratulations, my major.
Thank you!
Good morning, major.
Congratulations!
You're going to Mexico?
Órale !
See you later.
How much are they paying him?
There're players here, buddy.
No, no, no.
What took you so long?
It's a Colombian lunch,
not a Mexican one.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- Move, move.
Where are we going?
Hey, dude.
You got some nerve
coming back here.
Or you're dumber than I thought.
Maybe both, yo.
Look.
Here you are.
Balance for the tow, the
repairs and extra for damages
to the toilet door, bro.
Look, like I said,
my word is my bond.
It's in full.
Count it.
- All right.
- Okay?
Dude, I need another favor.
What would you charge me
to store this bus here?
Five hundred million.
Come on, yo. Are you nuts?
Dude, I'm being cool.
I kept my word.
We could negotiate.
But five hundred million?
- Five million, then.
- A month?
- A week.
- For real?
Go. Get off now.
All right, buddy.
A week. Okay.
Twenty million a month.
But then you'll give me a key.
- What for?
- What do you think?
For twenty million,
I should get in and out
as I please.
- Okay.
- Good.
Month to month.
Cash up front.
- All right.
- But I don't know you.
I don't know jack.
Fine. Understood.
There's something else.
You selling that? How much?
Thirty million.
What about that one?
Serious?
Your name's Juana, right?
Yeah.
I had an entire house before
detached and all.
But all the lawn care
and upkeep.
I was just tired.
The blinds are new.
Everything's been painted.
And utilities are included.
Okay.
Hey, and you got cable?
Yes. Internet too.
You have to call to activate it.
I like the main bedroom
very much.
And the bathroom has tiles.
Awesome.
There are three rooms, then?
If I got drunk,
I wouldn't use
these stairs, for sure.
So? You're interested?
Definitely.
And you're good with NPNS?
Sorry. What?
No smoking, no pets.
You want to smoke,
you do it outside.
It's cool. No worries.
Okay.
I need the last income statement
a labor certificate,
the last payslip
a guarantor with real state
and former address.
The usual drill.
Get me all the papers.
If it's all copasetic,
I'll call.
Okay.
See, I could pay in advance.
Unbelievable.
I'm currently
in-between situations.
- Please.
- No. I'm not renting like that.
I got all the money.
I'll always pay on time.
Please.
My dad's not really
a "make exceptions" kind of guy.
Trust me.
- Your dad?
- Yes, he owns the place.
I help him manage it.
Look, if you can fill
in the papers
you do it
and get me the rest.
If not, go run your game
somewhere else.
I got nowhere else to go.
And I got no game.
Really, I just need a chance.
Please.
I'll be honest with you.
My folks, they kicked me out.
I'm a disappointment.
Now I'm like Cain for them.
I swear, I'm a good person.
And I work hard.
I will pay you on time.
Please, help me.
Come on.
Rent just went up.
Two hundred thousand more
a month.
- Cash price.
- Okay.
You won't regret it.
Thank you!
Two months upfront,
nonrefundable.
- Okay.
- You mess this up, I leave you
- like Barbie's boyfriend.
- Gotcha.
Like Barbie's boyfriend?
With no balls.
I see.
- I live next door.
Really?
Yes.
So, if you blow this my friends
will have your skinny ass out.
- Okay.
- Fill this in.
Just sign your name.
I'll take care of the rest.
It's José, right?
Jose. Jose what?
Mercado.
Mercado, like the name
of the supermarket.
Yeah.
Thanks for the explanation.
Here too.
Ta-da.
Let's see.
What are you doing?
What's it look like, honey?
One of the two things
I like most in life.
Brewing.
Come on, taste this one.
The fermentation process
is much more elaborate.
- It's a lager. Taste it.
- No.
And tell me if you liked it.
No, it'll give me a stomachache
this big.
Okay, your loss.
It's a "Henry Special."
So, let me get this straight.
You called in sick today.
They're making you an offer
to go to Mexico.
We both know
that means a promotion
that is, more money.
And you, not only
didn't give them an answer
but prefer to stay home
brewing beer
like a retired cop
- Okay, all right.
- who is growing
- a pot belly.
- Relax.
Don't tell me to relax!
Don't you ever tell me to relax.
Sorry.
David said I should express
what I feel
especially, if it upsets me.
María, what's wrong
with me staying here
taking a day off?
I want to work and to think.
What's the matter?
Why don't you go back
the way you came
so I can see your beautiful ass?
Yes or no?
That's it.
ll right, then!
All right.
Mother fucker!
Okay, so what's the plan
now?
Which plan?
This plan.
The plan is we cook.
We produce.
To sell it to whom exactly?
How much do you think you
can sell on your own?
Say if I cooked during the days
and you worked the nights.
Dude, come on.
What? Prior to Tuco, that
was your plan, wasn't it?
I know we'll produce
much less than before.
But still, what do we do?
What do we do?
First of all, there's no "we."
There's no "us" here.
You're talking me,
selling product here and there
in personal doses
on the streets.
I got profile now, bro.
Don't forget that.
Anti-Narcotics already know me.
I'm not risking my ass
for chump change.
- Then what do you suggest?
- No way!
You want us to jump into bed
with another crazy one
like Tuco?
Hell, no.
I got bills too, man!
- Responsibilities.
- You've got bills?
- Yeah.
Poor thing.
I've got rent
and services to pay.
I've already lost
more than I have made.
And to be honest
I am tired of dicking
around out here.
- You know how much I've lost?
- Tell me.
You want to know
how much I've got left?
After paying for treatment
and financing
our weekend alibi?
Zero! Zip! Nothing!
Nothing for my family
which, as you might remember,
was the damn point!
Listen to me, Jose.
Throwing in the towel
is not an option here.
That leaves us with two choices.
We go into business
with a homicidal lunatic
or you and I...
You selling whatever you can.
Well, no.
There's a third way.
What would that be?
We got to be Tuco.
Cut out the middle man.
Run our own game.
Right.
So you're going to, what?
Snort meth off a bowie knife
with some Texan boots on?
You gonna beat your homies
to death when they dis you?
For once in your life,
listen to me!
Look, I know some guys.
We can create a network.
What we should do
is to control distribution
and production.
That way,
we stay off the streets
while moving some serious glass.
We start to make money,
sky-high stacks.
- That's the point, right?
- No. No.
- Why not?
- I am not willing to do that!
- I don't agree.
- You don't agree?
- No!
- I have bad news for you.
- You don't get to vote.
- Listen to me.
I don't want to get anyone else
involved in this organization.
You know what, yo?
I'm so sorry.
- I beg your pardon?
- Yes.
This is a partnership, remember?
And we had a division of labor
at the beginning.
Remember?
You cook, I sell.
And that's exactly
how we should have kept it.
Because if it had been like that
I wouldn't have found myself
locked in a trunk
or humiliated
or with a gun to my head
or behind bars.
All that happened
after you came along.
All right.
I will admit I made mistakes
because I was overly ambitious.
But it's not gonna happen
that way anymore.
Damn straight.
You're damn right.
You know why?
'Cause we do things my way
this time, or I walk, bro.
You need me more
than I need you, Walter.
Think about it.
- All right.
- Come on.
- Quick.
- Thanks.
- El Tripa.
- What's up, brother?
- What is it, dude?
- You okay?
- Oof.
- My...
- Duplex and stuff.
- It's awesome, bro!
Yep.
Welcome to my humble abode,
bitches.
This is cool.
It echoes and everything!
- Hello, hello!
- Hey, hey!
Let me quickly give you
a virtual tour.
My room is upstairs.
Look, on this wall
a huge HD screen,
fifty inches, buddy.
The biggest one.
Buddy, you should buy 3 D!
Homo, porno 3 D!
3-D ta-tas right in your face.
Easy, jerk.
And here, right where you are
a pair of big trendy chairs
reclinomastic whatever,
like a cinema.
That's what I'm talking about!
I'm gonna leave the rest
as it is
empty, a minimalist style.
That's the new craze now, right?
Listen, buddy.
Use some Feng Shui stuff.
It rocks!
No, I mean it!
It's for the energy
and what not.
And I'm thinking of putting
just a bunch of candles
for relax.
- A massaging bed.
- The ladies like that.
The candles
and all that spiritual stuff.
This homo is setting up
a motel, buddy.
You see?
- The reclino--
- Let's get down to it.
There's some refreshments
over here
if you want to partake.
You got any other refreshments?
Yeah, don't you have some?
It's been days I don't smoke.
- No, not here.
- I'm in, dude.
No beer, no weed and no bomb.
We're talking business here,
okay?
So listen up.
This is how it goes.
I front each of you an ounce.
You sell it for five million.
I keep four
you keep one. No cutting it.
Five million an ounce?
That's too much!
- He's nuts!
- Yeah, dude.
Three and a half
so we can sell it quick.
You don't get it.
You have never tasted a
product of such quality. Ever.
And it's dry out there.
Or who else is selling
right now?
- No, nobody else.
- Okay.
So you point it how you want.
Quarter, half, teener, whatever.
But I make what I make.
Four million. No exceptions.
Cut it, you're out.
Short me, you're out.
Understood?
This is a big opportunity
I am giving you.
We'll make money big time.
All right?
Badger, what is this?
What am I giving you?
A big opportunity.
- Exactly.
- That's right, bitches!
This is the ground floor.
How far you go
is up to you, gentlemen.
All right?
Now, I got mad volume.
So bring out the product, yo.
No, not here, all right?
Not ever.
I'm not risking our necks
like that.
We're doing blind drops.
I will let you know
when and where.
But never here.
All right?
Let's get on to work, dude!
It's an armpit.
The border between the US
and Mexico is horrible.
And cartels are worse than here.
There they open up dead bodies
and take their hearts out.
They cut them here
so their tongue sticks out.
They hang them.
Those things don't happen here.
Pretty sure
that's why I'm going there.
But I thought
they would send you to D.F.
If they want you
to train with the DEA
why don't they send you
to Washington?
Why sending you to that armpit?
Or if it's Mexico, fine.
But a weekend in Acapulco,
at the very least!
Just a weekend!
Cielo?
I'm just saying.
- You finished, Walter?
- Yes, thank you.
You do this.
And then you take it.
Uncle, what's the name of that?
"Sineruto."
I saw some beautiful hotels
in D.F.
Such a pity!
I would've loved to go.
All that Mexican culture
of the flowers
the food and the colors
seems amazing to me!
I was talking to Merlinda
Henry's boss's wife.
The one with the helmet hair
- and the permanent brow--
- Shh.
Shh.
Apologize.
What?
I will not listen
to one more word
until you apologize.
For?
You know perfectly well.
Obviously I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Because you lied to me!
Because I almost ended up in
jail 'cause you robbed a store.
For everything, María.
Do you really think
you can go on like that?
As if nothing had happened?
If you hadn't tried
to return it--
Apologize!
Now or never.
Cielo
why are you punishing me?
If you don't respect me enough
to apologize,
to tell me the truth...
I need my sister back.
I'm sorry.
Uncle, I want the gory details
like you always tell me.
No, you don't.
Not this time, buddy.
It'll keep you up at night.
- So was it scary?
- Hell, yeah.
But you were
way faster than him.
I'm here telling you
the whole story, aren't I?
You're right.
But the stiff was another.
Junior.
Nah, it's fine.
You know what it is?
A cockroach comes out
from under a fridge.
You see it
and you don't think about it.
You just go and...
C'est fini.
Where do they come from?
Those guys, those crooks
like the one you dealt with.
What makes them who they are?
No.
I don't know.
All I know
is they're like the roaches.
You don't know
where they come from.
But there's a whole armada.
Be right back.
What up, man?
Okay, get off.
What's up, man? Sold.
Just joking, buddy.
Cops. Cops! Run!
Son of a bitch!
It's the cops! Run, buddy!
Fucking cops.
They can't leave you alone,
mother fuckers. Run.
Run! Come on!
Hurry up!
Over here, buddy!
Come on!
- Look. Look at him!
- The money.
- Asshole! You fell for it!
- Easy, man.
What else have you got?
- I can't believe it!
- I've got no more.
- Asshole.
- He's got no more.
- Bye, dude. Bye.
- Let's go. Let's go.
Open!
Bitch!
I wasn't sure it was you.
New car?
You know I go for the classics.
- Great ride! Congratulations.
- Thanks.
And this one doesn't bounce
like the other?
It works fine for now, yo.
Your half.
Thirty three million.
Yeah, you're welcome.
What a prick.
Help me understand the math,
okay?
I gave you one pound, correct?
It's 15 million
for every three ounces.
That's seven million
and a half each.
One pound, that's 16 ounces.
Five times seven million
and a half
it's 37 million and a half.
Not thirty three!
Wow, apart from a chemist,
now you're a mathematician.
Something came up.
Something came up?
Tripaseca got held up
by a couple junkies.
Lost an ounce and some money.
But it's cool, okay?
Shit happens.
Sorry?
Your guy got robbed
or, rather, you got robbed
- but it's cool?
- Walter, they're incidentals.
Any business considers them
in the percentages.
Even supermarkets consider
their employees may drop bottles
by accident, right?
- So it's normal.
- These things happen!
It's breakage.
You're sweating me
over five million?
No, sorry.
You're right.
I'm just the chemist here.
I'm not the street guy, yo.
But it seems to me
that what you call "breakage"
is just you
making a fool of yourself.
No! I've got
another technical term for you.
"Non-sustainable
business model."
Have you noticed,
Walter, you only
focus on the negative?
Really, dude.
We're making ten millions a day.
What's your fucking problem?
Tell me something, Jose.
What?
What happens when word gets out?
When those morons you hired
pluck up courage?
No, tell me.
What happens
once everyone knows
"that José Miguel Rosas,
the drug lord
that moron
can be robbed with impunity"!?
That's not gonna happen.
- No?
- No.
You think Tuco had breakage?
And if he happened to have any
he handled it himself.
Tuco.
Are you really comparing me
with Tuco?
You want another five million?
Is that it?
Jose, that's not the point!
Take it. There.
- It's not that!
- Then what is it?
What is it, then?
You have almost
thirty eight million
that you didn't have yesterday.
We're making bank!
And the rest, well!
Shit happens, yo.
What do we do?
Look, the guys I've got
are okay.
They get
what they're up against.
And they're careful.
So am I.
What do you do?
You're at home
all tucked in at night
with your family.
So why don't you just
give me a break for one day?
You've made
the division of labor
very clear, right?
So what the hell
do you want me to do, Walter?
Tell me! What the hell
do you want me to do?
Hey.
- How are you?
- Hi.
Didn't even know you were home.
You snuck in.
What you eating?
Pizza.
Thought we wouldn't buy
frozen food any more.
Wouldn't we?
No, you said so yourself.
Aren't those the ones
with the off-the-chart sodium?
I had a craving.
Once is no big deal.
So where's Junior?
Out.
With whom?
Lucho.
Out where?
I don't know. Somewhere.
He'll be back by 9:00.
Somewhere?
I just thought you might have
a clue where your son is.
Why don't you?
Why am I the only one
who needs to keep track
of our son?
You want to know where he is?
Just pick up the phone
and ask him.
Like I do all the time.
Perhaps you might know
something about this.
Perhaps.
Perhaps I don't.
Perhaps I smoked them
in a fugue state.
I'd like an explanation!
Give me a break, Walter!
Sorry?
Why would you do this?
You're pregnant!
Three and a half cigarettes
won't harm the baby.
I'm glad you're so sure, Doctor!
Three and a half!
That was it!
I tossed the rest!
And you'll be very glad
to hear that I feel ashamed.
Cielo, I don't get it.
This is so unlike you.
- What happens?
- How would you know?
What was
that?
Henry, wait.
Where do you...?
Shh.
Wow.
What do you want, bro?
You asked me
what I want you to do.
I want you to handle it.