What's going on?
Some meeting with your lawyers.
- Me?
- Yes, sir.
They're waiting for you.
Hi, Jairo.
Come with me.
Did you hear about Carlitos?
People say he escaped
to Venezuela.
He's dead.
It wasn't me.
It wasn't a message.
It wasn't payback.
It was a mistake
made by a third party
who has since been dealt with.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
The second point.
The deal you had
with Gustavo Cortés
is still in place.
- Okay.
- Don't "okay" me.
Let's speak clearly.
Do you have something to say?
No, Mario.
I'm keeping my mouth shut.
I didn't say a
word.
The laundry
was right above the lab.
There's no way
I could say I wasn't in on it.
I'm looking
at eight years
minimum.
But I'm doing my time
like I'm supposed to.
I'm no rat, and you
know it.
I'm doing my part in
the deal.
Good.
The deal is the deal.
What I don't understand is
how
the other party is paying
me.
They seized all my money.
How am I supposed
to live in here?
to provide for my family?
I knew the risks.
We all did.
But the police
and anti-narcotics
left me broken,
and that wasn't
part of the deal.
And I know for a fact they
got Enano and Mugre
yesterday.
They're getting all of us.
All of us with no money.
Now, it's not going to be
me,
but remember this.
Absent the hazard pay,
sooner or later,
someone's going to
flip
and will ruin us all.
No one's flipping.
Everyone gets their hazard pay.
I appreciate
what you're saying and
all,
Mario,
but the man is dead.
The lab's a hole in
the ground.
Where will you get
the money from?
There's something new starting.
It's going to make you whole.
Something new right now?
With the police looking at you?
How?
"How" is my business.
Hanging tight
is your business.
Your family is going to be fine.
You have my word.
Do you need more?
Okay.
Who's next?
That's your choice.
Enano is across town.
Mugre is in Medellín.
Unless we take a plane,
I don't really think
we can visit them all today.
We have to visit
them all today.
We have
to do it.
So they made me
a job offer
and...
And here I am.
In action.
I think the best way to
describe what happened to me
is to say that I
opened my eyes
with a poem
written by William Blake,
the English poet.
Recite it.
[laughing
]
No, no.
No, please.
That would be pathetic.
No, please, come on.
Go on.
Basically, there are three
verses of the poem called
"Proverbs of hell",
and it
"The road of excess
leads to the palace of wisdom.
Prudence
is a rich ugly
old maid
courted by
incapacity.
He who desires
but acts not,
breeds pestilence".
"We are compelled
to consume our lives
today".
I have always thought
if the best thing to do
is to be a good
person.
Because, finally,
nobody is going to applaud
you
for that.
But I think
that this is
the only way to feel
the real pleasure
in life.
And we have to allow ourselves
before it's too late.
It's now or never.
- Walter.
- Hi.
What are you
doing?
I'm unpacking.
I'm moving back in.
I'll keep the condo for now,
selling it in this market,
I'd get killed.
I'll keep it a little longer
to see what happens.
Do you think
this is a good idea?
Yes, yes.
Of course.
I don't know, my friends,
but do you really think
it's necessary
to bring scary Mario here?
You are an amazing pair,
like Batman and Robin,
two friends.
Why do you want to be
the three musketeers?,
Huey, Dewey, and Louie?
You're going to look
like the three stooges.
Okay, okay, Saúl,
we get your idea,
but we need Mario.
You know how this works, Saúl.
Mario knows the distributors
and how to manage them.
I must remind you
he said he was going
to break my legs.
Let's be honest here.
All of us wanted
to break your legs
some time.
- And we didn't.
- Very good!
Thank you very much
for your calming words.
Listen, listen.
Don't take it personal, bro.
Mario threatened me,
he threatened the teacher,
he probably
threatened someone
before breakfast this
morning.
It's what he does.
And that's why we need
them.
Okay, okay.
Let it be noted
that I do this under duress.
Okay. Duly noted.
Tell Mario he can come in.
All right, Mario.
I want we raise our white flags
and that we don't--
Yes, yes, yes.
Now that we're all together,
here are the ground rules.
Division of labor.
I handle the business.
You cook the meth.
I don't tell you
how to mix your
chemicals
and you do not tell me
how to take care of
business.
Is that absolutely
clear?
Sure.
All right.
Let's take the tour.
Of course.
Please, Mario, have a seat.
Very good, gentlemen.
Clearly, we're talking
about renting,
not buying.
You need an ongoing business
someplace you can slide in,
do your thing, and remain
anonymous.
That said,
show time.
This is your best bet.
Got machines running,
forklifts,
people coming and going.
You're going to stay
way under the radar.
And the owner's solid.
He can't wait to throw up
a curtain wall,
stack some boxes,
give you the space you need.
Regarding privacy,
he's got his business,
you've got yours
and never the twain shall meet.
Like the successful marriages
do.
The ones that work.
What do you think?
Machines like this
need to have
a lot of power, right?
- That's good.
- Yes.
What about the smell?
More good news.
I've been there
when it's up and running.
This place stinks already.
You'll blend right in.
How many employees?
Good question.
I knew you'd ask.
Sixteen poor people.
They provide for their families
with their earnings here,
so they'll be deaf,
blind and dumb.
Of course you can
investigate them all you want.
If there's somebody
you don't like, we fire him.
What does the alchemist say?
Wait a minute.
Is that a corrugator?
That's an antique.
This machine works
with steam and salt.
They use it to mould
paper.
And it's really noisy!
It's perfect, right?
Of course not!
Steam and
salt.
When this thing is
running,
it's like a jungle in there.
There's a lot of humidity.
It'll ruin the product.
Can't you just get
a couple of
dehumidifiers
in some construction
store?
No!
Okay.
Moving on.
Spacious, isolated location,
a lot of light
and , the best of it
you get all the free tortillas
you want.
Sorry.
What's that Saúl?
No, that's my cousin.
Forget about it.
Let's move on.
The problem with that
is that it'll make the tortillas
smell like cat piss.
Somebody's bound to notice that.
There's have to be some kind
of workaround, right?
It's a technical problem.
You guys are technical guys.
Be creative!
No, Saúl.
Anything food-related
is going to have unannounced
government inspections.
We don't want any risk.
Okay, fine.
Gentlemen,
all I'm asking
is that you keep an open mind
and think real good
before answering
about the next option,
my favorite option.
This one.
- No!
- Not even close!
What's that place?
Don't ask him
because he will end
selling it to you.
Do we have any other option?
I know it's a long shot.
But you lose nothing.
We were around here, anyway.
All I can say
to recommend this one
is we're talking about an owner
who is highly amenable
for dirty business.
Gentlemen, here you have it.
If you're going
to break my heart,
please, do it now.
I'll start.
This is way too small.
Saúl, we have no space.
What do we do with the smell?
That thing rolls up,
and we're open to the world.
It's useless.
I don't know if anybody noticed,
but there's a cop shop
a quarter of a mile away.
It's like being
inside the wolf's mouth.
Okay, so let's go have lunch.
Saúl, what is this for?
That's a protection mesh.
Like a safety net.
They use it to cover
the constructions
or destructions,
like this company,
and to avoid debris
fall over the people
who pass by.
This is perfect!
Didn't you hear him?
What do you mean "perfect"?
This is interesting.
When they're going
to demolish some place,
they cover all the front
of the building with this,
and that lets the house isolated
from the exterior.
Nobody goes in there
because there's nothing
valuable.
But couldn't the neighbors
suspect anything
if they see movements?
No, not at all.
Not at all
because there is always
some kind of watchman.
There is the watchman
and the workers.
The watchman also prevents
people to go in with drugs
or to look for something else.
And the construction market
is rising,
so we have houses like this
everywhere.
We have places to choose from.
Okay.
And what do we do with smells?
We have to look for houses
or buildings
near those places
that send horrible smells out.
I don't know,
near the river
or some tannery.
Listen, bro.
Speak clear to me.
What the hell is a tannery?
It's a place where the
leather
is processed.
You will smell them.
I think it's an option
we could use.
The problem
is that we have
to move in and out
for every cook.
Set up the lab, cook, and then
take everything down?
- That's terrible, awful.
- No, no, no.
It's challenging but doable.
Take it as a challenge.
Saúl, did we investigate
these people?
Yes, Mario told me
their contacts in jail
know them
and we can be relaxed.
This is a family business,
they're three brothers.
Roberto, the bigger brother,
he's the owner.
That over there, he's Fernando.
And the younger there,
he's Peto.
They live by this demolition
company,
buy they have an extra job.
What kind of job?
They are experts
in demolitions,
so they're
magicians
disassembling doors and
locks.
So they rob other
near houses
that they see are empty.
They study the
houses
while they're
working.
And how do you know them?
Because they have
had
legal problems,
they called Saúl
and Saúl helped them.
With the right amount of money,
they can keep their mouths shut
in a real loyal and clean way.
Because hygiene
comes first.
Good energy,
brothers!
Do you think so?
Tripa, bro,
we sound great.
What do you think?
It's out of tune.
Good, boys.
I have some discounts
in guitars,
- if you're interested.
- No, man.
We're looking
for something else.
How do you call
those big cases
where you put all
the equipments?
It's something really big.
Yes, sure.
What size are you
looking for?
- Big.
- The biggest you have, man.
Come, I'll show you.
Recessed hardware, foam
lining,
German wheels.
This is very resistant.
You'll say.
Man, I have
one question:
How much weight--?
How much weight will this hold?
It's rated for 900 pounds.
So unless your band
plays lead bricks,
you should be okay.
Hey, man, hey!
Enough, enough, stop that!
Let the grown-ups work.
Don't worry about him,
he has some mental problems.
I'm going to need four of them.
- Credit card?
- Cash.
Man, cash.
Cash, bro.
Okay, friends,
I'm going to give you some gift.
I'll throw in stenciling.
What's your band called?
How are you, Tripa?
- Is everything okay?
- How are you?
How's everything
going?
So what?
Are you back?
I'm really back, bro.
Awesome! Good!
Here you have what I
promised.
The boss is loaded, man.
Listen, bro.
If you need something,
anything, just let us know.
Okay. You know it, bro.
If you need references,
let me know.
Mono, why would he?
He has already worked
with us.
Okay, okay, okay.
- I'll let you know.
- Okay.
Okay. We better hit it then.
See you later.
Okay, it is the same
job
as always.
You arrive, isolate the house
or the
building
the same way as when you
are going to demolish
it.
Everything's the same
except for one important detail.
No stealing
the houses around.
Exactly!
No stealing.
Not a toothpick,
not the spare change
in the floor.
Nothing
From now on, the houses
around the place
are out of bounds.
Understood?
From time to time,
you're going to see
these two
in the house isolated.
As far as you're
concerned,
they are ghosts.
You don't see them.
You don't hear them.
You don't say
"good morning".
You don't speak
unless you're spoken to.
If they tell you to
jump,
you don't ask what
for,
you jump.
Now, you need a name for
them?
You have them.
You call them "yes,
sir"
and "no, sir".
If you have any problems,
you come to me.
That's all.
Here's the deal.
The finishing tank
is a tight fit.
So...
With this motor
you've got here on top...
- The agitation motor.
- The agitation motor on top,
the tank's not going to fit
in the box.
It's just too tall.
Besides, the biggest
equipment's cases
we have
will finish here.
- Right?
Now, I thought
we'd put a collar on the tank
and carry the motor in
separately, alongside
the condenser.
On the day,
we just twist it
into place
while we're setting up.
Yes.
Very good.
Yes, sir.
Do you think the old man
and his guys
can build it up?
Yes, yes.
I know they have bought
a new welder
for the aluminum work.
So...
And if they can pull off
the magnet,
- they can handle this.
- Of course they do.
Now, listen,
about the smell
I was thinking on doing
something I saw in Mexico.
They put some tents
and install several tubes
because there--
Shit.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Hi.
Sorry I'm interrupting.
No, not at all.
We were just wrapping up.
He is Walter.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
I'm a friend of Jose.
This little man is Byron.
Byron, hi!
I've heard a lot about you.
Pleased to meet you.
Do you know what I've heard?
That you were in the hospital
and you were very brave.
I'm sorry, he's really shy
and he mostly just wants
to play his game.
I know them well.
I have two of my own.
And...
Well, I should go.
Don't you want to stay
for dinner?
No, I have...
I have to...
I have several things to do.
No, I mean it.
Stay with us.
At least for a beer.
Okay, yes, thank you.
I'll help Andrea
and bring you the
beer.
Go, please.
Sir.
Gentlemen.
The house has
security cameras.
Don't go to the backyard.
What's your name?
They call me Peto.
You're listening modern jazz
in JMFA.
I have to say,
seeing you with
Andrea and that
little boy...
It was nice.
It's good, perfect.
- Do you think so?
- Yes.
Yes, I know.
I like it too.
I feel good. It's nice.
You two look right.
And the way she looks at you?
She looks at you
and I see she wants
something serious with
you.
Do you think so?
And do you want
it?
Well, bro...
That wouldn't bother me at all.
You know?
Of
course.
And what's the plan?
What plan do
you mean?
I mean this.
Work.
Are you going to tell her
all the truth?
I don't really have a plan.
I don't even know
what's going to happen tomorrow.
But...
Well, I...
I think she knows
I'm into something,
something weird,
but...
She's not stupid.
But she doesn't ask me
and I didn't tell her anything.
I don't think that changes.
- I'm not going to tell her
anything.
- No, okay.
That's my secret, you
know?
- I'm not telling her that.
-I know, I know.
I believe you,
Jose.
I can't pretend
that this doesn't
affect me.
It does.
You
know?
This is our job.
But...
I trust you completely.
This has to be your decision.
I mean, you've earned that.
Seriously?
Are you really saying so?
I really mean it.
Listen, Jose,
I'm speaking from experience.
I can tell you
that secrets
transform and, finally,
create barriers
between people.
All that you've done,
it's a part of you.
That's the truth.
If you choose to spend
the rest of your life
with this person,
then you'll have to
decide
how much of that truth
you'll share with her.
Let me understand.
Let me check
if I'm getting
what you're telling me.
Are you saying
I should tell her everything?
Every little detail?
Like what happened with Guido?
I'm not proud of that.
No, no, Jose, Jose.
I'm just telling you
that I trust you
and that I know you're
going
to take the right call.
If she loves you,
she'll understand.
Cielo, no.
I don't like the work
that washing expert
is doing in my car!
He's polishing it
horizontally,
and you're
supposed
to do that in
circles.
I don't mean to tell
him
how he has to work,
but it's simple quality control.
That's called
"processes standardization".
Let's change the subject.
Guess what.
- What?
- Guess what?
No, María.
Now I can't be--
Henry's back at work.
That's
wonderful.
We are happy.
But I don't forget
they laughed him
out of the office
when he told them
about that chicken man.
They said he was crazy.
They didn't believe him.
But he was right.
And he loves his job.
Clearly, if it were me,
I'd tell them all to go to hell.
But it's what he
wants, right?
- He's fine.
- It was moving.
To see him going to work,
with his cane, but walking.
He's alive again.
And I...
I want to thank you
for that, really.
You and Walter.
We couldn't have done it
without your help.
We are really grateful.
I'm just glad
he's feeling better.
Yes.
Speaking of husbands,
have you thought about what
you're going to do?
- About what?
- What do you mean "what"?
Walter's birthday
is coming. Did you forget it?
Whatever you need,
I'm here.
I don't
think
we're going to do
anything this year.
What are you talking about?
He was diagnosed around his
birthday, right?
So it's been a whole hard year,
specially for him.
Listen, I've had my problems
with him.
I'm still angry with him
because what he did
when Henry was threatened
and we went home,
all of us protected
by the police,
but I'm trying to forget
all of that
because there are
more important things in life.
- María!
- I really mean it.
At his age, a new birthday?
Cielo, this is really important!
After all he's been through,
you have to celebrate.
We're talking
about another year of life.
What are you doing?
You don't smoke.
You are a grown-up also.
You can't be doing that,
you have to take care
of yourself,
and you can't do this
around Valentina.
I hope you don't.
And you can't smoke
around your employees.
- I know that that is illegal.
- Shut up!
Why do you talk to me like that?
I'm trying to help you.
- I'm' trying to--
- Will you shut up?
- What's wrong with you?
- Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Cielo.
Done. 1.45 and 1.50.
1.45 and 1.50?
Yes.
49 pounds.
Good yield, right?
Excellent.
And now?
What do we do?
- We leave.
- Just like that?
Peto and his people
will destroy this place.
Okay.
- Hi.
- Hi, Walter.
How are you?
I called you ten times.
- I left you messages.
- Yes.
- Hi.
- What happened?
- I'm sorry.
I saw your calls,
but I was really busy.
I have a thousand
things going on.
Something happened with you?
Not me, Cielo.
¿Cielo? What?
What happened with Cielo?
Now she's fine,
she's resting,
but she had a
breakdown.
She's very depressed.
¿Very depressed?
And that...?
Who diagnosed her?
I did,
because I don't know
what else to call
what happened today.
- But, what happened today?
- She started screaming like
some crazy woman.
What did she say
when she was yelling?
She was talking to
me,
she was shouting to
me.
She just yelled, "Shut up,
shut up," over and over again.
And then she started crying.
I don't
know.
What happened?
Are you gambling
again?
No, no.
And how is she?
Is she fine?
Yes. She's sleeping now.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Did you know she's smoking?
Yes.
Occasionally, maybe.
It's not a regular thing.
Is it the
cancer?
No, this has nothing
to do with the cancer.
Well, something
happened.
I know Cielo,
she's not like that.
I don't mean to point
the finger,
but I need to know
the truth.
- Tell me!
- María...
You can tell me now.
Okay.
All right, I'll tell you.
You heard about Ernesto Silva?
Ernesto, her boss?
Yes, her boss.
No, what happened to him?
- You didn't?
- No, tell me.
To make a long story short,
he fell a couple of weeks ago.
- An accident?
- Yes.
- He died?
- No, no.
Almost.
He gave himself a concussion,
and fractured
a couple vertebrae.
He may never walk again.
You can imagine.
Yes, but...
That couldn't explain
why Cielo is in
this situation.
Couldn't that?
Of course it can.
I can understand her feelings.
What?
Don't you know they...?
Didn't she tell you?
Tell me what, Walter?
María, you talk
about everything.
Tell me!
Don't you...?
I messed it up!
I'm a stupid!
Wait a
minute.
She was having an
affair
with Ernesto?
Yes, yes. No.
Yes, but not now.
Not at present.
But, they did?
Yes, yes.
Cielo and I
are trying to get back together
and move on.
Walter, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I swear I didn't
know it.
We have been trying to put
things back together,
and then the accident happened.
I understand
this is a lot of pressure
for her right now.
María,
I'm begging you,
please, keep this to yourself.
I'm really asking you.
Please, don't tell
this to Henry.
You know he's a chauvinist,
and I...
I don't want him to think less
of Cielo.
Walter, I'm really sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
Do you promise me
not to tell him?
I promise, yes.
I'll leave.
I have to
leave.
I'll walk you out.
No, relax, you don't have to.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
- Say hi to Henry.
- Yes.
Tell Cielo to call me.
Yes,
yes.
Once upon a time,
there was a princess
with big green eyes
who was recognized
because she had
a diamond here.
She's beautiful, right?
The princess lived
in her castle
in the top of the mountain,
that had 15 rooms.
The princes lived far, far way.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Where were we?
Okay, once upon a time,
there was a princess
with big green eyes
who lived far away
in the mountain.
What about that?
Look at that, dad!
My favorite gun!
M60.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Argh!
That's
awful.
Okay, this is our share.
80.000 dollars each.
No, wait a second, Mario.
After the payroll,
the dealers,
the
demolishers,
we should have 270.000.
I don't understand it.
You're forgetting
about the mules.
30.000 for them.
30.000?
All that money?
They are taking a risk.
We have to pay them.
Yes, but...
What did Gustavo pay his
mules?
Gustavo didn't use mules.
He didn't need them.
He spent 20 years
building his own distribution.
He had 16 refrigerator trucks
running his product.
And you know where they are now?
Government impound.
You don't like paying the mules?
Maybe you shouldn't have
killed him.
Hey, hey, hey.
There's still a lot
of money here,
and just from one
cook.
Relax.
I'll be good this time,
since you're putting on
the green eyeshade.
My supplier and I
came to an agreement.
The methylamine was free
this time.
But brace yourself,
because the next barrel
is going to cost big.
Can we continue,
or you have anymore
burning questions?
No, no, no.
Go on.
Okay.
Only José and me
had the money to start
the business,
so you owe us that, Walter.
Jose, thanks for that.
Good.
We have to pay
the old man and his guys
because they built
the portable lab.
This is Saúl's cut.
Legacy cost.
Legacy?
What's that?
There are nine guys
that were part
of the previous operation.
They are in jail
and they know a lot.
This is the cost
of their silence.
Police and anti-narcotics
seized their hazard pay,
so we are going to make
them whole.
Poor guys!
But why are we paying
them?
These were Gustavo's employees.
They might have been
Gustavo's employees,
but they're my guys.
Really?
So what are they doing
to further our interests?
The cops are looking at them
very closely.
We don't want them
furthering our interests
before the cops.
We want them far from us.
So why are we paying them?
Because it's what you do.
No, it's what you do.
My guys are keeping
their mouths shut.
We make them whole.
- As simple as that.
- Not that simple.
It sounds like a simple
shakedown.
We're paying for their silence.
That's blackmail.
This is what we do
in this business.
- End of story.
- No, sir!
Hey, hey.
This is your problem.
It should come out of your end.
Okay, okay.
If it's that important,
just take it out of mine.
I don't care.
Here you have.
No, Jose, it's okay.
I'll pay my share.
Don't worry.
Let me tell you something.
This is how it's going to be
from here on out.
My guys are ongoing expenditure,
Walter.
Take it as it is.
35.000 dollars.
That's less
than with Gustavo.
Listen, Walter,
just because you shot the boss
don't make you the boss.
Jose, are you okay?
Yes, I guess.
Are you
sure?
You are not
the same.
Well...
Bye.
Broke it off with Andrea.
She told me
she's going to tell Brock today.
I'm thinking about that.
I'm still going to take care
of the rent and stuff.
But the working situation--
I meant this.
What happened inside.
The money
distribution.
And I'm telling you
my personal problems.
Thanks for asking,
I'm going to be fine.
Bitch.
So what?
About the money,
you're looking at it wrong.
You know?
We cooked for Gustavo
about 220 ponds a week.
And now, despite it's good,
we have 50 pounds.
We maybe cleared less money,
but we have a bigger piece
of the pie.
It's like you said,
now we're owners, not employees.
That's the thing.
I've been thinking
about Victor.
- Víctor?
- Yes.
Not Víctor himself,
but the moment
Gustavo
cut his throat.
Why are you thinking
about that, man?
- Are you insane?
- I don't know.
Maybe because...
All this time I was sure
that Gus did what he
did
to send us a message.
And now?
Maybe there's another
reason.
Víctor decided to cook
that batch on his own.
Do you
understand?
He took liberties
that weren't his to take.
He went too far.
- No.
- What Gustavo did
was just a business
measure.
Listen, Walter,
I will tell you this just once.
Forget those ideas
you have, Walter.
I know Mario very well
and he's a good guy.
He knows what his place is.
I hope so.
Because I know very
well what my place is.