You can come on out.
It's an actual vacuum store.
It says so on the card,
doesn't it?
I guess I figured
Vacuum Cleaner Repair
was just a facade,
a term of art.
Leave your luggage
and step right here.
There.
What are we going to do
about this?
I wouldn't like to look
like a professional boxer.
We'll delete that later.
Chin up and hold still.
There.
You'll most likely
end up in Santuario.
Santuario? What's that?
It's a little town,
very cozy.
Very nice weather.
When am I leaving?
It's gonna take me some time
to get your
new situation fixed.
And in the meantime?
Until then,
you're gonna be staying here.
I got a place downstairs,
out of sight.
It's not the Ritz-Carlton
but it's comfortable enough.
How long
are we talking about?
Considering you got your face up
in TV recently,
maybe not in the best channel
or the best time slot,
I'm thinking, two days.
Maybe three.
The only thing is...
Under these circumstances,
what's another problem?
I don't like to do this,
and I usually try to avoid it,
but you'll have a bunk mate.
A bunk mate?
Hold on, is he...?
He's still here?
He's a special case.
Gonna take some doing.
How's he holding up?
You be the judge.
You can see the room here.
Don't worry, Maria,
we will find him.
We will find Henry
and Gómez.
You have my word.
Stop, the door is open.
Call it in,
get her out of here.
Move.
I, got to his door,
and I could hear music inside.
I knocked on his door.
Does this pussy cry
through the entire thing?
This looks
like a chick flic.
Turn that cry baby off.
Just watch.
It's important
you see something, Joaquín.
Then, you know, we turn around,
and there is this kid
on a dirt bike, looking at us.
Then I heard he was called
Agustín Herrera,
that kid that went missing,
that was everywhere.
And then out of nowhere, Peto,
that opie,
pulls out a gun
and shoots the kid.
Like it was nothing.
He just shot him.
This is Peto Calderón
we're talking about?
Yes, that's him,
he's crazy.
He has no morals,
he has no feelings, he--
What do you think
about this?
Let's go and kill
that motherfucker.
Hey, Uncle. Hold up.
What? What now?
-No, nothing big.
-So?
I think we should keep him
locked up for a while,
get a couple of cooks
under our belt.
Peto, you seriously giving me
this turn-the-other-cheek crap?
He ratted you out.
Personally.
No problem.
I know, I know,
but we still got
600 gallons of methylamine.
We can make a lot of
money here.
We've got all the money
in the world.
We won the lottery.
Who gives a shit about meth?
We can make a lot more money
with that meth.
What do you say?
No matter how much you got,
how do you turn
your back on more?
You little...
son of a bitch,
it's the other thing.
No.
It's that Lidia woman.
You're sweet on her,
you little bastard.
You just want to stay here
and keep seeing her
and talking to her
as if you were Romeo.
Right?
Look at his eyes sparkling.
Hey, it's all about this
right here?
Come on.
You can do better.
I mean,
that one's so uptight,
she's probably got a wood
chipper for a coochie.
- Nothing there.
- Ha, ha, ha.
You stick it in down there,
you're pulling back a stump.
No, I think it's the opposite.
She's one of those
who order you around in bed.
This way, that way,
more, less, more, more.
She's always like that.
Ha, ha, ha.
The heart wants
what the heart wants,
right?
Let's not get into that.
Let's go back
and watch some more
of that crybaby rat?
How sweet!
Ha, ha, ha.
What?
Nothing.
Don't you want to know
what happened to my hand?
No.
Just as well, it's none
of your business.
Make yourself useful.
Give me a list
of hitters,
mercenaries, gunmen,
precise people.
People that don't miss.
Then I need
a background check,
I need every detail.
Make sure there are
no undercover cops
on the team.
I need a list
of 15 men to pick from.
Five should do it.
Providing they're the
right men for the job.
- Job?
- Write it down.
Who are we hitting?
What do you mean
who are we hitting?
Who? Saúl.
We're hitting Joaquín.
Peto's uncle and his men.
What?
They murdered Henry,
they stole my money,
everything I worked for.
They have to pay!
Write!
I don't know any hitmen.
Yes, you do!
I'm sure you defended one,
you know a guy
who knows a guy....
Don't play the fool!
I'm paying top dollar.
People need to work, right?
Anyone can do it!
- Walter.
- Think, Saúl!
You mind if I give you
a nickel's worth of advice?
Just for old time's sake?
You're worried about
your wife and kids?
Don't leave.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Some people might say you're
leaving her high and dry.
As far as the police
are concerned,
Cielo is fine.
She is a blameless victim.
She's not my accomplice.
Yes and no.
The phone call
was a smart move.
It exonerates her.
Odds are it was recorded.
It's gonna play great
for a jury.
But, Walter, this story
runs too deep,
it's too fucked up
to just go away.
What do you think will happen?
- They're going after her.
- She knows nothing, Saúl!
Well, too bad for her, then.
She's got nothing to trade.
This is serious.
There are two agents missing.
They have to show some results.
They will dig into Cielo's life
until they find
something on her.
If they can't catch
Walter Blanco, the big fish,
they will turn her
into the bad guy
to replace you.
She has nothing to do
with this! Nothing!
She must've had something
to do and they'll find it.
First thing they're gonna do,
they will RICO your wife
and kids out of the house.
Your bank accounts,
they're frozen.
Everything.
Her picture's probably
on TV right now,
next to yours.
Who's gonna hire her?
Saúl, money's no problem!
I know, I know.
I don't mean
to contradict you,
but getting it to her,
it's impossible.
The Feds are just praying
that you'll make contact.
For them to get something.
Internet, the phone--
It's all tapped.
If they receive one peso,
they will take it.
By now they must be working
together with the DPA
to try and find you.
They will take
everything you've got,
like they did with Mario.
So you propose what?
I propose what?
Stay. Face the music.
I mean, how much time
have you got left?
And you bring a barrel full of
drug money, maybe that soothes
some troubled waters.
Maybe they let your family
stay in the house.
And your family can be well off.
You think I want to run,
Saúl?
I'm doing this
for the good of my family.
What I do,
I do it for my family.
My money
goes to my children.
Not just this barrel.
All of it!
I'm going to kill him
and his entire crew,
and I'm gonna
take back what is mine
and give it to my children
and then, and only then...
Am I through!
Until then!
Do you understand?
Everything good?
Define "good."
You're set, Saúl,
time to go.
You'll be a little longer.
I'm still working
on transportation.
Change of plans.
- Excuse me?
- Saúl's coming with me.
No, that's not--
Saúl, we're going together.
I can use him.
I'll give you
two or three minutes
to work this thing out.
I'll wait for you up there
or we'll talk later.
No, no, no, no, hold on.
Walter, listen to me.
I'm a civilian,
I'm not your lawyer anymore.
I'm nobody's lawyer.
The fun's over.
From here on out,
I'm Mr. Low Profile.
Just another douche bag
with a job
so no one can find me.
I have to start over!
You're still part of this.
Whether you like it or not.
I'm sorry.
I don't think so.
You remember what I told you?
It's not over.
It's over, Walter.
It's over.
You cooperated
with the Justice.
We will take
all your assets...
Your houses,
your cars...
All your properties...
You have to cooperate...
Is she even listening?
Do you understand
what's happening here?
Yes.
I understand that you will use
I'm in terrible trouble.
everything in your power
against me and my children
unless I give you Walter.
Ma'am, is there anybody
else in the house?
What about your son?
If I go look in his room,
am I gonna see him?
Are you lying to me?
He's not gonna pop out
and surprise me?
If this guy
takes his hand away,
are you gonna scream?
Scream or...
Please, my son is not here.
He's at his friend's house.
Please don't hurt my baby.
Shhh...
We got a lot of respect
for professor Blanco.
There's just something
that we gotta straighten out.
We know that you've
been talking to the police,
and that's okay.
You gotta do that.
But you've seen some people.
Like that lady
who came into the car wash.
Remember her?
Yes.
You said anything about her?
No, I haven't.
You sure about that?
I swear, I didn't say a word.
The police don't need
to know anything about her.
I'm gonna
need you to say it.
I... will... not...
say anything about her.
Ever.
I swear it.
Okay.
When we leave,
you're not gonna go
running to those
police officers out front?
They're out front.
No, no, I swear I won't.
Okay. Okay.
You know what?
We don't want
to come back here.
Okay?
Mmhmm.
I don't like
the nocturnal meetings.
Stay there,
we'll talk this way.
I went to
professor Blanco's house,
we talked to his wife.
You don't...
have to say the name.
Sure.
The message?
was received loud and clear.
Yeah.
Look, I know
you did your best.
But I think right now
a message won't do.
Good evening,
will you have tea as usual?
No, I brought my own.
No, yes...
bring me one
and some sweetener,
I'm out.
Sure.
The person we're talking about
saw my face.
We can't just settle
for you sending messages.
I know.
Really, if you'd been there,
I think you'd see it different.
She seems like a nice lady
watching out for her kids.
You're not going to have
a problem with her.
I wish I had your
certainty,
but I'm not like
you and your uncle.
I'm not used
to this kind of risk.
We're gonna have
to take a break.
Util things
settle down.
I have 23 kilos
packed and ready to go.
I wish you luck with it.
It's 92%.
92%.
Tested it twice.
And it's blue.
Just like before.
Lidia...
-92%, that's Heisenberg level.
-Mmhmm.
He's not... with you?
Well, next best thing, Rosas.
They're looking for him.
Well, they're not going
to find him, he's with us,
and he's not going anywhere.
Lidia, this is what
your guys in Europe
have been begging for, right?
I just think
we work together... good.
We make a good team.
It's mutually good.
92%?
I'll show you the way,
the only entrance,
we'll unload later.
Welcome to your new identity
and your new house.
Kitchen, bathroom,
bedroom, deposit.
You got about a month's
worth of food on hand,
most of it's canned goods,
but there's steaks
in the freezer.
You got a generator outside,
ought to be enough in the tank
to last a month,
providing you save up
and use it moderately.
There's no heat
or chimney here,
there are some blankets
if you're cold.
There's no TV either.
Mountains won't allow us
to have any signal at all.
The reception's
pretty much nil.
There are some books here.
I hope they're good,
Literature is not my thing.
If you need anything
from the outside,
I'll need some notice.
That means I'm paying you
50 million pesos
to bring me food
once a month?
Well, yes.
It's a risk, Walter.
I'm protecting you.
It's no that I'm charging you
for the deodorant,
or the cans.
And we are very far away--
Yes, that's clear.
My clients and I don't usually
have an ongoing relationship.
Normally, you and I
would have already gone
our separate ways,
but you're you.
Where's the phone?
No phone, Walter,
there's no signal here,
so no one will be able
to trace you.
There's no car either
so you don't go running
into the wolf's mouth.
Whatever you need, just...
I know, you'll bring it
once a month.
Look, I have business
to conduct..
Your business is your business.
My business is keeping
you out of custody.
That's my business.
What if I need to go out?
If I want to go out?
You can walk up to the fence
or walk down
to the nearest town,
it's 15 kilometers away,
all I'm saying is,
if you leave this place,
you will get caught.
And, I gotta tell you,
if I find out that
you've left the reservation,
I won't be coming back.
You understand?
Sure.
Okay, fine.
Let's get the things
out of the truck,
you'll tell me what you need
and I'm off.
Tomorrow.
- Thank you, uncle.
- Come on.
Rosas, you awake?
Yeah.
Okay.
I wanted
to congratulate you, Jose.
That batch that you
just cooked was 92%.
Thanks.
You know what?
We just went
by the bakers' store
and got some donuts
fresh out of the oven.
Okay.
Peto!
What?
Would you mind
leaving the tarp off tonight?
Please.
I don't think it's
going to rain.
Might get cold.
I just...
I just wanna see the stars.
I like the stars too.
Sure. Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Got a whole new batch.
Sure.
Goodnight.
Run, run!
Come on!
Hold still!
Just kill me now!
What did you do
that for?
Kill me now because there's no
way I'm doing one more cook!
You psycho fucks!
What do you think
you're doing?
Where do you think
you're going?
You think
you're going anywhere?
Get walking.
Bring him over here.
Come on!
Do as you're told!
Where was he going?
Hi!
Hello.
You're Andrea Cantillo, right?
Yes.
How can I help you?
Hi, I'm Peto, I'm a friend of
José Miguel Rosas.
Are you a friend of Jose's?
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
How can I help you?
You used to date, right?
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here
so late.
I was calling him last week
but I got no answer.
That's why I'm here.
Do you know how Jose is?
Fine.
He keeps talking about you.
Peto Calderón.
Nice to meet you.
Do you know where he is?
Yeah, he's right...
over there.
In that truck.
He didn't want to get down,
he felt embarrassed.
Wait, he's here?
I wanted to meet you--
How come?
Andrea, no!
Andrea!
No! Andrea! No!
Now, now, it's over.
Hey, remember.
There's still the kid.
He's still in there.
Think about that.
Did you bring
the glasses I asked for?
Without a prescription,
I had to take an educated guess
and shotgun it.
One of these
ought to come close.
Do you have news
from Cielo?
Is she in a better place?
Nah, she's still at that
place with the kids.
There's no court date yet.
The news was talking
about a grand jury,
but they didn't say when.
I saw her
public defender on TV.
These will do.
Really?
What are they doing for money?
She's working part-time
in a call center.
She dispatches taxis.
Leaves the baby with a neighbor
when she goes in.
She looks pretty good.
It seems.
I took a run
by your old house.
And?
The auction's
still pending.
Put a fence around it.
They put up a fence?
To keep the homeless
from coming in,
they were using it
as a hotel.
The neighbors complained.
You ready?
Yeah.
Sorry about last time.
It should go better now.
I watched a couple
of YouTube videos.
It's all about
finding the vein.
That's the important thing.
Let's see.
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
Here.
You-- you do it.
I'll leave this here.
All right.
I will see you on
the afternoon of the 15th.
Stay a little longer?
Yeah, I got a long trip
ahead of me.
It's really far.
I'll give you
another 15 million.
Just for a while.
15 million.
One hour.
Cards?
Yes.
Well.
I guess I'll deal.
Poker?
One of these days when you
come up here I'll be dead.
And all my money
is over there.
What will you do?
Will you give it
to my family?
Would you do it
if I asked you to?
If I said yes,
would you believe me?
Walter Junior Blanco,
to the Principal's office.
I'm sorry to pull you
out of class,
it's your Aunt María.
It sounds very important.
You can take it in here, okay?
Go on.
Hi!
Here he is.
Aunt María?
Junior, it's me.
Don't hang up, please.
Carmen's nearby, right?
She cannot know.
It's so good
to hear your voice.
I...
Son, the things
that they're saying about me...
I did wrong.
I made some terrible mistakes.
But the reasons were always...
Things happened that...
I-- I never... intended.
Junior, your friend Lucho,
does his family still live
in that same place?
Mmhmm.
He's a good kid.
He's like you.
He'll understand.
Yes.
This is what
we are going to do.
I'm sending Louis a package.
It's addressed to Louis,
but it's for you.
Your mother and your sister.
Okay?
There's money inside.
It's all that I could fit
into the box.
Some 200 million pesos.
It has to be a secret.
And if anyone says a word,
then...
the police will know
and they will take it.
You understand?
I wanted to give you much more,
but this is all I could do.
Junior, can you hear me?
Do you understand?
You want to send money?
Yes. Good.
You'll talk to Louis, right?
Why don't you shut up?
Junior, Junior,
your mother needs that money.
It can't all be for nothing.
Please, Junior.
Why are you still alive?
Why don't you just die
already?
Antinarcotics.
I'd like to speak
to the agent...
in charge of the Walter Blanco
investigation.
Who may I say is calling?
Walter Blanco.
One moment, please.
Hello?
Sir.
Hello.
Mr. Blanco?
You ready
for that drink now?
Double.
Neat.
Look.
Thanks.
Your charity announced
a million dollar grant,
about 1,800 million
Colombian pesos
for a treatment center
for drug addicts in Bogotá.
Yes, yes.
What do you think
about the column
on the
"El Observador de Bogota"?
Can you turn that up,
please?
Gladly.
To sure up the stock price
after the downfall that came
once the public knew
about your association
with Walter Blanco.
To cleanse yourselves,
sort of speak,
of having
a methamphetamine kingpin
as cofounder of your company.
I'm glad you brought that up.
I have to believe
that the investing public
understands we're talking
about a person
who was there early on,
but who had virtually
nothing to do with
the creation of the company,
nor with growing it
into what it is today.
So what was Walter Blanco's
contribution?
You know, to be honest,
the company name.
We did some brain storming,
he came up with a name,
we liked it
and that was that.
His contribution begins
and ends right there.
There are continuing reports
of blue methamphetamine,
his signature product,
throughout Europe.
So my question is,
is Walter Blanco
still out there?
No, he's not.
You sound very sure.
I am.
I can't speak
to this Heisenberg
that people refer to,
but the sweet, kind,
brilliant man,
Walter Blanco,
that we once knew,
long ago, he's gone.
And with that statement,
we now move on
to some important messages,
we'll be right back.
Show us your hands!
Your hands!