You guys didn't tell me
that acid smells like cat piss.
That's life, right?
I'm sorry,
but I had to do it.
Obviously,
some of you
don't agree
with what I did.
But I didn't see
any other choice.
It's not like
I wanted to.
The kid was
on a dirt bike.
He could've just been gone
before we even
had a chance to blink.
I saw a threat,
I dealt with it.
A threat?
A threat, asshole?!
The kid
was waving at us.
He wasn't going anywhere!
You don't know that.
Not even you.
I didn't want
to take that chance.
It was you who said
that no one
had to know
what we were doing.
Yes or no?
That, if anyone saw us
the whole mission
failed.
How could we have let
the kid go?
It was him or us.
And I chose us.
Wait outside.
I just want you
to know something.
You're the kind of people
I've always dreamed
of working with.
You told me
to show my guts.
That's what I did.
Thanks, Peto.
And I've got connections.
My uncle's got
his hookups in prison.
They could be of help
to us if--
Take off, bro!
So what?
That dude? Whack-job.
He's totally insane!
Let's just stick
to the facts here.
You want to stick to the facts?
How about the fact
that the man
shot an innocent kid, bro?
Jose, the boy had seen us.
Understand?
What if he told somebody?
We can't know,
what could've happened.
because that asshole
shot him, Walter!
I understand you're upset,
trust me.
And besides
what was that crap
about his uncle
with the prison connections?
Some intimidation move?
And we'll let him
intimidate us?
It's true, though.
Peto does have
some connections.
Is this a problem?
They're not a threat.
I checked them out.
It seems to me
that we have
three options here.
One, we fire Todd.
- Yeah, right away.
- It's not so easy.
He knows way too much.
Knows the whole operation.
We'd have to pay him
to keep quiet.
We've got enough of that
going on.
Option two
- we dispose of him.
- No, no, no.
So what, Walter?
We'll keep on
adding dead bodies to this?
Okay.
That leaves us option three.
We keep him on payroll.
Put him back
on tenting houses
setting up the lab
and so forth.
We keep him
under our control.
Option three
would be my choice.
Shall we vote?
- I vote three, kid.
- No shit!
So what?
A subordinate
can do our job?
They take liberties
and make decisions?
Just say it!
If that's the case,
I'm out of this.
Fucking unbelievable!
Peto, come in.
Go fuck yourself.
You're still in.
Thank you so much.
It's very important
for me.
The next time
you bring a gun to a job
without telling me
I will stick it
up your ass sideways.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Now, go.
See you later.
Wake up, Contreras,
isn't that hard!
Hey, boss. What's up?
- Anything going on?
- No, same thing.
He's hanging out
with his granddaughter.
Nothing else.
Here, let me see.
It's a dead drop.
What?
He's writing something.
He's leaving a message.
Roll on it.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
- Roll on it!
- Okay, okay.
Write the time down.
Okay.
You have it?
Yeah, I do.
All right.
Listen,
boss.
Why don't you help me see
if anybody's coming
for it?
Wait for me here.
All right.
GO FUCK YOURSELVES
I know everybody
is freaking out, but...
It's not an issue
from my department.
It's an HR issue.
Yeah, I read the report.
I'm calling again
because that's
the wrong case file number.
No, no.
No, obviously
Mario Arboleda
is laughing at you
he's screwing with you, man.
What'd you do?
How'd he make you guys?
What do you mean?
The same as always.
You know what we do.
The thing is
this guy is slippery as
hell.
The guy's sly.
He's a pro.
Well, even pros make mistakes.
I'm sure our old man
is gonna slip up.
Just gotta be there
when he does.
How have they been?
Fine, they're all right.
Valentina's so sweet.
She brightens
my day.
To see her waking up,
sleeping. I love it.
- She's cute.
- Yes.
Then, Junior,
I don't see much of him.
With that car of his
he's always going out
here and there.
I see.
What about you?
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
Yeah?
It's great you're seeing
a therapist.
Mine helped me
so much, Cielo.
How's your guy?
- Pedro.
- Pedro, right.
Walter told us.
Pedro;
just keep working through it.
When you start
and keep on going
then you start realizing
that's doing you good
that the therapy
is working for you.
Babe, what is
it?
Cielo, what...?
What's going on,
wrong?
happening?
Cielo?
The thing is...
I just...
I need to make
the right decision.
I need them to be safe.
Safe?
What do you mean?
Of course they are.
Cielo, you just
have to tell me
and I can bring them
back home.
- You can have them back.
- No, no.
They need to stay with you.
I don't know
what to do here!
I need to make
the right decision
and it seems like...
whatever I choose
is wrong.
Cielo, tell me
what's going on.
I know you think
I have a big mouth
sometimes
and that I am
overly communicative.
But if you don't talk
to me
I don't know
how to help you.
What's all that
about protecting the kids?
From whom or what?
From us.
From Walter and me.
No, no, Cielo.
No, not even
close.
Don't think that.
You're excellent
parents.
María.
There are things
you just don't know.
That if you knew,
you'd never speak to me again.
Try me.
No.
Okay, okay, Cielo.
Let me help you out.
You feel like this
because
of your affair
with Ernesto.
- What?
- Yes.
You can't keep
beating yourself up
over that.
It happens.
It was just a fling.
It's over.
It's all over.
- Walter told you.
- Yes, he did
but I practically
forced him to.
And if I'm telling you
right now
is because
I cannot stand
to see you like that.
to watch you blame
and torture yourself
like this.
You have to forgive
yourself.
Forgive
Makes sense.
Walter and you
were having
all these problems
and this really
good-looking man
treats you well,
he's a perfect
gentleman.
It's normal
normal.
you fell for it.
I've thought about it,
Cielo, sometimes.
But I can totally get
why you
fell into
temptation.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
I feel better.
You had to get it off
your chest
or you'd choke with it.
- I love you. Don't worry.
- Thanks.
I'm here
and the kids are fine.
Jose, come on.
Break's over.
Euro is worth twenty pesos
more than yesterday.
Go, go!
Now me move
into social services.
Agustín Herrera's parents
keep on a desperate search
for their son.
Police still doesn't have
a lead on the kid
who disappeared
four days ago
in a country area
40 miles from Bogotá.
Authorities are extending
their search
while dredging tasks
are being performed in rivers
and streams around the area.
Nothing can change
this, Jose.
Yo, it's just...
Everyday I think about
that kid's parents.
- I know. Believe me.
- It's so hard.
Exactly the same thing
happens to me.
I haven't been able
to sleep
the past few nights.
But we have
to get through this,
Jose.
There are
other things.
Now, finally, we're
self-sufficient.
We have
everything that we need.
no one to answer to.
I mean, except ourselves.
Listen to me
in a year,
year and a half
once we've cooked through
all this methylamine,
we'll have
plenty of time
for self-analysis
and deep soul-searching.
Until then,
we keep going.
We can't afford
not to, Jose.
We've got
a business
and we have
to manage it smartly
so this
never happens
again.
Something like this
can never happen again.
Definitely,
it won't happen
again.
Look, let's do this.
Why don' you go home
and rest a little?
- You sure?
- Absolutely.
You go on.
Hey.
Yeah, I'm on my way home.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
What's up?
We need to talk to you.
What's going on?
Anti-narcotics are all over me.
What?
Did they follow you here?
No, I threw them.
I'm not so dumb, Walter.
How long has this
been going on?
Since about the time
we started here.
What?!
Your dear brother-in-law
seems to be in love with me.
And you're just
telling me this now?!
What, you didn't think
this information
would be of interest?
How can you be
so irresponsible,
Mario?
Did you know
about this?
Mario just told me.
- So absurd?!
- Calm down.
I've got it under control.
And I've already decided.
I'm out.
Okay, Mario,
sorry to see you go.
But I really don't see
any other way.
This makes things
complicated
you get it, right?
Jose, you'll have
to take over
the distribution task.
I trust that you'll
bring him
up to speed.
That's also
gonna be complicated.
I'm out too.
You're
what?
Yeah, bro, I can't do this
anymore.
I'm retiring.
You know
how much methylamine
we've got here?
When cooked,
it's worth billions.
And you tell me
you're walking away
from it?
We walk away from the meth,
not the methylamine.
Jose and I will be selling
our two-thirds.
I've got a connection
from my time
with Gustavo Cortés.
He has the capital,
and he's motivated.
Mario's thinking we'll clear
like five million. Each.
I'll pay off my guys in lock-up
out of my share.
You won't have
to worry about that anymore.
And then
I will be going on my way.
Jose too.
Yo, you should think about it.
It's a solid plan.
Retire once and for all.
You'll be selling
to my competitors.
Whole lot of meth-heads
for everybody, Walter.
They're offering you
pennies!
That's what
you're gonna
sell out for?!
Five million
isn't pennies for me.
Really, yo.
And when it comes down to it
are we on the money business
or in the meth business?
Relax, kid.
There's no one here.
You sure?
Yeah.
I wouldn't be here
if I wasn't.
Look, they're here.
The gallon.
Glad to see
you could make it out.
I was
surprised
to get your
call.
Good surprise, I hope.
Well, as discussed
there's one gallon.
You take that back home
to your people, test it.
If you're satisfied,
I can get the rest.
That's fair enough.
Then shall we talk money?
That one's free.
The price for the rest
is ten million dollars.
A round figure.
Makes it easier
for my partner and I to split.
That's steep.
Mm.
It's worth it.
We good?
I'll talk to my guys
but I should be able
to put together
that cash.
- Perfect.
- Of course...
you'd get
your blue stuff
off the market.
I need that crystal
Let me
get this straight,
Mario.
The first time we talked
you told me you had
six thousand gallons.
And that you could
even get nine thousand.
Where are the other
three thousand gallons,
Mario?
That's not
all the methylamine
you have.
Right?
You two have a partner
you haven't mentioned?
This other party wouldn't be
a problem for you.
His territory
won't impact yours.
You see,
that doesn't work
for me.
I'm not just buying this
for the supply.
I'm buying this
for the demand, Mario.
I'm looking to increase
my market share here
you see?
I don't know
what to tell you.
I want you to tell me
that Gustavo's blue glass
will be off the streets.
I'm paying fifteen million
for all the methylamine
you have.
I can't sell the rest.
It's not mine.
Well then, no deal,
Mario.
Let's
go.
Yes?
Yes.
I don't know.
I guess.
Why don't you come over
to my house?
Yes, seriously.
Sit down.
You sure this is okay?
All right.
This is what happened.
Something's come up
and Mario wanted to come
to give you the hard sell
but I figured
if it came from me
you would take it better.
Tell me.
Mario's connection
said
he won't buy
mine and Mario's shares
unless he
gets your share, too.
He wants the entire
nine thousand gallons.
That is totally unacceptable.
Yeah, I figured
you'd say that.
But I've been thinking
about it
and it really makes
sense.
Really.
Kinda.
Not
completely.
You remember
when we started this thing
with the bus
and everything?
Did you ever
dream of having
five million dollars?
You
didn't.
And I know it for fact
because I remember you
doing the maths beside me,
on the bus
and all you needed
was 1,300 million pesos.
I remember
you worked it
all out
mathematically,
the way you like
to do things
and you didn't
even reach
the million dollars.
Yo, these are
five million dollars.
Think about it
like this.
If you ask me
if selling
the methylamine
means that no one else
ever gets killed
because of us
then I vote for that,
man.
Hands down.
Don't you
think?
And the best part is
that if you say yes today
we could have it tomorrow.
Just figure
you could be here
spending time
with your family,
your kids.
No more worrying
about having to hide.
about our safety.
Isn't this what we
have been working for?
No.
I have not been working
this hard just to sell out,
Jose.
No, it's not selling
out.
On the contrary,
this is doing
the right thing.
We have suffered and bled...
We have literally bled
for this business, Jose.
I will not throw it away
for nothing.
I don't think
you understand me here.
How else can I say it?
It's five million dollars.
It isn't nothing.
It is a whole lot
of money.
Big time.
Really.
Have you heard
of a company
called "Atomic Number"?
- No.
You want me
to tell you the story?
I co-founded it
in grad school
with a couple of friends.
We decided to create it.
It was just small-time.
An emerging company.
We had a couple patents
pending and stuff.
'Course, we all knew
the potential.
We went step by step.
We didn't want
to risk too much.
However,
we were absolutely sure
that some day,
we didn't know exactly when
but some day
we were gonna take
the world by storm.
Well, all of a sudden
we started having
some problems.
I'm not gonna go
into detail.
But I decided
to leave the company.
And I sold my share.
I took a buyout
for ten million pesos.
Ten million pesos
at the time,
was a lot of money for me.
Care to guess
what that company
is worth now?
Millions?
Billions.
Billions, with a "B".
I know because I look it up
every week.
And I sold my share for ten.
I sold my kids' birthright
for a few months' rent.
This isn't
the same thing, bro.
You asked me if I was
in the meth business
or the money business,
right?
Neither.
I'm in the empire business.
Walter,
if you ask me
a meth empire
isn't something
to be that proud of,
really.
Cielo?
Hi.
You remember José Miguel?
Jose, she's my wife,
Cielo.
Mrs. Cielo, how are you?
Hey.
You have a lovely home.
The plants there
give it a cool touch.
I'm sorry
you run into me here.
I was just heading out.
No, no, stay.
No, I've got some stuff to do.
Stay.
Seriously, stay.
We'd love
you stayed for dinner.
Wouldn't we, Cielo?
We'd love him
to stay for dinner?
We don't have anything
special planned tonight.
Sure, we'd love to.
Mm!
Mrs. Cielo
this salad's great.
Really.
You see, I'm not
such a fun of vegetables,
but I liked it a lot.
I know they're good
for your health and stuff.
But the thing is...
I live by myself
so if I buy
too many vegetables,
they go bad.
Sure.
This dressing is--
How did you do it?
What did you put there?
It's delicious.
Lemon.
They say lemon
fixes everything,
right?
Not that it needs
fixing
'cause it's delicious,
but, I mean...
Um!
Let's say I feed
mostly on delivery
frozen food and stuff.
I know
it's usually pretty bad.
They say the nourishment
isn't so concentrated
and they go bad and...
But it is what it is.
You know what?
I just hate the people
from the frozen food industry.
Really.
They're lying bastards.
You go to the fridge
and it seems like
the perfect lasagna
with all the cheese on top.
Then you nuke it
and it's not
like that.
The cheese gets
all rubbery.
One should be able
to sue them.
As a consumer
I feel insulted
by those men.
Really,
that is called...
Misleading
advertising, right?
Really, it's an insult
for the consumer.
So how's business?
It's a car wash, isn't it?
The man here says
you're a great manager.
He did?
Yes, he speaks
very well of you.
He says you've got it running
like a machine.
Like, well-oiled.
As if you were
a great mechanic.
I mean, you're the manager
so I guess
it's like a metaphor, right?
But still, he speaks
very well of you.
That you are
a great person.
What else
did he tell you?
Tell me.
When he speaks,
he says just good stuff.
That you are
such a great woman.
Did you also tell you
about my affair?
About your what?
Affair.
Excuse me.
You know my kids are gone?
Yo, I don't judge them.
I'd done the same thing.
You're a crazy
couple.
I don't mean
they're out for the night.
They're gone.
They were taken
to the house
of my wife's sister.
The one that's married
no less
than with Henry Navarro.
She made me kick my own kids
out of the house.
And you know
what she told me?
That she was counting
the days
until my cancer came back.
She's waiting
for me to die.
This business is all
I have left now, Jose.
And you want to take it
away from me.
[Mario)
I thought you might try
something stupid.
- Look, Mario--
- Don't bother.
Come join me
in the office.
- No.
- That's not a request.
No.
On the stairs.
This deal
is going down tomorrow.
It's happening
whether you like it or
not.
There's nothing
you can do to stop it.
Got it?
Yeah, got it.
- You're stealing
my methylamine.
- No-one's stealing anything.
And to ensure that,
you and I
are gonna spend
the rest of the night
together.
Like it's my birthday.
Look, Mario--
When the deal is done,
you'll get your money.
I guarantee that.
I promise.
Mario, let me cook it.
I'll double your five
and you still walk.
I've never seen anybody
work so hard
not to get
five million dollars.
Mire, you need to listen
to me, okay?
Please, listen to me.
The last thing I need
is listen to you,
Walter.
Sit down and be quiet.
Wake up.
I've got something
a bit of a quandary here.
I need to attend to
before this deal happens.
But I don't trust you
so I'm gonna have
to restrain you.
You gotta be
kidding.
Stand up for me.
Stand up, goddamn it!
Arms up and out to the side.
This is
unbelievable.
Sit down.
Give me your wrist.
Sorry.
To what do we owe
the pleasure?
Gentlemen,
we're here
to discuss
the illegal harassment
to which you're
subjecting
my client.
This should be good.
Mister Mario Arboleda
has become the victim
of a vicious, relentless,
and, above all
unwarranted persecution
from the Anti-narcotics
Department.
Gómez, that sound
right to you?
Don't tell me
you're doing things
behind my back.
I have no idea
what he's talking about.
No, no idea.
Nothing?
Zero, zip?
Come on, we all know
you've been following
my client day and night.
The poor man
can't even spend
a few minutes
with his granddaughter.
Why?
'Cause you're
playing
hide-and-seek
behind the bushes
sneaking away,
hiding
peeping through
your little
binoculars.
It's disturbing.
You should feel ashamed.
And it's taken a toll
on his mental
and physical well-being.
- He looks fine to me.
- It's possible.
Why?
Because some hurts
only show
on the inside.
And generally,
those hurt the most.
Let's see.
You guys
don't even have warrants
for these tails,
do you?
Theoretically
to do these tails
we don't need a warrant.
It's within
the bounds
of the law.
We don't need a warrant
to follow somebody
through a public place.
You know that, doctor.
Yeah, that is
theoretically correct.
But a surveillance
so open-ended and unrestricted
turns into...?
Stalking.
You're so funny, buddy.
Really.
And stalking is illegal.
I don't know what it is
you find so interesting
about my client.
But I'm not here
to judge anyone.
Different strokes
for different folks.
Men with men,
women with women.
The problem is that, sadly
he's just not that into you.
So, I have filed for an order
a temporary restraining order
against Anti-narcotics
and on behalf
of Mr. Arboleda.
Look, Saúl.
Where'd you get
your law degree?
The same clown college
you got that suit?
Hey!
Let me tell you.
You know who likes
this suit
very much?
Judge Débora Peña.
She admires my motley
dress sense, let's say.
I agree with her
in that.
You know what
Judge Peña hates?
When senior citizens
are being harassed
sorry about
the senior part
by the police.
Therefore, gentlemen
that's all for today.
You can expect
the written notice soon.
Let's go.
You should have it
within the hour
over your desks.
That is, if you have desks,
which I don't think.
Maybe over your school desks
or your T squares?
What the hell
kind of judge
would issue this thing?
That Débora, man.
She's always finding
fault
with every security
organism.
She's shit.
- So what we do?
- Well, not a lot of choice.
We back off for the moment.
Anyway Saúl knows that TRO
won't stand for long.
What we've got to do,
Gómez,
is knowing
what they're playing at here.
And if Mario Arboleda
wants a fight
he's gonna get one.
That was
a hell of a gamble.
Risky, right?
Worked at least.
Not for long.
He's right about that TRO.
It's gonna get tossed
toute suite.
That Henry Navarro has
a hard-on for you, right?
What you gonna do?
How you gonna get rid
of him?
How much time I got?
Maybe 24 hours.
- It's enough.
- It better be.
Whatever you got
on your mind
or have planned,
you better do it quick.
Playtime's about to be over
for you.
Where is it?!
Mario, please!
Hold on, okay?
- Get out of my way!
- Mario, please, listen to me!
- I am gonna count to three.
- The man's got an idea.
One, two...
Mario, don't shoot,
please!
Just hear him out!
It's a solid idea!
We both get
our five million each
he gets his methylamine
and we're out of this.
Just hear him out.
Is that true?
Yes. Everybody wins.