This, the chemistry,
is my realm.
So I am in charge of this place.
I cook,
you deal with the street.
As far as our customers go,
I don't want to know anything about them.
I don't want to see them. I
don't want to talk to them.
This operation is you and me,
and I'm the silent partner.
I'm invisible.
Absolutely invisible.
- Whatever, professor.
- And one more thing, no more bloodshed.
From now on, no matter what happens,
no more violence.
Are you okay?
You don't have to stay.
I like to be with you.
Right,
but maybe you have things to do.
Actually,
it would make me feel better if you left.
You know, for the baby...
For Junior.
I'd like you to be there when
he gets home from school.
Don't you think that's better?
- As you wish.
- Yes.
You'll call me when
you're finished?
Yes.
I haven't seen a check from
Marcela. Do you know about that?
Yes... Yes,
I got it. It came last week.
I put it into my credit account,
I forgot to tell you.
Good. That's good.
- So call me.
- Yes.
Could you not deposit this until Monday,
please?
Sure, no problem.
Mr. Walter,
call us if the discomfort's too much.
That's why we're here.
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
If a chemical reaction
take place gradually,
changes in energy are equal.
You don't even notice
the reaction is happening.
For example, when rust collects
on the underside of a car.
But let's just say...
If a reaction happens quickly,
otherwise armless substances
can interact in a way that generates
enormous changes of energy.
Great bursts of energy.
Who can give me an example
of rapid chemical reaction?
Hint, hint.
Like an explosion?
Right.
Explosions are an
excellent example
of chemical reactions
happening almost instantaneously.
And...
Mercury fulminate...
is a prime example
of an explosive that,
the faster they undergo change,
the more violent the explosion.
So open your books
on chapter seven.
Are you okay, professor?
Would you like something?
Want me to call someone?
No, no, no. It's fine, Hugo.
Don't worry,
professor. Don't you worry.
I'll take care of this.
Might as well have a rest.
Thank you.
When you don't let me in,
when you don't tell
me what's going on,
I feel like you don't want me near you,
and it hurts.
It really hurts.
I feel like you don't even
want me around sometimes.
No, please.
And besides, you leave,
- and we don't know where you are.
- Yes, dad, we don't know.
Walter, is there anything else
you're holding back from your family?
Look, speak calmly.
It's nothing. It's just that...
I's just that I
like to be alone.
And it's not about you.
It's not that I don't
want to be with you...
It's just...
That's it, I like to be alone.
In silence, I mean.
Not to talk at all
about anything.
And especially,
not to have to listen to anyone.
Sometimes it bothers me.
Well, Walter, alone time can be
helpful for some types, you know?
But I think your family would
have more peace of mind
Well, then...
Well, sometimes after class
I like to go for a walk.
One, or a couple of times a week,
it depends.
For instance, the weather.
I usually go to
the National Park.
I really like that park
because...
Well, it's huge, it's green.
And I just get carried
away by that sensation.
Like...
I feel I'm free
watching the sky,
the green trees,
to feel the breeze.
It feels like nature
is becoming very
therapeutic for me.
What's up, dude?
- What is it?
- I'm dizzy, really dizzy.
- I need air.
- Come here. Sit down, sit down.
- I can't breathe.
- Wait--
Okay, okay.
I feel like I'm burning inside.
Breathe in, breathe. Calm down.
Better?
- Okay?
- Yes, a little.
When were you going to tell me?
- Tell you what?
- Cancer. You got it, right?
- How do you know?
- Because my grandma had one of those...
dots on her,
to target the radiation.
Professor,
I'm your partner, man.
You should have told me. That's not right,
man.
What stage are you?
Three-A.
It got to the lymph nodes.
How bad was she
when they caught it?
Bad enough.
How long?
Seven months and
four days exactly.
I was always by her side.
I get it now.
That's why you're
doing all this.
You got a problem with that?
I don't know. You tell me.
Are you going to be
able to finish the batch?
What is it?
No.
No, I can't. You'll have to.
- Me?
- Yes, José, you.
You're the great cook.
Mr... Cappuccino?
- Espresso.
- That's it.
You can do it. Go.
If you need anything,
I'll be right out here.
Next time, put an ice pack
on your head during chemo.
My grandma said
it helped her a lot.
- What's up, Gómez?
- Hey.
What, another gift? Come.
I was going to say, Gómez,
that even if you give me
present or stuff like that,
I'm not giving anything to you,
okay?
That's the one we
found at El Páramo.
Do you have the report?
That's not true.
What is it?
It was right here.
What does it say?
Chemical Laboratory,
Los Monarcas School.
Doesn't your brother-in-law
Walter work there?
We were supposed
to start at three.
Calm down,
everything's five. It's all good.
Prepaid cell phone. Use it.
Ok, look.
There you go.
- How much is this?
- Two and a half grand.
- Is that all?
- No, not all.
1,500 yours, 1,500 mine.
Minus 25 bucks for that phone.
How much meth did you sell?
Nearly an ounce.
Last time I checked,
there were 16 ounces
to a pound.
Did you smoke the rest?
You know what? I've been out
there all night slinging crystal.
You think it's cake moving a
pound of meth one tenth at a time?
And then there are
those who buy less
because sometimes
they just ask for a dose.
Why don't you just sell
the whole pound at once?
What do I look like? Pablo Escobar? No,
man
- Look, José Miguel...
- José.
You have no idea what
I've been going through.
I am breaking the law here.
I could go to jail.
For this? This return
is too little for the risk.
I need more.
I thought you'd be ready
for another pound tonight.
No, professor. You know what?
You may know a
lot about chemistry,
but you don't know
jack about slinging dope.
Maybe not.
But I'll tell you,
I know a lack of motivation when I see it.
I'm really good at that.
We can't stick to crumbs, man.
You've got to be more imaginative,
think big.
We have to move our product in bulk,
wholesale.
How do we do that?
Well,
I don't know. Maybe get a distributor.
Exactly.
That's what we need.
We need a distributor now.
- Do you know anyone like that?
- Yes, I do.
I mean I used to.
Until you killed him. Remember?
So who took El Loco's place?
As far as I know,
the path was free for the Mexican, Tuco.
Then we got to the Mexican.
Tuco? Yes, right.
So we just go over
to his door and say,
"Hey,
old Tuco. I came with some meth."
He'll let us right in.
Even offer us some wine.
Hey, that's not an attitude.
Listen, Tuco's O.
That man is dangerous.
Don't you understand?
Mexicans have been doing
this for much longer than us.
They already have their cooks, and they
have suppliers. They won't be interested.
Nobody produces the
stuff as purely as we do.
We have the best product.
Okay, let's say I got for it.
Okay? We take
the risk. Then what?
You need an intro. You
need someone to vouch.
If you have no contacts,
you're nothing, like in everything.
So how did you get to El Loco?
Who introduced you to him?
- Well, Emilio.
- There you go.
But that's because Emilio
and I played soccer as kids.
And we can't talk to him either because,
well,
- you might remember--
- Right, fine, okay.
Listen, professor, listen.
Let's not get involved.
Why can't you just be
satisfied with the way it is?
I mean, we're making money,
and you should be happy.
Jesus! Just grow
some fucking balls!
Okay, Shall I wait until Monday,
Mr. Blanco?
Yes, please.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Take care.
Professor.
Thank you, Hugo.
- Hey, Walter.
- Hey, Carmen.
- Are you alright?
- Yes, yes, I'm fine.
Someone's here for you.
- Hi there.
- Henry?
- Let me know if you need anything.
- I will.
Man, that chick got an ass.
- What's up?
- How are you?
- Okay, and you?
- What are you doing here??
Well, I had some questions I
wanted to run by you, work-related.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, yes. Go ahead.
Okay.
Do you recognize this?
- No.
- No?
That was used to cook meth.
We found it on the outskirts
like 25 miles
right after Páramo.
And the weirdest thing of all
is the old label: "Lab,
Los Monarcas School."
I can't believe it.
I don't understand how
that came from here.
I was hoping you could help me.
We found this mask
near the same
place where we found
a car belonging to
one of our snitches.
- Snitches?
- Yes, one of our confidential informants.
Domingo Molina, aka "El Loco".
Went missing a while back.
We're pretty sure he's chopped up
in little pieces and fed to the buzzards.
That's why you
should be very careful
where you buy sausages.
Listen.
Have any of these masks
gone missing lately in the lab?
No, I mean, not that I know of. I'll
need to take a look at that inventory.
Because for a while... Want
to see it? I have a copy here.
- Sure.
You mind if I take a
look at your storeroom?
Not at all, no.
Has anyone else got keys?
Yes.
The Science faculty, Carmen,
the janitor
the vice principal and me.
- How about students?
- No, not at all.
- I should hope not.
- No.
Do any know where you keep them?
I don't think so.
I keep them right here
in my pocket anyway.
Come in.
I know they're your students,
but do not underestimate them.
That's the worst
mistake you can make.
Look, I know cases where the
least expected person... bam.
So keep your eyes open.
Are there any more of these?
No, only those there.
But you need three, right?
Well.
Glassware looking
a little sparse.
Is it?
Just look...
Two test tubes missing here.
A couple of Erlenmeyer
flasks at least.
The flasks are complete.
And these balls
with round bottom...
How much do these hold?
500.
You need a big one,
5,000 milliliter.
Meth heads love to brew in that.
Won't you answer that?
Answer.
Surely it's not important.
What if it's Cielo and
she needs something?
Answer, man.
I'll hang around here.
- Hello?
- Professor, it's me. Bad time?
Yes.
You know that Mexican
we were talking about, Tuco?
Turns out I'm here
with my boy Tripaseca.
He was in the same
cellblock with him,
They stayed in touch and
are friends. So we got our in.
Tuco agreed to see me,
so we're waiting.
We're hauling a pound
to the dude right now.
Okay,
then. Thank you very much for calling.
Same to you.
The doctor.
It's amazing. The people from
the hospital are very solicitous.
They call me every
day to know how I am.
That's great.
- It is.
Look, buddy,
the last thing I want to
do is get you in hot water,
but some meth monkey
had a feeding frenzy.
You got to keep a better
watch over your turf.
We don't want people
to start wondering about you,
right?
What's you think? That I was
going to read your rights or what?
- No...
- That was funny.
Listen, that woman...
So you're sure you're
tight with this guy?
Absolutely.
Yo, man.
Hey, what's going on?
It's Pedrito, Tripaseca.
Okay.
Maybe this isn't such a good idea,
yo.
Come on, Jose. Man, trust me.
What did I say? See that?
So what now?
Tuco's waiting for us.
Clean.
Hey, I said easy!
What's up, Tuco?
No love.
What's it been?
Like a year since
you've been released?
- This your boy?
- Yes, that's Jose.
The dude with the glass
I was telling you about.
Hey, man.
Let's see it.
Show me.
Come on.
No worries, man. I'm no cop.
What kind of idiot
would do that?
Hit it.
Fuck me!
This kicks like a mule
with his balls in duct tape.
- Where'd you get it?
- I cooked it.
Bullshit!
Where'd you get it?
- Who you working for?
- No one, man.
I mean, I have a partner that I cook with,
but that's it.
He does crystals.
That's good news.
We got a deal.
See? I told you Tuco
would hook you up.
Cool,
but we still haven't said how much.
How much?
Well,
this shit is of much better quality
than everything
you get on the street.
How much?
25 grand for the pound.
What?
At a single dose for
powder meth on the street?
Come on, boy.
Well,
that's the street in the market.
I'm the market.
Besides, there's missing.
I weighed that. There
should be a pound.
It's a joke. Fine.
Well.
Thanks for coming.
No, no, no. Dude,
where are you going?
Just a second,
Tuco. You didn't give me the money.
Later.
Later? You expect me to
stay with 25 grand in credit?
Don't you trust me?
No, let's not get dramatic, man.
But Tuco,
you know business isn't handled like that.
You're calling me useless
for not handling my business?
- Hey, what's up with him?
- Easy, easy.
Tuco's good for it.
I don't need your punk
ass to vouch for me!
Then I'm taking it.
No,
I'm not doing business like this.
God luck.
Calm down, boy, calm down.
It was a joke,
my friend. I'll pay you.
Do you really want your
money up front? I'll give it to you.
Alright.
Here.
Man, hold it.
Hold it, man!
Hugo.
Can I call you?
Isn't that my uncle?
Mrs. Carmen,
how long has he worked for you now?
A long time,
and we never had a problem.
- They work--
- Nice job, Gómez.
They work like that, you know?
They get along nicely,
they're good people.
He had a record,
I don't know if you knew that.
No, we didn't. Officer,
there must be a mistake here.
No, no mistake.
Go back to work. Excuse me.
Thank you.
You've reached Jose's crib.
Leave me your plates,
and I'll see.
Where are you? I
need you to call me.
Walter.
- Henry's done.
- Okay, honey, coming.
You look better,
Walter. Your color's better.
He's actually on the
pretty strong stuff now.
Dr. Sánchez is
trying to talk him into
taking some time off from work,
but Walter...
Actually, I talked to Carmen this morning,
and they're getting a substitute.
Really?
I just didn't have a
chance to tell you.
- Cielo, your bet.
- I'll pass.
Honey,
the green ones are 20,000 each.
Well,
then it's 40. That's how I bet.
Hey, uncle...
why were you arresting
Hugo? He's a pretty cool guy.
Because there were signs
that he was one of the thieves
of the lab gear.
He has a minor record.
for disturbing the peace.
And the other is that
he was one of the
people who had the key.
Fits the profile perfectly.
When we searched his truck,
we found
a big old fat blunt.
Which goes to prove old Hugo
isn't so cool after all.
Your bet.
I can't believe the
school system didn't know
about this guy's record.
I mean, that's pretty scary.
Well, my personal opinion
is that Hugo is not a thief.
Well, nothing personal, Walter,
but if they were to point at you
with a water gun,
you'd give away even your mom.
Yes, yes.
Well, coming back to Hugo,
We tore his house apart.
Turns out he's a
major league pothead.
But you're right
about what you said.
But he didn't raid
your chemistry set.
I bet 10,000. Last card here.
What?
I've got nothing. I'm out.
I'm out too.
Let's see.
I'm out.
Well,
if Mrs. "That's How I Bet" leaves,
looks like it's you and me,
buddy.
What will happen to Hugo?
He's going to lose his job,
and then it's up to the judge.
He could get a
fine or time in jail.
You going to man up,
or you're going to puss out?
- Henry.
- Sorry.
Sorry.
I'm all in.
What have you
got? Straight flush?
Henry! Come on!
- Okay, okay.
You know what? I'm out.
- You talker.
- Let's see.
- Let's see that.
- ¿What? No peeking.
Why do you look at them?
Really? You risked
everything for an ace and a K?
- Well.
- No.
Let's see what Walter has.
My God.
All for nothing.
Such a liar.
- No, uncle. No.
Hello?
Hello.
I need to speak to
José Miguel Rosas.
Listen, man,
Jose can't come over.
Why not?
Are you his man?
Yes, I'm his "man".
How is he?
Got some busted
ribs and like that.
Got messed up pretty good.
I was all like "Damn,
Tuco, chill, ease."
But he wouldn't stop. I
don't know what got into him.
Jose.
No.
He's out, man,
way out. They got him doped up big-time.
Are you the cook?
I figured you differently.
Nice to meet you.
Pedrito Tripaseca.
Tell me about this Tuco.
Good morning.
Wow,
Walter. You look like a criminal.
Would you pass the butter,
please?
Tuco?
I need to talk to him.
And I'm not leaving until I do.
What's your name?
Heisenberg.
"Haisenber"?
Wow,
what a name! How do you write that?
With an A?
With an A and an E.
- Have a seat, dude.
- I won't be long.
No?
Why don't you start talking
and tell me what you want?
30 grand.
What? 30 grand?
25 grand for the meth you stole,
and five more for what
you did to my partner.
Your partner?
Your partner, partner.
I remember that little bitch.
That's your partner.
Let me get this straight.
You're accusing me of stealing?
I beat the piss out
of your mule boy
and then you bring me more.
You bring more.
Yes.
You got one part of that
wrong. This is not meth.
You son of a bitch!
- Are you nuts?
- You want to find out?
No, no, no, no!
Calm down,
calm down. Put that down.
Put it down.
Calm down.
Damn.
You got balls.
I'll give you that.
I'll give you your money.
That crystal that your
partner brought me,
it sold faster than ice-cream.
- Cash?
- Yes.
Put that down,
damn it! Didn't you hear?
What say you bring me
another pound next week?
Money up front.
All right. You give me
the meth. Money up front.
A pound is not enough for me.
You should buy two pounds.
Two pounds.
Fine, two pounds.
"Heisenberg".
Sometimes you got to
rob to keep your riches.
Just as long as we
got an understanding.
Hey, hey.
What is that shit?
Mercury fulminate.
A little tweak of chemistry.
Son of a bitch.
Yes!