Shit!
MISSION FAILED
CONTINUE/ABANDON
And you'll polish it
yourself, okay?
Thanks.
They'll make anything
for you to deliver it.
Hey, and how's Junior?
Well, he's not talking to me
since I told him
we had to deliver the car.
Let's hope
he'll get over it soon.
I spoke to the dealership.
They didn't want to take it.
How come? Why?
It's got 17
miles
on the odometer.
Well yeah, I spent more than
an hour talking to the manager
about the restocking fine.
What? A fine?
They're collecting a fine?
Five million pesos.
What?
For two days?
Well, the law says
they don't have
to take it back at all.
But that was in the fine print!
or keeping the car.
Bunch of thieves.
Look, here's all the paperwork
and the bills.
Talk directly to the manager,
his name's Jairo.
Jairo.
And please, just don't
tangle with anyone.
Call me if there's a problem.
And give the boy his tip.
Hey, would you change me
a 50 dollar note?
I've no change.
Woooo!
Fuck!
Hello, miss, I need a cab.
Walter Blanco.
I'm at the exit for Bogotá,
three miles after the tollbooth.
Yeah, exactly.
Next to the wineries.
La Nacional.
No, don't you worry.
I'll wait here.
Hello. No, look.
No problem. I'm sure
he'll find me.
I'm next to a huge bonfire.
Thank you very much.
He's so sorry!
He's really sorry,
He's even willing
to pay for it, literally,
so that this doesn't
become known.
Besides, he swears
it won't happen again.
Sure. In cash?
Yeah, don't worry.
I'll make sure you get the
suitcase.
Thanks, mate. Cheers!
We have to thank
I've been working
on the campaign
for the mayor
and in the traffic department.
They owe me a few things.
Well, you'll have to pay a fine
or throwing garbage away,
how's that?
You won't have to attend
the educational course.
They get rid of the car,
and you
are sending my friend
a thank-you present
with some zeros on the right.
That's it!
The arson thing was only news
for a school radio program.
Not even students listen to it.
To sum up...
this little game
cost you three times
the price of the car.
Okay.
Saúl,
I don't want any details, okay?
The main thing is,
it has to be fixed.
Excuse me,
I woke you up.
What a shame, I'm sorry.
You haven't realized
what's just happened here.
What did I do?
Magic!
I work miracles.
Not even your wife
will find out.
You could at least tell me,
"Bravo, Saúl, bravo."
Okay, give me that.
Let me see...
And what's keeping
your head so busy? Gustavo?
Yes.
I'm sure he must have already
figured out a plan
on how to kill me.
And I've nothing to do about it.
The only thing I can do
is wait.
Are you sure about that?
Because José says
they really need you.
José...
José Miguel has no idea
where his head is.
So what are you thinking of?
Saúl, I was thinking...
I don't know.
Could you happen to find me...
s troubleshooter?
A troubleshooter?
Is than an euphemism
for hit man?
Yeah, well, I don't know,
do you still call them that?
No, no, no.
It's a really bad
idea..
We're dealing here
with high-level people,
these people are dangerous.
No, no, no. Saúl,
I just need a phone.
I'll handle the rest.
And you'd have
a good commission.
Walter, let's suppose
there's no other choice.
I could give you
a couple of names...
two guys from Cali,
they're good boys.
The thing is,
Mario knows them
and they know Mario.
Well, now it turns out Mario
knows the whole human kind?
For God's sake!
Mario's the one
who game me their names.
Besides, he taught them
everything they know.
Let's just think that--
whoever we find,
if we happen
to find anybody,
will end up facing Mario
and that will represent
a problem for all of us.
Now, Gustavo...
Gustavo's got tentacles
and we don't even
know about them.
It's most likely
he'll find out
you're hiring someone
to get him killed
even before you actually
find them.
So what shall I do?
Shall I sit and wait?
I've already tried
to do it personally.
I couldn't get
even close to him!
Well, if we're talking about
getting pretty close to him--
why don't you talk
to your partner?
Yeah, I met Gustavo.
And you preferred
go telling Saúl
than coming to me?
Let's see,
let me explain myself.
The thing is, Saúl's
pissed off because Mario
would break his legs
because he lied
about my whereabouts.
So every time I enter
this man's office,
Saúl hassles me
about talking to Mario,
wants me to speak well of him.
So in order to soothe him
a little,
you well know
Mario doesn't like to talk,
the only thing I do
is telling him the latest.
That's everything
that's going on.
So don't take it personally.
What happened exactly?
Nothing happened.
I was there,
at a bar with Mario,
and...
Well, nothing,
this guy arrived.
- And "this guy" is Gustavo?
- Yes.
They came in, started to talk
and took me out for a while.
So that happens regularly?
No, mate.
Not regularly.
I don't have weekly meetings
with the big boss.
No, that's not what's going on.
How close were you to him?
Close enough.
Closer than you and me
right now.
Did you talk?
Did he tell you anything?
Yeah, we talked
for like ten seconds, that's it.
What did he
say?
José, what did he say?
He told me he saw
things in people.
Things? What people?
Me, mate. I'm the people.
He said he saw something in me.
He saw like--.
I mean, one month ago, Gustavo
was about to kill us both.
And now he pulls you
out of the lab
and employs you as...
What, an assistant gunman?
A junior bodyguard?
I mean, it's completely
meaningless.
Face it, man!
Gustavo coming to tell you
he sees something in you...
There must be something else!
I mean, he can't believe
you're so naive.
Let's see.
I don't understand
where you're going
with all this.
Well, José, I mean this:
I don't understand.
I can't believe
Gustavo thinks
you suddenly forgot
he was going to kill you.
What about Guido's death?
And Víctor's?
Not to mention
your girlfriend's brother.
Tomás?
I still hear him
in my head...
when he told you,
looking directly into your
eyes,
"No more children."
That same night, "Bang!"
Tomás got killed.
I can't believe
Gustavo really thinks
you'll forget about all this,
just like that.
- Enough, mate.
- No! It's outraging.
This prick Gustavo
thinking you're so weak-willed--
Well, enough!
I've already told you to finish!
Drop the sales pitch.
Leave it for some other time.
- I told you I'd do it.
- What are you going to do?
I'll kill him.
First chance I get,
but drop it right now.
- Done, look.
- Thanks.
Thank you, come back.
I don't get it why people love
this bubblegum scent so much.
I find it repulsive, smells
like a school bus, right?
- Yeah, but they buy it.
- Really?
And this one's rice pudding
with cinnamon? Can't believe it!
Yeah, I couldn't
believe it either.
But the customer's always right.
Speaking of customer,
I think it's not too late
to have a grand opening.
We could have a barbecue
right over there
with balloons,
and we could have them bring
girls with hot pants
to serve the customers,
we could have a discount,
something really chic.
And tell me, how's Henry?
- Much better.
- Really?
He is.
He's doing better,
he's on a better mood.
He's changed attitude.
He's like a maniac
with his physical therapy. He's
doing better.
That's good news.
It's not easy.
I'm telling you this
because it's a slow process,
but I feel that...
we're finally getting
to the right path.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You're a hard worker.
- Hello.
- Everything alright?
- Just fine.
Let me tell you, your wife
is quite the salesperson.
He almost talked me into buying
a rice pudding air freshener.
With cinnamon.
How do you like it?
Nice.
That's the salesperson
we needed here.
Well, may I congratulate you?
Let me say hi.
Hello.
Thanks for bringing the
order.
- Shall we organize it?
- Yeah.
I'll let you work.
My car must be ready right now.
- Yeah, bye.
- Bye.
- Cheers.
Would you please give me that
to show Henry?
- Sure.
- Kiss Walter Junior from me.
Ramiro was making
19 cars during the rush hour.
We're making 22.
22. Real.
That difference
covers it well for us.
Yesterday I deposited
like ten million pesos.
Hey, hey, how much?
How much do you have there?
I don't know exactly. They paid
three hundred thousand dollars.
At today's rate,
you do the math.
It must be more or less
600 millones.
Wait, wait, wait.
We have to count it again.
And you're bringing this
how often?
Every two weeks.
Thursday's good for a drop-off?
Are you serious?
Are you going to earn
like 15 thousand million a year?
I don't know exactly.
The negotiation
was made in dollars.
That makes eight million a year.
Sort of, yeah.
Sort of?
Yeah, more or less.
It depends
on the output factors, Cielo.
Walter, that's too much.
It's too much, Walter.
You're earning more
than what you expected,
and now you think that's what?
Bad news?
No, that's not the point,
Walter.
The point is, no car wash
in the world can make that much.
I don't know what happens
in other countries,
but it's impossible here.
It'll take me years
to clean this money.
I don't know.
Put away some part
of the cash
and save it for a rainy day.
- I don't know...
- Rainy days?
There are no rainy days ahead.
And where do you want me
to keep that?
I can't put it in a bank,
I can't have it here...
Cielo...
I didn't ask you
to do that.
I thought you had it
completely under control here.
But I didn't think it was
so much money.
Look, whatever,
our work is split
from the very beginning.
I bring in the money,
you launder the money.
This is what you wanted, right?
I never wanted any of this.
But you accepted it,
at some point.
And that's real.
Now, think it through.
Really, if you feel
this is too much for you,
just tell me.
It's okay.
You want to get
out?
You made this in the lab?
Why not?
We've the best equipment there.
Besides, I thought making it
in your own lab would be...
Appropriate.
There's not much of it.
We had more for Tuco.
It's enough, believe me
Besides,
it's most efficient.
You go after Gustavo with a gun,
you won't make 100 feet
and you'll be shot.
You can slip this
into his food or drink,
there shouldn't be
any taste or smell.
In 36 hours he'll be...
Besides, a man like Gustavo,
working as hard as he does,
no one will be surprised
if that happened to him.
What about Mario?
Mario.
He will surely be suspicious
but he won't do anything.
Wouldn't it be better
to recover health
once and for all?
One psycho at a time, okay?
I don't know when I'll see him
again, if I ever do.
It doesn't matter.
You just keep this with you
all the time.
When you have the opportunity,
be ready.
What if they search me?
Will they do that?
I don't know, they may.
No, it's the wrong way around.
Don't you see
that's my lucky cigarette, man?
Well, whatever you do,
don't smoke it.
I'd give you a hand,
but I'm busy.
Relax, brother...
I can do it on my own.
Maybe this thing helps me
stretch my legs a bit.
Hey, you know?
I liked that driver stuff.
No, no, no, really,
I felt good.
That stuff puts you
on a higher level?
Hey, that stuff from here
to there, it'll take
an eternity.
We'd better still be hungry
when we arrive, then...
You must love this chicken.
Coming all the way here...
Just a whim, brother.
I'm not telling you
it's the best car
I've ever driven.
It was the best car
I've ever gotten into.
it was like a spaceship, uncle!
And where did you get
that car from?
I mean, suddenly your dad
said, "I wanna buy this car"?
And he bought it,
just like that?
No, the worst thing is
I couldn't even drive it.
Mom said we couldn't
afford a car like that,
and she made him give it back,
I couldn't drive it,
not even for 30 miles.
Well, at least you drove it.
When I was your age,
I wasn't even allowed
to touch my granddad's car.
Really.
Not even park it.
And I had a girlfriend,
buddy,
she lived outside Bogotá.
It took me an hour and a half
to get to her.
I had to take the bus.
But when I didn't have
the money,
I had to use my legs.
Well, sure, but my legs
are sort of like this...
Yeah, I know.
Really.
Listen, seriously,
why did your dad buy that car?
I just don't get it, why?
I don't know, uncle.
He was taking me
to school and...
all of a sudden, we saw
some cars there, and well...
I told him I needed...
I needed one be-because...
I have a pro-problem?
Stop being an asshole, man.
- Uncle, don't start on me.
- What is it, bro?
Look, you know what?
This car business
didn't work for you.
And you know why?
Because you're ambitious.
If you had chosen
a simpler car,
you'd have your car today.
And you wouldn't need
a ride with your uncle
in order to drive it.
Am I right or what?
Am I?
You're ambitious!
That happened to you
only because of that.
Hell, no?
Agent, I'm glad to see you here.
Don Gustavo! Too bad
I can't get up, man.
- Don't you worry.
- Remember my nephew?
- Of course. How are you?
- Hi. Fine.
Glad to see you're recovering.
Well, no,
you know, brother,
broccoli and cauliflower
make you feel better.
I love telling that joke!
If I had seen you
when you entered the restaurant,
I'd have served you
personally.
You're a very special customer
here at Pollos Hermanos,
and I'd like to tell you
you can eat for free
whenever you want.
Careful with what you say,
I'll surely come.
You'll be welcome.
So, how are your parents?
They're fine, sir, yeah.
- Tell them I say hi.
- Yes, sure I will
Are you okay?
Want a drink?
No, I'm fine, thank you.
Well, if it's okay,
I'd like to have
some more soda.
Of course.
Same one you're having?
Yes, diet soda. Thanks.
Excuse me.
You
ready?
I'm ready.
So, what's today's plan?
Today's a very important day.
Big doings today.
The order of the day is...
eyes open, mouth shut.
Not the other way around.
Sound testing.
- Testing.
- Mario.
Leave the snacks on the table,
where everyone can reach them.
Jose, you know
how to make coffee?
There's the machine.
Make some, please.
Both strong, no sugar.
Want a report?
Besides the men
you can see there,
we've three men
camouflaged by the door.
And five by the rear,
camouflaged and backed up.
There's also Mosquera
on the roof, he carries a .50.
They're here since last night
in case anyone arrived early.
Jose.
Weapons don't grow from trees.
Don't you throw it away.
If you're here,
you have to be armed.
Sir, is this loaded?
Keep it where nobody can see it,
and show it only
when I show mine.
Understood?
Only in case of emergency.
Well, there's the first car.
Let's go.
Lots of weapons.
Nobody's asking you
to give up yours.
You want to sweep the place
before you bring in your guy?
I am the guy.
Let's go then.
Welcome.
Where's the rest of the group?
There's no rest of the group.
The only person representing
the cartel's interests
in Colombia is me.
Good.
Have a seat, please.
By virtue of
our previous relationship,
I have an offer for you...
An only payment.
Fifty million dollars.
In return, we'll be in peace
and safe and sound.
No more payments,
no more commitment.
No communication.
A total break-up.
Yeah.
Accepting any kind of break-up
from you would mean
you can partner up
with any other cartel.
Or you could export
the meth yourself
into America.
That means,
you'd be the competition.
My offer's a big one.
No. You know pretty well
what the cartel wants:
employees.
Talking of something else
would be wasting our time.
The way you're putting it,
it's hard to negotiate.
There's no negotiation
to make here.
It's a question of deciding.
No shades of gray here...
It's either yes or no.
You've something
that belongs to me.
Yeah, here it is.
Glove compartment.
Figure I better teach you
how to shoot.
Could be things
are gonna get hairy.
See. what is this?
Slow down, bro,
'cause I don't get it.
First you give me a gun
and tell me to pay attention,
'cause I may have
to kill someone.
Now you're giving me
shooting lessons
At least I deserve
an explanation, don't you think?
Am I part of a team or what?
And apart from all that
Gustavo comes and tells me
he sees something in me.
What is it
that he sees in me?
If I had to put it in a word
I'd guess it's "loyalty".
- Loyalty?
- Yeah, only maybe...
you got it for the wrong guy.
Jose?
Nice to see you around here.
- It's a miracle!
- What else?
Yeah, I've been
working hard.
Sure.
So, how's everything going?
It's all fine.
Good.
Well, we're inside.
If you wanna join us...
you're welcome.
Okay.
We can't change the past?
In life, what's done...
is done.
It's no use to be
our own judges
and executioners.
It just ensures we're going
to repeat the cycle.
It's no use to tell yourself,
"I'm hopeless, useless,
I won't be able to make it".
Those burdens
are totally worthless.
Well, who wants
to share something with us?
How about you, Jose?
Tell us what's been
going on lately.
Well...
I went back to meth.
I'm using it again.
But, are you sober right now?
Yeah.
For four days.
I should get a medal?
Well, four days
is four days.
You're finally here,
and that's what matters.
Are you still working?
How's that doing?
Sucks ass.
Sounds goos.
Is there anything special
you want to talk about?
Well...
A couple of weeks ago
I killed a dog.
How come? You hit him
with the car or something?
No.
I put him down.
I watched him go
as he was looking into my eye.
The poor thing didn't...
He didn't know,
he didn't understand.
He was just scared...
And then he was gone.
But was he suffering?
Sometimes you just have to
be merciful.
No.
No, the dog wasn't sick.
He was just...
He was a troubled dog.
What did he do?
Did he bite someone?
No, the dog never bit anyone.
If you give in to temptation,
you end up crossing
to the dark side.
And there's no way back.
No, I wasn't tempted
to kill the dog.
So, what's the matter?
Why did you kill him?
- Hey, Ursula.
- Why?
Maybe it's not the details
that matter,
how the dog died.
Maybe...
the important thing here is...
How do you feel about
what you did, Jose?
- I don't know.
- Who cares how he feels?
- Who cares?
- Hey, Ursula.
What kind of a person
kills a dog for no reason?
- Ursula, please.
- No, you take it
to a shelter...
Give it for adoption.
You just don't sit there
and talk about killing him.
Relax, Ursula. We're not here
to sit in judgment.
Why not?
Seriously, why not?
Maybe she's right.
Maybe I should've done
something different.
You know what the thing is?
If you just do bad stuff
and nothing happens,
then what's the point?
What's the point there?
I understand
we're all here...
to get to know
and accept ourselves, right?
Well, Jose, we do understand
how you're feeling,
but beating the hell
out of yourself
is useless.
No, so what shall I do?
I just stop judging
and start accepting myself?
That's a good start.
So it doesn't matter
what you do?
I just have to feel happy
because I'm a good person
down deep?
I can kill the dogs I want
and just keep a record...
I accepted it.
Camilo, you killed
your own daughter.
You knocked her down!
So what? You're accepting it?
That's it? Bullshit!
Hang on a sec, Jose.
They're two different things.
You know what?
Let me finish.
You wanna know why I'm here?
I'm here to sell you all
some meth.
You're nothing to me
but potential customers!
And you, Camilo.
I used you, bro.
I made you my bitch.
You okay with that?
Are you accepting it as usual?
Sure, right?
No.
I'm not accepting it.
About time, bro.
About time.
Jose!
Jose.
Bring me the torch, please.
I need some light in here.
I think it's full of residue,
but I can't see it.
- That way.
- Where?
On the bottom.
Down there, lower.
- Here?
- Get down, man.
- There?
- Jose.
It's been a week
and I haven't heard from him.
What's going on?
I haven't seen him, bro.
Yeah, I can't see
anything strange here either.
I guess it's already clean.
That...
Look who's coming.
Gómez.
- Congratulate him.
- How come?
He got promoted,
now he's...
a doorman.
It's unbelievable...
to miss one of those guys?
- María.
- Hi. Nice to see you, Gómez.
Welcome, bro!
Thanks.
How's it going?
- Real fine.
- Good.
No, honey, I'll take it up
with Gómez from here.
Really? Take this.
Come this way, for support.
No, no, no. No touching.
No touching.
He's a real fox, you know.
He may end up touching up
the disabled.
Bye, love.
Take care.
Call me if you need anything.
- Sure I will.
- Take care of him.
- Bye, hon, thanks.
- Bye.
You already got the news?
What, Gómez?
Finally got your period?
Really?
I got promoted. Er...
I'm going for Internal Affairs,
for the whole Latin America.
That's great news, bro.
Come here.
Congratulations, bro,
you really deserve that.
You're brave.
Henry, but...
Gómez said you also
have some news for us.
It's more than that.
What I'm going to do...
is drop some theories,
and you'll give me
your opinion.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I've a friend at the Homicide
Department. Remember Rozo?
He's working on a murder case,
a 34 year-old male,
by the name of Guido Bermúdez.
Last month,
this guy was at his apartment,
the bell rang,
he opened the door, and bang!
He got shot in the face.
End of story
for Guido Bermúdez.
Now, it may look...
as a case for Homicide.
Yeah, right.
But hang on a minute.
On analyzing
Guido Bermúdez's profile,
I found out the guy...
was a bona fide
chemistry genius.
A strange guy,
weird and extravagant.
He's a vegetarian, a vegan,
his tastes for music...
are quite singular.
I'd say the guy's
sort of gay,
if you can ever be
"sort of" gay, right?
You know what's
the weirdest thing I found?
Well, this guy
was also the best meth cook
in the whole country.
His specialty product's blue.
Heisenberg!
No, it's not that.
I thought about it,
but then said,
"No, this isn't Heisenberg."
He was Heisenberg's former cook.
And he'll take us to Heisenberg.
Behold, amidst the weird stuff
we found at the scene,
there's something
that's not matching
Guido Bermúdez's profile.
Pay attention.
This is it.
I searched for this number
on the Internet
and I analyzed it.
Turns out, it's a serial number
for a machine.
So here's...
the copies...
Right?
From the catalogues.
Industrial air
filtration system.
High volume.
It's called HEPA,
it's an acronym.
It costs around
three hundred thousand dollars.
Used by pharmaceutical farms,
food processors...
Or otherwise,
to make the biggest meth lab
in Colombia.
Mm-
The filter is manufactured
by an international concern,
Madrigal.
The've a subsidiary
here in Colombia.
I obviously called them,
a very nice woman answered.
One of those pretty voices...
I don't know why
these women love me...
She ended up
helping me a lot.
I started asking questions,
and then told her,
"Help me with this case,
I don't know...
if you know about the filter."
And she suddenly went, "No,
well, we shipped one of those
to Bogotá, six months ago."
Guess who signed
the receipt...?
Mr. Guido Bermúdez.
I kept on searching.
I said, "Come on, help me,
why don't you look up
who paid for the filter?"
So she called me up later
and said, "You know what?
Nobody."
Boss, no one paid
for that filter.
I kept on asking.
Called her the next day.
Surprise! She wasn't
working there anymore.
I got an answer
from the Legal Department,
was asked to give up
my badge number.
A couple of questions.
I mean, brick wall.
There's something else.
This kind of companies
don't give in information
without a legal warrant.
- If there's no pression...
- What did you find?
Madrigal is
an international corporation
based in Madrid, Spain.
They work
with industrial machinery,
they handle chemicals,
they're also
in the construction business,
and they're even investing
in South America.
Among those investments,
they're here in Colombia,
in the fast-food business,
especially in broaster chicken.
Most specifically...
in Pollos Hermanos.
Too much coincidence.
Or we're splitting hairs.
Both, both.
I back the two theories,
none of us
have no proof
there's a meth lab.
You're right.
The only thing I want
to tell you is something
that's spinning in my head,
I can't sleep because of it.
Well, break it through.
It'll help you sleep.
Tell me one thing, boss.
Guido Bermúdez's a vegetarian,
a vegan, he's obsessed
with the subject...
What the hell
was he doing
at a broaster chicken place?
Los Pollos Hermanos?
Well, maybe
he had his meeting there.
Who with?
With this guy here?
Let's see, what do we know
about this Gustavo Cortés?
Apart from him being
"the police's best friend."
Is he making donations?
Boss, this guy has the dough
to finance an operation
like this one.
The guy has connections.
All I say is, he may be
the guy we're looking for.
With all due respect,
I think it's sort of
a weak argument.
I...
I think that...
We'd have the same suspicion,
wherever he'd gone to.
Well, you're right, okay.
Gustavo Cortés, meth lab,
Guido, yeah.
It must be the drugs cocktail
I was given in hospital,
it's making me
rave a little.
But I don't want to leave
this place
without you taking a look
at my last proof over here.
This glass
has the fingerprints
of Mr. Gustavo Cortés.
And you know what I found?
Gustavo Cortés' fingerprints
were also present
in Guido Bermúdez's crime scene.
I just want to...
I hope you...
also have trouble to sleep.