Operation Icebreaker.
We never used that
before. How do you like it?
Well, I don't know, it...
It means nothing to me. It
doesn't suggest anything to me.
You know why, Gómez? Because
your imagination is very limited.
It's hard for you to think of a large ship,
right?
A ship that breaks ice crystals.
You lack brains for that.
If I try to think about it,
let's say I see a ship.
I see the ice and everything.
But in the North Pole, buddy.
But in these lands?
Okay, okay, okay.
No, no,
no. Wait. What do the rest think?
"Icebreaker".
- What do you think?
- Come on.
You don't like it? It's easy to criticize,
right?
I haven't seen you
coming up with a name.
Have you come up with a
name? Nothing! But I warn you
you'd better not begin with
those mythological names.
Like Operation Orion or Phoenix.
No. All those names were already used.
- Who can think of a name?
- Operation Poet, my Major.
Sorry?
- Operation Poet.
- Wait for me on the taxi, will you?
- Let's see. What do you say?
- Operation Laser.
Laser. Gosh,
no. I have an idea. Look.
- Operation...
[Henry writes BALL
BREAKER on board] - No.
It's perfect! Isn't
it? You don't like it.
Well,
you know what you will like? This one.
This one. Operation...
- IBH. Right on.
- IBH?
Do you know what that means? "I'm
the boss here". So that's the name.
Let's move on. Here we
have Mr. Domingo Molina.
Aka "El Loco".
Way smarter than your
average cheese-eaters.
No wonder he worked for us.
I've been on his trail
since he began selling E.
Now he's moved on
up on the business
and has a complete
catalog of designer drugs.
Mr. Molina, aka "El Loco"
became famous because
he squealed on dealers
and ended up snaking
their customers.
Let's give Gómez a
big round of applause.
- Bravo, bravo!
- Bravo!
What an intervention!
It's a great contribution.
Shall I go on, Gómez?
El Loco, one of our snitches
now turns out to be missing.
We think he was cut down.
Found his car
out in the boonies.
What do you want now, Gómez?
Everything suggests they
killed him for being a snitch.
That's true. Let's see.
Here we have Emilio Molina.
He's missing too. There's a
relationship there. Bear that in mind.
What matters here is that,
in El Loco's car
we found two grams... Well,
not "we".
"I" found two grams
of methamphetamine
which was totally transparent.
Take a look at it, please.
The lab guys had the
same reaction as you.
They tell us it is the
purest they have ever seen.
Ninety-nine-point-one percent.
This is something different. It isn't
the crap with which we usually deal.
No, these aren't colored
candies they give to rich kids
to get them horny so they
stick it up some other kid's ass.
No way,
gentlemen. This is something big.
We believe this methamphetamine
was cooked here in Colombia.
Why? Who asked why? Was it you?
Be careful.
Because of this!
Come on, Gómez, try it on.
Try it on, buddy. It'll look good
on you. It has the same eyebrows.
We found this gas mask in
the same area as the drug.
What's more,
our guys swabbed the filter element
and found the same 99.1 meth.
And this means what,
gentlemen? It's crystal clear.
Now we've got a new cook
who's making his debut
with his first product.
We don't know if
it's one guy or more
if it's a kitchen full
of people cooking
if the guy's breath
smells of tequila
or if, when he goes to the bathroom,
he shits coffee beans.
We have no idea if the guy is Colombian,
Mexican or gringo.
Gentlemen,
the only thing we know for sure
is that we're entering the big
leagues of methamphetamine.
Such purity can only come
from a high-skilled specialist.
Me, personally,
I believe we're facing up
to a new kingpin,
who's producing
something we'd never
had here: crystal meth.
You're eating chicken
with hormones.
Jesus, Walt,
you're burning the shit out of them.
Honey! Order some pizza!
- He burned the meat.
- Okay, okay.
No, I'm not eating that.
- The coleslaw has mayonnaise?
- Yes.
Is it low-fat or
regular mayonnaise?
I don't know, it's store-bought.
It's in the fridge, go check it out.
All right, looking good.
- Henry, you need another beer?
- At last, buddy.
I have to be almost dehydrated
for you to bring me something?
Can't you go get it,
or you lost your hands?
Never mind. María?
Yes, please.
- Hey, I want a beer too.
- Yeah, sure.
And I want Shania
Twain to give me a tuggy.
The poor deluded creature!
How about some more soda?
Honey, do you need anything?
Okay. Be right back
Will you bring me my
jacket? It's getting cold.
- Sure.
- Why didn't we eat inside?
No, no, no.
What, are you kidding me?
Girls gotta be lining
up left and right.
You look like a damn movie star,
man.
Despite your... you
do have something!
Seriously. You tell him. Tell
him how good-looking he is.
- You're adorable, my dear.
- Adorable? No, no, no.
Please,
don't buy that crap of being adorable.
You'll be pulling down
panties from every girl...
Henry!
in Colombia.
You don't wanna be adorable,
you want to be hot.
That's women's perspective.
They only want us to
become their gay friend.
And, before you know it,
you'll end up saying
"Did you have your hair
done? You look gorgeous!".
I'll give you some
advice for you to get a girl.
First of all you gotta be
constant and persistent.
You just gotta have confidence.
That was what I
liked most from María.
I kept bugging her for a date,
she kept saying no.
Liar! You should've seen
everything he did to get to me.
It's true. Your uncle
here is a sick obsessive.
Yeah, I wouldn't like to be one
of those thugs he chases down.
Do you want a good
example of a real ladykiller?
- No.
- Good old Walter.
Yes,
sir. Do you know how they met?
Mom was a waitress in a restaurant,
right?
No,
your mother wasn't a waitress.
- Yes.
- She worked the cash register.
And it wasn't
really a restaurant.
It was a very nice café
in the Industrial Area
close to the lab
where I used to work.
One day, I got out from work,
went to this café
and suddenly saw your mom,
this beautiful woman
sitting at the cash register.
I got totally smitten with her.
Since then, every day, I got out from
work and made straight for the café.
And I watched her for hours.
Of course, she never deigned
to raise her head to look at me.
Sometimes,
people don't notice you're there, Walter.
Shut up.
- I'm just joking.
- The thing is
when I noticed this woman,
then I started going every day.
I rushed from work to the café
sat at the same table,
and she was there
just staring at the counter.
Until I discovered what she was doing
she was doing crossword puzzles. Right?
Pretending that
she was still working
she was only absorbed in
her crossword puzzles, so--
I hate crossword puzzles
but once I caught on to that,
I'd do crossword puzzles too.
Eventually,
I caught her looking over at me.
I took my chance and
began saying: "Excuse me.
I need help with 14 across.
It's a really tough one.
Four letters,
you can run it without legs.
- Risk.
- Risk."
What a lucky bastard!
How did she came
up with that word?
- That's persistence, you see?
- Cielo, are you all right?
- What's the matter?
- Mom, what is it?
Ask him.
What's she talking about,
Walter? What did you do to her?
I have cancer.
Lung cancer.
No way!
Ask him how long he's known.
How long, Walter?
I guess a month, maybe.
For God sakes, Walt. We're just
sitting out there like nothing's going on.
He made me promise
not to tell anybody.
But Christ, these last 48 hours
have been the
worst of my entire life.
Buddy, why? I mean,
why wouldn't you wanna tell anybody?
Walt, don't you see?
Everybody just
wants to help you.
We're family. We get
through these things together.
And I don't get it.
You know,
lung cancer? How can that happen?
- You don't even smoke.
- I guess it goes back
to the time when he worked
in the applications lab.
All those chemicals they had
you working around. They're lethal.
They're shit.
Honey, that was 15 years ago.
And we always took
the proper precautions.
We should hire a lawyer
and sue that fucking
lab! This is their fault--!
Okay, Cielo. Let's focus here.
Because we kept our mouth--
Okay, so,
what's the next step for Walt?
Certainly a second opinion,
right?
- What do you think?
- Right. Right, absolutely.
Tomorrow I can talk to my boss.
He knows every doctor in town.
We'll find you the best,
the oncology dream team. I promise.
Thanks.
I'm gonna go check on Junior. I really
didn't mean for him to find out that way.
I'll go with you.
Oof...
Walt, buddy,
I want you to know that
whatever happens,
I'll always take care of your family.
You can count on
me. As long as I live
your family will have
everything they need.
Jose!
Jose. Jose, didn't you hear?
- Shit!
- Hey, Jose.
Hey, yo, what happened to your hallway,
man? Did the ceiling fall down?
Yeah, no,
bro. I think the house is just settling.
A piece fell down.
Jose, my uncle could fix you up,
he's a contractor.
He could fill the hole.
What?
That I have an uncle
who could fill the hole.
Which one? The basuco smoker?
No, the boozer.
Yeah? Yeah, right on,
I should grab that number.
Say, Jose
you still cook a little crystal?
Yeah, Gordito.
Could be, yeah. You know,
from time to time.
I heard you lost your
partner. Is it true?
Tell me, Gordo,
what's the word out there?
No, man, he's out.
Really?
He got lucky. They let him out
because of the judicial strike.
What a lucky bastard, bro!
I think he skipped
town or something.
I have no idea.
Hey, Jose,
maybe you have anything to have a trip?
Acid, E, coke,
sour mulberry juice--
Hell, yeah! It's Saturday night
and we're here doing nothing.
I want to get high, bro.
Didn't I tell you, bitches?
What is it?
Well, the last batch I cooked
was the best batch
I've ever cooked.
See, these are
transparent, no color.
It's like seeing the
future through a window.
So you learned to cook real crystal,
man?
Real crystal, Tripa.
But you know what, bro?
Lately it's been kind
of making me paranoid
and I didn't like it.
You know, Gordito,
health-wise, I'll just lay off.
Yo, if you're not into sharing,
man
- Tell us to piss off.
- We don't need no soap opera.
Yo, no! Soap opera? No way!
Look, what I have it's the bomb.
We could make three
joints and blow our heads off.
- Hell, yeah!
- Yeah? Three joints.
Five, if you want.
I'm off, bro.
No, Gordo. Gordo. No,
no. Tripa! Hey!
Yeah, I'm off too.
Hey, buddies, no. Don't go!
Hey, bitches! What's up?
Look. Look at this beauty.
Look what I've got here.
When have I let you
down? Let me introduce you
to the new collection
of José Miguel Rosas.
Crystal! All that you
want. There you are.
- Easy, Gordo, easy!
- Jose!
- When...?
- Brother! I love you!
Okay,
grab the pipe and light it.
The pipe. All right,
wait, careful.
Yo!
Tripa, don't go, bro. I--
Yo, there's more there, buddy.
No, no. Gordo, Gordo,
come here. Don't go.
Buddy.
Tripa!
Yo, don't leave. There's more here,
bro.
These are crystals. They
weren't cooked in Colombia.
Oat cream! Oat
cream! Cold oat cream!
Oat cream! Oat cream!
Cold oat cream!
Just drop it and let's go.
Do you say so?
Yes,
we've got a lot of work to do.
You're right.
Honey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you sure? I'm right
outside if you need me.
Yes, I'm coming.
Yeah, any time on Friday is absolutely
fine. How much is the appointment?
Okay. And in case he
does treatment with you
how much would it be?
Okay,
so Friday 10:45. Thank you so much.
Honey,
I've just called an excellent oncologist
one of the best in the entire
nation. Doctor Sánchez.
He founded the Cancer,
Science and Health Institute.
He's a busy man. He had all
covered for another five months.
But he worked us in and gave
us an appointment for Friday.
I mean,
María really came through for us.
How much is it?
Two hundred the
first appointment.
The treatment is expensive,
but never mind, honey.
We'll put it on the
credit card or whatever.
Our health plan doesn't
cover something like that.
What do you think Doctor
Sánchez's gonna say?
We already know what happens
with me. What difference does it make?
The difference is our
health plan won't pay for this.
Also, he'll be seeing you soon
and it's a quality
service. What can I say?
It's a private place so,
yes, it's more expensive.
But Doctor Sánchez is one
of the best in the country.
Patients come from all
over the world to see him.
Honey, in your condition, I won't
want you to deal with State bureaucracy.
Just imagine how
long could it take
for you to be referred
to a specialist? Months!
The doctor who saw you
didn't even return my call.
Is that the treatment
we'll receive from now on?
Do you know how much
does a private treatment cost?
One hundred and fifty,
one hundred and eighty million?
Not including medicines.
Where will we get
the money from?
What if we mortgage the house?
Don't even think about it!
We haven't finished
paying this house yet.
It's our only asset.
Well,
María and Henry have some savings--
- No, no, no!
- They could--
Sorry.
We're not gonna do that.
Well, maybe we can ask your mom.
Have you even called her yet?
Walt, regardless,
you're gonna have to tell her about this.
She has every right to know
what's happening to you.
And if she wants to pray,
don't judge her, leave her.
She might even do us
a favor with her prayers.
This is the right moment for
you to come closer together.
If you don't want to,
I'm willing to do it.
No, no, no. I'll call her.
I don't even want us thinking about
money. Money is not the issue here.
It's your health what
matters. Nothing else.
No matter how expensive it is,
no matter how much we have to pay.
I only want you
to get over this.
That's why I want you to see
the best doctor in the country.
It really would feel better if I
know you're in good hands.
Don't you see it?
Okay.
All right, we'll go on Friday.
But on one condition: I'm paying for this,
okay? I'll figure it out.
All right? Thanks.
Hey,
why don't you knock before entering?
The latch was off.
What happened?
Nothing, the rubber of the
valve was damaged. I fixed it.
- So, what's up?
- What do you mean?
I don't know.
You're acting weird.
- Junior.
- You're acting like...
You're acting like
nothing is going on.
Hey,
asshole! I was waiting for that spot!
Great! What I really liked most
were those butts I saw over there. No,
Carolina.
We look like two grannies.
We drank almost nothing.
I think I ended up paying
like a million two hundred.
Nothing,
buddy. We drank nothing.
No, come on,
tell me what Carolina said to you.
That I want to know.
Sir, would you please hang up?
You can't use cellphones here.
Which cellphone? No,
no, this is--
Sir,
I don't care. You can't use it here.
No,
I did see him. He's such an asshole.
I've seen him at
the club many times.
He's one of those morons
who pretends to be rich
but doesn't have a cent.
- Sir.
- Sure.
Sir,
I'll have to ask you to leave the place.
I hung up already.
Next customer.
Sir.
He doesn't have a cent.
- Sir, your turn.
- He pretends to be--
What can I do for you today?
Thanks,
I'd like to make a deposit.
Sure.
I can assure you they're real!
What do you bet?
Anything you want!
What do you want to lose? Half
a bottle. No, a bottle at the club.
- Thanks.
- Are you afraid or what?
Sure! I'll take her...
I don't see why they force you to
choose between the cello and the piano.
You show so much
promise with both.
They say they can't have any
switching between woodwinds.
Because no matter how they divide it up,
someone would be left out.
Rules are rules, I guess.
And rules are to be kept,
my dear.
If so,
it's much better that you play the piano.
It's an instrument
of a higher level.
With cello, you might go unnoticed
among the rest of the orchestra.
And you have to train at
the best schools in the world.
For example, in Jiulliard,
New York, right?
You have real talent,
and I'm not just saying that.
Was that in our backyard?
Who's there?
We have security cameras!
Sofía, set the alarm off.
God, José Miguel,
you scared the hell out of me!
Why can't you go in
like a decent person
instead of freaking
us out like a criminal?
Mom, dad, little bro, what's up?
Got new patio
furniture. Right on.
Sorry about the
flowerpot. I'll fix it.
- What do you think it could be?
- I don't know.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Guillermo, I think...
- we should check his arms.
- Heroin?
No.
So much computer will do you no good,
bro.
Good old Sebas,
when did you get this?
Last year.
"Outstanding Student". Congratulations,
bro!
What's this? "Environmental
Consciousness Award".
What, you, like,
recycle cans and shit?
No,
it's an article I wrote to complain
about the paper used by
companies for their advertising.
It was in the newspaper.
I thought you'd read it.
Right on, little bro.
Right on.
Now, hey, remember
not all learning
comes out of books.
There's another
intelligence out there.
We should hang out more often,
so you get away from...
You know,
just... Just kick back and chill.
Maybe your elder brother
gives you some advice
that can come in
handy. Don't you think?
So what, little bro?
Are you already an
expert with the bass?
I'm getting better in hip-hop,
you know?
We could even make a duo.
- Yes or no?
- It's a cello.
Yeah, no. Cello,
I find it boring.
Hey, guys, how we doing in here?
We're good.
- Sebas?
- Yeah. Fine, Mom.
If you need something,
just let me know.
You see this?
What am I,
some criminal or something?
- Whatever.
- Whatever?
Now they must be like:
"No, Guillermo. We can't
let them spend time together.
He'll corrupt our kid."
They think I'll warp the
mind of their favorite son.
I'm the favorite?
Yeah, right. You're practically
all they ever talk about.
What a homo!
"Why does professor Blanco
love Chemistry so much?".
Stupid fart old man.
It's the last straw. I've
got to do things right.
- Yeah?
- Yo, man, it's me.
Hey, listen.
You know that... product?
You got any more of that?
No, Gordo,
you homo. I'm done doing charity.
No, no charity. No.
I got this cousin,
he's got him some rich friends.
These dudes are in town,
they're looking to party.
What they had didn't
even make them dizzy.
So, I was thinking
that your stuff is,
like, so sweet.
We can do business together.
So, what do you say?
What the hell are
you doing here?
I said I didn't want
to see you again.
Yo, I waited till the ball
buster and your kid left.
Why are you here? You
wearing a wire? Who sent you?
Homo.
- You setting me up?
- What's wrong with you?
- Where's the wire?
Let me see it! Where is it?
You want a wire? I got a wire.
Speak into the mike, bitch.
A wire! Cut the crap
and all that paranoia.
So who did you tell about?
Nobody. What, are you nuts?
Then why are you here?
I don't know. I thought that,
after what we did and how we did it
maybe we needed
to talk about it.
Talk about what?
Everybody digs
the meth we cooked.
I got dudes that
would give their left nut
- for a little more.
- So?
I'm just saying,
if you ever saw your way clear
to you and I cooking
a little more...
- Get off my property.
- What? Why?
Go! And don't you ever
come back to this house!
Get out! Now!
All right, you know what?
Eight million.
Your share from selling that
batch. That's why I'm here.
Yeah,
I didn't smoke it all. I'm here to pay you.
Ungrateful bastard.
Non-small-cell adenocarcinoma.
Stage 3A.
It's spread from the
lung to the lymph nodes.
There's no denying
it's very serious.
But it's curable.
I prefer the word "treatable."
The current treatments
can be very effective.
Through chemo and radiotherapy,
in some cases...
I can't make any promises,
but in certain cases
it's prolonged a patient's life and,
in some other cases...
Again,
I'm not making any promises
but it even resulted in remission. That is,
the patient recovers.
What about the side effects?
Well, in fact, there are.
They can be mild
or pretty darn awful.
I'll be totally honest with you.
Some people don't feel a thing.
For some other patients,
it's like torture.
Typically, there's hair loss.
During chemotherapy
you may find yourself unusually fatigued,
not much energy.
You won't want to get out
of bed. You may lose weight
due to reduced appetite.
Muscle aches and pains,
gums will get sore and bleed.
Possible kidney
or bladder irritation.
What is this?
- You know nothing about it?
- Nothing.
How many times have we had the
same conversation over and over again?
Where you look us in the
eye and you plead ignorance?
And it makes us feel like fools
because our elder son
manipulates us as he pleases.
Enough, José Miguel.
What kind of example
is it for your brother?
We are not going to
have this in our house.
We need you to
leave once and for all.
Unbelievable.
Thanks for not telling on me.
Do you think I
could have it back?
What are you doing?
You've got to be more careful,
little bro, okay?
It's skunk-weed anyway.
This is awesome,
honey. You've got to read it.
Here.
Look. There are
a lot of testimonies
given by patients that
are actually very hopeful.
So can I call them?
And tell them you'll
start next week?
Don't you think that we
need to discuss it a little more?
Later?
What is there to discuss?
They're the best doctors.
We don't have time.
Well, for example,
there's the money discussion.
It costs 250 million
including surgery. It's crazy!
There's financing.
There's installment plans.
I could quit selling brownies
and go back to work
in some company.
Let's say that there is a way. And
we spend all that money. And then?
What do you mean?
Your health is priceless,
Walter. Don't you get it?
What if it doesn't work?
Honey,
am I supposed to leave you
with a 250 million debt?
Then why don't you just fucking die,
already?
Just give up and die.
An old woman's crossing
as if she owned the street.
Hey,
everything's all right. Today's my day.
Great, hole in one. Yeah,
perfect.
And you know who was
there? Paola Gutiérrez.
Son of a bitch! My car,
you bastard, son of a bitch!
What happened? My car!
Somebody! Somebody help me!
Help! My car! Call
the fire department!
Hey, man, what happened?
You were here! What
happened to my car?
Help! Put it out!
Bring some water!
Help, help! Somebody help me!