What did you say to Gustavo?
Why is he on to us?
What do you mean he's on to us?
He's walking to his car.
Then suddenly he isn't.
He looked around
and then turned back.
What, does he have
some kind of sixth sense?
What did you say to him?
Could I ask my own question
right now, Walter?
Tell me you don't have a bomb
in that diaper bag.
How do you bring a bomb here?
What? Was I supposed
to leave it on his car?
You're supposed
to bring it into a hospital?
- Jose.
- Are you out of your mind?
Where can we find Gustavo?
Name a place.
Name me just one place
where I could surprise him.
- I don't know.
- Not the restaurant
nor the laundry,
nor the factory farm.
They're all wired with cameras.
Jose, think.
Give me one place
where I can get him.
- I don't know!
- Please!
Because if you can't tell me,
we are dead.
- Well, maybe--
- José Miguel Rosas.
I'm Juan Osorio.
He's Detective Adrián Franco.
We're from the Department
of Special Investigations
and we need to talk to you.
Could we have
a few minutes of your time?
About what?
- I didn't catch your name.
- About what?
It concerns
Andrea Cantillo's son, Byron.
How about you come with us?
We just want to clear
a few things up. No big deal.
- Am I under arrest?
- No, you're not under arrest.
We're just talking.
A friendly
conversation.
So if I get tired of talking,
I may get up and leave?
We'd prefer you didn't.
- You'd prefer?
- Yes.
José Miguel, tell us.
Why did you tell Brock's mom
that the boy had been poisoned?
Look...
You say it like that
and it sounds...
It sounds weird, overblown.
I just asked Andrea
if doctors had considered
that Byron
might have been poisoned.
You know, in a cover-all-bases
kind of sense.
I were doing nothing
but simply trying to help.
And I'm sure doctors
appreciated you helping
them out like that
especially
with how specific
you were.
Ricin.
Nobody talks about ricin.
You don't see that every day.
So when doctors hear that
they take it very seriously.
- As do we.
- Yeah, all right.
And nice, you trying to
help out like that and all.
Sharing your knowledge
and expertise.
I ain't go no expertise.
I was just trying to help.
You just guessed
this one rare poison
might be the thing
that put this kid
in the hospital.
Congratulations!
His doctors
are beginning to think
that you might be right.
But come on,
tell us.
Why ricin?
How did you come up with that?
I must've saw it on a TV program
about doctors and stuff.
No, you know what?
It was the science channel.
Sometimes your brain
makes these connections.
Your brain?
Yeah, mine does.
That's interesting.
Look, buddies,
I've really got to get back.
But why?
We're still talking.
So I'm not under arrest
but I can't leave.
So, then, I guess I should
call my lawyer. Right?
We're just
chatting,
José Miguel.
Why can't we keep
talking
as friends?
Keep it light?
Man, you know how it is
when the lawyers get to it.
Things change,
it's not the same.
A serious breach
usually opens up.
And, in the end,
somebody gets angry.
It turns adversarial.
Then we gotta book you.
There's no need!
You've been around the block.
Look, José Miguel,
let's be straight here.
You're no boy scout.
Saúl Bueno.
So do you call him,
or I gotta do it?
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
I need Saúl.
Right now!
So you break into the place?
You've got to go
the hard way?
You didn't bothered
answering the phone
or the door.
What else could I do?
You know? Forget it.
Where's Saúl?
Goddamn it!
Why would he be here?
You know where he is!
I need a number!
Look. Let me explain
something to you.
My partner and I--
You don't say!
Are in danger, right?
No shit!
Why do you think he's not here?
What idiocy did you two
do this time?
And what gives you the right
to break down my door?
Look, for God's sake,
give me the number.
You are such a pain in my ass.
You're the reason
I've got to go on unemployment.
I've already taken that in.
And I was ready to leave,
but no!
Now I've got to wait
for a plate glass guy
to come and fix this door
for who knows how long.
And who pays for this?
Look, here I have
more than
one and a half million pesos.
That will more than cover it.
Now, I apologize profusely.
I didn't want to do this,
but I need Saúl urgently.
Please, the phone number.
You think this will cover it?
Door like this
is going to cost
way more than that.
I bet you
it winds up costing...
Forty million pesos.
What?
Are you insane or what?
Who the hell is going to charge
forty million?
No reputable vendor could.
Right.
Now I'm thinking
fifty million pesos.
I'll be right back.
Fuck!
Hi, Rebeca, how are you?
It's Walter Blanco,
your neighbor.
Yes, madam.
Look, the thing is...
Fine, fine, thank you.
Yes. Growing up
by leaps and bounds.
Rebeca, Cielo and I
are out of town.
Yes, yes.
Way deserved. Thanks.
Junior's with us and,
you know how he is,
he just told us
that he thinks he may
have left the burner on and...
Yes, God forbid there's a fire.
Exactly!
That's why I'm calling.
Do you still happen to have
the key we'd left you in case--?
Exactly, that's right.
Would you do me that favor?
Yes, madam.
I'll await your call.
Thanks, Rebeca.
Rebeca.
Yes, go ahead.
That's good!
That's a relief.
Really, you took a weight
off my mind.
Yes.
I owe you one, big time.
Yes, same to you.
I'll tell her, thank you.
Bye.
So how's he doing?
You could at least say
instead of being
a couple of dicks about it.
José Miguel, prove it to us
that you really care
about Byron.
Tell us what you fucking know.
Yo, man!
I already told you what I know.
Tell us again.
What are you,
like broken records?
I was trying to be helpful.
Period. End of story.
Nothing else happened.
If that's gonna be it
we'll have to wait and see
what the tox screen says.
This like a hollow!
Not cozy at all.
What did you tell them?
I told them they were
a couple of dicks.
You see?
My client, he's a wordsmith.
All right, gentlemen.
You've been so nice
and so polite
it's been a pleasure.
Now, up you go.
Pretend. Make like you respect
the rule of law.
You've never studied law
at all, right?
How do you need me to say it?
Au revoir, auf widersehen,
arriverderci.
Get the hell out.
Come on!
That's it. Right on!
Close it, please.
What am I gonna do with you two?
If I ever get anal polyps,
I'll know what to name them:
"-" and "Aha".
You gonna get me out of here?
No.
Not even if I could.
We're gonna let them
look into this ricin thing
and meanwhile
you stay here
for as long as necessary.
You're a lot safer in here.
They just tried to get
your partner in his own home.
Jesus! Is he okay?
Well, he's okay
like a fruit fly's okay.
He says the only option's
to cut Gustavo down.
Shit.
I thought we did this
for money's sake
not for us to kill one another.
That's disgusting!
You two want to stick
your wangs in a hornet's nest,
it's a free country.
But how come I always gotta get
sloppy seconds?
Why? It's my fault.
Nobody forced me! My bad.
Your partner wants to know
if you've got anything for me.
I hope so.
Tell me I didn't poke my head up
for nothing.
Yeah. I've been thinking.
- Casa Tranquila.
- What's that?
It's an old folks' home.
Our boy tells me that Gustavo
took him there
to visit one of the patients
- who, he says,
you'll definitely remember.
- Who is he?
Héctor Salamanca.
Old guy in a wheelchair.
Doesn't talk, rings a bell.
Does that ring a bell?
Yes, I know.
I remember him perfectly.
It's really possible
to communicate through a bell?
Listen, Saúl.
How often does he go?
How often does he visit him?
Gustavo goes and visits
an old cartel associate
in an old folks' home.
That information
doesn't help me much.
I can't hide out
in a nursing home for six months
waiting for Gustavo.
It's not even like
they're friends.
According to José Miguel
Gustavo was torturing
the old guy.
What? What does that mean?
He went there to tell him
the last of his family was dead.
And as per José Miguel words
Gustavo seemed to enjoy
telling him.
Rosas asked him about it
and all that Gustavo would say
was that this Uncle Héctor
once murdered someone
close to him. To Gustavo.
Wait. Héctor murdered
someone close to Gustavo?
I know it sound
not particularly fruitful.
- Sorry, that's all I got.
- It is. Of course it is.
They're not friends.
They're enemies.
Well, gentlemen.
Your next number
in this coverall game is...
B number 3.
B as in baby, bike
or bed.
Followed by O.
Four, seven.
On the other side of your card.
I know you despise me
and I know how badly
you want to see me dead
but I know a man
whom you hate even more.
I'm here to offer you
an opportunity for revenge.
Héctor, you need something?
You need to go poopie?
Want me to get
the board for you?
A.
E. I.
O. Row O.
O. P.
Q. R.
R.
A.
E.
I.
Row I.
I? Okay.
A. E. I.
M. N.
A. E.
E. Row E.
E.
F.
G.
A. E. I. O. U. U.
A. E. I.
O.
Row O.
P.
Ring up.
Who do you want us to ring up,
Héctor?
How's everything?
No news, sir.
Everything's under control.
Good.
- So what, buddy?
- How's it going?
- Come here, look at this.
- What's up?
- Look.
- No kidding!
Again with the laundry?
You buying it?
No, no, no, hear me out.
See this electricity panel?
See what it says?
It's is a 7,200-amp service.
This place has two of them.
Laundry this size typically
has only one, okay?
So what's with the extra panel?
In case the other fails?
No way. Now what?
You're some kind
of an electrician?
- Thomas Edison.
- No, no.
I looked on the Internet.
Freakin' Internet!
Find anything on it these days.
I went into something
called chat rooms
and asked
a bunch of electricians.
We started talking
panels, amps, plugs
and ground.
You name it!
It was great!
I can give you the blog's name.
So let's pop over,
have another look-see?
- What do you say?
- Maybe we should wait.
Meantime, let me tell you.
I think we may have a lead
on something.
A lead? On what?
Look, I have this guy
down at the office.
Says he has some information.
The thing is
he'll only give it to you.
Really?
Let's see.
Remember that friend of yours?
Héctor Salamanca.
Sounds familiar?
The old cripple guy
with the bell?
Rather crap on our floor
than talk to us?
No, I don't remember him at all.
Well, he's the guy.
His nurse calls us.
Says he wants to powwow.
We have this guy
at the office for three hours.
You know him already, right?
Can't talk, can't communicate.
And he still just wants
to talk to you.
Do not even think
about going down there, Henry.
- María.
- I mean it.
This is clearly a trick
to get you out into the open!
That old man's bait
to have you killed.
That's what we thought, but--
That's all this is!
Well, listen.
We were checking up
on Héctor Salamanca
and it's been years since
this guy's been a player.
He only had Tuco
his nephew, who's gone.
Doesn't have anybody.
The nurse checks out.
And let me tell you
there's not safer place
for Henry than the office.
Of course, if he wants to.
I don't think this sounds
like a good idea.
Uncle, don't go there.
There is no way
you are going to do it.
You're not leaving home.
End of story.
Hi, Henry.
- Hey, boss.
- Thanks for coming down.
No problem. Let's see
what he wanted to tell me
our friend here.
Hi.
A. E. I. O.
Row O.
O. P.
Q. R. S.
S.
A. E. I. O. U.
Row U.
Is it U?
U?
U.
A. B. C.
C.
A. E. I.
Row I.
I. J. K.
K.
A. E. I.
Row I.
J. K. L. M.
A. E. I. O. U.
U. V. W. X. Y.
SUCK MY
All right, that's enough.
Thank you.
Sorry, gentlemen.
I am just so, so sorry.
At least this time
he didn't shit himself
and leave the place
stinking of poop, right?
Guess that's progress.
- Yes.
- We may have a problem.
I've got eyes on Anti-narcotics
and they just had a visitor.
- Who?
- Héctor Salamanca.
I don't even know
what to say to you.
How far you think that kind
of behavior is going to get you?
You just sit here
and think about
what you've just done.
It's not getting you far,
let me tell you.
You heard me?
Any second thoughts?
Then let's get to work.
I've missed you a lot.
I'm knitting a scarf for you.
It's beautiful!
My dear son.
Look. Come here, son. Look.
It's a beautiful scarf!
I did it for you!
I've thought of you a lot.
So you don't get cold
when you go out.
Rosas.
You're free to go.
Why? What happened?
Tox screen came back.
No ricin poisoning.
Surprised?
No, why should I be?
Your cap!
Till we meet again.
Hey, Andrea,
I'm just checking on Byron.
Hey, it sounds like-- Taxi!
Listen, just call me
if you can, all right?
I'm headed back over.
Buddy, can you tell me
how to get
to 145 and 85-80?
Get him in, get him in!
Close the door. Quick.
Hi.
It's done.
We picked up Rosas,
no witnesses.
What about Héctor?
I've checked inside and out.
No wires, no camera,
no surveillance.
A police cruiser rolled
through about an hour ago.
Seemed routine.
It's just him,
alone in his room.
I'm on my way.
Maybe it's better
if I do this myself.
No. I do this.
It's all clear.
What kind of cartel man
talks to Anti-narcotics?
No man.
Not a man of honor!
A crippled little rat,
that's what you are!
What a reputation
to leave behind.
Is that how you want
to be remembered?
Last chance to look at me,
Héctor.
Aah!
The southern motorway
is very congested
so we suggest people
to take another road--
Sorry to interrupt you,
but I have breaking news.
There has been an explosion
at a nursing home
called Casa Tranquila.
We've got very few details
on it so far.
The initial report is, though,
that three people were killed.
Being a nursing home,
this news is disturbing.
Our hearts going out
to the victims of this tragedy.
Our most sincere condolences
to all those affected.
We'll bring you more
details as soon as we get them.
Let's go to commercial break
and then back with more details.
You wanna cook
with a broken arm?
All right.
What, you got a problem
with stairs?
Gustavo is dead.
We've got work to do.
Out!
Everybody! Get out!
There's a fire, go out!
- He's going to pull through.
- Yeah?
It looked
kind of touch-and-go there
but it seems
he's gonna make it.
Thank God.
I'm glad to hear that.
Don't know how much, really.
That's good.
Yo.
They still saying
it wasn't the ricin.
I don't understand.
If it wasn't ricin,
then what was it?
Saying it was most likely
a flower called
lily of the valley
or something. Like it's common
'cause it's sweet
and little kids eat them
and wind up poisoning
themselves.
So Gustavo didn't poison him
after all.
Still he had to go, right?
We had to get rid of him.
You're damn right.
He had to go.
Yeah.
You know, I should get back.
Andrea's waiting.
I'm here at Casa Tranquila
where three people are dead
following an explosion
that rocked this nursery home.
The fireball
consumed one resident's room
and damaged common areas.
Apparently, two more bodies
where found in the operation.
Walter!
Experts in forensic medicine--
Let me get somewhere
where I can hear you.
The first report
about the events--
Tell him Uncle Henry was right!
- Junior!
- Tell him.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
How am I doing?
How are you doing?
I'm good.
I'm doing quite well.
You saw the news?
Gustavo Cortés is dead.
He was blown up along
with some person
from some Mexican cartel.
Anti-narcotics has no idea
what to make of it.
- Walter, I need to know.
- It's over. We're safe.
Was this you?
What happened?
I won.
LILY OF THE VALLEY