Well, Mr. Walter,
fortunately,
there was no need
to clean up the sticky
blood as last time.
Sticky blood?
Yes, it's just that
a few days ago
I hit a stray dog.
- I told you that, remember?
Right.
This car is in good shape.
And as to Junior's call,
well,
the crankshaft was replaced,
also the break fluid
and the oil.
Haver.
What about the noise
I told you about?
It was a problem
on the door window.
- Right.
- That's all.
Junior,
don't give me
that look.
This is a very fine
car.
It looks like
it's made for a woman,
but it's a very nice car.
Don't get carried away
by appearances.
And you're good to
go.
But if you stress out
with the city traffic,
that's not my
problem.
I ride her nice and slow, Haver.
Right.
This car, well,
she brings me
so many memories.
Memories?
Yes, this was my wife's car,
Junior.
She'll never forgive me
for selling it.
They don't make cars
like this anymore.
- This is a fine car.
- Haver,
let's do business.
What are you talking about?
What would you give me for it?
You know it well.
You know exactly
what it's worth.
What's more,
I'll give you a discount.
- Are you kidding me?
- No, I'm actually serious.
And this one.
Dad, what about me?
Don't you want a new
car?
Yes!
I do.
The thing is, Mr. Walter,
a minute ago
I wasn't thinking
- about buying a car--
- Perfect, then think it over!
Buy one, take two.
Walter,
are you nuts?
Why?
Are you the only one
who can have a new car here?
Are you being serious?
Very serious.
You're so slow!
Yes, of course
we'll be working closely
on the investigation,
and if there happens to be
any movement
or something strange,
we'll let you know in Spain.
Don't you worry.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
Yes, sir. All clear.
Don't you worry at all.
Goodbye.
I can't talk,
I'm at work right now.
Yes, I know.
This is a heads-up.
You've got visitors.
Visitors? You mean today?
- I mean 30 seconds.
- Mario, Mario.
Come in.
Boss, someone's here for you.
Mrs. Lidia Barrera!
Remember me?
We met at the office
the other day.
Right?
Let me introduce myself again.
My name is Henry Navarro.
This is agent Gómez.
We're from Anti-Narcotics.
Yes, of course I remember you.
What can I do for you?
There.
The one over there
in the navy clothes.
This can't be.
Ahhhhh!
Yes?
They got Ronaldo,
Ronaldo is done, Mario.
- Okay.
- Okay?
No, no, no,
this is not okay at all.
The look he just gave me
was the antithesis of "Okay."
Breathe, Lidia.
No one's talking to the police.
Neither him
nor the ones we've got in jail.
I told you I'll handle it.
Did you not understand?
Half a dozen cops
just came through the door!
Screaming and yelling at me,
and they made me
take them to the warehouse.
To the warehouse!
Look, Ronaldo
was my person of trust.
He was the one
who turned off the cameras,
the one who drove
the transport truck.
I can't do this alone!
Let's be real here, Mario,
this is messed up.
Nothing's messed up.
I'll send someone else in.
Thanks, O
appreciate
it.
No, It's
just...
How can you buy a
car
with only 500,
500 horsepower?
500 horse-- Ha, ha, ha, ha!
That 500-car,
it looks like a skate!
Horsepower isn't
everything.
You have to factor in
drag and torque
and suspension
and weight of the car.
I beat you good!
No, you drive
like a geezer--
What, a geezer?
Tell me, can a geezer
do donuts?
You've never done a donut
in your life, dad.
Never in your life!
Let's bet on that!
So you have done donuts?
- Never, never.
- I mean it--
What's more, if you behave,
if you show me
just a modicum of
respect,
I'll teach
you.
Okay, I take your word for it!
- I really do.
- Fine, then.
You've got a deal.
No, you know what?
I take that back.
- No, not that.
- No!
- No, no.
- No, come on... No.
- No, it's a deal.
- No, it's not.
We didn't sign anything,
we didn't shake on it--
- Yes, we did shake it.
- Hey, no cheating!
- You did now!
- That doesn't count!
Don't be a cheater, no--
No, it's a deal, dad.
No...
Walter...
Donuts.
Yes!
Um, I figured
out a way
to justify buying the cars.
No problem.
Mine, we'll call it
a birthday present
to myself.
Anyone can
understand that,
right?
And Junior's,
well...
His dad's too giving,
too soft,
who spoils him too
much.
What?
Sound
familiar?
So what do
you think?
- Don't be upset about it.
Wait.
Before I forget,
there's something
I want to give you.
Tomorrow we'll get more.
Did you start cooking again?
I had to,
yes.
We have to make up
somehow
what we lost
with that Ernesto issue.
Walter.
What do you think about...
a student exchange
abroad?
You mean for Junior?
There are great offers
for Canada.
Why's
that?
Junior
can manage with the language.
It's a
bilingual
school.
And the next year
he'd be off to
college.
I don't know,
Cielo.
What if he studies
abroad?
We'd miss out
on a whole year with him.
Right, but this exchange
is not only
about the language.
It's also about the culture.
If he goes to French Canada,
he could learn French.
Why are you considering this?
No, I don't know...
I just Just thinking
about the kids.
So have you thought
where we could send
Valentina?
A place for
eight-month-olds?
I don't know,
maybe a Norway school,
or something
like that?
I don't know, I just--
I'm thinking maybe--
I don't know.
Some other environment.
I just think they could be
better.
They could be better
in another
environment.
Cielo...
Cielo, I mean
it.
What's wrong
with this
environment?
No.
Nothing.
I know these last few
days
have been rough.
What happened to
Ernesto,
the threat to Henry.
But that's all
over,
and there's
nothing
to be afraid
of anymore.
From here on
out,
everything will be
easier.
I promise.
You know what I'd like?
I want us to try
and start looking forward
to things again.
I don't know,
plans.
Speaking of
which...
what have you
planned
for my birthday?
Okay, just
kidding.
With everything
that's been going on
lately,
I'd understand
if you haven't
even given it a
thought.
But we should.
You know? We
should...
I don't know,
celebrate.
I think it might be good
for all of us.
It would really
cheer us up.
Let's have a
birthday party.
What do you
say?
Alright.
I could
dare...
ask for
chocolate
cake.
How about
it?
Aha.
That's
it.
Life is good,
Cielo.
We have to enjoy
it.
Good night.
It's daddy's birthday.
Look at this little flower.
- Happy birthday, dad!
- Aw, thanks!
That's tasty!
- Hey, mom.
Why didn't you do the
number
with dad's bacon
like you do every
year?
Don't worry, I'll do it.
But mom's always
done that.
You know? He's right.
Well, it is sort of a tradition.
Look, Valentina.
Watch what mom does with that.
Look.
It's five and one.
No, but that one
is too small.
Yes, that's true.
Hey!
- No!
- What do you mean "hey"?
Hey, young man. Easy now.
This is very good.
That's so you learn
how it's done in this house.
Making sacrifices.
Thanks.
Look.
Man, this is unbelievable!
This guy Gustavo Cortés,
six feet under
and half a face,
and he's still screwing with us.
No!
So, what's next?
Well, let's see
what we've got.
Take this, for example.
Manolo...
in Spain.
He kills himself.
Right.
And who's on the other side?
Gustavo Cortés.
You know what I need?
Someone here, in the middle.
Someone who connected
or introduced them.
I think we're not
seeing
the whole picture.
But what about someone else?
In Madrigal, maybe,
or what?
There!
What about that woman
we visited, what's-her-name?
The nervous one, with a ring.
The one who...
Who talked all "".
- Lidia?
- Lidia!
Lidia Barrera,
yes, sir!
- What do you think?
- No.
- What?
- No, not her.
She's too psycho.
Too uptight in bed, surely.
- No, what--?
- Uptight--?
Don't you underestimate
chicks like that, man.
Those women are usually
nymphos or sadomasochistic.
I mean this, man,
seriously!
She's the master
of being together.
Her?
How together can she be?
She was wearing
mismatched shoes.
Didn't you
see?
You call that
being together, Gómez?
Man--
- Gentlemen.
What's up, boss?
No, no,
don't get up, please.
How is the Cortés case?
We're on it, boss.
Working through the grief.
How soon
before you submit a final?
Well, we've been kicking around
a few ideas.
I wanted
to comment on something.
This Gustavo Cortés
case.
At first,, I
thought
this was just a mop-up job.
And then you changed your mind?
Yes, because now,
now that we've been questioning
all of Cortés' people,
no one is talking to us.
Nobody saw anything,
nobody knows anyone.
You know?
So we find that really
weird.
You know why?
If it had been
an enemy of Cortés
the one who killed him,
somebody
would have told out on
him.
So what, then?
Well, me and Gómez here think
it's likely
there's somebody out there
putting pressure on them,
forbidding them to talk,
keeping them in
line, right?
Here's what we think, sir.
It could be
Mario Arboleda.
The thing is he's a tough one
to get passed...
He knows how to move,
how to protect himself.
- He works on strategy.
- Aha.
We've got three men on him
as we speak,
watching on him 24/7.
And one more thing, boss.
Look.
About the Gustavo Cortés case.
This may have nothing
to do with it,
but there seems to be
a comeback
of blue meth on the streets.
Tell him, Gómez.
It showed up in Bogota, sir,
and in other nearby cities.
It's the same one
as last time.
We took it to the lab,
and it's the same one.
It could be old inventory
leaking out.
We don't
know that
yet.
Or it could be
somebody's rebooting
using former cooks
of Gustavo Cortés'
team.
I thought we had the cooks
in the burned bodies
found in the fire
over at the lab.
I even dared to believe
maybe one of them
was Heisenberg.
Well, everything's
possible.
There's still
a lot of questions.
- Gómez.
- Sir?
Could you give us a moment?
Excuse me.
Henry.
I've got to say your work here
has been excellent.
Thank you, sir.
But we've been thinking
it's time you made a change.
I'm working on my retirement,
and I think you'd be perfect
for the promotion
in this department.
I'm not sure what
to say.
No, no words to--
It's a very big step up,
Henry.
You'd have to supervise
every case that comes from here.
And you'd also
need to reassign
all your own cases.
Gustavo Cortés included.
I know, Henry.
We'd be losing
a good field man,
but we could also gain
much strategy at the office.
So what do you say?
Well, considering my
wife,
if I said "no"
to this offer,
she would
murder me,
yes, I accept, boss.
The job's yours, Henry.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, dad.
Hey.
Where's your
mom?
In the kitchen.
Hey!
Hey.
So what's the plan?
- Henry and María are coming.
- Aha.
Roasted
chicken,
mashed
potatoes,
and chocolate cake,
as requested.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Trying to download
a pirate game.
Pirate-- okay.
What's up?
Me? Nothing.
Thought you'd be
more jazzed
about the new job.
Baby, I'm so proud of
you.
Really, congratulations.
- María!
- Alright.
Careful.
I'm
sorry.
You can congratulate me later.
No need to crash
into something--
I'm
sorry!
Honey, what's the matter?
María, you're acting weird.
You look upset.
What is it? Tell me.
What's wrong?
I made a
promise to
someone.
I can't tell you.
Okay, you made a promise,
and you can't tell me anything?
To who?
María!
María,who did you make
a promise to?
Walter.
I'll tell you what.
- Give me a clue.
- No.
- Well?
Just one little hint!
And I'll take a guess.
Just one clue!
Only one word!
Okay?
Starting now,
one, two, three.
Alright...
It involves
infidelity.
But I can't tell you
anything else.
But that explains itself!
That's absolutely obvious.
What's absolutely
obvious?
Walter's infidelity.
He had one going on.
Second cell phone.
We've known that
for a while now.
So no worries, it's okay.
You didn't break your promise.
I've wondered about that
for a long time.
You're moving,
and I was way ahead of you
on this one.
Right, because
of your cop training,
you know everything,
right?
Yes.
And...
instinct.
Well, you should check
your instincts
because it
wasn't Walter.
Nooo.
María...
You don't say! Really?
Cielo?
Nooo!
Well, will you look at her.
- Henry.
- No, but--
- How did you find out?
- You don't know about this!
- Fine.
- It's a secret!
You didn't hear a
word!
What did I hear?
Nothing.
Nothing over here.
So with who?
Henry!
- Hey.
- Hey!
Hey, Cielo!
[María
laughing]
What's up,
sister?
Where's the
birthday boy?
Walter!
How's everything? Okay?
Great!
Hey, you never made
chicken like this here.
Henry.
- No, really.
You have no idea
how powerful that car is.
My dad's a master.
- He is.
When the highway's
empty,
you get out of town
with a blink of an
eye
- and bruuuummm!
- Really?
And with a blink of an eye
you get you license
taken away.
Uncle, but you'll
help me.
- Aren't you the boss?
- Sure I'll help you!
For my spoiled brat
car wash millionaire nephew?
Sure I'll help you.
Help you with what?
I'll make sure you get a cell
with a huge view.
They call it Buba.
Uncle.
Well, I'm out
of here.
- Congratulations, dad.
- Thanks.
Congratulations
for the promotion,
uncle.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Have a nice evening.
Drive safely, okay?
I will.
Slow down. No,
I mean it.
Slow down with the crutches.
Hey, hey,
Don't say that to
your uncle.
No, he's gotten
out of control.
Want some
more?
No. But really,
some cars!
- Did you see them?
- Both of them!
- Really?
- Truly fantastic cars!
Honey, take note!
For my next birthday
I want a private jet
and a Jacuzzi!
No, no,
no riding that!
To get those legs on fire!
Well, maybe I over did
it
a little with the cars.
The thing is,
with these new lease
rates,
they're too hard to
refuse.
You should think about it.
Right?
[laughing
]
Delicious dinner.
Those were some bad-ass
whipped potatoes.
That's mom's recipe.
You sure make it
awesome.
Or do you have a secret
for this?
- No?
- No.
No.
Well, Walter,
congratulations, buddy!
- 51 years old!
- Cheers!
Thanks.
That's a whole lot more
than half a century.
- What are you--
- Much more than that!
That's old!
It's been almost a
year
since I got diagnosed
with cancer.
- My God!
- That's intense.
- Come on, that long?
- Incredible.
I can't believe it.
Tomorrow it'll be a
year.
It was a day
after turning
50.
I was told I had cancer.
It was awful.
What a year--!
- No.
- A horrible year!
But it wasn't just cancer,
it was also surgery,
you being
attacked.
- Imagine that!
- Truly awful days!
- Wow.
- No, man.
But there were also
fun moments.
Remember about
the pillow?
That.
- What was it called?
- The pillow session.
- The Talking Pillow!
No! That was
useful!
I didn't want treatment.
I was...
so afraid and so
angry
about what I was
going through.
And all I wanted
was to just give up,
call it quits
and forget about the whole
thing.
But you were
always there,
there was
always
someone.
Every time
I was about to lose it
someone or
something
helped me,
gave me strength,
pushed me through.
That's why were here, man.
- Yes.
- Thanks.
- No, man.
- And Cielo.
What a warrior.
Cielo, honey!
Remember that first night
of chemotherapy?
That night was...
maybe one of the
worst ever.
I woke up
on the bathroom floor,
just lying there.
It was so hard at first.
- No, I can imagine.
- But Cielo was always there!
She was always there
looking after me,
giving me support and strength.
And I remember this one night.
I had my head on her legs.
And I felt that night I'd--
Cielo, Cielo,
what are you doing?
That water must be
ice cold
- Cielo!
Cielo, what's
the matter?
- Cielo!
- No.
- Cielo! No!
- What's she doing?
Cielo, get
out of there!
- Baby.
- What's going on?
- Come, come.
- Help me, I'll hold her.
- Get her out!
- I got her.
I got her.
- Let's go inside.
- What's going on?
- Good evening.
- Who are you?
What do you mean who am I?
The guy from around the corner.
Who sent
you?
What do you mean who sent me?
- Who do you think?
- Hey!
I'm asking you a question,
don't answer with another one.
Mario, Mario sent me.
So what's this Mario's
last name?
Listen, lady.
It's late, I haven't slept,
and I still have to
take
that truck.
Can we just make a
move on this?
Arboleda.
Mario's last name is
Happy now?
I'm not going to apologize
for being careful.
The way things are,
I'd better be informed.
You could be
one of those undercover people
they send into high schools.
Besides, I'd rather be careful
than get ganged
by prison guards.
Which one is it?
Three, three, two, five, six.
That's the one
I erased from the inventory.
Can you reach it?
With a forklift, yes.
Wait, wait, wait! Stop!
- What's up?
- Come.
Please tell me
that's not what I think it is.
Has anything like this
ever happened before?
No, no, no,
never.
- Weird, isn't it?
- It is.
I don't know,
maybe it has to do with...
Lately, Cielo and I
have been having...
You know, certain
issues.
Right, I heard.
You did?
No, María told me...
What you're thinking,
that she...
More or less what you just said.
That you have some issues.
It may be good
to talk to someone.
Like a
therapist?
Right, right,
I...
Yes, I suppose
it would be good
to get professional help.
María has this therapist.
She seems really happy with him.
She's satisfied.
Well, not that María
is an advertisement
for advanced mental health.
I just had no idea
Cielo was taking it this hard.
No, I don't get it.
Some birthday present?
Tell me
about it.
She fell asleep,
she had calmed down.
She was?
Thanks.
You're soaking.
Yes, I have to change.
What happened was too weird.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
I have no idea.
Well, but we agree
in that
it might have been an attempt--
Wait, wait,
María, María.
Nobody tries to kill themselves
in a fountain, right?
We were talking with Walter
and said it would be good
that they spoke to someone.
Yes, you should!
You can have
my therapist's number.
- He's so good.
- Sure, thank you.
Maybe it's natural
for something like this
to happen.
There's always issues
within couples.
Long marriages...
It's normal.
But there's always a way
to solve things.
If you're thinking of
therapy,
that's a wonderful
idea.
I mean it.
I don't know if Henry
could guess these problems
- could happen.
- María, María.
He knows that I know.
Walter, I swear,
I swear I didn't tell him!
He guessed.
I don't know how, but he did.
Anyway, the point is,
I think it's a great
idea...
that we could take
the kids for a while
so you can be alone
and you know,
have some alone time
together.
No, wait, you're saying...?
Junior and Valentina
out of the house?
But we're talking
about two, three days,
or the time you
need.
We can take good
care of them.
I know, I know, that's clear.
I just don't see
how that's a solution
for Cielo and I.
Besides, María,
these kids are--
They're a burden,
they're hard to--
No.
No, I mean, take Junior.
He's independent,
does stuff on his own.
And Valentina...
I see Valentina
nearly every day.
I know how to take care of her.
In fact, I think
it's a great plan for
us.
Don't you think
it's a good idea, Henry?
Yes, sure, sure.
María.
Was this your idea?
No.
- No, it was Cielo's.
- I see.
But she basically
begged me, Walter.
Is that so?
I gave Henry and María
a case with Valentina's
clothes.
They'll get milk on the
way
and whatever else they
need.
I spoke to
Junior.
And after discussing a
lot,
he agreed to stay.
And so, voilá,
magically,
the kids are out
of this bad environment.
What a coincidence.
Cielo, look at me!
What was that about?
Can you explain it?
What was all that
situation?
I don't want
the children here
anymore.
- It's not safe.
- Cielo.
How many times
have we talked
about this?
They've never, ever,
ever been as safe
as now!
Never been safer than now?
A couple weeks ago,
we almost got murdered.
You were in the crawlspace,
screaming and laughing.
I told
you!
I dealt with him.
It's over.
No, it's not.
- You're still in the business.
- Yes.
But now I'm running
things!
Now that you're in charge,
everything will be fine
and it's going to be
smooth sailing from here on?
I don't see why
not.
I keep the work at work
and the rest elsewhere.
Nothing will ever impact you
or the kids.
- Nothing!
- You don't know that.
You can't make that promise,
Walter.
Yes, I can
promise that.
Gustavo Cortés
is dead.
And he was the
threat.
He was the danger.
I thought you were the danger.
Didn't you say that?
So that was it.
So all that show downstairs
was about that,
to, trying to protect
my children from me?
- To protect them from me!
- And from me!
There's blood on my hands too!
Blood? What blood?
- Ernesto's?
- Yes, yes!
Ernesto is at the clinic
because of me!
- No!
- Yes!
Because of what I did!
No, Cielo,
no, no.
You can't beat yourself
up
over this thing!
You
can't...
Cielo, you didn't set
out
to hurt anybody!
You made a mistake,
that happens!
Cielo, what you did,
you had to do
to protect
your family.
That doesn't make you
a bad person,
it makes you a human
being.
No, no, no!
Stop, stop it!
I don't need to hear
any of your bullshit rationales!
Stop it!
Alright, I'm in this business.
I'm compromised.
I will not have my children
living in a house
where dealing drugs
and money laundering
and killing people
is commonplace!
No!
And all that is shrugged off
as "it happens"?
- Cielo, Cielo.
- No, no, no!
You know what?
We're back at cooking meth?
Fine.
But the kids stay away.
- And that's that!
- That's that?
That's what?
They're no longer here.
They're gone,
that's the important thing.
So you think
that's the solution?
A sleepover
at their aunt and
uncle's?
Junior's
happy!
Nobody tells him
he has to go to bed
early!
And then what?
- Then we'll see!
- No!
No, I'll tell you
what will happen!
My kids come home.
To their parents
who love them.
They come back home,
where they belong!
No, I will not let
our business endanger them!
Cielo, how many times
do I have to say--?
I said no!
I swear to God,
I won't have them back here!
What are you going to do
to stop it?
- Whatever it takes.
- No.
Like what?
I mean, specifically.
What is your next move?
My next move
is maybe I hurt myself.
Make it clear
to Henry and María
that we need more time,
that we're still
struggling.
No, more like
you're still struggling!
And that could be
the perfect excuse
for me to send you
to a medical institution
if something like that
ever happens.
And I take care
of the kids myself
because
you're mentally disabled.
Is that what you want?
Well, I can change
my mind.
I show up with a
black eye
say that you
beat me
when you found out
about Ernesto!
Just great!
So you want
to involve the lover now?
Ernesto and the police!
That's just fun!
But not as much fun as telling
your 16-year-old son
that his father
is a wife-beater!
No!
You know what?
I don't like your idea.
What else have you got?
I could send him
away to school.
Really?
With what explanation?
How would you tell him?
"I know you've only got
one year left in high school,
but I would love it so much
if you would drop everything,
leave all your friends
and your father behind,
who was about to die,
and your baby sister
so I can send you
to rot in Canada!
Fantastic!
No, Cielo!
That's not a good plan either!
Give me more!
Because I'm not hearing
a solution to your problem.
Nothing!
How are you going
to save our kids
from this terrible environment?
How?
- Tell me!
- I don't know!
Will you take them away
to another country?
What country? Argentina?
Japan?
Or maybe you can change
the locks again.
Can't you be serious?
You want to take me on?
You want to take away
my children?
What's the plan?
I don't know! I
don't know!
This is the best
I could come up with.
I will count every minute
that the kids are away
from here
as a victory.
But you're right.
It's a bad plan.
It's a terrible
plan!
So what do I do?
I don't have any of
your magic!
I'm a coward,
a fucking coward.
I can't even...
I can't call the police.
I can't stop...
laundering your filthy money.
I can't keep you
out of this house.
I can't even keep
you
out of my bed.
All I can do is wait.
That's the only good option.
Hold on...
and wait.
Wait for what?
For the cancer to come
back.
Hello?
Yes, alright.
Yes...
Calm down. Hey, calm down.
I'm on my way.
It's a tracker, isn't it?
Listen, if Anti-Narcotics
is tracking those barrels,
we're screwed.
Where will we get
another supplier?
You know all the methylamine
coming into this country
is controlled
or tracked in some way.
Why did they put
the tracker outside,
and not inside
where nobody would see
it?
Look, it's inside,
it gets wet and damaged.
They made these things
not to get wet and work.
What about the other
barrels?
I don't know.
That was the only one I saw
because Lidia showed it to me.
Once she spotted it,
she freaked out.
I put the barrel back
and we got
the hell out of there.
She found the barrel
and pointed at it?
Yes, she showed it to me.
She out the GPS
on the barrel...
so we thought
it was the cops
and leave her
alone.
You really think so?
We've got to get
another supplier
and put a halt in the meantime.
But that lady's dead.
I gave her a pass.
That's what I get
for being a gentleman.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mario, wait a minute.
Calm down, okay?
Just for a second.
How can you be so sure
that was her?
What if we're wrong?
We just kill her,
and that's that?
So?
Won't you say something, man?
Weigh in here, would you?
What do you think?
The methylamine keeps flowing,
no matter what.
We're just getting started.
We are not ramping down
for anything.