Thanks.
Hi. How much do I
owe you then?
Cigarettes plus food,
that's 40,000.
- 40,000?
- Aha.
Right.
Darn it, I'm out of cash.
I spent it
in gas for the truck.
Can I give you my card?
Look, only cash here.
Only cash.
Do you know
where there might be an ATM?
There's one in town,
but it's like a half
hour
from here.
Like a half hour.
Can I go there
and come back and pay?
I swear I will.
I believe you,
but if the owner came
and checked the
register,
I'd be the one in
trouble.
Right. No, don't you worry,
you're so nice.
So do you like Fucking People?
- Who?
- The English band.
The Fakin Popol!
Sure, they're the best
ever.
They're cool aren't they?
Those guys sure make
good music.
Dirty bitch, dirty bitch,
dirty bitch...!
Yes, they're the
best ever.
I'd do anything
to get a hold
of what that man gets
to make that music.
Because it's not pot.
I smoke a lot, but...
The Fokin guys
have something else.
Really?
So you smoke pot?
No, what those guys do
is meth.
No, we don't
have that here.
What if I told you there is?
Could I pay you with that?
But isn't that
like dangerous,
addictive, like basuco?
This?
No, no way.
There's no comparing this
to basuco.
No, basuco is nasty,
basuco's for poor people.
Look, this has little crystals.
Pure glamour.
This is the stuff
the rich people in Bogota
are doing.
So do you smoke
or inhale that?
Anyway you want.
So how does it
feel?
How does it feel?
It's kinda hard
to explain with words.
It's like...
Like all your senses
are sharp,
and all of a sudden,
everything's more interesting,
everything makes sense,
you know?
Like the music
by Fokin.
Hello, child.
Two coffees, please.
Just a moment, please.
So what do you say?
Well, thank you for your
purchase, and come again.
Okay, thanks.
Hi.
How do you feel?
I can't move,
I can't breathe.
- It itches.
- Loosen it up.
There!
- Better?
- Much better, obviously.
Right, right.
You know when you'll start
to feel bad,
really bad,
you won't be able to breathe
and your neck will itch?
When you don't get compensation.
So from now on,
do me a favor
and fasten this tight.
Nice and tight
as much as you can and hold it
until the day of the trial.
You're not taking it off
in public, is that clear?
Right, now,
if you know of anyone else
that has suffered
some light or strong
psychological or physical trauma
because of the plane accident,
send them over to me.
I'll see you at court,
alright?
Fine, doctor.
- See you later, excuse me.
- Go ahead.
There, that's the spirit!
Is there a problem?
You slept
with Ernesto Silva?
With that clown?
So that's how you call
the people
not in the underworld?
You seem to be an expert
in calling people names,
aren't you?
You called me a "charlatan",
didn't you?
- No, I never said that.
- But you implied it.
You dared me
to tell the police
because you thought
I'd never do it.
And you know what,
Walter?
Yes, you were right.
You win!
I'm a charlatan,
but not in everything.
There are things
that I do dare say and do,
like sleeping with Ernesto.
And you know what?
I liked it, I loved it!
You can't imagine
how much I enjoyed it!
Why are you doing this?
This is very simple,
Walter:
If you want to live in
this house, it's fine,
I'd have to put up with it.
But know and understand
we're not a marriage anymore.
Cielo, I'm not
cooking meth anymore,
I promised you that.
Why should I care?
After everything
I've done to this family?
If you don't like it,
you can leave.
And take your filthy money.
Everyone's happy.
What was that?
She's blending the soup
for the baby.
Well, first things
first, right?
You want to kick me out
like a dog,
but I won't let you!
Sleep with Ernesto,
sleep with the production guy,
sleep with the Human Resources
guy, for all I care.
The Human Resources person
is a woman.
Well, sleep with her too
if you want!
I still won't be leaving!
Great, so be it!
Is that good or bad?
There's more.
"So be it?"
That's how it ends, then?
No, we'll see how it ends
for that moron
when I go after him.
Ernesto should sure as hell
watch his back!
It' bad.
- How much is it?
- Seven.
Thanks.
- Hello.
- Good afternoon, sir.
How can I help you?
My name is Walter Blanco,
and I came to speak
to Mr. Silva.
Mr. Silva
is very busy at this time.
He's unavailable now,
he's in a meeting.
No problem, I'll
wait.
Sir, I'm sorry
but he's in a meeting
and it'll be a while.
Miss, I have all the time
in the world,
don't you worry.
Dr. Silva,
Mr. Walter Blanco
is at the reception desk.
What should I do?
Fine, sir, alright.
Ernesto. There he is,
there he is, don't worry.
- Ernesto, Ernesto!
- Sir, what are you doing?
You cannot go in there, sir!
Open up, Ernesto,
I can see you!
I know you're there,
don't you hide!
Ernesto,
don't be such a paranoid!
I just need to talk to you.
Open the door!
I need us to talk
in a civil manner!
Walter, it's just that
I can't talk right now
because I'm busy,
in the middle of--
Yes, exactly!
You're in the middle
of something,
and that's precisely
what I'm here to talk about.
Open the door!
Ernesto, open the door!
You're not going to open it?
Perfect,
because I have a plan B.
Because you asked for it.
Walter, Walter, calm down.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to
Ernesto.
Please, calm down.
What are you doing?
- Move over, move over!
- Hey, hey!
Hey, Walter, my God,
what are you doing?
Wait, Walter!
And next time I tell you
to open the door,
I suggest you open it!
Walter, Walter!
What is this?
I just wanted to talk to him!
Whatever happened
to dialogue?
Let me go, let me go, let me go!
I just wanted to talk to him!
nothing happened, relax.
Relax.
Just let me go.
I'm calm, alright?
What's going on?
What's the matter
with you, Walter?
That's not a reasonable
man's attitude.
By God, man, look.
I found my second wife
with her personal trainer
doing the 69 on my bed.
Jesus Christ!
The world is tough, you have
to get used to it.
I just wanted to talk to him.
Well, I'm the one who
needs to speak to you.
I need you to pay attention
and grow up, please.
Let's take what I'm
about to tell you
as a simple
legal counseling.
What if the police
would have got there
and caught you?
I mean, considering
your job
and how you get money,
your living,
what do you think
must be done?
I'm going to help you.
You have to behave
and keep the police away,
feet away!
Now, let's look
at the bright side.
Because you have to
be optimistic.
This is a good time
for you to focus
all that energy
that's coming from within
into something
truly positive...
Like cooking.
- How did you know?
- What?
How did you know
I had a problem with my wife?
where to find me?
Look, let's please
not change the subject
and talk about what's really
important here.
Did you wire up my house?
Are you tapping
my phone calls?
You're intercepting
what I say!
No, no, wait.
You must consider
that right now
that's not your home.
You had left, and besides,
you asked me to.
Me?
I asked you to do that?
Basically.
You implied
you were afraid
about what your wife
would tell the police.
No, that's not true,
Saúl!
Look, let's not get
into this,
about who said this
or who said that.
Why does it matter
now?
This is not a boyfriend
and girlfriend argument here.
What's really
important here?
That your wife
didn't say anything.
What?
She remained silent
and didn't say anything.
This is a tough game
where you win or you lose.
Right now the business
is safe, and that's it.
Why does it matter
that your wife's enjoying
the hardware store
guy--?
What are you saying,
you piece of shit?
What's wrong
with you?
What is this?
You're fired, Saúl!
You're no longer my lawyer!
And I'm not cooking
meth again!
Do whatever you want,
you baby!
You won't be getting
any more donations
in Junior's account!
- Listen to me!
- No more laundering!
You're going to take
all those wires out of my house!
- No more money laundering!
- Shit!
What's with this
freak?
What do we do?
Let's do what
this idiot says.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're leaving it like this?
The walls
are covered in holes.
A couple of repairs
and it'll be brand new.
Check that not even one
is left in there.
Just two observations.
This little devices
are imported
and cost 2,000 dollars each.
What you say is
not interesting at all,
so there won't be one
left.
Aren't you tired of doing
all the dirty work?
Everyone does
what they know,
and I like my job.
What?
You want a hug
and kiss goodbye?
You know what, Walter?
Sometimes it's good
to have someone
watch our back.
What do you mean by that?
You should stop
looking at yourself
and start paying attention
to your surroundings.
Goodbye.
Walter...?
Walter?
Walter, are you
alright?
Hey, Carmen.
Can we talk in
my office?
Sure, of course.
Take a short break.
Let me be clear on this.
I don't approve
of this trip, Henry.
Well, darling,
what can I do about it?
This is a great chance,
a great second chance
I've been given.
Mexico is like a Ph.D.
for those of us
who work in Anti-narcotics.
Right, so what?
What if something like
the other day happens,
when a head got blown off?
It seems over there
it's like that every day
basically.
You want to see
heads been blown off?
Just turn on the news.
Or is it that Colombia
is Switzerland now?
No, Henry, I don't want...
I don't want you to leave,
I'm scared.
I think it's too dangerous
out there.
Listen, honey,
I'm a cop.
I follow orders.
No.
Hang on.
My boss.
Sir...
Blue?
Are you sure
you found on that guy
blue crystal meth?
No, no, no,
first things first.
I'm on my way sir. Bye.
What
happened?
Remember the drug
I'm trying to track?
- Yes.
- It's back.
So is that good or bad
news?
For you, it's very good.
- I'll call you later.
- ¡Henry!
Trust me, in this school
we understand
what you're going through,
Walter.
In fact, we imagine
you must have had
many sacrifices to make.
But you know
we have a responsibility
with the students.
What's your dog's name?
Martín.
It's a French Bulldog,
isn't it?
No, it's a Boston Terrier.
- Really?
- Yes.
Unbelievable
They're so
alike...
The ears, the...
They're just identical!
Yes, yes, Walter.
Can you please sit
so that we can continue
our conversation, please?
Yes, of course.
He's a beauty.
Congratulations.
Walter, I'm honestly
really concerned about you.
Ever since you
came back to work
I've noticed you're
far away, distracted.
I think you've had
behavioral problems, Walter.
Are you feeling okay?
I don't know.
Maybe we could call Cielo?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry,
you have something here...
Thanks.
Can I tell you a secret?
Of course.
Walter, what is it?
Miss, I need a cab
for Walter Blanco.
Los Monarcas School.
Do you have the address?
Yes, that's it.
No, I'll wait for it
at the parking lot.
Yes, thanks.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
I'm sorry
to have just showed up here,
but I needed to speak to you.
I went yo the residence
and didn't find you, so...
No, I told you
that was temporary.
- I'm back home.
So what's with the box?
Did they fire you?
No, it's a license...
for indefinite time.
So yes, I've been fired.
How are things?
Are you sure you don't
want to go
some place else to talk?
No, it's fine here.
Okay.
Okay, here's the deal.
I'd like you to introduce
me to the guy.
What guy?
That guy Saúl introduced
you to, the distributor.
No.
No, Jose, please.
Listen, listen, I've been
thinking about it,
and I want to come back.
Cooking meth is the only thing
I can do right.
No, don't say that!
You know how to do
tons of stuff!
Like what?
Well, think about your problem,
about your addiction.
No, teacher, I'm clean.
Really, I mean, this
is the healthiest
I've been in my
entire life.
All I want is to get back
into business, that's all.
Not me, I'm sorry.
No, no, no, I know.
I know and it's great,
I mean it.
I'm not asking you
to cook with me, you
know.
What's this?
Well, it turns out
I had to use
two reflux
condensers
because I didn't want to lose
the pH value, right?
But the rest, the
whole process,
I did it exactly
how you told me to.
I was super careful
with the amounts,
super precise
with the timings at each step.
How about
it?
It's okay, isn't it?
- It's nice.
- What is this?
What do you mean?
- Well...
- This is my formula!
Mine, this is my product.
No, sir.
This is out product.
What do you
mean?
Relax.
I'll give you your share,
don't worry about it.
You're going to give me
my share?
Yes.
I got you into this!
What's gotten into you,
man?
All I'm asking for
is some information.
Well, no, no, no,
definitely not.
- Not a chance.
- Why not?
- Yes, why not?
Do you think
that I'll put my name
on a low-quality product?
Look at the diameter
of those crystals.
You obviously
messed up the shortening.
What did you use?
Platinum dioxide, right?
- No, no, no, no.
- Yes.
I used a mercury-aluminum
amalgam.
You know dioxide
is very hard to keep wet.
Then you messed up
in some other step.
I mean,
look how cloudy that is.
They're absolutely cloudy.
What was it,
the reduction?
Now, this is very shoddy work,
Mr. Rosas.
I'm embarrassed for you!
Well, it's not, actually.
I gave out lots of samples
and everyone said
it was the bomb,
I mean, the best stuff
ever.
And who were they, I wonder?
A bunch of meth heads?
They should know,
right?
They are the ones
who take it.
- I can't help you.
- Fine, ass-wad.
I'll contact the guy
myself.
My guy is a pro and he
doesn't deal with junkies,
Mr. Rosas.
- Eat me.
- Anytime, loser.
Hey, hey!
We all need coffee today.
This day is perfect
for napping, isn't it?
It's dragging.
I wish I could stay.
And not have to go anywhere
right now.
So why don't you stay?
What's stopping
you?
What, like everything, you mean?
How about
my lunatic husband
refusing to leave the house?
So move in here.
And then my son
hating me even more.
I went through that with
the girls.
They adapt.
It's not that big
a deal.
And now everyone at work
thinks I'm an evil
ladder-climbing whore.
They're all fired,
effective immediately.
What more do you
need?
Aren't you the answer man?
But I also have
questions.
Where did it go wrong,
exactly?
I mean, with you
and Walter.
I always saw him as kind
of mild-mannered.
Something changed
when he got sick?
I don't know what changed.
And I just don't feel really
comfortable talking about it.
Sorry. Just asking
out of self-interest.
Gotta make sure
I don't make the same
mistake.
No,
I would be amazed.
I'm off.
Bye.
Just let me see
if I'm following you.
Suncho, you're saying
you gave this stuff
to a guy wearing shorts
and that had a moustache.
Am I right?
-Am I right?
- Suncho.
- Yes.
That's your brain
working at maximum capacity,
or can you help us
with something else?
Let's see, come on.
- Suncho.
Hello!
No.
- Pirateque!
- What?
I remembered,
his last name was Pirateque.
So what's Pirateque's name?
The name, we want the name.
Come on.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on, pal, make an effort.
Come on, come on.
Pirateque?
- Pirateque.
- No...
No.
I think it was Piraquive.
Piraquive.
So what's Piraquive's name?
- Come on.
- I'm not sure right now.
But I can sure as hell
tell you this.
- What?
- His last name
started with a P.
Because I remember
the sound was like...
P, P, P...
Okay, okay, hey,
hey, hey, easy now.
You'll damage
everything in there.
Okay.
It's starting to smell like
something's burning here.
- Right.
- Come here.
Díaz.
Take my friend here.
Come over.
Remind me to get a vasectomy.
Nice and easy.
It's because of guys like these
that contraceptives
were made, brother.
You know what we should do now,
Gómez?
Let's go to the bar
where they found this Suncho.
- What for?
- What do you mean what for?
To see if we can find a lead
to Heisenberg.
It was only a matter of time
before this guy booted up again.
So who predicted that?
I did!
No, wait, wait.
Heisenberg
is in jail, brother.
He could be an imitator.
maybe there's someone
they're doing something else,
he left,
but he's locked up,
Henry.
Understand this, Fredyliso
is not Heisenberg, brother.
They made us believe it
and we absolutely fell
for it, trust me.
Heisenberg
is out there cooking!
Okay, I buy it.
There you go, I buy it.
How do you know
he's gearing up again?
How do I know?
Because I know.
- Don't fool me.
- Yes, sir.
Do you know
why you're sure, brother?
Because you're blowing off
the trip to Mexico, aren't you?
That's why you're looking
for crazy guys and hippies.
You can trust me,
tell me.
Okay, you know what?
I'm getting tired
of all the
second-guessing.
If you're not that
stimulated by this case,
do us both a favor
and do something for me.
Ask for a transfer.
What is up with you lately?
What do you mean?
What is up with you lately,
brother?
Looking for crazy guys, hippies,
starting bar fights.
- What's up with you?
- So what'll it be?
Okay, fine, I'm sorry.
You know what's the thing?
I'm just worried about you,
brother.
- Really?
- Really.
Really worried?
Appreciate that, brother.
Now take your hand
off my shoulder.
Search,
search thoroughly.
It doesn't have to be the wing
or the turbine of the plane.
It could be anything
that fell off the plane,
anything about the accident
is good enough.
Any little thing at all.
It could be a nut or a bolt.
If you find any little thing,
we already have a case.
We'll be in touch, okay?
Goodbye.
No, no, no,
don't coming
bugging me now.
I've had enough emotions
lately.
I understood
when you stopped
cooking,
didn't I?
I told you
to get him cooking again
before he went crazy.
I wanted to show you
his potential.
And what do I get in
return?
My best tie gets
ruined--
Well, hello,
hello.
How in the hell did you get
Walter to do it?
I made it.
I need you to call the guy
who knows the guy, alright?
Well, good news is
for a stage-three cancer,
Walter's doing well physically.
I'm think of making
an investment for the future,
but for that, I
need to know
if he'll live
long enough.
Yes, at least a couple of years,
God willing,
and if he doesn't get a visit
by a few Mexicans
with an axe.
The lawyer also told me
José Miguel
is looking for a buyer.
I don't work with
junkies.
That's what I thought you'd say.
What I hear,
he and Walter are splitsville.
I see.
According to Saúl,
cats and dogs.
Do the deal with
Rosas then.
Agent Navarro,
this is Formation and Logistics
of the National Police.
We you need to be
calling us back
to confirm your trip to Mexico.
We haven't received
an answer from you,
nor have you sent us
your papers.
Please, contact us
as soon as possible. Thank you.
- Hey.
I'm looking for Dayana.
I'm Dayana.
Dayana,
my name is Henry Navarro,
I'm an agent
in the National Police
Anti-Narcotic Department.
I'm here because a friend
of yours gave me this
and told me
you'd given it to her.
So I need you to tell me
who gave this to you,
and I hope you talk,
unless you want me to speak
with Mr. Manuel, your father.
- Shall we speak to Mr. Manuel?
- No, no, no.
- Mr. Manuel!
No, no, no, please,
please,
don't tell anything
to my dad, okay?
I've had enough trouble
already.
I gave it to Laura
because I didn't like it.
- I tried it and didn't like it.
- Who gave it to you?
- A guy.
- What guy?
A guy that came
and had nothing
to pay with.
What was his name?
- I don't know.
- What did he look like?
- He was...
- Tall, short, cute,
black hair, from the coast?
- He was cute.
- Cute.
Any particular features,
piercing, tattoos,
black fingernails?
He didn't know or
pronounced
"Fokin Popol" weird.
Okay. What other features?
- We was on a bus.
- What do you mean a bus?
What color was it?
How was this bus,
big or small?
I don't know,
I don't know about
bus makes.
Please don't tell my dad, okay?
Work with
me.
I don't know,
that might not be possible.
Does that camera work?
No, it's broken
and hasn't been fixed.
No wonder
stores are being robbed.
But there's a camera that
works
outside, in the gas station.
- What? Where, where?
- At the gas station.
On the corner over
the vault.
The vault?
Damn, you bastard.
Mom, the eggs are delicious.
Thanks.
Isn't it weird
that it's been three days
and nobody made a donation
to my dad's web site?
That's how people are.
They suddenly lose interest.
Dad, when...?
When will you come back
to school?
I don't know?
What's more,
I shouldn't have gone back
to work too soon.
I probably pushed it.
Well, now that
you'll be at home,
you should take care
of Valentina
so my mom
doesn't have to take her
to the office.
Right, mom?
We'll see.
It's getting late.
I'll go brush my teeth.
What's up?
Your half share.
What do you mean?
my half share?
This isn't about halves!
How can you give me
half?
What the hell?
We won't work with
halves, man!
All we need to know
is if you're still willing
to go to Mexico.
Me?
Of course, you!
I'm always there.
It's just that now
we just got a lead
on the Heisenberg case,
you know?
Henry, please.
Heisenberg?
Yes, and I know
you think like everyone else,
that we already got Heisenberg,
but this drug
was just found,
which proves us that he's
still out there cooking.
The blue meth, you mean?
But that was a tenth.
Okay, I know, but look,
that tenth got things rolling.
And we got to this lead.
Look, look at this.
These buses.
Remember when we
decided that in order to cook
these people
needed mobile labs?
Look what these people use.
Take a look here,
only this part.
Do you see the suspension
on this one?
See that it's much higher?
Why is that?
This thing
has been cleared out
and stripped down
to its tight-and-curlies.
For what? Blood bank?
Maybe a bookmobile?
And if we add in
that the driver
is using the meth
to pay minor debts,
we conclude that this is what?
A mobile lab.
But you can't see
the plates.
No, no, no,
but thanks to these pictures
we could find out
the make of the bus.
We were at Traffic
doing some research
and tracked down all the buses
there are in this make.
- Know how many there are?
- How many?
-29 in Bogota.
- Only 29?
So I gotta go, you know,
knock on some doors.
But that's my job,
isn't it?
Henry,
they need you in Mexico.
You bet. I'm just gonna
wrap up this thing first.
Henry,
are you telling me
you're refusing the
assignment?
No, no, all I ask
is for a little more time
so that I can close this case.
Wait.
You're not hearing me,
Navarro,
you're not listening to me.
It's a simple yes or no.
Are you going
or not?
I need your answer today.
No, boss, I can't.
You know why I can't, boss?
Because here, in Bogota,
I'm about to find something
really big.
Trust me, boss.
Low selling prices,
hard business conditions,
getting into the imported
milk market
from the United States
and boarder trafficking
have cattle breeders
and milk producers
in the North of the country
on the verge of leaving
their trade definitely.
In other news,
our top story this hour.
Air-traffic controller
Diego Maldonado,
accused for his role in
the recent air disaster
in which two aircrafts collided
over the Capital sky
was found wounded.
According
to the psychiatric report
on the inmate's
physical and mental state,
the engineer was suffering
from a deep depression
after his daughter's death
from an overdose,
Juana Maldonado.
It was advised that he be taken
to a nursing facility.
However, this incident
took local authorities
who were on the process
by surprise.
The details
have not been provided yet,
but he has been reportedly
transferred to a hospital
with no vital signs.
The accident victim's families
have made themselves heard.
There's your half.