More.
Careful, sir.
Hot day like today,
too much oil in the machine
can cause it to blow a gasket.
Look, man.
There are two kinds of men
in this world.
Those who drink
and those who pour.
Shut up and fill my
glass.
Hey, you two.
I used to be just like you.
Worked dirt for the man
till my hands bled.
But no more.
Do you know why?
Because I learned
that a man can never
drink his fill
by waiting in line
for the tap.
That's
it!
Listen to him.
He can teach you
something!
Boss.
Good to see you,
my friend.
And to hear that great
speech of yours.
You know, I never pegged you
for such a deep thinker.
Such a philosopher,
right, Tortuguita?
I keep thinking
I should write a book.
I just need to learn
how to write.
So, what brings you
to this burro's ass hole
of a town?
You'll see.
Can we talk,
or do you have
something to deliver?
Lots of time.
Tortuga has his pace.
Tortuga may be slow
out of the gate,
but he always finishes
first.
I like the way you
talk, Tortuga.
You've got
such a way with words.
They just pour
out of your mouth.
They flow like a
waterfall.
But that's a talent,
isn't it?
- You think so?
- He!
Cheers to that!
Did you think I'd
forgotten
- about your birthday?
- My birthday?
Of course not, man.
So bad I came all the way
here
to this burro's ass
hole
to give you your
present.
Present?
No need to go
through the trouble.
Forget it,
I wanted to.
I have it for
you in the back.
- Back there?
- Yes.
Come.
Follow me. Come.
look, look, look.
Is that my present?
Yes, do you
like it?
A pet.
You won't be able
to take this one
to the park and throw
a ball for it.
It has the same pace
as you.
The pace of the turtle,
which is the best.
This is a very
special animal.
Why is that?
Imagine that its little
head
doesn't fit in its
shell.
- It doesn't?
- No, look.
Look at it.
Boss!
No, let me go!
Let go, let me go!
Boss!
Boss, no, let me...!
It's alive and kicking.
By the looks of him, he has
no idea how close he came.
I'm assuming
Saul doesn't need to know.
Mum's the word.
It never happened.
Son of a bitch!
Hi, Cielo, how are you?
Walter,
What are you doing
in the house?
I'm back.
No, no, you're not
back,
get out of here!
Cielo.
Just come on inside
and we'll talk this through, ok?
No!
I am not coming
in there
until you get out.
Look, this is also my house.
I have every right to be here.
But Walter,
we had an agreement.
an agreement I didn't accept.
you made on your own,
It takes two people
to make an agreement, Cielo.
But come,
why don't you come
in?
Let's talk here
quietly.
No!
No, there's nothing
to talk about!
What I need is that you
get out of my sight now!
That's really what you
want?
Yes.
Walter, Walter!
What's the matter with you?
What are you doing here?
I have every right to be
here.
No, this is not your house
anymore.
You don't live here anymore.
We're getting a divorce.
I don't want a
divorce.
Well, that's not up to you!
Cielo, this is all pretty
unfair, and you know it.
Look, Walter, if you don't get
out of here right now
I'll have to make
dramatic decisions.
You kicked me out of
the house,
you're asking me
for a divorce,
and now you're talking about
dramatic decisions?
I'm warning you!
It could be worse for you.
Anything that's worse for
me is worse for both of us.
Please, be reasonable!
No, I'm calling the police,
and I'm telling them
absolutely everything.
There's the phone.
It's ringing, they'll answer.
Bogota Emergency Line,
how can I help you?
Yes, I'd like to report a...
a domestic issue.
I'll put you through
to the Domestic Department.
They're connecting me.
Right hand to God,
I will tell them.
Do what you have
to do.
This family is
everything to me.
Without it,
I have nothing to lose.
Good afternoon,
this is Lieutenant
Armando Paredes,
of the Women Protection area.
Tell me what your
current situation is.
Thank you.
This is Cielo Restrepo.
Yes, how can I help you, ma'am?
My soon-to-be ex-husband
broke into my house
and I need an officer
to come and remove him.
The system shows this address:
52 and 50.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, that's the address.
Yes, ma'am,
I will send the agents
right away.
- Okay, thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Hey, dad!
How are you?
- I'm good, and you?
- Good!
Did you make up?
Are you back for good?
Why are you home so soon?
Did you get out earlier?
No, I'm not early, mom.
-How about a grilled cheese?
- Sure!
Okay, you want one too?
No.
Go, go, Junior,
we'll catch you later.
Your dad and I have something
we need to discuss.
Mom, can't it wait?
I haven't seen Dad
in, like, forever.
- Let's go, Dad.
- How is everything, okay?
- Yes, all good.
- Are you sure?
- Are you behaving?
- Yes, yes, Dad.
So are you gonna be
at work tomorrow?
Yeah, that's the
plan.
What's going on?
- Good afternoon, ma'am.
- Hi.
Is this the Blanco residence?
Yes, come
in.
- Thank you.
- To the back, please.
We were called
about a disturbance?
Yes, yes, that was me.
Good afternoon.
You called the cops on Dad?
I came home from work
and he was back.
He had just moved back
into the house.
And I asked him to leave,
but he won't listen.
Well, there's a couple questions
I need to ask you, ma'am.
- Tell me.
- Did he strike you??
No.
Has he ever hit you?
This is not about violence.
This is about trespassing.
I asked him to leave
but he wouldn't, that's it.
Let me get this straight.
You're divorced, then?
- Separated.
- Legally separated?
There's not a court order,
if that's what you mean.
But we've been living apart
for almost two weeks,
each on their own.
I changed the locks.
Sorry, another question.
Whose name is on the title
to the house?
Both of us.
But I need you
to please get him out of here!
Ma'am, we can't arrest a man
just for breaking
into his own house.
Not without a suit
or court order
requiring he stays away.
The baby!
No, calm down,
I'll handle this.
Please, I'm begging you!
Help me get this man
out of here!
Yes, ma'am,
but we need a reason to do that.
Are you sure
he hasn't threatened you
or your children?
No. But having him in the house
is not a good thing.
Trust me.
Officer.
I'm aware that lately
I haven't been
the best father in the world.
But you know, this happens
in every family.
Ma'am,
is there anything
you'd like to tell us privately?
Would you like us
to have a word outside?
No.
No, I'm fine right here.
I'm gonna level with you, ma'am.
If you want him
out of the house,
you'll have to help me.
Something to justify this.
Is it possible maybe he's broken
any laws or committed a crime
that you know of?
Even if it's just a suspicion.
It's my mom's fault!
She won't even talk because
he didn't do anything.
Mom's going crazy, dad!
Hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey!
Junior, no, sir.
Son, it's not your mom's fault.
No.
I don't know what to say.
Well, that being the case,
there's no legal basis
for us to remove your
husband from the house.
So if you'll excuse us,
we have other cases
to attend to.
- Reyes.
- Thanks for coming.
At your service.
Let's go.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Please, I'm sorry.
No problem.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Dad!
Ma'am, excuse me.
If you still wish to provide
me any information,
please call me.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
Mom, I hate you!
You're the worst ever!
Why did you call the police?
Why you gotta do this to Dad?
Junior, come on now.
Don't blame your mother
for this.
I'm so sorry.
Welcome
home.
Come in.
Hey!
You're alive!
Thank you, Lord!
Happy housewarming.
Here is okay?
Interesting decor
in the house.
It's really subtle.
Minimalist, I think
that's what they call it.
Minimalist.
It's the latest trend
in New York and Paris.
So?
How are you doing?
"Talk to Saúl", he he!
So are you still
in all that
"Say No To Drugs,
Say Yes To Life" thing?
- Yes.
- That's real good
because you were missing
in action
and didn't answer
my calls,
so I got
worried.
I thought you'd gone
back to...
You know,
dope.
And that's not good.
You know why?
Why what?
What's not good?
Do heroine.
It's like logical, isn't it?
Of course not.
I don't mean that.
I can tell you're still
not too good.
You realize how
stupid it is
is to ignore the
phone calls
from your counselor,
that's me?
What if I was trying to
warn you
that the police was gonna
kick down your door?
What then?
Why don't you spare me
the sermon?
Sermon?
Sermon, me?
When?
Remember when I
brought up the idea
of you getting back in
touch with your partner?
No, no, no,
wait, easy, easy!
Just calm down.
I'm not suggesting
you to get back to cooking.
Of course not.
I mean, you being in rehab
and all.
I only want you
to convince the master chef
to get back to cooking,
to do his thing.
What's that sigh for?
Alright, whatever.
Ok, you
know what?
I need to be alone,
so please...
Yes, yes, yes, sure thing.
Just one more thing, one more.
Don't give me that face.
Look around.
You invested a lot of money in
buying this house,
and it's empty.
You can't live like this.
Look,
if you get Walter
cooking again,
I swear...
I'll help you improve
that Minimalism big time.
I'll make it worth your while.
I'm going, I'm going.
Hi, it's Juana.
I'm not able to answer you
or don't feel like it.
Leave me a message
and I'll see if I can
or will answer.
Bye.
Boss.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes,
yes.
No, no,
you can imagine, boss.
Yes, sure.
No, really
happy.
No, no, no.
When have I ever failed
you, boss?
Count me in.
Yes, I appreciate it.
Okay, boss.
See you.
Ha ha!
So you gonna keep me
in suspense or what?
- About what?
- You're not telling?
About what?
I'm being sent to
Mexico again, brother.
- No way!
- Aha!
Nice, brother!
The damn bastard is
going back to Mexico!
To drink tequila, dude!
That's fantastic, brother.
Congratulations!
Great, just great.
Salamancas.
Mr. Héctor.
Welcome, gentlemen.
- Gustavo.
- It's a pleasure.
How was your trip?
Any problems?
No, no, no.
The day I have a problem
to get into Colombia
is the day I retire.
Perfect.
Well, welcome.
Please, come in.
First of all,
we owe you an apology, Gustavo.
We should have informed you
we were performing
a few actions
here in Bogota.
It's just that
we had no idea
that you were working
with this man...
Heinsenberg,
or whatever.
Is that with an I?
It's with an E and an I.
Gentlemen, let's try
to focus on this again.
- There is another matter.
- Let me fill you in.
Mr. Héctor
had a nephew,
Tuco, Tuco Salamanca.
Yes, I know who he was.
He had his area and sold
what little meth you sent him.
We never had a problem.
The thing is that Mr. Héctor
loved him like a son.
When Mr. Héctor
had to come to Colombia because,
well, because that's how it was
decided up there,
he brought him.
And when he was paralyzed,
Tuco took care of him
and took his place.
We could say that Tuco
was our trusty man here.
I thought
I was your trusty man here.
Sure you were,
of course you were.
But I mean at a smaller scale,
a symbolic one.
It's a thing between Mexicans.
It's logical.
The thing is that
I don't know how or why,
this Mr. Heinsenberg,
or Walter Blanco,
became Tuco's supplier
and he betrayed him.
Now we all know what happens
in cases like that, don't we?
Blood must be repaid by blood.
I mean,
we're talking about
personal reasons.
It's about feelings,
not business.
It's the same thing
sometimes, Gustavo.
Oscar Luis and Luis Oscar
are Tuco's cousins,
and they want
exact vengeance.
They have the right, don't they?
At least in that,
everyone up there agrees:
the Salamanca family
and the Tapatío Cartel.
Mr. Héctor, gentlemen,
I feel your loss deeply.
Please accept my condolences.
But I must say
I am presently
engaged in big business
with this man
Walter Blanco
and his death
would be inconvenient to me.
We have all
gone through similar situations,
and we know we must
choose the mind
over the heart.
But we need an option from you.
We won't take no for an answer.
All I can tell you right now
is that this situation
must not change
until our business
with Mr. Blanco is done.
For now, I need him alive.
Gentlemen,
excuse us for a second.
Look, Gustavo...
I don't tell you how
to cook your chickens,
whether fried or roasted,
so you should leave matters
of my organization to me.
We're talking about an
exclusively financial situation,
of running a territory
you consider mine.
I've never worked
for anyone else in Mexico.
I'm unconditional
to the Tapatío Cartel.
Yes, yes,
Gustavo.
Your loyalty is not being
questioned here, understand?
But I recommend you
finish your business
with the man quickly.
Or you risk losing the
good graces of the cartel.
My financial interests
are the same as the cartel's.
The things is, Gustavo,
these kinds of things,
we handle them differently
in Mexico.
Family is family?
And being things
as they are,
I can't guarantee
anything
with the boys up
there.
They are not like you
and I, Gustavo.
Hi, it's Juana.
I'm not able to answer
you
or don't feel like it.
Leave me a message
and I'll see if I can
or will answer.
Bye.
Hi, it's Juana.
I'm not able to answer
you or don't feel like it.
Leave me a message
and I'll see if I can
or will answer.
Hi, it's Juana.
I'm not able to answer
you or don't feel like it.
Leave me a message
and I'll see if I can
or will answer. Bye.
Coming, my love, coming.
I'm sorry, honey.
Yes, mommy's here,
mommy's here.
Cielo, want some
help?
It's occupied.
Use the one downstairs.
What do you mean
he did it
against your will?
Was there physical retention
or verbal mistreatment?
No, no, no, no,
not at all, no.
Then what?
Cielo,
I need you
to gather your thoughts,
please.
I told him not to come back,
and he showed right up.
And doesn't want a
divorce.
I had to call the police
and was about to--
About to what?
No, nothing.
Cielo,
I can't advise you properly
if you don't give me
all the facts.
Um?
Understand, I'm bound
by the attorney-client privilege
to keep everything
you tell me confidential.
Everything you tell me
is in absolute secrecy.
I can't tell a soul
unless you authorize me to.
- Even if it's illegal?
- Especially if it's illegal.
I'm your lawyer, not the police.
My job is to protect you.
What I'm about to tell
you
might not sound
nice.
That is part of the job, Cielo.
Walter makes meth.
What?
Methamphetamine
s.
It's a widely used drug in
Mexico and the United States,
and now it's in Colombia.
It's new,
but it's getting
very strong.
Your husband's a drug dealer?
A manufacturer,
technically.
He says he has nothing to do
with the selling business.
They call them cooks.
I looked it up
on the Internet.
This is my advice,
and you should take it.
File for divorce immediately
and sue your husband
to the police.
This is more than enough
because with this
he will get a restraining order
and won't be able to come
near you nor the kids.
No, no, no,
I can't do that.
Do you think
he might put in danger
- you life, something like that?
-No, no, absolutely not, no.
Because if you do,
what we can do...
Well, we can fill out papers
to exchange information
for protection,
and we can also do this
with the Anti-Narcotic area.
No, no, no, I...
I don't want my
son to find out
that his father
is a criminal.
I just...
I can't do that to him.
He will find out
some other way.
Drug dealers have a way
of getting caught.
Maybe not the best way,
but this country
has plenty of cases like this.
Walter has lung cancer.
His treatment
bought him some
time,
but the doctors...
What I mean is...
I can't see why
I should lay all
this on my family
when things...
may resolve themselves
on their own
without anyone else
knowing.
Right?
Gentlemen, your order.
Did you ask for all this?
Do you want to kill me with
so much cholesterol or what?
The heart blows up with that
for sure, no!
Come on, eat and stop
fussing, man.
Can I get you anything else?
No, honey,
not for now, thank you.
Okay, excuse me then.
Very nice.
Let me ask you.
When a woman tells you
"anything else",
will she give you
something else or not?
- Should I call her?
No, no, no, no.
If I eat that
I won't be able
to sleep tonight.
Come on, relax,
grandpa.
When are you going to Mexico?
In two seeks.
Two weeks?
Hey!
Congratulations, brother!
Straight to action,
just how you like it, man!
Cheers!
I have to take a leak.
Those two guys over there...
are double-crossing.
Come on.
Stop being paranoid, man.
Trust me.
They were double-crossing.
What are you doing?
Calling the police in this
area, see what happens.
Hey, since when
can't we both
handle a couple of guys?
It's called
protocol, sir.
A good education,
you might say.
Let's suppose so.
So what if
they're doing an undercover
operation here?
And we're in
the middle of it?
What then?
You know what? Forget it.
Let's just leave.
I invited, you pay.
Thanks for waiting.
I have to take a leak.
You could use a diaper instead.
What have you got there?
- Stop bothering!
- Bothering?
Hey! What's going on
there?
Let him go, let him
go!
Hey, show some respect
in my business!
Police!
Hi, it's Juana.
I'm not able to answer you
or don't feel like it.
Leave me a message
and I'll see if I can
or will answer. Bye.
Hi, it's Juana.
I'm not able to answer you--
The number you are calling
is not available at the time.
Please, try again later.
There, honey,
we're going, we're going.
Just a second.
Yes, yes, yes, honey,
there, there.
Yes, we're leaving.
We're leaving, sweetheart.
Come.
What, what, what?
Let's go, darling.
Come.
Yes, yes, yes.
Cielo.
Internal Affairs
is waiting for you.
This is the deal.
We were hanging back,
saw a deal go down.
I went outside to call it in
because there was no signal
outside.
That's when they attacked you.
What I didn't say...
is that you left your gun
under the seat
before you went back inside.
I've done a terrible thing.
But I did it for a good reason.
I did it for our family.
Cielo...
That is college tuition
for Junior and Valentina.
That is health insurance
for you and the kids.
For Junior's physical therapy.
It's money
for house maintenance,
the basic stuff,
groceries and gas,
that kind of thing.
But I want you
to know especially
that there's enough money
for the mortgage.
When I'm gone, your salary
will not be enough for that.
- Walter--
- No, no, no, let me finish.
Cielo, I didn't steal
that money.
That money
doesn't belong to anyone.
I earned it
doing what I know.
Maybe it's the only thing...
I've achieved
with excellence in my life.
You know?
You picked the wrong
talent.
You'll hurt so many
people.
I know.
That's a burden I have to bear.
But that doesn't matter.
None of that makes sense.
All the sacrifices that I have
made would be for nothing
if you don't accept
this money.
Don't tell me anything now.
Think about it.
Think about it good,
and tell me
after you come back from work.
Didn't you have lunch?
No.
Some coffee?
No, this one's
enough, thanks.
Yes.
Alright.
- Well, Cielo, I, I...
-No.
Will there be anyone
at home?
- No.
- Your kids?
- No?
Hi!
Hi, Cielo, how are you?
Good evening.
Hi.
- Hey, Lucho, all good?
- Good.
Hey, honey.
Cielo?
Hi!
How are you?
Can you come with me
to the kitchen for a second?
I'm making a feast here.
Listen, I hope you don't mind
I invited Lucho
over for dinner.
You know, as a thank-you
for driving Junior
to school.
Aha.
Cielo,
I just wanna say that...
I feel good about our talk
this morning.
I'm very thankful
for you giving me a chance
to explain all this.
I'm very eager to hear
what you think.
No, no, no, no,
whenever you're ready,
of course.
On the contrary.
I think what I mean to say...
is that I'm thankful
that you let me be honest.
I think we should always,
be honest.
always tell the truth,
no matter what.
I slept with Ernesto.
Guys, dinner is ready.