Enjoy!
Is everything all right?
- Yes.
- What's that?
It's a number.
52.
It's the years
I'm turning today.
Is it your birthday?
Congratulations!
Thank you.
We offer discounts
for people on their birthday.
No, thanks.
It's a small discount.
I need your I.D.?
What do you say?
Okay.
You were born in Cartagena.
Are you from the coastal region?
I didn't think you were.
Appearances can be deceptive.
- Do you want more coffee?
- Yes, thank you.
I'll be right back.
Thank you
Green like I like it.
Long live uncle Sam!
I forgot to ask you
for a guide.
It's a shame.
But I'm very intelligent.
I downloaded something
from the Internet.
It's with the toy.
Good.
Take it.
Do you know
what?
Good luck.
Mr Ricardo,
happy birthday.
Thank you.
- Hi.
- How are you doing?
How am I doing?
No, how are you doing?
I'm fine.
I'm very well.
Have you seen the news?
Gustavo Cortés was killed.
He was blown up
with someone
from a Mexican cartel.
Anti-narcotics agents
don't know what to think.
- Walter, I need to know it.
- It's over.
We're safe.
Was it you?
I won!
Let's see, my friends.
You'll eat well.
Eat, eat, eat!
Yes, yes. I'll tell him.
- Is something wrong?
- Yes.
What is it?
Gustavo was killed.
- Dad, are you here?
- Yes. Hi!
- Where are you?
- Here, in the living room.
Hi!
What are you doing, boy?
Dad, did you see the news?
Er, no, no, no.
I was...
Mom, did you tell him
about Mr. Gustavo?
He knows it.
Hi.
Welcome.
Everybody is talking about it.
- Really?
- Did you see something?
No, no.
No. Listen. What matters
is that Henry is fine.
Nobody knows about it,
but uncle Henry
- says it's a drug dealer.
- Really?
It's crazy!
How does he know
he's a drug dealer?
Uncle Henry
was investigating him.
He didn't say it,
but he had his eye on him.
I had lunch with him
in Chicken Brothers and Co.
- Really?
- Henry's friends think
that Mr. Gustavo
was going to kill him.
But somebody got to him first.
It's terrible, isn't it?
Reality is terrible.
- Aunt María--
- It's so sad.
- Aunt María was scared.
- Wait.
Can I help you¡
Listen.
She was very scared.
She didn't want us
to leave the house.
But mom said it was time to go,
and it wasn't too dangerous.
Yes, er.
Sure, I see.
Okay.
There were a lot of cops there.
But everything is quieter now.
I'm glad.
I'm really glad.
I'm happy to have you back.
Look, dad.
I think when truth comes out,
- my uncle will be very famous.
- Of course!
Much more famous than now.
He's a super cop.
Exactly! Yes.
Why don't we watch the news
to find out what's going on?
Sure. Go ahead.
Turn the TV on.
I'll be right there.
Okay?
I'll say hi to the baby.
Sure.
Hello again.
Hello.
My baby is sleeping.
Hello, pretty girl.
Hey.
I deserve a special greeting
from my family that's back,
don't I?
"Hello."
That's it?
Won't you talk to me?
Cielo...
Aren't you going
to show some kind of... relief?
Some kind of happiness
that I'm alive?
I'm relieved you're alive.
But I'm scared.
Scared of what?
Of you.
Shit!
What happened?
Say it.
- I said it already.
- No, say it.
Say it quietly:
"Gómez, you're an idiot."
Say it.
- Gómez, you're an idiot!
- That's it! That's it!
Let everybody know it.
Say it. Say it.
"It was Gustavo Cortés."
I told you so, didn't I?
This looks like
Guido Bermúdez's drawings.
Look. The structure,
the beams.
Everything!
The stairs are here, too.
Are you sure?
Where did they find the bodies?
Over here. Look.
Do we still don't know anything?
Who were they?
Nothing.
According to the coroner,
at these temperatures,
you don't get even the teeth.
Who ever did this
knew what he was doing.
Look at that.
- What?
- Over there. What's that?
Son of a bitch.
Do you know what that is?
That's a camera.
Yes, sir.
Take some pictures.
Be careful with the computer.
There're treasures there.
No, no.
Don't put that face.
I'm not talking
about those treasures.
It isn't pornography.
Show me what you have there.
It's over, son of a bitch!
You're done!
- Calm down!
- Get out of my way, José.
Listen to him, please!
I'm tired of listening
to this asshole.
Mario, listen to him! Please!
Why? You don't have any idea
what this means.
Of course we know.
It means your life
isn't in danger anymore.
It means
nobody will kidnap you
- to make you work as slave.
- Shut up!
Mario... my friend.
If you kill him,
you'll have to kill me, too
What do you have to do with him?
Mario, can I talk?
Whatever differences
you and I had in the past
they won't change.
But right now,
we have to move on.
We've got bigger fish to fry.
- What are you talking about?
- The video cameras.
The video cameras from the lab.
The ones they used to control us
all the time, do you remember?
Those cameras
not only filmed Jose and me.
You were there, too!
We're all screwed up
with those cameras.
Listen to me.
Those video are in a file.
We have to get them
before the police does.
Walter, you're the worst thing
I've met in this life.
No, listen to me, Mario.
Those files
have to be in a hard drive.
Where did Gustavo keep them?
In his laptop.
He had it
at the office.
- At Chicken and Brothers Co.
- So?
Let's go there now.
No, there's nothing
we can do there.
I understand.
Okay, thank you
for the information.
I owe you one. Bye.
- What? What happened?
- We're screwed.
I'd say it was my pleasure
to meet you, but I'd be lying.
Mario.
Won't you say anything
about the laptop?
Mario, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
I'm disappearing,
and you should do the same.
- We're running out of time.
- Mario.
Please, tell me
where the laptop is.
Does it matter?
They have it.
- End of story.
- No! Tell me where it is.
Don't even say
that you're considering it.
It's at the office
of the district attorney.
It was labeled and filed.
It's in an evidence room.
Do you know the place?
Can you describe it?
How's the room they have it?
Describe it?
It's a place full of cops.
Don't you think it's enough?
What are you thinking of?
Will you come down from the roof
with a black mask?
What am I doing here
talking with you?
I'm leaving!
Mario, wait.
We have to do something.
I'm doing it.
I'm running away.
No. He's good
in these situations. Seriously.
Give him a chance.
Look, Jose, in this case,
it's the same if the laptop
is in Mars.
Evidence rooms
are like bank vaults.
Do you know why?
To keep men like him away.
But different from banks,
those evidence rooms
are watched by policemen
24 hours a day.
There's no way of entering
and taking the laptop.
Who said we have to take it?
We have to destroy
the information contained in it.
So, you want to blow up
- a place full of cops.
- No, no, no.
Aren't you happy
after putting a bomb
at the old people's home?
Those old men
will have nightmares
until their last days.
No, we won't kill anybody.
I'm just thinking
of introducing a device.
- A device.
- Yes, a small device.
We put it there as evidence.
- Once inside the room...
- What about a magnet?
You want to commit another crime
to introduce a bomb
in the evidence room?
No, I didn't say a bomb.
I said device.
- What about a magnet?
- The idea...
The idea... I don't know.
I may design a device
capable of causing
a small fire.
Don't you think
they're ready for that?
They have a team
to deal with those situations.
Not only to suppress the fire,
but also
to avoid evidence destruction.
Okay.
We'll put a bomb outside.
You'll just ruin
the front of the building.
- Don't be a jerk!
- What about a magnet?
What can you do with a magnet?
I was thinking of those magnets
that make... and boom!
All the information
is destroyed, isn't it?
Giant magnet?
Yes, like those
you find in movies.
Those used to load vehicles
in places like this.
I know they appear on movies,
but they aren't used here.
We're screwed.
I can get you one.
Haven't you say
they aren't used here?
They aren't used
doesn't mean they don't exist.
In this corrupt country,
you can get anything.
Specially if it has to do
with scrap from the gringos.
How long will it take you
to get one?
It depends on the money
you're willing to pay.
- Hello.
- Lock the door.
What did we say?
You shouldn't come back here.
Yes, yes.
About things
that'll make you angry, Cielito.
I'm here to tell you
that police may contact you.
What?
Let me explain so that you know
what I'm talking about.
No, no. Why would the police
contact me?
They won't contact you.
They may contact you.
There's a possibility.
It's remote, but real.
I need you to be ready.
Ready for what?
What happened?
First thing you have to do
is nothing.
I mean.
"I see nothing.
I hear nothing.
I know nothing.
I speak nothing."
If you do so,
I'll be very proud.
Saúl, tell me what happened.
Well, there's been
a small incident
with your ex boss, Mr. Silva.
Ernesto?
We can't say
things have been done wrong.
It was fortuitous
I mean...
How can I say it?
I've never thought
something like this may happen.
Is he dead?
Dead? Ernesto? No.
No, no, no. For God's sake!
Just the opposite,
he just woke up.
Woke up?
Cielito.
With an activated load,
it's capable of attracting
- even a big car.
- Okay.
Do you think
what we want to do is possible?
With science progress,
everything is possible.
- The only bad thing--
- Yes, you said it.
It's expensive.
Very expensive!
Okay.
Where're we putting it?
I suggest this truck.
It has a motor
to take it everywhere.
What is the container made of?
It's aluminum and wood veering.
And the most important thing
is it doesn't have a plate.
Therefore, it's impossible
to track the owner.
Do you want to talk
about concrete numbers?
Let's go to the office,
and do the numbers.
Yes, just one second.
Jose.
I need a favor.
I don't have cash.
My wife had problems
with the tax division.
I have no money.
Can you pay for me,
and I'll pay you back?
- Yes, of course.
- Let's go.
Shall we go, Mario?
If I were you,
I'd take your money,
and leave.
That easy. Right now.
Don't you think
it's going to work?
Are you asking seriously?
Of course, Mario.
This is a job
for three people.
If you don't help us,
it's obvious it won't work.
If you do,
I think we'll succeed.
I'm confident.
Be confident.
This will work out.
Go!
- Ready.
- Okay.
Watches, rings and chains off.
- Hey!
- No, it isn't worth it.
They are non-ferrous.
- Okay.
- It's the same.
And you?
What about that stuff
that young men wear
on the end of their dicks?
If you have it,
take it off now.
Otherwise,
it'll be destroyed.
I don't have one of those.
Why would anybody
wear something like that?
What are you looking at me for?
I don't know!
Stop it!
Leave all kind of weapons, too.
- Guns, knives, machetes.
- In the car.
If you have plates in your body
as a result of an operation,
or artificial hips.
- Is it in the car, too?
- Go on.
Who will have the honor
of turning this on?
Me.
- Okay.
- Where do I stand with this?
Five meters away.
Five or six meters away.
We'll see.
I'll explain it.
You turn it on.
If you need more intensity,
you turn it
- this way.
- Perfect.
Ready?
Ready!
Is something going on?
No, not at all.
Approach slowly.
- There?
- No.
No. There, there, there!
It's working!
Is being erased.
It's gone!
Yes!
Great!
How many batteries
does it have?
21 wired in series.
They're about 250 volts,
approximately.
I need 21 more
wired in parallel. Okay?
It's expensive,
but I can do it.
- It's okay. Let's do it.
- Okay.
Everything goes flying
in that evidence room.
It's going to make
one hell of a noise.
There goes
your element of surprise!
It won't matter.
In a minute,
we're out of there.
I love magnets!
Wonderful, Professor!
Hello, how are you?
I'm fine, thanks.
Intensive care?
Straight ahead,
and to the right.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Hello.
I'm a friend of Ernesto Silva.
I wanted to visit him.
If it isn't a good time,
I can come back later.
- Don't worry. I'm done.
- Okay.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
If you need me,
I'm down the corridor.
Thank you.
Hello.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Ernesto... I...
- I...
- Cielo, I won't say a word.
I told everybody
it was an accident.
I slipped and fell down.
I have a family.
I have two girls.
I won't open my mouth.
I won't say a word,
I promise.
Don't do anything to me.
I understand it now.
Okay.
They're robbing!
Here, here.
Call the Central Station.
Do it!
They're robbing.
Unplugged the monitor.
Is this distance good?
Yes, yes. It'll work.
Don't worry.
Let's do it.
Seventy five.
What's this?
CARTRIDGES
VOLTAGE REGULATOR
Can you do it fast?
They'll catch us.
Easy, easy.
We have to do it slowly.
One hundred.
One hundred and ten.
It's enough!
Let's go!
No, no, no!
It isn't enough. Calm down.
Two hundred.
- It's the limit.
- Just a little bit more.
Turn this shit off!
Turn it off!
I'm trying!
- Turn it off!
- I'm trying!
Out, out!
No, it was like
getting drunk
and ride a roller coaster.
Shut up!
Mario, what's up?
It worked.
No, it didn't work perfectly.
Where's the truck?
It isn't a problem, Mario.
You've heard the scrap merchant.
The truck isn't traceable.
And neither is the magnet.
Here we are.
Your man
escaped in a motorcycle.
- What if they find prints?
- There're no prints.
Do I have to believe you?
- Take that on faith?
- Yes.
Why?
Because I say so.
07-66 432,
Vallejo, Felipe.
Hammer, undamaged.
In a bag.
32-257,
Cortés, Gustavo.
Personal laptop.
The screen is damaged.
And it's broken
in different parts.
Damaged.
In bag.
09-32 256,
Cortés, Gustavo.
Photo frame
with picture of two men.
The glass is broken.
The picture has moved.
The bag is broken
because of the glass.
This isn't in the inventory.
37010412
0004267821
First of all,
I'm not a marriage counselor.
Second,
and I'm not taking sides,
It was you
who put her in charge
of your money,
which I advised against,
if you'll recall.
I don't want it to be construed
as "I told you so."
But that's how it is.
I told you so.
Let's go to they point.
She came to me
because she had a big problem.
She's been manipulating
Ernesto Silva's accountings,
and soon there'd be
an audit
from the Revenue Office,
she thought
she might be caught, too.
It's a long chain of mistakes.
What did I do?
"Talk to Walter."
"No."
She wrote a check
to pay her debt.
In my opinion,
she was protecting you.
I'd love if you add something
to the conversation.
Just a little bit.
My mouth is dry.
Did you tell her:
"Speak to Walter?"
Yes, I told her.
"No."
And it didn't come to your mind
contradicting her?
I mean, didn't you think
of calling Walter
and telling him
what was going on?
I remind you
that you were very busy
trying to save your life
or solving one of those problems
you get involved into.
Then you took responsibility
on that matter,
and let her give money
to the man
she was sleeping with.
Walter, she's my client,
just like you,
it's a family group.
There're some confusion times.
But I can assure
that I did everything possible
from an ethical and professional
point of view.
Ethical?
I'm sorry.
Have you mentioned
the word "ethical" here?
Stop talking nonsense, Saúl!
You're my lawyer,
and you work for me!
Yes, but I never had clients
that make such requests
as difficult as yours.
Speaking of which...
What do you think of this?
Your mini-atomic bomb of poison.
I put my ass on the line
for you.
We could have been all dead!
Did I complain?
No. Why?
Because I'm a lawyer
who works happy
to satisfy his clients requests.
It would have been nice
if you told me that the kid,
the son of José's girlfriend
was going to end up in hospital.
Now that I think of it,
it was bad.
It was disgusting
and it's far away
from what I can bear.
So, please,
get your chemical weapon,
and take it away from here
because this partnership
is over.
This partnership ends
when I say so.
Hello.
I heard about Ernesto.
He wont' say a word.
He won't speak. I swear.
He won't say a word.
Good.
I forgive you.