Hello, Mariano.
It's Walter.
I need you to get Cielo
on the line.
Tell her it's urgent.
I don't care, get her!
What do you mean
she won't get off the phone?
I'm telling you it's urgent!
Get her now!
Mariano, I am giving you
permission.
Tell her to hang up.
Interrupt her!
What do you mean
she's locked up?
Mariano,who is she
on the phone with?
No, no, forget it.
It doesn't matter.
Aaah!
Yes.
Yes, Henry.
I understand.
Have a brilliant day, sir.
Mariano, where is Cielo?
She just left.
- Where did she go?
- She didn't say it.
Do you want something to drink?
- Coffee?
- Coffee.
Coffee, please.
My head is spinning.
Spinning real bad.
And yours...
I can't even imagine.
So much makes sense to me now.
You jumping in the pool,
you sending us your kids,
I just wished
I'd seen it sooner.
The only thing I don get
is how I didn't see it.
He's a monster.
Walter is sick.
Really sick!
I don't know what he did to you
to force you
to keep his secrets.
If he threatened you,
I don't know if there was
psychological or physical abuse.
I have no idea.
But what I want you to know
right now
is that you can be open with me.
Don't hold anything back.
Okay?
I don't even understand if you
know the full extent of this,
what he's done.
I don't know--
Not just the meth cooking.
No!
But the lives he's destroyed.
All the violence, the killing.
But that's all behind you.
That's behind you, Cielo.
Okay?
Yes?
From now on,
you're done being
Walter Blanco's victim.
Not anymore.
Because here's
what we're going to do.
Okay?
You and the kids
are going to move back
to our house
where you'll be safe,
you'll be protected.
Walter can't get you there.
María...
Does María know?
No, no, no.
This is between you and me.
- Aaah!
- Okay?
Before we get you back
to the house,
I'm going to ask you to tell me
everything you can.
Okay?
Well...
Take as long as you like.
I have no rush, okay?
Good.
Henry...
Okay.
Just start from the beginning.
Tell me everything.
How it happened,
when you first became aware
of Walter's activities,
when you knew,
all of his contacts, everything.
Just try to be
as detailed as you can.
Okay?
- Come on.
- How?
- Here?
- Yes.
Now?
Why not?
The sooner it--
Come on.
Think about it, remember.
State your name and the date
before you start.
Do we...?
Do we have to do this right now?
No.
No, we don't have to do this
right now.
We don't.
But here's the thing.
I need something solid
that I can bring to my people.
I have all these little pieces.
If I go with that,
nobody's going to believe me.
Because that's my point of view.
That's what I believe.
So...
You testifying
to Walter's criminal activity,
can help me a lot.
Cielo, this is a big case,
and gathering all this evidence,
enough to get a conviction,
we're talking a long-haul
proposition here,
and I don't want
that bastard
running out the clock
before being punished
by justice.
What do you mean
running out the clock?
- What are you talking about?
- His cancer.
His cancer is back,
he told me so.
What?
He didn't tell you?
Who's to say it's even true?
Lying piece of shit.
Let's believe him, okay?
Let's believe him.
You have to help me
anyway, Cielo.
That son of a bitch looks me in
the eye and says:
"If what you think
about me is true,
I'm going to be dead
before you can prove it".
What do you think?
Cielo, you have to understand
that you are a really
important piece
in this case.
Without you, I can do nothing.
I'm sure that if the judge
hears all you know
about this case,
he will get Walter
in jail in that very moment.
And we could avoid
he keeps doing what he wants.
Do you understand me?
Cielo!
Maybe I need a lawyer.
No, no, no.
You don't.
- Maybe I do.
- No, Cielo, no.
I am here to help you.
But to do that,
I need your help.
We start bringing in lawyers and
they start putting up
roadblocks
where they don't need to be.
I need to have the control
over this situation.
Do you understand me?
Yes, but I need...
I need to defend myself.
I should have
someone to talk to.
You have me. I'm your biggest
advocate here.
I'm taking care of you.
Believe me.
And I'm telling you,
for your own good,
you need to get out
ahead of this thing.
Cielo.
Listen.
If you start getting defensive
and have a lawyer,
people won't know
what side you are in.
The prosecutor
will want to interrogate you.
The important thing here
is that you show
you are cooperating.
If you cooperate,
the prosecutor
will treat you differently.
He will treat you
like a victim
and not like an accomplice.
And there's where
everything goes south.
But you don't know
that for sure.
No, no, but I'm almost sure!
That's the way
prosecutors act.
It's in your best interest
to get out there
and show the world
you have nothing to hide.
Cielo!
Look...
No one in the world
is more important to me
than your sister.
If something happens to you,
she will be affected.
So I'm doing everything I can
to keep you safe,
to keep you out of this.
You telling me
not to talk to a lawyer
doesn't sound like that at all.
On the contrary,
It sounds like what you want
is to get Walter at all costs.
No matter the consequences.
Listen...
Let's slow down.
Relax.
You can talk to a lawyer later,
but not now.
Now, what we need to do,
we need to go get the kids,
we need to bring them
to my house.
María is there.
She will take care of them.
They will be safe.
An we are going
to help each other
to put this animal away.
Okay?
Henry...
- Come on, come on.
- Henry!
- Let's talk in the car.
- Am I under arrest?
What?
- No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No, no, I didn't say that!
You're not thinking straight
about this.
You have to listen--
- Come here.
- No, no, no.
- Am I under arrest?
- No.
What are you talking about?
Are you arresting me?
Am I under arrest?
Brother...
I have to do something.
There is no other way.
What are you doing, Stewart?
Are you going to tell me
that you didn't think about it?
When are we going to have
another opportunity like this
to do it?
We are here to do a job,
not to play.
I know, but this feels good.
Screw it.
I'm just saying one thing
to take it out of my head.
Anybody could think
of escaping with all this money.
I'm just telling one thing
for you to forget about that.
The owner of this money
killed ten guys in jail
in two minutes.
I have already forgotten it.
Good.
Listen, kid, you have to hide
those bags.
The monkey is in the banana
patch, understand?
Please, call me
when you get this.
Aaah!
This was the third message.
Where the hell is that kid?
- That's Cielo.
- Don't answer.
- We need to talk.
- No, no!
You answer that phone
and Henry Navarro
is on the other end of the line
with a legal wire tap
recording everything you say.
You're not doing
anybody any favors.
In fact, why do you still have
a battery in that thing?
Take it out.
They might be trying
to triangulate your movements.
Take it out!
I'm not being paranoid.
I'm sure she talked to Henry!
She just panicked.
She went right to him
without even talking to me.
Without a moment's hesitation.
Now you have to relax.
I'm not saying it's not bad,
but it could be worse.
How much worse could it be,
Saúl?
You mean like a fire rain?
Something like that?
I'm just seeing the facts.
Let's think.
What does she actually know?
What can she tell
your brother-in-law?
It's only hearsay.
The only real evidence
that she can lead them to
is your money.
Once we take care of that,
then they have nothing.
- There is no evidence.
- Nothing?
What do you mean, Saúl?
Henry knows the truth.
That's not nothing!
Okay, that's something.
I don't know what to do!
Have you given any thought
to sending your brother-in-law
on a trip to a Caribbean island?
What does that mean?
You know, where Mario went to,
for instance.
- Henry is family!
- Okay, it's an option.
No, no!
- Family!
- I'm just telling--
You have to understand that!
That's sacred!
I'm just telling you.
No, you are sick!
You don't mention that option.
It's an option
that has worked very well
for you in the recent past.
That's why I mention it.
- No, no!
- Okay, okay!
I take it back.
You respect family.
- I didn't talk.
- Exactly! It's sacred!
I'm just throwing
thoughts out there.
This is a creative meeting.
I'm going to send you
to some island!
No, you don't need to say
this ugly stuff, Walter.
Relax.
Finally.
What took you so long?
Have you two been followed?
If they had, we'd all be
in handcuffs right now.
Let's go.
I took the tops off
in case you wanted
to see it's all there.
Good.
But I don't.
A few bills
won't make a difference.
If you need any help
transporting these,
just tell us.
We could hold the barrels
because they really move.
I'll manage.
Saúl.
Pay them.
Take your cut.
The rest is mine,
in case I need you.
In case you need me?
I'm thinking
the probability is high.
Find José Miguel,
that's important now.
Keys.
Close it.
I need to talk to Saúl.
I'm Cielo,
Walter Blanco's wife.
Francisca, don't tell me that.
I know he's there,
but he doesn't
want to talk to me.
Get him on the phone.
Okay, okay.
Just tell me
if my husband was there.
What do you mean you don't know?
Was he there or not?
Aaah!
Open the door
because I'm not leaving.
I will be here
as long as it takes.
Just you.
Cielo, tell me Henry went
crazy.
Tell me he doesn't know
what he's talking about.
That he's not fine.
Please, please!
You have to give me something
because I can't believe this.
I can't believe it.
This is not true, right?
Is this true?
This can't be true, Cielo!
How long have you known?
Please, tell me.
Tell me!
When you did that in the pool,
that's when you knew.
Was this the reason
you did that?
Tell me, please.
Tell me.
No.
Do you know this
since Gustavo Cortés?
Aaah!
The money.
All that money that he made...
And your whole gambling story.
That was all a lie.
Of course you knew
because you
made up all that story.
God!
Tell me, please,
did you know it
before Henry was shot?
Tell me, please.
I'm asking you!
- I'm sorry, Ma--
- You're sorry?
You're crazy!
You won't talk to Henry
because you think that Walter
is going to get away with this.
Mom.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Don't touch my child!
No, stop!
- You won't take my child.
- She's coming with us.
I'm not leaving her here.
- Let her with me.
- No!
She's coming with us.
- Give her back to me.
- No!
- Henry, help me!
- I'm calling the police!
- Give her back!
- No!
- Give me my child back!
- Let me go!
- Give me my daughter!
What's going on?
María, give her back.
Give me my child right now!
- No, Henry!
- Let her go.
María!
María, now!
It's okay, darling.
It's okay, honey.
It's okay, it's okay.
Everything's fine, darling.
It's okay.
Promise this to me, Henry.
Promise me you're going
to get that son of a bitch!
Promise!
34, 59, 20.
106, 36, 52.
34, 59, 20,
Walter?
Where are--?
What happened to you?
Walter, Walter,
You moved the money, didn't you?
You buried it somewhere.
Did you get my messages?
Walter,
I told Henry nothing.
I swear I didn't.
I didn't say a word to him.
Say something.
Talk to me, say something.
Please.
Talk to me.
Walter, Walter!
How long was I out?
I don't know, hours.
The cancer's back.
Right?
Does that make you happy?
I can't remember
the last time I was happy.
Just tell me.
I know you talked with Henry.
I know you made a deal.
Tell me.
I'll make this easy.
I'll give myself up.
If you promise me one thing.
You keep the money.
Never speak of it.
Never give it up.
I want--
You pass it on to our children.
All of it.
Please, Cielo,
Give them everything.
Please don't let me
have done all this for nothing.
How did Henry find out?
Did somebody talk?
No one talked.
I screwed up.
When I talked to him,
he only had suspicions.
Not much else.
You can't give yourself up
without giving up the money.
It's the way this works.
I think...
we should stay quiet.
We should stay quiet.
Okay, you can take it off now.
So, tell me.
What's so important
you had to come
all the way out here?
For the amount of money
I'm bringing in,
I think I deserve to see exactly
why it's all going so wrong.
Are you an expert
on meth labs now?
Are you going tell us
how to fix our operation?
Are you going to teach us
how to do what we do?
And what if I can help?
What will it hurt to show it?
Nothing.
I don't like
my time being wasted.
Well, I'm here,
and ten minutes
is a small sacrifice
when we're talking
about a 50 million shortfall.
Don't you think so?
So?
Go ahead.
Safe to come down?
Yes.
Ladies first.
Aguirre, wake up!
Okay, now you've seen it.
Yes.
I've seen it.
So what?
You could start cleaning
a little bit.
This place is filthy.
What are you, my mother?
This is not filthy.
The problem
is we don't have
much light down here.
This doesn't have
the quality standards
of your predecessor
Not even close.
I don't care a shit
about my predecessor.
The product we're making here
is selling just fine.
Heisenberg's standards
don't matter anymore.
To whom?
A bunch of scabby
local tweakers?
They matter to my buyer
in the Czech Republic.
Therefore, they matter to me.
- Listen, lady--
- You listen!
I cannot move
what this person is making
if it's substandard.
No offense.
You can do better, do better.
I don't know what to tell you.
I mean, you tried to get
the man back, right?
That Heisenberg.
He said no, so I mean,
what do you want me to do?
Peto.
Use Peto again.
He learned from Heisenberg.
At least Peto's first two cooks
were at 74%.
On his third cook,
he started a fire
we almost go all to hell!
Listen, lady...
I want to cook in my territory,
I want to use guys that I trust,
not Todd, who I don't.
And do you know
why I don't trust him?
Because he's not
one of my people.
And that's the end
of the conversation,
as far as I'm concerned.
- Period.
- It's a shame.
I really wish you'd have given
him a chance.
Boss!
We have a problem!
Mrs.,
You wait for me here.
Heisenberg!
Who is Heisenberg?
I can't believe you.
Open!
Done!
I don't want to see anything.
Maybe you should
close your eyes.
I'll help you.
Slowly.
The other leg.
Okay.
Now I need you to lift
your right leg.
Higher, higher.
That's it.
Relax, everything's fine.
Now to the left.
That's it, walk.
Wait a minute.
That's it.
Don't worry.
Here we have a stone.
Right.
Hold on one moment.
Uncle, what about this one?
Ouch! Look at him.
Tell the lady
to close her eyes real tight.
We are saying it beforehand.
Now you can go on.
- Relax.
- We're good now.
I need you to lift
your right foot a little bit.
Easy, that's it.
Now lift the left leg.
Higher, that's it.
Okay, boys.
Let's get everything
in the lab.
- We pack and we leave.
- You heard him!
Let's see.
Let's get all that stuff
and get out of here!
Could you sleep?
Not much.
And you?
No.
Are you going to work?
No, I don't feel like it.
And you?
You have to tell them, Henry.
Today.
No, María,
I just don't have it yet.
I don't have anything.
I don't have what I need
to prove Walter is Heisenberg.
I have nothing, María.
But...
Why don't you tell Gómez?
Ramón?
They are going to believe you.
Honey, put the whole
anti-narcotics
working on this.
That's how it works.
No, María, no, no, no.
You can't do it alone, Henry.
- You can't.
- María, listen to me.
They have warned me
at the office.
I can't work on this case.
Do you get it?
It's different now.
Show them what you have.
Look, the day I go in with this,
that's the last day
of my career, all right?
Get it, María!
What am I going to do?
I'll walk in there, look them
in the eye and tell them:
"Partners, the person
I've been investigating
for so long,
the drug dealer,
the murderer,
is my own brother-in-law".
María, if I do that,
that's the end for me.
I have nothing left.
Done.
I'll be no more than a civilian
and I we won't be able
to help Cielo.
So...
when I go to the police,
I need go with proofs,
not with suspicions.
I can be the man who caught him.
I'm going to be
the man who caught him.
What if you wait and they catch
Walter without you?
If they find out that you knew
and you said nothing?
Wouldn't you go to jail too?
Hey, boss.
What's up?
- How are you?
- Brother!
So good to see you, bro!
- Yes.
- How are you?
Better, brother, better.
Did you miss me?
I couldn't stop crying.
Really?
Like I miss
my balls.
Do you have balls?
I didn't know it, bro!
- What's new?
- Everything's fine.
I organized your schedule.
You have a budget meeting,
and then you have
a meet and greet
with the guys.
Let's see if we can get
that budget meeting pushed.
Why?
I need to check something.
Boy.
- Easy, brother.
Don't ask, just help me.
Okay.
- Good.
- Thanks.
Welcome.
Thanks, bro.
Did you hear
about that money thing?
What money thing?
Don't you know?
It involves your old pal,
José Miguel Rosas.
Rosas?
Ha ha, you're going to love it.
I'll tell you later.
I'll give you this, Rosas.
You're never boring.
So, bro.
Do you want to say something?
Why were you tossing
millions of dollars
all over the south of Bogotá?
Talk.
I promise you we can hold out
just as long as you can.
That's a fact.
I got a bladder the size
of a hot water bottle.
All that cash?
I wouldn't be able to stop
talking about it.
And I don't think
I'd be tossing it
out my car window.
I barely can take vacations
with my salary.
And I definitely
can't be playing Robin Hood.
But apparently Rosas here
is just raking it in.
Yes.
He's just missing the costume.
Osorio, you know what?
I believe he has a good reason
for doing what he did.
And I'm sure he has a perfectly
reasonable explanation
for where he got it.
He found it.
Yes.
Or won it in a card game, maybe.
Who knows?
That's it!
Lucky night at the casino.
Rosas!
Are we right?
Did you have a lucky night?
Okay, boy.
We're going to let you gather
your thoughts.
Do you want something?
Coffee? A soda?
Thought not.
So?
Not talking?
Not a word.
Gentlemen, I'm in the middle
of another investigation,
and I would like to talk
to José Miguel Rosas,
if you and your office
don't have problems with that.
I have a history with him.
Personal.
He hates me,
he can't stand me.
Maybe I can get him cranked up
enough that he starts yapping.
Do you understand?
He can start talking.
You know, any kid like him...
starts talking with something.
I go in, when he's ready
to deliver the information,
you go in and finish with him.
What do you say?
Of course,
if he gives me anything useful
while he's with me,
I'll share it.
What do you say?
I could use a smoke break.
And you?
Maybe you could keep an eye
on our suspect for us.
Just for a few minutes.
- Do it.
- Thanks, gentlemen.