- Good day, sir.
- Good morning.
Can you please
turn the music down?
Down means off, sir.
The car's papers, please,
license and registration.
Is there any problem?
Driving with a broken windshield
in this state is a violation
to the Federal Traffic Law, sir.
Yes, officer, I know.
In fact, I'm on my way
to the repair shop.
I live near the site
of the planes crash.
Have you heard about it?
Yes, yes, I was there
giving a hand
when the debris
was being collected.
Well, just figure,
I was there, precisely,
and wreckage from the plane
landed on my windshield
and broke it like this.
What a coincidence?
Excuse me,
what are you doing?
I'm giving you a
ticket, sir.
But you don't believe
what I just said or what?
Look, sir, regardless
of what I believe or not,
I have to write you a ticket.
Wait here, please.
You can't lock me in here.
Sir, stay in the car.
Listen, officer.
Please, let me explain, yes?
So now you're
tasering me or--!
This is a violation
to my rights!
Don't you get the scale
of what happened to me or what?
Motherfuc--!
José Miguel...
Hi, dad.
I see you're remodeling
the place, cool.
Yes, yes.
We did some work to it.
That's great.
And you, son?
Are you doing okay?
Yeah, dad. I'm great.
I was in the neighborhood
and I haven't been here
for a while, so...
Well, I saw the "On sale" sign.
It's the best option.
No one in the family
is using it, so...
And the upstairs bathroom
you fixed it too or what?
Sure, we changed the tiles
we had it all redone.
Cool.
Can I come in to--?
I don't think so.
The builders
are working and...
You know.
Yeah, I know.
Well, dad, I'd better stay
out of their way, then.
There are some pretty pics
on the state agency's site.
Cool.
Say hi to mom for me, will you?
Sure.
She'll be glad to know
I saw you
and that you're
doing good.
Great, and maybe
one of these days
we can have lunch together.
Lunch.
Yes, yes.
One of these days.
See you, then.
Take care, son.
I know he committed
contempt for authority
and lack of respect and
premeditation, but...
Look, I can assure you,
he's a nice guy.
He wouldn't hurt a fly.
The thing is he's got
some problems right now.
As it happens,
he's got lung cancer.
His wife kicked him out.
He's screwed.
Come on, help him out.
Walter, do you have anything
to say to the officer?
Look, in fact,
I have no valid justification
for having defied
your authority.
I made a mistake.
I'd like to apologize
for being disrespectful.
Thanks a lot.
Look.
Thanks, bro.
Do you know where my car is?
Cielo said she would
have it fixed.
Cielo wants to divorce me.
Bro.
I don't...
She doesn't want me to see
the children either.
She told you that?
You know me, bro.
I don't like sticking
my nose, you know.
But if she's asking you
that much,
it's because you screwed it
big time?
Can I get a ride?
Yeah, sure.
The car's over there.
At last!
What? I'm the ugly
girlfriend or what?
You don't call, don't write,
don't talk to me.
- What is it?
Saúl...
I've had many women
in my life
who had used me,
you know?
They just want my body,
my flesh,
and then they disappear.
I'm their sex toy.
They just leave without
noticing that within this body
there's a man
who has feelings.
Don't do that too,
Walter, please.
Tell me I'm something
more to you than that.
Or am I your toy as well?
Enough, Saúl!
Please, I'm not in the mood
for your jokes today?
This day had
a pretty bad start for me.
What? What happened?
Anything in particular
I should know?
I'm your lawyer.
No, nothing worth mentioning.
Get to the point, okay?
Why are you here?
Wait, in there...
wouldn't you have dirt laundry
on the floor
or a fat woman snoring
or anything of the sort?
What?
No!
Of course, not!
I know who I'm dealing with.
But, you know?
You should think about it,
because I've got a cousin
I can introduce you to
and she can help you--
Enough, Saúl.
Knock it off, will you?
Please.
Fine, we'd better talk
inside.
I don't know when,
but my life turned
into a complete disaster,
not even in my
worst nightmares
I went through stuff like this.
Please.
You don't need to exaggerate.
You have no idea
how I'm feeling.
Of course I do!
I'm much more experienced
than you
when it comes to break-ups.
The first two times
you're kicked out of the house
you feel you're a mess.
But then when you learn
to do the dishes,
and to replace
the toilet paper roll,
you realize it's not
that big of a deal.
Enough.
I'm not in the mood
for your jokes, man.
I'm being serious.
But, anyway,
let's leave aside
the romantic aspect of it.
This is very simple:
your wife won't talk.
She'll keep her pie hole shut.
She will?
How can you be so sure?
Just one word:
consequences.
Look, if she blabs,
it'll be a disaster for her.
Let's analyze it.
What would happen if everything
is out to the open?
I go to jail,
she hates me, I die.
End of story.
No, no, it's not the end
because there are
more characters in the story.
Sorry for making you think
beyond your belly button?
Let's analyze things
from Cielo's point of you,
for example.
What would happen to her?
First, her brother in law,
the anti-narcotics genius.
He'd be so screwed!
You were right under his nose
and he didn't even see you.
He'd end up a supermarket guard.
Then, your kids.
They'd need therapy
for the rest of their lives.
"My dad is a gangster
and my mom turned him in."
It'll be like
those Peruvian TV shows
where they say:
"Let the bastard come in!"
That would be you, in this case.
And then, the house.
Bye bye house.
They'd apply
expiration of ownership
and the house will become
headquarters
of a random emerging
political party.
No, she won't talk.
She's smart
and I'm sure she analyzed
the consequences.
Do you know
what she really wants?
She wants you to
swallow it.
The problem isn't wether she
talks to the police or not.
The problem is she kicked me
out of her life.
I lost my family, Saúl.
That was the only thing
that mattered.
I did all this for them.
Fine, I get it
and it's hard,
but you've got to fight,
you know?
One day at a time.
Besides, let's see the
bright side of things.
You're back on the market.
Second-hand, but,
anyway...
No, I don't want to be
at any market!
I just want my life back!
Walter, don't jump
into conclusions.
You have no idea
how women are nowadays.
Did you know that young girls
get waxed completely
from head to toes?
Each one of their hairs, man!
They have nothing.
It's like the slide
of happiness!
In the meantime, Walter,
and only to distract you
from your dreadful thoughts,
you could do what you do best.
You and I know
what that is.
How about,
I don't know,
some cooking to kill time
and clear bad ideas?
Definitely, no.
I won't be the bad guy
in this movie.
No, I'm not the bad guy
in the story.
Okay, I see you need
more time.
Fine, take your time.
I'll talk to you later,
I'm with you, man.
In the meantime,
try to stay alive.
Be strong, bro.
Be strong.
Enjoy what you have now,
I don't know,
this room's nice,
you could do something.
I can call my cousin,
if you want--
Knock it off with your cousin!
Be strong, my friend.
Pop-pop, can I have some
money for some cotton candy?
You should promise me something.
Don't tell your mom
because she always
tells me off
when I get you candy, okay?
That should be enough.
Yes?
We have a problem
with the cook's wife.
I need eyes on it.
We got an address?
Honey, aunt María
and Henry
are bringing takeout
in a while.
But I can fix you something
if you're hungry.
How about that?
What?
Is there any problem
with my sushi?
I've had enough trans-fat
for one lifetime.
I just have one question.
How long was it for that fish
since it left the ocean,
they put it on a boat,
it got to the restaurant,
someone ordered takeout,
and now it's on María's table,
Let me tell you something,
that bullshit
the Japanese tell us
that you have to eat raw fish,
I won't buy it!
You know why the Japanese
do that?
You know why?
Because they want to save what?
The grill, the oil,
the grill chef.
Sure!
As if I didn't know
these Japaneses!
Right, buddy?
Hey!
- Well.
You remember
that Morgan is looking for a job
to help in the house?
So let us know if you happen
to know of something.
Walter, my name
is Walter Junior,
like the man
you never mention.
Fine, if you don't want
to use that nickname
you like so much,
and you want to go back
to your name,
I have no problem
with that.
My dad had red eyes
after so much crying,
but you don't even care!
And now he won't even
drive me home
and I know that's because
you don't let him do it.
Honey...
I know
you don't love him,
but I do love my dad,
and I love him a lot.
And you don't let me see him
because you're a bitch!
Hey, hey, Junior!
You can't talk to your mom
like that.
Junior!
It's okay,
no problem.
Cielo, I know you must have
your reasons for all this.
Cielo, look, I know
it's none of my business.
But keeping Walt from the kids?
Don't you think
you're exaggerating?
You're right,
it's none of your business.
Something weird is going on.
Aren't you curious?
No, I'm not curious.
So what?
I'm imagining things now?
Look, when I knew Walter
had two cell phones,
everything was clear to me.
Believe me,
I've seen it a hundred times.
You saw what?
Stop dancing around it.
Look at Walter.
He's a decent guy,
a smart guy, a nice guy.
But he hasn't done well
in life.
He's failed in almost
everything.
He's done,
am I right?
He's got no willing to live,
he's got cancer.
What does he do?
He gets a lover,
the wife finds out,
and the guy, out of guilt,
confesses.
Besides,
Walter is the typical guy
who can't say a lie.
I don't know.
You don't know
what, María?
I don't know.
I think it's something else.
Cielo would've told me
if it was that.
- Something else?
-I don't know. I don't know.
I want surveillance
and monitoring
24 hours a day.
How much will that be?
What?
No, I'm in the wrong business.
No, no, no,
it's okay, look.
Fine, anyway,
we'll work things out.
Don't worry about that.
Fine.
Bye, bye.
The return of the prodigal son!
So nice to see you!
- How are you doing?
- I'm good, hanging there.
Hanging there?
Man, you're great!
Young, rich,
no commitments.
I would've loved to be
in your position
at your age
with my mouth and loaded.
Speaking of money...
Here's your stash.
I took good care of it,
you know?
Hey, by the way,
your former partner
is giving me an ulcer.
After all he did
to build this great business,
now he wants to walk out.
How about that?
He's got a great talent, but
he flushes it down the toilet.
Look, I know you're not
into this any more, but
could you help me out here?
I mean, you could try
to convince him,
and then--
Look, Saúl...
Fine, yes, I know.
Yeah, he won't listen to me,
and he won't listen to you.
Can I interest you
in a business?
Sure!
- Hello.
- Yes, sir. Good afternoon.
- Your key. Come in.
- Thanks.
- Hello.
What are you doing here?
Does your mom
know you're here?
Can we talk?
- Hello.
I'm sorry,
do you need the space?
I don't have enough room
for all this
on my desk.
No, no, no, I'm here
to see Valentina.
Hello, sweetie!
Hello, Valentina!
She's so beautiful.
Ernesto,
I wanted to thank you
for being so flexible
on me coming in.
Honestly, you have no idea
how easier my life is
having Valentina here.
Look, I'd do anything
to keep you here longer.
You do brighten
up the place.
We need to talk about something
you're not gonna like.
I really can't sing off
on these balance sheets.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
So? What can we do?
If you're going to cook
the books,
it can't be so glaring!
Tell me.
There's revenue with
no backup everywhere.
It's all there is.
Nothing has its backup.
This can't be done!
Cielo, this is all I have.
You know what?
I'll keep you
out of all this.
Okay?
Have you even thought
what your kids would think
if they knew about this?
What would you tell them?
I don't know...
I don't.
I'd say that everyone
makes mistakes,
that I did it
thinking of them,
for their own good.
And I'd ask them to try
to understand.
I don't know.
You know what?
I'm too busy worrying
about solving
my present situation.
I don't know what
will happen tomorrow.
Walter, I'm at a meeting
right now, I can't--
Listen, I just wanted
to tell you Junior
is here with me.
He was waiting for me
when I got back.
- What?
- Don't you worry.
I talked to him already.
He knows he has
to come back home.
But, dad!
Junior has to head back home
immediately.
Yes, Cielo,
I know that.
What's more,
I'm giving him a ride.
Don't you worry.
No, I'd rather
you brought him right now
here to my office.
Yes, but I don't have
my car right now
and going to your job
at this hour
it's a nightmare,
with all this traffic.
Isn't it better if I take him
home directly?
Well, do that,
but not too late!
Yes, sure. No problem.
See you later.
Dad, why does mom do this?
She doesn't want us to meet
and you help her!
Well, it's not like that.
How is it then?
Well, your mom...
She has her reasons.
What reasons, dad?
Well, they're just a little
difficult to explain.
But, let's see, Junior,
there are two sides
to every story, you know?
And in this case,
well, your mom...
I don't know. Whatever.
This is just how
it has to be for now,
you get that?
You've got to be with your mom
at your house--
And you too, dad.
Aunt María,
uncle Henry and I
know you haven't done
anything wrong.
And we are on your side.
Well, it's not
about taking sides, though.
I don't know what's going on.
But why you let her
treat you like this?
Why?
Junior, enough, calm down.
Take it easy, champ.
Listen, the important thing here
is that whatever happens,
our feelings for you
will never change.
You should get that straight.
Your baby sister and you
will always be
the most important thing
in the world for us.
Above anything else.
You get that?
Junior, do you get that?
Show me some teeth. Say yes.
Yeah! Good!
- Attorney, how are you?
- How are you?
Hello!
Mrs. Sofía, how are you?
- Mr. Guillermo.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm Saúl Bueno.
You're the attorney
in the late night show, right?
Yes, I am!
"Better call Saúl "!
Well, very well.
Let's cut to the chase.
We're meeting today
to discuss the details
of the sale of our property.
Of course!
The meter is not running
and the time flies, right?
Well, today's your lucky day.
I represent a client
who chose to remain anonymous.
But for you to get
the picture,
imagine someone
with a bag full of cash.
Well, this person
wants to buy the
property from you today,
instant payment.
- Instant payment?
Great?
Fine, I've been talking
with Leopoldo already
and showed him my client's
pertinent financials
and, you know,
we're talking
about serious figures here.
Yes, indeed.
That's in Guillermo and Sofía
best interest.
That's why we're sitting here,
attorney.
Sustained, attorney.
So, let's proceed then
with the signing of
the deeds.
That expense will be paid
by my client,
of course, and that's it,
we're ready.
I can wire you
your money today
to your account
abroad, in dollars,
just like Leopoldo told
me you wanted to.
There's just one tiny
little detail
I'd like to discuss with you.
What we call "one little
hair in the soup."
- The price.
- Okay.
We've estimated
that 800 thousand dollars
would be price
for this excellent property.
We feel that's a fair price.
Of course,
we're open to negotiation.
Well, so we could think
of 400 thousand,
and we're all happy.
Excuse me?
That's half the price.
Are you making fun of us,
attorney?
No, no, let's see, sir.
The house,
even before the remodeling,
was worth much more than that.
That's my offer.
What kind of joke is this?
Let's go, come on.
It's a pretty good offer
taking into account
that in that house
there was a lab
that processed
and produced
illegal drugs.
In the basement, remember?
I've read in detail
the clauses of the contract,
because that's how I am,
and I didn't find
any mention
of this matter.
I didn't find either
any report
to anti-narcotics
police, right?
This would be an
excellent case
for my TV show!
I'd call it:
"Fraud with concealing
of a felony."
And I believe
that people like you,
so respectable, the Rosas,
a family
with such a good
reputation
in the society of Bogotá,
would get stained
if related with a case
like this one, right?
I'm not judgmental,
whatsoever,
not me, of course.
But here, in this country,
people like gossiping.
Leopoldo,
are you blackmailing us? Fuck!
How could you present us
with such a motherf--?
You have every right
of course,
to refuse negotiations
with my client.
If that's the case,
good luck
in trying to sell
a meth-contaminated
house.
The modern devil,
the demon of these days.
And god luck
with the future lawsuits
from buyers
who'd feel defrauded,
and who I could,
eventually,
represent and make this
business last forever.
I'm telling you for information
purposes, of course,
because you're mature people
and can make
your own decisions,
the ones you
consider pertinent.
Now, what's your advice,
counselor?
- Hey!
- Hello.
You heard us coming?
Look, I brought pizza.
Junior's dinner
is ready.
Well, we'll put it
in the fridge.
It'll be delicious tomorrow
reheated.
Hello, honey.
I'm sorry.
He's a bit agitated.
But a slice of pizza
will change his mood for sure.
I told you already.
Junior's dinner is ready.
Cielo, let's talk.
About that?
What kind of example
do we want to set here?
Please!
We sit at the table,
have some pizza,
and talk about his as grown-ups.
I already said
what I had to say.
There's nothing else
to discuss, Walter.
Haven't you understood
a word I said, or what?
Cielo,
it's pepperoni pizza.
Hello?
When I went out this morning,
I found a pizza
something threw away.
Do you happen to have
anything to do with that?
Walter, please!
Get your act together.
Accept the situation
and keep your distance.
You know what?
If you don't do it,
I will get a restraining order.
Cielo, please...
And I'm not cleaning that!
Cielo, I'll do it.
Cielo, hello!
Goddamn!
Hello, Cielo, Cielo!
I don't get why I had
to do this myself.
We should've called
the gardener.
No, I won't let
that random person
who bought this house
gets the plants as well.
But I'll hurt my back--
No!
- Good day.
Son, I'm sorry
but it's really not a good time.
- Okay.
- José Miguel.
José Miguel,
look, the new owner of the house
is on his way.
Yes, I'm going in.
This is my house, see?
I bought it.
In fact, you know what?
I'm going to need
this spare set of keys, please.
And the plant also stays.
I planted it
with my grandma, okay?
Good luck! Take care.
Hush, my love.
Bye, take care.
Drive safe, okay?
Bye, my love.
Give me a kiss.
Cielo?
I've got information.
Boss, a call.
I'm listening.