What happened, yo?
What happened?
I feel dizzy, I feel dizzy.
I need some fresh air.
Come on, come here.
Sit down.
- I can't brea--
- Sit down here.
It's okay,
it's okay.
I feel like I'm burning inside.
Inhale, breathe, relax.
When were you
going to tell me?
What?
About the cancer.
You have cancer, right?
How do you know?
'Cause my grandma
had one of those...
marks that
radiotherapy leaves.
Dude, we're partners
in this.
Why didn't you tell me?
That's not good, bro.
What stage are you in?
3 A.
It's already in
the lymph nodes.
In what condition was your
grandma when you got to know?
Very bad.
How long did she last?
Seven months and
four days exactly.
I was always
beside her.
It's pretty obvious.
Now it's clear.
You're doing all this
to leave some money
for your folks, right?
You have any problems with that?
Simmer down
there, sparky.
Easy, man, you lost.
You're fucked up, easy.
Uncle, I don't see
José Miguel, he's gone.
Anybody got eyes on Rosas?
No.
You two go find him,
see what happened.
Boss, see what we've got here:
cops.
Nice.
No, no, no,!
Joaquín, don't do it!
Please, don't shoot!
Get me out of here,
Peto, don't shoot!
Joaquín, Joaquín,
don't shoot, please.
Don't shoot, don't kill him!
- Get back here.
- Easy.
The hell not?
He's a cop.
He's my family.
Say again?
He's my
brother-in-law.
So this fucking cop
has something to do with you?
Didn't cross your mind
to maybe tell us you had a cop
for a brother-in-law?
Did you know about this?
I called you off, remember?
God damn it!
What are you doing here?
I told you not to come!
It seems to me
we did you a solid.
No! You weren't
supposed to be here!
Too late now.
How's about you telling me
what was the fuck going down
out here, buddy.
From what I see,
you and your brother-in-law
don't seem to be
getting along too well.
It doesn't
concern you.
We just wasted
his partner here
and he's wearing a bullet.
So, yeah,
I'd say it does concern me.
No! This is between
him and me.
No cavalry coming?
No, no!
You bet your ass
the cavalry's coming.
They're almost here.
No, no, no!
That's not true!
I swear!
Henry, Henry, I know
nothing can change
what just happened
but you can walk
out of here alive.
Henry, please,
you just promise us
promise that you'll let this go,
this didn't happen, tell him!
Yeah, I thought as much.
Sorry, man. Just no scenario
where this guy lives.
No, no, no!
Joaquín, Joaquín, no!
I have money! I have money!
It's buried out here.
It's eighty million dollars.
They're yours.
So that's what got
this party started?
You know what's the problem?
This money of yours
won't do me much good in prison.
Yes, it will!
Joaquín, think about it.
You can do anything.
It's eighty million dollars!
150 billion pesos.
All you've got to do
is let him go.
That's a hell of an offer.
What do you think, Fed?
Don't call him Fed.
His name is Henry.
How about it, Henry?
Should I let you go?
I'm special agent Henry Navarro,
and you know what I think?
That you can go fuck yourself!
No, no, no, Henry!
No, Joaquín, wait!
Henry, you gotta tell him now
that we can work this out.
Do it!
God damned it, tell him!
You're the smartest guy
I ever met.
But you're also the
most stupid.
Don't you see?
Ten minutes ago, this guy
made up his mind to kill me.
So do what you're
gonna--
No!
Most people
tell me to be somewhere
"After that house
there on the left,
or 2 miles after the bridge
on the right, there's
a post and a sign
whatever, but these are
pretty specific directions.
It's very weird.
Not even back in the day
we used those references
nor shit in the sticks.
That money is around here.
That fancy phone of yours,
where does it say
this is exactly?
Look at this.
He brought all the gear
shovel and everything.
Boss, the kid now.
Then we'll take
care of him.
Says this is it right here.
So dig.
What's that?
What's this?
Look, boss!
Boss.
Joaquín.
Hell yeah!
That's right,
lift the lid.
What's this?
That's what I call guts!
Out of there, man.
Come on, get it out.
Come on, show me, show me.
Whoo! Look!
All right.
Go get the bodies.
Yeah, boss.
Thanks, uncle.
Pull a barrel off the truck
and load it in that car.
Seriously?
That's, like,
10 or 11 million right there.
Do the maths.
I don't know, but think that's--
You gonna make me say it again?
What have I told you?
Go. Chop, chop.
Whatever you say, boss.
You heard him.
Jesus.
What's with all the greed here?
In my day, nobody showed
their true colors like that.
Hey. I'm leaving you a barrel.
Boys are gonna load it for you.
You got the keys
for these cuffs?
I'm sorry for
your loss.
My nephew here,
he respects you.
He would never forgive me
if things went another way.
Also, I'll be honest,
you caught me in a good mood.
So here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna get in your car
and drive out of here.
You get lost.
All right? No hard feelings.
We put all this behind.
We square?
Why do you have to be
so rude?
No, no, man.
Let me tell you something.
I gotta know we're square.
Or we're gonna have
to go that other way.
Very good.
Rosas.
You still owe me
If you can find him,
we'll kill him. Count on it.
Found him.
No! Get off me! Get off!
All right. Good to go?
Uncle, wait.
He was out here
working with those
feds.
Shouldn't we find out
what he told them first?
Maybe he told them some
stuff that might not be
good for us.
And I'll bet I could get it
out of him back home.
Me and him, we got history.
I'm sure he remembers.
And we'd take care
of the job after that.
We bring him back dead.
Works for me.
Works for you?
No, no, Walter, no, no,
Walter! Get off!
Wait!
Remember that girl you had?
That you loved
so much, Juana?
I watched her die,
you know?
I was there the night she died.
I was standing there.
You were both completely wasted.
Until she began throwing up.
I saw her choking
in her own barf and did nothing.
I could have saved her.
But I didn't.
Hi.
Hello, sir.
That truck
belong to you?
It does. It's mine.
I'd like to buy it.
No, sir. It's not for sale.
Buddy.
I told you it's not for sale.
That truck brings back memories
of my family.
Sir.
Thank you.
Walter, it's me again.
What time would
you be back?
Just give us a call
whenever you can. Bye.
Hi.
Auntie!
How's my favorite
nephew going?
I haven't seen you for a while.
I've been busy, you know.
This and that.
But I need to talk to your mom,
so I thought I'd stop by.
I wish you'd called first.
This isn't the best time.
Well, I guess Morgan
can hold down the fort.
Yeah, sure. I got it.
Okay, honey.
Thanks.
Why don't we go
into your office?
How can I help you?
María, I have nothing to say.
Well, I do, so you can
just sit there and listen.
I got a call
from Henry.
He arrested Walter
three hours ago.
It's over, Cielo.
They are working with a former
associate of Walter
José Miguel Rosas.
You know him, right?
He has supplied them
with everything they
need.
They're booking Walter
as we speak.
And I, for one,
could not be happier.
I almost didn't come here.
Christ, I barely even know
who you are.
And you know what?
I don't even know if I
can ever trust you again.
And then I think about the time
you were so upset with Walt
and asked us
to stay with the kids
because you wanted
them out of the house.
And all of this makes me believe
that there has got to be hope
for you.
Because I don't know what
Walter did to your head
but it can be undone.
And I've been forcing myself to
remember that you are my sister.
And so I'm here.
But everything changes now.
And you have got to prepare
yourself.
Henry will help you,
I know he will.
And I will support you,
but I have conditions.
I want you to give me
every video you did
every single copy
of that obscenity
that the two of you made
to discredit Henry.
You understand me?
Answer me.
Do you
understand me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Now you'll dry
your eyes and get Junior.
You're going to tell
him everything.
He deserves to know the
truth from his family.
Not a bunch of uniformed
strangers.
No, no, no.
Please, Junior cannot know, no.
You tell him. Or I
will, Cielo.
Junior needs to know
the truth
and he needs to
know now.
Good afternoon.
Look, I gave you
what you wanted.
I don't know anything else.
Just go to Henry Navarro's
house, the tape is there.
I swear, no one else
knows about it.
Just me and his partner.
I can't stand it anymore.
Get out. Or you want me
to help you climb?
Yo, I swear, I did nothing.
Get out.
The day's nice out here.
Come on.
I'll hold the ladder so you
don't get hurt. Easy.
One foot, then the other.
That's it. Slowly.
Watch your head.
Relax, I got you.
There it is.
I got you.
Let me help you.
There you are.
Relax, okay?
All right.
You ready?
Let's cook.
You're out of your mind!
It's the truth, honey.
I'm sorry, but it's the truth.
Then both of you are
out of your minds!
No.
Then how could you keep
this a secret?
Why would you go along?
Why wouldn't you
tell the police?
I'll be asking myself that
for the rest of my life.
So you're saying all of this
time you were lying about this?
You're a liar, mom!
No more lies, lies!
So were you lying then,
or are you lying now?
Which lie is it?
Morgan, now your mother
is telling you the truth.
Right here, right now.
Believe it.
This is bullshit!
I wanna talk to dad.
Your dad's in custody.
He won't be able to answer.
Then I'm calling
my uncle!
I've tried.
He's not answering either.
He must be in the thick of it
with your father.
Sit down and calm--
Don't touch me!
I don't want
to be here.
You'd better go home to stay
with Valentina and Junior,
so you can calm down
and talk about all this.
I'll stop by later.
Put your seatbelt on.
Junior, could you put
your seatbelt on, please?
Honey, I'm serious.
Please, put it on.
You know it's not safe.
You can get injured,
or even police can stop us
and give us a fine and--
You're shittin'
me, right?
If all this is true
and you knew about it
you're as bad as him.
Honey...
Whose truck is that?
Dad!
Come on.
Come inside and pack right now.
Pack your stuff.
Mom and aunt María,
they said you were arrested?
What? No, I'm here.
Don't you see?
They say that you're
some kind of drug dealer?
What are you talking about?
- Talk to me, dad!
- No!
Go and pack! Our priority
right now is to pack.
Just tell me, dad!
I'm talking to you.
Go, go. Junior, I need you
to go into your bedroom
and pack your stuff.
Uncle Henry,
they said he arrested you?
You were with him?
I will discuss
all of this
later, okay?
Why not now?!
Just because!
It has to be now!
Go to your bedroom
and pack your things!
Go! Now!
Cielo, you too.
Please, go grab your things.
Why are you here?!
Grab everything
for you and the kids.
Right now!
But Henry had you in custody.
He wouldn't just let you go.
What happened?
Where's Henry?
I negotiated.
Negotiated?!
- Yes, negotiated.
- What does that mean?
It means we're fine,
Cielo, okay?
Everything is gonna be fine,
but we need to leave right now.
No, no, no!
Tell me where's Henry?!
Why do we need to leave, dad?
Cielo, I have 11 million dollars
in cash right outside
in the truck.
We can have a fresh start.
Whole new lives.
But I need us to go right now.
I'll explain everything later,
I promise.
You killed him.
- What?
No, no, no!
No, Gosh, no!
I tried to save him, I swear!
No!
Please, trust me.
Cielo, trust me.
Junior, I'll tell you everything
later.
No! Tell me now!
It can't be now, Junior.
I need you to trust me.
Talk to me!
Tell me what's going on.
I'll tell you later.
Stop fooling around.
I'm not fooling around!
Junior, we have to go now.
What happened to uncle Henry?
Get out!
Cielo, I promise you, we
will figure this out.
Enough!
Get out of here!
- What are you doing?
- Out!
- Get out of here!
- Put it down.
Mom, please, calm down!
- Get out.
- Put the knife down.
- Get out of here!
- Put it down now!
- Mom, watch out!
No, no, mom!
Go!
No! Don't hurt her!
Get out of here!
Watch out!
Let go!
No, no!
What are you doing?!
Mom, are you okay?
What the hell is wrong with you!
We're a family!
We're a family.
I need the police.
My dad, he pulled
a knife on my mom.
He's going to kill her.
He's a murderer.
Please, come quickly.
Yeah, he's still in the house.
He might attack us.
He's dangerous.
We're at 21 12-1.
You've gotta come quick.
Dad, what are you doing?
Mom?
What?! No, no, no.
Not Valentina, Walter.
Walter, no! Let her go!
Please, Walter!
You can't do this!
Walter, you can't take her!
Give me my baby back!
Please, don't do it!
Give me my child!
Please, Walter, Walter!
Let her go!
Walter! Please!
Daddy got you a new sweater.
The other one was filthy.
This will keep you warm.
Everything will be okay,
you know?
Look, do you like it?
Beautiful.
Let's throw this away.
Mommy.
Confirming the abduction.
Valentina Blanco Restrepo,
18 months
Caucasian, last time she
was seen wearing a white jacket
with a kitty and pink pants.
Henry called and told me
he had caught Walter
and had him in handcuffs.
I don't get it.
Are you expecting a call?
Cielo, it's me. Pick up.
That's him.
That's my husband.
Start tracing the landline.
The number's 50-51-77-85-86.
I know you're there,
so pick it up.
Got it.
If you're there, I need you
to pick up the phone.
Walter, where's
Valentina?
Are you alone?
No police?
No. No police.
Tell me, where are you?
Where's my girl?
- What the hell
is wrong with you?
- Walter!
Why can't you do
one thing I say?
Why don't you do as I tell you?
What?!
This is your fault.
This is what comes
of your disrespect.
And I told you, didn't I?
I warned you for a solid year.
I warned you
that if you crossed me
there would be consequences.
Didn't I make myself clear?
What part of that
didn't you understand, Cielo?
You took my
child!
'Cause you need to learn.
You bring her
back now!
Maybe now you'll listen.
Maybe now you'll use
your damn head.
You know,
you never believed in me.
You were never grateful
for anything I did
for this family.
No! You kept whining:
"No, Walter.
You have to stop.
Walter, it's immoral.
It's illegal.
They're gonna get you."
You're always judging
and complaining.
While I do everything,
absolutely everything,
on my own.
And now, on top of it,
you tell my son
what I do,
everything I've done
after I've told you and told you
to keep your damn mouth shut.
You stupid bitch!
How dare you?
I'm sorry.
Listen, Cielo.
You have no right
to discuss anything I do.
No right! What the hell
do you know about it anyway?
You never knew
about anything I did, did you?
And you didn't care to know.
I built this. Me. Me alone.
Nobody else!
You hear me?
You're right,
you're right.
Maybe now you'll be able
to mark my words.
Listen carefully, Cielo.
You tow the line
and do what I say
or you will wind up
just like Henry.
Please, we need to know
what happened to Henry.
You're never gonna see
Henry again.
He crossed me.
And bear this in mind family
or no, you sink with me.
Walter, please, I just
want my daughter back.
Please, just come home
and bring Valentina back.
No, I've still got things
left to do.
Thanks.
Who turned on the flares?
Mate.
Shh, shh.
What I can tell you
is that you're also
in a position to buy an eraser.
An eraser?
It's an extreme,
desperate solution
but if you really want
to protect yourself,
you must consider
disappearing without trace.
I know this guy, an eraser,
a "disappearer"
a Copperfield who
might do the job.
He's expensive, and I mean very
expensive, but he'll give you
the possibility of starting
a new life elsewhere
Costa Rica, Argentina--
You say like some sort
of witness protection program,
something like that?
But without being a witness
to anything.
New name, new life, all new.
You'd become
totally unreachable.
The only thing is
once you make up your mind
there's no chance to back out.
None whatsoever.