What's up?
What do you need?
Yo, you buyin', or are you
just stopping to envy?
Punk bitches!
Tripaseca, it's Gordo.
Brother, there's two guys here.
I'm getting eyeballed hard.
I got a bad feeling, man.
I need some backup.
Can I have your hat?
What did I say?
Get out of here!
What are you waiting for? Go!
Walter, we've made such headway
with your treatments.
Now it's time we talked
about sealing the deal.
Absolutely.
As you know,
my initial diagnosis was
that your cancer was inoperable.
That may no longer be the case.
We think now that a lobectomy
may be a viable option.
In this institute we have one of
the few surgeons in the country
performing lobectomies.
Lobectomy?
It sounds aggressive.
Uumm... Very much so.
It's a very delicate procedure.
But if you don't have this
surgery, you're waiting
for the cancer to spread.
Through the treatment
you've had already,
we've bought you some time.
Maybe a lot, probably a little,
but that's all.
In my opinion, Walter,
if you're willing
to take some risk,
then this offer
is the best chance.
Doctor, insurance
won't cover this.
How much would it cost?
For international standards,
I'd say some
250 thousand dollars.
But around here,
for one of our patients,
I think it would be around
300 million, give or take.
This is obviously
a big decision.
You might need some time
to discuss it.
No, let's do it.
I'll do it.
Don't you think we should at
least talk this through first?
Sure, honey.
I just think it's the way to go.
I have to say I think
it's the right choice.
When can we schedule
the surgery?
It's just that the baby
is almost here.
That's what I was about to ask.
When's the due date?
By the end of this month.
What we can do is,
I'll book the surgery
so Walter can be on his feet
for the birth of your baby.
Is that okay?
Yes, that's fine.
14 messages?
Hi. What's up?
Where the hell were you?
I called, like, 20 times.
I see.
Gordo's dead.
They shot him
several times.
Which one is he?
You did not just say that to me.
Eat shit, motherfucker!
What's the word on the street?
No one's dropping no names.
How come, Tripa?
That's odd.
You know everything
on the streets.
It was like a ghost.
So we've got nothing.
I told you already.
Gordo rang me
before it went down.
Said dudes were
mad-dogging him.
That's all I know.
Shit, shit, shit!
Can I ask you a question
without you getting all mad?
Come on.
Why'd we have to go
pushing into new turf?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Is that all you got?
So we just did what Heisenberg
wanted and that's that?
No, no, no, Tripa; things
are not that easy up there,
it's complicated.
Come on!
You're the man,
you're in charge.
Yes, I'm in charge.
See...
As the man in charge,
I swear I'll do right
by Gordo's people.
- It's the least you can do.
- Come on...
But before we can make our minds
up about what to do next,
make sure you bust up the cell
phone where you got that call
and throw it away right now.
Done. Done.
But this is as far
as I go.
Come on, you can't be
serious. Right?
Man... With Gordo gone and Mono
laying low out in Medellin,
I'm the only one left.
What do you mean?
- What about me? Don't I count?
- You're covered, man.
I'm the one putting his
face out on the street.
They will bust me
or kill me.
Come, Tripa, Tripa,
listen up.
We're on the verge
of making some serious money.
What, you're gonna jump ship
now?
Jose...
Everyone on the street
knows you didn't kill Poke.
- Everyone knows?
- Sure.
Everyone knows that thing
to the head, the ATM,
his junkie bitch copped to it.
No, Tripa, come on,
why didn't you say something?
I don't know, man.
Listen...
I'm telling you,
just sit tight.
We'll get by. We'll make it.
Come on.
Sorry, I'm out.
If things calm down,
you can count on me.
This is my advise to you:
take care of yourself, man.
That's fine.
Thanks for everything.
See you, Tripa.
We have had a setback.
- What?
Sorry, that's an accurate
description.
What do you want me
to say?
- How about your fault?
- Don't lay that on me!
You are in charge
of distribution.
You said expand the territory.
That doesn't mean
you become careless!
Guys, guys, please.
Who do I look like?
I'm not your marriage
counselor.
Now, you're professionals.
Act like it.
Let's get to the point.
What happened?
one of our dealers.
was murdered,
It was some kind
of turf dispute,
we lost and then
everyone quit on us.
We have absolutely
no distribution!
Is there any way any of this
can be traced back to you?
Good news.
Come on.
How about you?
How's the health situation?
- It's better.
- Better?
I may have more time
than I thought.
Outstanding!
Now, as to your dead guy,
may God keep him
in his Glory,
but it's an occupational
hazard.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
and say it's been
known to happen.
If you are a girl
on the streets,
you might get AIDS
or a venereal disease.
If you sell drugs,
you might end up dead.
It's in the contract.
Come on.
What about product on hand?
How's your inventory?
- 17 and change.
Ounces, grams...?
Kilos.
Kilos?
Kilos?!
My God!
Why the long faces here?
You're sitting
on a gold mine!
A gold mine we can't sell.
We need a proper infrastructure.
We need foot soldiers
and dealers.
We need muscle,
and we need enforcers.
Payback.
That's what we need.
This entire process
has just been so...
It's always been one
step forward and two steps back.
We need help, Saul.
All right, all right.
Let's start with some
tough love, all right?
You two suck at peddling meth.
Period.
So give up on trying
to do it all yourselves.
I'm amazed you got this far.
Me too.
We are not going to deal with
another high-level distributor.
We have been down that road.
No, no, I'm not talking
about some tattooed speed-freak
who only knows ten words. No.
What you two need
is an honest-to-God businessman,
who treats your product
like the high-margin
commodity it is.
Someone who's been
doing this
for 20 years and never
been caught.
Someone who might be interested
in the meth business.
Someone who knows
their shit.
You know someone like that?
Let's just say I know a guy
who knows a guy
who knows another guy.
Let me make some calls,
see if I can get you a meeting.
What's his name?
I have no idea.
He's very low profile.
He's careful like that.
From what I do hear about him,
he sounds a little like you.
You know what, Juana?
Um?
I need you to leave.
Why?
There's some stuff
about me you don't know.
Like what?
Like you're a drug dealer?
I kind of got that.
You use an alias,
you pay in cash, so...
And I'm still here.
Know what?
One of my guys, a friend who
worked for me got murdered.
It was my fault.
I put him on that corner.
So, now...
I'm gonna smoke some crystal,
and get really high.
And I just think you should go,
being that you're
in a program and all and...
You could come with me
to a meeting.
No meetings.
We could just get out of here.
It won't help.
Yeah, it will.
And I don't need you
telling me that it won't. No.
I really just need
you to go. All right?
One Combo 3.
One Combo 3 for Table 4.
Half a roasted chicken,
one potato salad and a soda.
Table 7; table 7, combo 4.
A roasted chicken,
two potatoes and a side dish.
Combo 3 to go.
One potato, half a roasted
chicken and two sodas.
Table 8.
Table 8, combo 3.
Half a roasted chicken,
two side dishes...
You're late.
We ran late.
So?
Today's the big day.
So where's the kingpin?
Your guess is as good as mine.
- So you get the dude's name?
- No.
So let me get
this straight.
He's allowed to know
all about us, but not
the other way around?
Why don't you
get yourself some food?
So we won't sit here with
our Happy Meals, looking
like a couple chumps?
Gentlemen, is everything
to your satisfaction?
Need anything?
No, thanks.
Yuo know what?
I don't get you, man.
A week ago you were all
ready to hang it up.
And look at you now.
- We've got 17 kilos to sell.
- So?
After, you gonna make up
some new magic number?
"I got bills. I got bills.
I gotta make more."
Things have changed.
- Don't you understand?
- I know.
We got a guy killed.
Are you going to spend
the rest of your life
thinking about that?
You know what? This is bullshit.
I'm out of here.
Jose, come on,
Jose, come on!
Idiot!
She's waking up
from a nap.
Uhm, aha...
She is certainly going
to want to get out.
We'll keep an eye
on your fluids.
You're on the low side
of normal.
- How low?
- It's not a problem,
unless we see
a growth drop-off.
We'll just have you in
for an ultrasound next week
and keep an eye on things.
All right.
Thank you.
Sorry!
Man, you would
not believe the traffic.
- That's why I left early.
- What did I miss?
Here. Here you have a picture
for your refrigerator.
My God!
Look at her.
Incredible.
It's like she's here already.
It's time to make a decision.
We've been talking about it
for months now.
Um... The C-section?
Yes.
And if it's a yes,
we need to schedule it.
My last labor
was pretty tough, so...
We had talked about it,
right?
For the baby, let's do it.
Okay.
So why don't we schedule it
for next Tuesday?
Is it Tuesday 13th?
16th.
I like it.
Sure, if that's what you want.
Will you please
tell doctor Sanchez
so he can schedule
your surgery?
Sure, I'll tell him.
Speaking of birthdays,
I have to go buy a cake.
It's the boss' birthday.
Why do you have to do it?
I said I would.
So you'll be late?
I don't know, I might.
Do you want to keep
the car?
No, no, you keep it.
- Sure?
- Yes.
Save me a slice?
Sure.
- Bye.
- Hi.
- Aha.
Let's get out of here.
- Let's do something.
Aha.
You know that museum
you talked about?
- Let's go dancing.
- Aha.
Come on.
- What's the emergency?
- This is very important.
- Excuse me.
- Hi, everyone.
- Surprise!
Happy Birthday!
Okay...
Wow!
Haha.
Thank you very much.
You're like family to me,
you know that.
Ehm...
This is beautiful, guys.
Are you making a wish?
You gotta make a wish.
- Bravo!
- Thanks!
A wish!
China's undercutting us
at every turn...
- No, seriously!
There's one thing...
There's something
I always do on my Birthday,
and it seems to work,
it's good luck.
Ehm...
You are going to help me.
- No!
- Come on, Cielo!
- No, no, no, no, no!
- Yes!
It's my wish.
You cannot deny
your employer his birthday wish.
- It's for the good of
the company.
- No, please, no...
Look at me!
I know what you
are talking about!
- Claudia, no!
- Did you see?
I have it here.
Wait a minute.
- Claudia, no!
- Yes, yes, yes.
Please, I...!
Valentina is coming out
of me!
Do it calmly.
This is no problem, right?
Found it!
That's it,
ladies and gentlemen,
I give you
the three times award winning
Soluciones Silva!
Bravo!
Now, come on...
- Ay, no.
- Yes, yes!
Cielo, Cielo, Cielo, Cielo!
Music, please.
Boss, come over here.
Get comfortable.
Bravo!
Thank you.
He wasn't there.
He didn't show up!
He was there.
All I know is my contact
says he was there.
Are you sure you were
at the right restaurant?
Yes, I'm positive.
A fried chicken place.
Los Pollos Hermanos!
How can I forget
that name?
Maybe he stayed out
in the parking lot.
You said
we would meet inside.
Maybe he checked you out...
and saw something in you
that he didn't like much.
Anyway, it doesn't matter now
because my contact says
it's a no go.
He can't do that!
God dammit!
How can he decide without
meeting me? That's unfair!
What did I say?
He's skittish,
like a little animal.
He won't show his head.
Like a deer.
- Call him back.
- No, I can't do that.
Call him!
I can't.
First of all,
I never called him, all right?
I called a guy
who called a guy.
Second of all,
it's over.
With this particular individual
all you get is the one shot.
I'll see if I can scrape
something else together,
but don't get your hopes up.
No one else handles
that kind of bulk. Get it?
Thank you.
Excuse me,
can I take that?
Yes, thank you.
Can I help you, sir?
Sparkling water, please.
Yes, sir.
- Anything else?
- No, thanks.
Sandra, from this moment on,
- we no longer make deliveries.
- Okay.
Help me close down
the register.
All right.
Can I help you, sir?
A sugar free lemonade,
please.
- Of course.
- And five minutes of your time.
Gladly, go to your table,
I'll bring you your order.
- Your lemonade.
- Thank you.
Have a seat, please.
Please.
How can I help you?
I would like to know why you
wouldn't meet with me today.
I'm sorry?
I'm not following.
I sat here this morning,
waiting to meet with someone.
I believe that person
was you.
I think that you're confusing me
for someone else.
I don't think I am.
Sir, if you have a complaint,
I suggest you submit it through
our complaint box.
That's what it's for.
Otherwise, you may also
use our e-mail system
which you will find
in our website.
I've been watching
you carefully.
I have a hypothesis.
I was told that the man
I would be meeting with,
is a serious, elegant,
very cautious man.
As far as I know, I believe
you are that person.
If you are
who I think you are,
and I'm pretty sure
you are,
you should give me
another chance.
I believe we're alike.
I don't think we're alike
at all, Mr. White.
You are not
a cautious man at all.
Your partner was late,
and he was high.
Yes, he was.
He's high often, isn't he?
You have poor judgment
to choose your partners.
Are you familiar
with my product?
I've been told it's excellent.
It is impeccable.
It is the purest.
My crystals could go
head to head
with anything you can find
in Mexico or the US.
That is not the only factor.
You could charge twice
the current rate, and
your customers would pay it.
See...
Who I choose to do business
with is not your problem.
You won't see him.
You won't interact with him.
Forget he exists.
I have to ask.
Why him?
Because I can trust him.
Because he does what I say.
How much product
do you have on hand?
17 kilos. Ready to go
at a moment's notice.
Will I hear from you?
I have your number.
When I need you, I'll call.
You can never trust
a drug addict.
Good night.
Look, this is what I mean.
It's all kind of little
dribs and drabs.
Three million pesos here,
another two there.
Two thousand dollars
for imports
which don't exist.
Another four thousand
over there...
It's a lot.
You said it,
it's all dribs and drabs.
Sure, Ernesto.
Once you add it all up,
though, it adds up to a lot.
The revenues are almost
10 percent less than
was actually received.
And this is every quarter,
for the last two years.
When I saw that, I got worried.
That's why I'm here.
So I checked Accounts Receivable
on other customers.
I found six other
instances
of revenues being
under-reported.
And I've only just started
to look into it.
Yes.
You know what the deal is?
Some of our clients
they overestimate their needs
for the next quarter,
and if I don't,
they'll go elsewhere.
Obviously, we forgot.
But the money's coming in.
Right, but...
I took a look at storage,
there's no backup for the
reported revenues at all,
I found Xeroxed copies
with the dates changed.
Let's talk plainly.
All right. You got me.
This is all upside down.
We're talking nearly
700 million pesos
of undocumented revenue.
Almost as much in dollars,
some 400 thousand there,
floating for all to see.
Cielo, I'm thinking
about saving this company.
I'm thinking about people's
jobs, not to mention my own.
It doesn't mean that you
have to break the law.
- Yes, it does!
- The Government can catch you
just like that.
Yes! I have to do something.
- That's what I'm doing.
- People go to prison for this.
My dad built this company
from nothing.
The people who work here
are like family.
I can't let that all
fall apart because
of a couple of bad years.
I can't do that.
That's why I'm telling you:
I need you to help me, please.
What are you saying?
Ernesto, I can't
get involved in this.
My firm would be backing
these numbers.
Forget it!
I'm sorry. No.
You are right, I'm sorry.
Okay?
Help me.
Hey, man,
this is Tripa.
Just checking in with you, man.
We missed you
at the funeral today.
The whole crew was representing.
Even Mono came all
the way down.
Everyone was all choked up
and shit.
And you should have seen
the coffin.
It was like this shiny,
white pearlescent.
I hope you are not mad at me
for leaving you hanging
with the job.
Watch your back out there, bro.
Peace.
I like to mix some ice with it.
I never did heroin.
What's it feel like?
There's a chill,
don't freak out.
It passes.
Ready? Come.
Where to?
Close your hand.
Hold it tight.
Ready?
I'll meet you there.
Guys, phones off, please.
All right, time's up.
Please, sign your exams
and hand them over,
and go to recess, please.
Thank you.
Close on your way out, please.
Yes!
Hi, Miss.
What can I do for you?
Where's the manager?
I'm the manager.
Can I help you?
I'm sorry,
there's some confusion.
I'm actually looking for the man
who was in charge yesterday.
He's... He's a tall man,
he was wearing a tie,
very proper.
No. That's the owner.
That's Mr. Gustavo.
That's who I'm looking for.
Uhmmm... He could be
at any one of his branches.
- How many are there?
- Fourteen.
Is there any way
I could get in touch with him?
I'm sorry, sir.
I can't give that out.
That's private information.
Sure, I understand.
- Thank you very much.
- You are welcome.
Seventeen kilos,
1,200,000 dollars
in Colombian pesos
at current change.
It will be in the Shooting
Range, near Soacha.
How long do I have?
It's about 40 kilometers
from here.
One hour.
You're in or out?
In. In. Absolutely.
But I just need a little
more time. I won't make it
in this traffic.
If you miss it,
don't ever show your face
in here again. One hour.
Jose Miguel, come on!
Where the fuck is he?
I need the product now!
I'm coming by.
My cell phone.
Ouch!
Jose Miguel!
Jose, open up!
Jose!
Jose, Jose!
Wake up, Jose!
Jose Miguel,
wake up, you moron!
Let go.
Wake up!
Where's the product?
In the kitchen.
Where?
Wake up, moron!
BABY IS COMING
No! Shit!
Not now!