- Walter!
- HI!
Leave me.
Cane. Cane.
My God.
Thank God you're here
to rescue me.
This Mother Teresa
can't leave me in peace.
- How are you?
- Hi, Walter.
- Let me.
- Are you ready?
Are you ready
to get some chicks?
Okay.
So that "Mineral show"
is just some sort of guy code
for strip club.
Is that your secret code?
She caught us.
Did your bring cash?
Those girls take no pennies.
Come on.
- Do I help you?
- No, don't worry.
Walter, don't let him
get too crazy.
If he gets home
with a giant geome...
Geode!
A giant geode,
we'll be sleeping in the garage.
Let me put the belt on.
- I can.
- Bye, María.
- Bye.
- OK.
- Bye, babe.
Be safe.
- Bye.
- Have fun!
- Thanks.
Longest week ever.
I just hope we get
something good, you know?
Keep your fingers crossed.
What's up?
Relax, buddy.
This isn't a dramatic movie,
one of those
that make you cry.
This is different.
Just think about the adventure
we'll get in.
An action movie.
Action. Adventure!
All right.
So you know
what you have to do, right?
Yes, the same as the other time,
but just the other way round.
Repeat it.
Come on.
I'll walk by Gustavo's car,
I bend down,
as though I'm tying my shoes,
I take the device, get in,
buy something and come back.
Fine, and then we go home,
download it on the computer
and see where this mother fucker
has been going.
Ready?
- Yes.
- Do it.
What happened?
Why didn't you go in?
I don't know, Henry.
I messed up.
- No.
- All this makes me nervous.
Yes, but this
might be suspicious.
Someone might be getting you
on camera.
What do I do?
Go and buy something?
No, no, no.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Here.
Well, let's see.
What the hell?
What is it?
That's work, that's home,
that's work, that's home.
that's work, that's ho--
He just went two places
every day all week?
It's unbelievable.
- Listen, Henry,
- Can't be.
Is it possible
that maybe, just maybe,
this is not your guy?
No, no, no.
A guy this clean
has got to be dirty
Right now we just have
to figure out
what's his play.
When he less expects it, we'll
catch him with the guard down.
Yes...
But how?
What?
Hello.
My name is Walter Blanco.
I live in Los Alcázares,
on the corner of 35th and 21st.
I want to report
some very strange movement.
It's been several days now,
but there's a man
staring at a particular house.
Yes.
No, no, no.
He's in a blue car.
Plates BXA 189.
He's tall, white skin,
light blue eyes.
I'm sure he's dangerous.
I'd really appreciate it
if you could send anyone
to arrest him.
Thank you.
Yes, I'll be alert.
Late, isn't it?
- Let's start.
- It's all set.
Really?
Can I have one?
- One what?
- A cigarette.
It's still in there, all right?
I didn't get a chance yet.
Give me one.
You shouldn't be smoking.
Don't worry.
I'm not interested in dying.
If you say so.
I'll do it.
What will you do?
I'll kill Gustavo.
Dude, I told you I'd do it
and I will.
Just give me some time.
It doesn't matter any more.
We're both dead men anyway.
Hi. Talk to me.
So Mr. I'm Almost 16
So Leave Me Alone
doesn't want a big thing
for his birthday.
He just wants to hang out
with his friends.
That's fine by me.
And you?
Fine by me too.
So...
I don't know...
Should we get him a car?
A car?
Yes, I know we've been
through that,
but it could be
something simpler.
The problem is not the car,
but the kind of car.
Yes.
Yes, I agree.
Well, I was thinking
about a used car,
but no more
than five years old.
It should be automatic
so that it's easier for him.
What do you think?
Does any car come to mind?
Or do I look for one?
OK, go on.
Fine. Good.
On another subject,
the business is doing good.
Very good.
So good that...
Maybe you won't need
your second job anymore.
Really?
We're having profits?
We're almost there.
In a month, two top.
I'm just saying this
because maybe you cold start
looking for...
an exit strategy.
Yes, I'm working on it.
Perfect.
That's good.
So...
Bye.
Hello?
Hey, buddy!
Did I wake you up¿
No, no, no. Don't worry.
I was awake already.
Look, I don't want
to waste your time,
but I've been thinking
about Gustavo Cortés.
This thing about him going
home, one restaurant, right?
He comes and goes every day.
Well, just let me tell you
that's bullshit.
The man owns
other 13 restaurants
of Los Pollos Hermanos,
a total of 14.
So he didn't go
to any of those restaurants
these days?
Who supplies them?
Doesn't he go to the plant
or factory
where they produce the chicken?
I've been looking into this
and outside of Bogotá
there's a plant
of Los Pollos Hermanos.
I'm looking at the pictures
online right now
and this place is enormous.
This place is so big
that there could easily be
a meth lab.
So what do you think?
What do you say?
Do we go on another field trip?
I'll take the sandwiches
and the beers. What do you say?
Yes, Henry, that sounds great.
The thing is...
Look, I won't lie to you.
You caught me
somewhat indisposed.
What do you mean?
Like taking a dump indisposed?
Why don't people just say:
"I have diarrhea"?
Just say it!
"I have diarrhea."
Must be a burrito
I ate yesterday.
I can't find
any other explanation.
I didn't eat anything else...
But I'm really sick.
I'm...
Don't worry.
You don't need
to go into details.
You're right.
Probably one guy in a diaper
is enough for this trip anyway.
I'm sorry.
I'd have really liked--
No, don't worry, dude.
Don't be.
I've been asking a lot of you
lately.
I'll find another ride
for this one.
Another ride?
My trainer, for instance.
He can help me.
I'm sure he'll help me.
Don't worry.
No, no. Henry, look...
You know what?
I think in 24 hours,
24 hours top,
I'll be fine.
Buddy, the thing is
you know what this is like.
- This has to be--
- Henry, just wait.
I'd really love to go with you
because I'm trapped
by this story
and I don't want to miss
a single detail.
You get me?
Well, I really appreciate it.
I won't break your heart.
So let's do this.
Just call me
when you feel better.
Yes, yes, yes.
I will.
I'll call you.
Thank you!
- Hello?
- Mario...
Mario, I just want to say,
first off, don't be angry.
What is it, Walter?
My brother-in-law
will soon probably visit
certain distribution center,
you know what I mean?
He wants to look around
for things
and you and I know--
Hello?
Mario?
Mario!
Move.
Pick all that up.
Secure them tightly
so that they don't fall.
Put them
at the same distance.
Clean it. Clean it.
It has to look impeccable.
Mario,
what's all this going on?
Stop asking so many questions.
I told you
to put all that in order.
Here are the keys.
- The boy will give you the car.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Come back soon.
Yes, sir.
Today we washed
the rugs in the black van.
Perfect!
But vans are more expensive
and it was a special wash.
We washed the engine.
Sir, thank you.
Take this.
The boy
will give you your car.
Hi.
Someone from the office
said you worked here,
so I thought to come and say hi.
Hi then.
You look great.
No. You look...
I probably look crazed.
Happy.
Last time we met
you were...
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
I know.
I need to talk to you.
Wait a second.
Hi. How are you?
Let's see.
Yes, sir.
Your car is ready.
Fifty thousand pesos.
These are your car keys.
The boy over there
will give it to you. Thanks.
I need to talk to you.
Ernesto,
I don't mean to be rude
but I don't really think
we have anything to talk about.
Actually, we do.
An audit?
Tomorrow?
Ernesto, how long
have you had this?
A while. I didn't know
whether to contact you or not.
Why me?
Why don't you get a lawyer?
They're accusing you
of tax evasion,
and you can go to prison.
Yes.
They're sending you to prison.
Cielo, I was thinking...
Maybe you could help me.
ME? How could I help you?
You know the books,
the moves inside the company.
You want me to uncook
your books?
No, no, no.
I don't want you to uncook
the books,
but see if there's something
you can do.
No, no, Ernesto!
You have to understand!
It doesn't work like that.
The damage is done.
My name and my signature
are there.
I'm responsible for this, Cielo.
Not you.
No, no. Let me explain
what's going to happen.
Once the Tax Department
discovers this fraud,
they'll ask for an investigation
and they'll build the strongest
possible cause against you.
You have an 80% chance
of going to trial and sentenced.
They'll monitor your calls,
your mails, and not just you.
Everyone involved
in those books.
God.
- No, no. You know what?
I don't have time now.
I can't be investigated now,
much less have an audit.
Look, you'll be all right.
They're after me.
I'm the captain they want,
not some cashier
at a car wash.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to figure out
a way through this.
Don't worry.
Look, there. There.
Here?
So then?
Is he going to kill him?
Who's going to kill who?
Gustavo.
Mr. Blanco's brother-in-law.
He's the reason
for all this right here.
Because it's totally logical
for him to off the dude.
Nobody likes a cop
getting in your place.
Especially if he's
from anti narcotics.
It'd make sense
if he wanted to put an end
to that problem.
But killing a cop...
I don't know.
If the guy who's investigating
you is suddenly murdered,
then you'd be a suspect.
Not to mention Mr. Blanco.
He'd get totally nuts
if they killed his family.
He'd be totally furious.
He'd never cook
for Gustavo again.
Never again.
Guess there're a lot of angles
to consider.
And if anything happened to him,
would you have a problem
with that?
Who cares what I think?
- You get comfortable, kid.
- Son of a bitch!
Stay here.
I'll be right back.
Son of a bitch.
Get down!
No.
Let's go.
Hello?
Tell them the answer is...
yes.
Coming!
Should I even ask?
What for?
I wouldn't.
Is this going to be
a regular thing now?
Meth cooking
and corpse disposal?
Grab us a barrel, Walter.
What was it this time?
What did this poor bastard do
to piss off Gustavo?
No, wait.
Did Gustavo just need to send
another message?
Shut your mouth.
I don't want you talking
to me or José.
Just get the barrel.
If you plan on calling the cops
on one of my guys again,
you go ahead and get two
barrels.
And here again.
Unreported income.
That's more than a year straight
so far.
Do you want to say something
about this?
Because I'm having a hard time
figuring out.
Yes, sure.
I'd have to have a look
at the copies of the receipts
to refresh my memory.
Take all the time you need,
Mr. Silva.
That's why were here.
To clear out
all inconsistencies.
Thanks.
Hello, hello.
I'm sorry I'm late.
Traffic was terrible.
And this building
is so confusing.
There're doors everywhere.
Let's see.
I'll sit over here.
- Hi, Ernesto.
- Hi, Cielo.
And you are?
Fiscal detective Jaime Betancur.
You're a detective!
Wow! Pleased to meet you.
Cielo Restrepo.
Mrs. Cielo,
As far as I can see,
you're the accountant
who signed these reports.
Yes. I'm guilty.
Perhaps you can shed some light
on this history
of missing revenue.
Missing?
No, no, it's all there.
No. It's not in the records
nor on the reports.
That's weird.
Let's take a look.
Look at this one.
Ferreterías Don Fabio.
Mr. Fabio is a close friend
of Ernesto's father.
They've been friends forever.
Mr. Fabio always sent us
an electronic payment,
which I hate
because I'm a paper person.
But he said he was one
of those environment people.
Since there wasn't
a physical check,
I didn't enter it into the book,
but the money's there.
Madam, are you aware
of this country's taxation laws?
What do you mean?
How gross income for a business
id defined.
You can't do this.
Yes, I can.
No, no, no.
Fine, don't worry.
You know what they say
about opinions.
Everyone's got one.
You have to respect opinions.
One should be tolerant.
If its an electronic check
or a paper check,
income is income.
You're not allowed
to not declare it.
When I input everything
into the computer
nothing flashed red,
That has to mean
it's all right.
What program
did you use for this?
Some home software,
just like everyone does.
You used a home software
to manage books
for a business like this?
Yes, it's so easy.
It's like having
a giant calculator
on your computer.
Excuse me, madam
I'll ask you
sort of a personal question.
Anything you want.
How did you get this job?
- Ernesto hired me.
- Yes.
I guess you have qualifications.
Where did you study?
Well, I didn't have a training
per se. No degree or diploma.
No, I don't have one.
But I've always been
naturally good for numbers.
- Yes.
- Right?
Very good.
All right...
I can see why this is this way.
One last questions.
You're not managing accounts
anywhere else, are you?
Right now?
No.
I'm a cashier
at a car wash.
Okay.
Fine.
Let's move on.
Pay back taxes,
pay the penalties,
and don't get
in any other legal trouble.
Just move on from here.
Cielo, I don't have
a single cent.
I can't pay for this.
I have no resources.
Just figure it out.
You've just dodged prison.
I know.
Well, then just do something.
Sell your house,
your car, anything.
No.
My house
is under mortgage.
I have no assets.
I have nothing to sell.
I can't.
Please, Ernesto.
If you don't pay taxes, they'll
reopen the investigation.
And that little fiction
I just spun up there
will completely unravel.
You have to pay.
Good night.
Come in.
You want to help me?
I rather watch.
You don't like cooking?
It's not my stuff.
So how do you cook
at home?
Delivery.
You'll now see the difference
between delivery
and home-made food.
- Are you hungry?
- A little bit.
Well, I think
we'll have to wait.
It still needs to get cooked.
Be patient.
Hum.
Mario told me
you had some questions for me.
Yes.
But I like to concentrate
when I cook.
If not, I can confuse
the ingredients
and change the flavor
of what I'm doing.
I see.
Wait outside.
You don't want to cut yourself.
What am I doing here, Gustavo?
I can understand your concern.
What happened yesterday
was terrible.
You mean the dude
who got his head blown off?
Yes, that was terrible.
I invited you home
and cooked for you.
I want to discuss the business.
Like men.
I'll explain everything
that's happening.
I'll answer your questions.
But first, I need you to answer
one question for me.
What?
Can you cook
Walter Blanco's formula?
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Can you cook Walter Blanco's
meth formula on your own?
With no help?
Why are you asking me that?
You ask me if I can cook
Mr. Blanco's formula on my own?
Without him?
Me?
The junkie loser
you almost killed a month ago?
Is that your master plan,
Gustavo?
Invite me to your house
and cook
whatever this shit is.
Be my buddy, make me
feel important, what for?
So that I cook on my own
so that you can kill Mr. Blanco?
Is that what you want?
You want us
to talk like men?
Let's talk like men then.
If you kill Mr. Blanco,
you'll have to kill me too.
Did you get that?
That's not why I asked you.
You're here because
circumstances with the cartel
are untenable.
And I need your help.
I need you to help me
prevent a war.
That's why I need an answer.
Please.
Hey.
I need to talk to you.
I don't know if you're
with your family
but this is important,
so I hope you can come.
- Thank God you're here.
- What's up?
You want a beer or something?
- No, no, no.
- Come, sit.
Well...
This is the thing.
Word has come down that they
want me to go to Mexico.
There's some sort of war
brewing between Gustavo
and the cartel.
"Word has come down"?
Yes, the cartel has been messing
with Gustavo's operation.
The other day
they jacked a truck
to sort of send a message.
Gustavo has been
holding them off,
but between the cartel
taking put shots
and your brother-in-law
trying to throw a net over this,
it's like a rock
and a hard place situation.
So the business
will get out of control.
Gustavo has to give in.
The cartel wants half
of Gustavo's entire operation.
But not just that.
They want your formula
and Gustavo
is giving it to them.
- Good.
- I mean, not Gustavo,
I have to give it to them.
I'm supposed to go to Mexico
and teach some cartel chemists
how to cook
a batch of blue meth.
Gustavo doesn't trust you,
so I have to go.
You know what the problem is?
That you're a chemist.
I'm not.
I'm not a chemist
I don't know what to do.
Mr. Blanco, I need your help.
I was thinking
that maybe you can coach me,
give me some notes,
some advice.
I can study that
and learn.
So you saw Gustavo?
What?
- No, I didn't see Gustavo.
- No? You didn't see him?
Then who told you all of that?
It's just rumors.
- Rumors from whom?
- Yes.
From people. Mario, Mosquera,
all those guys.
So you never met Gustavo,
didn't talk to him,
didn't see him.
Why? Why Gustavo?
You weren't with Gustavo
last night?
What?
What are you--?
It's still here.
Just as I supposed!
Look at me in the eye
and tell me you weren't
with Gustavo last night.
- I didn't have time,
couldn't find the moment.
- "I didn't have time".
I didn't have time.
That's why I didn't tell you.
I knew you would get nuts
and not believe me.
What did you expect me to do?
There was just
one big pot of soup.
And we both ate from it.
Was I supposed
to poison myself too?
You were with him
for two hours and 18 minutes
- and you couldn't find
a way to do it.
- He never left me alone.
- Liar!
- I was never alone!
Don't be such a liar!
One thing, José.
Just one thing.
You just had to do one thing
to save our asses.
You were at his house
and you didn't do it.
Two hours and 18 minutes?
You never had any intention
of killing him, did you?
How do you know
I was there last night?
Are you following me?
This.
From 19.10 to 21.28.
Two hours and 18 minutes.
- You bugged my car?
- You didn't even try it!
You didn't even make
the slightest try!
You're following me, right?
After all I've done for you?
Excuse me?
You put me a bug?
You know what you did?
You killed me!
You've signed
my death warrant.
A bug...
I'll you some advice.
Go to Mexico. Go.
Go and screw up
like I know you will.
I don't care.
I hope you'll end up
wind up in a barrel somewhere.
Son of a bitch!
Can you walk?
Yes.
You get the fuck out of here
and never come back.