Hurry, princess.
Give me that!!
Give me the money!
- Motherfucker! The money!
- Asshole!
What? What is it, love?
What? Tell me.
Beautiful princess.
Yes.
Thanks.
Done.
Ready!
Are you okay?
I'm fine!
So, Saturday 9 a.m. then?
Yes, dad. 9 a.m.
Great.
Dad, can you do me a favor and
pick me up half an hour earlier?
Yes, sure.
I'll be here 8:30.
Great.
Hey, hey.
Congratulations.
You're doing great.
Thanks.
It's okay.
See you.
Hi.
Hi, how was your day?
Fine, fine.
Do you have a minute?
Yes, sure.
Can you keep an eye
on your sister
while I talk with your dad?
Behave yourself!
Sure.
Have you thought
about what we discussed?
"Thought"
meaning reconsidered?
No. No.
What's the problem?
What's the flaw you see here?
It's not a flaw.
Cielo.
Flaws.
Plural.
Where do you want me to start?
Walter...
...I don't love
this situation we're in.
But here I am.
We've got to find
the best option possible.
We've got the story.
We start
with the gambling thing.
We've got the money,
the startup capital
to invest it in the car wash.
You know the business.
You've worked there.
And you hire your wife
as a bookkeeper.
And why?
Guess.
Your wife is actually a
bookkeeper.
Anyone would believe that story.
Now, tell me,
what am I am missing?
Look, you don't understand this.
You just get the money
and look the other way.
Pretend you don't know anything.
Listen, if I ever get caught,
God forbid,
it would be much easier for you
to deny everything.
Walter!
My estranged husband
who works as a teacher
and barely
makes ends meet,
all of a sudden,
starts shoveling
money at me.
And when the police
questions me, I'll just say:
"No, I didn't think
anything weird was going on."
Really?
Is that plausible deniability?
Walter!
Come on! The car wash
is the best option
to get out of this situation.
Which already sucks,
and can get worse!
Okay, fine.
However, your argument
has a flaw.
Why?
Tell me.
Why your estranged husband
would do that for you
all of a sudden, why?
Because he loves his family
above everything else.
And he'll do anything
to get his wife back,
even if it's impossible.
And knowing him as I do,
he'd try anything.
Yes.
There's still a flaw.
It'd be much more plausible
if the husband
were no longer estranged.
Let's say, if suddenly,
he has the chance to sleep
in his own bed again.
This has turned
into a fictional story.
Well, no.
Okay, okay, I admit it.
But...
I want to have dinner
here
every night.
Every night? No. No.
Fine. Six nights a week.
You get a night fee.
Two! Not weekends!
And you give me a day's notice.
No! Five
nights, with no
notice.
Three nights.
Six hours' notice.
Five, two hours' notice.
Four. Don't insist.
Fine, fine.
And I want the keys
to the house.
No.
Yes! Yes!
Cielo, for emergencies.
I don't know, appearances.
I don't care.
I want to see my
daughter.
I want to help Junior
with his homework.
I want to be part
of this family again.
And that's my condition
to agree to your
fiction.
Professor.
I was thinking that...
...when we're done here
we could go for beers.
No, thanks.
Maybe some other time.
No, listen.
Professor...
I think we should do it today.
So?
What are you doing, moron?
Why did you bring this here?
That's the product we cook,
right?
Take a look at it and tell me.
It's ours.
Put that away!
Where did you take it from?
The lab?
No.
I bought it from the guys
who killed Gordo.
Well, the guys who ordered it.
Those motherfuckers
are selling our product.
That means they're working
for the same man we are, right?
Not necessarily.
They could be reselling it.
Can you prove it?
Look, you shouldn't jump
to conclusions.
I heard it
from the sister of the kid
who killed Gordo.
And yes, you heard me.
I said kid.
Tomás Cantillo.
An 11 year old kid
was the one who received orders
to kill Gordo.
These two scumbags,
they got him dealing.
They use kids, man!
Why not?
They are easy to fool.
Easy to manipulate.
And if anything happens,
easy, they take them to rehab.
They get out right away.
And they go back doing
the same they were doing before.
Those motherfuckers
recruit them
when they're young
to have their loyalty
for ever, man.
Those men killed Gordo!
They manipulated a kid
and got my friend killed, man.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I need your help.
How?
I need ricin.
Are you poisoning people now?
Walter, these men...
Listen to me.
No!
These men have to go.
I've planned everything.
No.
Walter.
Listen, the only thing
I need from you
is the poison.
I thought
of the delivery, everything.
I said no.
Walter.
Please.
You won't have to lift a finger.
I guarantee that. I do.
Listen to yourself, goddamn it!
You don't even know
what you're talking about.
Those two men must go.
This is what we have to do.
This world would be
a better place without them.
I'm not even talking about that.
Listen.
I know an old woman
who buys drugs
from these two, okay?
She sees them
at lest once or twice a week.
She gives them food.
She indulges them,
gives them hamburgers.
And she gets a discount
on her crystal. It's perfect!
That's my delivery method.
The best thing is
I don't have to be there.
I can be miles away
just checking
everything's perfect.
Get it?
That's worse.
You're trusting a meth-head?
Yes, man.
A meth-head who stood up
to your brother in law,
don't forget it.
He questioned her for five hours
and the woman...
didn't give it up.
How do I know this?
Because you and I
are sitting here
and not rotting in jail.
I'll rot in jail.
In jail or some place worse.
And with you!
This is a ridiculous idea.
Completely ridiculous.
Ridiculous?
Ridiculous.
So, you're already assuming
this won't work?
It was a good idea
when you came up with it
and now it's not a good idea
any more?
You came up with
that plan to kill Tuco, man.
You said it yourself:
"The man eats the ricin
and in two or three days
he gets sick,
a heart attack and he's gone.
And there's no way
they track it back to us."
Walter,
they won't track it back to me.
Not even that other scumbag
we work for
is going to ever figure it out.
It was a good plan for Tuco
and it's a good plan now.
Tuco
wanted to kill us.
These guys don't!
Honestly,
do I really need
to explain you the difference?
Gordo
was one of us, man.
He was one of us.
That means nothing to you,
right?
Tell me something.
Why didn't you track them
three months ago?
Because I just found out
about this.
Really?
And what did you find out?
Genius! That is was
a dispute over turf?
That's absolutely obvious,
right?
Wouldn't have been easier
three months ago
when it happened?
Why didn't you do it then?
Shall I tell you why?
Because at the time
you was too high
feeling sorry
for just anything.
So, why now,
after all this time?
Being a murderer is part
of your 12 steps program
in rehab?
Jose, please.
This is not about blame
and make amends, man.
This idea is pointless!
What do you want
to get with this?
You know what?
If you don't see
what I want to get,
there's no point in trying
to explain it to you.
Listen, Jose.
You're no murderer.
Neither am I.
We're no murders.
Jose.
You know what, man?
I'm doing this.
With or without you.
But I'm doing it.
The hell I am.
So, who's turn is it
to steal one?
Mine.
Listen, María...
two hours to steal a letter?
No, but I'm organizing my cards.
Bummer.
Diamonds Queen.
I got a trio.
María, you can't say
what you've got.
Why not? That depends
on the player, Henry.
It's the rule, María.
Fine, I'm winning anyway.
Not so fast, aunt.
Look.
Why?
Eight, nine,
Joker, Queen, King.
Straight Flush?
This moron won
three times in a row.
You've been practicing with dad
or what?
No.
No, why?
And your dad, how's he doing?
Is he still teaching?
No, nothing. My mom nor my dad
are working now.
No?
What are they doing then?
Junior, did you know
uncle Henry was released?
He can go back home
whenever he wants now.
Yes? Great!
Yes.
No, it's not advisable yet.
Henry, don't give me that look.
I didn't say anything wrong.
I'm simply repeating what the
doctors said.
Yes? And why did the doctors
say that?
Because they need the room.
To change the sheets
and accommodate the next
cripple.
What for?
To get more, kat-ching, money!
Uncle, you look okay to me.
You're feeling better?
Yes? Do I look okay?
Are all of you
in this together or what?
No, my God.
Do you think I'm okay?
I'm shitting my pants every day.
Henry...
- I'm peeing in pitchers.
And apart from that,
I can't move my legs.
I can't walk.
So? Is that being okay for you?
Uncle, so people in wheelchairs
should be in hospitals?
What about people on crutches?
So, make me some room there.
Make me some room!
Is that what you mean?
I'm sorry.
- Okay, deal there.
- I'll do it.
Give me that.
You know I charge by the hour,
right?
He promised he'd be here.
He promised?
So, let's keep waiting,
no problem.
No, I meant it, Walter.
He won't come!
I mean it, he won't come!
Let's forget it.
Any plan B?
No, Saúl. There isn't.
So, let's do some brainstorming.
How about that?
Are you sure he was serious?
Why do you think I'm here?
Judging by the way
he talked to me,
I guess he's doing it.
Or at least he'll try!
Perfect, so we pay him off.
Period.
No, this is not about the money.
Saúl, we need to find the way
to get him off the streets,
getting him to calm down.
Maybe.
I don't know, Saúl.
You can do something.
Why don't...?
Why don't you get him arrested?
You want your partner in jail?
I know!
I know it sounds risky.
But that's it, I don't know,
less dangerous
than him making something stupid
which jeopardize the business
eventually.
Kind of a minor offense,
let's say.
"Minor offense!"
Rosas in jail, I don't know.
I don't think so.
It's not advisable.
Fine, no jail, then. Fine.
What about something like
having him doing community work.
That kind of thing.
No! He's not a minor.
He'll go straight to jail.
I don't know, Saúl.
There has to be a way
to get him off the streets
till he calms down
so we can move on!
Well, I'm guess
home arrest could work.
So, there is a chance?
Sure! That's included
in my Premium Services Package.
But thanks God
you can afford that.
You can afford almost anything.
Don't worry.
I'll call my private
investigator.
Home arrest. Sure.
Guendy.
Do you understand
what you've got to do?
See, you can't tell
no one about this. Ever!
Never ever. Got it?
Yes.
See, I read on line
that this thing takes
three days to kick in.
You only thing you've got to do
is never tell anyone about this.
Just be silent.
If you do that, I swear
there won't be consequences
for you or me, okay?
Guendy, do you agree?
You picture this
as what you always do.
The only thing you've got to do
is taking them the hamburgers
like any other day, that's it.
It's not just
like any other day. Because
we're not talking
about just delivering food.
Guendy, you have a son, right?
- Yeison.
A handsome kids?
Well, see.
Just picture
that these men
have Yeison working for them.
Working as a mule.
And they make him kill people.
Wouldn't you do anything
to protect your kid?
Of course, I'd do anything
to protect him.
Exactly.
Well, these men
have kids working for them.
They take advantage of them.
They have them working.
We should take care
of these scumbags?
Don't you
think?
Yeah, right?
Fine.
Very well.
Yes, Guendy?
So, we'll do it tomorrow, right?
- Yes, yes.
- Don't back out.
Done. I'll be back.
How are you?
Will give me a second?
Yes? I won't take long.
What are you doing here?
If you need me, call me.
What we need to talk about
can't be talked over the phone,
Walter.
Aren't you inviting me in, man?
She's a beauty!
Tell me what you need, Mario.
Take a seat, man.
I've been talking with Saúl
about your plan for Rosas.
- So?
- I'm not doing it.
Why not?
Basically, because it's stupid.
Saúl told me
you've done it before.
That's not the point.
What's the point?
The boss won't like it.
Saúl?
Your boss, who's my boss too.
Look, take it
as professional courtesy.
No one knows I'm here.
The boss will find out.
If Rosas were arrested,
I'm sure he'll see it
as a problem.
A big one.
Walter, I mean it.
You've got
a very good thing going.
In fact, we both have.
Things are going well.
Think about it.
Is it worth to risk it all
on one junkie?
I do realize you two
have a story and all.
But this kid's been
on the bubble a while now.
This isn't new.
- Don't you see it?
- What?
I used to be a cop
many years ago.
I saw it all.
Stickups,
domestic violence,
street fights.
Anyway.
Every scumbag you can think of.
At the time I knew
a guy I'll never forget.
Pacheco.
He was huge.
I guess he weighted
about 240 pounds.
And his wife was small.
Thin. Like a bird.
Well,
the thing is my partner and I
get called out to the house
every weekend
to save that poor woman.
We'd get there, pull her aside
and tell her:
"Come on, do it,
press charges
against this beast
and get rid of him once for all.
But no.
This wasn't one of those setups:
"Deep down
he loves me."
That excuse
is still widely used.
But not this one.
Where are you getting at?
Well, that woman
looked pretty scared.
She'd shiver with fear.
But she didn't have the guts
to report him.
And there's nothing else
we could do.
The only thing
we could do was
putting him in a car,
taking him for a ride,
and then to the police station.
Then, the next day,
out he went,
as if nothing had happened.
He'd get drunk again,
and went back home to beat her.
It was like a vicious cycle.
One day, my partner
was out sick
and I went there alone.
The same fucking call.
I handcuffed the man
and took him with me.
But that day was different.
When we were in the car,
that asshole was singing.
And that made me really mad.
So, instead of taking him
to the station,
I took him to an ally I knew
and was good
for what I wanted to do.
I got him off the car,
down on his knees,
and the gun in his mouth.
"This is it."
He started weeping,
he peed his pants.
With the gun still in his mouth
he was yelling,
swearing he'd never do it again,
he'd leave her alone.
I told him to shut up
because I need to think
what I was going to do with him.
Of course, he was silent.
He stayed there, in silence,
not even a word.
He looked like a street dog
waiting for leftovers.
Then, we simply stayed there.
I pretended to be considering
what to do with him.
And he was there,
kneeling on mud.
Shaking.
I waited for a while,
took the gun out of his mouth,
and told him:
"God help you,
because if you ever
touch her again,
you won't imagine,
I'll do this
and that, and also that."
A warning?
Sure.
At the time, I thought
I was doing the right thing.
Two weeks later, he killed her.
He broke her head
with a mixer.
When we got there,
there was so much blood,
it was slippery.
I'll never forget
the smell in that house.
The moral of the story
is that I took a half measure.
When I should have
gone all the way.
I'll never make
that mistake again.
Listen to me, Walter.
No half measures.
I don't get it.
I'm only seeing the kid.
Where are the men, Guendy?
I don't know.
They are always there.
Burgers are getting cold.
Are you sure this is fast?
Yes, Guendy.
Don't you worry.
Act normal, okay?
Nobody's gonna know anything.
Relax.
Can I have another bump?
No, I gave you
what you needed already.
When this is done, I'll give you
all you want, okay?
Where are these guys?
Walk, motherfucker!
What happened?
You get lost! Out of here!
Where are we going, man?
Take a seat.
I understand you have a problem
with two of my men.
It is true that they killed
one of your associates.
It is possible
they acted rashly.
But, on the other hand,
there was provocation.
The man was selling
on their territory.
There is blame on both sides.
This will go no further.
It will be settled right here,
right now.
You told him, right?
Damn it!
Now, listen to me.
You have one friend here.
This man.
Those men who just left
are my employees.
And I fully trust them.
When I learned about your plans,
if it wasn't for this man,
and the respect I have for him,
I surely would be dealing
with this
in a very different way.
You don't look at him.
You look at me!
I'll tell what will happen now.
My men will come back inside.
You'll shake hands.
You'll make peace.
And that will be all.
The end of this.
- No.
- Jose.
Excuse me?
They use kids, man!
Those assholes you hired
have an 11 year old kid
killing for them.
You're supposed to be some kind
of a reasonable businessman.
This is how you do business?
And you, what?
Are you okay with this?
You got nothing to say here?
Bring them back.
No more kids.
Got it?
And you,
you keep the peace.
Say it.
I'll keep the peace.
Now, shake hands.
Listen, María.
Why don't you let the people
who get paid to do this
do this?
Because the people who get paid
to do this
do a lousy job.
- Ay.
- Henry, relax.
This is what you want?
Just lying in a hospital bed
getting sponge baths
from nurses.
Listen, María.
Henry, it's time to go home.
How many times
I have to tell you
I'm not going nowhere
till I get better, María?
Hey, hey!
- What are you doing?
- I'm just seeing.
- Seeing what?
- What I'm seeing.
- Listen, María.
- Don't move! Careful!
Hey, hey, what are
you doing?
- María, please.
- Relax.
I'm not at my best
here, Marie.
I think you are.
María, I'm in bed.
There's a reason why
I'm in bed.
You're wasting your
time,
I mean it.
María, what if someone
comes in?
I don't care
if someone walks in.
They can look.
What's into you?
Let's do this:
If it shows up to say hello...
That won't happen.
Get your hand out of there.
I bet it will.
If it will, we go home.
Let's see.
I'm not going to bet...
on whether I can get a boner
or no, okay?
- So, no betting.
- Why? Are you afraid or what?
María, what's wrong with you?
You're being foolish, you know?
Tell me, what's the point
of all this?
Well, I'm trying to prove
you're not as dysfunctional
as you say.
So? Bet on it?
- Fine, let's bet.
- Okay.
- You got one minute.
- One minute?
That's more than enough
for me.
Let's
see.
This is just sad.
Honestly.
Bad day?
I don't even know.
Anyway.
It's better now.
Tell them you're busy.
Okay?
Hello?
Hello, mom.
Mom, slow down. I can't--
Mom...
Mom, what is--?
No!
No, no!
God, no!
What happened?
Tomás!
They killed him!
No! No!
No!
Hi.
I'm not available.
Leave a
message. Jose.
You're 42 minutes late.
I'm starting without you.
Welcome, lovely audience!
We're back once more
with our last two contestants!
Let's see
if they're the winning couple
of words per second.
So, get ready.
- Dinner is almost ready.
- What noun...?
- Coming!
- Ten million pesos!
- That guy is very good!
- The hint is, one word
of seven letters.
"A loud cry".
Be right back.
My dear contestants, remember
- I'll go to the toilet.
- ...words per second.
And the clock is ticking!
Hi.
I'm not available.
Leave a message.
Hello.
Jose, it's me.
Look
I hope you're not waiting
for an apology
because I did not rat you out.
On the contrary
I was looking out
for your best interests,
as well as my own.
I stand by my decision
100 percent.
So...
Well, at least
I hope we can agree
to disagree
Anyway...
Call me as soon as you can.
... manufacturing
and dealing of drugs
and it was proved
the accused has sent...
Aren't you turning the TV off?
No, no, no, don't worry.
I do it.
And the local news now...
The murder of a kid
in the South area
has outraged the whole
community.
The police have yet
to release an official statement
but sources indicate
that Tomás Cantillo,
an 11 year old kid
was victim of an execution
related to the gang
who operates in the area.
- An anonymous caller
alerted...
- Will you turn it off, please?
...the authorities
and took the police to the place
- ...of this tragedy.
- Walter!
- Coming.
They couldn't save the kid.
And that makes
another boy victim
to what seems to be
the struggle for territory of--
Well, I'll serve your dad.
I'm sorry,
but that story
has been on the news all day
and it's just.
- I'm moved.
- Yes.
Honey,
we wanted to tell you
that your dad and I are thinking
of starting a business together.
Really?
Yes.
A car wash.
Like the place you used to work?
- Exactly.
- Yes.
I've got to go.
Can I borrow your car?
Yes, yes.
See how useful is having a car?
Please, I'm really sorry.
Get lost!