- Good morning.
Hello.
You're not thinking
of going to work today, are you?
Yes.
You should take
the rest of the week.
I'm fine.
That inhaler
seems to be doing the trick.
Yes, honey.
But you shouldn't push it.
I want you well
for the weekend.
Mom wants to party.
It's just a little get-together.
Just the family
and a few friends.
We've got a lot to celebrate.
Don't you think?
Yes, sure. Sounds good.
Walter.
- Do you want something else?
- No, I'm fine.
What are you doing today?
Nothing.
You changed your mind.
Yes.
If you take a good nap,
you'll have your reward tonight.
Have a nice day.
Thanks.
Are you busy?
Can we meet?
I actually thought
you were gone for good.
I mean,
that you have passed away.
I was even checking the obits.
No such luck.
So how are you?
Are you still coughing up blood
and saying you don't deserve it,
and you're an asshole?
A little bit of both.
I still think the same
about me.
And the cough
is there.
What did the doctor say?
Which are the studies results?
- Radiation pneumonitis.
Shit.
Actually, it isn't as bad
as it sounds.
- Yes, sure.
- Really.
It's part of the process.
The treatment is simple.
These are mild side
effects.
And the cancer?
There's good news.
Is it what I'm imagining?
The tumor isn't smaller,
is it?
Yes, it is smaller.
Really?
I'm not cured,
but there's been a significant
size reduction.
I know you aren't cured,
but how significant
is the reduction?
Eighty percent.
Eighty percent?
That's a lot!
It's like three quarters.
No.
Three quarters would
be 75 percent.
So it's a little bit more.
Even better!
Cancer is still there,
but I have options now.
That's the word they used
"options."
It's great, man!
I know you aren't an optimist.
But you have
plenty to celebrate.
I know why I'm saying it.
I rather be prudent.
My grandmother
didn't even make it
to the phase you are now.
We never thought
that the tumor
could be reduced.
In my case, it's smaller.
Unbelievable.
But I have to admit it.
It's much smaller now.
You did it, man!
You should be celebrating!
Let's have some brandy.
Easy, easy.
Now what?
No, no,
hold on, hold on.
That's your part
from the selling
of the production
while you weren't here.
Do we still have
stock?
Yes, we do.
But it won't last much.
- It sells like hotcakes.
- Great.
Considering this big news,
what are we going to do?
I don't want you to think
I'm pushing you.
Not at all, but--
Yes, yes. I know.
I think
we should stay cautious.
Let's sell off what we have.
Then, we'll...
Say it, man.
Don't worry.
Jose, you know
I got into this
because I was dying,
because I was very bad.
I had nothing
to leave to my family.
You aren't dying now, are you?
I hope so.
I think it would be
very irresponsible
if we stay in
this business,
which is too risky.
Circumstances have changed.
You know you may disappear
in this business overnight.
Then, you're saying
you made up your mind.
I think it's the best.
Let's sell what we have,
and we're done.
The first thing they do
is to cool the glasses.
Then, they add
some salt here
to improve the taste.
Look! It's done!
- How...?
- The salt...
Sorry to interrupt.
Can I make a toast
with a non-alcoholic beverage?
If you're carrying
quintuplets, you can.
Let's make a toast, then.
I know one party
can't begin to repay
all the love and support
you've given us.
Therefore,
we have a bartender
who came from Mexico.
Bravo!
He learnt to prepare margaritas.
If there's sadness,
fill up your glass.
In case of happiness...
- Your glass fill up!
Okay!
I really want to thank you,
all of you.
These last few months
have been... hard
to put it mildly.
Walter has come through it
like a champ.
Honey, I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
We all are.
For the first time,
we look at the future
optimistically.
I want to thank two persons
who couldn't be here today.
They are Edgar and Marcela.
For those of you
who don't know them,
they're very generous people.
They paid
for Walter's treatment.
Without them,
I don't know
what we'd have done.
They're our angels.
To Edgar and Marcela.
- Cheers!
We want to hear the king!
Tell your father!
Come on, Dad. Speech.
I'm not good at this.
Come on!
Well, what can I say?
When I got my diagnosis,
the first thing I thought
was "Why me?"
Now that I got the good news
that I'm much better
that I'm getting better
every day,
I wonder the same thing:
Why me?
Thank you for coming.
Cheers!
Those were inspiring
words.
He's as cold
as ice.
I have to admit it.
They are original.
Pay attention:
They made a mercury switch bomb,
add it a 9-volt battery,
and use
less than eight ounces of C-4.
And there's more.
They take the man's head,
and put it on a turtle.
Don't say they aren't original.
Why a turtle, uncle?
That's the best part.
They use the turtle
as... not a metaphor,
not an analogy either.
What's the word
I'm looking for, Walter?
Well, whatever.
The point
is that the man we had there,
our snitch,
was called Tortuga or Turtle.
I don't know why.
He resembled a mandrill
more than a turtle.
That was
the beginning of everything.
Can I have one?
I know what the word
I've been looking for is.
Poetic!
They use the turtle
in a poetic manner.
Do you understand?
Cheers!
Come on, drink it.
Wait until your mother
doesn't see you.
Drink it, drink it.
No, uncle.
It's too bitter.
Let me see.
He's growing a beard.
You have some down here.
It was about time
you became a man.
No, uncle.
Uncle,
is there a worm there?
No, no, no.
Mezcal is the one
that has a worm.
This is tequila,
not mezcal.
It gives you a hangover.
I went to Cartagena once
for a practice,
and after the practice,
the instructor
takes a bottle of mezcal,
and we started drinking.
By my fourth mezcal,
I couldn't even think.
But the man didn't stop
until he ate the worm.
Come on,
poor me some.
He didn't stop.
He ate it.
Hey, Walter!
What are you doing?
What do you think
I'm doing?
He's only fifteen.
Do you want to be
the father of the year?
Why do you look at him.
We're celebrating.
All of it.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Hey, hey, no, no, no.
It's enough.
- Walter!
- Drink all of it!
I wouldn't have drunk that.
I think people
are drinking too m--
Henry, give me the
bottle!
Do you know what?
No!
These are my house,
my son, and my
bottle.
Give it
to me!
Calm down. Easy.
You've heard me.
Give it to me.
Everything is okay.
What happened?
My dear, my dear.
It's okay.
What happened?
- I can't believe it.
- What?
It's okay, honey.
- Water?
- Yes.
What did you drink?
You bring him in,
I'll get the water.
Ups!
You weren't supposed to
wake up.
Ever?
No, I was just
thinking
I'd bring you breakfast
to bed.
Do you want me
to go back to bed?
No, it isn't
worth it.
Can I help you?
No, I got it.
Just have a seat over there.
- Here?
- Yes.
Let's see how it tastes.
Is there any coffee?
Coffee!
I knew I was missing something.
It'll be right there.
No, I'll do it.
No!
You won't do anything.
- Just stay there.
- Okay. I'll stay here.
Let's see how it tastes.
What did you
cook?
You'll see.
It's a surprise.
- Surprise.
- Let's see.
It's huevos rancheros
with sausage.
Yes, there're many
sausages.
Try them.
Can I have a fork?
It's hard to eat them
without a fork. Right.
Do you have to
work today?
Whatever that means
to you.
- No.
- No?
Today, I'm all yours.
Really?
Yes.
They're simple.
But delicious.
Thank you.
Leave your message
after the signal.
Hi, my love.
Look...
I wanted to tell you
something.
Well, I don't know. Perhaps
we should talk tonight,
once you're home.
I wanted to say
that I'm not exactly sure
who that was
yesterday.
But, definitely,
it wasn't me.
I'm feeling bad
for everything,
and I wanted to apologize.
I love you.
See you. Bye.
I wanted to say
that I'm not exactly sure
who that was yesterday.
But, definitely,
it wasn't me.
I'm feeling bad
for everything,
and I wanted to ap--
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
Ups, who brought brownies?
I did.
If I leave them at home,
I eat them all.
Go ahead,
please.
Thank you.
I cooked them for a party
I organized for Walter.
Really?
Was it his birthday?
No, er...
He's battling cancer.
I'm sorry.
We're really optimistic.
We got good news
last week.
That's great!
Bring these any time.
I love it.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Take care.
We have storage tanks,
tankless water heaters,
electric tanks.
The best ones are
the ones with C3 technology.
All of them
are cistern tanks?
No, not all of them.
We have tankless heaters.
They're really good.
But they have a problem.
They can't be used
for two showers
simultaneously.
The good ones are continuously
increasing their prices.
Let me show you this.
This works
with high and low pressure.
That's really important.
It has a built-in safety system
for fumes evacuation
and for overheating.
It has a surge suppressor,
and a temperature display.
It also has
automatic activation.
It's very simple to install it.
I see.
It costs 1,159,000 pesos.
The price is fine.
Wonderful.
Do you want
the installation service?
No, I'll do it myself.
There you go.
Is this like a skater
without his board?
No, that's Hover-Man.
Okay.
The man can skate,
surf and glide
without a board.
He always has
a 6-inch cushion of air
under his feet.
That's cool.
I like the idea.
Let's see what else I can find.
What's this?
Kanga-man!
Half-man and
half-kangaroo?
Exactly.
- And this one?
- That's Pocho.
He's his assistant.
He always travels there
and fights crime.
Then Kanga-man
isn't a man.
It's a female.
Females are the only ones
that have that pouch.
Did you know that?
Obviously.
But Kanga-man
is definitely a man.
He's the result
of an unsuccessful experiment.
It wasn't that unsuccessful.
It has good legs,
and a good ass.
An this?
What's this?
That's an R
for Retarder.
No, not for Retarder.
Rewindo.
He can make
everything go in reverse.
He walks backwards.
Does he travel in time?
No, no, no.
He just walks backwards.
No.
- Yes.
- Is that a superpower?
- Of course!
He does it really fast.
Okay.
Imagine he's walking
down the street
and there appears a man
with a knife.
The man walks backwards
away from him.
It's really easy to escape,
do you understand?
Sure, yes. Why not?
If you say so.
I draw all of these
when I was a child.
But all of them
look like you.
- What?
- Yes, they're cute.
They all remind me
of you.
- Really.
I don't want to
imagine
what would a shrink think.
Sure.
You never wanted superpowers.
But...
- What happens?
- What's that?
- What?
- Is that your door or mine?
I don't know.
It's mine.
- What are you doing?
I have to go.
Why?
Where are you going, Juana?
What are you doing?
Juana! Juana!
Juana...
What's wrong?
- Hi, dad.
- Hi, my dear.
What happened?
I've been knocking for a while.
I was drawing
with my headphones on.
Sure.
I have the afternoon free.
I'd like you to join me.
Let's have something
to eat.
Yes, yes, yes.
Sure. Let's go.
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
I don't know.
A hamburger?
What do you want?
Yes, yes.
A buffalo burger.
Hi! Is this your father?
- Diego.
- Jose.
He's the new tenant.
Did you need something?
- No.
- Shall we go?
- Yes. Excuse me.
- Nice to meet you.
- Dad, are you there?
- Yes! I'm down here.
- Hello.
- Hello!
You're home early.
No.
A new heater,
isn't it?
Finally, hot water.
No more toxic waste.
It was about time.
We'll finally have hot water
whenever we want to!
So what?
Shall we try it?
Sure!
Okay. I'm coming.
Go to the kitchen.
Open the kitchen faucet.
Yes, yes.
Let me know
when there's water running.
- Ready?
- Ready!
- Okay!
- It's open!
Coming!
It's 117,000 BTU,
corrosion resistant,
draught reducer,
automatic pilot.
Wonderful!
It also saves energy.
What are you doing?
Be careful.
- Did you burn?
- No, dad. I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm fine.
We have to adjust
temperature.
Junior, about
yesterday,
I'd like to--
Er, dad.
Dad, I'm sorry about the pool.
No, not at all.
It isn't your fault.
It was my fault.
Your old man
embarrassed himself.
I'd like you to
know
that I'm not proud
of my behavior.
Just the opposite.
I feel very foolish.
Henry and you
seemed pissed off.
No, it's okay.
Everything is fine.
We're fine.
I called him
to apologize.
I owe you an apology
most of all.
What I did was
terrible.
Forcing you to drink
was very bad.
I'm really sorry.
But I did it okay, didn't I?
Because I kept up with you.
I had almost
as much tequila as you.
Er... I have some
tools to put away.
- Hello.
Do you want to watch a movie?
Hey.
- What?
- Explain it.
- About your father.
There's nothing to explain.
- Really?
- No.
So what?
I misread your attitude.
I was doing you a favor.
A favor? Really?
My father is an ogre.
He seemed cool to me.
It's all yours.
What happened, Juana?
I was protecting you,
okay?
How's that?
I let you smoke in here.
Do you remember it?
I bought a filter,
my lady.
The less my father knows,
the better.
Juana, you acted
like you didn't even know me.
So?
What do you mean?
What did you want me to say?
"Dad, meet my lazy
neighbor.
All he does is fuck me
all the time."
That's all we do,
don't we?
Why do you care
what my father thinks?
I'm not talking
about your dad!
Then what are we talking about?
I'm talking about us!
- About us?
- Yes, you and me.
Yo and me what?
- Do you know what?
- Look, Jose, don't...
- I'm out of this.
- No, come.
- Jose!
- What?
Don't react like this.
It isn't worth it.
What isn't worth it?
That you're embarrassed of
me.
It isn't that.
So what is it?
Dad?
- Dad?
- Down here!
What are you doing?
It's rotted.
What?
Look at this.
Do you see it?
Yes,
yes.
- Wood?
- Wood.
Wood with strange bodies.
Bodies?
Fungus.
They're everywhere.
I don't see
anything.
But there they are.
You have to know
where to look.
Give me the lever
and the hammer.
Yes, I'm
coming.
We have to cut it out
and start fresh.
Is the house
going to collapse?
No.
While I'm here,
put that out.
Okay.
The hacksaw!
Give me the hacksaw again.
Do you think you'll have
a better salary
if you stay working late.
- I'm going.
- Okay.
May I ask you
something
about Ferreterías
Don Fabio?
Ferreterías Don Fabio?
Yes.
It's listed as a current
asset on this balance sheet,
but the invoice was never
presented to accounts.
God.
I need time to analyze
my dad's stuff.
He did business by saying:
"Don't worry.
Pay me on Friday."
He thought small companies
deserved that chance.
Tomorrow,
after having some rest,
we'll talk about it.
- Okay.
- Don't stay longer.
Cielo, I'm serious.
I don't want to leave you here.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Ye's, I'm fine.
Don't worry.
It's the
hormones.
It happens all the time.
You can go.
No, I won't leave you here.
What's the matter?
I think I don't see
the difference.
I don't understand.
After the good news
about Walter's health,
I thought things would
change.
But it's all the same.
I thought I was going
to find the light
at the end of the tunnel,
but...
The tunnel goes on.
- Look, I...
- I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be bothering
you.
Don't worry.
I understand you.
I went through a very hard time.
It was a virus.
Once my father
was at the clinic,
before dying.
When he finally was dismissed.
I got sick.
It was a very strong virus.
I couldn't move from bed.
I couldn't stop thinking "why?"
He's at home.
Why I can't be with him?
Why was I there,
and not with him?
I think some time,
when I could relax,
my defenses went low.
When you're the strongest
at home,
you're more tired than anybody.
Aren't you going to work?
No, there're
fungi.
There're fungi everywhere,
rotting everything.
I have to
continue.
Okay. Bye.
I'll call you.
My God!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- No, hold on.
I'll take that.
Thank you.
It's a shame.
You shouldn't buy those matches.
What?
These matches
are the wrong kind.
Red phosphorous is found
in the striker strips
not in the matches themselves.
Get some boxes
that guarantee more surface.
Something else.
Don't buy everything
in the same place.
Buy in different places
so that
we attract less attention.
- Are you following me?
- Yes, sure.
I ran away.
You're so silly.
We don't have time
to waste in silly things.
That's the man.
Stay out of my territory.