These people.
I have better magazines
in my office.
At least not this old.
María.
You guys really don't need
to hang around.
They will make the tests now,
but we won't even get
the results
until next week.
Buddy, we're going to be here.
It is a full PET/CT, correct?
Or just the PET?
All of them.
He's getting all of them.
Good.
Some places skimp,
and they only do the PET.
They do it to save money,
but they tell you
they did everything.
That depends on the place.
I'm not naming any names.
So why did we come here?
This is where
Walter's doctor is.
With us, you wouldn't have
to wait until next week
to get the results.
I'm sorry, but these scans
are not that difficult to read.
In fact, if you want to,
I could take one look at them
and tell you how he's doing.
Yeah, sure.
For real, Junior.
Doctors like people to think
that they're so much smarter
than the technicians,
but you would be surprised
how much they come to us
for input.
I'm sorry.
Never turn down a chance to hit
the bathroom, right?
Are you all right in there?
Yes, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Sure.
You can get dressed,
Mr. Blanco.
So, how did we do?
You did fine.
Do you see anything?
I'm just a technician,
Mr. Blanco.
I can't tell you
anything.
But you know a lot, right?
You see these things
all the time.
That's right, Mr.
Blanco.
But doctor Sánchez will go
over the results with you
next week.
- Right. Sorry.
- Excuse me.
The money laundering
is pretty easy.
But, telling your wife?
She will want to know
why you suddenly got rich.
If she finds out,
it's after I'm gone.
How much time did they give you?
Weeks.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
I was hoping we could make
some real money together.
Let's cut to the chase.
Let's crunch some numbers.
How much money
are we laundering?
At this time,
16.000 dollars.
16.000?
How long
have you been doing this?
We've had some
extenuating circumstances
we've been through.
Apparently.
All right, 16.000 laundered
at 75 cents on the dollar,
minus my fee,
which is 17%,
comes to 9960.
Oops!
You just left your family
a secondhand vehicle.
Congratulations.
We'll just have
to cook more,
a lot more.
Exactly!
That's my legal opinion.
Make hay while the sun
is still shining.
Take advantage of your life.
Your life!
I'm sorry.
Do I call Francisca?
Honey.
We should do something
this weekend.
Get our minds off
the test results?
Yes.
Actually, I'm thinking...
I should go see mom in
Pereira.
Really?
You know, I never
did call her.
You told me to.
I'd rather go
see her.
You're going to Pereira
because you're expecting
the news from the scan
to be bad. Right?
No.
Honey, I'm begging you.
I need you to stay positive
with me here.
Yes, positive is
good.
But that doesn't change
facts.
It doesn't change the need
to be prepared.
I know.
I'm just trying to be hopeful.
Please, let me.
I need to have hopes, despite
you don't think that's good.
Don't be sad, I know
this is harsh.
Please understand
that I need to arrange
some things.
I have to talk to mom
about different issues.
Among other things,
I need to talk about succession.
I need to be sure
that everything I own
will be for you.
You know?
Just in case.
And believe me,
I'm going to earn
every penny of it, too.
I can hear her,
as soon as she sees me:
"Sinner! You didn't receive
the first communion!"
Shut up.
"Are you going to church?"
She might even call
the priest
in the neighborhood for me
to confess my sins
and don't go to hell.
See? You know
it's hard for me to see her.
But I have to.
Yes.
- Good night.
I actually think
the news from the scan
is going to be good.
We should do
something.
Yeah, we should.
No, something else.
We should go somewhere.
Where?
We should go to MAMBO.
No, I don't want to dance.
What?
I'm not feeling
like dancing right now.
- Really?
What?
No, no, wait a minute.
MAMBO is the Modern Art
Museum of Bogotá.
Don't you know it?
It's downtown.
Too bad?
Boy, you need some
educating.
Yes, I do. Come here.
Come on.
- No!
- Yes.
Do you want to go
to shitty downtown
just for a museum?
You are very romantic.
Get up, we're leaving.
No!
Why can't we just go
to the movies
or playing bowling?
That's good.
A little culture
won't kill you.
Besides, there
is a showing
about erotic art.
You might like it.
We could get some
ideas, if you like.
- Really?
- Yes.
This is Jose's house.
Leave me your message
and--
- I get it!
- I'll see, pal.
José Miguel,
Where the hell are you?
Pick up.
We need to talk.
Hi, here I am.
Give me one second.
Okay.
What do you want?
Where were you?
I've called you a hundred times
and you don't answer.
Where's your drop phone?
Dead.
Okay, listen.
Clear your social calendar.
We have to cook.
- Today?
- No.
You'll need today al least
to gather supplies.
Now, we're going to need
all new glassware,
heating mantles,
about a hundred pounds of ice.
You should be writing this down.
You know what,
teacher?
Go shopping yourself.
I have plans today.
I can imagine your plans.
Eating Cheetos, masturbating
and smoking marijuana.
Am I right?
You know what, man?
Screw you and your
opinions
about my plans.
I'm going to MAMBO,
not like you need to
know.
You're going to a museum?
Of course!
There is some erotic
showing
with pictures,
documentaries and sculptures.
A lot of stuff.
What are you talking about?
Why am I explaining
myself to you?
It's none of your damn business
what I'm doing.
All you need to know
is that I don't want to,
I can't, I won't buy
or cook anything.
Let me explain something to you.
You and I need to cook
all weekend
through to next Tuesday.
Four days straight?
- We have no choice.
- Who says so?
José Miguel, our methylamine.
It's going bad.
What?
It's losing
its chemical potency.
Unless stealing another barrel
sounds good to you.
So now you know it.
We have to act fast
before it goes to waste.
Do you have paper and pencil?
Six mantles?
What kind of mantles?
I wish you didn't have
to do this.
I'll be back in four days.
And I'll be here.
The signal is terrible there,
so, if you need anything,
call me on her number.
The number must be
in the notebook
I have on my bedside table.
Or maybe in the library.
I don't remember.
- Okay..
- Look for it.
Actually,
I don't want to talk
to your mother.
No, thank you.
You'd rather talk to
her
about everything
you need to talk.
I'll call you only in case of
an emergency.
- Let's hope not.
- Okay.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
I'm going to miss you.
Me too.
Tell Junior to behave.
And be good.
Okay.
- Fly safe.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Come on.
What's up?
You brought a meth lab
to the airport?
You said we were in a hurry.
I saved us a trip.
Did you get
everything?
Yes.
- Six mantles?
- Yes, man.
With reflux
condensers?
Yes, like I said.
Okay.
Can we leave, please?
I'm fine too.
Thanks for asking.
Drive!
Are we feeding ourselves
with chips?
Those chips are
awesome.
And they're natural, not
like those lemon-flavored
and those stupid flavors.
How about something
with some protein, maybe?
Something green?
Man, I'm getting no
service.
How are you even alive?
Teacher, check your
phone.
Do you have any bars?
I've got a signal.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let me use yours,
would you?
Are you crazy?
I have to assume my wife
checks my phone records.
It's not business.
It's personal.
Personal.
- Yes.
What, female?
Maybe.
Absolutely, that's all I need.
My wife hits "redial"
and some stripper answers.
No, no, no, respect her.
She's not a stripper.
Okay?
You can't call.
My wife checks the phone.
What can I do?
- Drinking water?
- Yes.
Is that all we've got?
Ten gallons isn't
enough for you?
Are you planning
on taking a bath in it?
What are you doing?
That is our work station.
That is our only set, right?
- Yes.
- Jose, please,
try to find a place
where it won't get lost.
Remember we are in
the middle of nowhere.
Why don't you try
sticking them up your ass?
Partner.
2.5 pounds.
That's the last of it.
How many in total?
42.
And how much money
is that?
Well, median weight...
That's 41.8.
Call it 42 pounds.
What are we selling it
for these days?
40 a pound.
40.000?
You said raise the
prices.
Very good.
All right, that's 40 times 42,
minus distribution charges.
672.000.
All that?
672.000 each.
Each, man?
Are you sure?
672.000 dollars each?
Are you sure, bro?
672.000 each?
I'm sure.
Yeah! 672.000 dollars!
That's it, teacher!
Come high, baby!
Come high!
Come on!
Yeah!
672.000 dollars!
Well, there goes the generator.
Perfect timing, bro.
How do you figure that?
We're done cooking.
I am not done
until this is empty.
Jose, we still have 35 or 40
gallons of methylamine.
Come on, where's
your ambition?
Jesus.
Seriously?
The generator needs gas,
we're almost out of propane,
and my back is killing me
from that piece-of-crap cot.
Come on.
Let's do something.
When do you have to be home?
- On Tuesday?
- On Tuesday.
Okay, on Tuesday.
Can we at least
just take the night off?
We'll be back like new.
We come back tomorrow
and start all over again.
Come on, let's go for some beef,
sausages, corn cakes,
cold beer.
There has to be some place
to eat good meals
around here.
In our way here,
I saw a motel.
A hot shower?
A bed?
Come on, bro.
Okay.
Separate rooms, right?
That's a given.
What's up?
The battery's dead.
What?
Yes, it's dead.
Back when I asked you
to put the keys
in a safe place,
where did you put them?
Here in the ignition.
Son of a bitch.
What?
Is this a genetic thing
with you?
- What?
- Were you born like this?
Or you fell from the bed?
What are you talking about?
Damn it!
You can't let the keys there
almost two days!
Look, I didn't turn the key
or anything.
- What did you do?
- I wanted to let--
It buzzes
when you put the keys in.
Okay, okay.
We need to jump
the battery somehow.
Yes, but how?
Are you okay?
It tastes bad, right?
No luck?
No, mail voice.
The call doesn't get through.
Leave your message
after the tone.
Mom, why don't we call
to the Nan's house?
Honey, I can't find
the phones' notebook.
I don't know the new number
of your granny.
But your dad said that,
if it wasn't here,
it could be in the library.
Could you go see?
Here?
Yes, this is fine.
Move it a little bit.
There.
And now what?
Red to red,
black to black?
Positive, negative.
Same thing.
Done.
- Let me know.
- Okay.
Done.
Start it up.
Ready?
What's wrong with this shit?
You have to really pull.
And what am I doing?
You're doing it like a girl,
not like a man.
You know what? Pull this.
I can't believe you, man.
Come on, come on.
What an idiot!
Bring something, fast!
Not that! Stupid!
It's dead.
Good.
We're out of water, you idiot.
Mom, I found it!
Don't make me
talk to her.
Say hello from me,
but don't make me talk.
Yes, mom.
I told your dad
we would only call
in case of emergency.
It's ringing,
but nobody answers.
I think they're not at home.
There?
This isn't working.
Now we have to use
your phone.
This is ruined.
It was hooked up
wrong
and blew up.
That is not what happened.
How do you know?
The only thing I know
is that you ruined the mantles
and dumped out the water.
This isn't serious.
Maybe we can find
some water around here.
- Don't you think
it's serious?
- No.
Where do you see water?
Here we have only rocks.
Aren't you a chemist?
I don't know.
Maybe we can lick
some plant
or wait till it rains.
And what do we do tonight,
when it gets cooler?
We'll be two penguins.
Come on,
teacher.
Teacher!
Give me your cell phone.
Somebody can pick us up.
Your wife won't notice.
We erase the call.
And what happens
when I receive the bill
with the detail of the calls?
Don't be so negative.
Help me out here!
Come on.
Okay, but make it snappy.
- Okay.
- It has a low battery.
Hi, Tripa.
How are you?
I need a favor.
I need you to come
pick us up.
You got a pen for directions?
Okay.
Okay, you go out of Bogotá,
30 miles away,
you'll see a park.
Not there.
Then you will find a road.
You continue until you see
a house with a blue sign.
You turn left
into another road.
You drive there...
- What do you say?
- 12 miles.
Hurry up that it's going to die!
12 miles more.
Hurry up because
we'll freeze tonight.
Okay, bye.
He's coming.
You see?
Tell me, bro,
have you watched the movie
of that man
that got his arm
wounded by a rock
in the middle of nowhere,
and he had to cut his own arm
to set him free?
He had to drink
his own urine also.
Weird, right?
What would be the flavor?
Did you watch it?
No, and I don't want to.
What if we make a fire outside
to warm ourselves?
If you want to die,
try lighting something
out there.
You'll feel the wind.
We should just call Tripa
to know where he's at.
Hi, Tripa.
How are you, man?
Where are you at?
Have you found the road?
Okay.
You just crossed the river?
Wait a minute.
What river?
Tripa, bro, what river?
There's no river.
No, bro, you went the wrong way.
You have to go back
to the road...
Hello?
Hello, Tripa?
Battery's dead.
What do we do now, bro?
We couldn't be better.
What are you
doing?
I'm trying
to charge the battery.
Just by turning that thing?
The commutator.
It's the part which generates
the electricity.
Usually, this little piston
engine turns it,
but considering it's lying here
completely totaled
due to some fire...
Apply a little elbow grease
It'll take longer.
A lot longer.
But theoretically,
it should work.
Theoretically.
It has to work.
Can I try?
I'll do it.
How much
longer?
I don't know.
Teacher, and now?
Man.
Man!
Is it ready?
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine.
I think it's ready.
Why don't you do it
a little bit more
to be sure?
Walter...
Methylamine doesn't spoil,
does it?
No.
You fooled me to cancel
my plans
and come here.
Don't you know the story
of the liar shepherd
and the wolf?
I think it's ready.
Go connect it.
All right.
Granny, please,
I'm begging you.
Make it work.
Damn it, please.
Come on!
Yes!
No, no, no...!
No, no, no!
Fucking bitch!
What am I doing here?
I should have gone
to the museum.
Teacher!
Walter...!
Walter!
Man, are you alright?
I had this coming.
I deserve this.
You snap out of it.
First off, everything you did,
you did for your family.
All I ever managed to do
was
worry and disappoint them
and lie.
I have told them
so many lies
that I can't even keep them
straight in my head anymore.
You know what?
Screw this.
I'm going to leave this place.
I'm walking.
You can come or not.
José Miguel.
Where's my other shoe?
Jose, your body is running
dangerously low on electrolytes.
Sodium, potassium, calcium.
And when they're gone,
your brain ceases to communicate
with your muscles.
Your lungs stop breathing,
your heart stops pumping.
You go marching out
there,
and within an hour,
you will be dead.
So what?
We stay here and we'll die
in three hours
in this cold.
You need to cut out it all
right now and do something.
I don't know.
Think of something scientific!
Something
scientific, right.
Of course, Walter!
Come on.
You're smart.
You made poison out of beans.
You made a bomb
with a toy.
You are just like MacGyver.
Come on, bro.
We got an entire lab right here.
Think of something.
Make some gas,
build a robot,
a battery, I don't know.
What if we just take some stuff
off of the RV
and build a buggy
to get out of here?
What is it? What?
Tell me.
Do you have any coins?
I got a bunch of them.
Then gather them.
Bring all of them.
And washers and nuts
and bolts and screws
and whatever little pieces
of metal we can think of
that is galvanized.
What does galvanized mean?
Metal covered with metal.
It has to be galvanized
or solid zinc.
Solid zinc, right.
And bring me brake pads.
The front wheels
should have discs.
- Okay.
- What are we building?
You said it yourself.
A robot?
A battery.
Move!
Brake pads, brake pads.
This doesn't look like
any battery I ever saw.
Well, trust me.
It is a battery.
Or rather, one cell
of a battery.
Cut up the last two sponges.
Remember the electrolytes?
Yes.
A battery is a galvanic cell.
It's no more than an anode
and a cathode
separated by an electrolyte,
right?
- Right..
- Look at this.
On one side, we have mercuric
oxide and graphite
from your brake pads.
This is the cathode.
This is the positive terminal.
This is where the supply
of current flows out from.
On the opposite side
we have all the zinc.
It's what we find in
our coins
and anything galvanized.
This is our anode.
So, the sponge
is the electrolyte?
Yes and no.
But very good.
The potassium hydroxide
is the electrolyte,
that's what I'm soaking
the sponges in.
Now...
What shall we use to
conduct this current with?
The electricity?
A wire.
Copper, Jose.
I was going to say copper wire,
but you interrupted me.
Right, right.
The only question now
is will this supply
enough current?
And how many cells
will we need?
We've only got material
enough for six.
We have to isolate
both contacts.
- And connect.
- Which one?
Positive cathode.
- Which?
- The red one.
Good.
Good!
That's a good sign!
The keys.
Come on, come on,
please.
- Come on!
Come on, come on.
Thank you!
Yes!
Drive.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
It's good to know
I can trust you.
Of course.
Whatever happens,
your family will get
your share.
Thank you.
So I'll be hearing
from you.
See you.
Yes, of course.
Bye.
How's everyone doing?
- Fine.
Is that baby ever going
to come out, you think?
I know.
It's almost here.
I'm teasing.
Everything in its time.
Okay, dear Walter,
I have your scan results.
Yes.
I have to tell you...
that you're showing
signs of remission.
Your symptoms have diminished.
In this moment,
you cancer is an inactive one.
I want to clarify.
It does not mean
that you are cured.
To classify someone
as in total remission,
we only need to determine
that the tumor hasn't grown.
Could you explain it better,
doctor?
Please.
Technically speaking, a tumor
can remain the exact same size
it was before, and the patient
could still be in remission.
Now, in Walter's case,
with a stage 3 adenocarcinoma,
I hope to see a 25 to 35%
reduction in tumor mass.
And how has my cancer responded?
Your tumor has shrunk by 80%.
Really? Tell me again.
80%?
That's a lot, mom!
That's a lot,
that's incredible.
Sweetheart, you were right.
It's very good news.
I knew it! I knew it!
What do you think,
Walter?
You were thinking
about the red card, brother,
but you only got
the yellow one.
Listen, Walter,
that cough is the other thing
we need to discuss.
According to your scan, Walt,
you have radiation pneumonitis.
This is fairly common.
Look at this.
I don't know if you can see it.
See that scary-looking thing
there?
Yes.
That's tissue inflammation.
That's a reaction
to your radio therapy.
It's usually not serious,
but it can produce
a cough like that.
I'll prescribe some prednisone.
Tissue inflammation?
Are you sure about that?
Because the other day,
I was coughing up some blood.
What?
You probably have
a tear in your esophagus
from the coughing,
and that can be very serious.
We have to see that today.
You could rupture and bleed.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I've been--
Walter, please,
no more secrets with me.
Your health is really fragile.
With something like this,
you have to call me.
Yes.
Now, with these results,
we are on the good path.
We have hopes,
we have some options.
I think you have
a very good reason
to celebrate.
Party!
You see?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You are strong!
Really strong!
I knew it, I told you.
Yes, you told me.
You told me.