Walter.
Walter, I'm not leaving
until you open the door.
I hear your cell phone,
Walter. Open the door!
This is ridiculous.
He seems silly.
At last!
I've called you like 20 times.
I've left you messages.
Yes, so?
So?
We need to talk
about the car wash.
This isn't a good time.
Let's talk later.
- Agree?
- No. We're talking now.
- No, if--
- Let me in.
What happened to you?
Nothing. I hit myself.
Everything's okay.
Tell me exactly what happened.
This is very complicated.
I don't want
to discuss it with you.
Are you in danger?
Please, tell me the truth.
Look at me in the eye.
Are you in danger?
I need to know.
No, no, no.
I have plenty of things
to think of.
I can't think
about the car wash now.
Do you understand that?
That's it.
- Let's call the police.
- What?
Yes, we can tell them
that you are a drug dealer,
but you fear for your life
and your family.
They can help us.
- Stop, stop. Ho--
- You said it.
- We're in danger.
- No, Cielo, wait.
Wait! When did I say "danger"?
Did I mention
the word "danger"?
Never. I said "complicated."
"Complicated."
And all of a sudden,
you imagine a full story.
I don't understand it.
What's this?
Is this part of the movie?
Did I make it up?
- What's that?
- Cielo, Cielo...
- Tell me. Tell me what--
- No, no. You're being paranoid.
- Do you really think I am?
- Yes, completely.
I don't answer your messages
for two days. Two.
I tell you
that I have a little incident,
and, all of a sudden,
you tell me to call the cops.
What is it about?
Then, tell me.
What the "incident" was?
- Tell me!
- I had an argument with a man.
He's a coworker.
That's it.
Sure.
Go on. Tell me.
We were at a cafeteria.
We were talking
about business.
Conversation got heated.
And I don't know why,
but he went out of control.
And he hit me.
He hit me with his fist.
I didn't even answer
because he is an old man.
An old man hit you with his fist
in a cafeteria?
Actually, he isn't an old man.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Yes, in fact...
I think it's good
we have talked
and things got to that point
because it was
some kind of catharsis.
Our relationship
is less tense now.
It was a good thing.
Now we know
we have to respect each other.
There's mutual respect.
So? What do you think?
I think it's beautiful.
It's wonderful and big.
It's very bright.
I love it.
It has good natural light.
That's why every room
seems so big.
It was rude of me.
I didn't offer you anything.
Do you want a cup of coffee?
A glass of water
would be fine.
- I'll be right back.
- Thank you.
It's beautiful.
- I'm sorry.
I don't remember your name.
Bárbara Cáceres.
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Bárbara.
I'm Manuela Saldarriaga.
- Nice to meet you.
- As you may notice
the house has three rooms,
three bathrooms,
two parking spaces, a warehouse.
At the back there's a room
you may use
as office or guesthouse.
The bedrooms
had wood floors.
The floors
of this area
is Indian green marble.
Yes, it's beautiful.
Are you married?
I separated recently.
I'm so sorry.
Do you have kids?
Yes, I have one.
In May he turned four.
He's Gemini.
He'll be very happy here.
He'll run around the house
and the beautiful backyard.
The architect
who built this house
had a very sophisticated taste.
There're very good kindergarten
in the neighborhood.
at would solve you a problem.
My idea
is that Mateo studies at home.
Really?
It's very
interesting.
For me is very important
that he gets full attention.
Obviously,
socialization is also important.
- The social part matters.
-Yes.
He took an IQ test.
It's an intelligence test.
It was high.
My priority
is to find a balance
between his left hemisphere
and his right one.
Yes, yes.
That room you mentioned
can be turned into a bathroom?
I work with pottery
I'll need water.
Sure. We just need
to check on the pipes
in the drawings.
But everything can be solved.
Of course.
- I love it.
- Yes, it's beautiful.
The space is perfect.
I'm home!
My love!
Henry!
Hello.
I had to go to three drugstores
to find your moisturizer.
But I finally got it.
I bought your chips.
Henry.
Look what I found.
Your favorite beer
half it's price.
And... I couldn't resist
myself.
Your favorite magazine.
Last edition.
María, did you buy potato chips?
I wanted sweet plantain chips.
How do I have to tell you
that I want
sweet plantain chips?
Do I have to make a drawing
or build a model?
What do you need? Tell me.
Do you know what I need?
That you don't be so rude.
María, they aren't the same.
Potato chips.
Plantain chips.
Okay. I understood.
- Where're you going?
To change it.
You're welcome, right?
María, I already have this.
María!
This is unacceptable.
- What?
- That.
There.
Look at this.
You always thought
this place could be bugged.
Now we know it.
This is different.
I don't like it.
It's a violation
of the work space.
If you say so.
Hey, do you want to go out?
And do what?
- Kart racing.
- Kart racing?
There's an indoor track
in Usaquén.
It's really nice.
Jose, thank you, but...
There's a meeting
I have to attend.
It's okay.
Next time we'll go.
Okay.
Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Is there anything I must know?
How's your bruise?
It's fine.
Is there anything
I must know?
For what it's worth
getting the shit
kicked out of you,
although you don't like it,
you get used to it.
Good luck.
This spoon thing is particular,
isn't it?
They belong
to the construction
company.
The owner say
they're for good luck.
In that case,
he should collect elephants.
According to feng shui,
elephant attract wealth.
I'm saying it
because he's a businessman.
It's a good idea.
Will these apartments
have warehouses?
No, this building
doesn't have warehouses.
It's a shame.
My brother works
in the Peace Corps.
He goes on missions a lot,
and I keep him some stuff.
We have a room
that will be more helpful.
It's a big room.
You can keep things there.
It depends on the size,
of course.
- Sure.
- I can show you the leaflet.
Will these rooms
have enough light?
Many times they're dark,
walls get damp,
and things rot.
Precisely, that's a point
to our favor.
They have very good windows.
That's the reason
that they're more attractive
than warehouses.
- I'll show you.
- Okay.
Can you repeat your name,
please?
Carlota Blandón.
Then I said:
"My love, I love you,
but you're fifty years old.
We have to change our lifestyle.
You better quit."
I didn't think
he would listen to me.
But he did it. He quit.
I'm sure it was
a wonderful experience.
I mean, not everybody
can study a degree course
as important as that.
I don't know anybody
who works on that.
Yes. NASA was
like a second family to us.
But we wanted some stability.
We wanted to be
with the family again.
And we came back to Colombia.
He has a good pension,
and I...
I've been hand modeling
for a long time.
Yes. Listen.
Is these real copper?
Yes, I think so.
The best heat transfer medium.
Did you know?
No. Do you have any children?
No, I don't like children.
It's horrible that I say that,
isn't it?
No, everybody
has the right to decide
if they want children or not.
Are you sure
they don't sell this house.
No, I don't think so.
It's a shame. I love it.
I'll talk with my husband.
He may speak with the architect.
What I like is the space.
Beauty salon.
It's the ideal business
for money laundering.
It's high volume
cash-preferred business
with a discreet work force.
Mireya, for example,
is an expert
in pretending to know nothing.
And she would help
to keep the other girls
on the right path.
- Listen.
- Would you like
something to drink?
- Coffee, please.
- And you?
- Yes, coffee.
- Saúl, call me Saúl.
We already know each other,
Cielito.
For the lady of the house.
Attention, ceremony, drums.
Cleansing, exfoliation,
manicure for life
and for free.
Go ahead, pinch yourself.
It's true.
- No. No. No.
- Isn't it exciting?
We aren't buying
a beauty salon or a nail salon.
No. We'll buy the car wash.
I'm sorry.
Am I missing something here?
I don't know.
I thought
you've already tried that.
I mean, Walter told me.
You talked with that man,
Ramiro Clavijo,
and he did nothing,
but mistreating you mercilessly,
and asked
for a big amount of money.
- Is it true?
- Yes, and then he doubled it.
That's business!
It's the business of the year!
Honey, don't worry, you failed.
It doesn't matter. Why?
It happens to all sometime.
Because you called me.
You called me.
That means you're intelligent.
Don't worry, relax.
Let a professional take over.
- Sugar?
- No, thanks.
- Coming!
- No, no, no. Calm down.
- It's for me.
- Are you sure?
What
happened?
- I'm in an important meeting.
- I have to go.
Why didn't you say it before?
I'm sorry,
may Estiwar use your bathroom?
Estiwar?
Yes, sure.
Where is it?
Straight ahead, on the left.
He won't take long.
He has a stomachache issue.
Where were we?
Professionalism.
Yes.
If he doesn't want to sell,
he won't sell.
Yes, but I don't accept that.
I don't accept he doesn't sell.
I think he needs
the right motivation.
- A cookie?
- Yes, please. Thank you.
Motivation.
Motivation, motivation...
Are we talking
about real motivation?
Let's agree on that.
I mean,
it's like making an offer
he can't reject.
No, no.
No. No, don't be so dramatic.
It's just...
Motivation!
An attitude adjustment.
That's great.
"Adjustment of..."
It's a nice phrase.
This woman is excellent.
Don't let her go.
Well, motivation.
I think of...
I know! An audit!
There's nothing
more motivational than that.
I know a girl in Taxes.
In ten minutes with a client,
and his accountant books,
she causes to rain toads
and frogs.
- Batrachians, anuran.
- No, no, no.
- Why not?
- No, no.
What do you mean?
An audit?
We don't want
to draw attention.
Especially,
of the Tax Office.
- You're right.
- We'll have to deal with them.
Once we have the car wash,
we'll have them on our backs.
We don't want them on our backs.
You're right.
I know! A surprise visit
from the Labor Ministry.
It's obvious that dummy
mistreats his employees.
I'm sure they aren't registered,
he pays half the salary,
and makes them work double time.
Why do people accept that?
Out of need.
- No.
- It's the same than auditing.
And we don't want to involve
innocent people either.
Of course.
We'll need them
once the car wash is ours.
They'll work for us.
- You're right.
- Listen, Saúl...
There have to be
plenty of car wash in this city.
- Yes.
- Am I right?
Who said it has to be that one?
- I did.
- Why?
- Just because.
- Okay.
It's crystal clear now.
Listen.
I don't like that man,
Ramiro Clavijo
- Why?
- He was very rude with me.
He was very rude with you.
- With me?
- I don't like him.
What will we do?
I don't like him.
Cielito, nobody likes
passionate woman like you
more than me.
But I must tell you something,
and Walter
won't let me lie.
In this type of business
it isn't good
to take everything personally.
- With all my respect.
Saúl. Saúl.
Rude? How?
With me? What did he
say?
He said you weren't man enough
to face him.
- What? Did he say that?
- Yes.
That you sent me
because you weren't capable.
He's so miserable.
Did he say that?
How can he dare to say that?
I'm sorry. I'm your lawyer.
I have to state it in writing
that I don't think
it's a good idea.
We'll buy that car wash.
Period.
End of story.
Okay.
It's decided then.
We have to find the way
to buy that car wash.
Without violence,
protecting innocent people
as long as it doesn't cost
40,000 million pesos.
- Yes, okay.
- Sure.
Don't speak all at once.
One at the time.
More coffee?
Thanks.
There's no more paper.
Ups! Uff!
Look what I found.
The house
is absolutely gorgeous.
It's beautiful.
Thank you, Margarita.
You're very nice.
- It's European style, isn't it?
- Do you think so?
Yes.
I lived in London many years.
The architecture looks familiar.
It's so nice!
- Doris.
- Yes, madam.
Where in London?
Our son is living there.
We visit him often.
He's downtown,
but we couldn't--
Hi. I need to see
the lady of the house.
My husband is a drawer.
We had to go to Geneva,
United States, France.
The kids were in school then,
and my younger daughter
was diagnosed.
Endocarditis.
My God.
What's that?
Inflammation
of the heart valves.
Mrs. Amparito.
- Yes?
- They need you at the door.
- I'll be right back.
- Sure.
And your daughter?
Excuse me?
How is she doing? The girl.
Hold on, madam. Wait.
I called the police.
- It's okay.
- No, it isn't okay.
I spoke with every project
and on sale house
in the neighborhood.
They all talked about you.
- We know you robbed us.
- Excuse me?
- Yes. You're a thief.
- What are you talking about?
- You're a thief!
- Be respectful!
How do you dare
to invent such a thing?
Are you insane?
Listen, do you know what?
If you don't want to be involved
in big trouble, leave me alone.
My husband
is an anti-narcotics agent.
It's a shame.
I thought he was a drawer
or an astronaut at the NASA.
You should organize your ideas
before saying them.
What's wrong?
You should thank
I have an appointment,
or you'll be in deep trouble.
You won't leave
until the police is here!
- Don't move!
- Let him go.
Do you need more evidence?
Hello.
What? No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't understand you.
Listen. Where are you?
No...
Why the hell...?
Why the hell
do you do that, María?
No. Listen, listen, listen.
Can you stop crying?
I'll make a phone call.
Calm down, my dear. It's okay.
Where? Where are you?
Okay. I'll call you back.
Okay. Bye.
Son of a b--
Good news.
An agent spoke with the owners.
They won't present charges.
Perfect. Neither do I.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Don't you want to go home?
Thank you.
I need to speak
with lawyer Saúl Bueno?
Yes. It's Cielo Restrepo.
Tell him is urgent.
I'm sorry.
I found the same inside.
You can't close my business
because of that.
I've checked
your waste water,
and all the drainages.
There's more contamination
than inside.
Let me show you.
Acetone,
benzene,
ammonia, nitrobenzene.
This is mistake.
Why the engineer
who always does the inspection
isn't here?
Alvaro Alzate.
He knows the soap I use
is very good
for the environment.
It's an ecological soap.
You should talk with him, okay?
It has nothing to do
with the soap.
The problem
is your filtration system.
You need to improve it.
Everything is leeching
into the waste waters,
into the ground water.
You'll have to replace
your system entirely.
Replace?
Do you know
how much cost that is?
One thousand million pesos.
You need to do it.
I can give you the name
of an approved vendor.
If you get going immediately,
you may be able to be open
in five weeks.
Five weeks?
You're right.
I promise we'll be more careful.
We'll keep it clean.
No pollution.
What do you think?
I think it's great,
but it isn't enough.
You know I work with the unit.
We're forced to suspend
all commercial activity
that doesn't meet
the minimum
environmental standards.
Where's Alvaro Alzate?
He came every year.
Why hasn't he come this year?
He was transferred.
If you don't agree,
you can file a complain.
No, that isn't the point.
I have done nothing wrong.
I don't understand
why you'll shut me down.
What laws did I break?
You're breaking
a lot of laws.
Really?
Tell me which laws.
Tell me.
Several laws.
Which ones?
Health and environmental laws.
Specifically...
Hold on.
Just a second.
Here it is.
Decree 2811 of 1974.
Sections 134 to 138.
It's related to pollution
control and prevention.
The environment
is a common heritage.
It is the duty of the citizen
to preserve it.
Section 58 states
property it's a social function.
It's a ecological function.
The offender will be fined
with 300 minimum wage
per day
or its operation license
would be canceled.
Payment of the fines
doesn't release the offender
from taking the measures
recommended by the authority.
Paragraph one, Section 85.
Act 1333 of 2009.
"Satisfied?
Was I specific enough for you?
for you?"
What happened with your
lunch?
You didn't touch it.
I'm not hungry.
There's a brownie,
in case you get hungry.
What part of "I'm not hungry"
didn't you understand?
Then don't eat it.
You should eat
a mountain of shit.
- Ramón.
- Hi, María. What's up?
- I'm fine, and you?
- I'm fine.
Is there any problem?
No, not at all.
I'm here to see Henry.
I'm glad you're here.
He'll be happy to see you.
- Come in, please.
- Thank you.
Henry, you have a visitor.
Look who has arrived.
What?
Did my wife rob a bank?
How are you doing?
I'm well.
I'm getting better every day.
I see.
You're looking good.
I've always been handsome.
Come on. Throw that stuff,
and grab a seat.
Thanks for my wife.
She suffers a lot.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm glad to help.
So? Rock collecting?
- Rocks? Which rocks?
- Those.
They're minerals.
It's hard work.
I have to catalogue,
classify and label them.
It's a lot of work.
I imagine.
Well, why are you here?
I wanted to say hi,
and ask you for some help.
I'm investigating a homicide
that may be related to drugs.
So, Ramón.
Do you want my help in a case?
How?
Do you want me
to chase the criminals?
No.
You're an anti-narcotics agent.
You know a lot about it.
I did you a favor,
now I can use your brain.
Have you heard
of a man called Guido Bermúdez?
Guido Bermúdez?
Let me think.
Let's see...
No. Not at all. Why?
Someone came along,
and shot him in the face.
Okay.
No signs of force entry.
No signs of robbery.
Crime of passion.
Where's the drug angle?
We found a notebook
at his place.
I made a copy for you.
It looks like it pertains
to some methamphetamine lab.
Okay.
There're scientific formulas
and drawings,
and chemical products
purchase receipts.
It looks big,
but I don't know about it.
I need your help.
Do you think I'm stupid?
What are you doing?
Some kind of charity?
"Let's help poor Henry."
No, I really need your help.
I don't know
if you realize my condition.
I'm in bed,
and I can't move.
I only do three things:
Eating, pooping and sleeping.
I'm not even useful to myself.
Do you want my piece of advice?
Talk with Gómez.
He may help you.
I can't give this case to Gómez.
He isn't here.
And you know about the subject.
Look at it.
Take a look,
and tell me what I'm missing.
Whatever.
Ey, ey!
If you want a rock, take that.
Take it easy.
Thank you.
I'll stop being hyperactive.
- I'll take this rock.
- Okay.
See you.
It was a good try.
And you, young
lady,
what are you doing
up?
It's time to take a nap.
Shall we
go?
Say
goodbye.
Yes.
Pretty girl.
The beauty salon
isn't a bad idea, you know?
I think it's promising.
What do you think?
I think we should wait.
Wait. We've been waiting
for five hours. More wait?
He'll call. Don't worry.
He'll call.
I hope so.
Cielo, it was a good idea.
It didn't work.
What's the problem?
Let's take it as a learning.
Hello.
Mr. Ramiro.
How are you?
If I'm still interested?
That depends.
No, no. What do you mean?
It depends on what?
Well, I know.
That was the original offer.
But it seems high to me now.
What?
- I'm offering 900 millions.
- No, Cielo!
Don't do that! No!
Why?
Basically,
you're an unpleasant person.
What are you doing?
- Are you nuts?
- You insulted me.
And you insulted my husband.
You shouldn't do that.
I spoke
with a number of sellers,
and the market seems
much softer than I thought.
My final offer
is 800 millions.
You're talking crazy!
Well, I understand
that you're disappointed.
but that's my final offer.
I'm sorry
we couldn't make it work.
Okay, Mr. Ramiro.
Have a nice day. Good bye.
What are you doing?
- I'm negotiating, Walter.
- Why?
Because I want to pay less.
Less? 200 or 500 millions
doesn't matter.
I have enough money.
That's the very reason.
We need to negotiate.
We don't want
to arouse suspicion
by not trying
to get a good deal.
Everyone here
asks for a lower price.
Okay, I get the logic.
But it won't work
because you insulted him.
No, I didn't insult him.
I just told him
that he's an unpleasant man.
Whatever.
He won't call again. It's over.
- He will call. I know it.
- No, no.
Do you know what?
I'll take plan B.
Better call Saúl.
Where's my phone?
- I'll get it.
- Don't. I'll get it.
- Can you let me? What will...?
- Of... No.
Hello.
Mr. Ramiro.
Nobody is paying attention.
But I swear
these things exist.
Yes, mom told me.
I don't mind
if a witch burns me.
No, not at all.
Or cannibals eat me.
No! But I'm frightened.
Many people
will want to escape.
There won't be enough room.
How are we going to push?
- How are we pushing?
- Hard.
- Fast.
- We'll all end up
- being Plasticine.
- Mashed potatoes.
Yes, like mashed potatoes.
Do you know
what the sad part is?
- We can do nothing.
- Nothing.
Nobody. Nothing.
- Nor you, nor me.
- Nobody. Nothing.
Hit! Come on.
When this situation begins--
- Hey!
- What's up with him?
Everybody up!
Who wants some money?
Let's see.
Money.
Who wants some money?
Let's see.
- That's mine.
- No. It's mine.
Mine. Mine.
- It's mine.
- Go away.
I'm glad
I was awake.
It's mine. It's mine.
Kill yourselves
for that money.
Give it to me.
It's mine.
No, come on.
It's mine. Woman.
That's nice.
What do you think?
It smells nice.
To car washing
and money laundering.
- Cheers.
I told you, didn't I?
What? Yes.
It was a perfect job.
It was.
It was impressive.
- Thank you.
- And, Saúl...
He finally came through.
He found the guy,
didn't he?
Yes, he found the guy.
But I told him
what to do and what to say.
You're right.
That's the hard part.
But yes.
Saúl was finally useful.
To Saúl.
Cheers.
- It tastes better every time.
- It's great.
It better be good.
It's 380 thousand a bottle.
What?
And I can't even
pronounce the name.
How did you pay it?
Cash.
No, I mean...
Walter Blanco,
unemployed Chemistry teacher.
Where did you get the money
to pay that bottle.
Cielo, nobody saw me.
Whoever sold it to you did.
But that's not the point.
The point is we're broke.
I didn't pay
some of the bills.
And I canceled our subscription
to magazines
and newspapers.
I even asked for an extension
of the loans.
Theoretically,
we don't have money.
I'm sorry.
You're overreacting.
Listen, I won't refrain me
from buying a bottle of wine.
And I won't apologize
for wanting to celebrate.
We deserve it.
I'm not asking you
to apologize.
I'm just asking you
to be smart.
It's a bottle of wine.
I pay cash.
That's it.
That's all it takes.
Do you remember Watergate?
What?
A microphone on a door
brought down the president
of the United States.
- I'm Nixon now?
No...
No.
I want you to understand
the devil is in the details.
One slip-up;
one little mistake in our story
and we'd be ruined.
The devil.
I mean, no. It's okay.
No, no, no. It's okay.
There's no problem.
We have to destroy the evidence.
Okay.
Don't be ridiculous.
We have a car wash.