So, how big's the batch?
Should be about 50 pounds,
give or take.
- No!
- Okay, okay.
Mr. Blanco says the fumes
aren't good to breathe.
Let me worry
about what I breathe, kid.
Just hurry this up
so you can check its purity,
we can finish
and I can grab a smoke.
76%.
Good! Nice
going!
Very good.
Wait a minute.
Where is the blue?
What?
The blue color.
Does it come
later,
when this hardens?
Where is it?
Mm.
I am correct in assuming
this should be blue?
See, I'm thinking
the headline here
should be
a purity of 76%.
The other dude
couldn't crack 70%.
Yes, I accept you
improved the purity,
congratulations, Beto,
but we don't have the color
and that's what Europe buys.
That's what they pay
for.
If we're down a bit in purity,
maybe they won't notice
but not if it's not blue.
I don't know.
To my eye, it's kind of blue.
It's blue-ish.
Please.
Beto, you are the chef here.
What do you think?
The thing is that we are
in a dark closed place,
but if it catches
the light just right,
I could see how you'd think
there's a touch of blue.
Aquamarine.
Wait a minute.
Are you blind or what?
We'll put food coloring in it.
Make it any damn shade you want.
No, wait a minute.
I want it as it was.
I want it as usual.
With or without food coloring,
we're going to make
a lot of money with it.
Boss, boss.
Call me Lidia, Beto.
Mrs. here is your tea,
the brand and the sweetener
you always use.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Look, about the product
I'm really sorry about the
color. For a minute or two,
it just got a few degrees too
hot in the mixing kettle,
I think.
You burned it, like a cake.
Yeah, sort of, I guess.
But the point is
I think I can fix it,
and I think I can bring
the purity up too.
I mean, I'm doing everything
just like Mr. Blanco taught me.
You know, it's bound
to get better, right?
It will be better.
I appreciate you making
every possible effort
because, as you know,
my buyers expect a certain
threshold, a continuity.
Yes. But you don't worry
about those buyers.
If you have any
trouble, I can ask my
uncle to smooth things
over with them.
No, no, no.
What are you talking about?
That's not necessary.
Okay. Anyway,
I'm here if you need me.
I believe in you.
Please do make the cook better.
It's very important
to me.
Thanks.
Hello.
Beto,
I think I might have another job
for your uncle.
Okay. Do you want me
to set up a meeting?
Please.
Let's do that.
Any heads-up I should give him?
Which jail, how many targets,
stuff like that?
Hello, teacher?
Just one target.
Not currently in jail.
José Miguel Rosas.
Okay, sir.
Let me know about the meeting.
Thanks.
So, how's everything going?
Fine.
Still with the beauty?
I'm surprised you
didn't strangle him.
What do we do with
him?
Do we take him
to anti-narcotics?
I'm sure he has plenty to say
against Walt.
Knowing what we know
about how Walt deals with rats
behind bars? No.
So?
He has to be safer in jail
than out here
where it's open season.
What?
Kid's got an idea.
What kid?
Now we call him "kid"?
What kid, bro?
The one that screwed up
our sting?
He's a bitch, man!
Just hear him out
and tell me what you think.
So what do you say, genius?
Da Vinci.
What's the idea?
You guys need evidence
to put him away, right?
Only he's too smart to
leave any
out there, right?
So you say.
Well, I know some evidence
that greedy ass hole would
never destroy.
His money.
Do you know where he keeps it?
No.
But I know someone
who might.
What's up?
Did you get it?
Here you have.
So what?
Stewart stayed there.
Do you have his phone?
So?
And he's on ice?
Isolated? cut off?
He's in the safe house 30,
with Orozco.
And what do we do
if Orozco
start asking questions?
Orozco won't ask anything.
I have to tell you this
up front.
If this guy decides that
he wants to lawyer up,
I don't care if you are my boss,
I'm going to put a stop to this.
Relax, brother.
Look at this beauty.
Ha!
What's up?
What the hell, man?
What's this shit?
You're up.
Hi, boss.
Orozco, wait outside, please.
Yes, sir.
Stewart Alfonso.
How are you?
Do you know who I am?
I'll take that as a yes.
How are you, Stewart?
First of all,
thanks for your patience.
As they told you here,
you're not under arrest.
So relax.
Let's talk.
If I'm not under arrest,
why am I here?
You're here
because it's the best for you.
This is personal protection.
What are you talking
about?
Well, we both know how dangerous
Walter can be, right?
I'll take that as a yes too.
There's not much new
you can tell me about Walter.
Multiple murders,
ties to a white power
prison gang,
ran the largest meth racket
in Colombia.
I know all that.
So relax, brother.
Listen to this, Stewart,
this isn't an interrogation,
so you can answer what you want
or not, if you don't want to.
There is a lot we already know.
Let's cut to the chase.
We have a wire
on Walter's phone.
We intercepted a call between
him and a certain...
Saúl.
Saúl, the lawyer, Saúl Bueno.
I know he's your employer.
Anyway, in the call,
Walter said
that he was going to take care
of José Miguel Rosas
and that Stewart Alfonso was
the next on the list.
That's why you're here.
We are protecting you.
Yes, of course.
Bullshit.
We have the recording,
I can let you hear it.
What's your friend name?
Your associate...
Pirateque.
Gonzalo.
Gonzalo Pirateque,
well, Walter said
he was going
to take care of him also.
And Pirateque is missing.
I'm sorry to say that.
I don't think
he has had any luck.
Believe us, don't believe us.
Suit yourself.
Whatever you do,
I would not call Saúl.
He betrayed you.
Have you seen his commercial?
"Better call Saúl".
Don't call him.
You're just playing
with me.
Don't take it personally.
Saúl does what Walter says.
He only does what the teacher
tells him to do.
Nobody else.
Of course Saúl
tried to help you
during 15 seconds,
maybe, but then he gave up.
He chose help Walter,
so they place a tracker
in your cell phone,
so when you call Saúl
Walter can find you
and, in just seconds,
you would end like this.
Shit, I didn't know they
were going to kill him.
I didn't know anything
about that.
Okay, relax.
Relax, Stewart,
We know you didn't know it.
If we thought you did,
you wouldn't be here.
You would be someplace else.
Let's do something.
Help us find Walter,
help us find him
before he finds you.
Why would he want to
kill me?
I didn't do
anything.
Who knows with this guy?
He's a psycho.
From what he said to Saúl,
it may have something to do with
him trying to tie up loose ends
regarding his poisoning
some kid.
What was his name?
Brock.
Or maybe it's because you know
where his money is.
I don't know that.
That isn't what we heard.
Well, you aren't listening
to the people in the know.
We only rented a van
for the dude,
loaded his cash up in
a self-storage unit
and handed over the keys to him.
And who knows where he took it
from there?
A van?
How much money
are we talking about?
Seven barrels' worth.
Seven barrels?
Yes, Gonzalo and I filled them.
It was a lot of money.
What do you mean "barrels"?
Something like this?
Something bigger?
You know, those blue
plastic barrels.
For 50 gallons.
I bought them myself
in one of those stores
for construction
in the freeway.
Where did you rent the van?
It belongs to my uncle.
I can give you his phone
and address for you
to go check it.
We handed Walter the keys.
He had us wash it good
before taking it back.
Why did he make you wash it?
Was it dirty?
It was filthy, man, like if
he had went off road with it.
He grabbed a shovel
out the back
and reminded us to wash it
before taking it back.
That was all.
Was it soil or sand?
I don't know, soil, sand.
What color?
Yellow with red,
something like that.
All right, Stewart,
thanks for your cooperation.
We are going to do everything
we can to find Walter.
Meantime, like I said,
you're free to go.
But if I were you, I wouldn't
take one step out that door.
They're going to kill you.
And remember, no phone calls.
I took the liberty of removing
the battery
so Walter
can't track you.
Stewart, you are
going to stay here with Orozco.
You're in good hands.
But don't talk much to him
because he has to be focused.
How long am I going to
be here?
As long as it takes
to keep you safe.
So just one guy this time.
Not even in lockup.
Right.
Some former partner,
Beto says.
Yes.
So what are we talking,
rat patrol?
No, he's not a rat.
He just won't listen to reason.
Of course.
He's just angry.
He's not a rat.
I want that clear.
All right.
Angry, non-rat.
Yes.
How angry are we talking?
Like, Hulk angry?
When he tears all his
clothes?
Or like your wife
when you arrive home late?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I want to understand something.
This is something
you wouldn't do yourself.
José is like family to me.
Look, I want what you do
to be quick and painless.
No suffering, no fear.
Bullet to the back of the head.
Something he doesn't see coming.
I respect that.
There's too many
savages out there.
Let's just talk about the money.
No, we don't want your money.
So?
We want you to cook for us.
You know I can't do that.
I'm out of the business.
Just a couple times to tutor
my nephew here, that's all.
No.
Get him on track to bringing
the purity up.
Get the color right too.
Absolutely not.
Look, what was the price
per head last time?
I'll triple it.
That's a drop in the bucket
compared to what we aim to earn
from the blue stuff.
Don't skimp on family.
You need us and we need you.
What's the price?
You cooking.
One cook after the job is done.
Time is of the essence.
It has to be
as soon as possible.
We'll do him tonight
if you want.
Just tell me where he is.
I don't know where he is.
But I know how to flush him out.
Make him come to us.
- Hi, Andrea.
- Hi.
I'm Walter Blanco,
do you remember me?
Yeah, of course,
Walter.
How are you?
I'm fine, thanks.
I'm sorry to just barge in
on you like this
but I was hoping that I could
have a moment to talk with you.
Yes, but I'm feeding Byron.
Do you want to talk inside
while he finishes his meal?
I don't have any problem,
if that's okay with you.
Yes, of course.
- Good.
- Come in.
Thanks.
You met Byron
before, right?
Yes, of course.
That dinner.
- Yes, yes.
- At José's. How are you?
Byron, he asked you a
question.
Don't worry. Kids are...
Enjoy it!
Have a seat, please.
Thanks.
I don't want to alarm you,
but I've been trying
to reach José for days.
He doesn't answer the phone.
He's not at home.
I can't find him anywhere.
Have you heard from him?
I don't know,
two weeks ago, maybe.
Really?
Okay. Well, you know...
He's using again.
What?
I have a bad feeling about this.
I want to find him.
I don't know.
Have you tried calling Saúl,
the lawyer on the T. V.?
Yes, yes. In fact,
he was able to verify
that José's not locked up
and he doesn't have problems
with the police.
The thing is that José and I
had this argument recently.
I won't bore you
with the details,
but you know that,
when we talk about addiction,
things get worse.
I'm worried for him,
that's why I'm here.
I'm thinking
that I could call him
to see if he answers me.
- That would helpful.
- And we'll see.
That would be perfect, thanks.
What number do you have?
This
one?
Let's see.
No, he changed it.
This is the new one.
Okay, let me see.
He doesn't
answer.
Leave you message
after the tone.
Hi, José, it's Andrea.
I'm at home
with Byron and your friend
Walter who came to visit us.
We're thinking of you.
Please call me
when you get this.
I want to know about you.
It's important.
Okay? Bye.
Perfect.
That will really help.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome to stay
a few minutes to see
if José
calls back.
No, it's okay.
You are busy.
If I find something,
I'll call you.
I've got your number.
Okay, perfect,
Walter.
Byron, have a nice day.
Bye, Byron.
Byron, say goodbye.
Hello.
It's done.
He should be here any time now.
Be alert.
Okay.
Remember, fast and painless.
And take him away from here.
I don't want the mother
or the boy to know.
Hi, José, it's Andrea.
I'm at home
with Byron and your friend
Walter who came to visit us.
We're thinking of you.
Please call me
when you get this.
I want to know about you.
It's important.
Okay? Bye.
Keep trying, piece of shit.
So?
Did the van of
Stewart's uncle
had a GPS?
Nothing. No GPS, no nothing.
So we're fucked up.
No, no.
You can't just give up on this.
Who said we're giving up?
Nobody.
So what?
Do you remember
what Stewart said
about the dirty van
and the shovel that had Walter?
I'm sure he buried that money.
Let's say he did,
what do we do?
We start making holes
through all Bogotá?
You said it yourself that the
van didn't have a GPS.
What do we do?
Nothing.
But Walter doesn't know that.
Here's your change.
Count it out, please.
5, 10, 15.
Exactly.
Have a nice day.
Thanks.
Give this to your car wash
professional.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Bye.
Honey, next time you say
"have a brilliant day".
Do I have to say so?
Yes, that's our motto.
It reinforces our brand.
Mom, it's Saturday.
Can I go?
Go where?
I want to go home
to pick up a few things.
I'm sure the smell
is gone by now.
Why don't you just stick around
here for a while longer,
to help me?
Okay.
Who do I give this to?
I'll take care of it.
That'll be 14.
You're the lawyer guy.
The one on T. V.
Did you recognize me?
Yes.
Better call Saúl. Ha, ha.
Your change. 30 makes 100.
Thank you very much.
What happened to your face?
I guess you'd call it
an occupational hazard.
Give that to your car wash
professional. Thanks.
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
Don't drink and drive.
But if you do, call me.
Ha, ha, ha.
Yes, sir.
Have a brilliant day.
Brilliant.
That's our motto, right?
Make sure you get in there
between the cushions, all right?
Between them.
What the hell
are you doing here?
José left so much powder
in my car
that if police stops me
I should call Saúl.
Couldn't you call, Saúl?
Don't you have a cell phone?
One of the two hundred
you have in your office?
My bodyguard is missing.
I don't have any idea
where he is,
he doesn't answer the phone,
nobody knows where he is.
What do you know
about José?
He hasn't shown up yet.
But he will. I'm sure
he's hidden someplace.
Or he got it loud and clear
and figured out it's a setup.
The kid is not as dumb
as you think.
Are you wearing
a bulletproof vest?
Did you miss the part
about my bodyguard
has gone missing?
I had him watching
the dog house,
figuring the kid might
show up.
Next thing I know,
radio silence.
You're exaggerating, Saúl,
José is not
on some killing spree.
It's me he wants.
It's just me.
So where is Stewart?
Hi. Any news?
No, not yet.
Mom, can you help me?
Yes, honey.
José.
Did you receive my photo?
That barrel looks familiar?
Because I just found
six more exactly like it.
So don't hang up.
I'll explain you what happened.
I found Stewart, remember him?
Saúl's bodyguard?
I pistol-whipped his head
until he gave up what he knew,
which led me to your rental van,
which, it turns out, had GPS.
How do you like that, genius?
You missed that, bitch.
Guess you didn't think
of everything.
José, José,
I don't know what you plan
on doing here,
but listen--
Well, I'll give you a hint.
It involves several
barrels with money,
a couple of five-gallon cans
of gasoline
and a lighter.
No, no, no! José, José!
Please, please, listen to me.
No, you listen to me, bitch!
You get your ass out here
as fast as you can.
Yes, I'm coming!
I'm coming right now!
And don't even think about
calling anyone for help.
You hang up on me,
put me on hold,
as soon as you do,
I'm burning all of it.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I understand it.
Well, you better hurry
because I'm burning
ten grand already.
They have a really nice
orange flame.
No, no, no! José, José,
please, listen to me.
Don't touch my money!
It smells weird,
burned bills.
No, no, no, José,
stop, please!
I'm dying.
My cancer is back.
You're not hurting anyone
but my family.
I won't be around
long enough to use it.
It belongs to my children.
Do you really want
to talk about kids, Walter?
Do you want to go there?
I am sorry about Brock.
Of course you're not!
Yes, I am, believe me.
Don't talk bullshit!
José, José, I am really sorry.
Please forgive me.
You're not,
but you're going be.
When you get here.
José, the most important thing
is that he is alive.
I'm not that stupid,
I knew exactly
how much to give him
and not kill him.
You know me,
I had it all planned.
I know you're a lying,
evil scumbag.
Manipulating people,
messing with their heads.
You know nothing,
damn it!
Can't you see that I
needed you
on my side to kill
Gustavo?
I ran over those gang
bangers, I killed Loco.
I did all of those things
to try to save your life.
Don't you see that?
José, José?
I'm here!
I didn't hang up!
José, I'm here.
Where are you?
José, I didn't hang up!
Talk to me.
What's up?
Ouch...
Wait a minute.
How do you do that?
Hello.
Joaquín, It's me.
I have José in sight.
He's coming for me right now.
He knows I'm alone.
I'm guessing he's got backup.
How many guys?
I don't know.
Where are you?
Get a pen.
Write this down.
These are coordinates. 34.
59, 20.
52.
Listen to me, Joaquín,
if you want me
around to cook,
you get here right now.
As fast as you can.
Walter, do you have eyes on him?
Tell me something,
Walter.
Wait a minute, no, Joaquín.
Forget it. Don't come.
It's off.
Do not come.
What?
What's up?
This is
clean.
He has to be somewhere.
He can't be far,
sick and walking.
And I don't think
he leaves us all the money.
Right?
Walter!
I know you can hear me!
Come on out!
Sooner or later
we're going to find your money!
Walter, give up!
This is over!
Freeze! Drop the gun!
Hands up!
Walk towards me slowly!
Slowly,
slowly.
Stop. Turn around.
Lace your fingers
behind your head.
Walk backwards to me.
Stop.
Get on your knees.
How did you like
my barrel photo?
Do you know where I took it?
In my house's backyard,
by the barbecue grill.
You know, where we used to
cook out with the family.
Remember?
Gómez thought the sand
might not match.
That you would find out.
But I thought
you were going to be so
worked up about the prospect
of losing his cash
that he won't catch it.
Looks like I was right.
I remember this place.
The very first place
we cooked.
When you told me you had cancer
and I had to cook alone.
Walter, do me a favor, brother.
Tell me where you have
the money buried
and save us the busywork.
Would you help me?
No matter.
I'll get a search team
out here even with dogs.
We'll find it
in less than five minutes.
Agent Gómez!
Yes, sir.
Shall we flip a coin
for the honors?
It's all yours.
Thank you.
Walter Blanco, you have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right
to speak to an attorney.
If you cannot afford
an attorney,
one will be provided for you
at the government's expense.
Right.
Did you understand?
Coward!
Son of a bitch!
- Okay, okay.
- Son of a bitch!
Come here.
Back off! Back off!
Get him in the car.
I'm going to take him down
for booking, okay?
I think you should stay here
until the search team arrives.
Right?
Okay.
You are unbelievable.
Congratulations, buddy.
Thank you.
Thanks for your patience.
I'd take the kid with me,
but they'd probably kill
each other on the way.
I'm going to make a phone call.
Hi, honey.
Honey, I got him.
Walter?
I have him in handcuffs
as we speak.
He won't escape this time.
Do you want me to wave
to him for you?
Wait a minute.
He's not feeling too friendly.
Thank God, Henry.
You did it. Thank God.
Things are going to be a little
rough for the next couple weeks,
but they'll get better.
Ha, ha.
Are you okay?
I'm much better now.
Okay, I have to go.
It may be awhile
before I get home.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I love you.
And I love you, Henry.
This can't be true!
Hey, Henry,
who are those?
Henry, watch out!
Henry, Henry!
No, no, no Joaquín!
Police, drop your weapons!
Don't shoot!
Who are you?
Show us some ID!
Drop your weapons!
Joaquín, Joaquín, don't shoot!
You drop your guns!
You are at a disadvantage!
Joaquín, Beto, don't shoot!
Beto, don't shoot! Henry!
Please, don't shoot!
Joaquín, I told you it was off!
Damn it!