- Like that?
- No, more.
A little more.
Okay.
Could you stop it
with the stick already?
Finally someone. Hey, hey!
No, man,
they're not taking you with that look.
Yes!
Stop, stop, stop.
You sure this is the way to go?
I do.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome, man.
Thank you.
- So what did he say?
- Well, not much.
He came in dehydrated and disoriented
but he got stabilized pretty quickly.
Right. But, I mean,
he knows where he is?
Yes,
absolutely. He's completely conscious.
He just doesn't remember
what happened to him.
You can see him if you like.
- Come in,
over there. Okay. Honey!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Walter, do you remember me?
Sure I do, come over here.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
I'm better, I think...
I just don't remember anything,
but I'm fine.
You have no idea what
we've been through.
I know.
You have no idea, dad.
Uncle Henry had a confrontation.
a shoot-out. He
almost got killed.
A shoot-out?
Some big Mexican drug dealer.
And he wasted him,
like the cops say.
My God... So is Henry alright?
He's fine, he's fine.
- Are you sure? Where did this happen?
- Everything's okay,
don't you worry. He's okay.
And you're okay.
Yes.
We're okay, we're okay..
Any other news?
No, not for now. But they're
going to run a whole series of tests.
What else did they tell you?
I mean,
there must be an explanation or something.
Why did it happen,
could it ever happen again...
We won't know for sure
until we get the results.
I really, I don't know...
I get this feeling they
gave him scopolamine.
Or maybe this has
to do with marijuana.
I don't know. But where
did this happen exactly?
No, wait, wait,
don't start all over again.
Cielo,
please don't get me wrong.
I'm just happy that Walter
showed up and is okay,
but, I mean,
naked? At a supermarket?
I mean, butt naked
before the customers
at the market. Please.
I hope it wasn't at rush hour.
In any case,
I'm going to get over there.
You know what? No, it's okay.
You don't need to.
Better stay with
Henry. How is he?
I only saw him a minute. I
thought it would be different,
but they yanked him away.
How did you see him?
Well...
No, thanks.
I don't know.
You know Henry.
He's a rock.
I identified myself and told the suspect
to show his hands, turn and face me.
At this point,
I identified the suspect as Tuco Salamanca.
He had a gunshot wound in
his midsection. He was bleeding.
- He was shot previous to your arrival?
- Yes, he was.
Again I instructed him to
show his hands. Didn't listen.
He lunged toward the
vehicle and fired on me.
I had to take cover
and started shooting as well.
He continued shooting at me continuously,
like crazy.
I had to stop at
one point to reload.
I got into the
line of fire again...
and I was able to take an
effective shot that killed him.
Agent, what were you doing in a
shooting fight on your own, with no backup?
The least I expected
was to find Mr. Salamanca.
I was tending...
- to another matter.
- What other matter?
An unrelated family matter.
Searching for your brother-in-law,
as I understand.
Your brother-in-law?
Yes. He's since been
found and is alright.
The whole thing was
a misunderstanding.
He'd been missing and,
since he's in poor health,
the whole family was concerned.
I volunteered to look for him.
I was talking to his
friends and acquaintances,
and that's how I got to
this José Miguel Rosas,
a former student of his at
the Los Monarcas school.
He was his teacher.
The car in the
middle of the gunfight
between Mr. Salamanca and me
was José Miguel Rosas's.
I got to the place
because I was
tracking down the car.
The least I expected
was to run...
into Tuco Salamanca there.
So how is this José
Miguel Rosas related?
What was his car doing there?
Did he say anything?
We haven't found Mr. Rosas yet,
but we're working on that, sir.
Man, they never give up.
They're like
Jehovah's witnesses.
Why don't they just take a log and bam,
bam, knock your door down?
How can you say that?
Are you dumb or something?
Besides,
they need evidence to get an order.
Evidence? But what'd
you do? Rob a bank?
I told you,
this is serious shit.
I'm like an outlaw.
Right, an outlaw.
If you say so, man.
Looks like they're leaving.
Gosh.
- Okay, finished, finished.
- Okay, man.
- There.
- Let's do this.
What a crib, José!
- Where's the pseudo?
- No, man, we don't use pseudo.
It's a P2P cook. We use methylamine,
which replaces pseudo.
Okay, let's do it. Help me out.
- No pseudo?
- Right, no pseudo.
Methylamine.
The meth is mine.
Come on,
man. Just take this and get it in.
But I can't just let you
break this down this altar.
Did you now see the cops out
there? Just come and help me, man!
Couldn't we just
cook one quick batch?
To get all wound
up for the road?
No, forget it,
all right? Just help me pack everything.
Come on, José,
do me that favor, will you?
You owe me! I'm not forgetting
you just left me stranded.
Come on, now, come on!
I've had just about enough...
Don't mess with me!
And help me pack.
Don't get all ramped up, José,
I'm just saying you owe me.
Dude, just stop it already.
One, two...
One...
Listen, José...
You sure these aren't gunshots?
I'm telling you they're not.
You should stop smoking,
you know? You're imagining things.
Come on, man...
Can we trust this dude?
Sure, man, he's my cousin.
So what now?
What had we say, 500?
We didn't say,
and it's double this time.
Double? What do you mean double?
This isn't going to Cartagena,
brother.
It's not the distance,
it's the cargo.
So what then?
Listen, I have 560 here.
No, fuck off, man.
What do you mean "fuck off"?
Hey, no, no, no,
what are you going to do?
- Listen, cousin Cousin.
- Get this right.
- No, no, no, no, hey.
- Germancho, come on, dude.
Hey, fix this mess, man.
Cousin, come here, come here.
He'll pay you the rest later.
He's totally good for it! Believe me.
I absolutely trust him.
- You're standing up for him?
- Listen,
I swear over my grandma who's
in heaven. And I don't just swear.
I'll give you half now
and half later. I'll get it all.
Don't try to fuck with
me. I'll go and get you.
Fine.
There you go.
- Come on.
- No. What? There's already 500 there...
Nice family you got.
Thanks, cousin.
I saved your skinny ass again.
Now you owe me one more.
What are you doing now, exactly?
I have to call in two hours.
From where?
I know, on a pay phone,
not a cell phone.
Alright. You're not
using your own name.
- Look, I'll just do what you said.
- That's right.
But, I mean, why all this?
These people want evidence.
I'll give them evidence.
Come on.
What's the last
thing you remember?
I was driving.
I was... I was going home.
You were at the
house and we talked.
- Don't you remember?
- We did?
No, honey. I'm sorry,
but I don't remember.
Nothing else? No
fleeting images?
Yes, there's...
I have this image of a...
of a highway.
It was so dark,
and I remembered I was scared.
There's definitely
some good news here.
The MRI shows no metastases.
That's great.
Meaning the cancer
hasn't spread to the brain?
No.
We're looking really good.
That's great.
So, what was it,
then? I don't get it.
What happened?
We really don't know. We didn't find
any strange substances in the body.
Doctor, sorry to intrude.
I know this isn't your field,
but...
is there a chance that all this
has to do with the
medication I've been taking?
I mean,
there's the antiemetic,
the antitussive,
not to mention the chemo...
He know a lot about drugs
because he worked in a lab,
did some research.
And being off all of them
for the past few days,
I'm feeling much better.
Besides, all those formulas...
it's page after
page of side effects
and warnings.
Right,
exactly. Could it be that simple?
We'll take another look at that.
I understand that you've been
kind of stressed out, Walter.
You've been under so
much pressure lately.
- No. No, not stress... Walter,
come on.
You have been stressed out.
I guess I've had a
lot on my mind lately,
but as I said,
I'm feeling much better.
In fact, I'd leave right now.
When can I go?
No, that won't be possible.
I believe you'll be with
us for a few more days.
A few more days?
Yes, and we'll schedule
a psychiatric evaluation.
No, man,
come on. I don't think it's that serious.
Walter, I'm sorry. Nobody
likes being in the hospital,
but until we know what
caused this incident
we can't be certain
it won't recur.
How much do you have left?
A hit.
Finish it quick.
- Stand still!
- What's going on?
- On the floor! Pin her down,
pin her down!
- Pin him down now!
- Now, now, now!
Come on, come on. Do it now!
- I'm going, I'm going.
- Get him tight, tight!
- Don't you move!
- Let me go, man!
José Miguel Rosas, I presume.
What, man? What did I do?
Walk,
we're talking someplace else.
Careful!
- Okay, stop, stop! Be still now!
- Hey, dude!
I'll tell you what...
Tell me the whole
story once again.
Again? What's there to tell?
- Her and I were partying, that's it.
- Partying?
Partying for three days
straight? How do you do it?
What do you do?
After you have sex,
you have a shower,
dance, sing, eat...
You have sex again? No,
wait, I know.
You smoke that crystal
you got from Tuco?
Who the fuck is Taco?
I don't know any Taco.
And I didn't say crystal,
- don't make me lie.
- Fine, enough.
The fags of the hall, right?
We believe everything. Three
days without eating or going out.
So did you order take-out?
I guess.
Where from, the Chinese guy on
the corner? Some dog they've got.
No, we didn't necessarily order.
We got stuff from the
vending machine at the hotel.
You know,
chips and stuff. I had a croissant.
Chips and croissant.
And you didn't notice
your car was gone?
No, not until you guys went
and busted down the door
and took me by force.
Even then I didn't notice
because the car was gone.
Now who's going to pay for that?
Management's going
to be on my ass for sure.
You can't get away with that
because I have no
money to pay for that.
So why didn't you
answer your phone?
It was in my car.
Weird. We found your car,
but your phone wasn't in it.
You found my car?
Awesome!
Anti-Narcotics all the
way! You guys rule!
- That's cool!
- Hey, don't touch me!
Since we're talking
about missing property,
did you leave anything
else in the car?
Like what?
Forty-five thousand
nine hundred and fifty dollars.
I've never seen that case,
man. That's not mine.
That's not yours?
Says it's not his.
I really thought
that might be yours.
- I wish I had that much.
- Imagine that.
If I lose an amount like that
I might as well kill myself.
Listen, Gómez,
That's a new interdiction
van right there.
We can get the truck with that,
the uniforms,
the mini-soccer team...
Perfect!
Who's your boss, punk?
What does that even mean?
I think your story's bullshit.
You knew Tuco Salamanca.
I think your car was there
because you were there.
Tuco Salamanca had a
bullet in his midsection.
And I think you know why.
So, what are you saying?
I shot someone? With,
like, a gun?
Duh, duh,
duh... Who shot Tuco Salamanca?
Man, I don't know... I told you
I was partying with Guendy.
That's all there is to it.
Chips and croissant?
Your turn, Gómez.
The man won't cooperate,
so I'll tell you what.
Let's talk to the lady.
Some hot chick. Nice girl.
That's a good idea, buddy.
We could talk to
that skinny ass.
I don't know why,
but I have the feeling
that woman is going to talk.
And not only will she talk.
She'll drown you, man.
Don't you go nowhere.
I was about to forget...
Kind of heavy.
We'll be right back.
I'm thirsty.
And I want to piss.
I got medical issues.
Medical issues?
This chick looks like a dude...
Alright, Guendy,
tell us everything
and I'll grant you a bath
and something to eat, okay?
I don't know about the piss...
- If you volunteer...
- I'll pass.
Guendy,
tell me about the last three days.
I told you,
we were shacked up since Saturday.
Neither of you left the room?
Not even for a little minute?
I don't know,
maybe for a second...
José Miguel left, didn't he?
Guendy, Guendy, Guendy,
come on, look at me, look at me.
José Miguel did leave? Here,
here...
He did leave,
didn't he? Come on, tell me...
Tell me everything,
and I'll let you leave, okay?
Guendy!
You have clients to tend to,
but there's an awful whore
who's taking them for you.
So? Do you really want that?
Do you really want that,
or don't you?
I know. You came
up the other day.
You wanted me to do that kid.
Wait, wait. What are you saying,
Guendy?
She's absolutely wasted, man.
- She has no clue.
- But is he retarded,
or maybe deformed in his body?
Your mouth will be
deformed if you don't talk!
Come on now! Speak!
Okay, okay, okay.
José came over...
on Saturday
at 11 o'clock.
We were together the whole time,
and he never left the room.
Nobody ever left.
I really need to take a piss...
I think I'm sick.
- What a damn bitch.
Wait. Henry...
You actually took your
nephew to Guendy?
Are you some kind of pervert?
Wait, it's a long story, man.
No,
don't tell me. And another thing...
- José Miguel Rosas has to be released.
- No.
I've got one more shot
at that little skid mark.
Just wait and see, brother.
And how are you sleeping,
Walter?
Fine.
Most nights.
Have you noticed any
recurring thoughts or images
- you can't get out of your head?
- No.
How about feelings
of guilt or persecution?
Look, doctor,
I don't mean to be rude,
but where is this going,
exactly?
We're starting a process,
Walter.
- How long will it take?
- We've only just begun.
Could be days, weeks, months...
Look, I feel fine, really.
I mean it! I'm great. I'm...
Now, if this is truly necessary,
can't I continue
as an outpatient?
Walter,
a fugue state is a very serious event.
What if you were to
disassociate while driving?
Or you could be in
danger with the police.
You understand,
we can't allow you to leave
until we're certain what happened
was a non-recurring event.
Would you tell me
about patient confidentiality?
It's very straightforward.
Without your permission, I can't
disclose anything you tell me to anyone.
What about my family?
Not your family,
not to the police, not to anybody.
The only exception would be if
you threatened to kill someone.
Then I'd be able to tell that person,
but only that person.
And you abide by these
strictures absolutely.
Right.
Okay.
Right...
I confess there
was no fugue state.
I remember everything.
Look, doctor...
The truth is,
I couldn't stand
being in that house.
I needed to get out of there...
I needed to
breathe. And so I left.
I took a cab and
went to the station.
Then I took a bus to a small
town... I don't remember...
I stayed at a hotel
just thinking. That's it.
So, being found naked in a supermarket was
your way of giving credibility to a lie?
- That's right.
- Why run away?
What did you feel
you had to run from?
Doctor,
my wife is seven months pregnant
with a baby we didn't intend.
My 15-year-old son
has cerebral palsy.
I am an extremely overqualified
high school chemistry teacher.
My salary is barely
enough to live for a month,
while all my friends
and colleagues are rich.
Maybe in 18 months...
I'll be dead.
And you ask why I ran?
José Miguel?
I have this Tuco-nuts
person to introduce you to.
Got it?
This man is Héctor Salamanca.
Tuco Salamanca's uncle,
who you already know.
So, Mr. Salamanca,
can you understand
me when I speak?
That means yes.
One time means yes.
Two times means no.
No,
this has to be the worst joke ever.
He doesn't even know
what planet he's living on.
No, no...
Okay.
Let's do an exercise,
Salamanca, listen carefully.
I'll name several planets.
When I get to the right one
just say yes, or no.
Right now we're on Saturn.
We're on Mars.
Mr. Salamanca, we're on Earth.
Seems like he's all there.
Go ahead, Gómez. Ask away.
Mr. Salamanca.
This man right before you,
was he at your house?
Mr. Salamanca...
Was this guy in
your house or not?
Do you know him?
Did he do business
with your nephew Tuco?
Calm down, Mr. Salamanca.
Tell us.
Are you afraid of this man?
How can he be
afraid of this prick?
Come on, granddad. Calm down.
Cooperate with us.
Take him. I guess that's a no.
There you go.
That's a Mexican
old-school mob guy.
They'd rather drop
dead than help the police.
Right, but we had to try something,
didn't we?
There has got to be a way.
We have got to kick
him loose anyway.
I can't tell you how pissed I
am that the punk got away with it.
He's a punk,
after all. He's nobody anyway.
Gómez, are you saying you
buy that lame-ass story of his?
Do you really think
that wasn't his money?
- Tell me! Do you?
- Enough, enough already.
Wait, wait, let's be reasonable.
That much money
has got to be Tuco's.
- Whose else?
- Tuco, you say Tuco, Gómez?
That money's the punk's!
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Pay phone?
Yes,
everything's fine. Are you alright?
Yes, all good. How are things?
They asked me a bunch of stuff
and got me on edge for a while,
but then they let me go.
So when will you be out?
Tomorrow.
Who questioned you?
What did they ask you?
That's where we have a problem.
The man who questioned
me was your brother-in-law,
and he's even got
my mattress money.
What?
Yes, my money. The guy took
every single penny and left me nothing.
Not even for a bite.
Wait. What does he
know about the money?
No, man,
he doesn't know shit. The plan worked.
But I got bills due,
man. I'm screwed.
Did he mention my name?
No, never.
But thanks for
caring. I appreciate it.
- What about the basement?
- It's clean.
And the bus?
A friend's cousin
took it to his garage.
It's all under control.
Can he get it running again?
What? Why?
So we can cook.
So you still want
to cook? Seriously?
José Miguel,
nothing's changed here.
38 thousand dollars
for my kids' college,
plus the mortgage...
That would be two and
a half pounds a week...
The cash on hand.
Sorry, honey.
Did I wake you up?
No, he was awake.
Want me to get you
something to eat?
No, I'm not hungry. Thanks.
Are you okay?
Don't tell me you're still caught
up in the chemical storage thing?
Look, buddy.
What's this?
It's the blue meth. It
was found on Tuco.
People in the lab say
it got cooked,
P2P-style. What did I tell you?
So what are you thinking? The
two stooges over here cooked it?
Lab said that blue meth's
the purest they've seen.
At least since this.
This is El Loco's.
My God.
So what about these two?
I want to find out if there's any
relationship, working one or personal,
or maybe this one cooked,
or that one...
A simple explanation,
only I'm not seeing it.
Wait, before that melon of
yours gets completely bald,
let's go grab a beer.
It's 11 in the morning.
I'm buying.
- What?
- I'm buying.
Hey, come on,
now. Just come, come on.
One for each,
or do we have to share?
- A beer, I said a beer.
- What did I say?
We can sneak on that girl.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Surprise!
You sneaky bastard!
No, come, come,
look, look, look...
Just as ugly,
but with a nicer face.
But I have more
hair in this one.
Wait a minute, hold on.
Just a second, people.
We're going to
hand out the gift.
This is from all of us.
Good job, Henry.
Wow, thanks a lot. Thank you,
all of you.
Let's take a look...
Let's see what you got me...
No, Gómez, no, no, no, buddy.
Was it this sick bastard's idea? No,
what's this, man?
Alright! Cheers!
Thank you so much!
- Dad, don't you want juice?
- No, thanks.
But the nurse said you
have to stay hydrated.
But I'm not thirsty.
Dad, just drink up, okay?
Please.
All of it.
- Mr. Walter!
- Henry!
- Hey, kid.
- Hey, uncle.
Hey,
I'm sorry for not coming earlier.
How are you?
Hey, María got that, didn't she?
That's just like her!
She did, she came this morning
and brought me some color.
Hey, I just saw Cielo,
They're rounding up
a wheelchair for you.
You free-loading bastard!
So tell us about the shoot-out.
No, no, it was nothing.
Just doing my job. Whole thing
was over in about ten seconds.
So how are you?
Really,
I'm feeling fine. I'm getting discharged.
That means I'm okay.
I'm actually much better.
- Really?
- Yes, the doctor said...
Well, he said it was a kind of
transient global amnesia.
So is that contagious?
No, it means non-recurring.
It won't happen again.
That sounds good.
I'll tell you what, brother.
I'm glad your back.
I'm really glad. And
you're healthy and well.
You really gave us a scare.
I know.
Henry,
I just wanted to say
I'm truly ashamed.
With everything that happened,
and you were in danger.
I'm really sorry. I
want to apologize.
What are you saying,
man? That's what we're for.
Wouldn't you do the
same thing for me?
At the office,
they're treating me like I'm the king.
Like a national
hero or something.
They're making
parties and stuff.
A massage. That's not true,
not that.
But you know what? You
ought to disappear more often.
Just kidding. Listen, listen.
Look what they
gave me at the office.
- Sick people. Look...
- What's that?
That is the grill of
this Tuco Salamanca.
Who?
The guy I shot a few days ago.
- That's weird.
- I know, right?
Mexicans use this now
like some sort of trend.
Can you imagine this
guy with one of these?
How would he talk? How would he?
"Weirth, heth speath weirth".
I'll wash these clothes.
Listen, baby.
I can't tell you how
good it feels to be home.
Thank you.
Honey.
I was just thinking about going
to the store. Want anything?
I don't know, maybe a banana,
couple of plums.
This will not happen again.
I swear this won't
happen ever again.
Walter...
Do you have a second cell phone?
No. Why?
The night you disappeared
you were very upset,
something was going on.
We were talking,
and then your cell phone rang.
You didn't answer,
and then you just left.
- Really?
- Henry did some searching,
and that phone call
never showed up.
That's weird!
I don't remember any of that.
But one thing I am sure of is that
I don't have a second cell phone.