- So?
- What's up?
So what?
Got something for me?
Yes, man.
What's this?
Is this a "five" or an "s"?
No, it's a "five."
Or an "s"?
Let me see.
Yes, it's a "five", man.
How do you spell "street"?
S-T-R-E-A-T?
Did you write S-T-R-E-A-T?
You should know better!
All I do is sell meth.
I don't have time
for spelling.
S-T-R-E-A-T isn't correct?
So what?
Do they have names?
Yes, man.
The woman is a beanpole.
They call the man Poke.
Poke?
Yes, man.
Like the cartoon characters.
Tripa, did you get jacked
by a man called Poke?
Really?
Man, don't be confused.
The most dangerous men
of the country have nicknames.
There is Chupeta, Fritanga.
I wouldn't trust
a man called Poke.
You're looking for a reason
not to do it.
- I understand.
- Wait, wait.
Did I say that?
I'd do it myself.
My problem...
You know.
I'm on parole.
I can't do it.
- I'd do it, but--
- It's okay.
I told you I'd do it.
I'll take care of it.
Yes, man. I'll do it.
Great, man!
This is it.
We have to teach them
who is the boss in the street.
Do me a favor.
Be hard on him.
He scared me to death.
- Okay. You got it.
- We'll talk later. See you.
Give me my money!
The money, and I'll go!
No! "That I'll go", no.
"That'll go", no.
Give me my money!
I saw it! I saw it!
That's it.
Give me the money!
You messed up
with the wrong man.
I'm going to--
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Would you do me a favor?
Do you live here?
Why?
I need to leave you
some information
about a squad
of the community.
We'd like to invite you.
Thanks.
Have a nice day.
Good bye. Take care.
You too.
Is there anybody here?
Anybody?
Who's there?
I'm glad
to have you back again
in this, that is your kitchen,
Felipe's kitchen.
It's a great day.
I'm really happy
because I'll cook a recipe...
Hey, man.
It's very tasty.
Is there someone else
in the house?
You can cook it at home
for dinner or lunch.
You'll surprise
your couple or your family.
Or why not?
You can cook it for yourself
when you are alone at home.
Let's make some vegetables.
Are your parents at home?
You'll do it really fast
and ingredients are easy to get.
What's your name?
These are the ingredients.
I'm...
Pelanga.
One red pepper in slices.
Three cups of soy sprouts.
Four chopped green onions.
Five hundred grams
of broccoli.
A cup of mushrooms in slices.
One kilogram of Chinese cabbage.
Don't you rather watch
something better?
Something more interesting
like cartoons?
Sliced carrots.
This is preheated
because, as you may know,
we don't have the time
to cook it live.
Therefore,
we'll add it
and we'll sauté it
during thirty seconds.
Now we'll add the red pepper.
Do you know
when your parents will be home?
What time
will Mr. Poke be home?
I'm hungry..
Hello, you three.
Well, the four of you.
I just wanted to wish Walter
a good first day back at school.
I imagine him talking
about valences and covalences
and all those things
I don't even remember.
That's it. See you.
Cielo, call me back. Bye!
Walter, Cielo. This is Marcela.
I've been thinking of you.
I tried Walter's cell phone,
but the line
seems to be disconnected.
Whenever you have the time,
would you call me, please?
Hello, Marcela.
This is Cielo.
Cielo, am I catching you
at a bad time?
No. No, no.
Not at all.
Walter's back at work
and he lost his cell phone.
That's why
he didn't answer you.
I was worried.
I'm glad you called.
I know Walter would kill me.
He wanted to handle this
with extreme precaution.
You know him.
But I wanted to thank you
and Edgar for everything
you're doing for us.
For all the help
and the money
you've given us
for the treatment.
You're very generous.
You are the best.
- I--
- You don't have to say a word.
I'm deeply thankful.
You've saved us.
Well, I won't talk anymore.
Not at all.
When will we meet?
Let's have
a cup of coffee or something.
How about this afternoon?
Perfect!
Monoalkenes.
Polyenes, diolefins.
The nomenclature alone
is enough
to make your head spin.
I get it.
But I'll give you a key.
It's a basic key
to understand
what's all of this about.
That key is here,
in our periodic table.
There's one key element.
Carbon.
Do not forget about it.
Carbon is the center of life.
It's the center of it all.
There's no life
without carbon.
Everything that lives,
lived or will live
has to do with carbon.
Our director, Carmen,
is carbon.
Go on.
I like to think that the diamond
and the woman
who wears it on the finger
are both formed
from the same stuff.
As well as the man
who invented the diamond.
They are carbon.
Exactly. This is the truth.
I finally got your attention!
Write this name down.
Mr. Tracy Hall.
In the middle of the XX Century,
this man invented
the first reproducible process
for making synthetic diamonds.
Synthetic diamonds
are used nowadays
in the petrol industry
in the bits
for well drilling,
and in electronics industry.
Multi-billion dollar companies.
They produce millions of dollars
per year.
Do you know
how much money did they pay
Mr. Hall
for his discovery?
They gave him
a ten-dollar bond.
How about that?
Ten dollars
for this discovery.
He made them rich.
It's absolutely unfair!
Do you know
what my point is?
That ten-dollar bond
was printed
on a carbon-based paper
paid to a carbon-based man
for discovering something
made out of carbon.
Walter, it's so nice
to have you back with us.
And you're looking great.
Thanks.
I'm a little skinnier.
Yes, yes. Maybe a little.
That's definitely
no tragedy nowadays.
There's the hair thing.
Well, the lack of hair.
That's a great look for you.
Thanks.
How do you feel?
Tell me.
I'm fine.
I'm very well.
I'm happy to be here.
We're happy, too.
And I--
Is everything okay?
No.
I just want you to know
that you can come to me
if you need anything, Walter.
Any doubt,
any question, whatever.
Completely confidential,
of course.
I have to go.
Thank you.
- Bye, Morgan.
- Bye.
Morgan?
Are they still on that?
Morgan, the pirate.
What's wrong with Junior?
What's that?
Nothing.
Let me see it.
Don't worry about it.
Your classmates
don't have anything to do.
Hello.
Booh!
No?
Come.
Come here. Come on.
Stop. I don't want to.
Shut up!
Stay here,
and don't move. Okay?
Go to sleep
and don't wake up.
No matter what.
I'm serious.
Okay?
Come on! Do it!
Shut up!
You dropped it.
No, it fell!
- You dropped it!
Both of you, shut up!
Shut up!
Where...?
Where's my stuff,
and where's my money?
Do you know who did it?
I think I know who did it.
Do you know
what we're going to do?
Let's get him,
and put a bag
over his head.
We'll take him to the
countryside,
and strip him naked.
And we'll make him sit
on a ant's nest.
I saw it on a movie.
Do you like the plan?
If there're scorpions, I do.
Scorpions?
I like the idea.
Damn, dad!
What's that luxurious car?
Who would be visiting mom?
Who knows.
- Go in, I'll be right there.
- Okay.
And this is Junior.
But now
he wants to be called Morgan.
- Mom!
Son.
I'm giving her
both options.
This is Marcela, my love.
We've talked a lot about her.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks.
Hello.
- Hi.
- Marcela, I'm glad to see you.
You've changed your hair.
A bald head
is a bit of a shocker.
I know it was for me.
You don't look bad.
Thanks.
Thank you so much
for what you've done
for my dad.
You're very welcome.
We're going
to find a way to repay you.
Don't worry.
I hate to say it,
but I really need to get going.
I just wanted to say hi.
You should stay for dinner.
I have a something to do
with Edgar.
Some other time.
Let me walk you
to the door.
Your bag.
Nice meeting you.
Likewise. Thank you.
Goodbye.
Edgar and you
are welcome any time.
I'd love to be in touch.
Of course.
- Bye. See you.
- Let's go.
Marcela. Marcela.
Marcela, please!
Marcela.
Marcela, don't go, please.
I'd like to know
what you told her.
I know we have to talk.
In the meantime,
I need a big favor.
Don't say anything
to Cielo, please.
Marcela.
Please!
My money and my goods!
Where are they?
- Where?
- Okay, okay, okay.
What will you say?
You hit me really hard.
I think I'm seeing double.
Shut up and sit down!
- Does your head ache?
We'll have to see the doctor.
- I have to go to the doctor.
- Shut up, my love.
Empty your pockets.
Hurry up!
- Stand up!
- Stand up. Yes.
- Are you making fun of me?
Stand up here!
Empty your pockets!
Hurry up, shit!
Empty them! Do it!
- Shut up!
- There's nothing there.
- Your back pockets!
- We don't have--
They're empty.
- Your back pockets!
Hurry up!
- They're empty!
The shoes.
Put them here.
Put them here!
Calm down, brother.
We don't have nothing.
What happened then?
Where's everything?
We don't have anything
because we used it yesterday.
Really? Everything?
Do you think I'm stupid?
An ounce in a day and a half?
- We really wanted to do it.
- Yes.
Yes, poor him.
You know where it is.
Where is it?
Where could it be?
He has it.
He has it in his ass.
There it is.
Stop! You know where it is.
Take it out of your ass,
or I'll do it myself.
Stand up!
Hurry up, shit!
- Here.
- Put it on the table.
Don't you like it?
He doesn't like it.
I said shut up.
You're a nice couple.
One keeps the heroine,
and the other the meth.
Well done!
You're very organized.
- We're well organized.
- Yes, very well.
- Sit down!
But--
It's not complete.
Where's the rest of it?
It isn't complete.
- Do you want to hear the truth?
- Yes.
She did it.
She dropped it!
Don't betray me,
son of a bitch!
- Stop it!
- Go over there.
You stay there. Don't move!
Where's the rest of it?
He has a headache.
He has a headache,
my poor baby.
- He has a headache.
- I'm going to faint.
- Let's go to the doctor.
- Is he going to faint?
Poor her.
Listen to me.
I have six bullets.
One for each knee and I'll
cure his headache with this.
What do you think?
- No, please.
- Okay? What do you think?
What do you think?
Stop it.
My poor boy.
This is a rude man.
Do you know
what will happen?
You won't do anything
until I get back
what's mine.
You know how it feels,
don't you?
No.
- Don't you?
- No! What? No.
- Don't do this.
- You went too far.
- Then what are we going to do?
Look...
We can pay you.
- Really? Tell me.
- Plus interest.
How?
Stand up slowly.
Slowly.
Shut up!
That's my bank, too.
What are you doing?
Calm down.
They don't charge for this.
- Shut up!
- Shut up.
How did you bring that here?
With the help of technology.
- Be careful.
- Shut up!
Be careful.
Were there any witnesses?
Did they saw you?
No, we were very careful.
Yes, very careful.
What do you want?
Help me open it,
and take your money.
Nothing happens!
You told me
you stole six of them.
Yes, I swear it!
Yes, but one thing
is to steal it
and something different
is to open it.
Sure, but look--
Be patient,
and you'll succeed.
Seven is my lucky number.
I'll open it this time.
He won't do it.
Don't listen to that bitch.
Don't call me bitch!
- Okay, okay.
- Bitch, bitch.
- I'm not a bitch!
- Calm down!
Both of you, calm down!
I'll shoot you next time.
Open that damn box!
You sit down there
and stay calm.
Where's the kid?
- Where's the kid?
- I don't know.
That bitch.
- Don't call me that!
- See? That happens
...because you're a bitch.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
Don't call me that!
Bitch!
Don't call me bitch!
- Are you all right?
Bitch.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
Don't call me bitch.
Stay here.
Don't move, okay?
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
- Bitch, bitch, bitch.
- Don't call me bitch
Don't call me bitch.
- Bitch, bitch, bitch.
- Don't call me bitch.
Don't call me that.
Why do you call me that?
- Don't call me that.
- No? Okay.
Open that!
What are you thinking?
Why aren't you a good mom?
Your boy is right there.
Use this for something else
than using drugs.
Buy him some food.
Buy him some clothes,
a decent television.
What's the matter?
I have a headache.
I told you I have a headache.
Give me some.
give me some and--
- You have a son, get it?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Yes. Come on. Come on.
- I'll become a supermom.
Come on.
Give us some.
Stay there. Don't move!
Think, please.
Shut up.
Move over there.
Hurry up!
You're useless.
Sit over there.
What?
I don't get anything.
- You're useless.
Don't call me bitch.
I agreed on coming here
because you told me
you'd explain it to me.
But you haven't say a word.
No. I asked you to come
to talk to you.
I really appreciate you came.
So you didn't tell anyone?
Not even Edgar?
Not yet.
What does that mean?
Exactly that.
It's a determination
I have yet to make.
Yes, I understand.
And I respect it.
Fair enough.
I also asked you to come
because I wanted to apologize
for involving you
in this misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
Yes. I'm really sorry.
Okay.
Tell me why you did it.
The reason
doesn't matter right now.
You told me your insurance
was covering the treatment.
Is it true?
If you're not paying it
with Edgar's and my money--
how are you paying it?
I'm serious, Marcela.
That isn't your business.
Yes, it is my business.
You told
your wife and your son
that I was paying the treatment.
Why?
I will clear this up with them.
Cielo thanked me
very moved
because of everything
I was doing.
The look on her face
touched me.
Why did you do it?
Everything has an explanation.
I'm just asking you
to let me give it to them.
In my own way,
in my own time.
All right.
And while you're at it,
explain it to me.
I don't owe you
an explanation.
I owe you an apology.
And I have apologized.
I am very sorry.
I've apologized twice now.
Marcela, I'm sorry.
Three times.
Let me just get this straight.
Edgar and I offer
to pay for your treatment.
We didn't expect anything
in return.
That offer still stands.
And out of pride
or whatever,
you turn us down.
And then you tell your wife
that in fact
we're paying for your treatment.
You involved us in your lie.
But you sit here and tell me
that it's none of my business?
That's pretty much
what I'm telling you.
What happened to you?
This isn't you.
What would you know about me?
Do you really think to know
who I am?
Who?
Someone who should go begging
for charity?
Do you really think
you can use your checkbook
like some magic wand
and make me forget
that you cut me out?
I don't understand.
I didn't think--
That was my work,
my research.
You became rich out of it.
- I can't understand that--
- Thank you.
I'm really thankful.
- You left.
Yes.
You've always been
the picture of innocence.
Just sweetness and light.
You left me.
My parents' property,
Holy Week.
I went up to our room,
and you were packing your bags.
Did you forget about it?
That's your excuse
to build your empire on my work?
You walked away.
You abandoned Edgar and me.
That's great.
Little rich girl
addicted to her millions.
I don't even know
what to say to you.
I'm so sorry
you feel like this.
I feel sorry for you.
Fuck you.
Little man,
are you hungry?
Booh!
Come, my love.
Look, Poke, I got him!
That idiot says
I'm a bad mother.
Come on, son of a bitch!
Who's the big tough guy now?
Try and hit me now.
Come on! Hit me now?
How many bullets do you have?
Six? Yes?
Come on, hit me now,
son of a bitch!
Come on! Stand up!
Stand up!
Good evening.
Hi. Good evening.
Should I ask where you've been?
Never mind.
It doesn't matter.
We need to talk
about more important things.
Marcela called a while ago.
We need to talk, Walter.
They won't pay
the treatment anymore.
What did she say, exactly?
She said she was sorry.
They couldn't help us anymore.
Good luck, and that was it.
She sounded apologetic.
I called her back,
and she didn't pick up.
What do you know about this?
I'll tell you something.
This is really strange.
She came home this afternoon,
and was very happy,
very calm,
but she got nervous
when you arrived
and decided to leave.
And now she called
and told me that.
What do you know
that I don't?
Where were you, Walter?
I was with Edgar and Marcela.
What? Why?
It was obvious
that she had something to say
when she came here.
For some reason
she couldn't tell you nor me.
I needed to clarify
that situation.
What happened?
Well, we talked
for a long while.
Actually, they talked a lot.
But they didn't say anything.
They used
a lot of business phraseology.
Leveraged, liquidity.
- Quarterly decrease.
- What did they tell you?
What did they say, Walter?
They were truly saying
that they're broke.
No.
Yes.
They made bad investments.
And they were too ambitious.
That's unbelievable.
I can't believe it.
Why didn't she tell me?
Out of pride, I guess.
Calm down.
My love, most of the treatment
has already been paid.
We're much better
than we used to be.
We're going to make it
I promise.
And she still drives that car?
Even when they're broke?
It's unbelievable what they do
to keep up appearances.
Showy.
It isn't worth it.
It won't work!
Yes, it will.
Don't you see
the lower part is weaker?
Who says so? Who?
It's logic.
If this were the strongest part,
it'd be facing up.
That heroin was too strong.
It's on my head.
You took too much.
I told you!
If I use some meth,
I'll even out.
No!
You've lost your share.
Just a little bit.
No! Shut up!
Don't bother me!
You're a stupid bitch!
Don't call me bitch!
You're a son of a bitch!
You are!
I want an apology!
- Let me do my job!
- Apologize!
- Now!
- Apologize.
You're unbearable.
Why do I have to apologize
for telling a bitch
that she's a bitch.
Bitch. Bitch, no!
Apologize! Say you're sorry.
No! Bitch, bitch,
bitch, bitch, bitch.
- Bitch, bitch, bitch.
- No!
I want you to apologize.
Say that you're sorry
for calling me a bitch.
Emergency line.
Good evening.
Can I help you?
- Help! Please!
- Hello?
Hello, sir, can you hear me?
Sir, give me your location.
Hello, how are you?
So? Do you remember our game
about covering your eyes?
Do you remember it?
Cover your eyes.
You'll cover your eyes,
and you won't open them.
Ever, ever.
You can't open them. Ready?
I'm taking you with me.
One, two.
Come on. Cover them well.
Don't look at anything.
Don't look.
Cover your eyes.
I've just received
an emergency call
from Primera de mayo St.
and Sesenta y Nueve St.
Go there immediately.
It's okay.
Let's change the game.
You won't go back inside.
Ready?
I hope life
is good with you now, kid.