The attack on my brother-in-law,
I don't get what it means.
- I fear for my family.
- Don't worry about your family,
Walter.
I am told the assassin that
survived is gravely injured.
I doubt he'll live.
I was told he's
recovering.
Now thank me
and shake my hand.
Mr. Gustavo,
thanks again
for everything you're doing.
Thank you
and Pollos Hermanos.
Our pleasure, Walter.
Good night.
One, two, three.
He's gone.
9:44.
The Police and other authorities
are working together
to identify
the dead suspects.
I can give you highlights.
Your nephews grew impatient.
They wanted my permission
to kill Walter Blanco,
but since I didn't grant it,
they settled instead
for Henry Navarro.
Right before the attack,
Agent Navarro
got a call
and that gave him leverage.
Oscar Luis
was shot in the face
and died instantly.
Luis Oscar
lingered for several hours more.
About who made the call...
That doesn't matter.
I have information
about Juan Bolsa.
The Federals went to his place
and in the confusion
he was shot dead.
It might have been an accident
or a mistake from his own men.
We may never know.
I thought you should hear this
from me.
That is what comes
of blood for blood, Héctor.
An eye for an eye,
blood for blood.
I can't talk now.
Leave a message.
I'm waiting to hear a report
on what we discussed.
Call me back, please.
I mean, one minute
I'm starting a new
business.
My wife and I are thinking
about having kids.
Walk into a doctor's office
and everything changed.
It was like an alert
for me.
It was a wake-up call.
I learned I had
to give up control.
It's like they say,
you know?
Man plans and God
laughs.
You definitely cannot plan
anything in life.
That's bullshit!
- Excuse?
- You can never give up control.
Live up on your own terms.
I get what you're saying,
but cancer is cancer.
To hell with cancer!
I've been living with cancer
for the better part of a year.
It's a death sentence.
That's what they
keep telling me.
Every life comes with
a death sentence.
So every few months,
I come here for my regular scan
knowing that in any moment
than can give me the worse news.
So fuck it all!
May be today, may be not.
But until then,
who's in charge?
Me!
That's how I live my life.
Those potatoes were frying
for more than seven minutes.
We have to deliver food in time
to the clients.
Besides, the potato loses its
flavor and texture.
Understood?
Pollos Hermanos delivery.
Yes,detective.
- Shall we?
- Take a seat, Gustavo.
Thanks.
I'd like to record
this conversation,
if that's okay.
- No problem.
- Shall we start?
Yes, please. I'm anxious to know
what this is about.
We found your fingerprints
in a crime scene.
Really?
That's surprising.
A drug-related homicide.
At Guido Bermúdez's apartment.
So you knew the victim.
About 12 years ago,
I started a scholarship
at the University of Science
of Colombia.
I called it
Maximiliano Arciniegas
for a friend who died young.
Mr. Bermúdez
got a scholarship.
- He graduated in...
- 2004.
That's it.
So you've been in touch
with him since then?
No, no, no. I lost his trace
for a couple of years
until I ran into him
a couple of weeks ago.
Where did you run
into him?
At my restaurant.
But "run into"
is not the right word.
He had intentions of getting
back in touch with me.
He invited me to dinner
and I accepted.
About a week later,
I heard about his death.
You said it was drug-related?
There's a great chance.
The paper didn't say
any of that.
I thought it was some robbery.
Let's see if I get this.
You hadn't seen each other
in a while, right?
So he showed up at your
restaurant our of the blue,
you talked, got up to date
and he invited you to dine
at his place.
- AM I following you so far?
- Yes. He needed money.
Excuse me, Mr Gustavo,
he asked you for money?
He didn't say it openly.
He talked vaguely
about some business opportunity.
To clear out your doubts,
I was surprised
by his invitation.
Guido was a talented chemist,
but for some reason I don't get,
he was more interested
in taking some shortcuts
that in what would have been
a very promising career.
But personal shortcomings
notwithstanding,
he was a warm,
gentle person,
and I thought a lot of him.
I declined his business offer.
We just had dinner and I left.
Mr. Gustavo,
can you tell us
were you were
on Wednesday 23rd
at about 8 PM?
It's not an accusation,
just a question.
Don't worry.
Let me check.
- 23rd?
- Yes.
It was quite an important event.
I was at a fundraiser
at Presbyterian Hospital.
Children with cancer.
We were there from 7 to 10 PM.
- Anything else?
- Yes, just a question.
Is Gustavo Cortés
your real name?
- My real name?
- Yes.
You're just related
to Pollos Hermanos.
Nothing else.
- Really?
- Yes.
I've been checking the records
and there's no Gustavo Cortés.
And when trying to access
the information,
it says "Access denied".
it's as though you didn't exist,
do you get me?
Don't you think that's strange?
No, I don't think so.
During a long time in my life
I worked for the government
trying to achieve peace
with the guerilla.
I helped making contact
and provided
some relevant information.
They decided they had to protect
my identity
for national security matters.
I guess they did it so well
you can't find the records now.
I shouldn't be telling you this,
but since it's necessary,
there's no problem.
After all,
we're in the same team.
I think that's enough.
Gustavo, thank you
very much.
My pleasure. I hope I was
of some small help.
- You were, absolutely.
- Fine.
- Thanks for coming. Goodbye.
- My pleasure.
- Say hi to Catalina, please.
- Thanks.
Goodbye.
No, it's not necessary.
I'll wait for you
at the restaurant.
Goodbye.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
- So what do you think?
- Of what?
This thing with the name.
If it happens to be true
that he made a deal
with the government
to negotiate with the guerilla,
we'll never get
this guy's real identity.
Much less anything
about his past,
that's totally erased.
Let's analyze the case.
He was in a witness protection
program
because his life was in danger.
That gives him a status:
Victim.
Perhaps, perhaps not.
Don't forget these witnesses
are generally snitches.
They choose this option
just to save their lives.
I don't know
what to think about this guy.
He could be a Messiah,
a drug dealer,
from the guerilla,
from the military.
All we know for sure
is that he's a ghost.
That's all.
- He's clean for me.
- Come on, Gómez.
No, he's not related
with this case.
I just had a doubt
about why his fingerprints
were in Bermúdez's house.
He explained that
and the scholarship.
I'll admit to a certain degree
of bias.
He's a friend of the Department.
He's one of our best
business relationships
and his story sounded credible.
No, we're not doubting
about this man's ability
to tell stories.
What do you mean?
Isn't it strange to you
that we're hearing this story
just now?
Didn't you just say
he's a good guy
who helps the community
and is a friend of the
Department?
Why didn't he call you
and tell you:
"Hey, I have a connection
with Guido Bermúdez"?
If he didn't want to ask you,
why not call
one of his friends here
and ask him
about the investigation?
But he didn't!
Why?
Why didn't he call?
We can't predicate
a criminal investigation
on a person
not making phone calls.
- Gómez?
- No, no. He's clean for me.
God! Ramón?
I'll investigate
about the scholarship
and the Presbyterian Hospital,
but regarding the story,
I believe him.
Ha!
Hi.
Good morning.
Is everything all right?
Thanks.
This is for this
month.
Plus a little extra
in case there's...
- Who's this?
- Byron.
Hey, champ!
How are you?
Buddy!
- How are you?
- Fine.
How's the new school?
- Really?
When I was your age,
I loved studying.
I liked reading, playing with
marbles and chasing girls
with sticks.
That was the best!
Old good times.
Don't you ever left him
go to Law School, please.
I'm just kidding!
All right!
He's definitely a champ.
Hope you'll be fine.
So can you thank José
for both?
Of course I will.
Sure.
How is he doing?
He's fine.
Perfect.
Very busy.
Bye.
My pleasure.
- Enjoy it. It's very nice.
- Thanks.
Mission accomplished!
So? What is it like?
Very nice.
It's a big house
with lots of light.
It's all right.
I saw the kitchen
and she's got a little
garden out there.
How's Byron?
José Miguel, I don't mind
dropping checks off
every moth for her.
For real.
I'm your friend,
your lawyer,
but if you really want to know
how they're doing,
why don't you go
see for yourself?
See you later.
That's it!
Do I wait for you?
No, it's okay.
Okay.
I'm the perfect bodyguard.
Ha!
Son of a bitch!
So how was your scan?
Did you get the results?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm still in remission.
So you're all going to have to
be stuck with me
for a while longer.
Cheers, buddy!
Cheers!
Cheers. Thanks.
Cheers.
And how are you
feeling?
Fine. I'm getting better.
The other day he
had a big pow-wow
with all the anti-narcotics
muckity-mucks.
What was that about?
Nothing in particular.
Just a dead end.
He won't tell me either.
Walter, can you do me a favor
tomorrow?
María is working tomorrow
and there's a minerals show
I'd like to go.
Can you give me a ride?
Sure, of course!
Walter, thank you.
You spared me that one.
You're so mean.
I had a collection of my own
back in high school.
Just entry-level beryls
and garnets,
one passable black
tourmaline.
- I should turn here, right?
- No, no, no. Stay on this one.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, stay on this one. Do it.
But I did have one piece of
morganite that was very special.
It had been heat treated,
so it had that classic cast to
it, that rose,
- almost salmon hue.
- Listen, Walter.
There's no rock show
today, okay?
I just told that to María
so that she wouldn't freak.
So that she wouldn't freak?
Why? Where are we going?
You'll see.
Stay on this one.
What are we doing here?
Are you hungry?
- No, no, no,
We're not here for the chicken.
- So?
Park here.
And turn the car off.
Buddy, are you ready?
You ready for your mind
to be blown?
Are you ready?
Yes, yes.
Come on.
Remember Gustavo Cortés?
The guy who went to hospital
after the attack,
the one who offered a reward,
he's a friend of the Police,
the one who sponsors
these police races...
Yes, those marathons.
Well, I suspect,
because I still have
no evidence,
that he's a drug dealer.
For me, this man
is the meth Pablo Escobar.
He controls the business
in the U.S., Central America,
South America.
You remember Guido Bermúdez?
This gay guy
from "Maldita Primavera",
- that karaoke I showed you?
- Yes, sure.
Remember you told me
this guy was no genius
and there should be
someone much tougher above him?
- Remember that?
- Henry, I had been drinking.
- It was just a speculation.
- No, I don't care, buddy.
Thanks to what you told me
I kept on investigating
And you know what I found?
Gustavo Cortés' fingerprints
appeared in the crime scene
of Guido Bermúdez.
So...
You think Gustavo
killed Guido?
No, no, no.
These guys use a dunce
to pull the trigger,
but those fingerprints
was enough for us
to bring Gustavo Cortés in.
You brought him in
to anti-narcotics?
Right.
He sat down to talk to us.
He was totally calm,
like nothing had happened.
And what did you ask
him?
Did he say anything in
concrete?
Will you let me
finish my story?
- Will you?
- Yes, I'm sorry.
It's just that this is
so exciting.
I'm just anxious
to get to the end.
Listen.
We began asking him questions.
We told him that his
fingerprints had appeared and...
The guy had an explanation
for everything.
We asked him
about Guido Bermúdez' murder
and he had the perfect alibi.
He'd been with the Presbyterians
and I don't know what else.
Whatever.
You should have seen him.
"How can I help you?"
He was so calm.
He left us all speechless.
So you think
he's not guilty?
For Homicides and
Anti-narcotics, he's not.
He's officially not a suspect,
but for me...
For me, this is the guy
I'm after.
The thing
is I still have no evidence.
And...
Henry, why are you
telling me this?
- You see that silver van?
- Yes.
That's Gustavo Cortés' car.
I need you to help me with this.
You have to stick this on it.
You know what this is?
A GPS tracker.
This is what wives use
when they think their husbands
are crewing around.
It's a magnet,
so they stick it
under the car
and see where
their husbands were.
You get it?
Unfortunately,
it's not live use,
so we got to come back later
and take it off
and stick it in the computer
- to see where he was.
- Listen.
Isn't that illegal?
- Isn't it forbidden?
- Don't worry, buddy.
This is called "extralegal".
It'll cause no problem,
believe me.
Trust me.
It's out little secret.
This is what I need you to do.
You untie your shoelaces,
get off the car
and walk normally.
When you walk
by Gustavo Cortés' car,
you look down, see your shoelace
is untied,
so you bend, tie it,
stick this, get up,
get in there
and order whatever. That's all.
Henry, you know me.
I don't feel good
about this at all.
- I get nervous.
- I know.
I know you're not used
to doing these things.
But you need to get some action
in your life.
You have to get out
of your comfort zone.
- Right?
- I think this is a mistake.
- Come on, buddy. Help me.
This is very important
to me, Walter.
Do I have to beg you?
Just give me a hand.
Don't make a mess out of it.
Just go, stick it
and that's all.
Come on!
It's not a big deal.
Just act normal.
¡Do it!
Fine.
Untie your shoelace.
That's it.
- Next.
- I'll do it.
- Can I help you?
- I need to explain this to you.
I want you to know
that I didn't...
- How can I help you?
- I didn't do it.
I won't do it.
Do it.
Can I help you
take your order, sir?
What was that?
I was just checking it was
in place and working.
And the nuggets?
Just kidding. Let's go.
I swear it!
I swear I thought
we were going to a rock show,
a display...
All of a sudden, he had me
pulling to Pollos Hermanos.
That's when he told me
he's investigating you.
He's operating
on pure conjectures.
And no one, not one person
that he works with him
thinks that you are anyone other
than an owner
of a fast food chain.
But if something
were to happen to Henry,
then that would only draw
their attention to you and me
and...
So we have a mutual interest
in resolving this
without violence.
I'll make sure
that he discovers nothing.
I promise.
José Miguel!
- What?
- Hi.
Sure, get in.
Don't wit to be invited.
Are we alone?
No. Can't you see
all the people here?
Where do we stand on what?
stand?
Where do we stand with the thing
you were supposed to do?
Have you done it?
You still have the poison
for Gustavo?
Have you lost it?
You'd tell me if you
lost it, right?
Why don't you check it
yourself?
You can't stop
fucking me around.
Go do it yourself!
Maybe he saw me coming here.
No, no. It's okay.
You do it.
José, you have to make
this meeting happen.
This week.
Tomorrow.
- Tonight if possible.
It'd be ideal.
- Yes, tonight.
- Yes, yes!
- Tonight, okay..
What? Are you high?
My brother-in-law
from narcotics
is on to Gustavo.
Did you hear
what I just said?
My brother-in-law is on Gustavo!
Fine, fine. I got it.
Let me think!
So what if this
is like Math or Algebra?
You add a plus douche bag
to a minus douche bag
and you get zero douche bags.
I've got some Math
for you.
Henry catching Gustavo
equals Henry catching us.
He's relentless.
He won't quit!
- He's got nothing.
- How do you know that?
Because he's still alive!
You think a dude like Gustavo
would let your boy
anywhere near him?
He'll break out his box cutter
on his sorry gimp ass.
You haven't seen him again
since that time at the diner?
He's got to be figuring
that we've talked.
That's it.
You need to tell Mario
that you're worried
about Henry's investigation.
Why?
Because he knows you.
Henry knows who you are.
Besides, you did kill Guido.
This is perfect
for you to ask
to meet with Gustavo
so you can discuss
what you'd say
in case Henry
brings you in for questioning.
You get that?
So in that moment,
when you're near him,
you poison him.
Mario will tell me
to shut my mouth
if I get busted.
He won't set up
any meeting.
Then insist on!
Do something!
Act panicked!
Gustavo's ass is at stake.
He'll meet you
if he thinks
you're a liability.
No, Walter.
He'll waste me
if he thinks
I'm a liability.
Whatever.
I'm going to take a piss.
You got a phone call.
Anything important?
Come in.
- I did some digging.
- And?
Neither Anti-narcotics
nor Homicides consider
you a person of interest.
What about
Walter's brother-in-law?
Henry Navarro
is looking into you on his own.
- A voice in the wildness.
- Does he have resources?
Just him,
his credit card
and his chauffeur Walter.
That means
- nobody ordered him
to track me.
- No.
He's on his own.
Let's watch our backs,
don't thrown them any bones.
He'll never get any evidence.
What about my past?
If they couldn't trace you,
I seriously doubt Navarro
can do it on his own.
Seems to me
the biggest problem
is the cartel.
We can handle them
if that's all we have
on our plate.
But dealing with both Navarro
and the Mexicans...
Do you get me?
If Henry Navarro
happens to be watching us
when they make a move,
they could be
the perfect storm.
Thanks.
I'll be in touch.
Hi, Héctor.
The cartel gave me
its ultimatum,
to which I've said no.
Agent Henry Navarro
from anti-narcotics
is a concern.
He's looking into my past.
Is today the day, Héctor?
Gustavo.
Calm down.
You're making me
nervous.
Stick to the plan.
It'll all be okay.
I know it'll be okay.
But I'm nervous.
They're coming.
Hello.
Mr. Héctor!
If the boss sees you,
he'll cut your balls!
Not if you don't tell him.
And they won't say a word
because they like what they see.
Mr. Juan, it's a pleasure
to see you again.
- Gustavo.
- How are you?
So Mr. Héctor?
You're not giving
anything to our guests?
Who said they're guests?
If the boss
wants them to drink something,
it's up to him, not me.
Pollos Hermanos is really good.
Mr. Héctor, the chicken is good.
I tried it in Colombia.
It's really good!
One is black
the other is white.
You don't look
like brothers to me.
The great Colombian chefs
are here!
- Mr. Eladio.
- How are you?
- Mr. Eladio, how are you?
- Hi. Take a sit.
Thanks.
I hope you're taking care
of my guests.
Yes, sir.
It's all good, Mr. Eladio.
Thanks.
Good.
- I've just tried
some great chicken.
- You liked it?
I swear for my mother
I'd never tried
anything like that.
That's good. You should tell
that to Maximiliano.
He's the chef.
Gustavo is so kind.
He's the reason
we're on business.
You should continue that way.
It has something
I haven't figured out yet.
- My men love it, right?
- Yes, there's none of that
in Mexico.
It's a rural recipe.
I adapted it.
And they bought it!
If you're the cook,
what the hell do you do?
Don't tell me you
just try the chicken.
No. I manage
Mr. Eladio's business.
- Gustavo is very good
at doing business.
- The businessman.
Offer me something else
you have on the menu.
Something special.
We have some side dishes.
Potatoes, fried yucca,
ribs...
- Ribs?
- Yes.
Juan loves ribs.
Anything else?
Any dessert?
Be honest, dudes.
I'm just asking
because when my men
went to Colombia
to make a deal over cocaine,
they didn't just talk
about the chicken.
So let me ask you,
are you producing
and distributing meth?
No, Mr. Eladio.
Excuse me,
but we didn't sell.
We sent samples.
- Samples?
- Yes.
What a businessman!
What we did with your men
was giving them some samples
so that you met our product.
Good.
Mr. Eladio, we didn't want
to bother you.
We just wanted to call
your attention
so that we work together
on this new product.
Don't worry.
We know meth here already.
We're producing it,
but not in bulk.
The business
just doesn't grow here.
They love it
but there's no business.
Excuse me Mr. Eladio,
I'm a biochemist.
I lived in the U.S. and
I've seen how this business
is growing.
The meth you sell
is not as good
as the one we produce.
It's not know in Colombia so we
have free access to inputs.
Besides, with our process,
we guarantee
it's crystal meth.
It's like glass.
It's pure.
The same molecule is different
and that makes
the structure different.
Therefore, the narcotic
effect is stronger.
Mr Eladio,
what we want to tell you
is this is the drug
of the future.
You could double or triple
your incomes
if you sold our meth.
The business has no owner
in Latin America.
This would be a big business
opportunity for you.
We could offer you
to build a lab in Colombia
so that you could produce it.
We think that's the way
for you to separate
from the Colombian cartels
and control the region.
You're not just good
cooks.
You're really good
at talking bullshit.
Héctor, they're my guests!
Go on.
Mr. Eladio, right now
you just do business
with Colombia
for the cocaine.
Mexico doesn't produce cocaine,
so that makes you
intermediaries.
We're offering you
a great opportunity
for you to gain independence.
The Colombians give you
money
so that you cross the drugs
through the border.
You're risking it all
and the Colombians
take the money.
Think about this.
Meth is more powerful,
more addictive and it can
be moved in bulk.
Best of all, it's artificial.
We can set up a plant
here in Mexico
or in Colombia.
As you wish.
You'd keep all the profit.
My men love the product, right?
Yes, it's really good.
Héctor, serve some tequilas
to my guests.
Come on.
Where did you get
this chemist stuff from?
I studied.
Gustavo paid for two careers.
I'm a biochemist
and chemical engineer. I studied
in Colombia and in the U.S.
With a minimum
investment,
you could set up a plant
here.
We could teach your people
how to make a better-quality
meth and in bulk.
So if I wanted a businessman,
someone to take care of business
over there,
what for would I want a cook?
And if I wanted a cook,
someone who cooked meth here,
what for would I want you?
Mr. Eladio...
Shut up, idiot.
What for do I want
any of you?
Coming to my own house
to do business
in front of my men
and disrespect me.
What, asshole?
- Please,Mr. Eladio...
- Please what?
We didn't intend
to offend you.
We just wanted
to have this meeting
in a friendly way.
We're sorry if we bothered you.
We just wanted you
to know our product.
Mr. Eladio,
Gustavo is the most loyal
and honorable person I know.
He got me out of poverty,
the place I was in.
He helped me become
who I am.
He's a genius!
He could make you earn millions!
Mr. Eladio,
please take into account--
Look at him.
Listen to me, bitch.
You know why you're still alive?
Because I want to.
I know you.
You're the fucking chemist.
From now on, you belong to me.
You work for me.
For the Tapatio cartel.
You'll sell us
all the inputs needed
to produce meth.
Don't be sad, dude!
Welcome to the family!
You want some advice?
Don't forget about the chicken.
Look at me,
Héctor.
Look at me, Héctor!
I should kill you
before the cartel kills me.
That would be
a great satisfaction.
But it won't be today.
Maybe next time.
I don't want to do you
that favor yet.
Expect no mercy from me.