Hey, my friend.
I'll watch it for you.
Okay.
Thanks.
This is stupid.
Do you have a better idea?
I can't think of a worst idea.
- Really?
- Yes.
You call me to a secret meeting
in a place full of cameras.
And you are acting
all nervous,
like if you're going
to steal something.
I'm sure the cashier
doesn't stop looking at you.
If you don't have
anything good to say,
at least shut up and listen.
Whatever, bro.
- When do we start?
- No cooking for now.
Could you stop staring at me?
Pretend you're buying something.
You really piss me off, man.
We have to wait
until things settle down.
What do you mean "settle down"?
I thought you're the one
that said nothing's changed.
I just put my family
through an ordeal.
I can't leave my house
for more than 20 minutes
without my wife worrying.
I need time to mend fences.
I'm not free right now.
I need to regain
my wife's trust.
So while you're fixing fences,
what about me?
Your brother-in-law
took all my money.
I have my own needs.
I don't have to pay
for your carelessness.
You're the one who wanted
to work with Tuco.
I told you not to,
but you didn't hear me.
Otherwise,
- none of this
would've happened.
- Just be cool.
Shut up for a minute.
POLICE
Are you going to grow up?
Can't you be patient?
It's easy for you to say so.
Jose, we're going to cook.
But, as for now, no contact.
Where are you going?
I leave first.
And buy something.
Do it, shit.
Really?
And where is the money?
Bitch.
Walter?
- Walter!
- I'm in the kitchen!
- Good morning.
- Good morning!
I didn't know you were allowed
to touch the stove.
You're missing your clown nose.
I have done orange juice.
- Good morning...
- Honey, good morning.
Don't worry.
I'm also doing all the dishes.
Have a seat.
Follow this delicious scent.
Let's see...
Look.
- We have orange juice,
grapefruit juice...
- Thanks.
We have pancakes, coffee.
Have a seat.
I've never been a fan
of grapefruit juice,
but considering
all the polyphenols
and the albuminoids,
can't hurt.
Grapefruit juice?
You didn't have to do this.
I wanted to.
Grapefruit juice?
- Orange.
Here you have your orange juice.
Gentleman?
- Here you have.
- Thanks.
- Are you ready, José?
- What for?
I don't know
why you called me here.
Go ahead.
No, no, no.
Not another intervention,
please.
Have a seat.
Okay, José Miguel...
Pursuant to article 376
of the Real Property Code,
you are hereby given notice
to vacate the premises
listed as street 31,
18A-51, where you live.
Wait a minute.
Are you kicking me out
of my own house?
It's your nan's house.
She gave it to me.
She never gave it to you,
José Miguel.
You were allowed
privileges for residence.
Your parents have always been
the property owners.
Look, we talked about this,
okay?
I'd sell the house,
we'd split it fifty-fifty.
What the hell happened?
I don't want my mother's house
to be a drug dealers residence.
What?
An anti-narcotics agent
came looking for you.
Because I've actually
been helping them,
which I could get into a lot
of trouble for telling you.
I saw your basement, honey.
I was worried, so I went
over there and I let myself in,
and I found your laboratory.
You guys have your own key?
José Miguel, the illegal
manufacture of drugs
is a second-degree felony.
Under federal asset seizure,
the government can take
the entire house.
It's not even there anymore.
I cleaned it all out.
Son, we can't stop you
from ruining your life,
but we will not allow you
to drag us down with you.
José Miguel, you have 72 hours
to vacate the house.
Otherwise, your parents have
authorized me
to contact the authorities.
I hope you understand it.
Do you have
any questions for us?
Okay. Three days, José Miguel.
You are served.
Please, come on.
Don't you know Daniel Santos?
I'm sure that some guy
like Daniel Santos
has a lot more of attitude
than any current rocker.
I'm sure about that!
And do you know current rockers?
Me? I know them all.
There is that...
The one with long hair.
He's dating that brunette.
What's his name?
Give me a second.
I will remember it.
Lucho is here for me, dad.
Good luck with that.
- Bye, mom.
- Tell Lucho to drive carefully.
I will remember.
Did you like breakfast?
You're welcome.
- No, relax.
- Thanks, Walter, thanks.
He doesn't know
who Daniel Santos is.
We have failed as parents.
I forgot to tell you.
There is a seminar
for amateur managers.
It's a course lectured
by one of those Hindu gurus
- you really like.
- And what about that?
The school sort of finances it,
and they give incredible
discounts for employees
and their families,
so I thought you would like...
I'll go with you, if you like.
Think about it.
I've been thinking
about the cell phone a lot.
I think what you heard
was my cell phone alarm.
The alarm sound was exactly
the same as the regular
phone ring,
so I wanted to change it,
but I'm not good with technology
and I think I messed it up.
We can go to the shop now
and I can get a new cell phone.
I can actually buy one
less complicated...
Cielo?
Cielo.
Cielo, honey!
Hi.
- How are you?
- Fine.
Good to hear that.
Honey, you know what?
I fixed the door
in Junior's bathroom.
It was bent.
- Not anymore.
Great.
How are you?
Where were you today?
Out.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
For what it's worth,
I was thinking about going back
to those meetings,
the cancer support group.
I think that's good.
Yeah, that's good.
You were right about that.
It's good to talk about things.
Yes.
I think that's great.
Jose...
José Miguel.
Jose!
- Hi, mom.
- Why don't you answer
the phone?
I've just been pretty busy.
How did you get in?
Right, you have your key.
What's up?
Mom...
So I've been thinking a lot
about our conversation
and I completely get why dad
tweaked off on me like that.
It's not just your father.
I know, which is why
I wanted to talk to you.
I've been thinking
real seriously
about business school,
maybe economics.
Are you listening to me, mom?
Hey, this is good.
You know, we're talking,
starting a dialogue.
The time for talking
has passed, José.
What do you mean?
Who are these people?
What are you doing?
No, no, no.
Where do you take that?
That's my trunk, bro!
What's going on, mom?
I thought
it was just a wake-up call.
We are putting it in storage.
When you decide to grow up,
you can have it back.
When I decide to grow up?
Why don't you grow up, mom?
My grandmother wanted me here.
I was the one
who took care of her.
I took her
to her doctor appointments
and made her lunch every day.
Don't lie, son.
I was here to see her
lying there dying.
Where were you?
Don't start with me.
I'm not going to answer.
Now what?
You've decided to make
your eldest son homeless?
Great mother,
you deserve some award.
Why are you like this,
José Miguel?
Why is this
the only way with you?
Leave your keys
in the kitchen counter
when you leave.
I have nowhere to go.
Where am I supposed to go?
I don't know!
I don't know. But please
turn your life around.
This is going to help
big time with that.
Thanks for everything!
- Hi, Lucho.
- Hi.
How are you?
- Come in.
- No, thanks, Mr. Walter.
Morgan and I need to get going.
We are late.
- Who is Morgan?
- Morgan!
Morgan?
Yes, why? Any problem?
No, not at all.
I like it.
Bye, Walter.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Have a good time.
- Thanks.
See you.
Why didn't you tell him
that we call you Morgan?
It doesn't matter.
Don't worry.
Morgan.
Morgan? That's how they
call him at school?
I can go and talk
to the principal.
He decided it.
It's what he likes
to be called these days.
He chose his nickname?
I don't understand.
In my time, other person
had to choose
a nickname for you. Why?
That's the name he uses
in the Internet. His nickname.
What's wrong with Walter?
Don't take it personally.
I'm asking because I think
Walter is a nice name.
It's about growing up.
He wants his own identity.
Do you think
he told Lucho about me?
About the blackout?
Lucho is his friend.
I don't think it's weird
if he talked to him
about how upset he was
because of your disappearance.
I made omelets.
Do you want some?
- I'm going out, but thanks,
though.
- Where are you going?
The phone is downstairs.
Can you get it, please?
Of course.
- Hello.
- Hi, can you talk?
What part of "no contact"
didn't you understand?
I know, but there's a problem.
We agreed...
Missus, I'm not interested
in that credit card.
No, no, no, we already
have one without problems.
Right, honey?
We don't need
another credit card.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm not interested.
No, no, no, thanks a lot.
Honey, Cielo.
Can you at least tell me
where are you going?
The cab is here.
You should get that.
I'll be back in a few hours.
What?
I know I shouldn't call,
but I'm in a situation over
here, and I need my money.
- I gave you money.
- Thanks for the charity, bro.
But now I'm in a situation
with my house.
- Did you smoke the money?
- What?
I didn't smoke anything!
Your problems are just that:
your problems.
And when I say "no contact"
I mean it.
Do not call here ever.
Bro, you're not listening!
You're not listening!
No, I don't want to listen!
Don't call again!
Teacher, they're kicking
me out of my house!
They're kicking
Teacher!
Bitch, you forgot
this light bulb!
Take it to your house!
- Who is it?
- Bro, it's me, Jose.
- Okay, come in.
- Thanks.
Darkness holds you
pretending beauty
but that's only
the trap of your head.
Darkness holds you
pretending beauty
but that's only
the trap of your head.
One second.
We should get the band
up and running again.
"Fucking putrefaction".
That was the best!
Marcelín, bro, thanks
for letting me stay here.
Two nights tops.
I made sure this
stock knock exterminator
put me on his speed dial.
Don't worry.
You can call me
every time you need me.
Are you still staying
at your grandmother's?
Yes, bro.
But I'm thinking of moving.
Really?
That will be a permanent party.
Rock and roll and chicks.
Benji, you have to eat
the carrots and the soup.
Okay, Benjamín?
If you eat all this,
you will have a dessert!
But you have to eat it.
- Honey, hello.
- Mom is home.
- Hi, honey.
- Hello, honey.
Do you remember Jose?
- Hi.
He's eating everything.
Jose asked me to stay here
for a few days,
and our guest room
is available,
so, yes.
Okay.
Could you help me
in the bedroom with these?
- Be right back.
- Okay.
- This is heavy.
- How are you?
Fine.
What's up, little bro?
I used to not like carrots, too.
Honey, Benjamín.
I think it's someone's
shower time.
Then you can eat.
Man, you're going to kill me.
I totally spaced
that the in-laws
are crashing this weekend.
I have totally forgotten.
I get it.
Jose, please...
I have a girl
who can do me the favor.
The in-laws are the in-laws
and you have to do it.
I'm sorry, Jose,
but you know that you can
call me when you need me.
And let's talk about the band.
Right, let's talk.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Sorry.
I'm asking to crash three,
maybe four nights.
No, I have already called Mono
and he can't either.
I called everyone.
I need a solid here, bro.
Yeah, whatever.
All right.
Bye.
No, no, no!
Where is my bike?
Bro, I went to take a leak
and, when I got back,
the bike wasn't here anymore.
What the fuck?
Shit! I can't believe it.
This is a national problem,
the lack of security, bro.
This is the mayor problem.
Bye.
Good morning, Walter.
- Good morning.
- Mom?
Out.
Where's breakfast?
Let's do something different.
What?
You'll see.
You won't regret it.
This is going to be really fun.
All right, ready?
Start it.
Good. Handbrake.
Let's put it in gear.
And I let the clutch go softly,
as you told me.
Exactly, go on.
Nice and smooth.
Let the clutch go. That's it.
Smooth, smooth, slow down,
slow down, slow down, that's it.
You'll do it much better
- next time.
- Sorry.
Relax, you are doing it right.
Lucho has been helping me.
- Really?
- Yes.
Don't forget the turn indicator.
Perfect. And let's make
that left-hand turn.
Slow down, slow down, slow down.
Slow down!
That's right. That's right.
Okay.
- Do you have your left foot
on the brake?
- Yes.
That's not the way.
You use the left foot
only for the clutch.
Why can't I brake
with the left foot?
You don't brake
with the left foot.
The left foot
is only for the clutch.
The right foot is for braking
and speeding up.
The left one is for the clutch.
Dad, this is way easier.
Come on, there's the easy way,
and then there's the right way.
We're doing things right.
So let's just try it again,
right foot only.
That's why we are here,
so you can practice.
Okay, let's do it again.
Go across there,
nice and smooth.
Take the wheel,
a little more, that's it.
The gas, the brake,
the gas, the brake.
And there you will brake
with the right foot.
Come on, the brake.
The brake.
No, dad.
My legs don't work that way.
Your legs are fine.
You just have to stick with it.
Don't set limits for yourself.
You're all right.
We'll get this.
Now let's just try again
with the right foot.
Here, straighten it.
Good, good, good.
You have the turn, the brake.
The brake, the brake.
Watch the cone here.
Come on, stop, stop.
Stop, stop, Junior!
Stop, stop!
- It's not stopping.
- That's the gas.
I told you.
Okay, Morgan.
- Hands up, ass hole!
- No, no, no, bro.
If you move, I shoot.
No, no, bro, it's me.
Jose, man.
It's me, bro, Jose.
This is my RV.
I'm a friend of your cousin,
remember?
Do you?
What the hell
are you doing here?
You smell like shit.
It's a long story.
If you want to, I can tell you.
No, I don't have the time.
So, I fixed up this shit.
I had to buy some spare parts.
I spent 2000 dollars.
- And the toilet also.
- Okay.
- Give me the money.
- No, no...
I'm going to pay you.
But I can't pay you today.
Look at me. I don't have it.
- You gave me your word.
- Yes, and I will pay you.
I can really pay you,
that's the truth.
Let's do something.
This will be my payment.
No, no, no, please, bro.
Let's do something else.
Did you say 2,000 dollars?
That's four million pesos.
I owe you
a little more than that.
You give me 2500 dollars
plus interest.
Okay, okay, bro.
Do me a favor.
Give me two days.
Give me two days
to get that money
and I will pay you.
Just don't take my cook stuff.
That's all I got left.
Come on, please.
Please, all right?
Come on, Germán, please.
I'm begging you.
The bus.
Don't be like that, bro.
Germán, please, bro.
Come on, please, Germán!
Bitch.
There's a bunch
of stuff in there.
It seems to be a lab, bro.
He has some big bottles
that read something like...
Methylamine, maybe?
Yes, methylamine.
Are you kidding me?
Is that the real value?
And do you know
somebody who can buy it?
So wait a minute...
Son of a bitch!
What is that?
What are you doing?
Stop, idiot!
Come here!
Stop him!
Avocado, pineapple, banana.
Get your papaya.
Avocado, avocado.
Avocado, pineapple, banana.
Cielo.
Junior went to school.
Can we talk?
I know you have
a lot of reasons to...
That you might feel...
Basically,
I wanted to apologize
for everything.
I want you to forgive me
My desire for permanent privacy.
My emotional unavailability.
The way I mistreated you.
I know I've been
an awful partner lately.
Having cancer doesn't excuse
all that. I'm really sorry.
Please, forgive me.
I love you.
And I love this family.
And I just want to make sure
that we don't lose contact.
Please.
- Thank you.
Is that all?
What else?
We can't keep like this.
- How?
- Like this!
Not talking to me.
Making gestures
I don't understand.
Going out all day and refusing
to tell me where.
You are obviously angry with me
about something,
so let's talk about it.
You think that I'm up
to something, right?
You think I'm having an affair,
right?
Is that it?
Is that why you asked me
about the some other phone?
- Because you think that I'm
being unfaithful?
- I don't know.
- So ask me.
- Would you even tell me?
Yes, of course!
I will tell you now:
No! I'm not having an affair!
I have nothing like that.
What do I do
to prove that to you?
Swear an oath?
My right hand to God.
I'm not having an affair.
Okay, I heard you.
You're not having an affair.
Congratulations.
No, you know what?
Congratulations to you.
Great job keeping us apart.
All right.
- Do you want to talk?
- Yes.
On one condition.
Tell me only one thing.
One damn thing
that isn't complete bullshit.
It's easy.
You have to tell me what's
really going on right now.
Tell me!
No more excuses.
No more apologies.
No more of these obvious,
desperate breakfasts.
You don't want to lose contact
with me? Then tell me.
Tell you what? What is it you
want me to tell you?
Cielo, I don't know.
I don't understand
what's going on.
Cielo, Cielo!
Cielo.
Cielo, don't leave.
Cielo! Open the window.
We have to talk.
Do you know
what I've done for this family?
Cielo!
Run!
I'm really sorry, okay?
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm sorry.
What's going through your mind?
My parents kicked me out.
I know this isn't
the best idea...
The best idea?
To park on my street?
- I know, I'm sorry...
- What are you thinking?
I told you I'm sorry.
What if my wife had seen you?
What was the plan then, genius?
- I don't know...
- Of course!
Because you have no brain!
Because you don't think!
I'm sorry, but I want
my half of the money
- and then I'll disappear.
- What money?
- What?
- You don't have any money.
- I have the money.
- No!
Why should I be penalized
because of your sloppiness?
Look, that is completely unfair.
We agreed fifty-fifty partners.
Partners in what?
I cook!
I'm the producer!
You are just a drug addict.
You are a pathetic junkie.
That is what you are.
A complete idiot!
Too stupid to understand
and follow simple instructions.
Can I use the bathroom?
Yes, right there.
Do you want some breakfast?
Yes.