Bro, this is less of the half
of what we need.
This is all the money
I have in the world.
At least I have something.
You are the drug dealer here.
I don't know,
try to negotiate.
Hey, wait.
Why are you doing this?
And tell me the truth.
Because of the money, brother.
Exactly!
Don't give me that, man.
A man like you,
looking like a seminarian
and who is 60.
Wakes up one day
and decides to change his path?
50.
I'm 50.
50, 60, same shit.
Look, bro...
If you lost it...
if you are depressed...
you have to tell me
because that will concern me.
Look, I know exactly
what we are doing.
So, if you know
what you are doing,
why are you doing it?
Because I finally
opened my eyes.
This shit, bro!
Very good, man!
Do it!
Those beauties are yours!
Ha, ha, ha!
Hey, hey, hey!
I have these two fine ladies
and they want to participate.
Two ladies, Gordo?
I only see one!
Are we going to please them
or what?
We have the funds, right?
You do what you want
because we have the funds, bro.
Bring me two bottles
of champagne,
we have the money for that.
And I don't want
that dispensable shit.
I want the tall, skinny glasses.
That's what James Bond drinks.
Have you seen
James Bond's movies?
This is the life we deserve.
I have a question.
Where did he get
all this money?
Yes, man.
Where did you get the money?
What if I tell you
that some ex teacher of mine
gave it to me?
Just like that?
Are you a gay hooker or what?
It's a long story to tell,
but I will tell it to you later
because now I'm busy
being heterosexual.
Me too!
I'm flying, man!
- Cheers! Cheers!
- Is this a toast?
Yes, because we
are going to live forever!
Yes!
Photo, bro!
Bros!
Man, this was...
This was amazing.
Good morning.
No, bro.
Gordo, I'm fucked up!
I only have 1100 dollars.
Jose, what do you mean?
What are you talking about?
That's good money!
You are paranoid.
- Let's go have breakfast.
- I'm not paranoid, man!
I was supposed to buy
an RV for today with that money!
- An RV?
- No!
I have to leave town
or change my identity.
He's blackmailing me.
The guy is crazy,
I tell you that.
Jose...
Do you need an RV?
I have one for you!
For 1100 dollars, Gordo?
Right on.
- Really, Gordo?
- For real.
Can you get an RV
for 1100 dollars now?
Give me the money,
I'll be right back.
Don't leave me
without breakfast.
Gordo, we'll see.
Juan Carlos, is that you?
What's up, Gordo?
Where were you?
And why don't you
answer your cell phone?
I was driving your RV.
Here you have it.
What RV are you talking about?
This is a bus, Gordo.
Not an RV, bro.
Jose, they are the same shit.
And you got it
for 1100 dollars?
My cousin owns it.
This is a family issue.
Okay, Gordo.
Don't be so pleased, bro.
I have just saved your life
and you don't even notice.
No, bro, the thing is
that I have another problem.
I was supposed to buy the RV
or the bus,
I don't know what that is,
and also fix it.
But I don't have
any money left.
Relax, brother,
because here is your friend,
Gordo.
Maybe I can lend you
some money.
Really, Gordo?
How much money?
1100 dollars?
1100 dollars.
Do you think
that will be enough, bro?
I have another cousin
who can do a cheap work on it.
So, do you understand
what I need?
Of course I do,
that's why my cousin
brought you here.
I need it to be
a good work, man.
Well, this is the plan.
Here, below the sink,
you will have a tap.
And here, next to the driver,
you will have the outlets.
You will have to tell me
how many of them you need.
In the center, up here,
we will make a hole,
a skylight for air circulation.
Right.
And you have to take
all those seats out
so we have more space.
It is very important
that this is finished today.
- Okay?
- You will have it done today.
And I will also put
a little table
so you have more room inside.
Can you add another table
in there?
Of course!
If you have the money for it,
I can make an helicopter
from a stove.
Right, cousin?
And here you have
all used spare parts, right?
What are you talking about?
All of our spare parts
are new, original
and factory made.
Yeah, right. It shows.
Wow!
I love this floor.
Can you control the temperature?
Yes, there should be a switch
right next to the mirror.
Wow!
This is the most amazing
invention ever.
I didn't know it.
It's not very common.
I had it in Germany.
My contractor talked me into it.
- And here it is.
- Yes.
It seemed to be too much,
but I tried it,
I liked it
and I had to have it.
I can never find anything
in this case.
You could leave
a few things here.
Tell your father
to come downstairs.
Yes, mom.
Dad?
Dad.
Yes, tell me.
Come to have lunch,
mom's asking.
Yes, I'll be right there.
I'm telling you.
I don't know.
Yeah, right, you don't know.
Don't you listen to me?
Give me the phone.
Like you didn't make
some deal behind my back
Correct. I did not.
I was in my house,
I went to the street,
minding my own business,
when suddenly the man
threw a bag of money on me.
Whatever, man.
You owe me that money.
Let me talk to him.
I owe you?
I owe you nothing!
And I will get
to the bottom of this, trust me.
Trust you?
No, thanks, teacher.
Why didn't you tell me that
from the beginning?
I should have known.
Do you want to talk
about trust, José?
Talk, bro.
Let's talk about trust.
I told you
not to cook my formula,
and what did you do?
I never said I wouldn't cook it
because it isn't yours.
It's ours.
Plural, bitch.
You did not have my permission.
All I know
is that I have half of the money
and you have the rest, bitch.
Escalating.
You're escalating.
My meth, my money.
And listen me carefully.
I will be a one-man
glass factory.
I will be the boss
and I will rock that RV
24 hours a day.
What?
It's closed, bro.
I can't see a damn thing.
There is no one in that RV.
Nothing.
There's no cook.
- Nothing.
- There is someone inside.
Gómez, believe me,
there is somebody inside.
Let's do something.
We come back later,
with a warrant.
- To do things right.
- We have no time, bro.
I'm not letting this sucker
out of my sight.
I have to find a way.
Find a way.
Hey, Henry, come here!
Shit!
There is somebody up there!
You bastard!
Pervert!
No, no, no.
What are you doing there?
- No, no, no!
- Come down, pig!
Listen, brother.
This is not what you think.
What are you doing?
Come down, if you dare.
What do you want?
I mean it.
Here I have something for you.
I'm really sorry.
I hope you understand.
- Sorry, agent.
- This is my job.
- Right.
- Excuse me.
Did he have something for you?
Nice.
What did you find out?
He's a good guy, man.
The worst thing he has done
was cheating on his wife.
Three RV's, one van,
everything's right.
He's a good catch.
Don't let him go.
There is another RV
I want to check out.
- Let's go.
- No.
- I have to go home.
- Why? Will your wife beat you?
- I have to pack.
- What?
- Where are you going?
That's it, bro.
I'll go to Mexico
for some training.
Nice.
Honey, are you home?
Henry?
Honey?
Can I come in?
Hi, babe.
How did it go last night?
Did you catch the RV guy?
No.
Do you want some breakfast?
I can cook you some eggs.
No, I'm heading back
to the office after the shower.
But you worked all night.
Get some sleep.
Those RV's
aren't going anywhere.
They're vehicles, María.
They transport people,
that's what they do.
You know what I mean.
I spoke to Blanca.
She told me about Gómez.
So?
- What do you think about that?
- Nothing.
I turned it down, right?
End of story.
Good, I'm relieved.
María, I can't leave right now.
I'm deep into this investigation
and I need more time.
I had to choose
between Mexico and Colombia.
I chose Colombia.
- Done?
- Of course.
You know that you can talk to me
about things, right?
You don't have to go
through this alone.
María, I made a decision.
I'm fine,
I'm not going through anything.
I'm just doing my job.
- But I would like--
- What would you like, María?
A five stars hotel in Acapulco?
Is that what you deserve, María?
You didn't let me finish.
I was going to say
that I would like to have
a better communication with you.
I'm worried about you,
I'm worried about you career--
Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
All right.
I only want to know
if you are happy
with your decision.
I want to know
if you don't want
to go back there.
I'm not blaming you, but--
María, María.
Aren't you late for work?
I just wanted to know that.
After what happened,
it would make sense
that you don't want to go back.
Mexico doesn't have
a damn thing to do with it,
María.
I'm into some important stuff
right here, in Bogotá!
And that's the most important
thing to me, understood?
And I would really appreciate it
if you stop judging me.
Because all I get from you,
María, are these
bullshit accusations!
And if everyone thinks
I'm jerking off
on this thing in Bogotá,
I don't care, María.
You know why?
Because I know
I am into something!
Understood?
María?
What exactly is this?
I'll tell you
what I think it is.
A ploy to get me cooking again.
And an obvious one at that.
How do you mean?
As if I would seriously believe
you would hire an addict.
José Miguel Rosas, please!
You vouched for him previously.
I took you at your word.
- I did that.
- No!
José Miguel was capable
of working under my supervision.
Trusting him
with a solo venture,
that's quite another matter.
How he could possibly produce
anything other
than a mediocre product at best.
I am told his product
was more or less consistent
with the quality
I had come to expect.
More or less?
More or less, Gustavo?
Really?
Boy, don't you think
that is setting the bar low?
Except you don't set
the bar low.
You don't accept a low level.
Do you?
Therefore, what conclusion
am I left to draw?
That you believe
I'm being selfish.
I'm being selfish
about my own formula.
Some sort of overweening pride.
You think it overwhelms
my judgement.
- And it doesn't?
- Absolutely not.
I simply respect the chemistry.
The chemistry must be respected.
I apologize
for being so transparent.
Walter.
Would you take a drive with me?
I'd like to show you something.
Hi, is everything okay?
She's already finished
an entire bottle
and fell asleep.
But I was thinking I'd give her
another when she wakes up.
Yeah, absolutely.
Fatten that baby up.
Will do.
Was that it?
So where are you?
Are you at work?
Yeah, I'm at work.
I shouldn't be much longer.
Is that okay?
You know I love
my little princess.
You can leave her with me
for the next 18 years,
as far as I'm concerned.
Great, thanks.
Are you sure you're okay?
What is it?
It's Henry.
Henry?
- What about him?
- I don't know.
I don't know
what's wrong with him.
He doesn't talk to me
since he came from Mexico.
God knows he went
through a lot down there.
Blood everywhere.
I don't want
to think about it.
Last week, Mexico
said they want him back.
So?
He's not going. Gomez will go.
I don't know.
Well, he's certainly
a lot safer here, isn't he?
Of course, and I want him safe.
I want him calm.
But I can't tell what he wants.
I don't know what is happening
with him.
He hardly even comes home.
He leaves really early
and comes late.
He's not the same, Cielo.
It's like something's
eating him away from inside.
Facing death,
it changes a person.
But...
You must know it.
I guess you've noticed
a change in Walt.
This way. Come with me.
What is this?
Your new lab.
If you want it.
This is truly amazing.
This reaction vessel
has to be 1200 liters!
Unbelievable.
Thorium oxide as catalyst basis.
Interesting.
This is a perfect design.
How did you know
how to put this all together?
I had excellent help.
As will you.
Quite a lot of planning
went into this.
I would say so.
The laundry upstairs,
I've owned it for years.
It receives large chemical
deliveries on a weekly basis,
detergents and such.
There is nothing
suspicious about it
and my employees,
to be sure, are well-trained,
trustworthy.
The filtration system
is state of the art.
It will vent nothing but clean,
odorless steam
just as the laundry does
and through the same stacks.
I need 200 pounds per week
to make this
economically viable.
You would choose your own hours,
of course come and go
as you please
so long as the quota is met.
Sorry.
The answer is still no.
Look...
I have made a series
of very bad decisions
and I can't make another one.
Why did you make
those decisions?
For the good of my family.
Then they weren't bad decisions.
What does a man have to do,
Walter?
A man provides for his family.
This cost me my family.
When you have children,
you always have family, Walter.
They will always be your
priority, your responsibility.
That's why a man...
a real man...
provides for his family.
And he does it even when he's
not appreciated, respected
or even loved.
He simply bears up
and does it. Period.
Any chance we could grab
a quick bite?
Pizza place around the corner's
pretty good.
I really have to head home.
All right.
Next time, then.
We were together
and she told me she liked sushi.
And I said it was okay with me
because she was really pretty.
I couldn't think
of anything else!
I'm a stupid.
Can I be excused?
To do homework
or to play video games?
Both things.
Okay.
Go.
You want to take her?
Yes.
Thanks. Come here.
Hi!
Half of an RV
in the backyard of a house?
No, that's useless, bro.
All right.
Vicky!
Come here, help me, please.
Because I couldn't find
anything.
But the people in the Transit
Office have already sent
the information on all the buses
they have before 1990.
Could you check it again?
Maybe you missed something.
- Help me, please.
- Does it have to be now?
Please.
Can I do it after the party?
I'm dead in the water here.
Okay, I'll check.
- Thank you very much.
- Okay.
I'm going to miss you all.
Thank you, thank you very much.
Thanks to all of you.
Who made this cake?
Who?
Who's going to cut it?
Who's going to put his finger?
So, Gómez?
Time for the little bird
to fly the nest.
The right guy for the job.
I only want to tell
you one thing.
Be careful
with the chili peppers.
Bro, I know you well
and I know you are weak
down there,
so if you eat one of those,
you will start...
Come here.
Come here, brother.
Here.
- What is this?
- Jesús Malverde.
He's the boss of all the drug
dealers there in Mexico.
Know your enemy and all.
He has many things there.
You will know.
Thanks.
The situation there is tough.
But don't forget it.
You are tougher, bro.
So...
Fight the good fight, brother.
Thanks, bro.
Henry, you know...
You know what you mean to me.
- My brother.
- Sure.
So, what are you drinking?
Just some soda?
I can't believe it.
I will fix this.
Dear!
Boss, don't leave.
Your hunch was right.
One more RV.
Transit said the registration
wasn't renewed,
but then they realized
it was never filed
as non-operational or destroyed.
And it was also used
for transporting students.
Lieutenant Rada!
- Thanks a lot.
- You're welcome.
I just don't know what the hell
I'm doing anymore, you know?
Damn it!
It's like I'm paralyzed.
Like if I take a step
in any direction
I'm going to make
a spectacular mistake.
God.
Anyway, breaking news...
I am sleeping with my boss
and I don't know why.
That's a lie.
I do know why.
I mean, he's a lovely guy.
He's a really good person,
but it's not like we're ever
going to have something serious.
And I didn't tell it
to anybody.
Unbelievable!
And everyone seems to think
that I am...
My sister.
My own sister.
My brother-in-law.
My teenage son.
All of them think
that I'm an evil bitch
that makes Walter suffer.
That I batter him
without any reason.
And I know that you told me
to tell them the truth,
everything about Walter,
but I can't.
I can't!
How could I?
And you know what?
This man that I'm seeing,
I'm doing it
to make Walter leave me.
I just want
that Walter leaves me.
But I have to admit
that I...
when I'm with him,
with the other man,
I feel so...
I don't know.
It is the only thing in my
day where I don't feel like
I'm drowning.
I feel free with him.
So he knows
about this other man?
- Yes.
- So then he'll sign?
Walter says
he's not going anywhere.
Walter is staying.
Because he's a genius.
He's a fucking genius!
He keeps money in the house.
How much money?
I don't know.
I didn't count it.
But it's a heavy bag.
It would make you think again.
Cielo...
Are you asking my permission
to spend this money?
No, no, God.
No.
I just...
I'm just trying
to talk it through.
Let me just say
that I'm half as qualified
and twice the price
of a therapist.
And this situation is so clear
that we don't have anything
to discuss.
I'm just saying, you know?
We have a history.
He's the father of my children.
And what he did,
he did it for the family.
I'm sorry,
but he's manipulating you.
He gave you an huge load
that you don't deserve.
Maybe.
I want to tell you something,
but I apologize beforehand.
You are a fool to stay
in that house one minute longer.
If your husband won't leave,
then you go.
If you stay there, you are
an accessory after the fact.
And that will make you guilty.
You and your children
could lose everything you own.
And why?
All courtesy of this criminal
you refuse to divorce.
I didn't marry a criminal.
Well, you're married to one now.
For our next meeting,
I'll have all the documents
for you to have
a good pension,
although they seize
that money from him.
I think we won't meet again.
Cielo, don't you want
to do this?
I think...
that I'm good
only with the divorce papers.
I really appreciate it.
Thanks.
Send him in, Panchita.
Good to see you.
Please, have a seat here.
Mr. Rosas...
You're late.
Good.
Gentlemen, if we could
come to some accommodation
here now.
There's always a way
to oil everyone's lock.
This young man is prepared
to offer you
a sweetheart of a deal
for doing precisely nothing.
- Really?
- Really.
Ten percent
of all future profits
from his solo venture.
That's money you get paid
for walking down to the mailbox.
Consider it a gesture of respect
for your valuable contribution
to the business this far.
I'm sure you'll agree
that's fair.
That's charity,
is what that is.
I do all the work.
You sit around on your fat ass
judging people.
You son of a bitch.
Listen, listen, please,
what did we say about your tone?
Quiet, quiet.
I continue.
So there's that, but then
there's one small detail.
Clearly a mistake was made on
the part of our mutual associate
when he paid you
half of José Miguel earnings.
He must not have realized
that you two had come
to a parting of the ways.
It belongs to you.
You're damn right
it belongs to me.
Ha! Great!
I knew I could trust you.
I knew I could count on you boys
to play nice.
Beautiful.
I'm almost crying.
Enjoy it.
Spend it in good health.
That is the last money
you'll ever earn
in this business.
What the hell
is that supposed to mean?
Well, I hate to break it to you,
José Miguel,
but our mutual associate
was only using you to get to me.
What are you talking about?
See, he needs someone
with expertise.
Someone who knows
what he's doing.
In other words, he needs me.
You're telling me
you're cooking again?
Let's see,
how should I put this?
Because I need you
to understand it.
I'm in.
You're out.
Hey, Walter!
Hold on there.
What was the offer, exactly?
If I may ask, of course.
It's three million
for three months of my time.
You're going to need
that money laundered.
What was our deal before?
Seventeen percent.
That's a shade high.
Let's settle on an even 15.
That's a nice round number.
Five percent.
Hey, hey, hey!
Fourteen's fair.
Five.
Thirteen is good enough.
Five per cent.
Twelve, for old times' sake.
- Five per cent.
- No, no, hold on.
I'm a reasonable guy.
It's a short-term deal.
Ten per cent?
Ten per cent.
But I can't go any lower.
Five!
What in the hell just happened?
You're my lawyer, not his.
Kid, you have
an important lesson to learn.
That's the way of the world.
Go with the winner.
You think this
will stop me from cooking?
- Yes?
- No, you can cook
whatever you like.
As long as it's
that ridiculous meth
or you make up something else.
But don't even think
about using my formula.
Just try and stop me.
Bitch!
Yes, tell me.
Mrs. Olga?
It's me.
Mrs. Olga, I'm Henry Navarro,
anti-narcotics agent.
We're interested in an RV
that's registered
to your name and address.
It was stolen months ago.
- Stolen?
- Yes.
Then I'm curious because the
theft was never reported.
I'm not seeing any records of it
with the police.
I'm really busy in the house.
I didn't have the time to do it.
You didn't have the time
to report the theft
of a bus of yours?
And I've been ill.
I understand.
So...
And don't you care
about that bus?
Don't you need the money?
Well...
Yes, I do.
Do you know
what is the problem here?
If the people that stole the bus
use it for something unlawful,
you will have the problem
because the bus is yours.
Do you get it?
The bus is registered
with your name.
Do you have any ideas at all
who might've taken it?
I didn't want him arrested.
He ran with a bad crowd,
but he was never a bad person.
I thought he could turn
his life around.
In every house
there is someone
who needs help.
Who are we talking about?
My son.
I'd really like
to speak with him.
He's passed away.
He was shot two months ago.
I'm really sorry.
What was your son's name?
Juan Carlos Ortega.
We called him Gordo.
Could you give me
more information
about Juan Carlos?
Come on in.
Except from the lamp
and the flowers,
everything is like he left it.
Thank you for your cooperation.
No problem.
I only hope our Lord
takes him out of the purgatory
and brings him to Heaven.