The sweet sounds
of dawn in the country.
The eternal freshness
of wrought land.
The colors and textures
of the best ingredients.
Grandma's unmistakable flavoring
mixed with the sweet heat
of fire.
The old ways are still best
at Los Pollos Hermanos.
An unmistakable flavor
that's part
of our best memories.
At Los Pollos Hermanos
we know words
are not enough to describe
the real sensations
that built memories.
We want to share with you
that unique satisfaction
that has been with us
since childhood.
The taste of being home.
Los Pollos Hermanos,
flavor with passion.
How much?
56.76 pounds.
Perfect.
We reached the schedule
and we have
an extra pound and a half.
Better over than under.
I thought you were all precise.
Let's save that pound and a half
for next week.
No, we'll ship it as
is.
Ship it as it?
How come?
Are we giving our
product away?
No, we're not running a
charity.
José, don't mess things up.
One batch, one ship.
It's simple.
Why are you purposely
giving him free meth?
He's bleeding us enough
already.
I can't believe it.
Are you listening to yourself?
You're paid extraordinary well
with this business.
And you even complain?
Don't pretend you're exploited.
Let's
see...
Speaking of that...
Look,
I been crunching numbers.
Have you?
So now you're a mathematician?
That's for spending
so much time with you.
I've been
crunching
numbers.
I don't have to
be
a mathematician
to figure out this deal you made
is bullshit.
- It's incredible.
- What?
You're so shameless.
How much do we take?
A million and a half
dollars each.
Why are you talking
in dollars?
Because in pesos
there're so many zeros
that I mess up.
Are you listening
what you're saying?
You earn an amount
that you can't even handle
in your head.
- And you even complain!
- Yes, I do. Yes.
But if we earn that,
then how much is taking
the owner of this shit?
Just think
about it.
He's got enough
meth
for the entire Colombia
and he's got some left.
So he's clearly exporting
it.
- So what?
- What do you mean "So what"?
You know what happens
when you export.
The price multiplies.
I don't know how many
times.
Five, six times?
- Ten, twenty. I don't know.
- Precisely! That's it..
He earns lots of money.
You are now a millionaire
and you're complaining?
José, don't be greedy.
No, bitch.
What's fair is fair.
Don't
you
think?
We should be earning
much more money.
Bye!
Can you listen to me
at least once?
Walter!
No, these ones are the same.
Put them there.
These pillows seem bricks.
They should use them
to make houses for the poor.
Do you want me
to ask for another?
No, but you know what?
Remind me to bring a better one
from home.
Excuse me.
Hello.
May I?
Yes, Gómez, come in.
Well, at least...
his color looks good.
And he talks.
Only when he wants to.
What's up Gómez?
What's up, buddy?
Come, buddy,
I need to tell you something.
- Tell me.
- Come here.
- What happened?
- Closer.
What is
it?
Scratch my balls,
they itch.
Henry.
At least you haven't
forgotten those bad jokes.
You know who can
scratch it?
The boss.
He even asks me.
Look at this.
I'll show you something that
will call your attention.
It'll make you feel better.
I've been keeping an eye on
that blue meth of yours.
Guess what?
Look at
Colombia.
There's nothing.
It disappeared.
Look where it appeared:
Venezuela, Brazil,
Peru, Ecuador, Panama.
What's more,
we're getting a report
from Chile.
It's the same that
happened in the US.
Why would that
make me feel better?
You're a genius.
You're the only one
who saw this coming.
Well, then,
put on your cheer leader
uniform and...
Three cheers for em.
It hurts me. It...
Call the nurse.
I want morphine right now.
- Really?
- Hurry up.
Okay, fine.
- Gómez.
- María!
Stop talking about
work.
I'm
going!
Buddy,
I have to confess something.
What is it?
I don't know what happened to me
with this case.
They caught me unguarded.
No.
No one would have reacted
like you did.
The only reason
I'm telling you this
is because I got
a warning call.
How come?
Who called you?
I don't know.
A voice scrambler.
I got a call and they told me
that someone
would kill me in a minute.
María's got my phone.
Run the incoming call
if you want,
but I'm sure that phone number
no longer exists.
Besides, that call
makes no sense.
I mean, why?
I don't know
but there's some big shit
behind all this.
About what Gómez said...
No.
I had nothing to do with
that.
Are we safe?
Yes.
Absolutely.
- And you?
- I'm absolutely protected.
I've been quitting it
little by little.
I've been clean
for three months.
It's been really hard
but I'm doing fine
and thanks to your help
I've quitted it.
Good, very good.
Thanks for sharing,
Rodolfo.
Who else wants to
share something?
talk to us?
Um?
No one?
What about you,
José?
What?
Don't you want
to tell us anything?
Talk?
About what?
I don't know.
Anything you want.
Your life. Whatever.
About my exciting life?
One day pretty much bleeds
into the next.
I've been working a lot.
That's fine, isn't it?
That's good.
Working is a stimulus.
Where are you working at?
In a corporate Laundromat.
But my job is...
I work in an office.
I hate my boss.
Pretty much.
I hate the owner as well
though I don't know him,
they don't even let me
see his face.
Okay.
And...
And what about your
colleagues?
Does anyone seem
interesting?
Are you friends
with anyone?
- No, no way.
- Nothing?
No, the people over there
are like zombies.
The place is full of dead-eyed
douche bags
and nobody knows
what's going on.
It's all pretty ridiculous.
I get you, I do.
It sounds
like...
Kind of Kafkaesque.
- What?
- Kafka, the writer.
He wrote "The Metamorphosis",
"The trial".
The environments were
oppressive, surreal...
Totally Kafkaesque, yes.
- Kafkaesque.
- That's it.
Absolutely.
Look at all these flowers
Henry got.
Do you like them, babe?
- Lovely.
Who sent them?
The Attorney General.
"To Henry Navarro".
- Very nice.
- So elegant!
And look at this basket
full of goodies.
This one as sent
By "Soluciones Silva".
Hey, your boss is wonderful.
Not only does he let you
be with us,
he also sends you
these delicious chocolate.
It's even imported.
You want some?
Hey, what a nice job you have.
I want one.
What should I do?
Hello.
- Doctor, how are you?
- Excuse me.
- How are you doing today?
- Fine.
Just going to do
a quick peripheral response.
See where we're at.
Okay?
- Let's see. Thanks.
- Let me help you.
It's time to know the truth.
No, let's not
exaggerate.
It's just a sensitive
reaction test.
I want you to
think carefully
what you'll answer.
All right?
Can you feel this?
- No.
- No?
The other
foot?
- No.
- Neither.
Let's
see...
- I feel that.
- Yes.
- Perfect.
On a scale form
one to ten,
how much did you feel?
- Four.
Four? And here?
Six.
Fine.
Henry, thanks so much!
So this is good news?
It looks like some of
the nervous functions
are returning.
That's good, isn't it?
So when do we get him
walking again?
Hey!
- There he is! Finally!
- What's up?
Now that you're important
we must wait for you, don't we?
What do you want?
Manicure? Pedicure?
- Exfoliate!
- No, no. Maybe later.
What about our chemist?
Isn't it enough just with
me?
Just tell me what
the hell I'm doing here.
Well, then since
you came alone,
today is your lucky day.
What a lovely business,
isn't it?
It should be yours.
- This?
- This!
This is a discrete and
profitable business.
What's most important, legal!
You went nuts,
Saúl?
Just went nuts.
And you must be blind
because you don't see
what's going on here.
On the outside,
it's a nail salon.
On the inside,
it's the best money laundry
a growing boy could ask for.
Wait, wait, wait!
Let's not talk
about that here.
Because of them?
Don't worry.
This business
used to belong
to an emerald seller
and then to a smuggler.
And they don't know anything,
do they?
You know anything?
You' You?
Nothing!
Fine, but no.
- No, thanks. See you.
- Hey, wait!
Excuse me, girls.
I'll be right back.
Hey, don't go!
- What?
- No, come. Calm down.
- Wait, wait.
You know you need to launder
your money, right?
I know I have to launder
my money
but I don't want
a fucking nail salon.
No, you want to stay
out of prison, right?
You want money and freedom,
don't you?
Wait. I'll get some
didactic material
and explain it all to you.
Don't go.
Mrs. Navarro,
the important thing
is to lower your expectations.
Henry has months
of hard work ahead.
And even then,
the odds are not good.
But you can't know
for sure?
No.
When does he start
physical therapy.
We've sent the paperwork
to your insurance.
We should have a response
in five days.
No, that can't
be possible.
The sooner
physical therapy begins,
the better his chances
are.
- Yes.
- He needs daily sessions.
Actually your plan's treatment
program
covers four sessions a week.
Actually,
she asked the doctor.
Four sessions is not bad.
If Henry had more
physical therapy
with better therapists,
wouldn't it be more
likely he would walk?
It's very hard to say.
Generally,
what the insurances give
is acceptable
from the medical point of view.
But each case is different.
Then screw the insurance.
I want the best for Henry.
Look, madam,
I get your frustration,
but my best advice
is stay in the network.
Later on they might apply
any of their clauses
and not make any
reimbursements.
Physical therapy
is just the beginning.
We're talking nursing care,
modifications to your home,
occupational therapy,
medical equipment.
That could cost millions.
So then?
What do we do?
Do we sacrifice Henry's health?
Getting what the insurance
gives you
doesn't mean you don't worry.
Doctor, who's the best
physical therapist you know?
I can give you some names
but they're not likely
to be on the plan.
Okay.
Then to hell
with the plan.
Excuse me.
Let's see...
This is you...
surrounded by girls...
and partying hearty, okay?
These two
are from the IRS.
They come, look at you
"This young man
has no inheritance,
no career, is sort of dumb...".
I'm sorry.
- It's just an example.
- Come on.
"Besides, he's got
lots of money".
"Is he a business genius?".
"That's all I can think of",
says the other,
"If not, what could he be?".
A drug dealer!
Exactly!
And a tax cheat.
You see?
It's all bad on you.
And what was Josecito's mistake?
Not laundering the money.
Since I'm giving you
some examples,
let me explain to you
how this works.
First, you give me your money.
This is your dirty money.
I get it and put it
in this nail salon.
That's called layering.
I make it work
in the nail salon.
It'll work and it'll start
making lots of money
because it's
a successful business.
That's called stratification.
After a while,
I give you your clean money.
It's all yours and there're
no suspicions.
You get me?
That's called integration.
This process is what makes
the difference
between a criminal
and a good citizen
who pays taxes.
Who pays taxes?
That's the point, bitch,
I don't pay taxes.
By the way,
you get your 5%.
- Sure.
- No.
- My share is 17%
- No, no, no.
I heard you say 5%.
It's privileges of seniority
and all.
That 17% could be arranged.
No!
Fuck off.
We can arrange 15%.
Hey, don't you know
how to do business?
Twelve percent!
How is your
brother-in-law?
Fine. He'll live.
I'm glad.
Walter, you seen troubled.
What is it?
I asked to see you
in order to clear the air.
There are some issues
that could cause a
misunderstanding between us
and I think it's
in our best interests
to just lay the cards
on the table.
Sounds good.
That's the best way
to do business.
Moments before he was attacked,
my brother-in-law
got a warning call.
I believe that same person
was protecting me.
I suspect...
the assassins,
those two men,
were after me.
They were steered away from me
to my brother-in-law.
And that's to that intervention
I'm alive.
And yet I think
that this person
was playing a much deeper game.
He did this because it
was convenient to him.
Excuse me if I give you
too many details,
but I want to be
as clear as possible.
Go on, continue.
Thanks to my brother-in-law's
colleagues,
I found out these twins
belong to the Tapatío cartel,
which, in Mexico,
is in charge of doing business
with Colombia.
By chance...
I happened to read some news
on the paper
that said that
practically at the same time
that the twin
that was left alive
was dying here in the clinic,
the Federals in Mexico
were killing some Juan Bolsa,
the head of that cartel.
The point is, Gustavo,
I don't think
these are isolated facts.
they're just because.
I think that behind all this
there's just one person.
There's someone who's capable
of producing the best meth
in bulk
in Colombia.
Someone who's also interested
of getting rid
of the Mexican cartel.
Gustavo, you and I know
who that person is.
What's your point,
Walter?
I know I owe you my life.
And more than that
I respect the strategy.
I would have done the same.
But yes, there's something
that troubles me.
Tell me.
I don't know what happens
when our three-month contract
ends.
What would you like to
happen?
I want security for my family.
Then you have it.
Speaking of business,
the offer remains
Three millions for
three months of work.
We could extend that
to one year.
With a 15% raise
if that's good for you.
This is a really nice car.
Thanks.
This is the latest
we have for this job.
It's powerful, fast.
Just what we need, right?
I want to make you a proposal.
Tell me.
Here I have
6 million pesos cash.
More than what you earn
in a month, right?
- Sure, yes.
- You want to earn this?
Sure, as long as
it's not illegal.
Not at all.
What do I have to do then?
- Park and I'll tell you.
- Fine..
So what you want
is just to race
to the end of the road.
Yes, sir.
All right, then...
Let's do it.
Ready.
Watch out!
Open your eyes, please!
Guide me.
There's a truck coming, please!
Son of a bitch!
Stop!
What's wrong with you?
I told you to stop!
Asshole!
Crazy son of a bitch!
Get off my car now!
Get off!
Don't you think
I'll give you your money back!
Son of a bitch!
For those who were
in the last meeting,
and for those coming
for the first time.
I'd like us to talk
about those daily things
that bother us.
those things
that drive us crazy.
I think it's important
to learn to identify
those situations
that makes us nervous,
that make us nuts.
I think that could
help us get ready
so that when we see
a moment like that coming,
we can do something
and avoid it.
That way, we'll also avoid
the chance of a relapse.
That's what identifying
those situation is for,
that's what it'd be good for.
So, let's see,
who want to start?
Who wants to say something?
I have to go to the toilet.
Fine.
Who? Who dares?
What about you?
It's ridiculous.
Henry is a hero.
He's a hero just like...
every cop
and soldier
that risk themselves
to protect us.
You don't deny coverage
to a hero.
Can't be.
They'll say
they're not denying it.
They won't accept it.
I've been through that
with Walter.
If you do it on your
own, María,
you'll burn through
your savings
and you'll end up
full of debts.
But you can do this.
You told me
that the money
that Walter's partners gave you
was not enough.
But you could do it anyway.
- I'm going to get some wine.
- No, take this.
- I'm going to the clinic.
- No, María!
You have to rest.
Go home
or stay here.
Why don't you go in
and take a long bath?
I want to be there
in case he wakes up.
Did you see
all the meds
they gave him?
He'll sleep until
tomorrow.
Hello.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I was worried about you
and I came to see how
you're holding up.
- Hi.
- Hello.
This id my boss, Ernesto Silva.
María, my sister.
- María, pleased to meet you.
- You too.
Thanks for the basket
you sent Henry.
We care about Cielo
so much
that naturally extends
to the whole family.
Come in, won't you?
it's very cold outside.
- Thanks.
- Yes, sure. Come in.
Thanks for sharing,
Carolina.
José,
now that you're back,
last time we saw you,
you were kind of
upset about your job.
Yes.
If you could do
whatever you wanted most
in your life,
what you desire the most,
what would that be?
What would you do?
Make more money.
I'm not talking about
that.
I'm not talking
about the money.
I'm talking about doing
something with you,
something sincere.
Well, it's not that...
It's not that I'm doing it.
I'm not doing it now but...
I think I'd like to do
something with my hands,
like handcraft.
Such as building things?
Especially carpentry.
- Fine.
- Carpentry.
It's just that...
When I was at school,
I just attended
the technical lessons
because those were
the easiest ones.
In fact, I never liked
any subject.
But I remember there was a class
that had a really good teacher.
He was called Hernando.
He was some kind of soldier.
He was hard of hearing.
You had to speak loud.
Whatever...
He once gave us a project.
We had to build a box
or something like that.
We had to build it
and give it to him.
I was really bad at school.
I just did the box
because I had to.
When...
When I gave him the box
for him to give me a mark,
he looked at the box
and asked me...
He asked me whether
that was the best I could do.
My immediate reaction
"Bitch, just give me a
mark.
I have to go meet my
friends.
They'll smoke it
all up
and I want to go
partying".
But there was something he said
that had an impact in me.
I don't know
whether it was his tone.
But what he said
was not wrong.
In fact,
he was right.
For some reason I thought:
"Yes, I can do better".
So then,
I just started practicing,
practicing, practicing.
I made one box after the other
until I finally made...
I made the nicest box
on earth.
It was lovely.
I made it with guaiacum,
some cedar.
It had some drawings
on the sides.
And a padlock.
A little padlock.
It was...
It was a beautiful box.
That's a nice story, isn't it?
Don't you think so?
It's nice.
And what did you do
with the box?
I gave it to my mom.
Well, that's even better.
Look, if you really
like carpentry,
that's great.
You could teach all of us.
- I think there are--
- I'm lying.
Actually not.
I didn't give it
to my mom.
I ended up changing the box...
for marijuana.
I have to get back.
I'll try to see Henry
at the clinic.
- Bye.
- It's been a pleasure.
- The pleasure was mine.
- Take it easy.
- Yes.
Ernesto, I'm really thankful.
Thanks for worrying,
but you know what?
- This is not a good time.
- No, no.
Let's talk for a minute.
Just one minute
Okay, tell me.
I know you need to be
with your
family.
But you just disappeared.
You don't answer my calls
or my messages.
I was worried about you.
You're right, I'm sorry.
You gave me all that time off
and I really should've--
No, I'm not talking
about work.
This is personal.
I was worried.
I didn't know
anything.
Yes, but you have to understand
the whole Henry thing
has been hard for all.
This is hell for us.
Sure, I know.
I know.
That's why I'm here.
I just want you to know
that I'm here for you.
But if you leave me aside,
I can't.
Thank you.
But it's not a good moment.
- For real, Ernesto, no.
- No, no, Cielo.
Your sister saw me here.
What's the thing between us?
How much longer?
I'm divorced, you're divorced.
Why do we have to hide?
Let's talk about it later.
Is there anything
you haven't told me?
I need to know?
No, no, no.
Let's talk later.
You really want
to do this now?
Are you going to make me
do this right now?
Okay.
You're right.
Okay?
We'll talk later.
Yes, yes.
Okay.
We'll talk
when I'm back at the office.
Take as much time
as you want.
Hey, dude,
I can't believe
you had to crush the RV.
It's depressing.
We should sort of...
keep a moment of silence.
No one misses it
more than me.
I was free to cook anytime,
anywhere.
I was free.
No responsibilities, no nothing.
Like a freelancer.
What's the point
of being an outlaw
when you got responsibilities?
They say on TV
that organized crime
doesn't pay.
They say Pablo Escobar
thought the same,
that's why he was so stressed
and worried
in the end.
The worst part
is I have to pay taxes now.
Pay taxes!
It's nonsense.
That's Kafkaesque.
Isn't it?
Yes, sure.
You know what, Tripa?
We should start slinging again.
- Yes, dude.
- Deal with the family.
We could get another RV.
Tripaseca and I will
take care of that.
No, no, no.
If we're doing it,
it needs to be different
this time.
A different way
of getting the product...
Other clients.
You get me?
Man...
How do you do that?
It's all planned, bitch.
How much does it weight?
José!
Hey!
Concentrate!
We haven't finished yet.
How much does it weight?
55 pounds.
"I'm no fool,
this is scorn
I own the money
and everything
I'm a foreigner, a traveler,
not just a cooker
I ain't no banker,
I come from garbage.
I'm the king of mortar,
they call me rude
Those treacherous bitches...
Why don't we start?
Who wants to begin?
You?
What's your name?
I'm Mauricio.
Welcome, Mauricio.
- Thanks.
- What do you want to tell us?
Well, I'm here
because...
I do meth.
Sounds funny, right?
"Do meth"
No, methamphetamine.
You get me, right?
That new stuff
that's hitting the streets.
I've left it
twice.
But there's a blue meth
in the streets now...
- It's so cool.
- No, no, no!
You just try
and it starts climbing up...
I'm sorry.
I didn't raise my hand.
That's fine.
What's your problem?
Pedro, but everyone
calls me Tripaseca.
Fine, then, Pedro.
Welcome.
Go on, Mauricio.
I'd never felt
life I felt with that blue
meth.
That stuff burns you
down.
I'm really scared
I might come across
that burning
and delicious meth again.
It's hard to get away from it
because you find it
on one corner,
you find it on the other.
It burns you down.
It burns your head down.
That's for meth addicts.
What do you do?
It's just so tempting.
That's... No.
It's really cool.
Yes.
It's the craziest
experience.
The craziest of all.
Excuse me,
what was your name?
Mauricio.
No, man,
you have to be strong.
Cheer up.
Pedro, thanks for your comments.
No, it's...
What a hard story.
I don't know what to do,
Cielo.
It's lots of zeros.
If I don't get it with the
insurance, I can't pay for it.
This is something daily.
María...
I want you to know
we're here for you.
Thanks, Walter.
I'm really thankful
for your support.
Walter, we can pay
for Henry's treatment.
Cielo, what are you saying?
Did you see the numbers?
Where would you get
that money from?
We have enough money!
- Cielo, please.
- No.
I think María
should know the truth.
No , Cielo, Cielo.
Wait a second.
Yes, I know it's embarrassing!
- No, no, no, please!
- But we have to tell her.
No!
María, Walter earned
lots of money.
- Gambling.
- What?
You know that Walter and I
have had problems lately
and it was because of that,
because of the money.
- for money?
- Yes!
When Walter was diagnosed,
his mood changed.
I just couldn't understand
everything he was going through.
He was not just afraid
of dying,
but of leaving his family
without anything.
So...
for better or for
worse...
he began gambling.
And he did well.
He did very well.
He even managed to pay
for his treatment.
What? Wait a moment.
I thought Edgar and Marcela
paid for your treatment.
Yes, I thought so too.
The truth is
he never took the money.
He was too proud
to take what he considered
to be charity.
Is that right?
You know Walter.
He began studying, reading...
and he made it.
He found a method
to count cards
and take money from casinos.
- Really, Walter?
- You know him.
He...
He solves problems,
he gets solutions.
And in this case he found...
What did you call it? A...
Statistical edge?
Yes, yes,
yes.
A statistical edge.
Exactly.
You remember when
Walter disappeared
and nobody knew
where he was?
Sure.
He was at the casino.
He was leading a double life.
What about your memory loss?
Was that a lie?
- No.
- No, no, no.
Not that...
In fact that night...
Walter had lost 30,000 dollars
in a clandestine bet
with some Koreans.
That was all our savings.
He was in shock.
he got out of the clinic
and went right to a casino
to get that money back.
Really, Walter?
- Well...
- I'm sorry.
What really matters here
is that with this system
to read cards
he didn't just recover
what he'd lost,
he also won a lot.
Although he didn't bet
again...
- Right?
- No, no, no, never again.
In spite of that,
we have enough money
to pay for Henry's treatment.
How much money
are we talking about?
How much?
Of...
I don't know.
Whatever you need.
I'm really good
with this system.
The one I invented
to count cards.
So I don't want you
to worry about the
insurance
or about the money.
- All right?
- Yes.
Wow!
I need a cigar.
A cigar?
- Yes, this is
too much information.
Come with me?
- Yes.
- Walter, thank you.
No, no, no.
Thanks to both.
Let's go.
Does Junior know?
No.
And he can't know
it.
No.
- Neither does Henry.
- Why?
Because Walter
would feel really ashamed
and Henry already has
enough things to think about.
Right?
- Don't tell him
- Okay.
María.
Henry woke up.
He's asking about you.
Thank you.
- Fine.
How did you come up
with that?
I learnt form the best.
I think it's the least
we can do.
Somehow something tells me
that Henry is here
because of you.
I'm not forgetting that.