Hello? Cielo, babe.
María, hi.
What?
She was born?
And how is she?
Is she all right?
Is everything okay?
Thank God!
No, no.
I'm stuck here on the 30.
I think there was
an accident. I don't know.
No, no, no,
don't wake her up.
Tell her I'm on my way.
I'll be there any second now.
Fine, thanks.
See you.
Cielo, babe.
Meet your daughter.
Hi.
Congratulations, Walter.
Ernesto, I'm sorry.
I didn't see you.
Don't worry.
Ernesto brought
me here.
Valentina wanted to come
out so hard
that we thought she was going
to come in the car.
Yes.
Almost like in the news.
I'm glad it didn't come to that.
Thank you, Ernesto.
No, it's my pleasure.
I'm going to leave
so you three are alone.
Thank you.
I can't thank you enough.
No, it's my pleasure.
It's what I had to do.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Bye, Walter.
See you.
Are you okay?
Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm perfect.
I just wish
you'd been here.
And the rest?
Henry and María
took Junior
to eat
something.
He has been
such a trooper.
He even changed
his first diaper.
- Did he?
- Yes.
You need anything?
You want me to bring you
anything?
The bag with Valentina's stuff.
Since it was going
to be a C-section,
I left it at home.
Just let me look at her
one more second
and I'll go for it.
You know?
I'm glad I did it
naturally instead.
It couldn't have gone
any better.
I'm so proud of you.
Hi, dad.
Hi, daddy.
I was in the shower
and didn't hear the phone.
I overslept, but
I'm on my way, I swear.
Yes, I'm on my way right now.
Okay, see you. Bye.
Baby, I have to go.
Bye.
Hey, I think somebody
broke in.
It's all right.
No, please, no.
Please, no!
Son of a bitch!
This week was tough.
Really tough.
It was my birthday and...
You know how everything
turns into a temptation.
I didn't feel good.
So I called my boss
and I told him
that I was sick.
I think my boss
didn't like it.
But what could I do?
As soon as I got out on the
street and met a friend...
Damn!
I'd fall back.
It's better to be alone
than in bad company.
I've got one year clean
to the day.
I'm clean.
I haven't fallen.
Bye.
So how are you?
Fine, daddy.
Fine.
Well, tell me something
about you.
There's not much to tell.
Everything is
just the same.
I just work on
my drawings,
a take care of my plants.
My days are
pretty boring,
but that's good news.
That means I'm doing
all right.
Yes, but you look tired.
- Are you getting enough sleep?
- Yes.
Yes, the thing is...
I'm working
an a new schedule.
I get inspired at night
and I'm working on a tattoo
that has me
sort of obsessed.
But it's almost finished.
I don't like you working
in that place.
I've already told you
it's not the same
as working at a bar.
Yes, but people
who get tattoos...
I don't think they're--
Look, I know, I know.
But I'm telling you
that not everyone
who gets a tattoo
is on drugs.
No, but most do.
I'm talking about
healthy students.
Nice little guys that go
and get a tattoo.
That's all.
It's not the same
it used to be.
- I hope so.
- Yes.
But let's talk
about something else.
- How's your job doing?
- Fine.
Sometimes I have to work
double shift,
they haven't raised my salary
in three years.
We have a lot of work.
Some are working abroad
and they get a better pay,
they have holidays.
Are you seeing anyone?
Look like we're playing
not to talk about oneself
and get information
from the other.
But I asked you first.
No.
- Yes.
No, I'm not seeing
anyone.
And you?
Is there anyone?
I'm just asking
because the other day
when I went to your place,
the guy next door
sort of wanted to talk to me.
Or kind of, right?
Must be because he knows
you're the owner.
You don't believe me?
Why would he want
to talk to you?
Dad, I'm not seeing anyone.
I don't want
to be with anyone now,
much less your tenant.
My life is way too
complicated
to get in deeper trouble.
I don't know.
I just think
sometimes it's good
to get someone
to be with you,
you get me?
At least to drink some wine.
- Whatever.
- Yes.
It's so weird to talk
about this with you, dad.
For real.
Just stop it.
Let's discuss something else.
Let's get some breakfast.
I didn't eat anything.
Fine, I'm sorry.
You didn't have breakfast?
That's what I'm talking about.
Are we starting all over?
- I'm hungry, that's all.
- Okay, I'll pay. Let's go.
She's just like her
mom.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Who was that?
They hanged up.
I won!
Watch your reflexes.
Hello?
Hello, Walter. It's me.
Hi, Carmen, did you
hear the news?
Can you talk now?
Yes, she's so beautiful.
Yes, she did it great.
Why are you calling me
home,
fucking junkie?
Yes, I know, I know, bitch.
I called your cell phone
and you didn't answer.
It's an emergency.
Somebody broke in my place.
I got robbed.
What?
Yes, all the product.
The blue meth is gone.
It's a mystery.
Are you listening?
This is serious
stuff!
They knew exactly
where to look for it.
It's as though
they were watching us.
Walter, say something!
Answer me!
Scream at me!
So something!
Just react!
Hello? Walter? Walter?
Damn!
Family, chicken is here.
Joint, legs, tights.
What do you want?
- Cool.
- Watch it. It's hot.
- Smells good.
- Yes, it smells delicious.
- Pollos Hermanos?
- Yes, yes.
The name is not that good,
but the moment you try
those tights,
you won't ever forget it.
Believe me.
We cops
eat lots of chicken.
- Right, babe?
- Yes.
She must be hungry.
- You think so?
- Yes.
Cielo...
Cielo, just hold on.
- Are you breasting her?
- Of course!
Babe, please.
The baby has to eat.
That's normal.
Yes, but it's
my sister-in-law's breast.
We're at the table.
Come on.
Then look aside, Henry.
That's even worse.
If you tell me "look aside",
I'll want to look.
Henry, can I ask
you something?
Sure.
You told me about
a security system
for the baby.
Yes, an intercom.
Yes, that's it.
Well, I was thinking
about something more
modern.
There are some alarms
with movement sensors
in case something falls
on the floor and--
- That sounds expensive.
- Thanks, aunt.
Yes, but that's the best
for Valentina.
Babe, we'll get that for you.
No, no, it's not necessary.
Come on, man!
No, No.
Besides, I'll go back to work
in a couple of days, so--
- Back to work?
- Of course.
Babe, you have
a scheduled surgery.
We have to pay for that.
We have to keep
that income.
Look.
We have to think about what's
best for the baby.
And the best is for her
to be with her mom.
At least during
the first year.
If we get organized, I can take
care of everything.
You guys got a printing press
in the garage
churning out 50s?
I wish, uncle!
mom's even talking
abut me getting a job.
- Really?
- Of course..
Some part-time job
that leaves him time to study.
But he should help us
with the bills.
Sure. I'll work
as a waiter.
I don't get it.
No one would hire me
in a job like that.
Give her the bottle.
I'll get her.
It's ready.
Hi.
Come.
Yes.
You want to see what daddy
did for you?
All this is yours.
Daddy got it for you.
This place
looks exactly the same.
At least get some
computers.
It's the 21st
century.
What the hell
are you doing here, asshole?
You took the meth!
I heard those messages
and figured it out.
- Did you?
- Yes.
Did you really
figure it out?
You're a genius!
You should work at the CIA!
You left me freak out
all day long,
like I dropped the ball!
I was about to go nuts.
You can't break
into someone's house
just like that!
Shut up!
And lower your voice.
Stop saying
"as I'd dropped the ball".
You always drop the ball!
We were about to lose
the most important deal
we've had so far
because of you.
What did you do this time
that you didn't even react
with my yelling?
What was that shit?
Heroine?
- Damn.
- You know what?
I was on my day
off
and I can do
whatever I want.
- Your day off?
- Yes..
Don't be so shameless.
You knew perfectly well
that we had
an important meeting,
piece of shit!
And I was there and solved it
without your help!
By the way, thank you.
You made me miss
the birth of my daughter.
- How much?
- How much what??
How much did they pay you?
1.2 million dollars.
So I get half
of that,
right?
No.
We have to take Saúl share.
That's 20%.
So where's the money?
Are you really
fucking kidding me?
You really think
I'll give you that money
so that you go and spend it
on heroine,
on coke, on some shit?
You'd be dead
in a week.
No, sir.
I tried heroine
once
and I didn't like it
because it made me...
Sick.
- Really?
- Yes.
And I'm clean of meth.
I no longer do that.
I'm clean.
- Are you?
- Yes.
- I'm clean.
Pee in that.
Can't you stop saying
so much bullshit?
Have it tested
at a drugstore.
Show me you're clean
and I'll give you
every last dime
of your share.
What is it?
You can't do that?
From now on
you'll have to ask some friend
to pay for you to high.
You should begin
with that junkie girlfriend
you have.
you'll wake her up.
Walter, be careful,
María,
I won't wake her up.
I have to change
her diaper.
Yes, but she's sleeping.
Give me a towel.
Hey, these towels...
They sell
hypoallergenic towels.
This is old stuff.
It doesn't matter.
It's good enough.
Give me one.
Grab this for a second.
Clean your hands first
and then get one.
Done.
Can you give me one?
You have to see this.
It's something Junior did.
Come.
Babe, I'm changing her diaper.
Just leave her.
I'll change it.
- Cover her.
Come, come.
What did he do?
Come.
Look.
Mom, I told you
it wasn't ready yet.
Honey, show your dad.
It's so sweet, Junior!
- Morgan...
- I mean, Morgan.
No,
wait a second.
You're not asking for money,
are you?
Yes, done.
It's for the donations.
There's the account number
so that hey make the deposit.
No, no,
we can't do this.
Hey, Walter.
But it's okay.
The page is really nice.
Thanks.
What else will you add?
Why don't you put a picture
of the whole family?
- What is it?
- Babe.
He worked really hard
on that project.
Let him help.
- Cielo, it's--
- Please.
If you don't let him,
he'll get really sad.
That's beggary.
That's such a hard word.
I don't know.
Charity.
What's wrong with it?
Or do you have
extra money?
This makes no sense.
I have so much money
that I can't even count it.
I had to weight it
in the bathroom scale.
Even like that,
I can't use it.
I can't tell my family
I have it.
People think
I'm starving and I--
Look, you never thought
about telling your wife?
No, not by any chance.
Why don't you get a lover
then?
What does that have to do
with it?
What does it have to do?
Some fresh meat
is always welcome.
Besides, you'd have someone
to share your
secrets with
and that would help you
get it all out.
I have enough problems
to keep on adding.
- No way, Saúl!
- Fine, fine.
I was just brainstorming.
We don't have to buy
the first option
that comes to mind.
I know!
What about telling
them you found a bag
full of money at
the bus terminal?
Get serious, man!
That has worked for me.
The uncle!
That's it!
You got an inheritance
from a depraved uncle
that abused you
when you were a child.
No! it can't be something
out of the blue!
Besides, I never had
a pervert uncle.
No, I earned that money!
Me, the one that appears
on that page
my son designed
to ask for charity.
SalvemosaWalter.com.
- No.
-Yes.
Just look at this.
There's even an
account number.
Very good!
Good?
Good for what?
To beg?
Walter, I think we have
the solution
right in front of
our noses.
No, forget it, Saúl!
I'm not putting my money in
there.
It'll look like some benefactor
saved me.
No, I'm not talking
about one benefactor,
singular.
I'm talking about
lots of benefactors,
do you get me?
Unintentional
figureheads.
All we need
is an illusionist,
a hypnotist,
a miracle wonder.
Don't look at me
like that.
I'm not asking
you to parachute.
Listen to me.
I have a cousin in Venezuela
that knows this
business pretty well.
He knows a hacker
than can get in any
personal computer
in the world
and make them do
whatever he wants
without them realizing it.
An illusionist,
a miracle wonder.
Can you imagine
getting donations
from anywhere in Colombia?
Or from other
Latin American countries?
They're all so
good-hearted.
Or 1,000 or 2,000
dollars
from some American.
Or Euros from any part
of the world.
There are generous
people everywhere.
Solitary people that
will be really happy to be part
of the salvation
of Walter Blanco,
the martyr of cancer.
That guy's an idiot.
He's always judging me.
- Okay, fine.
- Who does he think he is?
I taught him all this.
So now what?
I'm the slave?
No, no way.
- Okay, stop it.
- Right?
- So now what? The needle?
- Yes.
I don't understand
what you need
that guy for.
Exactly.
That's the point.
I don't need that dude.
- Ready?
- Yes, your arm.
Flat against your skin
so it doesn't
wiggle around
too much.
- This way?
- Yes.
How much does he owe
you?
480 thousand.
I'd be mad too
if somebody owed me
480 thousand
pesos.
Not pesos, dollars.
What?
Hold on, hold on.
How much?
480 thousand dollars.
Bay, turn.
On your side in
case you throw up.
That's it.
He tells me
not to preach him,
not to tell him off,
but he doesn't get it.
But I tell him
I'm not preaching him.
Part of the process
is taking about things,
facing them.
Hi, daddy.
I was sleeping.
I overslept
but I'm coming.
Okay, bye.
Wait, wait.
No, no, no...
No, no, let him go.
Let him go!
Let me go!
What's wrong with you?
Just leave him.
Come on.
What's up with this
dude, Juana?
You're a fucking junkie!
Get out of my house right now!
I'm not going anywhere!
I pay for my rent!
You're bullshit!
I have my human right!
Juana, you'll start rehab
right now!
Daddy, this just happened.
We were talking about it.
- I was going to tell you...
- Were you?
I was going to tell you, yes.
If you'd just let me.
Juana, what happened?
You were clean for 18 months.
18.
Why do you do this to you?
To me?
I'm using again,
I accept it.
But do you think
I do it because I like it?
You think I do it
on purpose?
You think I'm proud of myself?
That's why
you mess around
with this bastard.
You must know that for
yourself.
He's José.
You can't judge him
because you don't know him, dad.
We talk about rehab
all the time.
Sure, you talk.
That's wonderful, isn't it?
So you talk?
Thanks for trying
to understand.
That's just what I need.
Someone judging me
all the time,
telling me I'm weak.
Damn!
Juana, don't manipulate me.
I've spent ten years,
ten years!
trying to do
the best I can for you
in the good way.
But if you want
the hard way,
I'll do it.
Let's call the police.
- No, no.
- Mr. Diego.
Let's calm down,
please.
Please, dad, no.
National Police.
How can I help you?
This is Diego Maldonado.
There's a stranger at home
and I need you to come
right away.
- Is he dangerous?
- He's dangerous, yes.
Give me your address, please.
Sure, the address...
I'll start rehab tomorrow.
- Hello? Hello, Mr. Diego?
- Just a moment, please.
- Today!
- Tomorrow.
- I have to pack.
Just let me pack
and hand in
the design of the tattoo
I'm working on.
And I'll find someone
to take care of my plants
because you let it die.
Remember?
I don't want this one to die,
so, please, tomorrow.
I swear, okay?
I swear.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Juana...
Juana, listen to me.
You and I have each other.
There's no one else.
People who get in your life
are just that,
they get in and out.
You can't be an ex-dad
or an ex-daughter.
Do you have an idea
how much I love you?
Yes.
- You'll keep your promise?
- Yes, sir.
- Tomorrow?
- Tomorrow.
Juana...
Do you really mean
everything you've
just said?
If we had enough money,
nobody could make us
do anything.
Are you okay?
- Just let it ring.
- No, I'm going.
No, don't worry.
I think he'll be glad
to help you.
Just hold on a moment.
Babe, it's an ex-student.
She's studying journalism
and wants to interview you.
What?
- I think she's hungry.
- Come, babe.
Hello.
Who's this?
This is Juana,
José' girlfriend.
Or how you like to call me:
"The junkie".
How are you?
Yes, yes.
Of course I remember
you.
How are you?
Tell me, how can I help
you?
Who gave you this number?
José Miguel?
José,
he likes being called José.
Whatever.
You don't have to call me
home,
so please--
Wait, wait.
If you hand,
it'll be worse for you.
What do you mean?
I'm calling to ask
for what belong to José.
No more, no less.
What are you talking
about?
Don't pretend
you don't know
what I'm talking about.
We're talking about José money.
His half.
José told you about
the money?
He tells me everything.
You tell everything
to the person you love.
Is this some sort
of blackmail?
No, no,
I wouldn't call it that way.
This is just someone telling you
to do what's fair.
And what are you thinking
of doing with that money?
Waste it on heroine?
That's not your business.
For your
information,
I am holding Jesse's money
for his own good.
He will receive
every last dollar of it.
He will, not you.
Once he's clean.
You know what?
I'm tired of this.
Let's put things
the way they're.
This is blackmail.
I know lots if things
about you.
For instance, I know
your brother-in-law
works in anti-narcotics.
I know stuff
that will be of interest
to the police
and the press.
Tell me something.
Does José agree with
what you're doing?
We're a team.
That's it.
So this is quite simple.
You either do
what you have to do
or you'll have to stand
up to the consequences.
Are you in Mars already?
What are you thinking?
I'm worried
about that call to Mr. Blanco.
We had to do it.
He didn't want
to do things right.
Wasn't it too much?
What he did first
was too much.
No, I don't know.
I've had arguments with
him but...
I've been through a lot
with him
and I don't want things
to end badly.
He's a school teacher.
What's he going to do?
Send you with the principal?
No, Juana, this man
is not as dumb as you think.
For real.
Are you scared?
You were not serious
when you said
you'd call the cops,
right?
It won't be necessary
because he'll bring the money.
And if he
doesn't?
José, it's your money.
Look, he...
He's the bad guy.
You're the good one.
What?
Don't you want your money?
Look, we'll get it
and give it to poor kids
all over the world
and then we'll become monks
or shit.
But you can't let him
keep your money.
I don't know.
This is not me.
It doesn't feel
like me.
He's my partner.
I'm your partner.
The diaper...
We ran out of diapers?
No, we just have
one diaper left, babe.
Hi.
What are you watching?
Elephants?
Babe, can you please go
and buy diapers?
We're out.
Where's José Miguel?
José!
- José!
- Congratulations!
Nice job wearing the pants.
How do I know
you'll keep quiet?
I guess you
don't know.
You'll never hear from us again.
You'll regret this.
Listen to me!
You'll regret what you're doing!
José!
José, you know what
this means?
That we got paid.
This is freedom.
Freedom.
We can do
whatever we want.
We can go to Europe.
We can travel through
South America.
We could go to the Moon!
Let's go, let's go...
Let's go to an island
in the Caribbean.
Let's go to Galapagos!
Right away.
That one's in the Pacific.
So let's go to Cuba.
Let's go to Cuba!
You'll paint,
I'll write.
- We'll stay there. Okay?
- Yes, Cuba.
The land of
freedom.
But first
we have to get clean.
Did you hear me?
Yes.
But not because anybody
is telling us yo.
We'll do it for us,
right?
Yes, right.
We can't waste all that
on drugs.
No, of course not.
- I mean it!
- Yes, for real.
Because we can be
better than that, right?
You and I can be much better
than that.
We don't need this, right?
Good night.
Can I have a beer please?
Thanks.
Hi, babe.
Yes, yes.
I've been
to three different places
and I can't find any.
Do they have to be diapers
for newborns?
What if we went up a size?
Hum.
Yes. No, I'll get them.
In fact, I'm getting in
a supermarket right now.
Fine, see you.
Bye.
That was good.
Did it sound credible?
It's just that
you never know women completely.
Sometimes I think they have
some kind of superpower
to read minds.
Yes, that's right.
I don't have that
problem
because mine has been living
in the U.S. for years.
But you're totally right.
It did sound credible
but don't get home
drunk.
NO, I'll just drink this one
and leave.
I just needed a little break.
Yes.
Yes, that's necessary.
They found water in Mars.
Would that be good or bad?
Actually, they theoretically
can separate
the hydrogen from the oxygen
and process that
into providing fuel
for man's space flights.
At least that's interesting.
Turning Mars
into a giant gas station.
You know about the subject.
Are you a scientist?
I'm good at Science.
I like it.
I can tell.
That's good information.
A boy or a girl?
- What?
- The owner of the diapers..
It's a girl.
- Newborn.
- Yes.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
I have a daughter too.
She'll turn 27 next month.
I have another son,
he's 15,
almost 16.
It's incredible.
How can they grow so fast?
You have any advice?
Having a daughter.
I just have the impression
they're so different.
Yes, sure.
You must always accompany
them, be with them.
Give them good advice,
listen to them.
And talk to them.
After a certain age
they make their own
decisions.
Some are right,
some not so much.
That's when you have
to be understanding
and be with them.
- Be family.
I also have this nephew.
He screws up
once and again.
One mistake after the other
and...
But he's a grown up.
I can't treat him
like a child.
What do you do
in that case?
I get you
perfectly well.
I know what you're
talking about.
Nobody said it'd be easy.
All you can do
is always stay alert.
What do you exactly mean?
Always be with them.
Be by their side
in good and bad
times.
Stand, help,
give good advice.
Be always there.
José!
José, open up!
I just want to talk to you.
José.
José, wake up.
José,
I want to talk.