Boss?
I've already taken care
of the car issue.
Did you make sure
nobody followed you?
Yes, sir.
I stayed off the main streets
so that nobody is suspicious.
Did the old man
make questions?
No, sir.
I told him
what you said to me.
That you needed the same job
that he did on the bus.
And he put his men to work.
They took the car apart.
It's unbelievable
how they do it in a minute.
I've never seen
something like that.
Should we deal
with this other thing now?
Yes.
It's about time.
I don't want to talk about this.
Sure, sir.
It had to be done.
Yes, sir.
What's up?
I need to talk to you.
In private.
What happened?
Did you meet Mario?
Yes.
So.
How is he?
Did he run away?
Mario isn't here anymore.
He's gone.
All right.
I was thinking about this.
We have nine guys in jail.
Don't we?
They have no reason
not to talk now.
What are we going to do?
"We"?
As far as I'm concerned,
I'm the only vote left.
I'll handle it.
Prosecutor,
investigator Navarro.
My client is willing
to collaborate with the case.
He will supply vital information
relating to the production,
distribution and organization
of the criminal enterprise
of methamphetamine
that belongs to Gustavo Cortés.
All right! Wonderful!
In exchange,
we expect
all charges to be dropped
so that not only
he walks out of here a free man,
but also receives
blanket immunity
as regards this investigation.
You're good, man.
Do you work on stand comedy?
For all the information
he is going to give you,
this deal is fair.
All we can do
is to reduce his charges.
No, no, no, no.
All charges dropped.
We'll drop some charges,
and give him an individual cell.
No, please, gentlemen.
Let's talk seriously.
Okay.
I'm done here.
Where are you going?
Do you want to know?
I'll speak with someone
who tells me new things.
Excuse me.
Don't go! Wait!
I have information
that may be of your interest.
Listen.
Are you confused?
It's a supply and demand market.
You offer things,
and I buy them.
Do you understand?
I have eight other persons
who can talk
and want to talk.
Okay?
Four of them
are also in this jail.
And do you know what?
I also have the lawyer
who will give me
Mario Arboleda
and all the money.
What do you think?
So calm down.
And enjoy this beautiful resort
where you'll spend
the rest of your life.
Excuse me.
Order.
A coffee or something.
I don't want anything to drink.
If you order something,
we'll be less suspicious.
Nobody
will be suspicious.
I'm not thirsty.
Give me the list, please.
What happens?
Come on, Lidia.
We've already talked about it.
You're already here.
You have the list,
don't you?
Yes, I do.
Give it to me.
It's not written down.
Why is that?
It's in my head.
It's safer there.
Then I suggest
you pick up a pen,
and write it down.
Not yet.
I think I'm misunderstanding.
I thought
you wanted to take care
of nine guys who are in jail
and who could get us in trouble
if they talk.
With the lawyer,
now they're ten.
Ten. Whatever.
Lidia.
I'm doing this
for mutual benefit.
We don't want
any loose end,
don't we?
Of course.
Specially,
if I'm one of those ends.
The way I see it
is that if give you the list,
and you do what you have to do,
I'll be the only person
who knows too much.
So?
What you're thinking right now
is that you'd give me the list
and the next moment
I'll murder you here.
- No, not here.
- Outside.
You don't see what I'm saying.
No, listen.
You made me swear
on my children's life
that I'd respect
your life and your safety.
Didn't you?
We were talking about Mario.
You swore that Mario
wouldn't hurt me.
- It's the same.
- No, it isn't. It's different.
May I know why it's different?
Because Mario wouldn't let you
touch anybody in the list.
And if you're doing this,
it means Mario cannot talk now.
Therefore,
I think Mario is gone.
Am I wrong?
Why don't we focus
on what's important?
- I knew it.
- Be clear, Lidia, please.
If you don't give me the list,
you aren't useful for me.
I can make your business
grow more than you can imagine.
- Give me the list.
- Listen.
I can make you expand
to a bigger market.
- More important.
- Give me the list!
What do you know
about the Czech Republic?
What the hell
are you talking about?
Did you know that there
they use more methamphetamine
than any place in Europe?
Five per cent
of its 10,000,000 inhabitants,
500,000 people,
use meth there.
If you keep your market here,
but also export,
I can make you double or triple
your income.
I've been doing some research.
The average purity
is only about 60 per cent.
They've never seen
anything like your product.
You'll blow their heads off.
I don't know.
Thinking about exporting is...
You know?
I don't want
to get into trouble.
No.
Nothing happens
if you're Madrigal Locomotiva.
Madrigal
is under investigation
by Anti-narcotics, the DEA...
The restaurant division, mostly.
It's a minimum part
of the corporation.
We have 20 bigger divisions
and more than 100,000 employees
in Latin America and Europe.
Now that Mario is gone,
his people aren't a problem.
We can do things right.
That's what I want.
Efficiency.
Do you understand?
My job is moving things
from point A to point B
all over the globe
from Latin America.
Everything that goes through
the Panama Canal
is related to me.
I deal with 1.2 million tons
a month.
All of them
are under my control.
They're a click away.
Who's there
on the other end?
People I've been working with
for a long time.
People I've work with for years;
responsible people.
I'm very careful
who I work with.
If the business
is that easy,
why didn't you offer it
to Gustavo?
I did.
And he accepted.
We were in the final stages
of working it out
when somebody killed him.
Do you think Gustavo Cortés
built his distribution network
all by himself?
There're considerable advantages
to diversification
of distribution.
One of them
is putting 6,000 miles
between you and your product.
We know it
since the cocaine cartels
in the eighties.
What's the output?
With ten kilos per week,
you may be earning
around 2,000,000 dollars
per shipping.
Give me four kilos
to begin with.
Let's see what happens.
Okay.
My deal with Gustavo
was going to be thirty per cent.
- Okay.
- I think it's fair
if you consider
I'm risking a lot.
Lidia, I'm saying it's okay.
The list.
Do we have a deal?
We have a deal.
You and me
are making a lot of money.
Hello.
I think it's time
I meet your uncle.
Where're we going to do it?
Wherever,
except in the workshops.
There're a lot of tools
that can be used for defense
and a lot of witnesses.
It has to be simple.
Let's do it in the yards,
the showers and the cells.
Yes, that's easier.
The riots are ruled out?
Yes, I don't want a chaos.
I don't want it.
Something strange may arouse.
And we could end up
losing territory.
It's fast and certain.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Commando operation,
do you get it?
It's your call, boss.
How many prisoners
do we have in Bogotá's jails?
Fifteen in one;
25 in the other one.
Mostly, military personnel.
And in the other cities?
It's even easier.
Almost all the yards
belong to us.
Perfect.
Let's do it.
Okay.
I'm going to talk directly.
We are an organized army.
As such, we have rules.
Do you understand?
Yes, it's perfectly clear.
Therefore, I thank you
for listening to my offer.
Tell me something,
why do we have to do it
at the same time
if the places are different?
I don't want any reaction.
If they isolate one man,
the entire operation will fail.
In some way,
it has to be good
for our own interests.
Of course.
Money is ready.
You can do what you want
with that.
I still think
it's a problem
to do it at the same time.
I've already seen that picture.
I don't know
why there're so many.
It's as if they got a container.
Listen, my friend.
We're talking seriously.
I'm saying
that the job can be done,
but not in the way you want to.
It isn't me
who's wasting your time.
You're wasting it
by doubting.
The job can be done as I say.
I's your choice.
Do you want the money.
Figure it out.
Put me through fast.
It's urgent.
Fast.
What's the matter?
What's wrong...?
No!
Aaaah!
Argh!
Aaah!
Uff!
Mm, mm, mmmmmm!
Argh!
Aaaaaaah!
Perfect.
We continue
with some news
of public order.
It's last minute news.
New details have come to light
about the multiple murder
that occurred at the same time
in different jails
three days ago.
We don't know
the name of the victims, yet.
But authorities
are investigating
what can be the result
of a coordinated action
that was carefully planned.
Deaths took place
within minutes of one another
in four jails,
in three different cities.
- I'm sorry. I'll turn it off.
- Don't worry.
Henry has just come.
If we watches the news,
he'll be in a bad mood.
- Yes, it's okay.
- Come here, sweetie.
- Look, your aunt.
- Hi!
What happens, sweetie?
I think her teeth
are coming through.
- She's crying more.
- Yes. She's heavier.
Uff!
- Hi, honey.
- What's up?
- Hi.
- How are you?
How are you, honey?
Hello.
Do you want something to eat?
I cooked some chicken,
but I can also order
Chinese food.
Whatever you want to, honey.
It's okay.
And you?
One baby's bottle for you.
- What's up, man?
- What's up?
How are you?
I'm fine.
And you?
Saying hi to my baby.
I was about to go.
Come on.
Stay for a while.
Have a drink with me.
I don't know.
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
One.
They're the worst.
- Cheers!
Listen.
Do you know that lately
I've been remembering
a job I had
when I was 14?
I worked
for my grandfather's friend.
We had to go up the mountain,
collect black soil,
for plants nurseries,
put it in some sacks,
and carry them on our shoulders.
We went up and down.
All day,
up and down the mountain.
We carried... No!
Working outdoors is nice.
- Isn't it?
- No, man.
We got sunstroke.
Bugs bit us.
Why have you thought of that?
Because right now
I'd rather
get sunstroke,
and be bitten by bugs
than chasing
psychopaths and monsters.
Do you know what I think
when you tell me that?
That I love camping.
Wow!
It's beautiful!
Well done!
That's it!
Do you want to see it?
Shall we show them?
Yes?
Show it to me.
- Look.
It's beautiful!
He's more beautiful
than in real life.
- Look at it.
- I look the same.
He's all day
with that phone.
Sweetie,
shall we go to the movies?
- Do you like it?
- Hello.
Hold on, Mom.
What's up, Lucho?
Tell me.
- No.
- It's okay.
Really?
What else can we ask for
at that age?
Valentina.
Baby.
Your brother is gone.
You look much better,
do you know?
Much better, happier.
I'm trying.
Yes, but you're better,
aren't you?
I don't know. Yes?
Henry and I
have been talking
about...
well, the kids and you.
They miss their parents.
Doesn't Henry want them
to be here?
No, no, no, no.
Don't you dare to think that.
Henry loves them.
I love them.
We're happy
to have them here.
We want to help you, but...
What is it?
Sometimes I feel
that we're helping you
in the wrong way.
Do you understand?
That...
That perhaps
we're helping you too much.
María, look.
Listen to me, Cielo.
I know that Walter and you
went through
very hard times,
but I feel
it'd be very helpful
if you get back
your responsibilities, Cielo.
I mean.
I feel the best way
to recover your family
is, precisely that,
recover your family.
Don't you agree?
Walter.
I need to show you something.
Do you have
the car keys?
Come.
Can you explain me
what are we doing here?
This is a place
where people keep stuff
when they don't have
a place to put them.
I've rented this warehouse.
Close it.
This is
what you've been working for.
I started bringing it here.
I didn't know what else to do.
The laundering rhythm
isn't enough.
I gave up counting it.
I can't do it.
It was so much, so fast.
I tried weighing it.
As the Cali cartel used to do.
I figured one bill
weighs, approximately, a gram.
I could have been able
to do a calculation,
but the weight is different
according to the denomination.
Dollars are heavier than pesos.
So...
Honestly, I gave up.
Do you know
how much money is here?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
All I did lately...
All I did
was bringing it here
and keep it
away from humidity and bugs.
But there's more money here
than we can spend
in ten lives.
I can't launder it all.
Not even buying
ten car washers.
Walter,
I want to be with my kids again.
I need my life back.
So tell me:
How much is enough?
How big
does this pile have to be?
Hello.
What's up?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have come
without telling you.
In fact,
I called your cell phone.
I threw away
all my cell phones.
It makes sense.
Yes.
I called your home line, but...
It's disconnected.
It isn't
that I don't have the service.
It's unplugged.
Yes, yes, yes.
- Did you leave a message?
- No, no, no, no.
So? What happened?
Everything is all right.
I'm okay. Normal.
I was around.
I was in the neighborhood.
I thought of checking on you.
Do you want to come in?
Sure.
How are you? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'd offer you a beer,
but I drank the last one.
No, it's okay.
Don't worry.
I don't drink this early.
You finally didn't move.
No, I didn't have to.
Saúl told me what you did.
You didn't go to jail.
Neither did I.
I think
there isn't a problem.
Jose.
I need you to understand
I had to do it.
I didn't have a choice.
I won't go back.
I know.
It's crystal clear.
Then what are you doing here?
May I?
Sure.
This is very strange.
I was on the street
the other day,
and I saw...
You won't believe me.
A bus just like ours.
It was identical.
Do you remember our bus?
- Really?
- Yes.
I didn't think
there were two buses
like that one around.
I thought it was curious.
I had to tell you.
This was in better condition.
The owners have painted it
and there were no bullet holes
in the door.
What an adventure!
We were completely insane.
It was very primitive.
I remember it.
Whenever I hit a red light,
I used to pray
that no policeman appears
to fine me
because he would have caught us.
The noise it made.
The noise!
Sometimes I wake up
after having a nightmare.
It's as if there was
a box with cats inside.
- It was the timing belt.
- That's it!
Why didn't you change that?
I preferred the noise,
instead of having
a bus that stopped.
Yes.
The bus stopped.
Do you remember
when we ran out of battery
in the middle of nowhere?
- Yes.
- How long? Three days?
Yes, I remember.
- Do you remember the antenna?
- It had an aluminum antenna.
Where did you get that?
"First steps,"
"Guideline to..."?
And the gauge?
It didn't work.
Nothing in the bus worked.
All the buttons
indicate something different.
It was a lying bus.
Mythomaniac.
We had a mythomaniac bus.
Do you know which was
the craziest part?
We had money then.
With that money
we could have bought
anything we wanted to.
We could have sold the bus.
- Why didn't we do it?
- Because that's us.
I don't know why.
That's how human beings are.
We grew fond of things.
Did you grew fond of it?
Me?
Of course.
Well, not as much as you.
How you used to call it?
My crystal bubble?
The crystal ship.
Even worse!
Absolutely sentimental.
The crystal ship.
Why haven't we kept that bus?
Have you thought of that?
Inertia?
Inertia. I think so.
Well, I have to go.
It's late,
and I have to do some things.
Yes, yes, yes.
Don't worry.
I have things to do, too.
- Okay.
- I'm leaving, too.
I liked coming
and visiting you.
It was...
I'm glad you're fine.
I left something
for you outside.
Hello.
What?
I'm out.
I'm out of the business.
This is delicious.
With some big earrings.
I'm not sure about the earrings.
Perhaps I'd like
something different.
A look change,
doing something with my hair.
Like what?
Having your hair cut?
No, perhaps changing the color.
It may work.
Burgundy?
Where did you get this?
I made them bring it
from Singapore.
Really?
It's from there.
Hey, don't you like the...?
I'll have to...
María told me
to do something else.
What did you say?
Philately?
Something easier to collect.
Numismatics.
Numis--
It's good for saving, too.
Sure.
Do you know what's trendy now?
Pouring prenatal vitamins
in your hair.
Apparently,
they make it look nice.
For your hair?
It makes it grow.
It'd be good for...
Do you remember it?
I used to use rotten avocado?
With lemon.
It left it stiff.
Stiff?
Who wants something stiff?
Don't be vulgar.
Aren't you ashamed?
These are
the women's needs nowadays.
Any time,
you're ready to do it.
I'll put more sunscreen
on the girl.
The weather is terrible
at Bogotá.
It's strange, isn't it?
It's cloudy,
and then the sun comes out.
And everyone gets sunstroke.
Have you put sunscreen
on your forehead?
Yes, sure.
I'll be right back.
I'll make room
for the dessert.
No, please!
We're eating!
Why do we have to have
that image in our minds?
- I hope everything's fine!
- Don't be disgusting.
Disgusting.
They're delicious.
- Delicious.
- Aren't they?
"For my other favorite W.B.
It's my pleasure
working with you."
W.B.?
Who is he W.B.?
Wilson Borja?
Wilberto Buitrago?
Do you understand?
Walter Blanco?
You got me.
I give up.