- Cielo.
- What?
- They're here.
- How many are they?
I don't know.
Two cars, dunno.
- Toothbrush?
- Got it.
Phone charger?
In my back pocket.
Are Junior's clothes
already packed?
Yeah, I told him
to start already.
He's waiting for us there.
What's this?
Your clothes!
We've to talk to them
and go to your place.
- Cielo, Cielo...
- What?
- I'm not going.
I'm not going to stay
with Henry and María.
- Walter, we're in danger!
- I know! It's my fault.
- It doesn't matter!
- No, it does.
Forgive me. The only thing
that matters here,
is that you're both safe.
That's why you
have
to leave without
me.
No, we'll be all safe
at Henry's place.
No! If I go there,
no one's gonna be safe.
It's the police!
It's the good guys!
Cielo, you don't know
these people.
It's my fault, right?
No, how come you
say that?
I feel horrible
about the money!
No!
We've already talked about it.
I'm not blaming you.
You made a choice.
You though it was right,
that's it.
What's going on now?
Us, you...?
- What?
- You've got to move on
without me.
Believe me, it's the right thing
for all of us.
Those agents outside,
they're not going to just
leave you here.
They came to escort
and protect us.
No! No! They...
All they know is Henry's
in danger. They... Look.
We're involved here
only as a courtesy to María.
What am I supposed to say
to Junior, María and Henry?
I don't know. For God's sake,
just come up with something,
okay?
Look, Henry knows
María is always
overreacting.
Except she's not.
Okay, I'll talk to Henry.
Relax. You just back me up
with everyone else.
Perfect, Walter,
just chill out!
No! No, no, no,
there has to be another way.
There was, but not anymore.
Please, let's go. Move.
How long will it take?
When are you going to be sure?
When's this thing going to end?
I don't
know.
Cielo...
Look, I have lived
under the threat of death
for a year now,
and because of that,
I've made choices.
Those are my choices.
Mine. Nobody else's.
- Look, please--
- Cielo. Listen, please.
These choices have consequences.
I alone should suffer
the consequences
of those choices.
And those consequences
are here right now.
So please, no more
prolonging the inevitable.
Let's go. Come on.
I'll go get the baby.
Come on, Cielo, please!
Henry, bro, please understand.
I've got a car wash to run,
I can't leave it like that.
Bro, it'll be María
who kills me when she finds out.
Yeah, well, I'll get there
as soon as I can.
Tell Gómez.
I'll send you a message
with some of the guys.
Come, hang on a moment.
You know what?
I don't believe
any of this.
This whole thing's bullshit.
Yeah, bro,
but keep your head down anyway,
all right?
Fine.
Hi, my baby!
It'll be alright,
it'll be alright.
He's going to risk his life
over a stupid car wash?
Does he even understand
what's going on?
I've already told you,
he'll come when he's able to.
This is bullshit!
How hard did you even try,
or did you?
Hey, don't talk like that
to your mom.
He wouldn't be arguing
if Walter was here.
I don't understand
how you let him do that.
Why can't you tell your men
to get him in the car?
María, it's not that easy.
And why?
You know what?
I'm calling him.
I'm telling him
to come here right now.
Thanks, auntie! At least
somebody is listening to me.
We are all in danger here.
No one's in danger here.
Henry, will you stop
saying that? That is asking
for trouble.
This is Walter Blanco's phone.
Please, leave your message
after the tone.
He's not answering.
I got the answering machine.
Okay, everybody
calm down now, okay?
Cielo, you can stay here
as long as you want.
There's no problem,
we've plenty of room here
Don't you worry about Walter,
none of us is in danger.
Okay? This whole thing's
just a smoke screen.
How come?
Look, Cielo.
An anonymous threat against me?
I'm stuck in a wheelchair.
I'm not even on the job.
In my opinion...
someone doesn't like the way
I've been spending my free time.
What, the minerals?
Gómez, don't you think
it's odd,
when I start looking into
Gustavo Cortés,
I get stuck in my place?
I'm under lockdown
for my own protection?
Why do you say that?
Gustavo Cortés?
The one...
The one from Chicken Brothers?
No, I can't believe that
from this gentleman.
Such a pity.
That's my humble opinion.
I think the Chicken Brothers
is a front for the biggest
meth distributor
on this country.
Meth?
I can't believe that.
That's huge?
You're already
investigating it, right?
Well, first thing,
what Henry said:
calm down. Let's just relax.
It is being looked into.
We're working on actual facts.
And what's the fact?
Who attacked him?
The Mexican cartel.
No international corporation,
it wasn't a Spanish company.
What proof do we have?
Any leads?
Gómez, aren't you
being paid for that?
For getting the leads?
Remember that laundry
I told you about?
I'd start there.
- Man, Henry...
- That place's perfect
for a meth superlab, bro.
You know I'm right.
No-- Well, even though
I was right,
there's no way in hell
a judge is going to give me
a search warrant.
Who's talking about a warrant?
What happened to good,
old-fashioned knock and
talk?
"Hello, my lady...".
Well, no, truth is...
You were never very good
at those, were you?
- Hello.
- Morning.
Can I help you?
How are you doing?
We wondered if we could take
a look around, brother.
And why's that?
- Your name is...?
- Jairo.
Let me introduce myself, Jairo.
Víctor Gómez,
from Anti-narcotics.
What? Is there a problem?
No, no.
There's no problem,
don't you worry
Let me tell you
a story, Jairo.
- Sure.
- I bust this chef.
Well, to say a chef
would be too much.
The guy grills
expensive burgers
and he thinks he's a chef.
Yeah, sure.
Well, we bust this cook
with heroin possession.
Can't believe it!
You know what he said?
"That's not mine! Who told you?
So because you find it
in my clothes,
that makes it mine? No!
Maybe it came from the place
that launders my whites".
You know where he has
his clothes laundered?
- Here. how's that?
- No...
No, excuse me, but we don't do
that kind of stuff here.
No, no... I can see this is
a serious business.
It's easier to get heroin
in a church than here, right?
Yes, sure. Yes, sir.
But watch out.
Imagine this guy's the son
of a politician.
An important politician.
You know who we're
talking about?
Right, let's leave it there.
The politician's into deep shit.
He went to the station,
went to my boss,
my boss got me into this.
I was left with the whole story.
Help me, bro?
Man, the thing is,
I'd have to tell my boss,
and he's out of town,
I can't reach him right now.
I want to help,
but it'll be next time.
No, I get it.
But we'll be all implicated,
because I'll have to
bring in a warrant,
and I'll have to close this up
for a couple of days.
What? Why?
With a warrant,
I'll have twenty agents
poking around.
Everybody will have to be out.
Well, but that's your choice.
Help me, Jairo.
We'll be only two guys,
we take a look,
and that's it.
So, it'll just be
the two of you?
- Just the two of us.
- And it'll be quick?
You won't even hear us.
Promise?
- Man.
- Okay, fine, do it.
You tell the man, please.
Mister! Go on. Come in.
You may go on.
Come on.
Thanks.
Do me a favor.
Clear out some of your people
for us.
Confuses the dog's nose.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Done. Come on.
Thanks, Jairo.
Come on.
So how long we gotta be
quiet down here?
Come on, what happens
after this?
Provided they don't find us,
because if they do,
they'll bust our asses
out.
And meanwhile, what?
Are we staying here
under a laundry
for all eternity, amen?
For the record,
it sucks to be down here.
Hey, are you answering or
what?
Hello.
It's for you.
Give it to me.
Hello.
You know what's going on
up here?
I have a pretty good idea.
This is all the result
of your former partner.
Do you understand
the dimension of it now?
Do you see why
this can't continue?
I get it. The guy's a complete
and total dick
But I can't,
I'm not signing off.
Is that clear?
I'll repeat it for you.
If anything happens
to Professor Blanco,
you and I are going
to have a problem,
and you won't be counting on me.
So tell me
what you're going to do.
You'l have the right answer.
All in good time
Right?
What do you mean, right?
Hello?
He hanged up.
- Thanks, Jairo.
- Fine. Good luck.
Hello.
They've left, boss.
Fine!
We're good. Get back to work.
Get to work now!
This is Walter Blanco's phone.
I can't talk to you right now.
Please, leave your name
after the tone.
You have six new messages
José Miguel, it's Saúl.
I need you to call me.
It's me again!
I really need you.
Call me when you can.
Don't call me.
Come to my office right now!
- What's wrong?
Saúl's waiting for me.
- Slow down.
What are you doing, bro?
Move. Saúl, I'm here!
Stop it, man!
Stop now. Estiwar!
Not him, man.
Now, hush, calm
down...
Sorry, you can't be
too careful these days.
Please, go lock the door,
then you can take on your nap.
Come on in.
Time for a break,
Pachita HT.
You're going to stop calling me
that, or I'm going to hang you
by your tie.
Yeah, yeah, stop showing off
for the client.
Excuse me.
"Pachita HT".
Honey Tits.
I say it's endearing.
So what's so important?
Well, they're here.
The end times, José Miguel.
How come? The end of what?
Will you tell me
why I'm here, Saúl?
You want your money, right?
I guess so.
And that couldn't wait?
Mmmmh...
You ever hear the expression
"a fart in the wind," kid?
I don't think so,
Ive just made it up.
But it's quite literal,
you know?
Inside of an hour,
that's going to be me, okay?
I'm hitting the road.
I'm off!
- How come? forever?
- For as long as it takes.
I don't like my heat so hot,
if you catch my drift.
I'm not catching, like, anything
you're saying, and what the hell
is your problem?
You haven't talked
to your partner, have you?
No, not since last night.
Today he didn't show up
to work,
and the Anti-narcotics
paid us a visit.
Yeah, some coincidence?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
All I know is,
when he tells me
that your employer fired him
and threatened
to murder his entire family,
I made my choice.
Because after all,
I'm also part of his family,
right?
Wait, hang on a sec.
He was threatened?
When did it happen?
You know what?
Let's just drop it.
We both know Walter
tends to overreact.
Here.
I wanted to ask you a favor.
I'd like you to...
put in a good word
for me
with Gustavo,
your boss. I mean,
just for old time's
sake.
Okay? I can't afford
to butter the wrong
bread here.
Okay? Please?
Good luck, Saúl.
What?
Nothing?
Clean as a whistle,
that's suspicious.
Maybe that's what he wants
us
to believe?
But he'll have it
now.
This is Walter Blanco's phone.
I can't answer right now.
Please, leave your name
after the tone.
It's me again.
I'd like you
to answer the phone.
God. Call me, okay?
Please, call me.
Can I come out here
for a minute?
No. Just stay behind the bars,
for your own safety.
I wonder if you have
a cigarette?
Yes, sure.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hello.
Hi, how are you?
Hey, hey.
Calm down, what happened?
How come?
Wait, what hospital?
Okay, I'm coming.
Andrea!
Jose!
Where's Byron?
He's over there with my mom.
They got me filling out
all this paperwork.
How's he doing?
He had a stomachache
this morning,
and then we was pale
and passed out.
I don't know what it is, Jose.
He's getting worse.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry, Miss.
We're going to go ahead
and admit your son
to the pediatric ICU.
Please come with me.
- So you're the boy's father?
- No.
Then you'll have to wait
here.
You can't get in.
I'll be out here if you need me.
Let's go.
No, no, no...
No, don't do this to me.
Don't you dare do this to me.
No, no, no, no, no.
- ¡Andrea!
- Sir, you can't be here.
I don't care! I need to talk
to her! Come, it's important.
- Andrea, come here.
- No, no, no.
Jose, what's wrong with you?
Byron's sick.
- Come, it's urgent.
- I can't go right now.
Andrea, I think Byron
may have been poisoned.
- What?
- There's this stuff
called ricin.
- How do you know that, Jose?
- That doesn't matter.
Just tell them it's a guess.
Ricin. They'll know
what you're talking about.
If there's something you're
not saying, you've to tell me,
please. What's going on?
I gotta go.
I need to see someone, okay?
- I'm really sorry. Ricin.
- Jose!
- Go tell them right away.
Who is it?
It's me.
Are you on your own?
Yes, I am.
We need to talk.
Let me in.
Come in.
Come in, quick!
I don't know
what you're thinking,
coming here.
Tell me what you're thinking!
Well, it doesn't
matter.
This is the end, Jose.
It's over now.
Do you even know
what's happening?
Do you have...
the slightest idea
of what's happening right now?
Mosquera was waiting for me
at your place,
and he took me to a place.
They put a hood over my head
and had me on my knees
for who knows how long.
Then came Gustavo.
He threatened my family.
Not only Henry.
He threatened my wife
and my children.
It's just a matter of time
right now.
I was able to protect them
for now, but I don't know
how much longer I'll be able
to make it.
Gustavo is making his move
and I don't know when.
I don't know how,
but he'll make it.
And I'm powerless to stop him!
What are you doing?
Why, bro?
- Tell me why you did it!
- Jose...
Jose, put the gun down.
Please, calm down.
Put the gun down, let's talk.
Please, put--
At least--
At least tell me what
you think I did, okay?
Byron!
- Why did you poison Byron?
- Jose!
Who's Byron?
You know perfectly well
who Byron is!
You saw him!
Don't you dare fool me!
No, no, no, no!
Jose, I just saw them,
but I swear, I have no idea
who these people are.
Jose, I swear.
Look... Byron...
Was he poisoned?
Ricin!
Byron dying in hospital
because someone gave it to him!
And only you and I were
the only two people on earth
who knew about it!
No! Wait a second!
Calm down!
Maybe the kid got his
hands
on it by accident.
- That's impossible!
- Why?
It's impossible, I had
the cigarette in the pack!
This morning I had the cigarette
in my pack!
And the last time I saw Byron
was last night,
and this morning
I put the cigarette
- into a new pack.
- Calm down!
- He couldn't have taken it!
- You're not thinking clearly.
Look at me!
You've just said it yourself!
You had the cigarette
in your pocket this morning.
Then why could I have
possibly gotten it?
It was Saúl!
You had Saúl do it!
- How?
- Yeah, I went to see Saúl
this morning-
He called me and just had
to see me this morning.
When I got there,
his big man-mountain bodyguard
patted me down.
He searched my pocket,
that's when he got it.
- That was his fucking plan!
- No! Why?
Why would I poison him?
To get back at me.
Because I'm helping Gustavo!
You knew it was
your only way
way of ripping my heart out
before you're dead and gone,
son of a bitch.
- Admit it!
- ¡No!
- I didn't do it! I swear!
Shut up!
You're a liar, bro.
Jose, I swear, I didn't do it!
Tell me why I'd poison a child!
Who could poison a child?
Tell me. Who?
No... This is...
- Don't laugh.
- Jose...
- Don't you laugh, shit head!
- Jose!
Jose!
I have been waiting all day,
waiting for Gustavo
to send his men
to put a bullet in my
head.
And it's you!
Who's okay with using children,
Jose? Think!
- Shut up.
- Who?
Gustavo!
He has always been
ten steps ahead of me!
- No! No!
- He has!
The one thing that he needed
to finally get rid of me
was your consent.
And not only
does he have
that,
but he managed
to manipulate you
into pulling the trigger
for him.
No. Only you and I
knew about this poison.
We were the only ones!
No! Don't be such a
prick!
Think! Jose, Gustavo
has cameras all over the place.
He knew it all along!
Where were you this morning?
You were at the lab, right?
And you don't think it's
possible that Mosquera
lifted the cigarette
out of your locker?
There you are!
Jose...
You are the last piece
of the puzzle.
You were the only thing
he needed.
Gustavo wanted!
You're his cook!
You have to understand!
Jose!
And not only does he have
his cook,
he also has the person
who can run the lab without me.
And now that cook
has reason to kill me.
The plan's brilliant.
He's a genius!
Not only does he get rid of
me, he also keeps his cook.
So go ahead!
If you think I'm capable
of killing a boy in this war...
- Come on!
- I will do it!
- Put a bullet in my head!
- I will!
- Do it! Shoot me!
- I will, son of a bitch!
- I will!
- Come on, do it!
- Just do it!
- I will, motherfucker!
Do it!
I will.
Jose, are you going? Jose!
Where are you going?
I'm going to find
the motherfucker
and kill him.
No, wait! Wait!
You can't get close to him,
not even at a 50 meters,
they'll kill you.
- As if I cared!
- No! Please, calm down.
Look, take your car and leave.
No, bro
I'm finding this guy today.
I'm going to do this
one way or another, get it?
Just wait.
Let me help you.
Mr. Rosas, I don't want
to sound repetitive.
You can't be here,
unless the family allows it.
So please go away.
Mr. Rosas, did you understand?
Help me, please.
Don't make me call security.
Please leave, Mr. Rosas.
Please, do it for me.
Jose.
Hey!
You've work to do.
I already told you.
I'm not going. Stop that.
You've got a batch
that will be ruined, bro.
And an employer who will
be
very upset if that
happens.
And I could give a shit, bro.
I told you,
I'm not leaving here.
If he's got a problem,
he can tell me himself,
not send his errand boy.
What are you doing, bro?
what are you gonna do?
Security, there's a man
bothering me here!
Please, I don't know him!
That's it, walk, you
prick.
We've a problem, sir.
Jose, they need you.
They want to talk to you.
Bro, how many times
do I have to tell you
I'm not leaving?
Then go on now,
they're waiting for you
downstairs.
Walk.
¡Move!
Mosquera told me
what's going on.
There's a sick kid.
I understand your concern,
but I've business here.
I need you at the lab, cooking.
You can come back
when you're finished.
I can't.
It is, as you must know,
in both of our best
interests.
The kid's called Byron, bro.
And he's dying upstairs,
do you get it?
I can't be away.
I don't even want to be here
talking to you now.
I can't leave here.
If anything happens to him...
- If the kid...
- I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Is there anything I can do?
I know the board
of this hospital.
I can recommend doctors
that could give him
the best treatment.
But he's not sick.
He was poisoned.
How did that happen?
The doctors don't know.
The batch is lost...
Am I wrong?
Stay with the boy.
Mosquera will pick up
the shit from the lab
and clean the tanks.
When you're ready,
we'll work on a new batch.
Maybe next week.
Yes. Finally!
What is it?
That's it.
Yes, go on.
give me the pleasure
of blowing you up!
Come on!
No!
Why are you turning back?
Dammit!
What are you doing?
Shit!