Hello?
I need you to listen
very carefully.
Two men are coming
to kill you.
They're approaching
your car.
- Who's this?
- They're coming.
Who's this?
Hello?
Any minute now.
Kill him.
What's up?
Are you ready to go?
I'm ready to get out of here.
They haven't come
to pick you up yet.
I can see that too, dude.
I have to get back in
to work and--
Go, no one will miss you.
Hey, you can't smoke
here.
Why not?
This is an open space.
No, if you want to
smoke,
you need away from
the door.
So roll me further, bitch.
No.
Male, early 40s,
BP is 70.
Pulse 140.
Weak and thready
at the brachial.
No breaths sounds
on the right side.
Belly is rigid.
Hay several shoots.
- How many entry wounds?
- Four.
Shoulder and hip,
through and through.
Right lung in lower left
quadrant,
no visible exit wounds.
Sorry I'm late, man.
This fucking car
is fucked up, bro.
Damn, brother, look at
you.
That's messed up!
You look good
even now that you're
all beaten up.
So how are you
feeling?
Actually, Tripa,
I'm great.
I don't understand.
I thought things
were going pretty well.
We were becoming a real team
No.
A real team
needs other stuff.
Is this about
the temperature setting?
I can assure you
that will not happen
No, it's bigger
than that.
I don't know.
Could you elaborate?
So that I don't do the same
in the future.
Yes, I
could.
But, Guido,
it's nonsense.
Neither of us
would benefit from that.
This conversation
doesn't need to
be prolonged.
You get what I mean?
I set up this entire lab.
You said you liked
the configuration.
Yes, I do like it.
For the
most part.
Guido,
you're a fine chemist
with a promising future.
The thing is that I...
I mean, we have
different rhythms.
It's as if I'm opera
and you're salsa.
Salsa?
And there's nothing bad
with salsa,
on the contrary,
it's fine for me,
it's simply
that I require more...
- Opera. Exactly. That's it.
Bitch, what's up?
Man, this is the bomb!
We'll make real cook now.
There's even
a fucking spiral.
My replacement?
Look at this tank,
dude.
How much water does it take?
3,000 gallons?
- What's up, dude?
- Nice to meet you. I'm Guido.
What's up?
We should've ditched that RV
months ago.
It's all shinny up here.
It looks like an aircraft.
Professor, Walter,
I don't mean to be rude but--
Damn, this is
what we deserve.
- Don't we?
- It makes no sense!
All right.
That's it.
Excuse.
No, no, no.
Víctor...
I can assure you
this is for the best.
I do.
You already know
how much you have
to produce weekly.
Got it?
Walter,
you're the boss here, dude.
What?
Yes, you're a chemist
and all that
so this must be right for you.
Let's get down
to business.
What?
Let's start.
I need you to understand
how all this works.
- Right now?
- Yes, right now.
We've only got a couple days
before our first batch is due.
All this equipment
is new for you
and I need to get you
up to speed.
That's fine. I just thought
I'd have
some time to get
to know this and--
What?
How do you...?
I get it!
Have you talked
to your family today?
No, why?
If I were you,
I'd call them, you know?
María.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I don't even know
what to say.
How is he?
He's in surgery.
They haven't told us anything.
They gave him four shots.
And Valentina?
I left her with a nanny.
How are you, Junior?
Fine.
I need to get some air.
I'll come with you.
No, I want to be on
my own.
BP is 80.
Two units of normal
saline.
Right femur's like
a wet bag of gravel.
- See if you get a pulse.
- It's weak.
The left foot
is broken.
Walter.
This is my boss.
- Pleased to meet you. Antonio.
- Pleased to meet you..
I'm really sorry
about what happened.
Can you tell us anything
or any details?
Right now, all we know
is two men ambushed Henry.
They had no ID on them
but we think
they might be Mexican.
Why do you think that?
They have tattoos
of Tapatío cartel.
It's like an ID among them.
Why do you think
they attacked Henry?
It could be in relation
to an investigation
Henry was working on.
Maybe it was a general message
to anti-narcotics.
We don't know that.
What happened with these guys?
Henry killed one.
The other one's upstairs
in critical condition
and they're operating
on him.
In this hospital?
Yes. Life is ironic,
don't you think?
Anyway, Henry
is tough.
He took them both
even without his gun.
What did you say, Gómez?
How come Henry
didn't have his gun?
Why?
Madam, due to the assault
charge
I had to suspend him.
That means I had
to take away his
weapon.
It's a standard
procedure.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
If you all had listened
to Henry from the start
and let him arrest
that José Miguel Rosas,
we wouldn't be here!
If he had had his gun,
he'd have defended himself!
María--
What were you doing, Gómez?
You were supposed
to back him up!
Isn't he your partner?
What ere you doing?
Getting ready to go to Mexico
or what?
Is this how you protect
your agents?
You leave them unarmed?
What were you thinking?
Come and sit.
No, I don't want to sit
and I won't shut
until these two go away.
The Anti-narcotics Department
is not welcome here.
Get the hell out of here!
Go away!
And you know what, Walter?
This is also your fault.
Henry would have never heard
from Rosas
if you hadn't bought
marijuana from him.
- María.
- You can't imagine
how much Henry has suffered
because of you.
María, María.
I know you're upset.
You're looking for someone to
blame,
but this isn't
Walter's fault.
Don't blame it on him.
I'm sorry, Walter...
I'm sorry, Walter.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hello!
Eco!
Mr. Walter Blanco
go to the nearest
courtesy phone.
That's
weird.
I'll be
right back.
- Hello?
- What's up, bitch?
Are we cooking some time
this year or what?
What the hell
are you thinking?
Why are you calling here?
Tried your cell and it
went straight to voicemail.
How am I to get
hold of you?
You aren't.
We've wasted
twelve hours already.
Didn't you say
that we had to get
working,
that we had things to do.
My family comes before
any kind of work.
Walter, it's not my
responsibility,
this is a joint
remember?
You tell me
about responsibilities?
Fine. I'll stop talking then
and I rather start doing.
I'll just cook on my own.
- You will not do such thing!
- Why not?
You aren't the least familiar
with the equipment.
No, but there must
be
some kind of manual
I can read.
- José, don't touch anything!
- Hold on, hold on.
Don't tell me what
to do, okay?
Stop treating me
like I'm your assistant.
Remember we're
partners.
Don't forget
that.
José, please, wait.
Be patient.
I'll get there
as soon as I can.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thanks for worrying
and for your prayers.
- Goodbye.
What?
Id your wife there?
Yes, thank you very much.
Any kind of spiritual help
is welcome right now.
Wait, wait, you know
what?
Don't forget to tell your
fucking brother-in-law
that when he sees the light
at the of the tunnel,
he has to walk
right to it.
Good
luck!
Sure, thanks again.
We're going to have
breakfast.
Do you want to
come with us?
Yes, sure.
Don't you want to know
who called me?
These eggs are really not bad
for a hospital cafeteria.
- Look at that!
- What?
What?
This fork is absolutely filthy.
Disgusting.
Don't you see it's filthy?
María, those are just
water spots.
It's washed.
This is not water, Cielo.
It's dirty
because they haven't washed it.
It's covered in germs
from someone else's mouth.
Aunt, that's clean.
Ours at home aren't
any better.
But this is not your house.
This is a hospital.
They have to follow
some hygiene standards.
But this is the cafeteria,
we're not in the OR--
No, the cafeteria
is part of the hospital.
How could ill people
survive this dead trap?
How?
With this shit?
You can't survive like this,
Cielo!
I survived.
When I had the lobectomy done
I was so scared
I though I was going to die.
I tried to hide it.
But I couldn't stop thinking
that they'd cut me open
as some piece of meat.
When they anesthetized me,
I was sure
I'd not see my family again.
The first thing
I thought when I woke up was:
"I'm here."
But the best part
was my family was there.
You know why I'm saying this?
I'll tell you something, María.
I'm not half of the man
your husband is
and I survived,
so I have no doubt
he'll make it.
Hello, Juan.
What the hell
is going on there, Gustavo?
I was going to ask you
the same question.
You know about my men,
the Salamanca twins?
I heard that they
attacked
an anti-narcotics
agent.
I don't know
why.
Those guys are nice,
but whenever they do something,
they have a reason for it.
What do you want me
to tell you, Juan?
The Salamanca
wouldn't do such a thing
just because.
Someone gave the go ahead.
Are you accusing me?
I'm just saying
this is quite weird-
If you want to,
come to Colombia,
and we'll solve
this confusion together.
I have things to do here.
But listen carefully.
I order you to protect
the Salamanca
that survived
until I send someone there
so that he tells us
what really happened there.
- Understood?
- Got you.
When you get so
close to the spine
there's always going
to be
cause for concern.
But it's really too
soon to tell.
And what's next
after surgery?
The post-op and
what we hope will be
his way to recovery.
When can I see him?
Unfortunately not yet.
He's in intensive care
and have to wait
for him to stabilize.
How long will that take?
We don't know.
But we'll let you know
as soon as we
have news.
That's all I have to tell
you for now.
Thank you.
María, why don't we
take you home
so that you rest for a while?
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Me neither.
Is anyone else dying to brush
their teeth
or is it just me?
What if I ran over to the house
and picked up a few things?
Walter, yes, thanks.
See you later.
Walter, what happened?
We could say he's fine.
He got out of surgery
and now we have to wait.
That's good news.
Though the best diagnostic
is for the wrong person.
What do you mean?
That Mexican mother fucker
is recovering
and he got here
even worse than Henry.
Really?
You want to see him?
Come.
Come and meet him.
There's that piece of shit.
Hello!
Hello, eco!
About damn time!
I was--
Why aren't you cooking?
Mr. Walter Blanco,
go to the nearest
courtesy phone.
Walter Blanco,
go to the nearest
courtesy phone.
Excuse me, madam?
You have a call on hold
over there.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Hello?
- Hey!
You again?
How can I help you,
reverend?
We've got problems.
Bug ones.
Reverend, I'll turn on
my cell phone
so you can call me there,
is that all right?
I told you to wait for me,
to be patient.
I really can't find
another way to tell you this.
Then don't tell me shit
and listen to me.
That creepy, quiet guy
showed up.
- Gustavo?
- No, not the boss.
Apparently I'm not worthy
of meeting him.
The other one.
The one I'm qualified
to speak to.
Yes, Víctor, what did he say?
He asked why we weren't
producing anything.
And what did you tell him?
What could I tell him?
Nothing.
Just bullshit.
- Did he tell you anything else?
- No, he just reminded me
we have a quota due
tomorrow.
Walter, do you really
not care
about what might happen
if we don't do this?
I'm the one who's
here
for them to kill.
José, calm down!
Listen to me.
I need you to answer a question.
Do you remember when Tuco
kidnapped us?
Tuco, let's see, no,
no...
You mean that psycho
that was about to kill us?
Of course I remember,
bitch!
But what does that
have to do with this?
Just leave irony aside,
will you?
I need you
to remember something.
Tuco said
that someone from Mexico
would come for us, remember?
Yes, his cousins.
But what does that
have to do with this?
Yes, cousins.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Why do you ask?
Hello.
- Hi.
- Any news?
No, nothing.
I brought some clothes
for everyone.
María, I didn't know
whose toothbrushes were
whose
so I stopped by
and bought some for all.
- Thanks.
- There's paste...
- Whatever you need.
- I'm going to wash my face.
I need to wake up.
- Come with me?
- Yes.
Look, the book
you asked me for.
Is this yours?
No, the uncle
gave it to me.
And what is it
about?
It's about Pablo Escobar
and how much
he damaged this country.
I'd all be different here
if drug dealers didn't exist.
Yes, well...
In fact it's much more
complex
than what you think
because it
involves--
It's a pity that here...
what bad guys do
is most known
than what a lot of good people
like the uncle do,
don't you think?
Give me a second.
I'll be right back.
No, Gustavo,
we're working hard.
I can assure
you that.
So I can expect
delivery by tomorrow
as scheduled.
Well, that will be
hard because...
Well, I had a problem
and we're not going to be able
to keep our schedule,
but not for luck of trying.
Is there anything I should know,
Walter?
Yes, sir.
Well, to be completely
honest with you,
Guido screwed us up.
I mean, not on purpose.
He made a mistake.
That set us way back.
Besides, I've been out
running some technical
errands to catch up.
Some of the equipment
wasn't calibrated correctly.
So I had to...
Well, it's all very
technical and boring.
It's not worth
explaining it.
But I can assure you,
Gustavo,
that we'll do things right
and we'll work
twice as needed,
even on the weekend
if it's necessary,
but we'll do our part.
I promise next week
we'll have 400 pounds.
- I have your word on that?
- Absolutely.
I promise.
Fine.
Thanks for the update, Walter.
What's
up?
I don't know what's wrong
with me.
I need to control this rat
all the time,
if not, I don't feel safe.
I get you.
Is there any news?
No, nothing.
I'm just clearing out my head.
How's the family?
Fine, they're fine.
They're trying
to be calm.
Yes, there's nothing else
you can do.
Yes, it's just that not knowing
what's going to happen,
not having any news,
the waiting is unbearable.
So what?
You know anything
about the guy that died?
What did they want?
Where were they from?
We're investigating but
there's nothing so far.
We'll find out,
I'm sure.
Gómez, do you think
there're others?
I don't
know.
But no one
will ever get
near Henry again.
You know what I
want?
Walk in there
and shoot that bastard
right in the head.
That's it.
Me too.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Yes, I'll be right there.
You know Pollos
Hermanos?
Yes.
The owner is a big
booster for the agency
and when he heard what
happened to Henry,
he brought us all food.
That's wonderful.
He brought it himself.
Let's go.
Yes, I'll be right there.
It's delicious!
Come, please, Walter.
I want you to meet Mr. Gustavo.
He offered
50 million pesos
on any information
to clear Henry's case.
Thank you very much.
That will help a lot.
That's very generous of you.
No, please,
you don't need to say that.
I only wish
I could do more.
No, please.
This money will help us
find more details
on the investigation.
I'm really shocked
about this case
because I actually met
agent Navarro.
- Really?
- Sure
His company,
Los Pollos Hermanos,
sponsored the cop marathon.
Yes, I talked for
a few minutes with Henry.
We even talked about you,
Walter.
Did you?
He was preparing a collection
for your treatment.
We talked briefly
about your health problems.
I hope you're better now.
Yes, yes.
I'm really well
and getting better.
I'm glad to hear that.
He was really
worried.
It was clear to me how
deeply he cares for you.
They're practically brothers.
I've taken enough of your time.
I'll be following the news.
Excuse me.
Good night.
- Goodbye. Thanks.
- Let me walk you out.
No, it's not
necessary.
- Excuse me.
- Go.
Well, at least
that's some good news.
I'm going to the toilet.
Excuse me.
- It's tasty, isn't it?
- Delicious!
How's everything going, guys?
It's all right, sir.
Thanks for the chicken.
It was delicious,
wasn't it, guys?
I'm glad I can help you
with something.
Good night.
Mr. Gustavo...
Yes?
I just wanted to thank you
again in person
for everything you're doing
for my family.
It's my pleasure.
Good night.
And I wanted to ask you
if we could speak
for just a moment.
You knew my brother-in-law
was in anti-narcotics.
I investigate everyone
with whom I do business, Walter.
What careful man wouldn't?
Sure.
I can assure you Henry
is no problem for the
business not for us.
You being here...
Is this some sort
of message?
I'm supporting my community.
I hide in plain sight,
same as you.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
I don't understand this
attack on my brother-in-law.
I don't know what it means.
If you know something,
please, give me a clue.
I fear for my
family.
Don't worry about your family,
Walter.
I am told
the assassin that survived
is gravely injured.
It's doubtful he'll live.
Really?
I was told he was
recovering.
Now thank me
and shake my hand.
Mr Gustavo,
thanks again
for everything you're
doing.
Thank you and Pollos
Hermanos.
It's my pleasure, Walter.
Good night.
One, two, three.
One, two, three!
Patient is in asystole.
Continuing chest compressions.
One, two, three!
Give me a liter of saline.
One, two, three.
One, two, three!
One, two, three...
He's dead.
9:44.
Gustavo, you're a son
of a bitch.
I have Federals
surrounding my house
and you're behind all this,
bastard.
Why would I do this?
Because you're
the only one who knew
I was at my house.
But I got you, son of a bitch.
You're doing all this
to be on your own
because we don't let you
cook meth, right?
I think you're under lots
of pressure, Juan.
Call me back when you
see things more clearly.
Sure we'll talk, fucker.
Sure we'll talk.
I want you to know
there's no fucking prison
in Mexico than can stop me.
We'll pay you a visit,
son of a bitch.
Police, hand up!
Don't move!
All right, all right.
Calm down.