Honey mustard.
That would be the name
for its commercialization.
Clearly, this is not
the real flavor.
We have reduced
the mustard level
and we have increased
the fructose level.
In the second sample,
we've been more creative,
and we are satisfied
with the results.
It's a mixture
between tartar sauce
and some additive
very popular in Latin
America
made by mustard and
mayonnaise.
We've called it:
"tartarise".
Clearly, we will leave
the name decision
to the marketing department,
as usual.
Do you have some
comments
about the "tartarise"?
The third sample is
a mixture
between wasabi and avocado.
We have called it "aguasabi".
We are aware
this is a weird name,
but...
The fourth sample
is ketchup, basically.
Tomato sauce.
Simply that.
They're back, sir.
And not just the police
this time.
They are with
some Interpol detectives.
Sir, are you there?
Mr. Bisbal, the police
insist on talking
with you right now.
Teacher, it's starting
to drive me crazy.
It keeps me awake at night.
I lay there thinking
"Where is it? Where did it go?"
I can't stop
thinking about that.
Jose, Jose, please,
relax.
Did you check your house?
It might be in any
place.
No, man.
I've looked
everywhere.
I've seen it all.
Did you check your car?
I almost dismantled it,
I swear it isn't there.
Did you look thoroughly?
Look, it's not in my house.
It's not in my car.
And the more I think about it,
there's no way
it fell out in my locker.
Do you get it?
That cigar with the poison
must be on the street.
What if a kid finds it?
Some innocent person
could die because of me.
No, that is a strange
possibility.
Yes, but it's still
a possibility.
Listen, Jose,
stop thinking that.
You're being paranoid.
What if some kid
dies because of me?
I would kill myself,
I couldn't stand it.
Jose, Jose...
Take a deep breath.
Relax.
This is what we're going
to do.
Jose, do you hear me?
Yes, yes.
I'm going to come
over there, okay?
And we're going
to look
for it. Right?
Yes, please.
I'll be there in half
an hour.
Okay, thanks.
I'll wait for you.
What's up?
Shit, I can't find it.
What am I going to do?
Jose, how do you clean
your house?
I mean, do you have
a vacuum cleaner?
Yes, I have one,
and I have already checked it.
When was the last time
you checked it?
I don't know,
last week.
Do you have somebody
that helps you cleaning?
Yes, some lady
comes on Wednesday.
That means that the last
time
she came here
was three days ago?
Here it is, damn it!
- Is that it?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Take it. Careful.
Is it intact?
- I think so.
- Didn't it break?
- Let's see.
- Here it is.
Let me see.
Good.
Good!
Problem solved.
Let me get rid of this.
What a luck.
It's like taking a piano
off my shoulders.
I tell you, Jose.
Do you want some beer?
Jose...
Jose, what's wrong?
I almost killed you...
No, man, no.
- I almost shot you--
- No.
No, Jose, Jose, Jose,
it was a misunderstanding.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
Don't say that.
I don't know
how I could be so stupid.
Jose, it's over.
I'm really sorry.
You don't have to be.
What happened,
happened for the best,
you hear me?
I wouldn't change a thing.
This was for the best.
You and me having
each other's back.
Working together.
This had to be like this.
This saved our lives.
I need you to understand that.
I want you to think about that
as we go forward.
Go forward where?
Thanks for coming
to this meeting, Mario.
I'll cut to the chase.
We asked you to come
here today because...
We're here to talk partnership.
- Thanks.
Partnership?
we figure we're going to start
cooking again.
Why not?
It would be an equal society.
You, Jose and me.
We have a good product, Mario,
there's a market to be filled.
A lot of money
to be made.
All of it.
The tasks would be
clearly divided.
Jose and I, we cook,
that's what we do,
but there's still
distribution, support,
logistics, that sort of thing.
I'll give you an example.
We'll need a steady supply
of methylamine.
With your experience
and connections,
you would be a great help.
Granted, there's
a lot of work ahead.
There's a lot of rebuilding.
And, no doubt, our profits
will be smaller.
At least at first.
But each of us will receive
a larger cut.
Owners, not employees.
Thanks, but no, thanks.
Mario, I know
you don't care for me.
We've had our issues.
I would suggest
that you leave emotion
out of this decision.
Walter, you are trouble.
I'm sorry Jose here
doesn't see it.
You are a time bomb.
Tick, tick, ticking,
and I have no intention
of being around for the
boom.
I'm going to give you
some piece of advise.
Seep on it.
Don't answer now.
Don't forget
this is a great opportunity
for you.
This is a big business.
However,
Jose and I are pressing on.
You know where to find us.
Welcome, buddy!
- Hi, Gómez!
- How are you?
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you upstairs?
I came to see
if you needed any help.
If you wanted something.
No, I'm good.
I can do it alone.
Do you know
what I need?
Don't you have the phone
of one of those masseuses
you use to visit?
Brother, it's good
to see you walking.
Yes, little by little.
Not exactly running
marathons.
When have you run one?
Unless it was for the beer.
Let's see.
You know what?
I'm proud of you, brother.
Homosexuality behind,
are they here already?
You should see their cars
and their assistants.
- All of them have one?
- All of them.
Let's do something.
We're going to go there
and you'll be my
assistant.
- What?
- Hold my arm.
But don't caress me,
brother.
Are you of those
who like to caress?
Look at
that.
Claudita, how are you?
Mr. Antonio, I hired
Manolo Bisbal in 1992.
Almost single-handedly,
he grew up a little
restaurant division
into an industry leader
and a source of great
personal pride.
I am shocked and saddened
by his death
and the circumstances of it,
but also outraged
by the damage his actions
have brought
upon my grand-father's company.
Alleged actions.
No more lies.
An innocent man
does not kill himself.
My people and I
are here to help.
We'll help you in anything
you need for this investigation.
Through your investigation
I pledge Madrigal's full
cooperation and transparency,
not only
at an international level,
but also
in the Colombian branch,
represented in this table
by Lidia Barrera,
the logistics'
director in Latin America.
Thank you very much,
Mr. Kristoff.
I confess I have
my selfish reasons.
On the one hand,
I don't want that
the international attention
this case has drawn
affects our image
in the Latin American market,
one of our favorites.
But, on the other hand,
I want to prove
that Manolo Bisbal
was a lone anomaly.
But if that is not the case,
I want to know it, Mr. Antonio,
who is involved too.
just as you do.
Do you like it?
And this one?
I'm leaving, dad.
- Aren't you eating all of it?
- No, I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Bye, baby.
Say bye to mom.
Yes, I'll tell her.
- Have a good day.
- Same to you, dad.
Have a good day.
Could you wait here for me?
I'll be right back.
Cielo...
Cielo, get up.
The car wash will open
in 15 minutes.
I told Mariano he can open it.
You have to get up anyway.
Come, the shower is delicious.
Come on.
Come on, get up.
Boss, thanks a lot
for the whisky.
So when are you going
to announce it?
As I'm walking out the door
with my big cardboard box.
You know damn well
we're going to throw you
a big party.
Henry, I want to congratulate
you for you great work
in the investigation
of Gustavo Cortés.
I blame myself every day
for not listening to you.
It's not right,
them putting this on you.
Tell me one thing.
What was that giant magnet
in the evidence room?
It seems that they were going
for all the information
in the personal laptop
of Gustavo Cortés.
Anything left of the laptop?
They erased it all.
Let me get it straight, Henry:
Héctor Salamanca
killed Gustavo Cortés,
but who gave him the bomb?
Whole lot of questions
and not much in the way
of answers.
They are checking
his bank accounts
to see if any name pops out,
any data, any hint.
Unbelievable!
I had him out to my house.
We cooked out in the backyard.
And he's somebody else
completely.
I can't imagine
how you feel about that.
Being betrayed like that?
Not even to my worst enemy.
Hi, what can I get you?
Just tea,
please.
Chamomile.
We don't have chamomile tea.
Then some sort of bergamot,
but not Earl Grey.
What?
I like soy milk
instead of dairy.
We work with dairy milk.
Hard.
Do you have skimmed milk?
No, just dairy milk.
Let's do this.
I want a cup of tea,
but with filtered water.
Do you have stevia?
Never mind. I brought my
own.
Lidia.
Are you coming to me
or am I coming to you?
We'll talk like this.
I'm coming.
Relax.
Take a breath, will you?
This place is safe.
No one's going to see
you here.
Alberto, what a coincidence!
How did I not see you
sitting back there?
A friend of mine,
I just met him.
Mario, do you want
anything else?
No, darling. Thanks.
Okay, let's do
something.
Take that shawl off
your head,
and that sunglasses also
because you're only
drawing the attention.
Good.
Breathe in, breathe out.
Very good.
Drink your whatever.
Who killed Gustavo?
Haven't I told you
not to worry about that?
Let's cut to the chase.
Why did you call me?
What is so important?
What is this?
A list of 11 names.
You know them all.
I do.
So what with them?
Those men know us, Mario.
They can hurt us.
What?
No specific.
I'm just pointing out facts.
These men were on the payroll,
very publicly.
They trace back to Pollos
and the laundry.
They trace back to Madrigal,
and then to us,
because they're going to talk.
They're going to blame us.
What can we do
to erase them from the list?
Do you understand me?
And I'm not saying all of them.
But there's always
a weak link somewhere.
These are the 11 I know of,
but I'd love your input.
I never met your chemist,
for instance.
I don't know who he is.
I'd love your input.
You want me to kill every
man
on that list?
Do you think we should?
You're scared, right?
Yes, of course.
You're very upset,
which I'm going to
factor
into my response here.
These are my guys,
and they are solid.
I trust them.
- Got it?
- Are you sure?
What about Carlitos,
at the warehouse?
Didn't one time you have
to shoot him through the hand?
You think that didn't
stick
in his memory?
What about Jairo,
the one with the nickname
"Paleta",
at the laundry?
They're sure to pick him up.
They already have. Last night.
I tell you again.
My guys are solid.
I vetted them with great
care,
and Gustavo made sure
they were well compensated
in the event of a situation
such as this.
They're paid
to keep their mouths shut.
And they will.
How can we be so sure?
I don't know what kind of
movies you've been
watching,
but here in the real
world
we don't kill 11
people
as some kind of
prophylactic measure.
First, because that's not
good.
Besides, that's not
a good strategy
if you don't want
to draw the attention.
Got it?
Yes, I got it.
Good.
So we're off
that very silly idea?
Yes, sir.
Good.
My treat.
Next time, drink coffee.
We drink coffee
here.
Drink tea
when you're in England.
Good morning, lady.
I'm looking for
detective Henry.
No, no, no--
Hi, Carlitos!
How's everything?
Mario, they talked to
me,
but I
don't--
You can't smoke in here.
Careful with that, Carlitos.
Go walk.
Yes.
Mrs., detective Henry, please.
Mario, have a seat,
please.
Thanks.
I can call you Mario, right?
Yes, that's my name.
Good.
Are you waiving your right
to have an attorney present?
Yes, I don't think
it's necessary.
Could you state that
to the camera, please?
I'm waiving my right
to have an attorney
present
in this conversation.
Thank you.
We just have a few questions.
Okay.
You're currently employed
by the Pollos Hermanos chain.
Yes, sir.
And what do you do there?
Corporate security.
Corporate security?
And what do you do
in a place like that?
Do you avoid the food
flies away?
I conduct employees
background checks,
I oversee loss prevention.
And that's a full-time job?
We have 14 locations.
So, yes, it's a
full-time job.
Yeah, well, if I were you,
I'd start sending out
those resumes.
They aren't valuing your work.
It says here you're
a private investigator?
Where you licensed?
Bogotá, but I can operate
in all the country.
Are you licensed
to carry a firearm?
Yes, I am.
Mario, if we take a look
at your bank accounts,
will you have
everything in order?
I'm guessing you've
already done that,
so you tell me.
Don't you see his face
a little bit familiar?
Am I right?
Here it says that you are
a former cop.
Were you a cop?
Yes, sir. Ten years.
Ten years.
We know that your tenure
as a police officer
ended dramatically.
Tell me all about that.
I prefer not to,
if it's not necessary.
Yes, you're right.
You're right, Mario.
I'm more interested
in other kind of subjects.
For instance,
why Gustavo Cortés decided
to put a guy like you
in charge
of his corporate security.
I can't imagine you
investigating the background
of the employees.
Right?
You're not that kind of guy.
You have another profile, Mario.
You have an action guy profile,
in the streets.
With due respect,
you're like those guys
who get their hands dirty.
I believe Gustavo Cortés
hired you as security head,
but in his drugs society.
He must've needed help
running that drug empire of his.
First I'm hearing
about that.
I don't know
anything about that.
No, no, no, Mario,
not to us.
We have a guy that could put you
in that underground lab,
and he'll testify to it.
Do you remember?
So from here on out,
this can go hard or easy,
so what's it going to be?
If you have
something
against me,
you can handcuff me.
Please, I want to know
because I don't
understand.
Am I under arrest?
Please, state that
for the camera.
No, you're not under arrest.
Currently.
Do you have
any more questions for
me?
Because you've got me
very stirred up with all these
false accusations.
I'm not young.
If I'm not under
arrest,
I'd prefer to leave.
Yes, you can leave.
Excuse me.
Although we could talk
about the two million dollars
in your
granddaughter's name
in some Cayman
islands bank.
I seems Gustavo Cortés
had all these
secret
offshore bank
accounts
in those tax heavens.
And they're all in the names
of certain people
on his payroll.
People he trusted.
He gave money to them.
The manager of the laundry
has a bank account,
the distribution manager
of Los Pollos Hermanos,
Carlitos, the one
from...
The owner of a
chemical warehouse.
All of them have an account.
And the strangest
thing
is that, in this list
of people,
your granddaughter pops out.
I don't get it,
among those men.
Do you understand?
And it's also strange
that she has more money
than anybody else.
So my partner here
"No, no, this is really
weird".
- Right?
- A girl?
This girl is doing
all this stuff?
No, no, no.
A little criminal girl.
So I said:
"No, no, wait a minute.
Slow down, partner".
"Are you crazy",
I told him.
"Are you crazy?"
"Why are you blaming
the little girl?"
So suddenly I realized
that maybe it was
from her dear old granddaddy.
What do you say?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Lucky for you, Mario,
because I'm telling one
thing.
That money was
seized
by anti-narcotics.
Two million dollars.
I can't believe it.
I would go crazy.
Right?
Okay, but let's see
the context here.
Mario didn't touch that money.
He didn't even smell it.
So you are not guilty.
The ones that are guilty
are the other men
on the list,
who have used the money
and they're in a big problem.
Here's the thing,
Mario.
One of your guys is
going to roll on you,
and then we'll
definitely handcuff
you.
Okay, but before that happens,
you can help us
and we can help you.
Do you understand?
You can tell us what you know,
for instance,
you can tell us
who's still out there
and we don't know about.
Tell us this story,
Mario.
You cooperate, we help you.
Your granddaughter might be able
to keep some of that money.
It's in her name, right?
Everybody loves
this kind of deal.
So what do you say?
I don't know anything
about any money.
Excuse me.
First order of business
is to find a new place to cook.
Before anyone says it,
no more RV's.
No more buses.
- Nothing like that.
- Wait a minute.
The crystal ship
did pretty good for us.
- "The crystal ship"?
- Yes.
Who called it that?
I did.
When? I never heard you.
I said it to myself.
It's a cute and suitable
name,
at least for me.
"Cute".
Okay, all right.
I'll admit it held us on
as a starter lab.
- Well...
- But it's too small.
Too dark.
We need something
much better, Saúl.
Someplace safe from prying eyes.
Saúl, no, no.
Before you ask,
I tell you I don't want
your amusement park
you are trying to sell us.
No!
Security against detection
is paramount.
Someplace that doesn't
attract the attention.
No jungle, no mountains,
nothing like a cocaine lab.
That's too complicated.
In town is trickier.
I mean, you got a lot more
of your prying eyes.
If Gustavo can manage it,
then so can we.
Materials.
Where are we with that?
Good.
Except methylamine.
No surprise.
I think our best
option
is to switch back
to a pseudo cook,
like in the old times.
No, no old times!
We're not lowering the level.
And what do we do?
We get it. There is methylamine
out there.
- Where?
- Jose, have faith.
Can I offer a thought?
Thanks.
Let's think about this:
Say a guy wins the lottery.
Ten million bucks.
The biggest prize.
The very next day, what's
the one thing he does not do?
What?
He does not go buy
another lottery ticket.
He counts his lucky stars
and sails off into the sunset,
which, seems to me, some advice
you two might take.
Saúl, tell me,
what lottery did I win exactly?
You're alive, Walter!
After all that has happened,
you are alive,
and that's the biggest prize.
I'm alive, and I'm broke.
I owe Jose the money
he gave me
to do the magnet thing,
and I have other debts.
And you're asking me
to stop right now?
Saúl, there is gold
in the streets,
just waiting for someone
to come and scoop it up.
And you think this is
the right time to stop?
Are you also asking Jose
to quit right now?
No, that's not going to happen.
Again.
Wait a minute,
darling.
What's up, Carlitos?
Mario, can you talk?
One moment.
Yes.
The anti-narcotics agents
called me again.
They want to interrogate me.
- Did you talk to your lawyer?
- Yes, of course.
But these people
and the Colombian police
took all my money.
I have nothing left.
What do you
want me
to do about
it?
I don't know.
We have to talk.
Not on the phone.
Can you come to my house?
Give me two hours.
Okay.
Cristian, give me your weapon.
Slowly.
Right.
Come on over, let's talk.
Have a seat.
Carlitos.
How much was Lidia
going to pay you?
Ten thousand a name.
How far did you get
down the list?
Just Carlitos.
For you, she was
going to pay 30.000.
I'm very sorry about this,
Mario.
But I needed the money.
The police and
anti-narcotics
took it all, man.
I know.
Are you ready?
Mario, let me explain,
please...
Lucy!
Luciana, come
and have some cookies.
Come
down.
I'm coming, mom.
Go.
Do not
speak.
Don't hurt my daughter,
please.
If you stay silent,
she's going to be fine.
Do you know why I'm
here?
If you have anything to
say
to me, now's the time.
Two good men died
because of you.
Don't shoot me in the face.
I don't want my daughter
seeing me like that.
Your daughter won't
see you.
Nobody is going to find you,
Lidia.
What? No.
No, no, no, Mario,
I'm a single mother.
- Lower your voice.
- She has to find me.
Do you want her
finding your body?
No, I can't disappear.
She has to know
I didn't leave her.
what happened to her mother.
Keep your voice down.
I'll scream
and I'll keep screaming.
My daughter's not thinking
I abandoned her!
You have to promise, Mario.
You have to promise me
I won't disappear.
Can you still get your hands
on methylamine?
Focus, Lidia,
I asked you a question.
Methylamine.
Maybe. Why?
Hello.
You still plan
to move forward?
Yes, why?
I've reconsidered.
I'm in.
Good.
Go with your kid.
And don't forget the
cookies.
Lucy, come here, honey.
Come with mom.
Were you
sleeping?
Well, you missed a good
meal.
The lasagna came out
very well,.
I wrapped some up for
you
if you'd like some
later.
You know, it gets easier.
I promise
you that it
does.
What you're feeling right
now
about Ernesto
and about what
happened...
Everything. It'll pass.
We don't have to be
worried
about anything
because we do what we do
for a very good reason.
There's no better
reason
than family.