Good morning! Good morning.
For those of you not
with us this morning,
and for those who came in late,
this man is Tuco Salamanca.
With Mr. Gómez here,
we've been performing
a raid in his headquarters.
Also his last known
address. Even his girl's house,
His meth hag girlfriend. Right,
Gómez?
He fell in love.
He likes them skinny to
be able to suck their bones.
We netted a bunch
of Tuco's lieutenants.
The big man himself smelled us coming,
so he fled.
So get a big old raging hard-on
at the idea of catching
this piece of shit.
Alright? I need you to bring
me Tuco Salamanca here!
To all the ladies here,
I apologize
for the ideas I just suggested,
but I need you to get excited
with the idea of bringing
me Tuco Salamanca.
Use whatever image turns you on,
okay?
So let's talk for bit
about Tuco Salamanca:
Mexican citizen,
been living in Colombia for five years now.
he supplies products for
almost all Mexican cartels,
and he's currently head of the
rising methamphetamine cartel.
Please.
One thing we must know
about Tuco Salamanca:
he's a psycho. He gets mad at you,
you're dead.
Although we have no evidence,
we know he's involved
in the missing case
and death of our informant,
Mr. Molina, aka "El Loco".
So let's have a moment
for our favorite spy.
May an eternal light shine on him. Right,
so much for that.
Which brings us
to the good news.
After much digging and digging,
we finally got some actual
evidence against Tuco Salamanca.
This man here is No Doze.
His body was found
right next to Gonzo's.
These two are Tuco
Salamanca's henchmen.
They were found at a container
storage. So what happened there?
Gonzo, this rocket scientist,
was moving No Doze's body.
Either hiding it there or pulling it out,
still not sure.
He got his arm crushed clean
off after something fell over him.
The guy was trapped and lost
blood to death next to his friend.
Anyone want to see the photos,
they're on my web site.
Hilarious.
Okay,
but don't you get sad. Easy now.
After every massage
there's a happy ending.
- Gómez.
- Happy ending!
Mr. Tuco's fingerprints are here,
on No Doze's.
This evidence is more than
enough to hunt him down.
Anyway.
I ask you,
do you want to find Tuco Salamanca?
- Yes, sir.
Did you hear flies?
We need the fumigator over here.
Alright! Will you bring
me Tuco Salamanca?
- Yes, sir!Yes, sir!
- I can't hear you!
- Louder!
- Yes, sir!
- Will you bring him in?
- I can't hear you!
- Yes, sir!
- Louder, come on!
Do you think we'll catch him?
No way we're getting that dude.
He must be tucked in
Mexico having chilaquiles.
So what was all that fuss about?
Hey, it's all about motivation.
Gómez, I need a favor. Can
you cover for me this afternoon?
I've got to take
some personal time.
What?
Are you getting implants,
rays and all that shit?
Did you make up your mind,
Henry?
I'm all in for that.
You have my support.
Come on now,
enough. This is serious.
Walter, my brother-in-law,
is missing,
and Cielo asked me to
look for him personally.
Wow! Maybe Walter...
Okay,
I hope it's nothing serious, man.
Okay. Thanks for this.
Holler if you need me.
This is the most recent photo. That's
what he looks like now. Without the hair.
Ramón.
What's up?
Thanks a lot, man.
Ramón is coming
with us on his day off.
No worries. This is family.
Right.
I've been looking in the car
and there's nothing strange.
Ma'am,
what about Mr. Blanco's height and weight?
Five eleven...
About 170.
Now he weighs a little less.
He's thinner.
What about other distinguishing
features? Tattoos or moles...
No, not really.
Any threat that you know of?
Threat?
No.
Is that the list of medications?
Yes,
and confirmed by the doctor.
Has he been depressed lately?
- Depressed?
- Yes.
What do you mean?
It's very important to know
if he's been depressed.
Kind of.
No, he wasn't depressed.
We could say he was a bit...
Not as joyful.
But yesterday he
was particularly...
He was agitated. In a bad mood.
In a bad mood in general
or because of something?
When I asked him what was wrong
he said "I don't
know where to begin."
But there was
something going on.
We were talking upstairs.
I was finishing a session
of meditation exercises,
and then five or six
minutes later he was gone.
Nothing else missing
in the house? His or...?
I think he only took his keys,
his cell phone...
His wallet.
Do you think this was robbery,
extortion or something like that?
We can't jump to
conclusions just yet,
but we can't rule out
any options either.
Right,
but if it was robbery or extortion,
he could have appeared by now,
couldn't he?
And the call? What happened?
I'm looking into
it. I'm on that...
Much paperwork
and forms to fill out.
While we were talking, he got a
call on his cell and didn't answer.
And then he left.
- Could that be a clue?
- Yes, it is.
Anything else you'd
like to mention?
No... I called
to find out about
the credit card,
and there's been
no recent activity.
There's a little money in the
savings account, nothing missing.
That's why I don't
think it's a robbery.
I checked with every hospital,
every clinic every morgue.
I was actually hoping that
you had something else.
Being that you're
the experts in this.
I really don't feel
you're helping me at all!
Cielo...
I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to be rude.
Don't worry.
Gives us plenty
material to work on.
Nice to meet you.
I really appreciate this.
Take care, sir.
I'll walk you to the door.
Ramón,
the phone call Cielo mentioned...
What about it?
I looked into it.
There's no record
that the call existed.
Second cell phone.
Okay. Ramón, thanks again.
God damn it!
Don't worry, I understand.
Get out.
Come on!
So there was
the little lovebird!
Get away from
me! Don't touch me!
Calm down, little girl!
You going to shoot
me? Shoot me in here!
I hope I bleed like a mother,
too!
What a retard. It's your ride,
I ain't got to clean jack.
Now get out!
Get up!
Don't do it, Tuco! Please,
don't do it! Please.
Please.
Let's go up there.
Go on, you little bitches!
Inside, inside!
No more signs.
Junior is getting more printed.
Relax, Cielo,
he'll be fine. He'll show up.
Thanks
Okay, the whole tiara thing,
I thought it was
- the most gorgeous thing ever.
- María.
I can't believe you
actually wanted to return it.
¡María!
I stepped into this place
and it looked beautiful,
I thought it was
the perfect gift
Maria, please, not now! Please.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Empty your pockets, fuckers.
So Heisenberg is actually
called Walter Blanco.
Walter Blanco...
- Heisenberg is an alias.
- What?
It's a business name.
Don't we all have one of those?
...! There!
I like doing business
with a family man.
Look, uncle.
This is sweet!
You must use these with guys,
you faggot.
Don't you?
Can I trust you? Tell me!
Yes, absolutely.
Because this is about trust,
- about faith in the other.
- Right.
Get your stuff.
The police raided on my things.
And now they're looking for
me in every corner of the planet.
Why could that be?
Maybe you're the spies?
- No.
Picked up my whole crew,
except Gonzo.
Except Gonzo,
uncle. Isn't that weird?
Weird...
I mean it's unusual.
Hey, unusual.
That's a fancy word.
Heisenberg likes fancy words,
uncle.
I've been trying to locate
Gonzo for two days now,
but he won't answer my calls.
He's been acting all pouty
on account of No Doze.
As if we all weren't
meant to die one day!
As if I were to blame that the
asshole didn't know how to behave!
I saw this coming. I can see the future,
you know?
I knew last night they
were going to come
and that Gonzo
was going to talk.
I'm sure he's the one
who snitched to the cops!
That lousy son of a bitch!
I trusted him like a brother!
I see Gonzo,
I'm going to gut him,
make myself a whip and
hit myself on the back.
That way I finally
learn the lesson
that you can never trust
the people you love, ever!
Love is no guarantee!
Tuco, I'm really sorry that
Gonzo ended up being a traitor.
I truly am sorry.
I'd waste him, too.
- Shut up, you idiot.
- Yes, sir.
I need powder, I need something!
This smells like rotten cheese.
No, man. It's killer. Seriously.
Heisenberg...
I've been thinking.
Mexico's the answer.
- Mexico?
- Right, fucker, Mexico!
Or don't you like Mexico?
No, I do, it's just that...
- Have you ever been there?
- No.
So how in the hell do
you know you don't like it?
Everyone should go to Mexico!
I went to Mexico once, to Cancun
with my family. That was some place.
Shut up,
asshole! Cancun is not even Mexico.
Look, Heisenberg.
Mexico has the
prettiest landscape.
And the food... Isn't the
food the best ever, uncle?
And we have culture, music...
Maybe the ladies aren't as hot
as they are here, but they're tamed.
And the capital city.
You know what's in D.F.?
A bunch of stuff,
loads! Anything you want!
Never been there, but they say
in D.F. you can get anything at all.
We know what to
do with meth there.
We'll set you up in a super lab.
We'll do nothing but cook 24-7.
Every week,
all year. Nobody will mess with us
because I got my people there.
We're going to make beaucoup bucks,
Heisenberg. The lottery!
Tuco, I have a wife and kids.
So what? You'll get another one.
You just don't like Mexico,
that's all.
I do like it,
but I can't just
uproot my life like that.
- Neither can I.
- Who the fuck is talking to you?
- Who? Who?
- No, no, no, man,
calm down, calm down.
You need me,
I have knowledge too.
I cooked that
scante in your pocket.
It smells like that
because of the chemicals.
But you've never tried
nothing like it. It's like...
One bump,
you'll be flying high for days.
It's a new product him and I have
been working up, with a secret ingredient.
What's the secret ingredient?
Coffee.
I don't like coffee.
It makes my heart pound hard.
Don't make anything new.
This blue magic
is worth everything.
All right! Time to
burst the piñata!
No!
No, don't do it,
Tuco! Please, don't do it.
He's my partner.
I need him.
And if he doesn't go,
I don't go.
I'll tell you this,
little fucker.
My cousins are driving
up here right now
to smuggle us back down.
And you're coming with me,
or you're dead!
Bam!
Say your prayers, boy,
that there be a
place for you to come.
Mom, I'll be right back.
I'll give out these flyers.
- I'm coming with you.
- No, mom.
Relax. I'll go alone.
Cielo, easy,
you have to rest. Stay.
Call me if anything shows up.
I'll be fine.
You have a passenger
inside. You should rest.
Actually, I think the very fact they
haven't found Walter yet bodes well.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean,
if he... You know....
Somebody would've
smelled something by now.
What?
Henry...
There's got to be something
that we haven't picked up.
Some detail we just missed.
What about Walter's
second cell phone?
- María! What the hell?
- What?
We can't just ignore
a potential clue.
She should know
this. Tell Cielo.
What are you talking about?
I'm not telling her.
- Can you explain yourself?
- Nothing, that the call
Walter got before going missing,
that's what we're talking about.
Right, what about it?
Well,
I went to the phone company,
and in Walter's log
there were no incoming
or dropped calls.
- I heard it.
- Right.
His phone rang. I heard it,
I swear.
I know, I know you did.
The only logical
explanation there is for this
is that Walter must
have a second phone.
What for?
No. What sense would there
be in that? Another phone?
Look, I...
I'm not here to argue with you,
if it makes sense or not...
No, no, no. You can't just
bring up "second cell phone"
and then drop it.
What does it mean?
No, I mean... Maybe Walter...
- You know? That...
- No, I don't know.
We all have secrets. María
has secrets. We all do...
I can't believe
you're saying this.
I can believe it. Why not?
How long has Walter kept
the whole cancer thing?
Okay...
Let's assume there's second cell phone. So,
what?
Is he having an affair?
Walter? Please. A lover.
I'm thinking marijuana.
- Walter doesn't smoke that anymore.
- Really?
Why? Because he told
you and you believed him?
Chemotherapy and marijuana
go together like siblings.
Maybe he's addicted to the pot,
and he owes his drug
dealer a lot of money.
María,
you don't get hooked on pot like that.
You don't? How do you know?
You didn't even know he
had a second cell phone.
Henry,
what you should do is question
this pot drug dealer person
that has Walter into this.
Wait,
we're rumbling around too much here.
- No, no, what we want--
- I agree with you.
But we're making
progress. That's something.
No sugar, thank you.
Mrs. Sofía,
thank you so much for speaking to me.
It's been very hard
to take in this visit.
Last time I spoke to my
son things didn't end up well,
so anything having to
do with him bitters me.
Do you have children,
Mr. Navarro?
No, no children. I have a nephew,
he's like a son to me.
So I kind of know the feeling.
It's like anything else in the world,
completely different...
Especially, when it comes to
a young man like José Miguel.
He was a very problematic child,
and I'm the one to
blame for most of that.
I think we parents
raise up to a point,
and then it's up to the person
what to do with their life.
Right,
but the problem is I overprotected my son.
We was a very sensitive child,
not much disciplined.
That caused problems with his father,
and...
then came all the rest: the drugs,
the lies,
the problems... So we
ended up isolating him.
I'm here for a rather
personal matter
It's about Walter Blanco,
my brother-in-law.
Does the name sound
familiar? Walter Blanco?
He taught José Miguel
chemistry at Los Monarcas.
Professor Blanco! Yes,
of course I remember him.
He helped José Miguel so
much. He saw potential in him.
Did something happen to him?
He's missing,
actually. I'm trying to gather leads.
To see if I can find him.
So are you accusing José Miguel
of something? Is this his fault or...?
No, no, no,
calm down. Like I say...
This is out of the police,
this is a personal matter.
Do you know if José
Miguel and Walter
were in touch lately?
Do you know about that?
I have no idea.
No? Because I
have a number here.
Is this José Miguel's number?
Aha, it is.
I'm calling, and nobody answers.
I'm sorry,
but I can't help you. I...
I haven't spoken with
my son for about a month,
and I don't think I'll
be talking to him soon.
We had an argument
and haven't spoken ever since.
I understand.
Just one more question.
Does he still have the same car?
Yes...
I could never
get him to sell it.
Hello. What's up, Gómez?
How's it going?
It's fine, dude. Listen,
I need a favor.
I need you to take
down this plate.
Okay, it's FJA 319.
It's under José Miguel Rosas.
Let me know if it has a
satellite anti-theft system, okay?
If it does,
locate that car for me, will you?
Yes, yes,
I owe you one more, buddy.
Easy,
I'll but you beer one of these days.
Thanks, bye.
Coffee? The secret ingredient?
How many times did I
tell you that's just stupid?
But it almost worked.
At least I tried.
But your idea of leaving the
gun in the house is better?
No, right,
I absolutely was expecting
for you to come to
my house with Tuco.
At least he wants you alive.
Apparently linked to Mexican
drug dealer Tuco Salamanca.
The dead bodies of
these two gang members
were found at a container
storage in the outskirts of the city.
Authorities have not
confirmed their identities yet,
but alternative sources
have informed us
that they are apparently Gonzalo Cañas,
aka Gon--
If Gonzo's dead and Tuco didn't kill him,
what the fuck happened?
I don't know.
But that's the least
of my worries now.
If he finds out that Gonzo is
dead and not a police informant,
who does he automatically blame?
Ha!
We need a plan now.
Let's just bum-rush him, man.
You crack him over
the head with something,
and I'll go for his gun.
Right,
something like what? The cactus?
I don't know, take a shot.
You're as good as
checked out already.
You should be, like,
all sacrificial for future generations.
So my life is not
a priority here
because I'm going to
be dead soon anyway.
Thanks a lot.
Well, yes.
We got to get him to take this.
He doesn't like much
the taste of coffee.
So unless you can convince
him to booty bump eat.
Let's have lunch, uncle.
Okay.
Eat, it's a long trip!
Come on, you fucktards!
I'll go get chilies, uncle.
Start eating! You're looking a little weak,
Heisenberg.
I don't want you to go
belly up before we get there.
Calm down,
uncle. I told you already.
I will feed you. I eat
first. That's the deal.
What is it, Héctor?
I get it,
I get it. You greedy old bastard.
You want the big one, don't you?
These old people...
They don't care if
you buy them a house,
treat them well, care for them,
feed them. They
always want your share.
They never had anything.
Eat up, uncle.
Why did you do that?
You don't waste food.
Okay.
You don't waste food, uncle.
Hey, hey, hey!
That fucking cow didn't
know where it came from!
She's as good as a steak.
What is it, uncle?
Don't tell me you're hungry.
What is it?
What's up with them?
You don't like them?
One bell means "yes".
He doesn't like you.
Why don't you like them uncle?
You don't trust them?
Why don't you trust them?
No, no, Tuco, come on,
your uncle's not fir to make any--
Shush.
Did they do something to you?
- What did you do to my uncle?
- Nothing.
Bullshit! My uncle does not lie!
I swear we didn't
do anything to him!
Maybe,
I did change the channel on his TV.
But that's it. I didn't
know he'd get pissed.
Right! He was watching the soap,
and this dude
changed the channel.
- See? I told you not to!
- Stop!
Is that true, uncle?
Did they change the
three-o'-clock soap?
Or are they laughing
at me and lying as hell?
No, no, no!
Tuco!
Leave him!
Hold it there, bastard!
Leave him alone!
Move, you motherfucker! Go on!
Don't kill me!
Don't kill me,
please don't kill me.
What were you going to do?
What the fuck were
you going to do?
Poison you! We tried to poison you,
because you're an insane,
degenerate piece of shit!
How does it feel now?
Who's the bitch now?
How does it feel?
Leave him! Let him bleed.
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Man, the keys.
Tuco has them.
His cousins!
Ha...
- What the hell's going on?
- I don't know.
José Miguel Rosas?
You're a hard man to find.
Stand still...
Stand still!
Fuck me!
- It's Henry!
- Who's Henry?
- Henry, damn it!
- Who the fuck is Henry?
- Move!
- What are you...?