Come on, cutie pie!
Come on, beautiful!
Come on, please!
Hi, Jose.
What?
No, I don't get a word.
Jose, hey, come on.
Just take a deep breath.
And now tell me what happened.
Mmh.
No, no, no, no,
calm dow, please,
now, calm down.
Listen to me.
Jose, Jose,
are you listening?
Look, calm down,
everything will be just fine.
I promise.
No, no, no, no,
you stay right there!
Don't you move!
I'm making a call right now.
Jose.
Easy, please.
Trust me. I'll deal with it.
Saúl Bueno sent me.
Come on
in.
Where is she?
Here's your story:
I woke up, I
found her.
That's all I know.
Come on, say it, say it!
it.
- I woke up...
- I found her...
- That's all I know.
Say it again.
I woke up...
I found her...
- And that's all I know.
All over again.
I woke up...
I found her...
And that's all I know.
I woke up...
I found her,
and that's all I know.
Once you make the
call,
the police will come
up
with the
Forensic
Department.
You have to talk to
them.
There's nothing
incriminating you
here,
so I don't think
you'll be
arrested.
They'll piss you off a
little,
since you're the last
person
to have seen her
alive.
Easy now.
If they take you,
don't say a word.
You have a lawyer.
Call Saúl Bueno.
And do I need
to state the obvious?
I was never here.
You put on a long-sleeved
shirt
or a sweater,
and cover those track
marks
on your arms.
Make
that
call.
But first count down
from 20.
Come on, cheer up,
it'll soon be finished.
You're in the home
stretch.
Junior!
Junior, it's served!
Morgan.
What?
Remember he likes
to be called Morgan now.
Morgan!
Coming!
Are you okay?
- Humph.
- Humph?
Yeah, fine.
Dad, mom, come
here!
You have to see this!
You won't believe
it!
What is it, honey?
Look!
Are those donations?
- Yeah.
All this is for your dad?
Yes, mommy, look.
They've already given us
750,000.
No!
Look, and they've written
from all over the country:
Cali, Medellín...
Even a couple of letters
from America.
Look, there's a message here.
"Hang in there, Walter,
you can do it,
you've a friend in me".
"Walter, I went through
the same thing,
have faith".
Isn't this awesome?
Yes, it's
unbelievable.
Junior, really,
thank you very much
for your help.
This is a big, big help.
Hi, this is Juana,
right now I can't
or I don't want to talk to
you.
Leave me a
message
and I'll decide
if I want or can
talk to you. Bye.
Juana, it's your dad,
I knew you wouldn't
be answering.
Look, I need you
to have your bag packed,
wait by the porch,
'cause I'm on my way.
You're going to rehab today,
Juana María, please, okay?
I just woke up, and I found her.
That's all I know.
What's your date of birth?
It's July, 4th.
July 4th, 1988.
I need the mother's maiden name
and her address, please.
- My mother's?
- No, sir,
your daughter's mother.
Cecilia López.
Where's she from?
She was born here,
but...
she's been long living
in America.
We need to take the body
to the Forensic Department
to perform the autopsy.
Look, here's the address.
Do you have someone
who can drive you?
Yes, I have a car,
no worries.
Well, we'll be completing
the intake
and taking samples there.
You're also coming with us.
Come on.
Look, mom, another 30,000!
Walter!
Jose, it's me.
Er...
Well, no, I just...
wanted to know
how you're doing.
Our friend says
they've let you go
and everything went well.
That's good.
Er...
Okay, I don't know...
Just call me when you can.
I'd like to talk to you.
he's a good man,
a good person.
Thing is, right now
he has a disease.
I've been talking
to the doctor,
he says...
this operation
is a real chance for
him.
But this thing
will cost him
an arm and a leg.
So I need you all
to stick your hands
into your considerings
and think.
No, wait,
into your pockets.
Take out a big note
and make a donation.
It's for a good
cause, okay?
One last
thing...
The biggest
donation...
gets our last
Henry Special,
limited edition.
I've a question.
That also comes
with the purgative formula
you gave us last time?
Or does this one come
with the cane and all?
You're the ones missing
it,
no, they don't have...
Well, well,
that's for you, bro.
People really
appreciate
a high-quality
product, bro.
Alright, let's see,
what's in for today?
Juan Carlos
Ortega,
aka Gordo.
A month ago,
this chubby guy
was shot dead.
So today,
he's part
of our death bowl.
You may wonder
why this fat ass
wasn't in our radar.
You know why?
He was making his first
steps
as a dealer.
So no record,
no criminal history,
no nothing.
The only thing I found
was that the guy
stole a chocolate
from the cafeteria
of the kindergarten
he attended.
Why do I tell you
this, Gómez?
Let's see.
He was dealing meth,
Blue Sky.
I've a question, let's
see...
What do you think?
The fat ass was shot
and meth vanished from
Bogotá.
Not a speck to be found
in the streets.
Tell me, why is
that?
The answer's here,
gentlemen.
Because this man,
Heisenberg, Jaisenberg,
whatever he may be called,
is in jail.
Whether we like it or not.
So, Gómez.
Then you believe the
story
that this plain man
is Heisenberg?
He confessed, sir.
So, man, if you
give me
three chicks
in a delicious suite,
with three boxes of
whiskey.
I'd confess anything!
This stuff
has gotten me thinking.
Pay attention, look.
What do you think?
We've no more meth
in Bogotá,
not a speck to be
found,
why am I getting calls
from Venezuela, Brazil,
Peru and Ecuador
to say they're having
blue stuff in the
streets?
Blue meth
crystals.
Gentlemen..
Top-shelf product like
this,
it doesn't fall
off
the face of the
earth.
This guy
Heisenberg,
the real one,
is here in Bogotá,
and we have to track him
down.
This banana
plantation,
as you call it,
might be inhabitable,
but get out of here.
Four million?
Yes, please!
We've reached four million!
Another fifteen thousand,
and we'll have it!
Wait, wait!
Come on!
Look, another
thirty thousand!
Thirty! Four million,
fifteen thousand!
Yes, yes!
- My love, we did it!
- Good!
Four million, 15 thousand pesos,
for daddy?
Can you believe it?
Yes, yes!
Aw, no, honey,
don't you cry!
Don't cry, my love, don't.
We're happy.
We're happy,
yes, four million...
Come on, come on!
Move, you bastard!
I don't recommend it,
don't you turn up.
The police
are watching the place.
They keep an eye
on the comings and goings.
Where are
they?
Well, that's the point,
not to be seen.
But that's not
our biggest problem.
You could just get stabbed
or shot here
just for your shows.
Why don't you leave?
Go home, I'll handle this.
José Miguel!
Jose!
Jose, wake up!
It's me, Walter. Look at me.
Jose, I'm getting you
out of here, okay?
No, I'm fine, I'm
fine.
No, no, no,
you're not fine here!
Come on, hang on to me, come--
Come!
Trust me, come on!
Come on!
It's
alright...
Calm down...
I'm here with you.
- I killed her.
- What? What?
I killed her, it was me!
No!
You didn't kill anybody.
Jose!
Look at me, you didn't kill her!
I loved her, teach!
Hush,
it's
alright.
Alright
now.
Everything will be
just fine,
calm down.
Let's get out of
here.
Hello?
Yeah, I'm already here.
No, I haven't thought
about that yet.
No.
I don't see any yellow dress.
When was the last time
you saw her wearing yellow?
There's a blue one here.
It's the only different one,
they're all black and gray.
It's aquamarine,
no, no, it's not blue...
It has a pattern
of swallows flying.
Yes.
Yes, long sleeves.
No cleavage.
I don't know.
I don't know, look, you do what
you feel like, okay?
Yes, that's fine.
She'll look really pretty.
Bye.
Alright.
You'll feel much better
with this one.
Yes, warmer.
Mmh, that's it.
Do you like this one?
We'll be finished soon.
Let's go check out the noises
your brother's making.
Yes.
Would you mind turning
that thing down?
Junior!
Really, stop that dinging!
Dad, it's the messages
from the donations!
It's disturbing the
baby.
Can't you see it?
María, slow down, mmh.
Wow, I can't believe it!
Really?
Yes, no, yes, we can.
But after school.
Okay, I'll call you.
I'll tell him and call you back.
Bye.
- Guess what, honey?
- What?
They want to interview you!
- No!
- Yes, yes!
One of María's patients
at the lab
works at Las Horas.
María told him about the blog,
the donations,
the success you're having,
and he wants to do
a story about you.
With your picture!
Awesome!
- Humph!
- I mean, that's cool, mom!
Now, that means publicizing!
Sure.
- And more money!
- Yeah, mommy, nice!
Wow!
So you're saying,
San José de Guaviare,
all covered.
Montería, covered too;
well done.
Hey, what happened
with Cartagena?
Mmh...
Henry, Henry,
come here for a
sec.
Yeah, I'm coming.
Fine, okay.
Well, keep me posted
on Cartagena.
Fine, okay.
Well, as I was saying,
it's difficult by the borders,
- they're too long.
- But the airport--
Boss.
Henry, come
here.
Our agent, Henry
Navarro.
Come, let me
introduce you,
Henry.
Mr. Andrés Gaviria,
from Gaviria Hotel.
Nice to meet you.
My pleasure, sir.
Mr. Pablo Machado,
from El Último Piso
Real Estate.
- Nice to meet you.
- My pleasure, sir.
And Mr. Gustavo Cortés,
from Chicken Brothers and Co.
- Call me Gus, please.
- From Chicken Brothers?
Hey, look,
let me tell you something:
The best legs I've ever seen,
those are your chickens'.
Henry, Henry, look.
These gentlemen
are helping us this year
with our fun run.
- They'll be our sponsors.
That's nice!
Thank you very much!
No, the idea is to give them
a little tour.
But I called you
because I want you
to tell them something,
anything
on your department's
activities.
Well, let's see...
The Anti-narcotics
Department,
as its name well indicates,
is in charge
of everything related
to drug dealing, right?
We've a couple
of centers in Colombia,
and well, I'm in charge
of a group right now,
we're dealing...
with designer drugs.
I don't know it you're aware
of what methamphetamine is.
It's a drug...
Have you heard
of a drug that's entered
the country
quite violently, lately?
Truth is, I haven't heard of it.
No, you're not the only one.
There's no information about it.
People don't know
of the dangers of this drug.
Look, we've broken into
a couple of labs.
We've hit on a couple of bosses,
but this ain't easy.
- These people put it all in.
- That's right.
That's why it's
so important for me
to have this race be
sort of an informative event
on this drug.
- Well thought.
- Okay, come on, gentlemen.
Thank you very much, Henry.
Let's go to the department
right over here,
it's Borders,
let me show you...
- We'll talk again later.
- Of course.
Nice to meet
you.
So...
Is this one of your
agents?
No.
That's my brother-in-law,
Walter.
He's got a health issue
and we're trying
to give him a hand, see?
What sort of health
issue?
Lung cancer.
Wow!
That's a rough
one!
Come on, no, no!
What are you do--?
No!
That belongs to the office
Please.
- No! How could you?
I'm happy to do it.
It's a pleasure for
me
to be able to help
you.
Well, thank you then.
My pleasure...
Henry.
See you... Gus.
I'm going to have my
surgery
on Friday.
So I won't be
coming
for a while.
I'm hopeful it'll go
well.
But if anything
happens,
you have Saúl, okay?
He'll be taking care
of everything.
He's got your money,
he's keeping it for
you.
Jose, don't think
about it, man.
Stop lingering
on things like these.
You need to focus
on your recovery.
I deserve this.
That thing you said when...
when we got stuck there
and almost died.
I understand it now.
I deserve everything
that's going on right now.
He was born normal,
but then they saw it was
ataxic cerebral palsy,
that's when the brain...
Walter's arrived.
Aw, Walter, hello!
We were waiting for you.
We called you about 50 times.
We're doing a feature
on Walter Junior.
Hi, wai--
wait a second.
María, you told me
it was an interview
- for the paper.
- No, yeah, that too.
But I thought, if
it's
good enough for the
paper,
it should be good
for the TV,
that's it.
- The TV?
- Yes, come on!
Is that
him?
Okay, the father's
arrived.
Great. We're starting
now.
Please, I want you all
seated here in the couch.
- Junior...
- Walter!
You go in the
middle,
and mom and dad
on the sides.
Ready?
- Yeah, fine.
- Hi.
Let me see the shot
you're doing...
- What's this?
- Aw, María...
Sit down, sit!
We'll start with a
close-up, okay?
Wait.
Let's see,
here...
The jacket,
it looks weird.
Okay.
Alright, ready?
Fine, okay, good.
We're starting now.
¿Whose idea was it?
It was
Junior's.
Junior came up
with the whole thing.
Junior, you were saying
your dad's inspiring.
Tell us about that.
Yeah.
My dad's the best.
And...
I don't want to lose him.
It's not only me,
we all love him here.
Describe your dad for us.
My dad's the best dad.
And he's a very good teacher.
He knows everything you need
to know about chemistry.
He's very patient...
He's always there for us.
Always.
He...
He's very...
Hum...
He's very responsible,
and above all,
he always does the right thing.
He's an example for me
and for anyone.
Does that put him to
sleep?
No, this one
just relaxes him a little.
We're almost ready.
I'll be back to take him
in a minute.
Thanks.
Well.
Here we are.
Yes.
Are you relaxed?
Humph...
I don't know what they gave me
but this stuff's incredible.
Yeah, we've seen that.
We'll be here when you wake up.
Humph. I love you.
- Give me the glasses.
- Hum, yeah.
Hey.
Now, I have them.
Where's your phone?
Which one?
Mommy, why...
Why does he have two?
Henry had suggested...
Forget about it.
Aw, mom, don't start
thinking ill of him.
He didn't bring the phone,
period.
You may start.
Gauze.
So, my dear Walter.
Pain level?
Fine.
I almost don't feel it.
Shortness of
breath?
Yeah, a bit, but...
In general,
I'm much better.
Good, it seems
everything's doing
fine.
I can't predict
the future, but...
even conservatively
speaking,
I'd dare say that...
you bought yourself
some real time here,
Walter.
So there's no reason
- to be pessimistic.
- Nice.
And...
When can he go back
to his normal life?
He will gradually
go back to his daily activities.
Can he work?
I'd give it a few more weeks.
You know, Walter:
Make sure you avoid
any heavy lifting, and...
Make sure you rest.
But, I mean,
he can be on his own?
I mean, can he do things
on his own?
Yes.
Yes, that's just...
Use your best judgment.
I think so.
Fine, good..
That's good news,
especially for you.
One less baby in the
house.
Diego.
- Welcome.
- Santiago, thank you.
My condolences
about your
daughter.
Thank you.
I thought the best thing
was coming back to work.
What a
tragedy.
We're all sorry
and thinking about
it.
How are you?
Good.
Well, after I...
after grieving for a while,
I figured I'd rather be here,
focus on work.
It'll do me good.
Sure.
Contact Southern Terminal,
frequency 119,95.
Cielos Peruanos 0111,
turn right.
Aerocóndor 006,
proceed directly.
I'm going to stay
with Henry and María
for the weekend.
How come?
I'm taking the baby.
María is picking Junior up.
You're staying here on your own,
two days at home.
I want you to pack
your stuff up
and leave.
Why?
Henry offered
to help you,
so that you don't have
to carry heavy things.
Wait, Cielo!
Hang on a second,
I don't understand.
Walter, I don't want you here
on Monday.
I want you to leave the house.
But, can you at least
explain me why?
Because you're a liar.
You've two phones.
- What?
- Yes.
Right before your surgery,
I asked if you had packed
your cell phone,
and you said,
"Which one?"
When was that?
Cielo, I was doped!
I was on the stretcher,
I was delirious!
I mean, I could have said
anything.
No, you know what I think?
You said the truth.
You accidentally told the truth.
Honey, I thought
we were over this.
What happened is...
happened?
It got me thinking again
about all the strange behavior
you've been having lately.
That weird behavior.
Like the day you disappeared,
I was out of my mind,
looking for you
everywhere, Walter.
I was desperate, calling...
hospitals, even the morgue.
That thing...
Your fugue state.
I really needed
to believe...
all that was true.
Because, who would make up
something like that?
Who?
Cielo, I really don't
get it.
No, wait, no!
This is...
You think I'm cheating on you
Really?
You really think
I'm having an affair?
I've been thinking about
it
for the last few weeks.
Yeah? Who with?
Who am I having
an affair with?
I even thought it was Marcela.
Yeah, I could see omething
was going on between you.
For God's sake!
Marcela?
Okay, what do you
want?
Want me to swear on the
Bible
I've nothing to do with
Marcela?
No, I know,
I've already asked her.
Yes.
It really took me forever
to get in touch with her.
She wasn't answering
my calls.
So I finally left
a message saying,
"What exactly is going on
between you and my husband?"
I thought that would get
her attention, and it did.
Because she called me back.
And she told me
everything, Walter.
Money for the treatment?
Edgar and Marcela
didn't give you one peso!
They didn't pay for anything!
Because you didn't let them.
But none of it
made any sense,
because when I called
the people
at the Cancer Institute,
they said that,
except for the operation,
it was all paid for.
Yes.
More than
190 million pesos!
Where did you get them?
Tell me, where did you get them?
- Our of nowhere?
- My mother--
I also talked to your mother!
I started to think that,
that your mother had
some money stored away,
and you had borrowed from her.
I mean, that was possible,
you not telling me about it.
But it turns out, the money
not only wasn't from her,
but she also had no idea
you had cancer.
I left you at the airport,
Walter, and then picked you up.
You left for four days.
And your mother swears
you didn't go to see her.
- Cielo, honey.
- No, don't you touch me!
Lies, lies and more lies!
- Honey...
- No!
At least have the courtesy...
of not denying it, Walter.
Cielo, please, don't leave.
- Cielo...
- Don't touch me!
- Please...
- Hello.
If I tell you the truth,
will you stay?
- Stay, I'll tell you.
- No.
Whatever it is,
I'm freaked out
Walter.
Here's Captain Polanco.
Aerolíneas Andinas.
Flight number 3231,
coming from Trujillo.
Bogotá,
getting closer on position
level two, zero, zero.
Aerolíneas Andinas 3231,
turn right, course 095.
Direct to Bogotá VOR.
CJJ 3235,
traffic at 12.
On position.
You'll be crossing your position
from left to right.
CJJ, disregard
previous information,
You've traffic
on your same level,
at 30 kilometers.
You'll be crossing your level
from right to left.
Aerolíneas Andinas 2351,
radio interception,
frequency 119.5.
Go directly to Bogotá VOR.
ST 9666, you've traffic
on your same level.
At 300, 900 meters.