Clear the area
and look for the target.
Captain,
we can't see a thing.
Positive, Captain.
The fugitive is running away .
Let's go back.
Please, I need to get there.
I only need that.
Then I'll deal with the rest.
I want you to understand me.
I'm not saying
I don't like to experiment.
On the contrary, I love it.
But I'm just so tired
of having Fusión Gourmet
everywhere we go.
It was very good.
But sometimes,
I just want a simple
dish.
Something I can recognize
without passion fruit sauce.
Everything has
passion fruit sauce.
I want to see what
I'm eating.
Your attitude worries me.
You are trading
your intelligence
in order to be critic
about a restaurant
and you're walking away
from science.
No, don't mock me.
We all have the right
to go back to the
simple things.
No passion fruit
sauce.
Sometimes I just wish
I could have potatoes
with rice and meat.
I'm getting tired
of Fusión Gourmet.
Well,
there's
nothing
like a good piece of
meat
with salad and rice.
We should have
stayed home.
Really?
But I think it's fine
to try new things.
You know what?
We should go
to a Colombian restaurant.
To have some beans.
With chicharrón.
With no eggs.
I can't stand
eggs.
But you don't understand
what I'm saying.
When I go to a restaurant
to have something to eat,
I want them to serve me food,
not some herbs.
Well now, you are saying
This one?
to tell me you're
hungry.
Cabernet.
No.
You think I'm hungry?
Well, yes.
Now there's
two of us.
But it was your
idea.
Your idea.
But the thing is that dinner
was made of molecules.
You said you wanted
to try something new.
Well, since we are
trying
some new things,
why don't we go
to a raw food
restaurant.
A what?
They are trending.
They only serve
raw food.
It's all about the
juices
and the salads.
And the deserts
don't go to the oven.
They are
dehydrated.
We should try that.
I don't know.
It could be a
good option.
It's just that I don't like
that type of food.
The type of food
that I like is...
- I don't know.
- Considerable.
But not that
much.
I'm eating
better now.
If you say so.
I eat lighter.
I like to have
soups,
salads and stuff.
What happened?
Edgar, Marcela,
how are you?
Let me congratulate you.
This new house you have
is truly remarkable.
I've been taking a look
and the upstairs floor
has a wonderful view.
It is something.
-Walter...
-What are you doing here?
I saw you at an interview.
You look so well.
Camera loves you.
Very much.
Walter, if you
hurt us,
I will--
No, look, I came here
because I have
something to give you.
I have it in my car.
Can you come with me?
It'll be just a second.
I'm sorry. I couldn't get
the car much closer.
I have it on a road
quite near your house.
Edgar, do you really
want to solve things
that way?
You're going to need
a much bigger gun for that.
Put it there,
right over the table.
Marcela, Marcela,
be careful!
I don't want a single wad
ending up underneath the sofa.
That's it.
Thank you, Edgar.
On this table,
there are 17,500 million pesos.
Where did you get that?
And why is it here?
I worked a lot
to earn that money.
And you are going
to give it to my son.
I don't think
that's a great idea,
Walter.
When my son turns 18,
that is 2 months
and 3 days from now,
you are going to give him
this money
as an irrevocable donation.
I want you to tell him
that he can use the money
to whatever he deems necessary.
However, you will tell him
that it would be really nice
if he could invest it
in his education
and in the welfare
of his family.
Walter, if you want that money
to reach your family,
why don't you give it
to them yourself?
Why do we need
to be involved?
Because it's not possible.
My wife and my son
hate me.
I don't understand
why us.
Edgar, they wouldn't take it.
It's that simple.
And if they do,
there's a great chance
that the Government
will take it away from them.
So that's the part
in which you come in.
You are two rich benefactors
making generous donations.
Isn't that what you did
just recently?
How much did you donate?
A million dollars?
Nobody will suspect of you.
Everyone will understand
that you want to help
a family that's suffering.
This makes no sense.
It makes all the sense,
Marcela.
My family is victim
of a criminal,
a monster you knew well,
before he destroyed himself.
Everyone will understand
that you want to help
in this situation.
But I don't care.
You can justify it
however you want to.
Just do it.
And I don't want you
to pay anything
with your money.
If there are any expenses,
notaries, lawyers, taxes,
you take the money from here,
not from your pocket.
My family gets my money,
not yours.
Okay, Walter.
You've made a good
point.
We'll do it.
Fine.
What do we have to
do now?
Just shake hands,
and I'll go.
Hey.
Can I be sure
that you'll do it?
Yes, don't worry.
We'll do it.
Stop, please!
Don't move!
Edgar, don't move
a single muscle.
I don't want my
friends
out there to get
confused.
They might think
you are trying to
escape.
I will try
to put you
into context.
This morning
I had 500 millions here.
That money should be
right over this table,
but I decided to invest it.
I gave the money
to the best hit men
this country has.
Easy.
Regardless of what might happen
to me from now on,
they will be watching you.
And if for some reason,
this money does not reach
my kids,
a countdown will begin.
It might last a day.
It might last months.
But it will end.
Someday, you might be walking
in a shopping mall,
or walking through Europe,
or talking about
your molecular food,
or doing anything else,
and suddenly,
without noticing it,
you'll hear a noise
from behind.
- And boom!
Don't worry.
This won't happen to you.
You are good people.
You are the best
that Colombia has.
I know you will do
the right thing.
Goodbye.
Easy.
Easy, please.
He left.
Sir, with all due respect,
I'm feeling bad
about this.
You see, man, el Mono
is talking about
what we just did.
It's as if we have no morals.
I'm feeling truly bad
about this whole thing.
Yes.
How do you feel
now?
That's better.
I'm healed now.
Have you heard the rumors
about the blue product
being in circulation
again in the market?
What did you say?
Is it true or not?
Yes, it's true.
It's in circulation again.
And who's behind that?
Aren't you behind that?
Are you saying
that you are not cooking now?
It's an excellent product.
It's so fine
we thought it was you.
It has to be Jose.
Old Jose...
That's nice.
Didn't you tell me
he was in Argentina?
Yes, man.
That's what they
told me.
That means
that he's now the king.
- That's amazing, right?
- Yes!
And what's that?
The years I'm turning.
Is it your birthday?
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Good afternoon.
What are you having today?
Tea? As usual?
Yes, thank
you.
Hello.
Hi.
You look very good
on those clothes.
On what?
On this
shirt?
On everything. It's new.
Before you say or do
anything,
please listen to me.
Lidia, please.
Nobody knows I'm
here.
I'm begging you.
It's just two
minutes.
That's all.
Please.
Thank you. Thank
you.
I know you are
running out
of methylamine.
I was making
some
calculations.
You are using it a
lot.
The thing is
I have a new method
that doesn't need
methylamine.
It's very simple.
And... I can
teach it to you.
How did you find us?
You and I used to
meet a lot
in this very place.
Tuesdays at 10:00
A.M.,
and you are a woman
of habit.
Sorry.
I need money.
I spend it all
running away from
Police.
You see, Professor,
I think that right now
we are not in conditions--
How much will it cost us?
A million
dollars.
And that's nothing.
Believe me.
Make an appointment
with Joaquín.
With all due respect,
but I think that now--
Beto, please,
let me speak to
Joaquín.
Look, this is
convenient
for all of us.
I'm sorry, are you
having
anything else?
No, thank you.
He was just leaving.
I'm glad to see you again.
We'll keep in touch.
Of course. Thank
you.
And you?
I want a beer.
And more sweetener
for me.
Perfect.
Miss Lidia,
with all due respect,
he is the master, right?
I don't think
it's the right time
to be working with--
We won't be working with
him.
It's clear the guy's a mess.
So?
Do I have to
explain it to
you?
That man looks like
an astray dog.
We will put him down
and make him a
favor.
Hi, María.
What's going
on?
Walter is back.
Yes, they found the car
that he had stolen.
They tracked him down
and he appeared downtown.
And what's the name
of that neighbor
you used to have?
Miss Rebeca.
Miss Rebeca saw him,
in broad daylight.
He said 'hi' to her.
He went to that house
that you used to have.
Did he do anything
to Miss Rebeca?
He didn't do anything to her.
But she said he's pretty bad,
that he looks finished.
Cielo, the Police
is looking for him everywhere.
It seems they received
several phone calls
saying that he's planning
to blow up Anti-Narcotics
and that he has a press release
and that he will read it tonight
on the evening news.
Is he making those
calls?
They don't know
who's making the
calls.
taking advantage of
the moment
to make some bad
jokes.
However, the truth
is
that everybody is
worried.
And that's what he
wants.
Because Walter
is a terrorist.
And as far as I
know,
there are only 3 people
he would look for:
you, me, or Junior.
True.
Now, the Police
is arriving at
Junior's school
and they are alert
in case he shows up.
And they will surely
send some people
to your place, right?
However, Cielo,
the important
thing
is that Walter
won't get to you.
He won't get to
you.
I swear that.
That fucker thinks
he's the best criminal
in the whole world.
But you know what?
He's not.
But just be careful.
Yes, I understand.
Promise me, please.
Yes.
Thank you for your call.
Alright,
I'll talk to you
later.
Five
minutes,
and that's
it.
That's all I need.
Did you kill
someone
to get here?
No.
Did you hurt
someone?
No, I didn't have to.
But I feel good.
What do you
want?
Why are you
here?
This is the end.
I feel that everything
is coming to an end.
And I wanted to say goodbye
the right way.
Not like the last time
we spoke over the phone.
What does that
mean?
Are you going to
surrender
to the Police?
They will come for me.
to come
and threaten me again?
When I still had the
house,
three hooded men
came to threaten me,
Valentina and
Junior.
And they said
we were not allowed
to talk
about the women
in the car wash.
If they know
you are in ja--
They won't come back.
Not after tonight.
What will happen
tonight?
We don't want your
money.
I think that Junior
was very clear about that
the last time you two spoke.
That's right.
I don't have money for you.
The last money I had
I spend it coming to you.
This...
is the only thing
I can give you.
When I leave,
call Anti-Narcotics,
and tell them
that I was here,
that I forced you
to let me in.
Those numbers
are GPS coordinates.
To what?
To a mass grave.
There, they will find
the bodies
of Henry and Gómez.
I buried all our money there,
and some guys
stole it from me.
Those guys
killed Henry and Gómez.
And they buried them
in the hole I dug.
Cielo, you need to negotiate
with the Prosecutor.
You have to,
so you can have
a way out.
Look at me, please.
I want you to understand
that I did this bec--
No. Don't tell me you
did this for the family.
No. I did it for me.
I did it because I liked it.
Because I was very good at it.
I did it
because it made me feel alive.
Junior will be here
any second now.
Can I see her
before I go?
Thank you, Lucho.
We'll be in touch.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Walter!
What a miracle!
What about that new
look?
Those look good on
you.
Move on.
Turn around
and put your arms up.
He's clean.
Well, my friend,
since we are here,
put up your shirt.
You think I have a wire
or something like that?
You never
know.
Enough?
Can I have my keys
and my wallet back, please?
Don't worry, man.
We'll give them
back later.
Get in.
Wow, you hair is back
and it fits you well.
Congratulations
That looks
good.
We can't say the same
about the rest of your
body.
You look like shit.
Thank you, Joaquín,
I'm glad to see you too.
Shall we talk business?
No, I don't
think so.
No, wait a minute.
Beto, have you told him
what I'm offering to you?
Yes, sure.
He told me
everything.
But we are not
in the business
anymore.
No, but I know
you will run out of methylamine.
What are you going to do
after that happens?
We won't have any
problems.
Lidia has her own
system.
Nobody bothers her
anymore,
you know?
She can do her businesses
whenever she wants to,
and as long as that
works out flawlessly,
we don't need
to cook anymore.
Listen to me.
No, no! Wait!
Joaquín, let me talk to you...
Beto, tell them
about the benefits
of the system I'm offering you.
Will you? Please.
I'm so sorry for you,
Professor Blanco.
You shouldn't have returned.
Where shall I kill him?
How can I know, man?
But don't do it here.
No one will clean
if you blow his head off
here.
Take him outside.
Damn it!
Take him out of here!
Joaquín, Joaquín!,
Kill me, if you want!
But keep your word!
You owe me!
You should have honor!
Honor? What the fuck
are you talking about?
Motherfucker!
You gave me your word
that you would kill Rosas.
And you didn't do it!
You didn't keep your word.
Not only you didn't kill him,
but you also
made him your partner to cook.
Wait a minute!
I don't have any
partners.
Rosas is alive.
And he's cooking for you.
Or are you going to deny it?
Yes, he's alive,
but that doesn't
mean
he's my partner.
I can't be partners
with a filthy rat
like that.
He's a motherfucker
who didn't hesitate
to contact the
Police
and tell them
everything.
Where's that piece of shit?
He's finishing up a batch.
Well, go get him right
now.
But Uncle, the thing is that--
Shut your mouth!
If there's something
I've had
my whole life is honor.
Hurry!
Bring that son
of a bitch here!
And we'll finish
this shit
once and for all.
I will kill him
right in front of
your nose.
And then I'll
kill you.
Move!
You see, motherfucker?
Does this piece of shit
looks like my partner?
Take a look.
Take a good look
so you can see him well.
This fucker
is not my partner.
Yes or no, my friend?
He doesn't eat or shower.
We don't pay for his doctor.
We don't pay for his house.
He's the perfect partner.
And he's also a good worker.
So, what?
Are we doing this shit or not?
Let's go.
Beto, pick them
up.
No, Walter.
Walter, wait.
You want your money, right?
You want to
know
where it is?
If you pull that
trigger,
you'll never know.
Do it. You want this.
Shoot me.
Just do it.
Say it! For the first time
in your fucking life,
say what you want!
I won't do anything
until you tell me to.
Say you want this!
Say you want me
to kill you!
I want this.
Kill me.
Then do it yourself.
Hello.
Is it done?
Is he gone?
Yeah, it's done.
He's gone.
They're all gone.
Who is this?
It's Walter.
How are you feeling, Lidia?
Kind of under the weather?
Like you've got the flu?
That would be the resin
I gave you.
I slipped it into
that fucking sweetening
that you are always putting
in your tea.
My God.
And now,
it's just a matter of time.
You will feel
weaker and weaker
until you pass away.
You are dead.