José!
Come out!
Is everything all right?
It's all clear.
Seems so.
I'll take the car
to the boss then.
Stewart, do me a favor.
Can you go
to my son's high
school
and check
everything is fine?
I just want to
check.
Sure, no problem.
And you told me the
car wash
is also secured, right?
Yes, I have
some people there
but there're
no signals of Rosas.
Find him, will you?
Please, find him.
I will.
See you.
Voice mail.
Leave your message
after the tone.
José, it's me.
You obviously
changed your mind
about my house...
You didn't do it,
so thank you for that.
But we have to talk.
We have to fix this.
Whatever it takes, all right?
So, for now,
just sleep it off
and then call me.
Be safe.
How's it coming?
Fine, sir.
I'll change the hinge
and the lock.
Good.
Excuse me.
Are you interested
in a new master key
for all locks?
No, no, no.
I'll keep the exact same keys.
It's just that usually
with a break in,
people like to get new keys
and--
No, no, no.
I'm fine.
Just leave the original keys,
the original locks.
As though nothing had happened.
- Yes, sir.
- Thanks.
Good, good.
Perfect.
No, no, no, hey!
Turn that off!
Guys, guys,
you'll have to go over this
again.
We made three passes already.
Gasoline's tricky.
I know, but I don't care.
Do it again.
My wife is coming home
and I can't have any odor,
any stain,,
any sign that something
happened here.
Nothing, no traces.
As though nothing happened here.
I know I'm asking you
for a special service,
so there's no problem.
Here.
Walter, no.
Thanks, for real,
but no matter how much money
you give us,
there's nothing
else we can do.
Until you pull this up
and get new carpet, new
padding,
this is as good
as it gets.
Mariano, let's pick
things up.
Hi.
You can't imagine
what a mess this was!
What
happened?
This country is really--
Why do we have to be like this?
We don't do
anything right.
We'll be consumed
by mediocrity.
It's unbelievable.
- What's that smell?
- Gasoline, gasoline.
- No, no, no.
You have no idea, Cielo.
No, watch out!
That's wet.
What
happened?
I went to the gas station
and the guy who was supposed
to fill up the tank
wasn't there,
so I had to get off the car
and fill it myself.
I have no idea
how that thing works
so when I squeezed the--
I don't know, that trigger,
and all of a sudden
I had gasoline all over me.
The brackets around the hose
were loosen.
But no one told me!
That could have been a lady
with a baby, I don't know.
Who knows
what could have happened?
So I was soaked in gasoline.
You get the girl out of here.
I don't think this smell
is good for her.
Yes.
No, this is a mess.
I'm a beast.
Just hold on,
I don't get it.
If you got soaked
at the gas station,
then why does the house
smell of gasoline?
Wait, I didn't tell you
the rest.
I was soaked,
so I raced home
and my skin was burning,
so I stripped off my clothes
here.
I stripped them off
here in this room
and I jumped in the shower.
And when I was showering,
I realized I had left
the clothes here
and there was noting
I could do--
- Walter!
- What?
Why are you such a liar?
- Hi, babe.
Hi.
What are you talking about?
You fainted because
you're sick again.
- What?
- Just admit it!
- Stop lying about it.
- No
Hey, for real!
I didn't faint.
Dad, you inhaled the fumes.
You got dizzy and fainted.
And then you soaked your clothes
in gasoline.
Just accept it.
Hey, little man.
I might have inhaled the fumes,
but I didn't faint
because of that.
You have to believe me,
it's important you do.
Fine, I believe you.
Fine.
The thing is that I don't think
I can clean this smell
from the carpet
tonight.
No. And it's so strong.
- Yes, I know.
- Right?
I don't think
we can stay here.
No, not at all.
Let's go to the uncle's house.
- Yes, could be.
- Could be.
Do we go to the auntie's?
What about a hotel?
A hotel?
Yes. Why don't we go
to a hotel?
If it's a good one.
Fine, okay. A hotel.
Yes, baby?
Yes.
That's it!
Let's go to a hotel then.
Cool.
- Shall we pack?
- Yes.
I'm really sorry
for this mess.
I didn't mean it.
No, don't worry.
Those things happen.
Let's pack, baby.
Think this
will leave a
scar?
It'll change my
looks.
I liked my nose.
It had personality,
character.
Boss, if you don't mind,
I have a good cream for scars
at home.
I can bring it tomorrow.
I should have never
left my karate lessons.
You practiced karate?
Just once.
There he is.
What happened to you?
Did José do that to you?
Yes, he did,
but I know he loves me
deep down.
And I'm sure this hurt
him more than it hurt me.
So what?
Do we know anything?
Did you find him?
We're still after him.
Where did you search?
At his place,
at his friend's,
at his parents'.
Everywhere they sell drugs.
Even at that place
where he had those meetings
for addicts.
Even at Andrea's,
his ex-girlfriend.
Did you check at...
Those friends of his.
Not Intestinos,
the other one.
- Tripaseca.
- That one.
- Tripaseca and Mono.
- And?
No, they have no idea.
Aren't they covering his back?
No.
I posed as an employee
for the phone company
and put a bug
at Mono's mom's place.
All they talk about
is zombies, hay pets
and zombie cats.
What?
I didn't get it either.
And what else?
I checked with a pal
at the Police.
He's not in their system.
That means
that if he's not in the system,
they cops don't have him.
At least not yet.
Maybe he changed his mind
about leaving
and got back in touch
with the Borrador.
No, no.
When somebody
misses their first
chance with that guy,
there's no second
chance.
We have to keep on searching,
Saúl.
And then what?
What do you mean?
José is like a herpes.
He might
disappear,
but sooner or later he's
going to turn up again.
So we have to decide
what we'll do then.
José is just upset
about the boy.
I need to explain to him
why I did what I did.
He'll understand.
The kid's not up
for a discussion
of the virtues
of child poisoning
for your own benefit.
His plans are
stabbing you
to death
with a pointing stick.
If that's so,
what shall we
do?
I don't know.
Any suggestions?
We could do
what we did
with Confite.
Who's Confite?
I never told you?
Confite was a dog.
I had him at home.
He was somewhere
between a French Poodle
and an Alsatian.
It was really nice,
we loved it,
but one day
he showed up rabid
and he became
very dangerous.
So, for the sake of
the family
we had to...
You know.
You're full
of colorful metaphors,
aren't you?
The Caribbean Islands,
a rabid dog...
Just brimming with advice, Saúl.
You should be writing
self-help books.
Listen carefully.
Don't you ever
suggest that to me again.
Find him!
Damn it.
Hello.
I'm sorry I took so long.
Those people at the
pharmacy were incredible.
They didn't want
to give me change.
Not even buying the pills.
No, they didn't have change.
I had to buy some jam,
can you believe it?
I knew we didn't need any but...
Unbelievable!
They prefer not selling.
They're--
I checked in on Junior.
Hey, they got him a suite.
That boy
seems a sheik.
Digital TV,
video games, Wi-Fi.
Thank God
he doesn't have porn.
Don't worry about that.
How's Saúl?
Saúl?
You mean the lawyer?
Mm.
No idea. Why?
No?
You were just out talking
to him in the parking lot.
Cielo,
were you saying on me?
Yes, and I feel just
awful
about it.
Walter,
let's get serious.
I played along with you
with that gasoline story
because Junior was there.
But it's enough now.
Tell me what's going on.
Nothing.
Nothing serious, Cielo.
We're in a hotel
just for caution.
That's all.
You know how overly cautious
I am.
I'm exaggerated, that's all.
- Tell me what's going on.
- Nothing.
José Miguel Rosas,
the boy with whom we were--
We had dinner with him at home,
remember?
I know perfectly well
who he is.
Well, José is...
He's mad at me
because he thinks I did...
Well, I did something,
but it was
for a good reason.
It's complicated, Cielo.
I can't explain it
just like that.
No, hold on, hold on.
Just a moment.
What are you trying
to tell me?
That José Miguel...
tried to burn down
our house or...?
Burn down?
No, that sounds terrible.
José just had a bad moment.
He didn't think clearly.
That's all.
Yes, he did have the intention,
but he didn't do it,
he changed his mind.
Why did he change
his mind?
What made him think
change his mind?
things through?
Cielo, it's not that easy.
José is quite a particular guy.
he's got lots...
He's got lots
of personal problems.
Emotional problems.
He's a drug addict.
But he has always been
more of a danger to himself
than anyone else.
He just losses control
and then gets it back,
but he poses no threat
for anyone.
He's never hurt
anyone?
No, never.
I can't believe
you got her down so fast.
Maybe she likes hotels.
Walter, look.
What's your
course of action
here?
Cielo, calm down.
Saúl and his guy
are tracking him down,
they find him,
they'll bring him along
and I'll talk to him.
I'll make him see reason.
End of story.
When you say
you'll take to him
and make him see
sense,
does it mean you'll do
what I think you'll do?
- Or what?
- What?
No! No!
My God!
How could you think that?
I knew it!
I knew it, Walter!
I told you thousands of times!
I told you they'd get home
and hurt us.
- No.
- And that day is today!
And now we're here.
Cielo, listen to me.
José Miguel Rosas
would never hurt us.
He poured gasoline
all over our house.
He tried to set it on fire!
But he didn't.
He changed his mind.
What if he changes his
mind again?
And this time
he doesn't think it over.
What if he burns Valentina?
What would you think of
that?
How much have you been drinking?
Doesn't matter.
It does matter
I really don't know where
this conversation is going.
This makes no sense.
haven't I explained it all
well enough?
What did I tell you?
This is a big overreaction.
It has nothing to do
with what's going on.
Cielo,
José Miguel Rosas
is not a rabid dog
like Confite,
do you get me?
What the hell
are you talking about?
I don't know!
It doesn't matter!
José is a person,
a human being.
¡No!
He's a threat
to our family.
I'm tired of
lying.
Just look
where we're now
with María and Henry.
We made an awful tape.
After all the bad things
we've done,
you can't just tell
me
that you'll talk to
him.
"I'll make him
come to sense."
What are you saying?
Cielo,
What do you mean?
Be precise, please.
You want me to...
We've come this
far.
For us...
What's one more?
Son of a bitch!
Stop!
Stop what you're doing
and turn around!
José Miguel!
You want to know what your
what he did?
fucking brother-in-law did?
Put that out!
He poisoned a little boy.
He poisoned
a 6 year-old boy
just as a move!
Fine, fine.
We all know
Walter is a bastard.
We'll talk about it.
He can't keep on
winning.
he can't keep
getting away with it!
Not anymore!
That won't happen.
If you want to burn him down,
end with him,
let's do it together.
This is yours, isn't it?
Here.
So you've been following me.
Since Saul's.
Where are we going now?
Anti narcotics
So I'm arrested?
You know how this works.
Be a good witness for me,
it'll go better for you.
All right?
Sure.
I'll be absolutely relaxed,
waiting to be a witness
against Walter.
Hey, you're with me now.
Nothing will
happen to you.
You still have no idea
what he's capable of doing.
So you're angry.
I can't sleep.
I'm not eating.
Last night I was online
for six hours
looking up untraceable poisons.
This close family friend
had been keeping a secret
from you and Henry,
So now,
somehow this person's secret
became known,
and now you're sad
and hurt and angry.
Am I right?
How could it be?
How can you think
you know someone
and in fact you have
no idea who he is.
In the long run,
we all live double lives.
No, not me.
Not like him.
Not like that person.
María, I think it's time
you filled me in
on some more details here.
Who and what
are we exactly talking about?
I can't.
I can't do that.
This person made it clear
in that video
that we couldn't talk
about him,
if not, Henry
will be in danger.
I don't want that.
And yes,
I'm stupid.
I feel so idiotic,
so dumb
because I didn't see it.
It was in front of me
and I didn't see it.
And now the boy and the girl
are in that house
and I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
But if I think about it,
that betting story made sense.
How couldn't I see that?
Why not?
Why?
Tell me about that video.
I don't want to
talk about that!
Just not anymore.
Let's talk about my
feelings
or let's change the
subject.
Fine, good.
So how's work?
Last week you were upset
about the new parking rules.
María.
It's called saxitotoxin.
It paralyzes the body
but the person
stays conscious
and starts choking slowly
because it causes
respiratory failure.
María, look,
if you're not ready
to fill me in here,
that's fine.
But I want you to listen.
There is no problem,
no matter how difficult
or painful
or seemingly unsolvable,
that violence won't make worse.
I know.
I wouldn't hurt anyone.
But it just feels good
thinking about it.
It just feels good.
Hey, babe.
Hi, babe.
What's this?
What?
Something's come up.
I thought you might want
to get out of the house
for a day or two.
Okay.
You thought I might want
to pack up
and move out of my own house?
What's going on, henry?
I don't want to talk
about that now, babe,
but it's related to Walter.
There's been a development.
What happened?
Are you in danger?
No, no, no.
Not at all.
Don't worry.
We're just working
on the case.
We're moving forward,
so I thought it'd be
easier for everyone
if you weren't here
for a couple of days,
do you get me?
And I have a surprise for you.
Since you're so fond of spas,
I booked you three days
at Spacio,
that one you like so much
so they put masks on you,
you get some massages,
those river stones,
everything.
It's all included.
Henry Navarro,
what the hell is going on?
Henry.
We have a guest.
I gave him
some sleeping pills
because he was too disturbed.
Babe, I need
your help.
If I bring him to the
office
and put him in the system,
Walter will find
out
in five minutes.
Remember what happened
with the 10 witnesses
I had in prison?
They killed them.
I can't risk that.
I can use a safe house
because I'd have to ask for
permission in writing
and explain everything
that's going on.
And I can't risk
taking him to a hotel.
This is the only option
I have.
I have to keep him here.
Please.
It'll just be one
or two days.
Stop, Henry.
I have a question.
Is this bad for Walter?
Would this hurt him?
Pretty much.
Okay. Good.
I'll prepare lunch.
Babe, answer.
You have one new voice mail.
To listen to your mess--
José, it's me..
You obviously didn't do
what you intended to do
at me house.
You changed your mind
and I'm thankful for that.
But we have to talk.
We have to fix things.
Whatever it takes.
Just rest for now
and call me when you can.
Be safe.
Hey, dad.
Hi.
What are you still doing up?
I couldn't sleep.
That makes two.
Sit.
Why are you so meditative, dad?
Everything's okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I was just thinking
about some business stuff.
Going over some options.
You're still thinking
about buying the car wash?
Yes.
I don't know.
We'll see.
We'll see?
What does that mean?
Is it because you're ill
again
and you don't know
whether yo buy it or not?
No, no, no.
I'm not talking about that.
Junior,
what did we say?
You promised me
you wouldn't worry.
How can I not
worry, dad?
You think I came all this way
just to let a lung cancer
take me down?
I'm not going anywhere.
Get that in your head, Junior.
Don't worry.
See you in the
morning.
Have a nice rest.
I won't take long.
Okay.
Hey, do we have
breakfast together?
Hum.
Good morning.
Hi.
You want some coffee?
Okay.
Gómez, good morning.
Good morning.
What's up?
You want some coffee?
The lady has offered me one.
I think she's your wife.
You take cream and
sugar?
Black's fine.
Thanks.
Babe, you want some coffee?
No.
Gómez?
Thanks.
Babe?
Mm?
This will take a while.
Okay.
I'll go make some errands.
- Fine. Bye.
- Bye.
Bye, guys.
Bye.
You remember Gómez?
Of course.
So how are you?
Your head's clear?
Better.
This can't be what you mean
by burning him to the ground,
right?
I've got stories
that'll make your toes curl,
but it's just my word
against his word.
I don't really have
any proof or anything.
Why can't I see anything?
You know he's retired?
He's no longer cooking.
You're never going to catch him
with a camcorder.
Of course
I'm going to catch him,
and the first thing we'll do
will be this video.
So please, take a seat.
That's it.
Tell me about you.
You can tell me
about business
dealings
or personal stuff.
Any criminal activity
you were in with Walter
or anything you witnessed
Walter doing.
I need you
to tell me everything.
Everything is useful.
So first, start by telling me
How you met Walter Blanco.
Here it goes.
I met professor Walter Blanco
in junior year chemistry
at Los Monarcas,
the school I went to.
He was my teacher.
You believe him?
Yes, I do.
And I hate to admit
he's right.
There's no physical evidence,
nothing.
If only we had a body,
a gun,
a working lab,
something.
All we have
is the word of a drug addict
with a head full of meth
against a chemist teacher
with lung cancer.
We're screwed.
So what do we do
then?
Do we go
to see Lidia again?
Do we investigate
Peto?
Do we believe him?
Where do we start?
I say we start with this.
José, tomorrow at noon
I'll be at Los Pinos park.
I hope you'll give me the chance
to explain myself.
I want us to talk face to face
and calmed.
I'll be alone and unarmed.
So if you want to come
and shoot me in the head,
that's up to you.
Either way,
I'm in your hands.
What?
No, don't even think about it.
I'm not meeting him
He's nuts.
I'm not going to that park.
Go and listen.
We put a wire on you
and you just let him talk
and explain himself.
All right?
That's all?
That's the plan'
So your plan
is to do his plan?
You really think
he wants to meet me to talk?
Really?
No, man.
Why not?
How co--¿
I can't believe you two
are falling in this trap.
He wanted me
out of Bogotá
before I tried
to burn his house down.
I'm just a threat for him now.
I know him.
I know the professor.
He's got a zero-tolerance policy
on threats.
The moment I go to that park,
I'm dead man.
Look, we all know
Walter is ruthless
and that he'd do anything
to protect his interests,
but this is different.
You know why?
Because this is about you.
And Walter
worries about you.
Can't you see it?
So what you mean
is that when he's
not ripping me off
or calling me an idiot
or poisoning people
that I care about,
all that means
that he cares about me?
How couldn't I see that before?
Sure, José,
he worries about you.
I'm just based
on everything you told us.
First of all,
you said
he paid for your rehab.
Didn't he?
That was the first time
he saved your life.
He ran over two drug dealers
with his car.
He saved your life again.
He made you his partner.
He gave you
half of the money.
He had no reason
for doing that, did he?
Yes.
You know why he did it?
Because I'm the only person
who's close enough
and good enough
to cook just like him.
I don't know.
According to what you told us,
Walter has been manipulating you
all this time.
He doesn't want to lose you.
He wants you to stick around.
Just look at his moves.
Why would Walter
help you find
the ricin cigarette?
Better still, what for?
So you think
he's a good person,
that he's kind,
that you can trust him.
And this message
is the same thing.
What if it's about killing me?
For real,
What if I get there
and he's hired a sniper?
Or have me sit
on a poison needle?
Noting's going to happen
to you.
It's a public park,
full of people.
It's middle of the day.
Gómez and I
will be there.
Nothing's going to happen
to you.
You really don't get it.
You two are just common people.
This man,
professor Blanco,
he's the devil.
I know why I'm telling you.
For real.
That man
is the most intelligent person
I've ever known.
He's more intelligent than you,
He's more intelligent than me.
than Gómez.
Whatever you think
is supposed to happen,
the exact reverse opposite
of that is going to happen.
I can assure than.
That man is--
Rosas!
We're not brainstorming
to see what we're going to do.
I'm not asking you
whether you want to or not.
This is how we're doing it.
Did you get me?
Unless you have
some other way
to catch him.
Unless you want to spend
the rest of your life
singing hip-hop in prison.
We can get you that ticket
right now.
I have to piss.
Can I piss?
Down to the left.
We need another card
for this.
What?
What if the kid's right?
What if it's a trap?
This kid?
You call him kid now?
Which kid?
The junkie murderer
that's dribbling
all over my bathroom floor?
That kid?
Well, if the kid's right,
he gets killed.
And we'll get it all on tape.
Do we need evidence
against Walter?
There it is.
Look, dude,
I know you're hurt,
you're angry
and all that shit,
but you're here for answers.
So don't push him
with questions
because he'll get suspicious
and we'll screw all this up,
you got me?
Just let him talk
and yo relax.
One more thing,
don't cross your arms
because there's the wire.
Let's try the audio.
Say something.
One, two, three.
That's it.
Perfect.
Piqué over to Shakira.
Do you copy, babe?
Loud and clear, idiot.
How is it looking?
He's just sitting there,
relaxed.
So?
Are you ready?
Ready to take revenge
over that mother fucker?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Go.
Time to go.
- Are you sure about this?
- Go!
Close, close.
Henry, what happened?
He's just standing.
He's taking off, Henry.
He won't do it.
Where is he doing?
Don't!
Just lend me your phone
a second.
Thanks.
He's making a call, Henry.
He can't call anyone.
He'll ruin this.
Who's he calling?
Hang up!
Mother fucker!
Hello?
Nice try, bitch.
José, where
are you?
Walter stood up, Henry.
Son of a bitch!
I just want us to
talk.
Just you and me.
Walter, shut up.
I'll never again
do what you want,
did you get me?
This is just a heads up
to let you know
I'm coming for you.
I didn't burn your house
because I decided
that was nothing.
Remember I know you, bitch.
I'll go for what you care
about the most.
Remember this.
No, José. Wait, José.
Don't hang, José.
Get on!
Are you stupid?
Fucking junkie.
What the hell
was that all about?
What were you
thinking?
- Just stop it.
- Fucking idiot.
There's another way.
- What?
- Yes.
There's another way
to catch him.
A better way.
I know him.
Beto, it's me.
Walter Blanco.
Yes, fine.
I think I might have
another job for your
uncle.