If we tore apart the human body,
if we took all the
chemical elements
and components it's made of,
and put them in a recipient,
we'd find out that body
is made of the following:
63% of hydrogen.
26% of oxygen,
9% of carbon.
Nitrogen.
The calcium of the bones.
Iron.
Sodium.
Don't worry. I'll spare
you the calculation.
This adds up to a total of...
What happens here?
What's missing to complete 100%?
What's the human body made of?
It's the most disgusting thing
that ever happened to me!
That's because you
don't do things right.
You know what,
professor? I tried!
What? What's wrong?
- There, next to your mouth.
- Where? What?
[sound of brush
cleaning the floor]
I hate these shoes.
They seem to be a manicurist's.
Or of one of those women
whose names begin with "Y",
like "Yenny",
or "Yuly" or "Yulitza".
A woman's dignity is
definitely in her shoes!
Then what do you wear them for?
I like the support. My arches
happen to be extremely archy.
You know nothing about women,
do you, Junior?
Get this.
I'll be right back.
- What happened?
- I'm going to make a call.
And why don't
you call from here?
Is it a girl?
No, mom, it's not a female.
Honey, please,
don't say that word.
Don't call women that way.
"Female".
You missed a spot right there.
Should you be up on that ladder?
You're more than welcome
to take over for me up here.
No, no,
no. Walter should be helping you.
I know.
- María?
You've smoked your fair share
of pot in college, didn't you?
Why are you asking me that?
Because there's a neighbor that thinks
her son is smoking, but she's not sure.
- Which neighbor?
- Not even once?
You used to go out
with an anthropologist.
He smoked in front of
me two or three times top.
Do you remember if he changed?
Did his personality
change or something?
Well,
he sort of got on a bad mood.
When he smoked,
he got serious and quiet.
Walter Junior is on pot?
What? No!
No,
no. How could you think Walter--?
Not that I know at least.
Parents are the
last ones to realize.
That's why he didn't
make that call here.
He'd talking to his dealer.
María, María, María,
come here. No.
I'm just asking
because of my neighbor.
Stop making things up, please!
Junior is not on pot,
did you get me?
Yes.
I mean it!
Is it clear to you?
Yes, it's all clear.
Look at me.
Look at me!
You shouldn't do this to anyone.
This here I wouldn't do
this to my worst enemy.
I'm really sorry.
Kill me.
Kill me or let me go.
Just do some shit
but get this off me!
Walter,
you'll have to do something.
How do you know my name?
Because of José.
When he came by to sell your meth,
he told me a lot about you.
He said you're his
chemistry teacher.
You have a son who's retarded.
My son has a motoric condition.
That partner of
yours has a big mouth
and that's not good for the business,
you get me?
You seem to be a
good man. Don't do this.
What do you want me to do?
Let you go as though
we were best friends?
Either that or...
You know.
Do you want me to tell you
what's your real problem?
Your real problem
is sitting upstairs.
It even has a name.
What the hell, man?
He told me my
name! Where I work!
You even told him about my son!
And it's all
because of this shit!
Damn junkie!
This is going down the toilet.
No, don't throw it. That's
worth a lot of money.
It's worth nothing
when you smoke it all.
Get off!
What are you doing?
What's wrong with
you? That stays here!
No, no!
José!
Come here!
Where the hell do
you think you're going?
- You're not going anywhere!
- Stop!
Get off the car!
We've got work to do!
We?
We? Not we,
bitch. You've got work to do!
I did my part! I'm done!
You? Who helped
you clean that shit?
- If--
- I did! And that was your job!
I didn't want to
be part of this!
My whole house smells like
toe cheese and dry cleaning.
Because you didn't
follow my instructions!
Just think whatever
you fucking want,
but we played rock-paper-scissors
and that's sacred.
Just keep your word!
Sure, girl.
Didn't I tell you
what Carlos told me?
He says he's nothing
to do with Johanna.
So now--
Excuse me,
do you have these in purple?
She's a nurse, so she'll do
all the dirty things he
tells her to do at night.
No, sure.
Hey, where have you been?
I called you two hours ago.
I'm sorry,
baby. I'm sort of busy.
There's something important
I want to talk to you about.
- The thing is that--
- What's up?
What's up,
fucker? Against the wall!
Where are you going?
So?
Henry,
don't do that. You scared me.
- You're talking to me.
- Search him.
Thanks, Gómez.
All right. I'm free now,
honey. What is it?
There's something serious
going on with Walter Junior.
How come?
He's doing drugs. He's on pot.
Walter Junior? Come on, María.
María, who told you that?
Cielo. Well, she didn't tell me,
she sorts of thinks so.
She thinks so?
It's just like when a
man goes to the doctor
and says he's got a friend who
suffers from erectile dysfunction.
So I want you to talk to him.
No, hold on. Not me.
That's not my responsibility.
Walter should. Let him do it.
Henry, it'd be much better if
you talked to him. He respect you.
Show him something horrible,
I don't know.
An autopsy from an overdose,
for instance.
Honey, there exist no pictures
of autopsies for pot overdose.
Henry, don't fool me. You
know what I'm talking about.
Show him horrible things,
something that scares him.
Like the consequences
of drug addiction.
No, I don't know.
Honey!
I need you to talk to him
because you can help him.
And if we don't do it,
no one will.
I love you, honey. Bye.
I'm not good at having
open relationships.
I'm so fool that I
end up falling in love.
So are we going out? Wait.
Madam, I'm sorry.
You need to be wearing
footies before you try those on.
I'm extremely clean.
I'm sure you're clean,
but if my boss
comes and sees you
trying those with no socks,
you'll get me in trouble.
All right.
No, it's just that...
Will you try the gray shoes?
I have them at the back.
Don't hang. Hold
on. I'll bring them.
Let's see, boy.
Have you ever been
in a place like this?
No,
uncle. I've just seen it in the news.
They rob with guns and knives
and kill people as well, but that's all.
In the news? They
call me from the news
to interview me and stuff.
But don't get distracted.
No, uncle. I'm paying attention.
You're paying attention?
So if you're paying attention,
what do you think of this place?
What do you mean what
do I think of this place?
Yes. What are your conclusions?
How does it make you feel?
- It's ugly. It's dirty.
- Dirty.
Would you move
to a place like this?
No.
- No?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Why not?
Because I prefer
my home. It's better.
It's good that you
value what you have.
You have to value your house
and value your parents
because they sacrifice for you.
Uncle, why did we come here?
Weren't we going to eat hamburgers?
Yes,
but I took a detour for you to check out
how the other half lives.
Do you get me?
Why didn't we just go
to the hamburger store?
Because that's
not so educational.
- Educational?
- Yes. Pay attention.
You know what they
call this place? Eden.
You know why?
Because it's the paradise
of drug and heroin addicts.
And also of the ones that
are use methanpheta...
- Mine?
- "Mine", good.
I like it. You're
paying attention.
Remember I told
you at your house
that a new drug has
just hit Colombia?
Look, just to put it short.
All these people you see here
would sell their
grandma's coochie for a hit.
You think that's funny?
Tell me, what's funny about it?
The coochie part,
uncle. That's all.
Is it?
How do you think
they got started?
You know that? Tell me,
with what?
With brandy?
No, brandy, bro! With marijuana!
Marijuana! You know marijuana?
Why couldn't they just
begin with brandy or--?
Because that's something
else. This is different.
All right - All right.
Uncle,
why are you telling me all this?
I love you very much, son.
I worry about you.
I don't want anything to happen to you,
OK?
Do you get what
I'm trying to tell you?
Yes, sort of.
"Yes,
sort of." You don't understand shit!
That's the thing with the new
generations. You don't understand anything.
You're audiovisual,
multimedia, viral,
so you don't get shit!
Look.
I'll show you.
Wendy!
Come!
Uncle, do you know that girl?
Princess! Hey!
Do you know that girl?
No,
it's not that I know her. I do-- I don't--
It's not that-- Not closely.
- Uncle, let's go.
- Wait, wait.
Come, come here.
What's up, Wendy?
I'm not doing anything wrong,
all right?
I know. Come here.
This is my nephew. Say hi.
Do I fuck him?
- Let's see...
- No, no, no, uncle.
Oral, manual or full?
- It's $40 half an hour both.
- Wendy, Wendy, Wendy!
We're not here for that.
We're here for him to
learn about other things.
Uncle, why don't we just leave?
Other things,
all right? Do you get me?
What do you put in?
And I'm not talking of dicks.
Are you on the
pipe or the needle?
My only drug is God.
Really? And I have milk teeth.
Speaking of teeth,
let me see yours.
Check out those pearly whites.
Check that out.
That's for smoking meth.
Come on,
ask her whatever you want.
No, no, no.
Take the chance and
ask her whatever you want.
- Let's go, all right?
- Ask her!
- What do you want to ask her?
- Nothing, uncle.
Do you know how she started?
- Smoking pot.
- No.
I began drinking brandy.
Yes, but... But bran--
You mixed that, didn't you?
You like pot, don't you?
- Don't you?
- Why, you got some?
- What? No.
- Uncle.
Are you smoking a joint?
Smoke what? No one is smoking here,
all right?
You brought him to get him high.
What are you talking
about? Get out of here!
Get out!
Get out or I'll call the police!
Uncle, you're a cop.
Yes, I know. I know.
Get lost!
I hope you've learnt the lesson.
Let's go.
Let's eat some hamburgers.
Close, close that!
Who the hell was that?
A cop and a boy.
What did they want? They asked
you about me? What did you tell them?
They didn't even
know what they wanted.
I don't like this
shit. It's so weird.
José, just stop fucking around.
Did you bring it? Get it out.
What's the hurry?
Come on.
KILLING HIM
LETTING HIM LIVE
I'M NOT A MURDERER
KILLING IS BAD
I COULDN'T LIVE WITH IT
IF I LET HIM LIVE,
HE'LL KILL MY FAMILY
- Hello?
- Honey, hello.
I'm sorry I didn't
call you before.
I've been working a lot and...
Well, it's pilled up
and you know how
thing are at the car wash.
I don't have a
single free moment.
I know perfectly well
it's my fault because...
You know what?
You were totally right.
I have to make them
comply with my schedule.
I'll do it. I swear.
Hello? Cielo.
Are you at the car wash?
- Yes.
- I seriously doubt that.
You quitted two weeks ago.
I called asking about you and Ramiro,
your ex-boss,
told me everything.
Even that you insulted him.
Honey, I know it sounds
weird. Just let me get home
and I'll explain everything to you,
all right?
No, I have a better idea.
Stay where you are.
Darling,
what a sec-- Hello? Cielo?
Walter!
I'm hungry!
Are you all right?
I thought you were dead.
How long was I out?
About fifteen minutes.
I've never seen someone knock
themselves out just by coughing.
What happened?
You breathe in the same
thing you used on me?
I have lung cancer.
I'll make you another sandwich.
It's safe. It's not poisoned.
So you're thinking
of killing me?
I mean,
if you've already made a decision.
It's a chance.
Of course it's a chance.
It's quite an obvious chance
since you're a chemist.
You decide whether
you eat it or not.
No, I will...
I've eaten worse
things in my life.
Loco?
They've always called you that?
Yes.
I guess you have a real name.
Domingo.
I'd rather call you that,
if you don't mind.
It sounds more... I
don't know... Human.
I've never liked that name.
It's some old guy's name.
Just call me whatever you want.
So, Domingo, where are you from?
Do you always ask
so much bullshit?
What do you want to know me for?
So that you can't kill me afterwards?
You keep on repeating
I wouldn't kill you.
Maybe I wouldn't.
Maybe I would.
The truth is I'm looking for a
single reason not to kill you.
Any reason. Any.
Persuade me!
Help yourself!
Fine.
If you let me go,
it'll all be all right.
No deaths.
Let's just pretend we never met.
Anyone in your
situation would say that.
That's just survival instinct.
Maybe you're right.
But I'm telling the truth.
I don't know what
else to tell you.
If you don't convince me,
I'll leave you tied there.
So just think a little
bit! Help yourself!
Walter.
- Sit down. Let's talk.
- What for? Will it be any good?
Look, I'm not from here.
I'm from Medellín.
I've been living in
Bogotá for years.
I don't know anything,
not even Cartagena.
But I have lots of
friends from there.
I didn't finish high-school
but I would have
liked to go to college.
I'm really good at Math,
you know?
I guess that's useful
for your business.
In some situations it is,
but in others, it's not.
Sure.
You never wanted to study?
When my dad's restaurant closed,
I had no option but to work.
Did you have a restaurant?
Yes, it was famous.
It was called " El
Escondite del Tragón ".
It sounds familiar.
I told you it was famous.
Wasn't there a commercial
during the matches?
Yes,
it was always the same old one.
My dad used to tell me:
"Son, remember...".
No, wait. Don't say it. Wait.
It was...
"A full stomach makes
for a happy heart
at the Escondite del Tragón,
where you'll have
the best chicharrón!".
Yes, sure!
Pretty moronic. But it did
tend to stick in your head.
No,
besides the music was cheerful. It was...
- Yes.
- I think I've been there.
Didn't you make...?
You made some figures
with the sausages.
Yes. The most famous
dish was the Eiffel Tower.
That's right!
I was there.
What's more,
I met your dad. Did he manage the business?
He's called Domingo,
just like me.
A fat guy with a hairy beard?
That's him.
And did you help him?
Did you work with him?
I worked there for some time
until they closed it
But if you went there long ago,
we probably met.
I used to clean
every day for my dad.
It's incredible where life will take you,
isn't it?
The world is...
It's a small world.
Exactly.
You want another one?
Does José know you have cancer?
No one but you.
Just you.
You're kidding. Not
even your family?
No one.
Why not?
Not a conversation I'm
even remotely ready to have.
So you're cooking meth to leave them money,
I guess.
If that's so, I have money.
I can buy my freedom.
Walter,
you seem to be a nice man.
Good.
Don't ruin your life, man.
I don't know what to do.
You do know what to do.
You know what's right.
I'll get the key.
No.
Can't be.
You're doing the right thing,
Walter.
Would you mind turning around?
The lock is on the other side.
Aren't you angry?
Why do you ask?
I don't know. After what happened,
it'd be normal for you to be angry.
Yes, but we said we'd let this go,
right?
Yes, that's right.
Besides, I just want to go home.
Me too.
Come on, Walter.
Let me go.
The moment I do are
you gonna stick me
with that broken piece of plate?
I'm sorry.
What's this shit?
Dude, what's up?
I'm all bitten, damn.
It must have been the fleas
because the hotel is full of them.
Do they bite you too?
Not any more. I
must be out of blood.
I think I still have them on.
Check me out.
Wendy!
Shake it out so you
don't take it with you.
I'm taking a shower
to get this shit off.
Hey, José!
Don't get in there. I don't
even shower myself in it.
Then I rather shower at home?
You bet.
Good luck.
Hi, José.
Did I scare you?
- Rosita, just a little bit.
- How are you?
- Fine, madam.
When are you taking
me for a ride in this car?
Whenever you tell me.
All right. We just
have to set a date.
- Yes, madam.
- Is there something wrong?
- No, it's all right.
- Let me know if you need anything.
- Yes, madam.
- See you. Bye.
Hello?
Damn.
Settle down, please.
Pay attention!
Professor Walter
Blanco called this morning
to say he's feeling
under the weather today.
So the class will be different
today. We'll watch a movie.
It's about carbon.
It's an interesting
and educational movie,
so I suggest you pay attention
because he'll ask you
questions next class.
Enjoy it.
What's the human body made of?
What's missing to
complete that 100%?
I can't give you a
scientific answer.
You have to find
out. All I can tell you
is that it's not a
chemical element.
It's something that
goes beyond that.
And you're totally free
to decide what that is.
The soul?
Or is it just emptiness?
Just that.
What's up, Gómez?
Let's see what you think.
This is quite weird.
For me this is not a matter
between drug buyers and dealers.
Nobody came way the
hell out here just to buy.
You know what I think?
It's a cook site.
No,
that's not possible. This is too small.
Who would cook
cocaine here? No one.
No,
there are not just cocaine labs.
A meth lab fits
perfectly in this van.
No.
No what? Stop
saying no to everything.
It's been searched
already. There's nothing.
No pipes, no tubes, no nothing.
- Is this Loco's car?
- Yes.
Who searched it?
Let's go then!
Do you want me to show
you how to search a car?
Stand there.
Be careful. Be careful.
You know what's
the thing with this?
You do it the wrong way.
This is not simple. No.
You have to touch, bro.
With sensitivity.
- Sensitivity.
- Yes, sir.
Just like my masseuse,
with sensitivity.
That's it. With
sensitivity. Look.
You have to let the car
talk. You have to touch it
and it'll start talking. For example,
check this out.
This is supposed
to get here.
Look.
Yes!
Look, dude, what's this?
Excuse me, what's this?
Methamphetamine.
Methamphetamine!
You can't teach me
how to do my job.
You know what is needed
in this job? Sensitivity.
I've never seen it in this size.
This is not produced
in Colombia.
You know what I'm thinking?
That they killed this guy
and who knows
where they took him.
- There's no corpse.
- And there will be no corpse
because they made him disappear.
So we have no
snitch. We're fucked.
Hey, what did you find?
Show me.
What did I tell you, Gomez?
Cielo.
We have to talk.