Did you understand?
Saúl!
Tell me if you understood.
Saúl, shut up for a second!
Damn it!
Listen. I need you to give her
all the money.
Put it in garbage bags
if it's necessary.
Give her every cent.
Understood?
You've reached the Blancos.
We can't come to the phone now.
Leave a message.
Hi, Cielo.
It's me, Walter.
Listen...
I wanted to tell you
that I was thinking
of you and the kids, and...
Well, I love you very much.
Did you hear?
Hello. Can I help you?
Gustavo Cortés.
Excuse me?
Gustavo Cortés, your boss.
I need to talk with him.
No, Mr. Gustavo isn't here.
He is here.
I saw his car
in the parking lot.
He was here,
but he had to leave.
He's here!
Go and tell him
that Walter Blanco
needs to talk with him.
He knows what it's about.
I'll be waiting.
- Hello.
- Walter.
What do you think you're doing?
- Where's Jose?
- I'm with him.
And he's fine.
Do you want me to believe you?
I'm telling the truth.
Do you want me to swear
on the Holy Cross?
- No, don't swear. I want proof.
- Hold on.
- What's up?
- Jose.
Jose. Where're you?
- I'm with Mario.
- Jose...
Does he have a gun on you?
No.
Then tell me what's going on.
We're driving away from Bogotá.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
We're going North.
Why are you going there?
Jose, do you know exactly
where they're taking you?
No, no idea.
Put me through Mario again.
What's up, Walter?
Hello again.
Mario,
tell me exactly
what is going on.
What you need to do
is to go back to your lab
and get on with the cook.
You'll have to muddle through.
He'll be with me today.
No, listen, Mario.
- Goodbye, Walter.
- It doesn't--
Don't hang up on me, Mario.
Sir, sir.
That area is restricted. Sir!
You're not allowed back there.
This area is for employees only.
Leave immediately
or I'll call the guard.
What are you planning to do?
Are you planning
to leave me in some ditch
or throw me into the river?
What do you care?
I thought
everything was the same for you.
You're right.
But listen to me.
You better shoot straight,
or I'll slice off your other ear
before going.
What do you have there?
What we all want.
Let's go.
Or are you staying there?
We have to do it six times.
With a lot of miles in between.
Hurry up.
I'd like to finish before dark.
Look what he did.
He was completely crazy.
He's a combination
of a drug dealer and Bambi.
Is this Heisenberg?
I thought you've caught
him
a long time ago.
No, they caught a man
called Fredy Liso.
Those inexperienced
thought he was Heisenberg.
Are we sure this is him?
Yes, I think so.
Why was he killed?
Is there any rival drug gang
trying to move him away?
Do you have any name
to investigate?
I'd like to help you,
but I only know two persons
involved with methamphetamines,
especially with blue crystals.
The first one
is a big silly man
called El Mono.
He isn't a drug dealer.
The other one
is José Miguel Rosas.
He and I have a history.
Do you remember I was suspended?
Yes, yes.
Is possible that Rosas
is the killer
of the big cook?
I would be surprised
because he wasn't brave enough.
Okay.
All we have
is this composite picture.
According to the neighbors,
he entered the house,
inspected the body,
analyzed the crime scene,
and left without saying a word.
- I don't recognize him.
- Keep that copy.
Is this all you have?
We have a couple of prints
to investigate.
I'll get you updated.
Okay.
Ramón, I really appreciate
that you keep me informed,
but now that...
Heisenberg is dead,
I don't have...
I can't help you any more.
Why do you say that?
Henry, I said it,
and I repeat it:
Your help is very important
now and ever.
I appreciate your words, but...
But I'm done here.
Well, okay.
If you're done, you're done.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much, Henry.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
I can't walk you to the door.
Don't worry.
It's okay.
I'll call you.
Hello!
What are you doing?
Watching.
Why?
That's why you brought me here.
I understood it.
I haven't say that.
No, but it's obvious.
If I'm going to be here
as your backup,
shouldn't I have those things
that backups have?
What do you mean?
- Well, a weapon, a gun.
- No.
It doesn't make sense
that I'm standing here,
watching all around,
without a gun.
If something happens here,
it's useless for you
and dangerous for me.
If you have a gun
is useless for me
and dangerous for you.
Get in. Let's go.
Come on, man.
If you haven't brought me here
to watch or to be your backup,
can you explain me
why the hell am I here?
You haven't brought me here
to hold a conversation.
You aren't good at it.
- Can I smoke or not?
- No!
Chips?
I'll light one.
Do you know
I got your plan?
Can I tell you?
Do I have an option?
You want to bore me
until I'm death.
Am I right?
Congratulations, Mario.
Mission accomplished.
I'm about to shot myself.
Come on, Mario.
Let's talk seriously.
I know how the system works.
The hidden things,
the money bags.
I used a similar system
with my partners.
Obviously, the team I led
didn't deal
with the amount of money
you deal with.
But the scheme or the concept
are very similar, aren't they?
This thing of keeping
supplier and distributors
separated from each other
is very well thought.
It's very smart and useful.
Well done!
You do it very well!
If we're working together,
don't you think it'd be good
if we, at least,
talk to each other?
I've been talking all day,
but you didn't say a word.
You just take me
from one place to another,
taking the money.
Honestly,
I'd like to know something.
Listen.
I know I'm here
to do some work, right?
- I'm the man for the job.
- No.
You aren't the man for the job.
You can't be the man
for the job.
I had the man for the job,
but I don't have him anymore.
Do you remember?
What matters
is that you aren't the one.
Then what am I doing here?
I don't know!
It's not my call.
I do what I know best.
I obey.
I receive an order,
and I obey it.
Now you'll do
what I tell you.
- What is it?
- You'll stay there.
Remain quiet and in silence
until we've collected
all the money.
Any doubt?
I always have second thoughts.
Every day, every time.
Well, that's completely normal.
But we must be confident.
You have a solid business plan.
- Yes.
- Your expectations
are realistic.
Let alone your safety.
You're doing perfectly fine.
- Everything will be fine.
- Okay. Walter.
Walter.
- Shall we sign?
- Yes, sure. Of course.
No, no, no. You sign first.
So.. this is yours.
I'll bring these documents
to the notary's office
to certify the purchase.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- And, of course.
Next week,
I'll be the first one
to wash my car there.
- The first one is free.
- Okay.
You'll be charged
the second time!
Perfect!
- Have a nice day.
- Walter, have a nice day.
- Thank you very much.
- Good bye.
We're officially
the owners of the car wash.
How are you feeling?
And you? How are you feeling?
- Nervous. I'm scared.
- Why?
We have to do it right.
We'll be fine.
We're doing this right.
Will we?
Please!
I have to hear it.
- I guarantee it!
- Okay, fine.
If we're going to do this,
I mean,
we're really going to do this.
We have to promise each other
there won't be more secrets.
There can't be any mistakes
like before.
We have to be completely honest.
I'm all for that.
- Absolutely!
- Good. Okay.
Good.
How about a drink to celebrate?
Yes, yes. Definitely.
Let's celebrate!
- I have a bottle in the fridge.
- I hope it isn't expensive.
No, of course.
Nothing flamboyant.
Something simple.
- A simple drink.
- Yes, yes, yes.
But it has its effect.
There's a message.
I haven't noticed.
Hi, Cielo.
It's me, Walter.
Listen. I wanted to tell you
that I was thinking
of you and the kids, and...
Well, I love you very much.
Did you hear?
These sheets smell different.
Why?
I changed the soap powder.
A long time ago.
I like it.
I like you.
It must be the new look.
You didn't notice, did you?
Of course I noticed!
- I was about to tell you, but--
- Liar!
- What?
- You're a liar!
I didn't do anything.
You're being mean!
Do you want to have dinner
with María and Henry tomorrow?
If you aren't busy.
Yes, yes. I'm free.
I like that.
María says only us
and those rocks
he's collecting--
Minerals.
They're minerals.
Well, that.
Only us and the minerals
make Henry leave the room.
Mom, I'm home!
Shit!
Hi, Junior!
Dad!
Are you here?
Yes.
We'll be right there.
We're having a conversation.
Okay.
Shut up!
Did you have to tell him?
He was going to notice.
My car was outside.
He'll make questions.
What are we going to tell him?
He'll ask about our situation.
I don't know.
What should we tell him?
Perhaps you should move back in.
That would make it easier.
I don't know.
It'd be easier
to explain to everyone.
Don't you think so?
I have to get back to work.
I'm running late.
I have a shift now.
Hey!
Listen up!
This is a two-man job!
I can't do it alone!
I'm done! That's it!
It's senseless.
Nothing else happens
until I get my partner back.
Where's Jose?
I need him here.
You have me down here alone.
I'm doing the job of two men.
Understood?
This is senseless.
It's counterproductive.
And it's dangerous!
Jose operates that machine.
I don't do that.
That's one of the many things
he does around in the lab!
That keeps us on schedule.
I suggest that you get him back.
Are you listening to me?
Where do you want it?
This is the last one, isn't it?
I've been counting.
And this is the last one.
[engine starting
and speeding up]
You have to pick me up.
I'm two blocks
from the north warehouses,
where we do our collections.
Yes, at Juanita's store.
I'll be waiting.
Cancel that.
You don't know
what happened to me.
I was there,
and a few men approached.
One had a gun or a shotgun.
I don't know.
He got off,
and came after me.
The other one was blocking
the street on a motorcycle.
They were going to rip us off!
I swear it!
I didn't have a choice.
I had to put it in reverse.
I think I slammed
into the guy's car.
And I almost ran over
the motorcycle guy.
He almost fell
on some barbwire.
He fell down.
There were sparks.
I swear to God
I'm telling the truth.
Yes, I saw it.
What did you see?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
Do it.
You've earned it.
- Really, Mario?
- Yes. Let's go.
- Good morning.
- Good morning!
Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
- Do you want some juice?
- No, coffee.
- Coffee?
I didn't know
you drink coffee now.
I also started tying
my own shoelaces, too.
Sure! You're being funny.
That's good.
You're growing up.
- Milk and sugar?
- No. I'll have it black.
Black. Wonderful!
That's good.
- Hey, dad.
- Tell me.
I was thinking,
and I wanted
to tell you something.
Sure, tell me.
I wanted to tell you
that I like having you back.
I like being around, too.
I like to be back.
Mom said that on Tuesday
you're moving back home.
- Did she tell you that?
- Yes.
SOLUCIONES SILVA
On Tuesday.
We'll see.
It's nice.
Jose.
Jose!
Hey.
What are you doing?
Breaking crystal.
It's part of our job.
I'm not talking about that.
What are you doing here now?
Who brought you here?
I didn't see your car.
Mario dropped me off.
Jose.
Stop it.
I'm talking to you.
- Walter, what do you want?
- What happened yesterday¡
Where were you?
I was out with Mario.
Out?
Yes, he needed help
to pick up the money.
What money?
I don't know.
From the business.
They hide it. Mario picks it up.
I watch his back.
What?
No, no, no.
Hold on.
Are you watching Mario's back?
No!
Sorry for laughing.
It's a good joke.
Listen, Walter?
Stop talking without knowing.
For your information,
they tried to rob us.
I prevented them
from robbing our money.
They were after me,
but I drove away.
So this time,
I did my job.
And right now,
I'm doing my job, too.
If you aren't going to help me,
let me work
because I don't have time.
You don't have time?
No, I'm going out
with Mario again this afternoon.
Really? Again? Why?
Apparently, I have two jobs now.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Any injuries?
- No.
One twisted ankle.
That's it.
Nothing too bad.
It all went
like you thought it would.
I will, of course, reimburse you
to the damage to your vehicle.
Okay.
Any questions?
More than a
few.
But I know I shouldn't ask.
What matters
is that it all went through
according to your plan.
José Miguel is convinced
that he's a hero.
Very good.
The idea of owning a car wash
scares me.
But then I remembered
that I studied for that.
I'm an accountant.
I'm prepared
for running this business.
- What a nice baby!
- In this case,
the business is already running,
so it's much faster.
Of course!
I think we'll have to do
plenty of changes.
Hiring people, for example.
Beautiful Valentina.
Look at me.
May I have some wine?
No.
Well, we want to...
The idea is to succeed
in order to keep
all the current employees.
I really think
that if we do good,
in a couple of years
we may buy another one.
Or even sooner.
Are you going to put
Junior to work?
No! I'd rather study
than having my mom as my boss.
Hey, didn't you think
of including Valentina
in the advertisement?
As a pet or what?
Silly you!
As a marketing strategy.
People will think
it's a baby wash,
not a car wash.
Don't be silly.
Beautiful babies are used
in all kind of advertisement.
If I saw Valentina
in a big poster,
I'd wash my car there
every day.
Can't you use me
for the picture?
No, we're saving you
for your mother's next business:
the house of terror.
Walter, do you want more wine?
There's more in the kitchen.
No, no, no. I'll get it.
What will you do with Valentina?
You can't take her there.
It's full of fumes
and disgusting people.
María!
Am I lying?
Aren't there fumes?
And are people nice?
No, please.
Did you hire models
to work in your car wash?
Luckily, there's a good nursery
five minutes from there.
I can visit her anytime.
I want to congratulate you
because you started
a family business.
- You share it.
- Yes, yes.
You'll see the results!
We'll get the keys tomorrow.
Walter! Will you drink
all the wine there?
I'm sorry.
I'm coming.
Have you changed gaming
for this?
Why do you ask him that?
It's a joke.
I always joke with him.
I know, but Walter
needs your support right now.
He needs positivism, motivation
to recover, right Cielo?
Yes.
I don't think it's bad
that my father earns money.
Let's change the subject.
Hey, uncle.
What happened
with the case of the crazy man
who used to sing karaoke?
I'm not in the case any more.
I gave the information
to Homicides.
It's closed case to me.
The crazy man
who used to sing karaoke?
It seems like a horror film.
The man wasn't crazy.
Honey, what's that word
that isn't "crazy"?
- Eccentric.
- Eccentric! He was...
- He's a wealthy crazy man.
- Yes.
- Who's that man?
- Was.
He was killed.
A meth cook.
One of the best ones.
He was very good
for that stuff.
He was a genius.
He was an absolute genius!
If he had used his brain
to do something good,
he would have helped
humanity a lot.
I'm serious.
He was wonderful!
How many geniuses are there in
the world?
You can count them on one hand.
- He was one of them.
- Hey, hey, hey. Henry.
- It's a personality.
- Hey, hey. Henry, I'm sorry.
I know I'm nosing around
in something
that isn't my business.
But I don't agree.
- What? Which part?
- Well...
The notebook you showed me.
That notebook!
I saw it.
And this is just
my humble opinion.
He wasn't a genius.
Those were the notes of a man
who wants to follow a routine.
Someone who's copying
the work of a master.
I know what I'm talking about.
I've spent my entire life
around students.
It's typical.
Do you know what I think?
If I were you,
I'd think it twice.
Perhaps, your genius
is still out there.
POLICE ANTI-NARCOTICS DEPARTMENT
CHICKEN BROTHERS AND CO.
What's
that?
Hi, honey. I called Ramón.
I asked him to bring me
the information
on the case I told you
- The karaoke man.
- Yes.
I wanted to analyze it.
- Again.
- Okay.
I'm sorry for the mess!
Look what I've done.
It doesn't matter, my love.
Do you want a cup of coffee?
Yes. Thank you.
- Okay.
What have you found?
There's something strange.
This man, Guido Bermúdez,
is vegetarian, vegan.
Everything he buys is organic.
He eats tofu and that stuff.
But, now
there's something
I don't understand.
It's the napkin found
in the crime scene.
Tell me why a strict vegan
was at a place
like Chicken Brothers and Co.?
Don't you think it's strange?