Have you brought your passport?
This is a private jet,
but the entry is legal.
Yes, it's here.
What's the matter?
Will we travel alone?
Aren't we going to take
our escorts?
We don't need them.
Let's go. Let's go.
Jose, you can do this.
You have reached
Walter Blanco.
I can't pick up the phone
at this moment.
At the tone,
please state your name
and the reason for your call.
Thank you.
Third try.
Walter, if you're there,
please pick up.
Well, I really wanted
to do this together,
but Junior is awake
and he will notice it.
I'll do it on my own.
- Hi, mom.
- My love!
Happy birthday!
Thanks, mom.
I thought you might sleep
through your 16 birthday.
And I thought that moms
would not bother much by now.
That is never going to happen,
my love.
Well, honey.
since it's almost noon,
I think your first
big birthday decision
- is breakfast or lunch.
- Breakfast.
Great!
Can you do me a favor?
I never got the paper.
They must have left it outside,
can you grab it for me?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Hey! There's no paper here!
Surprise!
Honey, this is a present
from your father and myself.
What do you think?
I really did
a lot of research.
This car just really
stood out to me.
I also picked up the color.
Come, take a look.
Later we'll install the alarm.
That's it now.
Take a look.
It's got a ton
of electric features,
a solid engine,
a really big one
that makes a lot of noise.
And it's automatic,
so it's easy for you to drive.
And for your music,
it has 'RP4.'
MP4, mom.
Isn't it cool?
'Cool'?
Cool.
Isn't that what you say?
Yes, mom, cool.
Chévere.
You want to take it for a spin?
Why don't we first
have breakfast?
Yes, yes. It's not good
to drive on an empty stomach.
Yes, yes.
Come on, my love.
- Yes, Francisca?
- He's here.
Bad idea.
This is a bad idea.
Hello.
- Saúl, what should I tell him?
- Send him in.
Hehe! Mr. Silva!
Come in!
- Nice to meet you. Sit down.
- Thank you.
I'm truly sorry,
but I really
have no idea
what am I doing here.
Does it have something to do
with my creditors?
- Creditors?
- Yes.
Ehm... No.
I'll cut right to the chase.
Please.
I have some bad news.
Lately, that's nothing new
in my life. Believe me.
Your aunt Virginia is dead.
I'm sorry, who?
Your great-aunt.
Virginia.
She lived in Chile.
This happened
some eight years ago,
and you are the only family
she has left.
No. I've never heard of her.
Well, maybe your family
is quite reserved, right?
Now that I think about it,
I do have good news.
Your aunt left you
a sizable state.
- What?
- Yes.
This patrimony was frozen
all this time
while they were looking
for an heir.
And now they've found you.
I'm sorry,
but this is quite odd for me.
The Chilean authorities
were tracking her family
and they've found your father,
but he's dead, right?
Yes, my dad
died a while ago.
That's right.
So you are
the primary beneficiary.
Are you telling me
that I will receive money
from an inheritance?
And do I need
to pay taxes for that?
I'm only asking
because I'm currently
putting in order my
situation
with the National Tax
Agency,
and I like to keep
everything...
- good.
- I understand. Yes.
The Chilean authorities
solved all the problems
related to taxes,
and the Colombian too.
But my fees...
are also covered.
So you'll receive
a clean amount.
- A net amount
- Okay.
How much are we talking about?
It's...
621,372...
- US Dollars.
- What?
With 33 cents.
God!
I can't believe this.
This way, Mr. Gustavo.
This way, please.
Follow me.
- Gentleman, how are you?
- Fine, thank you.
That's nice to hear.
And where's Mr. Eladio?
Let's do the cooking first.
Who's the chemist?
The kid is the chemist.
I don't fucking believe it!
This fucking kid?
Are you fucking with me
or what?
Am I laughing?
Well, we've had the pleasure
of meeting each other.
Let's get to work!
Is that okay, Mr. Gustavo?
Where's the phenylacetic acid?
We develop it ourselves here.
We have all the ingredients
in order to do so.
Gustavo, I really don't know
how to work like this.
I need to work
like we do in Colombia.
What's going on, gentlemen?
Mr. Rosas thought
the phenylacetic acid
would be synthesized
on his arrival.
Any kid with Chemistry
from school can do that.
I won't allow these rookies
to come into my kitchen
and tell me how to do things.
Least of all an escuincle
crying like a baby
who knows nothing
about mixing acid.
Listen, man,
things are quite simple.
If you want to learn
how to do my product,
you are going to have to do it
my own way,
the right way, okay?
You're over your head, cabrón.
You're being disrespectful.
Either you get me what I want
or we won't cook shit.
How long will it take you
to get him what he needs?
I don't know.
Several hours at least.
How can you not know?
We're not going anywhere.
We have all the time
in the world. We can wait.
It'll give us time to talk
about the state of this lab.
Now, let's get to it.
This place is disgusting.
Don't you have
cleaning standards?
The first thing that we'll do
is to clean all the surfaces.
We'll clean
all the work instruments.
Look at this shit!
I'd tell you to clean up
every possible source
of contamination,
like flies and all that,
but it's impossible to do that
in the open air.
We'll make this place
shiny as a new penny.
Only then we cook.
Listen, pinche escuincle,
who the fuck
do you think you are?
"Listen, pinche escuincle,
who the--".
I have no idea what 'pinche'
or 'chingada' means.
I don't know what you're saying.
But you know who I am?
I'm the person your chief
brought in from Colombia
to show you how it's done.
If this is how you run your lab,
I wonder why you're not cooking
but tacos in Tijuana,
or someplace else.
There's still time
for that, though.
If you want to learn
how to do things right,
stop acting
like a soap opera diva
and get to work, alright?
Come on, motherfuckers!
Let's get to work.
Do what he says.
You've heard him.
Let's get to work.
Walter!
You have reached
Walter Blanco.
I can't pick up the phone
at this moment.
At the tone,
please state your name
and the reason for your call.
Thank you.
Dad! You there?
I'm outside.
I know you're home.
Your car is here.
You missed
my birthday party.
Tell me what's going on.
If you don't pick up,
I'll call an ambulance.
Come in if you're coming in.
What happened?
What happened to you?
I got into a fight.
A fight?
What do you mean a fight?
Are you going
to talk to me here?
Junior, not now.
Okay.
- What are you doing?
- I'm calling mom.
Don't do that.
Let's talk this out
you and me.
Well, then talk.
Look, I appreciate
that you're concerned,
but I'm fine.
Just don't call your mother.
Why not?
I was gambling.
If you tell your
mother...
I would never,
never hear the end of it.
You know that.
So please,
can we just keep this
between us?
Please.
I don't understand.
How'd you get into a fight?
And with who?
I made a mistake, okay?
And it's my own fault.
I had it coming.
No.
Dad, it's okay.
It's all my fault.
The thing is
I just... I'm sorry.
Dad, it's okay.
- No.
- Calm down.
No, don't cry.
That's it.
Are these the painkillers?
Yes.
When did you take the last one?
Yes, it was...
Around... Ehm...
It's fine.
Junior, Junior.
How was your birthday?
- It was fine.
- Really?
Yes.
- Get some rest.
- Yes.
Yes.
Hey, listen...
The new car?
Did you drive it here?
Yes.
You like it?
Sure. I do.
It drives great.
That's good, Jose.
I'm glad for you.
I'm sorry.
The important thing
is that Chemistry
is an exact science.
The numbers must be precise
in order to do everything okay.
Yeah?
That's red
phosphorous.
It's alright.
We need to put in a bit
of potassium permanganate.
Please, put on the masks.
Excuse me.
There you go.
Let's see, pinche escuincle,
if you're as good as you think.
My personal record
is 88 percent.
Many tried to beat me,
but no one could.
Yes! 96 percent!
There you go, fucker!
Well done.
Very well done.
First of many.
- Great!
- What do you mean?
What do I mean?
You're staying
to work with us now.
You belong to the cartel now.
- Hello.
- Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine, and you?
I'm fine. Yeah.
But your mom
is probably very worried.
No.
It's no problem.
I've talked to her last night.
You did?
I told her
I was staying at Luis'.
I've kept your secret.
So? Are you in pain
this morning?
No, no.
No, I'm perfect.
The thing is that...
I took some painkillers
for the pain
that I had
after the surgery.
Those painkillers
are quite strong
and I've made the mistake
of mixing them with beers...
Bad choice!
Look, I...
I'm really sorry.
Yesterday, I shouldn't have made
you go through everything I did.
- I screwed your birthday!
- No.
- No, you didn't, man.
- Junior.
I'm your father and...
Look, I don't want you
to think of me as if--
I don't want that
what happened yesterday--
You know?
What do you mean?
I don't get it.
My father died
when I was six years old.
You know that.
He had Huntington's disease.
What's that?
It's a disease that affects
portions of the brain
and muscle control.
Eventually,
after certain amount of time,
it leads to dementia.
It's horrible.
And it's a genetic disease.
And well, my mom...
Well, she was dying of distress,
and she was convinced
that I had the same disease.
So they made
several tests on me,
until, finally,
I came up clean.
And the truth is
that when I was
four or five,
my father fell very ill.
He would almost never
leave the hospital.
And I was never allowed
to see him.
And so my mother
would tell me stories
about my father.
She would tell me
all kinds of stories.
I knew about his personality,
how he treated people,
how he dressed.
He loved meat!
Just like you.
But the truth is
that when he died
somehow I remembered him
for all those things
that my mother would tell me.
And, deep down,
I think I was pretending.
I was pretending
and I thought that I had lived
all those things.
The only one real
actual memory of my father
it must've been
right before he died.
My mother took me
to the hospital.
And I remember
the smell in the hospital.
It was awful.
The chemicals...
It was...
a penetrating smell.
It was as if they used up
every single disinfectant
and cleaning product
so you could forget
they had sick people there.
Then, we went into the room
where he was,
and we saw him.
He was lying on the bed,
all twisted up.
And my mom
sat me next to him.
I remember
I was very afraid.
And suddenly,
he looked at me.
But I wasn't sure
the he knew who I was
because it was as if he was
looking into emptiness.
In the meantime,
my mom was trying to talk about
some cheerful stuff,
you know,
to ease up the situation,
but I only remember
his breathing.
It was a rattling sound.
It was as if you were
shaking a maraca.
But anyway...
Junior, do you why
I'm telling you this?
No, why?
Because I don't want you
to remember me
like you saw me yesterday.
I don't want that
to be the memory
you have of me
when I'm gone.
Remembering you that way
wouldn't be so bad.
The bad way to remember you
would be the way you've been
this whole last year.
At least last night
you were real.
A real person, you know?
And I prefer you like that,
like real person,
a person that feels,
that cries,
that doesn't hide
what's going on with him,
a person like everybody else.
I prefer you that way, dad.
Bye, dad.
Thank you for
everything.
- I love you so much.
- And I love you too.
Be careful on the way back.
See you.
Walter,
shouldn't you be
some place else right now?
Saúl, you can't come in here
like it's an every day thing.
Every person in Colombia
who watches bad television
recognize your face.
And that's about everybody.
They know that us, the stars,
need to wash our cars
once in a while, right?
Look, I wouldn't have come
if this wasn't important.
What's going on?
Well, I met with this guy,
Ernesto Silva,
just like you told me to.
And now it's a good time
to remember you
this was a bad idea.
A very bad idea.
You said that many times,
and I told you
I preferred that
to going to prison
for tax evasion.
- Let's move on.
- That's fine.
I gave him the money
you told me to.
Great, and what happened?
It's incredible, right?
He believed the story
of the great-aunt,
the inheritance and all that.
How naive!
That's the reason why
so many people get cheated on.
Well, that's perfect.
That's what we need.
He bought the story.
When you throw people a number
with many zeros on the right,
they are ready to
believe
anything you tell them.
Then what's the problem?
I don't understand.
Well since I'm not so good
as you are,
I decided to track
all his movements.
I wanted to see
if he would do with the
money
what we expected of him,
if he would pay
the Tax Administration.
- Did he pay?
- I have a friend
who knows a guy
who is a hacker.
And he got himself into
the personal banking accounts
of Mr. Silva,
and look what he found
three hours after
receiving the money.
He bought a car?
- A luxury car?
- A brand new luxury car.
He spent a lot of money.
He spent 200,000 dollars
in just this one thing.
Look, I hate to say this
to you,
but I have a moral
obligation
to do so,
and I'm going to do
"I told you so, Cielito."
Where's Ernesto right now?
Yes, it was short interval
that I had
due to a financial situation,
but in a week
I'll be 100 percent again.
Yes, in the same place.
Well, thank you.
Hey, I'm sorry about
this mess,
but I preferred
to bring it all here
and not renting a warehouse.
I understand.
So, how are you?
It's so nice to see you.
Well, I wanted to see
how you were doing.
So, tell me,
how's everything?
I'm perfectly fine, you know?
Some good things
have happened lately.
I think that fate
is trying to teach me
something really
important
because some good things
have been happening.
- Well, not good, fantastic!
- Wow!
Yes, in fact, my company
will be back in business soon.
- Really? That's amazing!
- Yes.
And how did that happen?
I received some money
I wasn't expecting.
I think that my dad
is helping me from heaven.
Yes, that must be it!
- Yes.
Is that why you have
a brand new luxury car
parked outside?
- Is it?
... yes.
That car is actually
a marketing action.
I wanted to get back
all my clients
and that's a sign of trust.
Sure.
- Economic trust.
Yes, I see.
So, and what about
the Tax Administration thing?
- Is it solved?
- It's fine.
It's really going on well,
on the right track.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Did you pay?
- No.
But I'm waiting
for the right time to do it.
I see, and when is that?
I don't know.
I have other things
to take care of
which are quite important.
I'm trying to get
better advice
to see if they can
lower the interests.
- Do you want more coffee?
- No! No, Ernesto, please.
They won't lower the interests.
You should be thankful
they gave you more time to pay.
You need to pay those taxes.
You have to pay the tickets
that you have,
and stay out of legal trouble.
That must be your priority.
No, my priority
is to save my company
and to save the employees
of my company.
That's my priority!
But in order to do that
you need to control
your financial situation.
I don't understand why
we are having this
conversation
in this moment.
Our relationship
ended because you wanted to.
I don't understand why now
you're getting involved
in my stuff.
Because this affect us both.
No, no. It doesn't affect
you.
I told you a thousand
times.
You are not going
to get involved in this.
Ernesto!
You have to pay the taxes
by the end of the month.
That's what you have to do.
It's quite simple!
- We'll see what we do.
- No, we won't see anything.
My company is affected
by your made-up accounts.
I need to leave this house
convinced that you'll pay.
I think you are out of place
at this particular moment
coming into my house
and getting yourself involved
in my stuff
and talking to me like that.
Cielo, I'm going to ask you
to leave through that door.
Get the hell out of here
and leave me alone!
Where do you think
you've got
those 621,372
dollars?
You really think
you have a great-aunt in Chile?
It was you?
He!
What do you think?
Fucker!
What's this then?
Don't I get to decide
if I want to stay here?
I promise you
that we will all stay
or we will all leave.
Calm down.
Get up.
Gustavito!
- Mr. Eladio.
- You look good, cabrón!
Thank you!
You too look wonderful.
Come here.
It's so nice to see you!
I'm glad you finally
came to reason.
I'm sorry what happened
with your friend that
time.
It's forgotten, right?
Of course, Mr. Eladio.
It's been many years.
It's forgotten now.
- Really?
- Of course.
And which one of these fuckers
is the cook?
Let me introduce him
to you.
Jose, this is Mr.
Eladio.
He's your new boss.
Nice to meet you.
He's a chemist with no degree.
And what the fuck do
I care?
He's better than you
with your degrees and shit.
Can you believe it,
Gustavito?
Welcome to the family, man.
Don't be shy.
And what's that?
- It's a gift, Mr. Eladio.
- For me?
Of course it's for you!
- Open it.
- And what's this?
Allow me, Mr. Eladio.
Get the fuck out of
here!
How did you get it?
It's a token of respect
to honor a renewed friendship.
Look, guys!
Bring the glasses!
Fuckers.
I wish I didn't
have to share this shit.
Can you believe it?
It's your choice.
It's your bottle.
- Let's share it then.
- Perfect.
Look.
Pour it to the guys.
And don't you fucking spill
a single drop
or I'll cut your hand off.
- Here, this one's for you.
- No, no. He can't drink.
He's a recovered addict.
He'll cook better
if he stays sober.
- I'm sorry. Help yourself.
- Perfect.
- Let's toast then.
- Of course.
- Well, then, cheers!
- Cheers!
Cheers, cabrones!
Cheers!
It's the nectar from the Gods!
Thank you, Gustavito!
Let's not talk
any more business.
I brought you a present, cabrón.
- And from Colombia too.
- No.
Yes!
Bring out the girls, fuckers!
Hi, handsome!
Do you want something?
- No, I'm fine.
- You sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Pay attention to my guests!
Sebas, serve him!
Cheer up, Gustavito,
you're ruining my party.
I'm sorry, Mr. Eladio.
I think I'm just tired
from the trip.
I said I was sorry,
what else do you want me to do?
I did what I had to do.
This is business.
I understand.
I would have done the same
if I were you.
There's no room
for emotions here.
Really, Gustavo.
I know. Mr. Eladio, please.
- Can I use your bathroom?
- Sure!
- Miguel!
- Sir.
Come here!
Show my friend Gustavo
where the bathroom is, please.
Yes, sir.
- Thank you. I'll be back soon.
- Sure.
- Miguel.
- Yes?
- Keep an eye on him.
- Yes, sir.
Get in.
Cheer up, man!
You are going
to have a good time in here.
Mr. Eladio!
Juan!
What's going on?
I don't know,
cabrón.
This is business.
No emotions.
Motherfuckers.
Listen to me!
Mr. Eladio is dead!
The bosses are dead!
There's no one
left to fight for!
Fill up your pockets and leave!
Or stay here to fight me,
and die!
Hang on. Hang on.
- Hurry up.
- Come on, come on.