The thing is the zebra
got stucked
and the lions came
and killed it.
The worse part
was that the zebra
was not dead yet
and they ate it.
You should have seen
how the zebra was doing.
That's more sanguinary
than any movie I've
seen.
Imagine watching that
while queuing at the bank
at noon.
No!
I understand
that nature is
nature
and it's cruel
and all that shit,
but that should be
censured.
After all,
it's a murderer
during day time.
Hey, are you alive?
is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You know what?
I've been thinking
and there's
something
I don't understand.
I mean, we're
supposed
to be doing this
like the bests,
right?
We're doing it
with all the equipment,
all the budget,
we're the major league,
right?
Then why don't we have
some equipment
maintainer guys?
Wouldn't it be
better
if we had some maintenance
team
come and clean this shit?
No one does it better
than we do.
Yes, but having some
slaves
wouldn't be that bad,
would it?
Are you done there?
Get down
and start with the condensers.
Since we have 15 hours,
I'm going home
and I'll come back later, okay?
These numbers
just don't add up.
What is it?
These numbers
make no sense.
Told you.
They're boning us.
They're burning our heads.
It's not that, José.
The inputs, the waste
and the production don't match.
We're 14% off.
What does that mean?
It means we're missing
between 7 and 10 ounces.
That's weird.
What about the spillage?
- No, nothing gets spilled.
- No?
What about
evaporation?
They're practically none.
The materials
aren't out that long.
It can't be that.
And the opposite to
that?
The drops,
like on cold beer.
- Condensation?
- That's it!
No, neither.
Neither?
What about the gank
we scrape out of vats?
That's got to add up
to a lot.
Vestiges.
- Could be that.
You see?
Science has an answer
to everything.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
450.
- Professor...
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes, yes, I'm fine.
Aren't you coming?
I'm staying five
minutes
to solve something
and then I'll leave.
Whatever.
See you.
No, no.
Yes, sure.
Of course everything
is under control.
It's all cool.
Fine, cool.
That was José.
He couldn't make it.
Really?
Then let's go and get a beer
since we have the day off.
No, you know what he said?
To start working
and he'll come later.
I think he'll revise
our account
or whatever.
Our
account?
Did you sell anything?
No,
I'm doing really well.
I've sold...
I haven't sold shit.
Víctor, this is the schedule
for next week.
And...
What did you want
to talk to me about?
About this.
This is our product.
So?
Someone in the street
we don't know
is selling it.
There're dealers everywhere,
Victor.
This is not any dealer.
It's selling it for less
that we do.
Let's not do anything for now.
But keep your eyes
and ears open.
I will.
Excuse
me.
What time is José coming?
Like in ten minutes, dude.
We still have time, right?
We should take that time
and if a client comes,
we should sell some meth.
No, Tripa,
José told us
not to sell anything.
Besides, he told us to wait
until he finished
that meeting.
I'm not doing well
with my stuff but...
You know what?
He's given us some rules.
No, no, man,
you have to be proactive.
That's how you accomplish
big stuff.
If he asks
for our numbers,
he won't catch us unaware.
You're doing shit!
You see?
Dude, you were selling
this shit in the streets,
weren't you?
You think I'm so fool?
How do you think
I paid for yesterday's beer?
What if José comes
and finds us selling?
In the middle of
the transaction.
Monito, just look
where we are.
This is a hole, dude.
We'll tell him
we were buying pot.
Why not get
some?
Yes, dude.
What's wrong with you?
Dude, I killed it!
Do I look familiar or have
you lost something?
He's coming back, dude.
He's coming back.
What's up?
What do you want?
Hey, I know this guy!
You won't get him!
- Get out!
- Calm down, man.
Go away, bitch!
Dude, you were lucky
I recognized them
before they sold you shit.
I know them.
They sell the worst shit.
Are you looking for good stuff?
I know some people.
Come, I'll take you.
Come on!
You know
I don't do that shit anymore,
but I keep my contacts.
Whatever you want.
What do you say?
No, thanks.
Anytime, du
That's fine!
What the hell is wrong
with you two?
Did you sell
him anything?
Did you show him the
product?
No, man, nothing.
Chill out.
No, dude, we didn't.
I've just saved your asses,
bitches.
it's miracle you're
alive.
Why can't you do
as I say?
I've told you
this would be where
and when I told you to.
That's all!
Yes, yes, sir.
You see, Mono?
I told him not to.
He insisted.
What's up, Tripa?
What happened?
Yes, yes, just let me...
I'll call you back.
I'm in the middle of something.
All right.
Hurry!
Close!
What's going on?
I feel like in a plane, dude.
- It's positive pressure.
- What?
- You'll fuck my ears.
- Just move your jaw around.
That helps.
I'm moving it.
It's not working.
Just yawn or something.
Stop acting like
such a baby!
What the hell is going on?
I've turned the ventilation up
to keep the outside out.
There's been a contamination.
What?
Hold up.
Something got in
the lab.
So do we evacuate?
Do we put the masks on?
- They're here.
-No, no, no.
It's not that kind
of contamination.
In fact, it's not
dangerous
to us.
What the hell is that?
I made it.
Walter, be more specific.
What kind of contamination
are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
A housefly.
A housefly?
Like one fly?
- No, man!
- Yes.
And I'll get it
out of the lab.
You scared the shit
out of me!
How could you say
there's contamination in the lab
just like that?
I thought like getting
a boob,
a third eye.
like peeling off.
What are you talking
about?
Yes, like in the movies!
You know,
people mutate
and they peel off
and--
How could you scare
me like that, Walter?
Look, that third eye
and boob stuff,
I really don't think
that's possible.
But the skin stuff is possible.
But not in this case.
So you're chasing around
a fly in the lab
and I'm the idiot.
When I say
"contamination",
I'm being very precise.
Exact.
If we want a clean
product,
we have to eliminate
that fly.
You get me?
Hey, did you by
chance
try our product?
This might sound weird, José.
But you have to understand.
In a highly controlled
environment
any risk of contamination
could mean--
Could mean...
Professor...
You didn't hit your head,
did you?
Is it because you didn't sleep?
You stayed here
and didn't sleep.
It must be that, right?
No, no, no.
I'm fine.
All that matters now
is to get to work.
We've already lost
enough time.
Freaking, finally.
What are you doing?
It's time to alkaline.
Have you not heard
a word I said?
No cooking
until this fly is dealt
with.
Have I been speaking
to myself?
You know what I heard?
An alarm telling us
the load is ready.
How long is this batch
going to be good for?
Two, three hours top?
We can't waste it.
The batch will be
good for nothing
if we don't clear
the contaminant.
The contaminant is a fly!
We're making meth here!
That burns people's
brains,
do you get me?
A fly in the lab
won't change
the product.
Do you get me?
No cooking
until the fly is dead!
What fly?
What are you talking
about?
I haven't even
seen a fly!
I know it's here.
I'm sure it's over here.
It's your call, José.
You either help me find it
or just get out of the way.
We're not cooking
if there's risk
of contamination!
Let's hunt then.
Any news regarding
Walter's personal life?
He looks better.
Has he been reckless again?
I think he's got used
to this reality
and not living with his wife.
What happened with the trucks?
A truck going
from Peru to Ecuador
was robbed.
What did you do about it?
We've retrieved
the product
and punished the
guilty.
The problem is they saw what
was on the truck.
And they're
spreading the info.
Would the Mexicans realize
we're exporting?
I think it's a matter of time.
We have to be prepared then.
I need to get more men.
Hire whoever you need,
the best ones.
People ready for combat
and ready to act
in case of an attack.
Excuse me.
Walter, come.
I have a proposal.
Why don't we take
a five-minute break?
Let's go get some air,
freshen our minds,
come back here
and get that fly.
You don't understand
how important this is, do you?
I'm not telling you
not to catch it.
We can't make no mistake!
Not with the kind of people
we're dealing with.
Do you get that?
I know! I know!
I'm not asking
something nonsense!
I'm just asking
for five minutes.
Five minutes,
that's all.
We deserve it.
Okay? Come on.
Fine.
Good, thanks.
- Five minutes.
- Yes, five minutes.
You have the keys?
I left mines
on the desk
and I don't want to--
What are you doing?
give me my keys,
mother fucker!
If you're not helping me,
stay out of my way!
Walter, open up!
Walter!
I'm sorry.
Be quiet.
Don't you move.
You're so fucked!
So you think a fly
is the problem, bitch?
You'll see now.
What happened?
Damn it!
What's up?
You need anything?
No, no, no,
I'm just kidding!
I want peace.
I have a proposal.
Done.
I think this is the best
option.
It's got pheromones
to attract the fly.
The fly
will stick to it.
Since it's not an
insecticide,
you'll stop talking
about the contamination
in the lab.
This is all
green-friendly.
You know that trend?
We have to make
permanent rounds.
We have to be alert
to see if this bitch
falls in the trap.
Ready.
Hey, Walter...
Did you get some
sleep?
Why do you keep asking me that?
Because I never know
with you.
I'm just asking because I
was heating up some coffee
and maybe you wanted
a cup.
But if you want
to fall asleep
and miss the fly dying,
that's up to you.
No, no, I want some.
I need a coffee.
- Fine.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Cover his arm,
please.
Cielo...
I'm really thankful
to you and Walter
for the economic help
you're giving us.
For real.
Thank you.
It's the least we can do.
Come.
What?
Please, I don't want
to talk about this again.
Remember it's a secret
between, you, Walter and me.
- Yes.
- For real.
Where's Walter?
At home with Junior.
Hoe come?
Wasn't Junior at Luis's?
I mean, Walter
went home
to wait for Junior
and rest.
Doesn't that scare you?
What?
I mean, with Walter's problem,
maybe he takes the chance
and goes to a casino.
No, I'm not
scared.
With all this Walter
stuff
I've learnt not to
worry
about things I can't
control.
It'll be whatever it
has to be.
Walter, how have you been?
With what?
what?
Your illness.
I went to see the
oncologist last week.
I'm still in remission.
So probably
I won't die soon.
That's good.
Congratulations.
You want more coffee?
- What?
- More coffee?
Yes, thanks.
Thanks.
José...
I want to tell you something
that seems weird to me.
Weird?
After today noting
seems weird to me.
What have you been
thinking about
lately?
I think I've missed
the perfect moment
to put an end
to this story.
Part of it
was because I hadn't gathered
enough money for my family,
but that doesn't matter.
The thing is
I should have
finished all this
before Cielo found out.
What do you mean
by "finish all this"?
Leaving the business
or drop dead?
I'm saying I've lived too
long.
No, don't say that.
You know what's ideal
when you die?
The ideal thing is
that people miss you,
have memories of you.
Have good memories.
But that's impossible
for me now.
No matter
how I explained Cielo
that this is what I had
to do,
she doesn't understand
it, she doesn't want to.
I should have
definitely die
before Cielo
found this out.
I'm sort of dizzy.
Why don't you sit?
I should have died
long ago.
You know
what the question is?
Which was the right moment?
After Valentina was born,
so I could at least meet her.
I know what that moment was.
It was the night Jane died.
What are you
saying?
I went to your place that night
to take you some money.
- Remember?
- Yes.
When I left
and on the way back home.
I stopped for a beer.
It was odd.
I never do that.
But there I was.
I never told you.
That you went for a beer?
That's not odd.
I ended up
engaging in a conversation
with a complete stranger.
But he turned out to be
Juana's father.
Diego.
He was called Diego.
Hold on.
What are you talking
about?
I didn't know
he was Juana's dad
at that time.
I didn't have a clue.
I didn't put it together
until after the crash
when he was all over the news.
I then understood
I had been talking to him
that night.
Juana's dad?
You're insane.
Think of the odds
of me going in,
sitting down that night
in that bar
next to that man.
Once I tried to calculate them,
but they're astronomical.
I left your house
and got in that place
to take a beer
and run across him, there.
That's incredible.
But it's even more incredible
that him and I
ended up talking.
What did you talk
about?
Water on Mars.
And family.
Family?
What about family?
I told him that I had a daughter
and he told me he had one too.
And he told me
that you can never
give up on family.
That you have to fight
until the end.
And that's what I did.
You know?
The universe is totally random.
It's simple chaos.
It's subatomic particles
in endless aimless collision.
That's what science
teaches us.
But what about
that encounter?
What about
this extraordinary meeting
between this man and me?
What does it mean?
What does universe
teach us with this?
How can that be random?
Is it fate?
Are you all right?
It's okay.
I was trying to establish
the perfect moment
I should have died.
It was that night.
I should have died that night.
I should never have left home.
Never go to your house.
Maybe things
would have been different.
I was at home
watching TV.
I don't know
whether I made it up,
but I think I heard Cielo
talking to Valentina.
In my mind...
I can hear her singing.
If I had just lived
right up to that moment,
it'd have been perfect.
It's not coming down, is it?
No.
Must be Thailand-hot
up there.
Must be worse than Africa.
Africa's hot, right?
- Yes.
- Then that's why.
It's not coming
down.
It's staying up there
forever.
Just wait and see.
What are you doing?
I'm going to
get that bitch.
I'm getting that fly.
Just forget about that
fucking fly.
No, no.
just let me do it.
No, you're going to break
your neck.
Take it easy.
Seriously,
it's not worth it.
Just let me, will you?
Just listen to me.
You'll kill yourself.
You know what?
Just stop talking
and grab this, okay?
Be careful.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry for what?
Being a lunatic?
I'm sorry about Juana.
Yes, me too.
I mean I'm very sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's not mine either...
it's not even hers.
We were two junkies
with a duffel bag full of cash.
You said so yourself.
We both would've been dead
within a week.
Things just moved ahead
for one of us.
And that's what saved me.
But I miss her, though.
Pretty much.
Anyway...
Here it
goes.
Just leave her!
It's not worth it.
What about the contamination?
It's all contaminated.
Just get down
and let's cook.
I definitely scared it.
It'll stay out of the way.
Walter.
Yeah!
Damn it!
Fuck you, bitch!
You see?
I killed it.
Walter, the fly is dead.
Bins are packed?
All of them.
Is production complete?
- Complete.
- Good.
See you
tomorrow.
Don't you want me
to take you home?
No, you've already
put up with me enough.
See you
tomorrow.
Whatever.
José...
One more thing.
I couldn't chance
saying it inside.
For all I know, the lab's
wired for sound.
I'm not accusing you,
but that missing product,
the one I told you about...
José pay attention!
If you had something
to do with this
and these people
find out--
I didn't take shit.
I don't have it, all right?
Just listen to what I'm saying.
If you did have something
to do with this
and these guys find out,
I won't be able
to protect you.
You know what?
No one's asking you
to look after my ass,
all right?
No way.