NORTH OF MEXICO
15 YEARS AGO...
Why is this still
under discussion?
Yes, I know
they've recommended him
but don't care who he knows.
I'd never trust him
out product.
He might be a great cook,
whatever, but not for me.
he's just as asshole to me.
- Don't trust them.
We've already seen
what they're capable of.
Your brother
was just having fun.
You'll get over it.
I wish he was dead!
Oscar Luis!
Grab your old uncle
a beer.
No, no.
A cold one.
Grab one from the bottom.
This is what you wanted, right?
- No, let him go!
- Your brother dead.
You're going to have
to try harder than that.
How much longer do you think
he has down there?
- One minute?
-No, no, let him go!
Maybe more? Maybe less?
Are you okay?
Calm down.
Don't you ever forget
Family is all.
Calm down.
- The ER?
- Through the corridor,
on the right.
Over
there?
- Where's the ER?
- At the back on the right.
Mrs. María de Navarro?
Hello?
[María talking on the
phone]
-Hi, honey.
I've just got home.
Do I prepare dinner for
both?
How are you, babe?
Henry, what's
happening?
Henry?
Babe!
You want me to take you?
No, no, the old man
called me a cab.
Well...
See you.
- Where's the RV?
- I don't get you.
- What RV?
- Don't fool me!
Where's the RV?
No, sir.
There's no RV here.
Go search it
somewhere else.
You've just got
in real fucking trouble,
you heard me?
Say whatever you want!
My kids are lawyers.
Are they?
Yes, lawyers.
Move!
What's up, bitch?
Hey, you got
nothing on me,
You can call my
lawyer,
Saúl Bueno.
You know him, don't you?
Talk to him.
What are you doing?
Son of a bitch!
You got my cell phone number,
my wife's name!
How did you do it?
Who are you working with,
fucker?
If you're ready to talk,
they want to get a statement.
Your side of what happened here.
Or we can wait for a while.
Whenever you feel ready to talk,
just call me and let me know.
Or we can hold them off
till another time.
Maybe you want to talk
to a lawyer.
Umm...
Let's
see...
There it
is.
Look, I know this is
not the moment,
but if I don't tell
you this now
I won't hold myself.
You look like Sofia Vergara
but from the back.
Easy, don't
worry.
I'm just trying
to cheer you up.
I'm your lawyer,
your friend.
Can you see this
picture?
You're not totally blind,
Are you?
I've got good news.
You see that?
It's your get-out-of-jail-free
card.
Just blink once
if you're following.
Good!
We won the lottery!
The lottery!
Can you imagine this face
out in public?
No, we won!
The anti narcotics
agency is shit scared
waiting for the lawsuit.
And that's not all.
If we wanted to...
we could make the press
fall on them
like a poop storm
raining down on them.
It'd be worse than the rain
of punches you got.
This beating
is the best thing for you.
Congrats!
You're home free.
What do you think?
Good, right?
Come in.
I've got good news.
You're now the cute one
of the group,
or at least the best looking.
José, I'm sorry.
Believe me,
I'm so sorry.
This shouldn't have
happened.
But it did.
Thanks to you.
But the plan did work.
We would've been
locked up right now
if we didn't lure
him away.
I'm not justifying it.
What he did
is totally unacceptable.
I never imagined
Henry would...
I mean, I didn't see it
coming.
What happens now?
I'll tell you
what happens now.
Your scumbag brother-in-law
is finished.
Do you get me?
I will own him
when this is over.
Every cent he earns,
every cent his wife earns
is mine.
I'll take everything from them!
I'll take his job,
I'll take his car,
I'll take his home.
I'll be like a shadow,
laughing my ass out,
and taking
dollar by dollar from him.
I will haunt
his crusty ass forever
until the day he sticks a gun up
his mouth
and pulls the trigger
just to get me out of his head.
Do you get me?
That's what happens now!
My advice?
That's probably
not a good idea
That strategy won't work
and I'll tell you why.
They're scared of you right now.
They want nothing to do
with you.
But if you hit them,
they're forced to hit back hard.
They will turn over every rock
hither, thither and yon
until someone
spills the beans on you
and anyone associated with you
present company included.
- With all respect.
- Yes!
José, I think
what Saúl is saying
makes total sense.
Move on with your life.
Live it behind, all of it.
Nothing changes.
Once I get out of here,
I get myself a new place
and go start cooking again.
How exactly do you think you're
going to get away with that?
José, they'll catch you.
So what?
- So what?
- Yes, so what?
Don't you remember
I have
a get-out-of-jail-free-card?
Well...
I may have
overstated
the power of your
picture.
I'm not talking
about the picture.
If the cops catch me,
I'll give them
what they want the most.
You!
They nab me,
I make a deal to give up
the great Heisenberg
and his million-dollar
drug ring.
Do you get me?
You're my free pass, bitch.
Asshole!
Are you sure?
Id he didn't give up my name
while Henry was beating him,
he's never going to talk.
What do you think
that was,
a bluff?
He wants your
brother-in-law.
He's coming for him.
And there's going to be
lawyers
creaming their Underoos
for a case like that.
I'd take it myself
if it wouldn't...
cause so much collateral
damage.
And him cooking again?
Let me tell you
this...
If he gets caught and
he's facing 20 years,
what will he do then?
He'll talk.
It's as easy as that.
There's no honor
among thieves.
Except for us, of
course.
- José will come around.
- And if he doesn't??
There may come a time
to talk options.
Options?
I'm convinced
Mr. José Miguel Rosas
is involved in the manufacture
and distribution
of the blue meth
we're looking for.
I tracked him
to a scrap yard
where he stored an RV,
which I'm sure he adapted
as a mobile lab
to cook meth.
The owner of the yard
asked me for a warrant
to check the RV.
I called, asked for the warrant.
While waiting
for the warrant to arrive,
I got a phone call
telling me my wife María
had been in an accident.
María, my wife,
Upon hearing the news,
I got on my car
and I left Mr. Rosas
in the RV and...
I went to the hospital.
I got to the hospital.
I realized that...
that the call was a hoax.
My wife, fortunately,
was unharmed.
So I immediately went back
to the salvage yard,
but the RV was gone.
I'm completely sure...
that they destroyed it
on the site.
There's no trace left
of that RV.
What did you do after that?
Did you go
to José Miguel Rosas's house?
Don't say anything else.
Gentlemen, I think
we're done for today.
Agent Navarro
must go home and rest.
That's fine.
Just to give you all
a heads up,
Mr. Rosas is pressing charges
in this matter.
Right now
he's giving his testimony
to clarify what happened.
We're talking about
the testimony
of a meth dealer,
gentlemen.
Let me remind
you that.
We've read the files,
we know his background.
No drug traces
were found in his blood.
What's more,
this young man
refused to take pain meds.
That's good ground
for the lawyers.
Right now,
everything is against this man.
Besides, he has
no police record.
He's clean.
So what?
Where do we go from here?
Some men from the OPR
are coming tomorrow
to carry out
the disciplinary investigation.
Vicky will give us
an exact time.
And you, gentlemen...
will be continuing
your internal investigation,
Thanks for your time.
But before leaving,
we need one more thing
for the record.
We must take some pictures
of agent Navarro's hands.
Bandage off, please.
On the table, please.
That's the procedure.
Hi.
Can we talk?
Yes, sure. Come
in.
I guess crime does pay.
I don't suppose
you just came by
to insult me, did you?
No.
We need to talk.
You heard about Henry?
About what happened
with this Rosas?
Yes, I know.
Henry was investigating
or searching for an RV.
You have anything to do
with that?
Is there any danger
that could lead back to you?
No. Why would it?
Is this why
you're here?
No, I'm here
to talk about Henry.
You know...?
You know what's going to happen
to Henry
if Rosas presses charges?
He could lose everything,
Walter.
His house, his car, his job.
I think maybe there's a way...
for you to help him.
Me?
How?
Talk to Rosas.
Get him to drop the charges.
I don't know
what kind of relationship
you picture me
having with this person.
Walter,
I'm not asking
but...
There must be
something you can do
or tell him,
don't you think?
Look, he was...
We're not friends,
we're not even close.
I'm not asking, but...
I do think
you can do something.
It's family, Walter!
Not in this moment.
What?
I said not in this moment.
Henry and I
are no longer family.
I'm sorry
but I'm late.
I have to go.
Good morning,
prof...
Walter.
I was starting to get
worried.
I had some trouble
with the bus.
It gets worse all
the time.
Whenever you need it,
just call me
and I'll pick you up.
Thanks.
What's that?
What happened today
with your floral shirts?
I just thought a bit
more professional.
Well, everything is
on track.
We've got our
distillate.
Let's get our trays ready.
I want them clean and dry.
No moisture.
- Done.
- Done?
It's done
already.
Have you filtered
the solvent?
Yes.
The catalyst?
Done.
It's all set.
That's good.
Every day
a new life begins.
Your coffee is
ready.
Come in,
gentlemen!
You have good
references.
Here's everything you
need.
Stop, stop there,
gentlemen.
What do you
need?
Rifles, A-K, M16,
mortar, rocket,
ammunition, lens.
Just look!
The boss called me
just in time.
I was about to leave
and get on the highway.
Gentlemen, you've got
good references,
so let's get down to
business.
Are you buying in
bulk?
For retail.
We can help you.
Whatever you need.
Look, this is the latest
we've got.
Take it!
This is for you,
gentlemen.
A gift from us.
You know what that's
called?
The black death.
As soon as that bullet
gets in,
Bum!
It opens like a
mushroom.
It destroys you inside.
It crashes your head.
I've already talked
enough.
You tell me.
What do you need?
- Vests.
- Vests?
We should have started
with that.
Vests.
When talking about vests,
this is the latest.
It's thermally
bonded.
It's ideal for this weather.
It's excellent.
It's like a condom.
It's soft.
You don't even feel it.
Try it!
- Do they work?
I wear one every day
to protect myself.
You broke my freaking
rib!
You maniac!
Son of a
bitch!
Guido, come here, please.
What temperature
did you set here?
In station five?
167 °F.
Why?
I told you 185.
I wrote 167 here.
That's what you told me.
You wrote it wrong!
I didn't say 167 or 200.
I said 185!
Guido, this is chemistry.
Each degree matters!
I'm sorry.
While you're sorry,
prepare 50 gallons
of sterile sludge.
Congratulations!
You've fucked it all up!
This batch is ruined!
You look nice.
If you like book-sellers...
That's fine.
You want some coffee?
- No, thanks.
- Some orange juice?
I'll have it in a minute.
No, I'm fine, babe.
Thanks.
What will you tell them?
Here's what you'll tell
them.
He attacked you.
- He attacked me?
- Yes, he attacked you..
He swang at you with
something,
with a pipe.
- With a pipe?
- Yes, he swang a pipe,
so your muscle memory
kicked in
because he was going
to beat you,
- so you just--
- Muscle memory.
- Yes, babe.
Years of training,
your body acted faster
than your brain
He was armed
and you had to disarm him
because he was going to beat
you, so you beat him first.
- María.
- So he didn't beat you.
- María!
- You just defended yourself!
- María, María!
- You defended yourself!
I'm not going to lie.
It's some lowlife degenerate
versus you, henry.
Why should you be the one
who pays for doing
the right thing?
You did the right thing!
What I did is
wrong.
That's not my job.
I'm a cop, I can't
follow my muscle.
I have to be better
than this, María.
It was just a mistake, Henry.
No, no.
You and I know it was
not just a mistake.
María, I fucked it up.
I have to accept it
and face the consequences.
End of story.
María, I'm not okay.
I don't feel well.
I think all the time about
everything that's happening
and I don't sleep.
I don't sleep, María.
I wake up paralyzed.
I can't move my hands,
my body.
My chest gets all tight.
I can't breathe.
I panic.
I'm scared!
How long has this
been happening to you?
Since that Salamanca
thing.
Since I had to kill that
fucking Tuco Salamanca.
That changed me, María.
I don't know, I...
I try to get up every day
and be positive,
not think about that,
you get me?
But...
But then Mexico!
María,
how could I do
what I did to
that guy?
To Rosas.
You know me, babe.
- You know that's not
who I'm supposed to be.
- Yes.
- Am I like that?
No, you're not like that.
And with everything
that's happened,
I swear to God
I think this might be
a signal,
they might be sending me a
message or something because...
Or God or the universe.
The other day I told
myself
I'm finally ready to
listen.
Because I don't know
what else to do, María.
I really have no idea.
I...
- You know what?
- What?
María, I'm not the man
I thought I was.
And I think
that...
I think I'm done as a
cop.
This is not an easy decision,
but it's the one
that I have to make.
Look, I'm really sorry.
This whole Guido situation.
Things are simply
not working out,
sir.
Yes, now.
It may sound unorthodox,
but I think our first best
option is...
I mean,
our best option
is José Miguel Rosas.
Hello?
No, no sir.
Not at all.
On the contrary,
there's history,
there's experience,
we share a long trajectory.
I'm never going to reach that
with Guido.
Sir, when I accepted your offer,
I told you the lab was mine.
And I know best how to run it,
what's best for it.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Yes, I will.
Okay. Bye.
Will I have to see you here
every day or what?
José, I want to talk to you.
I need to tell you
something.
Do I have a choice?
José, something's
come up.
I think it's a good
opportunity.
There's been a
job opening.
I need a new lab assistant.
I already did my time.
Why don't you just get yourself
a monkey?
I don't want a monkey.
I want you.
You're so good.
I've got my own things going on
and that's more than enough
for me.
Besides, I'm no fool.
Nice try, saving
your ass-head brother-in-law.
That's not why
I'm here.
José, there's more.
It's more than an
assistant.
Partners.
We'll be partners
again.
One point five million
dollars each.
No.
I don't think you heard.
I heard you fine.
I said no.
Let me understand this.
You're turning down one
and a half million dollars?
I'm not turning
down the money!
I'm turning down you!
You get it?
I want nothing to do with you.
Ever since I met you,
everything I've ever cared about
is gone.
You get me?
Look at me!
Look how I am!
I'm nothing, bitch!
I'm ruined!
I'm dead, you get me?
I died the day I met
the great Heisenberg!
I've never in my life
felt more alone.
I have nothing!
No one!
It's all gone, get it?
All!
Why would you get it?
You know why you don't get it?
because you don't give a shit
about people
as long as you get
what you want.
First you, second you,
third you!
You don't give a shit about me.
You said I was no good.
That I was useless.
What changed then if you told me
my meth was inferior?
You said that yourself,
remember?
Screw you!
Screw you, bitch!
Don't come back here.
And just
disappear
because I don't want to have
anything to do with you
again in my life.
Your meth is good.
It's as good as mine.
Hello.
What happened?
Fifty-fifty.
Yes, fifty-fifty.
Done.
Partners.
Perfect!
Is this the statement
that you want to give?
Yes, sir.
Henry, you don't have
to do this.
Yes, I do.
I accept it.
So we understand
if we write it up like that,
you'll sign it.
That's the way it happened.
I accept the consequences.
In the light of these facts as
of this moment,
you're suspended
without pay, agent Navarro.
I have to ask you
to hand over
your badge and your gun.
Henry, Henry,
hold up.
I just wanted to tell you
something
and you didn't hear it from me.
Don't want you to get
your hopes up
but the word in the pipeline
is Rosas isn't pressing charges.
Why not?
Who the hell knows?
Maybe you have a guardian angel.
Fine, babe.
Yes, it went fine.
That means
it went fine.
I'll tell you about it
when I get home.
You know what?
I think we may be okay,
you know?
Yes.
Okay.
I love you too.
Kisses, babe.
No, you hang.
I'm on my way there.
Bye, babe.
Hello?
I need you to listen
very carefully.
Two men are coming
to kill you.
Come
again?
They're approaching your car.
You have one minute.
Who's this?
They're coming.
Hello?
Mail box.
Leave your message
after the tone.
Gómez, why are you leaving me
those messages?
I don't get the gag.
Call me back
when you get this.
Kill him.
Too easy.