Thirty-seven. Number 37.
Hi.
Here's my resume.
Or curriculum, as you call it,
right? It sounds more professional.
Aha.
It doesn't say it there, but I have a
great background in sales as well.
What kind of sales?
A great range of products. Yes,
anything, really.
I think in these cases the person
is more important than the product.
I really feel I could be a
major asset to your sales force.
I'm thinking there's a
little misunderstanding.
This isn't actually a sales job.
Then what is it?
This is more like advertising.
OK.
Tell me, Mr. Néstor.
- Mono? Old José!
Yo, man! What up?
Do you know each other?
- Of course!
- Perfect!
Then you can teach him what he
needs to know about work in the street.
Sure thing! How about that?
Gimme five.
Come, Mono, give me a break.
Why don't you take off that
helmet? Makes me wanna go pee.
Nice pot, isn't it?
Come on, Monito,
don't get too excited.
This job you've
got is like the worst?
No, my friend,
not with this costume.
The taco costume is worse,
you don't know.
It's much bigger,
much heavier and all.
I get roasted in it, man.
Would you want to do
this lame ass job anyway?
Gotta prove to my
mom I'm rehabilitated.
I told her I wouldn't
do drugs anymore,
weird trades and all that,
you know?
So then what about this?
No, old José,
this is barely a little snack.
To be powerful and feel good
so I can move around and all.
Well, if you say so.
Listen, José, speaking of drugs.
You think you could maybe
hook me up with some crystal?
No, I've been out of the
business for a while, I retired.
That's just a loss for humanity,
José.
That stuff you made...
Unbelievable!
The eight wonder, for real.
That stuff was hot, right?
Wow!
I had this partner who
was helping me cook.
Complicated dude.
Anyway, pseudo's getting
harder and harder to come by.
That was getting really tough.
Not so much,
José. Is pseudo the problem?
I can hook you up with some
pseudo. Major pseudo. How about it?
We could partner
up. What do you say?
- Hey!
- No, I don't know, man.
Man, it's getting late for
me. But you know what?
Why don't you get to thinking?
Just think about it, all right?
Imagine, partners,
you and me. Gimme five, gimme five, OK?
- Think about it, OK?
- I will, man.
Hey, Mono!
Are you sure they said
not to bring a present?
That's what they said.
Wouldn't' it look bad
to bring this thing?
No, honey. They'll love it.
There's still time to go back.
No! Stop it.
You and I deserve a nice time
after all we've been through.
And despite everything,
I like them.
You've got to take care of friends,
don't you think?
- Friends... Come on.
- Where should I park?
- I don't know.
Everything will be fine,
alright? Over there.
Darn it.
Come on! Nobody will notice.
Nobody? I look like
a humble teenager,
badly dressed at a social party.
- There are worse things.
And they said
not to bring a gift.
Should I take your present?
- Yes.
- Excuse me.
This is even worse
than I imagined.
Don't look, here comes Edgar.
Edgar, happy birthday!
- Thanks so much.
- Hi!
Happy birthday!
Hi! Thanks so much for coming.
- Did Marcela see you? No.
Marcela!
- Hi!
- You look gorgeous! How much longer?
- Thanks!
- Ten more weeks.
- Walter. - How are you?
- Welcome!
- Thank you.
Edgar, well,
this is history by now,
but it's been a while since
we last saw each other,
and I wanted to congratulate
you for the Calnatur victory.
Appreciate it, Walter. But you
know that without your research,
this would never
have been possible
Come on,
now. Securing that patent was just amazing.
You were brilliant in that one.
I saw in the news not long ago
that it was called the best-selling
product in Latin America
for hepatic diseases.
- Right.
- That's awesome.
Can you excuse us?
Lucas just came in. Sorry.
I'll go greet the
rest of the guests.
I'm so happy to
have you my house.
- Thank you.
I think I need a
stronger drink than this.
¡Walter!
- Such a pleasure, man!
- Hey, Alberto, how are you?
- How's it going?
- OK, and you?
Good,
good. Let me introduce you to some friends.
- Walk with me, come!
- Fine, alright.
Gentlemen,
excuse me for a second.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- This is Walter Blanco.
- How are you?
- How do you do?
- The master of mineralogy.
- No, not so much.
Come on. Look,
when he worked with Edgar,
this man was the mastermind.
I remember this one time
we were stuck on
this protein problem
- Yes.
- Remember? For weeks.
We worked,
but nothing. This man comes in,
and bam, solves the whole thing.
What was that you used?
Synchrotrons.
They generate purer and
more complete patterns
Data collection takes
a fraction of the time.
- So are you still with Edgar?
- No.
No,
it's been a while... I kind of moved on.
So what do you do now?
I teach.
Are you managing
a college department
or something like that?
I'm... Yes,
I'm a teach in a school. Chemistry.
Well, cheers.
Cheers.
It's awesome, thanks.
Edgar,
it's a very special guitar.
Cerati used that one in
his last show in Colombia.
Really?
Wow! Nice historical
piece. Thank you!
Why's he doing this? He
looks like an eight-year-old
opening presents from Santa.
This one's from
Walter and Cielo.
A pack of pasta soup.
Let me tell you a story.
For ten months, this man and I
lived on this while
working on our thesis.
At breakfast,
at lunch and at dinner.
Thank you for reminding
me where I come from, Walter.
I really didn't know what
to give a man who has it all.
You touched my heart,
brother. Thanks again.
Life has its injustices, man.
Because you can be
whatever you want,
but you'll always be
remembered for your nickname.
Poor guy...
He was a genius in Chemistry,
but nobody ever
called him by his name.
So what did they call him?
- Turkey!
- Right!
Because of the double chin.
But he was great. I
learned a lot from him.
- You know what happened to him?
- Don't tell me he died.
No, no,
no. He was extradited to the US.
He was working in a
crack lab for a mob guy.
DEA caught him, and bam!
Extradited to the North,
brother.
That's impossible.
Anyway,
everything has an upside.
The news didn't mention him as
"Turkey" but rather as "The Chemist".
Well,
at least he got his dignity back.
It's amazing how in this country
chemistry can take you
down the narcotic road?
So how would that road be?
No, I mean the 80's,
the 90's... Don't you remember?
When the mob was like
crazy searching everywhere
for chemists to
make crack for them.
Right, right.
You could easily
send your resume
either to Pablo
Escobar or a drug store.
Right, right.
Well, turns out two of our partners
ended up doing the same thing.
They didn't end
up bad like Turkey.
Really? Who?
Vivanco and Montoya.
- The gay couple?
- Right! Now they have these bars,
and are solid businessmen
in the gay rumba.
That's just amazing.
I pay my respects.
Did you ever get the
offer to work for the mob?
No.
I did.
Are you serious?
Yes yes. But of
course I said no.
Though I won't deny
that I thought about it.
Really?
Yes,
I had plenty of debts at the time,
and these people
paid tons of cash.
There wasn't really much to do.
Just set up a lab, teach people
and stop by once in a
while to check on things.
Right.
I excused myself thinking
I was only doing chemistry.
But I really couldn't do it.
I understand. It's not...
It must be hard to
control your conscience.
And your fear.
Because if I think about it,
if I'd have said yes to them,
it would've
changed my life a lot.
For sure,
it would've changed dramatically.
We should get
together more often.
Sure! Of course,
let's make plans.
We can go to my place,
have dinner.
But I'm not only talking
about being social.
I mean you and I should
work together again.
There will always be a
place for you in this business.
Are you asking me to
come work for you two?
That's right, Walter.
You're brilliant,
you've got a ton of experience.
Thanks.
I wouldn't really
know where to begin.
I mean, I've got classes...
I don't think that
would be a problem
for a man as talented as you.
No, no, it's just...
I mean,
right now I'm going through this situation
that's rather complicated.
I know, don't worry.
This company has an
excellent health insurance.
Did you try the prawns?
They were amazing!
You know I'm not that
much of a seafood fan,
but they were great.
Is something wrong?
You told Edgar about my cancer.
I can't believe this!
No, wait, it's not like that.
He asked how you were doing,
and I am sorry,
but I don't have the best poker face
- where that's concerned.
- Yes, right.
So what did you
expect me to tell him??
How about you
just said "he's fine,"
Might as well hand
him my medical history.
I don't like the way
you're talking to me.
I don't like the way you talk to
people about my private affairs.
What exactly did he
say to get you so mad?
He offered me a job.
Kind of like some fig leaf.
And that he would
pay for my treatment.
So what did you say?
What would you want me to say?
No, obviously!
Give me five minutes to finish up,
and we'll go.
No problem,
a friend is taking me.
José!
José, man!
Come on, Mono.
Are those bullet holes, José?
No, no bullet holes, man!
Those are for, like,
you know, ventilation.
So how do you like it? Wow!
Nice set-up? I know.
Yes!
Hey, just look at this bottle!
Bottle, Mono? That's not a bottle,
don't be dumb!
That's a boiling flask.
And this is nothing. We
used to have double that.
We had this full of glass
until my idiot partner,
my ex partner,
messed all this up
and it got broken. But come,
over here
there's a beaker, a volumetric beaker,
Erlenmeyer. And this?
This is awesome!
We had one of these
but it was a
five-thousand-milliliters! Gigantic!
This glass is better
than any other,
it's used to boil.
That's cool, man.
You really know your shit.
- We could do great.
- Monito, I'm surprised.
You have to be a professional.
You have to know the business.
Speaking of stuff, Mono...
Did you bring the pseudo? I sure did,
bro.
This is where we'll
get the pseudo.
Leave that porn, Mono,
None of that shit.
Good old flu pills, man.
Great, Monito!
I thought this had
all been taken.
No. Have you not seen when in
ads they say "while supplies last"?
There's still supplies!
It's not sold out yet!
That's a boy, Mono,
that's how I like it, real partying.
Mono, man!
Ha!
What a woman!
Let's sit there.
Here?
Hey, hey, hey! What's with
Already drunk at this time?
Let's give a big
round of applause now
for one of the hottest women here tonight,
this is Alejandra.
Yes, La Terraza Coctelera friends,
get ready, because in five minutes...
Hear me out, in five minutes
we're having the best,
most perfect performance of the night.
Now comes Candy,
sexier than ever.
So welcome! Such a
pleasure to work here.
May the rumba continue!
This is going to be good!
So what are we drinking?
It'll have to be beer
because all the money
went to the
bouncer to let us in.
Hey,
no beer. It's not my fault I'm under age.
But it's your fault to make
plans like this, you pervert.
Right?
Turn off the music!
Rodríguez, over there.
This is a routine procedure,
folks.
Please cooperate
handing me your IDs.
Lucho, we're screwed, brother.
Hand me your IDs.
Galvis, thanks so much.
No, sir. You're the boss.
Right.
- What's up, uncle?
- Are you stupid or something?
Be thankful I know Galvis,
otherwise they'd have ended up
taking you away. You know where?
To the police station,
with the transvestites and the homeless.
They eat you alive over there,
and not exactly
with a fork and knife.
Right, uncle, I'm sorry.
Why are you doing this?
Hey,
it's not like I killed someone.
Me and Lucho just wanted to
see a hot chick dancing, that's all.
No, I'm not talking about that.
Look, if there's something I
respect that's the sacred right
we men have to
see a naked woman.
- Well, so?
- So what?
Why did you call me?
Why didn't you call your dad?
Go to your room,
young man. You're grounded.
I'll deal with you later.
I think you shouldn't tell
Walter about this, you know?
These things happen naturally.
You think it's natural for
him to go to these places?
Well, he's a teenager. He's exploring,
looking.
And he just found out his dad has cancer,
you know?
He's just acting out.
First the pot, and then this.
The pot? What are
you talking about?
María, you told me Junior was--
- Because you told me.
- I didn't say that, María!
You told me!
Well, you implied that with this
whole story about the neighbor's son--
No, I wasn't talking about Junior,
María,
I was talking about
Walter Senior.
What?
Walter Senior smokes pot?
Walter?
- Well, he admitted it himself.
- No...
Yes, lately,
Walter's been acting really weird.
He actually seems
like he's someone else.
Just think about it.
Don't you find that weird?
I mean,
why would anyone in their right mind
choose not to do treatment
when it's completely paid for?
I think we should do something.
What?
What we really need to do is sit
him down and make him. All of us.
You mean an intervention?
Like on TV when
they talk to addicts?
Right.
José,
you're a genius! Master of the universe.
This is absolutely unreal!
No, no, no.
I'm gonna burn
that dollar bill suit!
It's not right, Mono!
But José, I think it's perfect.
What more would you want?
It's cloudy. Can't you see that?
It's not supposed to be
cloudy but transparent.
Jose, so what? Cloudy,
not cloudy.
It looks good enough to me to blow
your mind out, isn't that what's important?
- Are you out of your
mind? Move over!
Come on,
José! Come on, old José.
Man, don't even think about it.
No,
man! How can you throw that away?
It's not right.
I totally would've smoked that!
It's not for you, it's for our customers.
They're gonna demand a certain standard.
So what now?
- We cook more.
- What?
We'll just do it again
until we get it right.
Hi.
Please have a seat and join us.
We can do better.
Come on, José. Three entire
pounds of pseudo wasted! Stop it now!
Man... No!
Did you see what you did?
It wasn't me, José! Why would
I throw away three pounds of
Why do you accuse me?
Stop fucking with me already!
What are you doing, Mono?
Stop fucking with me!
You're not getting out.
My eyes,
man! I don't give a shit about your eyes!
Bye, old Mono.
You fight like a girl, man.
Come on!
José, José, dude!
It's all good,
José! Don't leave me here, man!
José, José!
Walter,
I need you to share what you're thinking.
Because I really don't
understand anything.
I feel your decision is not
only not in your best interest,
it's not in the best
interest of our entire family.
- Cielo...
- Not yet.
Only one person
has the Talking Pillow.
Everybody gets to speak their minds,
and in the end,
you'll get your chance.
I'm sorry.
Edgar is willing to pitch
in for your treatment.
Money has always
been an issue for us,
so that would really help us,
Walter.
But you refused,
I don't know why.
I just want to make it clear...
that I don't agree with that.
It's okay to lean on people now and again,
Walter.
You need that.
We need that.
Are you done? Can I answer.
No. I think we need to
go around the circle first.
Go ahead, Henry.
Well...
This is kind of complex,
it's not a matter of...
Well,
I don't usually get the chance
to tell you this kind of stuff,
so I'm taking this chance to tell you,
brother,
that I care about you a lot.
You're like a brother to me,
you know?
This cancer thing, well...
It's like the other team scored a
goal when the game just started.
But that doesn't mean you lose,
does it? So what do you do?
You plan the game again.
You think about the formation.
If you're playing with two four-player
lines, you know what you do?
With two fives,
a play maker and two offenses up,
With wingbacks-- - What
are you talking about?
It's a metaphor from soccer,
honey.
Walter understands me,
don't you?
María, it's fine. Leave him.
That's what this is about. Talk.
And besides,
I have the Talking Pillow.
I'm going to use an
example we all understand.
Just imagine a
player gets injured.
The guy can't play anymore,
you know?
They need the doctor.
He comes, makes an infiltration,
uses that stuff
they use so that the
guys can keep on playing.
He gets help...
You get me,
don't you? What I'm...
No.
You have your pride,
I have mine.
We all have our pride, it's just that
sometimes we should forget about it.
If this Daddy Richy
wants to chip in
I say take the money and run.
Who wants this? I...
I have nothing
else... That's it for me.
Junior...
I know you have a lot
on your mind with now.
Now is the time
for you to speak.
- This is bullshit, mom.
- Hey, watch your mouth!
Walter, let him talk.
How do you feel? Tell us.
I'm pissed off, mom.
Tell him.
I'm pissed off because
you're being a coward,
a pussy. You're
ready to give up.
What if you gave up on me?
All the stuff I've
been through. Look.
And you're scared of
a little chemotherapy?
Come on, Walter!
Well...
I think, Walter,
that you should do
whatever you want to do.
What?
Yes. You told us to be honest
about our feelings. That's what I feel.
You're the one with cancer.
You have the right to
make your own decisions.
- María,
why are you doing this to me?
I'm not doing anything to you!
I wasn't planning on agreeing with Walter,
but now that I'm listening
to you all talk about his future
like he has no say in it...
He's not gonna have a future
if he doesn't get treatment.
First of all,
you don't have the Pillow.
Second of all, I work with X-rays
every day and have a ton of experience
despite my age.
I x-ray people in
treatment every day.
Some of them are
absolutely miserable.
And some of them don't
wanna spend their last days
being picked at by doctors
with pills and injections
as if they were lab rats. No.
Could I get the pillow back?
I agree with María on that.
No, Henry!
What? Maybe Walter
wants to die like a man.
I don't want him to die at
all! That's the whole point
of all this, for him to live!
We're here to convince him!
So either help,
or leave! Because--
Cielo,
we came here to give our opinion.
As honestly and
respectfully as possible.
No! You know,
this is not debate club.
This is my husband's
life we're talking about!
You just don't like anyone
to say anything against you,
so that's why we don't agree
and get all rattled
up. That's my opinion.
No, no!
- You're asking me for my opinion.
- María, please.
You always do this to me.
Why do we agree on something
and then you say the opposite?
All right,
I've got the Talking Pillow now.
I know you're all here
because you love me
and you're worried about me.
I am very thankful for that.
But what I want...
What I really need...
is a choice.
What does that mean?
Sometimes, I feel...
I never actually had the chance
to make any decision of my own.
I always end up giving.
And now,
with all this cancer thing,
I particularly feel
I should be the one
to make a decision.
Then make the right choice.
You're not the
only one it affects.
Think about Junior.
Don't you wanna see
your daughter grow up?
Of course I do.
It's not just that, Cielo.
There are other
things to think about.
Look, these doctors,
they just say that you...
should live longer
and that it's a
matter of survival.
To live how long?
One or two years?
Like it's the only
thing that matters.
But what about
the quality of life?
What use is it to me to be alive
if I am too sick to work,
to pick up the baby
or be able to enjoy a meal
or make love?
You know what I want?
I want to live my last
days in my own house,
to sleep in my own bed.
I don't wanna choke down
40 pills every single day
feel nauseous
and so weak
to even be able to lift my head.
And you having to
work twice as hard
and cleaning my
puke all the time.
I don't want to be
a dead man living
just to buy myself a
couple more minutes.
That's how you would remember me,
and I don't want that.
I want you to
remember me like this,
not like some old rag.
Alright
Alright what?
I'll do the treatment.
It's gonna be OK.
Are you OK, champ?
Thank you.
They say they usually bill the
insurance company directly.
But since our HMO is not paying for it,
we can pay up front with a credit card.
OK.
Will Edgar send a check...?
Don't worry,
I will take care of it.
Walter Blanco!
Yes, that's me.
See you in a minute.
Edgar, what's up?
... Walter, this is Marcela.
Hi, Marcela, how are you?
I'm good.
You know,
it was really great seeing
you two the other day.
What an amazing party.
Edgar told me about the cancer.
I'm so sorry.
Well, you know...
It is what it is, I guess.
I don't know what to say
except I'm here for you.
You can count on us.
Thank you, Marcela,
I really appreciate it, OK?
Edgar also told me
he had offered to
pay for the treatment
and you said no.
I'd like you to reconsider
because as far as we know,
that money belongs to you.
We wouldn't have the
company if it weren't for you.
- Marcela...
- No, listen to me.
Did you say no because of
what happened between us?
I appreciate very much
what you're doing for me, OK?
But let me just say it's
no longer necessary.
It turns out the insurance
came through after all and is
paying for the treatment. So...
it's all fine,
no problem at all.
Anyway,
I really appreciate you thinking about me.
Good, that's good news.
Yes. Well, once again,
it was great seeing you,
and we should do it again.
Please, keep in touch,
OK? I'd like to know how you're doing.
Of course.
Hey... Thanks for calling.
Thank you.
Where do you think you're going?
Do you think this is your house?
You wanna cook?