Yes!
This is Heisenberg's waltz.
Let's dance it
while we can.
Well done, Heisenberg!
Let's give him
a round of applause!
Ahaha!
Heisenberg,
this is just a warning.
We've already told you this.
I hope you're listening.
Haha!
Come on, come on.
Poor Heisenberg.
He should hide very well.
These men are very tough.
The king's wish
is their command.
Hydrogen and oxygen
make a bond and produce...
Do you know what a bond is?
A bond
is a strong force of attraction.
And there are
different types of bonds.
There're covalent bonds,
ionic bonds...
The coming together of atoms
and molecules to form compounds.
Chemical bonds
are what make matter be matter.
Bonds are what hold
the physical world together.
Yes, yes.
Bonds, relationships.
I know it.
Your test says otherwise.
I only needed two points more.
I was close.
Close?
There's no "close" in science.
There are right answers
and wrong answers.
"Close" didn't put men
on the moon.
Two points are meaningless
if you think it through.
I swear I've studied a lot.
A lot.
I really like chemistry.
I think
I have a learning problem.
Sure.
Can you help me
by scoring me higher?
I wasn't born yesterday.
It means the answer is no.
Next time, do it right.
You have to study!
Hello, what's up?
This is my house.
This is Jose's house.
Leave me your message,
and I'll see, pal.
José Miguel, this is
the third time I call you.
This is my third message.
What's the matter?
I'll be in this telephone number
15 minutes more. Call me.
That business I asked you
to take care of...
forget about it;
don't do it.
José Miguel!
José Miguel, open the door.
I know you're there.
Hello,
can I help you?
No, thanks.
- Jose!
- Hey, hey, hey!
I'm the owner. I really
appreciate if you lower
your voice. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Are you the owner?
Yes.
So yes, you can help me.
Look...
I very much need to get in
to see the person
who is inside.
If you have a master key,
it would really help me.
Do you have a key?
Yes.
I do have a key.
I understand
you don't trust me.
But it's very important
for me to see him.
So...
And you knocked, right?
You heard me.
And he doesn't open.
Madam,
I'm José Miguel's father.
Are you Mr. Mercado?
Yes.
Walter Mercado.
I'd be happy
to let you use my phone.
No. I don't want to talk
on the phone with him.
I want to...
let's see.
I'm worried. I'd like to check
on my son's well-being.
I'm going to say this clearly.
I understand you're his father,
and he's your son,
but I don't want to be involved.
If he doesn't open,
there's nothing I can do.
What's up, dad?
Thank you.
It's okay.
Walter Mercado...
Mercado?
I mean, I'm Walter Mercado.
You do have a phone.
Those machines are to be
answered if someone calls.
Whatever, man.
Don't bother me.
Leave me alone!
What are you doing?
Give me my pipe back!
Don't move,
or I'll break it!
Is that what you've been doing?
That's why you didn't answer.
Fucking junkie!
No, do you know
what I was doing? My homework.
- What homework?
Have you already forgot?
The homework you gave me.
Don't you remember?
Okay!
This homework, pal!
This homework!
Now you remember,
don't you?
Did you...?
You told me
to take care of it.
I meant intimidation.
I told you to scare them
so that they return the money!
Now you don't want
anybody to be killed.
- No!
- Too late.
That man is already gone.
- God!
I almost forgot.
Take it!
That's your part.
Eight million.
Four thousand dollars.
With all those conversions
you like so much.
I hope you enjoy it,
son of a bitch!
- Jose.
- What?
The gun has all the bullets.
I didn't say I killed someone.
So?
Tell me what happened.
The dude's woman...
The dude's woman
crushed his head
with an ATM machine.
- Crushed his--?
- Yes, she crushed his head.
She crushed his head
with an ATM machine
right in front of me.
The sound...
It's still in my ears.
And the blood.
The blood...
There was blood everywhere.
I didn't know
you could bleed so much.
Are you saying
that you didn't kill anyone?
Does anybody think
that you killed anybody?
No, no, no.
I called the cops, and left.
- Did you call the cops?
- Yes, yes.
And they came very fast.
They took her away.
Walter, that woman was crazy.
I've never seen
someone like that.
She killed him for nothing.
All he did
was calling her "bitch"...
Honestly, I do think
she was a bitch.
Do you think
she may identify you?
Is it possible
that she remembers that
you were in the house?
No, she couldn't identify
her own ass.
She was so zonked.
I've never seen
someone like that.
And the worst part is...
that they had this kid.
They didn't feed him.
I don't understand.
If she was in that condition,
why didn't you stop her?
She had a gun on me!
Yes, yes, Walter.
She had my gun on me!
Say it. I'm good for nothing.
I'm not Tuco or Loco.
I can't run a crew.
Hello, Jose.
I've got the pants
you wanted. Size 32.
Let's do some business, okay?
Well.
I'll call you back.
- Jose
- What?
Are you going
to get back up on that horse?
What horse?
All I want is to forget.
You take care of it.
It's about time.
I'm sorry.
What's up with that?
Jesús Malverde, patron saint
of Mexican drug dealers.
Yes, I know who he is.
All the Mexicans kneel down
and pray to him.
"Please, make me strong
so that I can fuck
one of those gringos,
motherfucker."
I'm just asking
why he is on your desk.
Sun Tzu.
Tzu, who?
Sixth-century Chinese general.
Wrote The Art of War .
"If you know your enemy
as yourself,
you'll fight without danger
in many battles."
Where's the Colombian?
Agent Henry Navarro.
Here I am!
Like Cantinflas who--
Welcome! How did they
receive you? All right?
Yes.
They've been nice.
Great group of guys
and "gals".
You couldn't have picked
a better time to arrive.
We're about to catch
a cartel.
- Right, Javier?
- Yes, sir.
- Would you like a beer?
- Sure!
- Let's go.
- Let's go
Come on, man.
These motherfuckers...
I used to come here
when I was a boy.
Don't tell me, man.
I spent the days here
shopping around.
What did you shop?
Small things
that fit in my pockets.
Hello.
I'm Heisenberg.
Of course.
You're Jose's friend,
the cook.
Nice to meet you.
Let's go straight
to the point.
- Where's Jose?
- He's busy.
It's okay.
- Yes, it's cool.
- Where's my stuff?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Put it on the cart.
There it is.
You can count it.
Do you want me
to count it here?
I don't know.
We're good people.
That's good pasta.
Grab the bag.
Yes, man.
We're serious people.
Yes, we're very respectful.
We work with good people.
We don't want
to get into trouble.
What do you know?
What have you heard?
This cough is killing me.
It's been said that Jose
squashed a dude's head
with an ATM machine.
- Who's saying that?
- Everybody, everywhere.
Yes, man. Look.
I don't even need
to ask people to pay me.
People come for me.
Is it true
that he squashed a man's head?
Don't tell anybody
that I say so.
Thank you.
I can do it.
I'm done, madam.
Excuse me, please.
Liliana, bye.
Goodbye, engineer.
Have a nice day.
Yes.
I've completed the form.
Okay.
Okay, Mrs... Blanco.
I'll give it
to Human Resources.
They'll call you.
Have a nice day.
I'd like to highlight
that I've already worked here.
When?
About... four years ago.
I spent about four years here.
At the Accountant Department.
I had to leave
because of family issues.
I can see.
When are you due?
Er... Several months.
Congratulations.
We'll definitely let you know.
Have a nice day.
Is that Ernesto's office?
It's our boss's office.
- Doctor Ernesto Silva.
- Yes.
- Yes, that's it.
- Thanks.
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you.
Yes, that's it.
Madam!
Madam, you can't go in there.
Madam, stop.
Madam, you can't go in there!
Stop.
Madam, you can't be here!
- Doctor, look, she--
- Liliana, it's okay.
- I can't believe it! Hi.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
Please, come in.
Liliana,
no calls, okay?
Sure, doctor. Okay.
- Sit down right there.
- Thanks.
How are you? Boy or girl?
You don't know?
Girl.
Okay!
One of each.
Yes. Yes.
- How did Walter Junior take it?
- Fine.
Walter is a big boy now.
He's in high school.
He's beautiful.
Yes, he has your genes.
Are those your twins?
- Look at them.
- Yes.
Beautiful!
They're really gorgeous.
The worst part
is they know it.
And they use it
perfectly well.
How have you been
dealing with the company?
Very well...
But I still feel
it belongs to my dad.
Your father
was a wonderful man.
Yes, he was.
I'd like to think
that he'd be very proud of me.
- Of course!
- Yes?
Of course he'd be.
Last year
was a wonderful year.
I'm glad.
How's Walter doing?
Fine. Fine.
- Does he still teach?
- Yes.
You tell him I said hello.
Okay. Thanks.
I haven't offered you
something to drink.
- No, no. I'm fine.
- Really?
Actually, I...
- I didn't stop by to say hi.
- So.
I was applying
for the filing clerk job.
Really?
The problem is...
Honestly, you're overqualified
for that job, Cielo.
You were the best
at your department.
This is life.
And the crisis.
Yes, but offering
that job to you
would be a mistake
I can't accept.
How about getting
your old job back?
We're expanding.
The whole company is a mess.
The files are impossible
to understand.
I need someone like you,
who will help me
put everything in order.
Really?
Yes.
Sure!
It's perfect.
Okay.
Currently,
this is our territory, isn't it?
Come on, Jose.
Wake up, focus.
Okay, okay. It's okay.
I want to know
what's going on here...
and here.
- That isn't our territory.
- No!
Do you know what's going on?
We aren't selling there
because we lack initiative.
Initiative.
You keep on repeating that.
It's the initiative
over and over again.
Yes!
We need vendors here.
They aren't "vendors", Walter!
They're "dealers."
They're called "dealers."
I don't care
what their name is.
Dealers! Whatever!
We need dealers there!
Those three I met today
should have three sub-dealers
working for them.
Exponential growth.
That's the key here.
Which part of "that isn't our
territory" don't you understand?
Do you think we can go there
and that's it?
- That they'll welcome us?
- No, of course not!
But they won't hurt us either.
Yes, sure.
Listen to me.
Don't do anything. Don't.
Wait.
You don't understand.
Rules have changed, Jose.
You're a killer.
What?
A killer.
That's what people say.
Someone bothered you,
and you crushed his skull.
That's not how it happened.
It doesn't matter!
As long as it's our competitors
who believe it, not the police.
Competitors and police.
You're going from bad to worse.
Jose, don't you see
how great this is?
Don't you understand?
You are like a blowfish.
What?
The blowfish is small,
slow, not cunning.
Thank you for the compliment.
- Let me finish.
- Okay.
The blowfish
has a secret weapon
that makes it special:
it seems weak,
but it has something.
What?
I don't know what it is!
I don't even know
what fish that is.
The blowfish puffs up
five or six times
larger than normal. Why?
To be intimidating.
To scare the other fish.
It doesn't matter
if they're aggressive.
Do you understand now?
- You're a blowfish!
- I'm a blowfish.
Who messes with the blowfish?
- Nobody.
- Nobody!
Exactly!
It's just all an illusion, Jose.
You're a blowfish. Repeat it.
I'm a blowfish.
- Say it like you mean it.
- I'm a blowfish.
- Yes, sir. Exactly!
- I'm a blowfish!
As I'm a good blowfish,
I'll puff myself up.
A blowfish!
There are too many men here.
Next time,
bring some girls.
I like watching.
Stop it, Tortuga.
Let's do business.
Calm down.
Hey, you.
What?
Juárez, please.
The newbie
doesn't speak English.
You don't speak English?
You better learn English, boy.
It's the language of love.
At least, of my love.
Do you know what I mean?
I'll teach you.
Let's make a deal.
Look at this.
I want one.
Item number 332L.
Chaps with gold buttons.
I want a pair.
Write it down.
Item number:
342L.
Look at this hat, 5000X;
it's the best.
I want twenty for my team.
Twenty?
It's two thousand each, Tortuga.
You won't pay for them.
You'll get three.
Five!
Five.
Five, or there is no deal.
Okay. Deal.
One is for you.
You must protect from the sun.
Okay, okay.
Stop wasting our time.
When and where is the meeting?
You don't know
how to do business.
I'll kick your ass
if you don't speak clearly.
- What's up?
- Hey, hey, hey. Sit down.
Calm down, Colombian boy.
They call me Tortuga.
Do you know why?
You'll know why.
Because I take my time,
and I'll still defeat the hare.
That reminds me of something.
What?
I saw a pair of crocodile boots
that are beautiful!
You're a son of a bitch.
Henry is doing
great in Mexico.
That's wonderful.
He deserves it.
After all the work
he has done.
Are you going there?
No, without mariachis
and margaritas,
there's no María.
Besides,
it seems it's horrible there.
It's a desert full of dust
with nasty men.
He's on an important operation;
very busy.
Yes?
Isn't it dangerous?
It isn't worse than here.
Apparently, it's an office work.
Between us,
that's what I wanted.
Hey, speaking of office work,
I got myself a job.
No way!
Who gave you a job
as big as you are?
Thank you.
You know what I mean.
Seriously, who gave you a job
in your condition?
Ernesto Silva.
No...
Mr. Grabby-Hands?
María.
It only happened once,
in the New Year's Eve party.
He was so drunk,
he could barely talk.
It's okay
if you justify him.
No, María,
he apologized plenty of times.
He's married.
He has a family now.
The last thing he wants
is a sexual harassment lawsuit.
It won't happen again.
Is money that tight?
Cielo,
you know we can always help out.
All you have to do
is tell Henry and me.
Thank you, María.
You know Walter.
He wouldn't accept money.
Speaking of the devil.
- Cielo?
- Hello! In the kitchen.
- Hello, María.
- Hello, Walter.
- How're you?
- I'm fine.
- Hello, my love.
- Hello.
I'll wash my hands
and be right back.
Don't you dare to tell him!
I wouldn't do that!
Mom, is this cheese
a different brand?
I think so.
But it's the same cheese.
No, it tastes different.
It's not the same.
My dear.
Next time,
you'll go to the market
so that you buy
the brand you prefer.
So we all win, okay?
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Walter, don't you
notice anything?
Honey, is there a funeral today?
A funeral?
Do I look that bad?
No, no, no,
just the opposite.
You look very well.
Mom got a new job.
A job? Why?
Do I need to show you
the bank statements?
It's not
that I don't want you to...
Honey, I'm just thinking
on your condition?
I'm afraid for the baby.
The doctor said I can work
as long as I'm not in pain.
I'm just going to be sitting
in an office.
I'll be better there
than here cooking brownies.
Where?
Construcciones Silva.
What about the welding fumes?
Isn't that why you had to quit?
Yes, they were building
the place then.
They've finished now.
And the office
is a clean and safe place.
Didn't Mr. Silva pass away?
- Yes.
- Who took his place?
Ernesto, his son.
Right. I don't want
to be late my first day back.
- Bye, honey.
- Have a nice day.
Bye.
Hello.
You left your cave.
Yes. It's too empty inside.
I'll buy a new television.
I know. It isn't easy
to live without Sesame Street.
What are you doing?
Are you drawing?
Can I see it?
It's really nice!
It looks like...
It's like a tattoo.
- That's the idea.
- Really?
I work part-time
at a tattoo place.
That's great!
It's a really good draw.
I used to draw, too.
Really?
What stopped you?
Things happened.
I suppose you have tattoos.
You don't?
A tattoo artist with no tattoos.
It's a big commitment.
You have to take it
very seriously.
I do have one. Look.
José Miguel Rosas!
Everybody's been talking
about you.
I respect you
for what you did.
Well-done.
Okay.
Rosas?
Yes.
I thought your name was Mercado.
I have to go.
Bye.
Tortuga is really earning
his nickname.
Wait.
He'll show up.
As long as he doesn't want
more stuff from the catalogue.
Calm down.
He's a good cop in Colombia.
I'm not so sure.
Compared to us,
Colombian are girls.
Okay, okay, calm down.
Is there a problem?
Why don't you speak
face to face?
What's up, man?
Calm down. Take it easy.
What's that shit?
There's our man.
- Hey! Come, come, come.
- What's up?
- Look.
- What?
Look over there,
next to the leaves.
- Look.
- Let me see.
- That's our man.
- Didn't I...?
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Look... Look at it.
Look!
Look the end of Tortuga, man!
Step by step.
He ended up here.
What's the matter?
- Poor him!
Poor Tortuga.
Where are you going, Colombian?
I'll get an evidence bag.
What is it, Colombian?
You've never seen
a head on a turtle?
Welcome to Mexico, man!
Let's take a picture!
The Colombian feels sick.
Look at it.
Guillermo!
My leg!
No, no.
I can't feel my leg!
No!
The game has changed.
This is our city now,
all right?
Bogotá is our territory now.
We sell where we want to
and when we want to.
Understood?
We're the kings.
Well, I'm the king.
You will be
the princes or princesses.
Let's say we're the princes.
No, I want to be a knight
with his sword and armor.
Okay, okay.
Let's begin.
We need more people.
We need people on the streets
working for you.
They work for you,
and you work for me.
Layered, like a lasagna.
This is called
exponential growth.
- Am I clear?
- Clear as water.
Yes. Just one thing, man.
Let's think of a water
clearer than Bogotá river's.
Okay. It's all set.
Begin.
Okay. See you.
Let's work.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Ready.
They'll do the job.
We'll be rich!
Pesos, dollars.
You understand me, don't you?
We are not charging enough.
Really?
First,
you monopolize the market.
Then, you raise the price.
Simple economics.
- May I come in?
- Of course.
As if you were
in your company.
You're all set up.
Yes.
The office is beautiful.
It's close to the bathroom.
I don't have to walk far.
Yes, I thought
that would be important.
Yes, thank you.
I wanted to thank you
for having me back.
You don't have to thank me.
I need you here.
You need a bib.
This happens
every time I'm with the girls.
Do you have some paper or...?
No, no.
Hey, and Diana?
How is she doing?
We split up a year ago.
I didn't know it.
- Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry.
No, no...
She was...
She's happier now,
and calm.
So am I.
I have some crisis.
We've been together
since high school.
- I remember that.
- Yes.
I don't know.
People change.
Well, we're here to work.
And to work hard, right?
I'll see you by the cafeteria.
Yes, sir.
Welcome.
Keep on creating.
- Thanks.
- Take care.
We should have lunch one day
and remember the old times.
Yes, sure. I'd love it.
Okay. See you.
Hello.
My name is not Jose Mercado.
I'm José Miguel Rosas.
I like to be called Jose.
The man you met the other day
isn't my father.
Don't kick me out.
I really like this place.
I don't make it my business
what you do.
But if you're doing
illegal things,
don't do it here, okay?
Okay.
I bought a new television.
- Really?
- Really.
I've hired cable television.
I have all the channels.
Do you want to see it?
I was told the blacks in
this TV were really good.
They're the best.
And the sound is even better.
But...
Well, I'll keep it down,
so that neighbors
don't complain.
I don't know why the signal
is taking so long to appear.
When you were a little girl,
didn't you pretend
to have magic and that you
were able to turn on the TV?