Hi, teach?
It's me.
I don't mean to bother,
I know you're pretty busy
with your retirement
and everything.
But it's very important for me
that you know about
everything that's been going on.
Remember the buyer
you introduced me to?
The guy I was
cooking with?
Well, it turned out
that...
Well, this guy and I
had some sort of...
misunderstanding, you
know.
So...
Well, the thing got
a little messy.
But you don't have to
worry,
it's all straightened
out now.
Just a heads-up,
there's been a kind
of change in management.
Anyway, it's all fine now,
I'm taking care of it.
I was just calling because...
Well, er...
It's important for me
that you know everything.
I'm not bothering you
any longer.
That's it.
Feel free to call me
if you want the details,
'cause here I am.
Don't you worry.
Bye.
So there I was,
on the tanker, right?
Pumping the water in,
and the teach's down there,
watching to make sure we do it
exactly what he calculated.
And we gotta be real precise,
'cause you know
methylene and water
-weigh different.
-That's obvious.
This guy did
his investigation and all,
because we couldn't screw it.
Anyway, I'm up there
with my hose,
we were running out of time.
And remember
we had that accident there
-that we made up.
-The bikes and everything.
-The bikes, we know.
-Of course, yeah.
And it was just going on great,
until suddenly...
this truck appeared,
and we were pretty much screwed.
No, no, no,
that was the whole fuss
because the man wanted
to tow the other car, right?
To clean the road.
But, what did
you do then?
Could you do
something
about the man?
What could I do? Tell him?
"Would you please
help me
and take it slower?
We're still stealing
cargo back there".
No, we couldn't do
anything about it.
I was watching there,
and in the meanwhile,
the gallons were just slowly
ticking away.
Until the teach
gave me the sign.
He said, "Cut it".
And so I fling the hose,
I'm grabbing the cap,
I'm screwing in the bolts
and all,
and that was it.
-But guess what?
-What happened?
-The truck started moving.
-And you were on top?
Of course, what could I do?
No, I'd have pissed my pants
But everything went smoothly,
as the teach had organized it,
he's a genius.
Those guys didn't realize
we were stealing.
It's been the biggest
tanker robbery
in the whole Latin America.
Just imagine,
and who was there?
My nephew.
-Well done, uncle.
-Well done, dork.
Good, that's it.
Can I get you anything
else?
No, beautiful,
I think we're leaving.
I'm ready for the check.
Good.
Can you pay at
the register?
-Fine, thanks.
-Okay.
You ready to cook or what?
For sure.
Are you sure you'll be
able
to run your own lab
and all?
After all I've been telling you,
you've no faith in me?
Trust me!
Well, no more talking, man.
Let's start
making money.
-Good.
-Fine.
You pay, I need to pee.
-Of course.
-I'll be right back.
I'm leaving you too.
This country's
changed.
In my time,
you could really think
of helping others
and all that.
That's why
I got into this stuff,
to see if I could make
a social change.
But I don't know what happened.
I don't know when it was
that we started losing
our moral principles.
No everything's a question
of business, money, bro.
That's too sad.
But you're making money, right?
Well, yeah,
that's the good
part.
You have to be positive.
You've to see the glass
half full.
[laughing
]
Well, then...
Good.
That's it.
Smart asses.
Let's go, we're out of here.
Wake up, we're leaving!
Fine, it's done, let's go.
That's it.
That's it, baldy.
José Miguel Rosas.
How are you?
Not so
good?
Well, luckily,
I'm here to help you.
I came to talk
about your partner...
What was his name?
Jaisenber...?
Heisenberg...?
Walter B...?
[laughing
]
That was the look
I was hoping for.
Thanks for confirming it.
So, bro, lucky for you...
I'm not interested in
you,
I'm more interested in
him.
Besides, I got an offer
for you.
If you help me out
here,
if you tell me everything
about you and Walter,
how you cooked the
meth,
who you sold it to,
where you distributed
it,
I promise I'll
help you.
I've a friend on the
case,
he's an attorney
and he'll wipe it off.
Nothing happened
here.
What do you
think?
Look, I know Walter
is the mastermind
on this operation.
And, well...
according to the things
you've been doing lately,
I can tell the relationship
between you two
is not going that
well.
No more chemistry
between the two of you?
Am I wrong?
Why don't you suck it?
[laughing
]
You really want us to
handle it
like this?
Why don't you try
and beat it out of me?
That's your thing, right?
Faggot, look at
yourself.
You're into deep
shit.
What? He
humiliated you?
And he
threatened you,
I guess.
I don't see
happiness
anywhere.
Well, for me
happiness doesn't mean
going out there
throwing millions away.
I don't think
Walter
liked that much.
But maybe that's why you
did it,
I understand.
I'd have done the same
thing.
And you know...
Walter's my
brother-in-law.
And that
shithead...
lied to me in
the face.
He used me for a
year,
that motherfucker.
Me, he was
mocking me.
So I understand
what you're going through.
Let me tell you,
help me out.
The two of us can catch
him
and put him behind bars.
What do you
say?
Talk.
With you...
never!
Agent Navarro,
glad yo see you.
How many suspects
have you beaten to death lately?
That's his favorite method,
you knew that?
Hasn't he told you?
Hasn't he told you the story
with my client?
Last time they were
alone together, he knocked
the poor kid unconscious.
Who'd think of that?
He's so nice,
with that big smile.
You shouldn't trust him.
So, what do you want, gentlemen?
Another lawsuit?
I could start writing
your names down.
Hey, bye, Rocky!
On your guard,
hit left.
Defense.
And you, boys,
just go and have a coffee,
this will take me quite long.
That's it, no sugar,
it's bad for your nerves.
So...
Let's see, where shall
we start?
First thing, I'm gonna try
to remain calm,
but will you do me a favor
and tell me
what you're thinking?
What the hell is up
with you?
My guys are
busting their asses
trying to hide Walt's
money
from anyone holding
a Government ID.
And you're tossing
yours
out a window?
Like a drunken
Marilyn Monroe?
And I also have to hear
about your little act
of philanthropy on the
news.
What's wrong with
you?
Did you hit your
head
or something
and didn't tell me
about it?
Why didn't you call me
the second you got
arrested?
What did you say to
Navarro?
I didn't tell him anything,
chill out.
Chill out! Chill
out!
Tasty, easy.
Chill
out!
I can't chill out right
now.
Why? 'Cause
things
have gone nuclear.
You get it?
Biblical.
I guess Navarro shared with you
his recent discovery.
Did he? Ok, well,
then...
You realize why I can't
be chilled
or relaxed,
I want you to use
the money I left you
for unexpected events, Saúl.
No, listen for a second,
Saúl, lis--
Saúl, Saúl, listen...
Look, Saúl,
could you please
stop talking for a second?
No, I don't care!
Just make it happen.
You're the one who knows.
Do whatever you have to do, OK?
And call me when he's out.
Good.
Dad, I'm home!
I'm upstairs.
Are you going to work
today?
Yes.
You were out late last
night.
-Dad!
-Yes!
I'm gonna head out,
okay?
Where you going?
I'm going to aunt
María's.
She's just called,
and asked me
to help her out
with the
computer,
and asked me to stay
for dinner.
-Is that cool?
-Cool.
-Alright, bye.
-No, no, no.
Junior, wait a second,
Junior.
I wanted to talk
to you.
Dad, what happened to you?
This? Nothing.
No, I'm fine.
You sure you're fine, dad?
Im sure.
Come, let's talk.
-What?
-I want...
I want us to talk
about a couple of
things.
Sit down.
Er...
Look...
You
know?
I think you
deserve to know
what's happening,
the truth.
I don't want to make up
lie
to you anymore,
any more stories.
I passed out
yesterday.
It was a second,
it was very briefly,
but that's how I
got this.
But, why did you pass out?
Because...
Well, my latest scans
show a little shadow on my
lung.
But my doctor put me
right on
a new round of
chemo,
which is why I've been
so weak lately.
Of course, I know I was
pushing myself too hard.
I know that's
bullshit...
But I've learned my lesson,
really.
I know I've to take care
of myself, and I will.
But, what's next?
What do we have to do?
What did they tell you?
Nothing, relax,
calm down.
Don't worry, we'll go on.
That's what we've
always done.
Look, I beat this once.
There's no reason to
think
I won't again.
So don't you
worry.
Besides, the
doctor told me
I'm responding great
to the treatment.
I'm fine, okay?
Junior, I need us
to be positive.
Really.
Can you do that?
-Mmmhh.
-Good.
Say you
will.
That's it,
perfect.
Well, that's what
I wanted to tell you.
Go to your aunt María's
and help her with the computer.
We'll talk about this
later with your mom.
No, dad, no way.
I'd rather stay here with you.
Hi, love.
Hello.
Hey, wasn't Junior
coming with you?
He had to come? How
come?
How was it?
How'd it go?
That bad?
-I didn't tell them, María.
-Why not, Henry?
It's just not time yet.
María, I can't go there
and tell them,
"Look, the person
I've been chasing
all this time
is my brother-in-law,
I had him in front of my eyes
and didn't see him."
-I can't do that, María.
-Why not, Henry?
Why not? We've already
talked about it this
morning.
You've to tell them
as soon as possible.
What if they found out
you already knew?
I've got some things
I gotta chase down.
-What things?
-Leads.
I've no proof,
I need to gather some proof.
Leads, proof, okay,
what's going on?
Where are you right now?
I want to know.
Look, I'm not hiding anything.
Please, do me a favor.
Let me do my job.
You sure you wanna do this?
Yes.
Now.
My name's Walter Blanco.
My ID number is 970
451 822.
I'm currently living in Bogotá.
This is my confession.
They're here.
Thank you for coming.
Cielo and I
wanted to tell you--
Good morning, ladies.
My name's César. I'll be
taking care of you today.
Can I start anybody off
with some beverages?
Want to see our wine list?
How about some cocktails to--?
No, thanks,
we'll think about it.
Of course.
I'll leave you the menu.
Excuse me.
-So...
-You're confessing?
There's nothing to confess here.
We're here to talk
about Walter, Jr.
Walter Junior and
Valentina
should be living with
us.
And while we respect
your opinion, María,
we also think that your concern
is exaggerated.
-You do?
-It's misplaced.
Look, this thing you're doing
to take Junior
away from us
and lure him to your house...
-I wasn't trying to lure him.
-Call it what you want.
But the thing is, we believe...
you should leave our children
out of this.
Junior's already had
enough for this year.
How about
that?
Henry, do you realize
what this investigation
will do to Junior?
If he hears all these things?
What do you prefer
him to hear?
Me kicking your door
and arresting
you?
That?
If that day ever comes,
so be it.
But in the meanwhile,
you have no evidence
to support your claims
against me.
Why tear this family apart?
I wanted to tell
you
we've a couple
of specialties
that aren't in the menu:
Raw sea bass,
grilled provolone
cheese--
Look, do us a favor, okay?
We're talking here.
Can you come again later?
Thanks.
How can you sit there
and listen to this?
The kids are in danger,
keeping them under the same roof
as this monster.
-You know that.
-They're safe.
Are they?
You yourself asked me
to take them to my place.
And I brought them back myself.
Look, María...
Whatever you think Walter did,
this is not
an ongoing situation.
-Cielo...
-No.
They need to understand.
It's over, really.
It's over.
It's over, it's in the past,
understand me.
And you expect us
to believe you?
After all the lies
you've told us,
you expect us to believe you?
I don't even know
what's true anymore.
That affair of yours?
Did that even happen?
Look, María, that's not
the issue here.
The issue here is that
Junior has just found out
that my cancer's back.
He's already facing the idea
of living without his father.
To put this on top of that?
It's just not right.
Well, look,
are you going to tell me
what's right?
-No, I don't mean that.
-What's right?
Killing
people's right?
Cooking meth?
Controlling a drug cartel?
-Henry...
-Is that right?
-There's no cartel.
-Quit that bullshit!
What do I do
for you to believe me?
Why don't you kill yourself,
Walter?
Why don't you kill
yourself,
cut your veins
or eat some poison,
This whole thing
dies with you, right?
That's what you wanted
to ask Henry, right?
Time, 'cause you're dying.
Come on, do it.
-Kill yourself.
-That's not the answer.
You're right,
it's not a solution.
This motherfucker's not
getting off that easy.
-Henry...
-And the same goes for you,
if you stick with him.
You know what, brother?
This is it.
Because I'm not going to allow
you to walk away
with this one,
did you understand?
That is not what we're saying.
We're here to talk
about something else.
Enough with the bullshit!
You're just a couple of liars.
I'm not here to negotiate
your way out of this thing.
No, sir.
There's only one solution here,
and that would be your facing
everything you've done here.
You get it?
There's no other way.
Let's go now.
OK.
My name is Walter Blanco.
My ID number is 970 451 822.
I currently live in Bogotá.
This is my confession.
If you're watching this tape,
I'm probably dead.
murdered by my brother-in-law,
Henry Navarro.
Mr. Navarro has been building
a meth empire
for over a year now,
and using me as his chemist.
Shortly after my 50th birthday,
my brother-in-law asked me
that I use
my chemistry knowledge
at his service,
to cook methamphetamine.
He would then
be in charge of the rest,
like the distribution
of this drug,
using the connections he made
during his career
at the Anti-narcotics agency.
I was astounded at first,
I thought it was impossible
for a person
with Henry's high morals,
that I've always considered
to have an irreproachable
code of ethics,
to be making
such a proposition to me.
Well, at that time
I was particularly vulnerable,
something he knew
and took advantage of.
I had been just diagnosed
with cancer at the time,
and the whole thing
had affected me deeply.
Above all, I was worried
about my family's wellbeing.
So Henry took me
for a ride one day,
let's say he invited me
to witness an operation,
it was a raid on a lab,
one of those meth labs,
and he did that,
among other things,
to show me how...
such a small meth operation
could make me earn
loads of money.
So I was weak and accepted.
At the time, Henry
had partnered up
with an important businessman,
Mr. Gustavo Cortés.
He's a well-known entrepreneur,
he owns a huge
chain of restaurants
He managed to somehow sell me
into servitude
to this Mr. Cortés,
they made me cook,
as they say,
this synthetic drug
at a very sophisticated lab,
owned by Mr. Cortés.
At some point, I wanted to quit
and retire from all this,
but Gustavo Cortés's answer was
not only threatening me,
but also my family:
he threatened to kill
my wife and my two kids,
so I had no other choice
but stay.
Eventually, they started
having some trouble,
Gustavo Cortés
and my brother-in-law.
I don't know the exact reason,
but those differences they had
put some distance between them
and they ended up having
a huge fight.
So much so, Gustavo Cortés
attacked my brother-in-law.
He failed,
but he was seriously injured
and had to stay in bed
for a while,
totally unable to walk.
During that time,
I had to pay his bills.
It was a total amount
of 350 million pesos,
that's what his therapy cost.
I've the proof
to support that.
The thing is, when he recovered,
he was bent on revenge.
So he partnered up
with some Héctor Salamanca,
and together they plotted
to kill Cortés.
Well, you know how that ended.
I was the one who built the bomb
they used
against Gustavo Cortés.
I had to do it.
My brother-in-law forced me to
I've to confess that
I've tried to kill myself
a number of times,
But I've never been able to.
I haven't had the guts.
I'm a coward.
I wanted to go to the police,
but I was scared, I didn't know
whom I could trust.
I didn't know if he had
more connections there,
and that's impossible now,
he's been promoted
to the head of the department.
Of course, having that position,
he kept me in line,
and he even kidnapped,
let's say he kept my children
at his house for three months,
just to put some pressure on me.
My wife doesn't know.
She has never been aware
of my activities,
and she was horrified.
I understand that.
I hated myself for what
I had brought upon my family.
I tried once again to quit,
and this was his answer.
I live in fear every day,
I don't...
I don't know
when he'll kill me,
or what's worst, if he'll do
something to my family.
So my last resort was
to make this video
and hope that somebody
will finally learn about it.
That the whole world finds out
the kind of person
Henry Navarro is.
That's what I hope.
I want him to be
finally exposed.
Who do you think ...
he's shown this to, Henry?
It's a threat against me.
He hasn't showed this
to anyone.
Henry, you've to show this
to your boss tomorrow.
I mean, anyone who knows you
must know you don't--
350 million what?
What's he talking about,
My God.
-María.
No, María...
350 million what?
Henry, I was told that money
was gambling money.
What was gambling
money?
María, please,
what are you...?
How was I supposed to know?
How would I know
where it came from?
So my treatment...
was paid with that
money, María?
What about my
insurance?
It wouldn't have covered
the treatment
we wanted to give you,
and I wanted
the best for you, Henry.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because you wouldn't
have accepted.
Without it, you may never
have been able to walk again.
María, I've nothing
left.
I'm done with this.
Son of a bitch.
What are we going to do?
If I were you,
I'd be more nervous.
Hey! But, why?
Why do these meetings
must always take place
at the bottom of the
world?
The typical kind of
place
where you get killed
and buried.
The car's clean.
I wouldn't have driven it here
if it wasn't.
You should get one of these.
It's easy.
Besides, it reads radio signals.
And you can get it
on the Internet
and save that pain in the ass...
What does Henry
know?
He knows you're Heisenberg,
but I think that's all.
Otherwise, you'd be locked up.
What did he say,
exactly?
He wanted to know
everything about you,
everything we did.
What else?
I don't think he's told
anyone else.
No one, not even Anti-narcotics.
Why do you say that?
Just him being there
all by himself.
He seemed to be acting
on his own.
Everything was on tape,
and he came
and turned off the camera.
He was acting weird,
he didn't want
the rest of the policemen
to hear anything.
Alright, good.
Could we now please talk
about that shit rain
he brought upon us,
thanks to this good Samaritan?
Do you want to hazard a guess
what his little charity drive
cost you?
Why don't you go
take a walk, Saúl?
Will you let me help
you, Jose?
Don't act tough,
man.
I don't like seeing you
like that.
Maybe it's time for a
change.
- What kinda change?
-I don't know.
I don't know exactly.
Maybe it's time for you to just
leave all of this behind, Jose.
Get away,
move away from Bogotá and...
start all over again.
Look,
Saúl knows a man.
He specializes
in giving people new identities.
He moves them far away
and sets them up
with a whole new life.
Maybe that's what you need.
No, I know it may sound
a little bit extreme,
but if you think about it,
it makes sense.
Imagine that!
Starting a new life,
far away from here.
You deserve that, Jose!
Just think about it.
You finally get
the job you want,
something you like.
A girl, a good woman
to start the family
you've ever wanted with.
Look, if I could,
I'd change a thousand things
in my life.
I'd change decisions
I've made,
I'd change moments,
people, meetings.
If I could simply
had a chance to hit
the reset button.
In a few years, this might
all feel like nothing more
than a bad dream.
Come on, bro.
Would you just,
for once, stop manipulating
me?
What?
You've heard me.
Can you just stop working me
for, like, ten seconds
straight?
Stop jerking me around,
please.
I am not working you.
That's exactly
what you're doing, bro.
Just drop the whole
concerned dad thing
and tell me the
truth.
This whole thing you're
saying,
that I should
get lost,
you make it sound as if
it was for my own good,
for my own interest.
But you know this whole
thing's
really about you, bro.
Am I
wrong?
'Cause you are the one
who's got an interest
in me leaving town.
And you know why?
'Cause you know
your dickhead brother-in-law
won't give it up
until you fall,
and he catches
you.
Just ask me to do
you a favor.
Face it, bro.
Just tell me,
for the first time in
your life,
that you don't give
a shit
about me.
It's either that,
or you will just
have to kill me,
same way you did with
Mario.
I mean, isn't that
what this is all about?
Us meeting
way the hell out here?
In case I say no?
Tell me, Walter,
just look into my eyes
and tell me you need
me
to save your ass.
Or just kill me out
here.
-Thank you very much.
-Thanks.
Hey, I've got my chemo
in about 45 minutes.
Can you take over
the register for me?
Cielo, are you listening?
Look, the tape thing
worked,
I assure you.
We're fine, we're
cool.
Tell me one thing.
How come Oscar and Rodolfo
are watching over
José Miguel Rosas out there,
at the lawyer's office?
I put them on
it.
How come, you put them on it?
Okay, fine, I've understood.
Since you're the boss
and they aren't my men,
they're not part of my team,
you can do
whatever you feel like.
I mean, why am I
asking you this?
There's one thing, Henry.
Rosas belongs to
another division, remember.
You got a history with this kid.
He could sue us.
You know what's going on?
What should I say
to the big boss?
I gotta pull my guys out, Henry.
Fine. Take them off.
Isn't that what you want?
Go take them off!
Sure you don't want
to say good-bye to anyone?
No.
Your family, friends,
Andrea or the kid?
No, I'm not saying good-bye.
I'll say it again,
this is the end of it.
Once I make the call,
there's no take-backs.
You get that?
Good.
Afternoon, I need
a new dust filter
for an extra-strong MX 322.
Yeah, I'll pick it up today.
No, no, the vacuum's
still working,
it just doesn't move much.
I mean, not like before.
Yeah, yeah, he's read
the catalogue.
The manual too,
it's clear.
I explained it to him,
he's good with it.
Okay, he'll be waiting for it
in an hour.
It's done.
This time it'll only cost you
500 million.
Your benefactor asked me to send
you out with something extra.
Get you started, you know?
Wants you to stay out of trouble
and be able to defend yourself
until you get into the groove
of your new life.
Of course, you don't toss it
out the window
or by the road,
as you usually du.
You might wanna think
about making a budget.
Hey!
Hey, no, you can't
do that here, kid!
Don't! Put that out!
Seriously, put that out.
Look, Mr. Naturist,
hippie, gypsy, tripy.
I'm not gonna let you
sabotage this thing!
You hear me?
This guy is not gonna take you
if you show up high.
So stop screwing around,
because we'll just
be in trouble.
Don't keep that, don't.
Leave it here, leave it.
Some people are immune
to good advice.
I'm gonna get a bag
for this cash.
Don't even think about
lighting up again!
Francisca!
I need a bag, a suitcase,
a backpack, anything.
He's gonna drop you
at the pickup spot
and he'll leave immediately.
Why?
Guy won't pick you up
if you've got company.
You have a phone?
No, the police took it.
Here, take it.
In case something goes wrong,
guy doesn't show, whatever,
you call me.
Is this for real,
Saúl?
Don't you have something
more manly?
Stop it,
stop busting my--
I dunno if it's for girls
or boys, but it's for free.
No, you don't look
a gift horse in the mouth.
Do you?
Stewart,
this is the address.
Now do me a favor
and behave yourself,
be patient.
This guy's punctual
with a capital P. Understood?
Don't move,
don't do no bullshit.
You just stay there, quietly.
He picks you up, you pay,
he'll take your ID.
He'll give you a new one.
So, that's it.
Good-bye, José Miguel Rosas.
Hello, Mr. XXX,
or whatever you may call
the man congratulated
by society.
Okay.
So, do I get to
pick where I go?
Well, of course.
It's your life,
you can do whatever you want.
Want a suggestion?
San Andrés.
I like it, it's sunny,
nice women wearing G-strings,
well-tanned,
you can swim with dolphins.
How about the Amazonas?
Well, you can swim
with pink dolphins there..
I don't know about the Amazonas.
The jungle, the bugs, dunno,
I get allergic,
but whatever floats your boat.
Amazonas is fine.
-Yeah, I like the Amazonas.
-Right, sure.
Anywhere you can get
a fresh start is gonna be good.
So, Jose.
-Good luck.
-Fine, thanks.
Good. Are you armed?
No.
Anyway, we better make sure.
-If you'll excuse me.
-That's it.
Okay.
That's better.
-He's clean.
-Fine.
Good luck,
and have a good new life.
If you'll excuse
me.
Okay.
What are you doing, bro?
Hey, Saúl, I'm here!
-Easy, this doesn't hurt.
-Easy, bro.
I think Byron
must have been poisoned.
Yeah, there's some stuff
called ricin.
How do you know that,
Jose?
It doesn't matter,
just tell them
it's a supposition.
Ricin.
Why did you poison Byron,
Walter?
How the hell
could I have gotten it?
Saúl, you made Saúl
take it from me!
What are you doing, bro?
Hey, Saúl, I'm here!
Easy, man, easy.
Tell me why you did it.
They didn't pick you up?
I thought--
Red code, red co--!
Stewart, Stewart!
What are you doing now,
shithead?
Stay where you are,
both of you!
What did I do?
I don't get it. What did I do?
-You stole it off of me, Saúl!
-Me?
You and that fat ass
stole from me!
You stole the cigarette pack.
Okay, calm down.
I had Stewart
steal your joint,
I couldn't risk the guy
not taking you.
No, no, no, before
that!
The cigarette! You had him
steal it off of me!
What?
The poisoned
cigarette, bro.
The ricin
cigarette!
You had him steal
it from me!
And all for that
son of a bitch, Blanco!
He poisoned Byron,
and you helped him!
-No, no.
-You helped him, Saúl!
Calm down, José Miguel, please.
Tell me one more time
to calm down!
Tell me to clam down!
Alright, okay, listen to me.
Well, yeah, that time
I told Stewart
to take the ricin from you,
but Walter forced me to,
you get it?
He told me he was helping you,
he was saving you.
I swear, if I had known
what it was for,
I'd have never agreed to it.
You know me, I don't do that.
Please, take it easy now.
Calm down now.
No, no.
You're a fucking
son of a bitch,
Saúl.
Back up!
Don't touch me!
What do I pay you for, Stewart?
It's me, it's me...
We're in deep shit.
Son of a bitch!