So what?
How does it work?
You are talking
to the wrong man.
I just wanted to tell you
that if you just have
some extra grams...
of meth.
Are you shitting
me?
It shows you're a cop
from a mile distance.
I just want a little bit
of something.
I see where you
are coming from.
See that truck there.
- What truck?
- The one parked there.
The blue
one.
You are spying on me,
right?
What's wrong with you?
A flower van over there.
Can't you at least be
original?
Everybody uses that van.
Do you get
it?
You know what you should do
is a garbage truck.
The agents in the middle
of the garbage.
With gloves and everything.
I could never figure that out.
Sure.
Don't you say
that I'm not
helping justice!
Did you hear that?
Just think about it.
Okay, okay, you know what?
If you're not selling me,
I leave.
Good luck, good luck.
Come here, bro.
You gave up easily.
Come here.
I'm not a cop,
do you understand?
I'm not a cop.
Then lift your shirt.
Show me you're not
wearing a wire.
Okay.
No! I'm blinded by
white!
Douchebag.
Come on.
I was joking.
Come on, bro.
I'm just joking.
I wish I had your abs,
man.
Whatever, dude.
I'm not even sure
I want to buy anymore.
Come on, bro.
Try to put yourself
in my place.
I need to be sure
that you're not a cop.
And how do we do that?
I don't know, I have to think
about something.
I need to prove it,
you know?
I know!
Go over there and
punch that dude
right in the face.
That man?
Are you insane?
No way.
He'd kick my ass.
True that.
He would destroy you
with just one fist.
You know what?
I believe you, bro.
Two grams cost 100 dollars.
100 dollars?
Of course!
Purity is valuable, bro.
And where do we do it?
Done.
Enjoy it, man.
Okay, good luck.
One more thing.
Get on the ground!
What's up?
No, bro! No, no!
Come on!
Check him, check him.
He keeps it there.
Handcuffs!
Good night, dear viewers.
Welcome to this new edition
of Better call Saúl!
We have open lines,
9800-321-21-00,
for you to communicate with us.
Better call Saúl!
Here we can solve any problem
you have, even those
you think nobody can solve.
Here I am.
Today we have a lot of guests,
all of them innocent,
that will tell us their stories
in front of the camera.
Here we have
our first guest.
Come here.
- She's coming from...
- Hello.
the beautiful county
of Anapoima
and now she will
tell us her problem.
Not only to Saúl,
but also to you
because you are
her witnesses.
Go on.
I came here because I work
at a clothing store.
Mi boss accused me of stealing.
He heard I'm going to quit,
that's why he's
accusing me of stealing.
How do you call that?
Blackmail!
Extortion!
That crime will be
punished.
His crime, not hers,
because she's innocent,
she didn't steal
anything.
But she can't prove it.
From now on,
she can prove it
because she called Saúl
and has his counsel.
Don't worry, Mrs.
Go in peace.
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Our next guest is John!
I was out partying,
minding my own business,
maybe in a place I shouldn't be,
but police arrived,
mistreated all us,
they asked me for my I.D.
and accused me
of something I didn't do.
I think that's abuse of power.
That's why I came--
Exactly, abuse of power.
What did he do?
He called Saúl. For what?
For solving his problem,
for avoiding the abuse of power.
Mister, don't worry,
you are advised by Saúl.
I will solve your problem.
And the authority will have
to pay for their abuse.
I really need
to get some furniture.
I suggest you start with
a bed.
God, I wish we could smoke
in here.
- Well, you can't.
- I know.
Besides, I really respect
my landlady.
Don't think I can't
smell that weed.
You better seriously
hope that airs out.
Open the windows.
My dad can come by
surprise.
If he finds out,
he will kick you out
and keep your security
deposit.
- Really?
- Yes.
He has a nose like
a damn bloodhound.
Has he ever caught you?
Many times.
Do you think he can come today?
What do you say?
Maybe we should
light up some weed.
No, thanks.
Is it cool if I burn one?
Maybe you'll change your mind.
Do what you want to do,
it's okay.
Is everything okay?
Are you all right?
Did I say something wrong?
What is this?
Am I that good?
This is a medallion.
My 18-month chip.
I'm in recovery.
And smoking weed
is like stepping stones.
That's cool. Right on.
Congratulations.
You know, I don't really
burn much anymore.
It's just a sometime thing.
But no more in the house.
I promise.
Okay?
Do you want
to go grab some dinner?
We can eat here.
No, I better hit it.
Are you mad at me?
Are we cool?
Juana!
Don't you think
he's asking a lot?
Yes, and he knows it.
He's done nothing but apologize.
Is this going to be
every Saturday now?
It's just the end
of the quarter.
You remember how that was.
The good news is
that I am earning double time.
Ouch!
When the sleepyhead...
When the sleepyhead
we have as a son wakes,
tell him to wash those sneakers.
And tell him not to put them
in the washing machine.
He has to let them air dry.
Okay.
What?
It's Saturday.
I don't know,
maybe you could get casual.
I'm just saying it
because you are beautiful.
Maybe we'll order
a pizza tonight?
Bye.
Cielo, hi, are you there?
I need to talk to you, Cielo.
I don't know what to do.
Call me.
Hi, María, what's up?
- Walter.
- How are you?
Thanks for coming.
You're welcome.
I came yesterday
and he was here.
He didn't even tell me
that he was coming back.
Who was killed?
Some Mexican guy
that was with him.
Three agents were wounded,
one of them lost his leg.
It was worst
than going to fight
with the guerrilla band,
where they have
land-mines
and bombs.
Because he lived a nightmare.
God.
And Gómez told me all this.
I heard him talking
to his boss,
but he didn't show
anything.
Then he hung up
and went to bed.
I asked him:
"What's going on?
What's going on?"
But he only said he was fine
and wanted to be alone.
- Is he upstairs?
- Yes.
- Should I?
- Please.
Not now, María!
It's me, Walter.
- What's up, bro?
- What's up?
- How are you?
- Fine. Fine.
- May I?
- Yes, come on in.
How are you
feeling?
Montezuma's Revenge, big time.
My stomach is really on fire.
Don't come too close
because I can...
Boom!
I'll take my risks.
Here.
I guess María told you about
what happened in Mexico.
Horrible.
And what did the boss there say?
That I should go back.
I was the man to stay
there,
- looking for those rats.
"Go back to
Colombia".
And what will you do?
Stay here?
No. Well, I don't know.
They are deliberating.
Do you want to talk it through
with somebody?
- Like who?
- I was thinking about María.
Or me, maybe.
Walter, I...
I don't know how to say it
because I don't want
to hurt you,
but talking with you...
How can I say it?
You and me don't have much
of what you might call
an experiential overlap.
What if I told you we do?
Look, Henry...
I have spent
my whole life scared.
Scared to death.
Frightened of things
that could happen,
might happen, might not happen.
50 years scared to death.
And 50 years is a long time.
Finding myself awake
at 3 in the morning.
But you know what?
Ever since my diagnosis
I sleep just fine.
Like a baby.
Okay.
Do you know what I found out?
That fear was my worst enemy.
I'm going to give you
some advice.
You can take it or not.
If I were you, I would get up,
I would get out
in the real world
and I would face reality.
Go get those bastards
and kick them
as hard as you can.
Because they deserve it.
- There it is.
- No, count them again.
- Walter!
- Again.
- That's it. 2000 dollars.
- Good.
You and I, we are going to feed
this machine 24 hours a day.
Right on.
Is this yours?
Give me that.
Okay, so this way.
We have 90.
110.
And this is for our parts.
Who's short?
Somebody didn't pay.
Okay, don't freak.
We didn't get ripped off.
Mono hasn't kicked in
his full amount.
I know he's planning on pulling
an all-nighter, so he's probably
still in the sack.
He's sleeping?
Then wake him up.
He can sleep after we're paid.
Why you have to be
such a hard on?
I'm not.
You're not his pal.
You're his boss.
This only works
when they're scared of you.
I can't believe you.
Leave your message
after the tone.
It's going straight
to voicemail.
Call again.
Walter...
You just count your money.
I'll handle this.
Is that okay?
Hi, Gordo, what's up?
Tell me, have you seen Mono?
Gordo!
Don't you cover for him!
I asked you
a straight-up question,
I expect a straight-up answer!
Yes or no?
What?
Okay.
What's up?
They were too scared to tell me.
Mono got busted.
Is everybody fine?
Did you miss me?
You've got more lives
than a damn cat.
Now if I can only learn
to lick myself.
Come here!
Good to see you!
Where is the tequila
bottle?
No, brother.
They seized it in customs.
- What a problem...
- How is that?
- How are you?
- Fine, fine.
Come here, tell me.
Tell me what
happened here.
- Could you work alone?
- Everything's fine.
- Everything's fine?
- How have you been?
So?
You don't care about those
criminology guys,
do you?
What do you think?
No, tell me.
You know me, right?
It's like if somebody
sleeps with your wife.
Would you like it?
- Hey, hey!
- It's the same thing!
I don't like people
looking into my cases.
I've been working on this
for a long time,
I don't need anybody
sniffing around
when nobody called them.
Let me explain you
what has happened.
We asked them to inform us
in case they would know
something
about the blue crystal.
Sure enough, last
night.
Let's do something.
Let's go to see
him.
You will know.
Come on, man.
Okay, let's go.
I don't want to talk.
I feel manipulated.
You told me to my face
you weren't a cop, man.
I thought we were
going to hang out.
We are, Mauricio.
Do I call you
Mauricio?
Or Mono, like they call you?
Talk.
I'm trying to help you
here.
I don't like the people
that lie, understood?
- I like serious people.
- Mono, Mono, listen.
I need you to tell me
who is your supplier,
who gives you the drug
for you to sell it, okay?
If you tell me, I think this
can end very well for you.
Mono, think about it.
This is a perfect
felony!
What are you doing talking to
my client without me present?
Bad call, bad call.
Wait a minute.
Who is who?
Did you graduate at 14?
You are really
young.
Have you said something
to this baby?
Did you say anything stupid?
By anything stupid,
I mean anything at all.
Close your mouth.
I'm seeing your molar.
Ouch! You have to lose it.
I'm talking about the molar.
You, out.
A police officer
must be the first one
respecting the law.
Ask your school teacher.
Go.
Come on.
And go grab your
baby's bottle,
I think it's
hot enough.
Very good, okay.
Who are you, boy?
You don't care if I
call you boy, right?
I like my clients
feel I'm trustworthy.
Yes, I'm Mauricio Mejía.
Mauricio Mejía.
Mauricio Mejía, good.
here you are.
Public masturbation.
No, bro.
Why don't you do it
at home,
like the rest of us
watching a good porn movie?
You don't do it in
the streets.
I'm not that man.
I'm the one
who was selling meth.
They say so,
but that's bullshit.
I wasn't selling anything.
Here it is.
That's it,
Mauricio.
That was a little
transpositional error.
Nothing a correcting fluid
can't take care of.
Meth.
In this country,
this is a crime.
Yes, but it was
just a little bit.
You know? A little bit.
Yes, but you exceeded
the minimum dose.
Crystal!
Crystal,
that's uncommon here.
Good luck arguing that
in court.
I'll do what I always do
with good people,
that is to say, the people
with a check book.
I'm going to get you
a second phone call.
You can call
anyone.
Your mommy, your daddy,
your parish priest,
somebody who can
deliver me a check
for 4000 dollars.
I'll write that down on the
back of my business card.
One four, three zeros.
And I need that
in a cashier's check
or a money order.
Actually, I want it
in a money order.
And make it out to
"Wool and fabric
from La Sabana
and Associates".
That's my loan-out.
It's totally legit.
After that,
we can discuss the strategy
because my motto
is "anything has a price".
Any questions?
You're going to get me off,
right?
I look like your high
school girlfriend?
Five fingers, no waiting?
What do you think?
That's a joke, man.
Lighten up.
I will give you the
best criminal defense
that money can buy.
I took the vitamins already.
The blood pressure too.
Yes, everything's fine.
Of course, Panchita,
don't worry--
So, while we're working,
Panchita?
And, suddenly,
a dog this big comes at
me,
- a Great Dane.
- Here they are!
Criminal investigation
and anti-narcotics,
all of them together.
Nice!
Why don't you hold your hands?
You are discussing
my client, right?
Anything you care
to share with me?
Can I have a picture
with you?
Because my mother
loves
your shitty
commercials.
- Of course.
- I want to show it to her.
Everything for your mother.
Is she in rehab
or she's still smelling bad?
Awful, awful joke.
You have free time
in anti-narcotics, guys.
That poor and innocent boy
without a real future
will have his life ruined
in two seconds
because a stupid thing.
Let's be honest, the meth
you found is nothing.
Gentlemen, please,
in this country
we have more important issues
to solve.
I will give you
some free advice,
Huey, Dewey and Louie.
Carpe diem, gentlemen.
Carpe diem.
Hello.
So how about we get him
a real attorney?
I mean, what the
hell is this?
This is who he hires?
Are you kidding me?
This is Saúl Bueno.
Haven't you seen him?
"Better call Saúl".
Do you remember Emilio?
- Of course.
- So, this man
got Emilio off twice.
Both times, they had him
dead to rights.
But he did it.
Man, when a criminal
needs to be defended,
he needs another criminal.
That's how it works.
Walter, I promise
everything's going to be fine.
I know Mono might seem
a little bit stupid,
but he's way too loyal to roll.
Plus he's scared shitless of me.
He's threatened.
We pay this man fees,
and, when he frees Mono,
we take it out of his payroll.
And it's only his first
dealing rap.
They plead him out,
they won't take Mono to jail
when there's no place for him.
All right.
Go.
I don't need them
seeing my face.
And do I?
- No, I won't go.
- All right.
Let's flip a coin.
Mejía.
Mr. Mejía.
Come on
in.
Mr. Mejía.
Come in, Mr. Mejía.
You are the uncle
of Mauricio Mejía, right?
You are disguised,
so I was confused.
I didn't see it coming.
Despite I didn't know you,
I couldn't recognize you.
Don't worry, I'm joking.
Welcome, I'm Saúl Bueno.
Come on, come on.
So it's a shame
that we have to meet
under these circumstances.
I believe you have
something for me.
Good.
I'm sorry if I'm
straightforward,
but I don't like
misunderstandings.
Perfect. This is the best.
My apologies, anyway.
Please, have a seat
so I can explain you
the situation.
That's it.
Good.
I have great news.
Mauricio is going to get out
in no time.
There's still a few details
to be ironed out,
but I think he's looking
at time served and probation.
Good, good.
Perfect, thanks.
And that's not an easy
thing to do
because he was busted
by criminal investigation
agents,
but anti-narcotics
is also involved.
So leave your number
with Francisca
when you go out
and we'll be in touch.
Anti-narcotics?
Yes.
I hope that I'm not
the breaker of bad news,
but your nephew got
mixed up with some
pretty nasty customers.
I understand that.
But what does that have
to do
with two different
forces
working in the same
investigation?
I will explain it to you.
They started working together.
They're after some mystery man,
some heavy-hitter that goes
by the name
Heisenberg.
I wonder if they wrote it right.
They want this guy like the ax
wants the turkey.
Seems your boy may have
information
that could lead to his arrest.
But don't worry
because your boy
was really good
and didn't say a word.
He didn't point fingers.
What does it mean?
We have good material
when the moment of
the negotiation arrives
and he starts talking.
No, no, Saúl,
there has to be
another way.
Another way?
Yes, there are two:
the first one,
Mauricio takes the deal
and starts telling stories.
The second one,
Mauricio goes to jail.
And you don't want to know
how they will resize his rectum
when he tries to bend
to get to the soap.
Yes, I know, Saúl,
but what if Mono...
I mean, my nephew
decides to inform on
this Heisenberg?
God forbids that
because these people
can take revenge.
Do you something know about him?
Because the kid keeps saying:
"if I talk, they'll kill me".
Right now, he's the only thing
holding up this deal.
Okay.
That's good.
Good?
God, that's terrible!
Mauricio won't last
in prison two weeks.
You let him take his chances
on the outside.
Besides, there are
other options.
Maybe I can work in
some witness protection.
No, look, Saúl.
These are vicious people.
I've been told that one of them
killed another man
by crushing his head
with an ATM machine.
People love to take credit
for the fun ones.
And other people believe it all.
Dear God!
The guy who got
his head smooshed
used to be a client
of mine.
It's a small world.
Do you know who did it?
His wife.
This is real life,
and that's a closed case.
Don't worry.
I'll convince Mauricio,
he will talk
and problem solved.
10.000 dollars.
10.000 dollars cash.
I'm not saying
to throw the case.
Just no talking
to anti-narcotics.
Are you saying
what I think you're
saying?
That dude wouldn't
take a bribe?
What do you think?
That son of a bitch.
"Morally outraged," he said.
He was really offended.
Threatened to call the police.
So Mono is going to spill?
Like the Exxon
Valdez.
So what do we do about it?
How about I follow you home,
Panchita?
I mean, Francisca.
For safety!
You can't go alone
in these lonely streets.
Isn't it dangerous?
No, no, thanks.
Don't worry.
What a shame.
God, you are killing me
with that booty.
Okay, relax. Relax.
Everything's fine.
Aah!
Talk to me, guys! Come on.
I have my wallet here,
it's in the left pocket.
And I have a golden ring
with an emerald.
And some collar not good,
but it was blessed
by Pope John Paul II.
Aaah!
No, no, please, no!
It wasn't me! It wasn't me!
It was Ignacio,
it was Ignacio!
I am your friend, guys!
Your friend!
Shut up, ass hole!
What are you saying?
Did Gordon send you?
Who?
Dear God.
Thanks, God.
If you save me from this,
I will come back to church
every Sunday.
Okay, what do you want?
What do you need?
Anything!
Just tell me what you need.
This afternoon,
an associate of
ours
offered you $10.000.
And you said no.
Wait a minute.
This is in regards
to what's his name?
Mauricio Mejía!
Mejía.
The uncle.
That was your guy?
No offense, guys,
but I don't take bribes
from strangers, you know?
Better safe than sorry.
But I'll take your money! Sure!
No, no.
That offer's expired.
It was kind of low anyway.
But okay, okay, I'll take it.
Just tell me what you need.
I'm easy to work with.
I'm going to keep a happy
thought and assume
this is just
a negotiating tactic.
I can forget really fast
that you tried to kill me,
folks.
- Listen to me very carefully.
- Yes.
You are going to give
Mauricio
the best legal representation
ever.
But no deals
with anti-narcotics.
If Mauricio
identifies anyone,
you will pay for that.
Me?
Why don't you just kill him?
Follow me, guys.
If a mosquito's
buzzing around you,
it bites you on the ass,
you don't go gunning
for the mosquito's attorney.
You go grab a flyswatter
and kill the bastard.
I mean, so to speak.
Listen, listen!
We're not killing Mono.
I mean Mauricio.
Then you got real problems.
Because anti-narcotics agents
will make him tell them
what his grandmother died of.
I don't know
if you know that boy,
but I could notice,
in the few minutes
I've been with him,
that he won't
be able to go through
the minimum time in jail.
He will have to talk.
He doesn't have
any other choice,
no matter what happens to me.
Mr. Mejía?
Mr. Mejía, my friend.
I recognize
a friendly coughing.
Why don't you take that mask off
so you can breath?
Take it off, breath.
Get some air.
Go on.
You are going to choke
with that.
Breath, relax.
Breath, go on.
Take it easy!
Breathe in, breathe out.
One, two.
That's it, perfect.
Gentlemen,
I'm going to stand up,
all right?
Just because I have bad knees.
Don't freak out.
Here I go. Very good.
Perfect.
The three of us
- are going to work this out.
- How?
First things first,
you're going to put
a dollar in my pocket.
Do you want attorney-client
privilege?
So that everything you
say
is strictly between us.
I mean it!
Put a dollar in my pocket.
Come on, make it official.
All I have is
a five-dollar bill.
I'll take it, I'll take it.
That's it.
Very good.
You're now both officially
represented
by Saúl Bueno
and Associates.
You can put the gun down.
Your secrets are safe with me
under threat of disbarment.
And I don't want
to risk my license.
Do you get it?
Hey, take the ski mask off.
I feel like I'm talking
to a muppet.
- Take it off.
- Come on.
Good!
Let's talk business.
Mauricio...
A prison shanking is completely
off the table.
- Are we sure of that?
- No shaking!
Then the way I see it
is somebody's going to prison.
It's just a matter of who.
His name is John Fredy Angulo.
In 1980, he was busted stealing.
In 1989, he stole a car.
In 1990, he used a gun.
Well, 1981, 1991, 2001,
and this is Fredy now.
They call him
Frediliso.
He knows almost all
the prisons in this country.
Bellavista, La Picota,
La Modelo, all of them.
He's been in prison
41 of his 59 years.
All his life in jail.
For a price,
Fredy provides
a very special service.
He pretends to
be certain man
and goes to prison for you.
on purpose?
The guy goes to prison
He likes to be
inside.
The outside world
hasn't been too kind
to him.
We know people,
we know their
prejudices.
What a
horror!
Fredy really is a
philanthropist,
he provides a service
and charges for it.
When does all this happen?
It's already happening.
The buy is set for tomorrow.
Cops bust Fredy, Mono gets out,
everybody's happy.
All it's going to cost you
is 80.000 dollars
and one pound
of your finest meth.
$80.000 for eight years
of his life.
He's not going to do
eight years.
I'm going to represent him,
and I guarantee
there's going to be
some unexpected problems with
the prosecution's case.
Another thing:
80.000 dollars for him,
150.000 for me.
Why is that?
Why he receives only 80.000?
Who's taking a bigger risk?
He likes prison.
Look, if this option
is too expensive,
there is no problem.
We only have to warn Mauricio
about all the things
the inmates will do with him.
Conscience gets expensive,
that's my motto.
Tell me, boy,
have you seen this
man's commercials?
They are good, right?
As an actor, he's a good lawyer.
He cooked you up
a pretty killer deal.
Right, Gómez?
Right.
Time served, no probation.
If you talk.
I couldn't believe the judge
went for it.
He's like a magician.
Don't get cocky.
You aren't home free yet.
If you don't give us
the name of your supplier,
you're going nowhere.
Understood, bitch?
Agent, the tough guy act
is unnecessary.
This young man
is cooperating fully.
Are you cooperating?
Let's start with a name.
Mauricio Mejía.
Are you a clown?
The supplier's name!
Not a name.
He just goes by Heisenberg.
Heinsenberg.
How old is he?
Old.
Really old.
Like 50 or 70 or something.
Height?
Average, I guess.
Medium height, medium weight.
He's an average man.
What color hair?
No hair.
He's bald.
Balder than you, man.
And that's a lot to say.
Careful, there is the guy.
There are the agents, go back.
- Go back.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Do they see us here?
No, no, no, we're fine.
Mono looks
like he's going to throw up.
Let me see.
Where is that
Fredy?
He should be here.
Do you think
he's actually for real?
It's really weird.
A guy who wants to be in prison?
There's more
than one kind of
prison.
We are really fucked up.
Not only a chemist,
but also a philosopher.
There he is.
No!
That can't be true!
What? What's going on?
Let me see!
- Who the hell is that?
- I don't know!
Heisenberg, I presume.
Time to move?
No, no, no, no.
Not till we see the exchange.
Son of a bitch!
What's up?
Now he shows.
- Is he there?
- Yes.
No, no, no, bro!
What are you doing?
What?
Fredy is sitting on
the wrong bench.
Shit!
- Where are we going?
- Get out.
- What are you saying?
- Tell Mono what's going on.
If they see me, we're screwed.
I'll do something
with Henry.
Go.
Go, go!
Henry! How are you, man?
- Navarro, Navarro.
- Hi, Gómez, how are you doing?
I thought that was you!
It had to be my brother-in-law.
- And it was you.
- Walter, Walter.
- What's up, Gómez?
- Go, go, brother.
- Get out of here, Walter.
- Are you feeling better?
- Good, good.
- Fine.
- Shit, I can't see him.
- Let's talk later.
Shit, I'm blocked.
Are you working on a case?
Yes, yes, go
away.
- You have to move.
- Is something wrong?
Wrong guy! Wrong guy!
Other bench. Other bench.
Come on, Walter,
move!
- Do I continue on this street?
- Drive, man!
Okay, relax.
I'll go and leave you alone.
I'm sorry if I interrupted you.
- Okay. Bye, Gómez.
- Go!
I lost him.
Shit, I lost him.
Where is he?
Where the hell is he?
There he is, there he is.
Looks like it's going down.
Is that the meth?
- Yes, there is the meth.
- Yes, yes, the meth.
They can move now.
Take them!
Police! Everybody down!
Hands on the ground!
- Shit!
- Could you do it?
Yes, they bought it.
- Drive.
- Let's go.
Perfect.
Yes, one pound of
blue crystal.
And do you know
who this Heisenberg was?
John Fredy Angulo.
Yes, sir.
It's my job, sir.
- Hi.
You weren't home,
so I them in.
I hope that's
okay.
Yes, thanks.
So you bought a mattress.
A king one.
You really are
a chemistry teacher.
Nice!
I was terrible at chemistry.
Really bad.
I'm more of a humanities
guy.
How did you find me?
We should talk about that.
It should be much harder
for people
to track you down.
My detective charged me
for three hours,
so I seriously doubt
it took him more than one
because he overcharges me.
What does this mean?
Are you blackmailing me?
God, I'm your lawyer.
Anything you say to me
is totally privileged.
I'm not in the shake-down
racket. I'm a lawyer.
Lawyers are necessary
to protect the democracy.
Everybody needs us,
even drug dealers need us.
Right?
Especially drug dealers.
So what?
Are you just doing this
out of the kindness
of your heart?
Of course not.
You already know
my rates.
By the way,
where do you keep
the money?
Is it in your
mattress?
Is it in a jelly jar?
I'll tell you
something.
Mauricio may be the first of
your guys to get picked up,
but he won't be
the last.
And if I can find you,
how far behind can
the cops be?
I don't understand.
What exactly are you offering
to do for me?
Have you seen
"The Godfather"?
Vito Corleone?
Vito Corleone had
an adviser.
I'm no Vito Corleone.
Of course not, you're still
far from that.
Right now, you're Fredo.
But with some sound
advice
and the proper introductions,
who knows?
You could be one of them.
You've
got the right product.
Anything that gets the
anti-narcotics panties
in this big a bunch,
you're on to something special.
And I...
I would like to be a small
and silent part of it.
Food for thought, yeah?
Relax.
Think about it.
One more thing:
If you want to make more
money
and keep the money
that you make
"Better call
Saul!"
Think about it!