Miss Rebeca, how are you?
Where were you?
Were you out playing?
You were?
Look what I got for you.
Mm-
I know you like it!
- A kiss for your aunt.
- Let's see.
- Beautiful, Valen!
- Another one for daddy.
- Another one for mom.
- Give her a kiss.
That's it!
Beautiful!
Aren't you going to eat that?
- No.
- What do you mean no?
- No, no.
- Are you throwing it away?
No, Walter.
You can't do that.
- No, no, no.
- Maria, look at this.
- No.
- Give yourself into temptation.
No.
What's
up?
What happened?
Your woman is going
to leave you no dessert,
hurry!
No, I'm not really--
I'm not feeling so good.
- You want some coffee?
- No, no, no.
I hope it's not something you
ate.
No, no, I'm fine.
Come on!
We have Pepto.
I'm sorry, I hate
to leave you with--
Don't worry.
I have plenty of help.
And by that, she
means me.
No, me.
Let's go.
Thanks a lot, family.
Let's do it again!
Walter, will you give
Valentina to me?
Of course.
Lovely!
She fell asleep!
Why don't we do something
on Thursday?
That sounds
great.
It's just that
Henry,
he's stuck with work
and I can't make him see
he can't go on like this...
Are you okay to
drive?
You sure?
- Maria!
- Coming!
Easy now.
Bye!
All
right,
let's get started
on those dishes.
I'll dry. You wash.
No.
Miss Rebeca,
how are you?
Walter,
how you doing?
How are you?
Have a good day.
How's everything?
Europe.
I can't believe it!
That's great!
You knew, right?
Yes.
Did you hear that?
It's just you were
so long in the bathroom
I don't know if you heard.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine.
This is great!
Funny how life is.
And, you know,
where they were
three or four months ago.
And now a second Honey Moon
in Europe.
We need to go to Europe.
We could go.
I'm dying to know Paris or...
Rome.
Any city in Europe, really.
Everything's gorgeous there.
You know what
though?
I may get fat over there.
Food over there
is delicious.
I'll gain 28 kilos.
Not 30, but some 28 for
sure.
Henry, you okay?
Henry, Henry.
Henry, what's wrong?
Henry!
Henry, you okay?
Are you okay?
What is it, Henry?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Call an ambulance!
You okay, honey?
Just take a breath.
[breathing
heavily]
Relax, relax, I'm here.
Relax. Relax.
Sit down now.
Wait for me.
Lay down a while.
You rest until you feel better.
I'm fine, okay?
I don't know.
I'll make the appointment
for next week.
I think it's strange--
I can't stand these heels.
What second opinion
Maria?
Three hours in the
Emergency Room?
All for nothing?
All they did
was check your heart
to rule out
a heart attack.
Just that.
Listen to me, Henry,
don't be stubborn,
what happened today
was no indigestion, okay?
Maria, it's just work,
I'm stressed out.
I have to ask you one
favor.
Do not tell Cielo, okay?
What? Why?
Just don't.
Do it for me.
Okay.
Where are you going?
Why don't you lay
down?
Jesus!
Morning, guys!
Enrique,
happy birthday!
- Thank you.
- Fine.
- How are you?
- Good morning.
- Hi.
- How's everything?
- Fine.
I was thinking,
why don't we
reorganize the shelves?
I was thinking,
air fresheners
are high margin, right?
But you can't
see them.
So I'm thinking
we reorganize the display.
The banana one
is the most popular.
- What do you think?
- Whatever.
Speaking of the
business,
Cielo,
you said the story comes
first.
So we can explain our income,
right?
The story is
that we are car wash
owners,
pure and simple.
- Yes.
- Great.
What do successful
car wash owners do?
They buy more car
washes.
You
know?
I don't know, Walter.
Cielo, Cielo.
We have a pile of
money
that we need to wash.
We'll be laundering
that money
for years.
Wouldn't two
be better than one?
There's one on the highway.
I do love that location.
So let's buy it!
I'll think about it.
Why don't we go
and check it out?
Let me think about it.
Think it over
and come back to me.
Angie, I'm
coming.
Come on, honey, to work.
- No, no, no.
- Okay, fine.
Feel well--
Sure, sure
What is it?
What's
this?
Some papers I have to sign
so they don't back up
in the office.
Honey, you are recovering.
- I know.
- So...
you can't be working
all day,
- non stop.
- Fine, honey.
Hi, guys.
Let's bring the other ones.
There, there, there.
Boss, your secretary
says
there may be some
boxes
without a label on them,
we can help you
organize that.
No, no, no, leave that.
Come on, come on. Thank you!
See you. Get
better.
- See you.
- Bye.
Thank you very much!
Have a great day.
A simple car wash with
waxing.
That would be 70,000 pesos.
We have a drop in
quality.
We are at 68%.
And falling.
That is 100.
Here's your change, 30.
I knew there would
be a drop in
quality,
but 68%?
This is not what I
agreed to.
I left a viable operation.
The rest was up to you,
Lidia.
- We need you.
- Here's 30,000.
Please, help us.
I'm asking for a few
days, a week.
Call it a tutorial.
Get the ship back
on course.
We'll make it worth your
while.
Is there anything else
or that's it?
An air freshener, please.
Listen, this is
a complicated
situation.
There are a lot
of moving parts, Walter.
None of which are my concern.
I'm out.
You're putting me
in a box here.
You know what could happen.
Again, none of my concern.
- Please.
- That's 20,000 pesos.
Here's your air freshener.
- Thank you.
- I'm asking you, please!
They'll give you
your car in the back.
There's some complimentary
coffee, if you like.
Thank you.
Thank you,
have a great day.
Who was that?
Don't lie to me,
she looked
suspicious.
She's a former business
associate who wants me to go
back.
And I won't.
Good.
Get out of here. Now.
Excuse me?
Never come back here.
- I just--
- Do you understand me?
Tripa, my man.
I think it's time.
Time for what, man?
To make a drastic decision.
I'll get a pet.
Really?
I have a lot of love to give,
and so
if I have a little creature
to love
and respect
as long as I live,
that will help me
grow as a person.
Man, man, man, man.
What kind of pet
were you thinking?
I can't have a dog,
we have no time,
we are very busy people,
right?
So get a cat, man.
Those bitches practically
take care of themselves.
A cat is very dangerous,
Tripa.
Is it?
It makes you gay, man.
Does it?
And here I was thinking
that you're gay
when you have sex
with other men.
No, but you sleep
with other men
once you are
already gay,
right?
But what makes you
become gay
is when you change
your lifestyle.
Like when you get a cat.
Think about
this.
He starts sleeping in his bed
and I sleep in mine,
but then he comes closer,
you see?
And then you end up
cuddling.
What does that
have to do with it?
There's the physical part.
Listen.
You start by stroking
the cat all day
and the hand
turns this way,
and then you can't
straighten that out.
So you start like this,
and then suddenly
it turns the other way around.
Sss!
I hadn't thought--
Uy, no!
Uuuh!
I'm dazzled!
And then,
on the other hand,
there's the spiritual part
as well.
Cats are so elegant,
they give you
that same elegance, man.
And then you start
cleaning after yourself,
pussy.
And when a man
watches after himself
that's because he's gay.
Sure, but...
But think about this.
You know.
Being gay isn't
such a bad deal.
What do you mean?
Do you get along with women?
No, not at all.
There.
You may not get along
with men either,
but at least you'll be
elegant and clean, right?
What does that have to do
with getting a pet?
You can take
one of those little bold ones,
they're all skinny
and they look like a chicken.
And there's your pet.
Can't you do that
with a female?
Mm, mm, no, man,
that is so macho.
You are right!
Jose, where are you
going?
Come on, Jose,
don't be a homophobe.
How much longer
do I have to wait?
Hey!
How much longer?
Can you tell Saul,
please?
Stewart.
Stewart!
Man,
you know you can't
smoke that up in here.
Are you messing with me?
Turn it off.
I know, but Jose Miguel Rosas
is out here,
smoking pot.
Mm-
Rosas, come
on.
Come on.
Pull up a bong and take a seat.
How about that?
I'm kidding about the bong.
Don't be doing that.
Sorry to keep you
on ice out there.
If I'd known it was you,
well...
Francisca.
I've warned her before.
But you know her,
she orders me around.
Thank you, girls.
Barn door open.
Again?
Okay.
So...
how is the maestro?
Things have been quiet
on this end.
I haven't seen
him.
Just as well, probably.
You know...
That whole thing
in the jails--
What happened
to Mario's kids
was too much.
I mean,
when they start
to whack the lawyers,
that's when I draw the line.
That really hurt,
it's a professional hurt,
you see?
I had to draw the line.
You done, Saul?
Yes.
Great.
This goes to Mario's
granddaughter,
and that goes to
Agustin Herrera's
parents.
A total of five million
dollars.
Divided in half,
it's 2 1/2 million each.
It's all in pesos,
you can go through it.
All right.
Hold on a minute.
Who's parents?
Agustin Herrera.
Agustin Herrera,
that's the kid
that's been missing,
right?
It's no longer news.
People forgot about that.
What those folks want
is to know
what happened
to their boy.
Sack full of cash
on their doorstep--
that's just gonna
raise more questions.
Why wake that up?
The other one's
for Mario's granddaughter?
So this is his money?
Mario's.
It's mine.
It's your money.
Okay.
And you're giving it
to Mario's
granddaughter.
It's what Mario wanted.
You've been in touch?
No.
So we're just
talking about charity?
A donation.
Okay, look.
Shelling out money to the ex
and her little boy
like you did with Andrea,
I kinda get it.
I mean, kinda.
Not quite, but kinda.
But this
is a bridge too
far.
I'm sorry to say, kid,
but you're still gonna be
two miracles short of
sainthood.
If you know what I
mean.
Brass tacks, okay?
My job is to advise.
And my advice
is...
Come on,
already.
Come on!
Mario left one step
ahead
of the boys in
blue,
and you better believe
his family's on the
radar.
A couple million bucks
shows up,
they're gonna snatch
it.
The feds have already
taken
their money
twice.
What are you
you going for a hat
trick?
-God.
-So what?
I'll freaking do it myself.
No, no, no!
I'll do it.
I was thinking out loud.
Enough bullshit, Saul.
Are you gonna do this or not?
Yes, yes, absolutely.
That's what I do.
I live to serve.
Good.
Hey.
And, kid, you might
wanna think about
cleaning up a little,
getting some rest.
You've looked better.
Just get it done.
Aah!
You know who this is?
Don't hang up on me.
Yes, yes.
There's a problem.
There's five million of them
here in my office.
No.
Don't. Just hold
onto it.
Yes.
Hold onto it.
I'll handle
it.
Yes.
Yes, easy.
I'll handle it.
All right.
What's up?
Déjà vu?
I feel I've lived this before.
You wanna talk me
through this?
What you were thinking?
What you asked Saul to do?
Jose, it's just nonsensical.
It's incredible.
You have any explanation
at all?
It's like you said.
It's blood money.
What?
You said it,
it's blood money.
Excuse me? I said that?
Yes.
When I went to collect,
remember?
Don't you remember?
You said we'd see
each other in Hell.
You said it was blood money.
-Yes.
-Okay.
But it was in--
in the heat of the moment,
Jose.
Remember?
It was in the heat
of the moment,
I was trying
to win an argument, all right?
But I may...
I may have acted
a bit childishly.
And I was wrong.
Jose,
this is your money.
You've earned it!
-That boy--
-Agustin Herrera.
He had a name.
Yes, of course,
Agustín.
That is a terrible memory,
no doubt about it.
A tragedy.
That needn't have happened.
But, son...
you need to stop focusing
on the darkness behind you.
The past is the past.
It's the past!
Nothing can change
what we've done.
But now that's over.
You're out, and so am I.
That's right.
I'm done.
I've been out
for about a month.
And there is nothing left
for us to do
except to try to live...
ordinary, decent lives.
To have decent lives.
Why Mario's granddaughter?
She needs someone
looking after her.
No, man...
Mario is capable of looking
after his own granddaughter.
I don't
think so.
I don't think he's
coming back.
What are you saying?
Walter, you doing what
you did--
offing Mario's guys?
If he was out there,
you would have to look
over your shoulder
for the rest of your
life,
and that's not
how you do things.
Actually, you seem
quite at ease.
That means you're not scared
of him coming back.
So I think
Mario's dead.
And I think you
know that.
-No, no.
-Yes.
Jose,
I don't know that!
Listen to me.
I did not kill Mario.
The last time that I saw him,
he had his bag--
the one that I brought him--
and he got into his car,
and he drove away.
And for all I know,
he is alive and well.
He surely is.
And if-- and if
he does come back,
and he doesn't understand
why I had to do what I did...
well, then, that's on me.
We'll settle that.
Jose,
I need you to believe this.
So you're saying...
he's out there,
he's okay.
Wherever he is,
Mario is fine.
Mario--
We both know
that he can take care of himself
just fine.
And he's certainly capable
to provide for his family.
Jose.
Jose, I need you to believe me.
Yeah.
Like you said.
Mario's alive.
Yeah, Mario's alive.
When are the tests?
I don't know,
I wrote it down.
Are they going
to prepare you?
A precollege or something?
I don't know.
No? No.
Do you know something
about the exam
that will determine
you getting into college.
Mm-
Without that test,
there's nothing.
There's a minimum score,
depending on your major,
did you know that?
Mm-
Junior, your mother is right.
College is very important.
Ay, Henry cancelled.
He's still not feeling well.
-Right?
You do not have to look
so happy about it.
Don't smile.
So you're spared.
I'll be right back.
Mm-
Did you see
my William Blake book?
What?
Complete poetry
by William Blake.
It's a special edition.
It's a nice
edition.
I didn't even know we had that.
I don't know where
it is.
You don't think Junior...
You're kidding, right?
Well, it'll show up.
What's wrong with Henry?
Mm, it's a stomach bug,
sounds like.
He hasn't been to work all week.
No?
Hey, mister.
Can you help me
out?
Spare some
change?
Hey.
Come back.
Yeah. You. Come here.
What?
I got something for you.
For me?
Take it. Go ahead.
-All that?
-All that.
Thank you, sir!
That's fine.
Have fun.
Anything you want us to
tell Gomez? He's worried
about you.
Tell him
more work and less worry.
That's Gomez' problem,
he worries so much
-and doesn't do anything.
-Insensitive.
You too,
get back yo work
-They'r working.
-Let's go.
-Walter.
-Hey, guys.
How are you? Good to see you.
Very good.
I'm glad!
How's your wife?
Good.
-And the baby?
-Growing!
-She must be beautiful.
-To work!
Sure.
-See you later.
-Bye.
They're good guys,
I like them.
They're great.
How you doing?
How you
feeling?
I've been better, but...
I don't know.
You look better.
Did you get to see a
doctor?
When one of these things
lasts more than three days
you really should
get that checked.
Yeah, no, I did and I'm fine.
It's a virus.
I'm getting better.
Good. Good to hear.
When I heard
you weren't going in
to work, I--
Well, looks like you have
the work coming to you.
Perks of being the boss?
Yeah,
you
know...
What about you?
How's things at the
car wash?
Good. Yeah, really good.
Hey, did you have
any of that potato pure Cielo
made the other day?
I don't know. Ma-- maybe.
No one else got sick,
so you probably shouldn't worry
about it.
That's probably not it.
I don't remember.
Okay.
Cielo will be very happy to
hear that you're feeling better.
She was worried.
Sure.
Which reminds me.
I better get back to it.
Henry,
If there's anything
I can do...
Okay.
I'm glad you're
feeling better!
Thanks.
See you.
Henry,
one other thing...
You're gonna
laugh,
but I have to ask you
about this.
I found this on my car.
Believe it or
not.
I mean, it looks
just like
the GPS tracker
that we used on
Gustavo Cortes.
Back when we were tracking him,
just the two of us?
You wouldn't know anything
about this, would you?
You okay?
I don't like the way
you're looking at me right now.
Aagh!
It was you.
All along, it was you!
You son of a
bitch.
Calm down, Henry!
You drove into traffic
to keep me from that
laundry.
That call I got
telling me
Maria was in the
hospital...
that wasn't Rosas.
You had my cell number!
You killed ten witnesses
to save your sorry ass.
You bombed a nursing
home.
Jaisenberg.
¡Heisenberg!
You lying,
two-faced sack
of shit!
A damn hypocrite!
Aagh!
I don't know where this is
coming from,
but just--
I swear to Christ,
I will put you under the
jail.
If it's the last thing
I do.
Henry,
just take a breath, okay?
Just listen to yourself.
These wild accusations--
they could destroy our family.
family?
You're talking about
Like you give a
shit about family!
My cancer is back.
Good.
Rot, you son of a
bitch.
I wanna beat this thing.
I'm back on chemo,
and I am fighting like hell.
"I'm fighting,
I'm fighting".
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up.
Think about it, Henry.
In six months,
you won't have
someone to prosecute.
Don't you lie.
Even if somehow
you were able
to convince anyone
I was capable
of doing these things,
I would never see
the inside of a jail cell.
I'm a dying man
who runs a car wash.
My right hand to God,
that is all that I am.
Have Cielo
bring the kids here,
and then we'll talk.
That is not going to happen.
I don't know who you
are.
[heavy
breathing]
I don't even know
who I'm talking to.
If that's true,
if you don't know who I am...
then maybe your best course
would be to tread lightly.