Hello?
Alright. Yes.
Come on, come on!
Quick!
Mario.
Are you okay?
Grab him there.
Grab him hard.
Doctor, this man needs help too!
He's dying!
Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Calm down.
Adrenaline!
Hey, man, I need help here!
Mario needs assistance!
Prepare the defibrillator,
nurse. Quick!
Hey, a little help over here.
I don't know what to do.
Quick, quick!
Stand by!
Hey, man, what do I do?
Come on!
Man, please. Help me!
28.05.
Any news from them?
I don't know.
What about Jose?
Let's be clear on this,
Mosquera.
If anything happens to Jose,
I'm out of here for good.
You know?
Don't count on me.
What'll you do?
I said 28.05.
Don't you trust me?
28.10.
Walter.
I need you to pay attention.
Mosquera,
you just don't seem to care,
do you?
My brother-in-law keeps talking
about driving out
to Chicken Brothers and Co.
I can't stop him any further.
He's eventually
going to find someone else
to take him out there.
So have you cleared it out?
Is it presentable,
does it look normal?
Mosquera.
I should be the one
to take him out there.
Why aren't you paying attention?
Can you just run it
up the chain of command, then?
Hey, I'm talking to you!
See anything suspicious?
Do you see anything unusual?
No.
Not yet.
Well, then, should we go?
You got someplace to be?
It's like the third time
you've asked me that.
No. No, I'm sorry.
It's just that these things
make me a little nervous.
I'm just curious
what the next move is.
Our next three moves
is sitting here and waiting.
Keep on the lookout,
see what happens.
That's my job.
They pay me to wait.
Everything people believe,
that cops are always shooting
or on a speedboat.
Or maybe looking
at the drug dealer models.
No, sir.
Watching too much TV lately?
Henry, any news
about what happened
with the Mexican cartel?
In the news here
you only see soccer,
heists and gossip.
What about the face
of the Virgin
that appeared on cornbread?
See that?
We get those too.
No, the thing is
the media here in Colombia
don't actually
pay much attention to anything
having to do with Mexico,
you know?
They treat that
as ordinary crimes.
But I found out about something
brutal that happened in Mexico.
Really? What was that?
Some big killing
within the Tapatío cartel.
They seemed to wipe out
the whole thing.
They were killed
among themselves.
And that cartel, Tapatío,
has the most interest here
regarding methamphetamines.
So any minute now,
these people
will start making their moves.
We just have to wait.
Hey, Walter.
So?
Won't you ever tell me
what happened to your face?
No, I'd rather
not talk about it.
No, that's really not the idea.
Imagine.
My brother-in-law shows up
looking like a rotten
passion fruit,
and he thinks
we're not going to discuss it?
Buddy, I'm concerned.
Understand that.
Once I had a friend, Hernández.
He had a gambling problem
just like you.
But I know he got on a ride
that was rough to get off of.
You know he managed?
He spoke, spit it out.
So look...
I might be the guy to talk to
if you have any issue
with anyone, you know?
Henry, listen to me,
it's not because of you.
I don't want to talk about it
to you or to anyone else.
I'm done explaining myself
to everybody.
Hey, man.
Doctor!
You think
Mario needs some more blood?
It's in the refrigerator.
You want me to put that on him?
Go ahead.
You're 25 years old.
You weight 160 pounds,
5.9 height.
You drink, smoke...
You do drugs.
You're physically quite alright,
But we did find
you're allergic to eritromicin.
Which is not a problem
because here we have
cefazolin.
How do you know all that?
He thought of everything.
O-negative...
That's what Mario needs.
It's time to go.
What? What about Mario?
With his injury?
No travel. At least a week.
So we're just
going to leave him here?
No.
I'll send for him.
That chain
doesn't match the clothes.
- Thanks.
- My pleasure, buddy.
You know now.
Much water and rest.
We have to leave quietly
so as not to look suspicious.
There's a chopper waiting
about three miles from here.
What? We're going to Colombia
on a chopper?
To Guadalajara.
There's a hot shower
and clean clothes over there.
Our way out of Mexico
should be as legal
as our way in.
Good, because I'd be concerned
to commit a crime
in a foreign country.
You did well down here.
And you also proved a point.
I think you can run the lab
by yourself now.
On your own.
Don't you?
Fine, let's say I do.
But let Mr. White go.
Don't kill him.
You know that won't work.
Then you've got a problem.
I won't do this then.
Gustavo, listen.
Let's do what's best
for everybody.
Let's not get complicated.
Seriously.
Hey, Morgan. I'm here.
Did you do your homework?
I did.
Okay.
Well, dinner is in about 30.
I'll be right down.
Cielo, sorry to call you
at home, but I think
you're not getting my messages.
Anyway, I've been thinking
about what we discussed...
I decided I can't do it.
You know? I just can't.
If you want, come over
at nine in the morning
and we can talk about it.
I'm here.
Wow. That's sharp timing.
This is serious.
Come on in.
First, I want to tell you
that I get it.
This situation
with Walter's gambling
must be really hard for you.
It is.
Yes, it's been hard.
That's why
I would greatly appreciate it
if you would just
help me out here.
Yes.
I know what I'll do
to help you out.
So how's Walter?
Do you know anything?
Yes. He's okay.
Right. I'm glad.
What is this?
What are you doing?
This is a check by management
to give you
the transference I got
for the so-called inheritance.
What? I mean, why?
- I can't take your money.
- Why not?
No, because
the source of that money
doesn't look legal.
The gambling field
is kind of obscure,
and I don't want any part in it
because it wouldn't feel right.
It doesn't feel right.
Yes. Listen.
Don't misunderstand me.
I'm not judging you or Walter.
I'm just saying
I feel uncomfortable with it.
Wait a minute.
Let me remind you
that the reason why we're here
is because you had me
cooking your company books.
That sure is uncomfortable.
So when did wrong
suddenly become a problem
for you?
Now, hold on.
That was a one-time measure.
I took an honest attempt
to save my dad's company
and protect my employees.
No, wait a minute.
You're not focusing
on the problem.
You have a debt with the IRS,
and if you don't,
they'll come and get you.
And then they'll come get me.
If they audit on me,
they'll find out Walter and I
pay millions
for a business
with undeclared money.
So you'll be screwed
and I'll be screwed too.
Do you understand?
Of course I understand.
You know what I think?
You...
You're overreacting.
All these issues
with tax management
can be fixed, Cielo.
No! You're being
too light about this!
Let's say I take your advice.
I pay the IRS.
Then what?
Then you don't owe them
and we're all happy.
Right. What about the banks?
I'll lose my business
and my home.
The employees will be left out.
That's just not enough!
That won't change anything.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Am I following this right?
You can't take the money,
but you could get more.
- Right?
- No, no. Wait.
No. Look, I appreciate
all the help you gave me.
Thanks, but the money
you gave me
doesn't really change anything.
Because it's not enough?
How can I speak
when you twist my words?
Ohhhhh....
- You know?
- This is not about that.
- This is about me
doing the right thing!
- No!
Are you blackmailing me?
No, no, no.
I feel like
I'm not explaining things right.
I think
you're explaining it fine.
And you know what?
It's not enough.
This isn't even half
of what I gave you.
I said I would pay.
If I'd known
that was your money,
I wouldn't have bought it.
I'll pay gradually, okay?
No, no, no. Gradually?
Yes.
If I go out to sell that car,
you know how much I'd get?
It would be little, Cielo,
but I'll pay you.
No, no,
I don't want you to pay me!
I want you to pay
these damn taxes!
I can't, Cielo, I can't.
Yes, you can!
I can't, and I don't want to.
You will want it.
And you will be able to!
I need to speak with Saúl.
This is Cielo Restrepo,
Walter Blanco's wife.
Yes, it's important and urgent.
Hey, Héctor.
Everyone, Héctor.
Mr. Eladio.
Paco.
César.
Reinaldo.
Fortunato.
And Luis Esteban.
All dead.
Your grandson, Joaquín,
he also got wiped out.
Do you want to know
who killed Joaquín?
Remember him?
He shot Joaquín
several times.
It was you and Joaquín.
That was all the family left.
Now the Salamanca Tapatío name
dies with you.
Look at me, Héctor.
I said look at me, Héctor!
Walter, I really appreciate
you doing this again.
I know you guys
must have your hands full
with the car wash.
No, no, no, not really.
The car wash
is Cielo's domain.
My pleasure to do this.
I'll take you
wherever you want.
And I like this! I think
it gives me a chance to see
a researcher's work up close.
It's interesting and exciting.
Like watching snails having sex.
And it's useful for me to...
I don't know, get distracted.
- From so much problems.
- Right!
Hey, Henry.
So any more news
on that thing in Mexico?
Same old thing. Bunch of animals
clawing each other's eyes out
over turf.
Not much more than that.
So you think all of them
were cartel members?
You sure are curious?
Listen, take a right
at this street here, will you?
No, isn't it to the left?
- No, no, no.
- No? But the chicken farm
is that way.
Right, but we're not going
to the chickens today.
We're going someplace else.
That's straight ahead.
What place?
There's this industrial laundry
I want to check out.
What laundry?
Well, it's owned by this
company,
a Spanish multinational
called Madrigal.
These kinds of companies
manage many businesses.
Among them, they own
Chicken Brothers And Co.
Sounds like a real shot
in the dark there.
I mean,
if it's such a big conglomerate
and there's shares everywhere,
then they've got
thousands of businesses.
So are you a private
investigator or something?
No, no, I'm just saying
because, I don't know,
that chicken business
doesn't sound good.
It usually doesn't sound good.
And also because I think
that place seems ripe
for some kind of
clandestine activity.
The storage units...
Want me to tell you
about clandestine businesses?
You know the same people
at Madrigal
are the owners of a factory
that manufactures
this state-of-the-art air
filtration system.
Guess who took delivery
of one of these systems
in Colombia.
Guido Bermúdez!
Really?
How about it? A chemist
who was in possession
of hand-drawn plans
explaining step by step
how to set up a meth super-lab.
And a day
before he was capped in the face
he see Gustavo Cortés
in his apartment,
ad he's the one
buying Madrigal these filters.
Not such a twisted idea, is it?
And you and me know
what a twisted idea looks like.
Well, I don't know why
I got this feeling, but...
I don't know,
I think I'd insist...
on researching the chickens
and not some laundry.
An industrial laundry
would be one hell of a place
to hide a meth lab.
You know why?
Because laundry's produce
very small odors
that can eclipse
all the chemical smells
and all that.
Here, make a right
on the next one.
This is it.
- Okay, just get in there.
- Aha.
- No, here, this turn.
- Here?
I'm sorry,
I just got distracted
with the conversation.
Then make a U-turn over here.
There, fine.
What ice-cream is
this?
It tastes like
nothing.
I was going to bring the usual,
but mom said
it had to be organic.
No, not the same at all.
Anyway,
this is a gift.
Don't judge an ice-cream
by its looks.
Honey,
can you handle one more visitor?
¡Walter!
The chosen driver!
Careful with the bollard.
How are you feeling, buddy?
Kind of feels
like one of those cones
they put on dogs
so they don't lick
their own balls.
Henry! Thank you
for the lovely image.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry about all this.
I don't know what happened.
That guy
just came out of nowhere.
Actually, he didn't.
We both saw him coming
a mile away.
- What?
- You crashed him.
Anyway, these things happen.
The important thing
is nothing happened to us.
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
Your Hardy Boys routine is over.
No more asking him
to drive you on stakeouts.
- Okay, mom.
- I'll take you.
No, forget it.
She's right.
It was a bit shortsighted of me
to ask me to take you
to all these places.
That's why I caved.
Took my hand off.
Wait, You caved?
I ordered me a gimp-mobile.
- That's not the name, Henry.
- Like a handi-van with a lift?
No, no, no.
It's got hand controls.
- On the wheel.
Right, right.
I sure hope
I don't have to use it
for too long.
And stop being
such a damn burden to everyone.
That's true.
Check if that's mine.
No! That's me, that's me.
What's that?
The laundry.
There's a problem...
Ice-cream!
Okay.
Taste that!
It's tofu, with miso and soy.
Ye, hello?
Can you talk?
I can hear.
That should be fine.
Okay, well...
He doesn't own a gun.
At least not one legally.
And his home security system
is really bad,
so this should be easy.
If that's still the way
you want to do things.
Like I said, what's important
is that
I don't want anyone hurt.
All I want is for him
to write a check.
It's going to be fine.
I've got my A-team
working on it.
- I'll let you know.
- Okay.
And you are?
Calm down.
Tell me what you want
and we can arrange it.
- Shhh.
- Easy, man!
This is easy.
What we're going to do
is do our best
to keep Estiwar happy.
- Who is Estiwar?
- Him.
Now you know him.
Estiwar, are you happy?
Right now I am,
but I could get unhappy.
So what could get you unhappy?
This little mofo
not doing what he's told.
Would that be good
for Mr. Silva?
I don't think so.
Alright, fox, look at me.
Look at me.
Did you get it? Great.
We're going to fill out
these payment forms.
Sign up.
You have a nice house.
Congratulations.
Such good taste.
Sign this.
Look, here.
You won't have to pay
one more dollar.
That amount is enough
to pay what you owe
to the IRS.
That's a check.
We'll pay the rest.
Because we know
you got a car, didn't you?
Well, that ride
will be on our name,
and everybody's happy.
Sign, please.
Cielo sent you, didn't she?
Doesn't matter who sent us.
The important thing
is we all must do
what we must do
as State citizens.
Sign up.
Sign up!
Fill out the form and pay up.
If you pay what you owe,
you know what you have.
Great.
Now the fingerprint
of the left finger.
Hey, Estiwar,
what's with the violence?
The man is cooperating.
Okay, the finger.
There we go.
Perfect.
See how easy that was?
Estiwar, are you happy?
I'm ecstatic.
Now all we have to do
is take these forms
to the IRS and pay up.
There, buddy.
Cool.
Does the clothes
have to be dirty?
No.
Was somebody cooking here?
Walter, you've been
out of commission four days.
Think we're going to shut down
the whole operation
just for you?
Who was it?
Who was here?
Do you really want to know?
- I'm going to kill no.
- No!
I got the grenade
and...
That's cheating!
Ouch!
Who's wining?
- Me, me!
- I'm wining.
Okay, Byron, great!
Have a chip here!
Keep it up
and don't make me lose, okay?
- Jose.
- What are you doing here?
I got nothing
to say to you, man.
No, no, please,
just a minute, okay?
- Jose, only for a minute!
Please.
- Get the hell out of my house.
- Get away!
- Please, listen to me.
- Shut up, they'll hear you!
- I'm sorry,
but you have to listen to me.
I know that you
have been cooking without me.
- That's right. So what?
- So what?
Isn't it obvious to you
what Gustavo is planning?
He's going to use you
to replace me, Jose.
He doesn't think
you need me anymore!
If you agree to replace me,
he will kill me.
What the hell's
wrong with you, man?
You brought your brother-in-law
to our lab. Think!
Sorry, but that's not my fault.
You know what?
We're through talking.
No, Jose, Jose.
I'm begging you!
You've got to help me!
"You've got to help me"?
You remember last time
I asked for your help?
When I had to go cook
in Mexico?
You said, "I hope you end up
in a barrel in the desert."
So you know what?
Get out, Walter!
Get out of here!
- Walter, we're going.
- What? Let go of me!
We're leaving,
we're leaving now!
Calm down and lay down the gun.
Let's talk.
- Put your hands down.
- What do you want?
Just walk already!
You're done, Walter.
I've had it with you.
Do not show your face
at the laundry again.
Stay away from José Miguel.
Don't even try to phone him.
I hope you're listening
very carefully.
What if I don't?
Excuse me?
What if I don't stop
seeing Jose?
What'll you do?
Kill me?
If you could kill me,
I'd already be dead.
You can't kill me.
You can't kill me
because if you do
Jose wouldn't cook for you
anymore.
That's it, isn't it?
No matter how hard you tried
to turn him against me,
he still won't let you do it!
He will never, hear me out,
ever let you kill me!
Maybe for now,
but he'll come around.
Now I'm concerned
about the matter
- of your brother-in-law.
- What?
He is a problem
you promised to resolve.
You have failed.
Now it's left to me
to deal with him.
No! You can't!
Yes, I can!
And I will.
If you try to interfere,
this becomes
a much simpler matter.
I will kill your wife.
- I will kill your son.
- No.
I will kill
your infant daughter.
No.
Perfect, you know.
And I said you were my A-team.
This was really an act of God.
No accounting in that case.
Besides, it's done.
All taxes paid.
No, perfecto.
I just have to say, "Cielito,
the good news is
the IRS has been paid off.
The bad news..." Shit!
Well, thanks for nothing.
Hey, I told you,
you can't come in!
- Saúl.
- No, no. This is just great!
How did you find out?
Find out about what?
Boy, go, scram.
We'll talk later.
Out, get out!
What happened to you?
Saúl.
You told me about a guy.
This person that you said
could disappear me,
give me a whole new identity
and a new life.
Who is it?
- An eraser. That's it!
- What about him?
- I need him now!
Gustavo is going to kill
my whole family.
This is going worse and worse.
Come on, Saúl, please!
Yes, fine, alright.
Walter, you're aware
- that there's no
turning back on this, right?
- I know.
If you disappear,
it'll be forever.
Yes.
You can't contact anyone,
your friends
or your relatives.
Ever again. Understood?
Yes, yes, understood.
How are you going to sell this
to your wife and son?
Saúl, I have got no choice!
Walter, you're wanted
by some scary individuals.
Not to mention the law.
You're going to need
the deluxe service.
It's going to cost you.
How much?
The last quote I got
on the deluxe was 125 grand.
Each one.
He collects cash.
I don't care!
I've got the money!
Here you go.
This is a vacuum cleaner
repair company.
What'd you expect,
Haji's Quick-Vanish?
- Saúl, so what do I do?
- Easy, calm down.
You just call that number
and leave a message.
Tell them you need a new filter
for an extra strong MX..
An X what?
I wrote it
right on the other side.
He'll call you back
in five minutes.
How long does it take
for him to arrange?
The guy works fast.
I mean, that's the game here.
That's why, Walter,
you've got to have your family
packed and ready to go
before you make the call.
He'll tell you
where to meet him.
What about after that?
He'll put you up in a safe house
until everything is set.
But you have to bring the money.
He doesn't lift a finger
unless he's paid in full.
Right, okay.
Saúl...
Walter...
Can't say
it's been a pleasure, but...
Good luck to you,
- anyway.
- I need you to do
one more thing for me.
- Something else?
- Yes, Saúl, it's important.
Call Anti-Narcotics
and tell them that Gustavo
has a hit out on Henry,
my brother-in-law.
I can't do that!
I've got to go on living here.
Please!
Just call anonymous then!
- No, you call!
- Me?
Saúl, these people know me!
I go to their Christmas parties,
they can recognize my voice!
I'm not calling! No!
Please, Saúl!
Please.
I'm begging.
Henry doesn't deserve to die
for this. Please...
I can't even mention Gustavo
in a phone call.
Think about the consequences
with José.
But he has to know!
The best I can do
is call and let them know
of a possible attack.
- No mentioning Gustavo, okay?
- Okay.
I can say, I don't know...
They're coming back
to finish the job
that they botched.
- Right, right.
- But that's all.
- That's all.
- Fine, whatever you want!
And... Give me an hour.
Make that call in an hour, Saúl.
Saúl, thank you.
This is not enough.
There's money missing here.
Where's the rest of the money?
Damn it!
- Walter!
- Down here!
Where's the money
What about the call
about us talking right now?
Where's the rest?
Cielo, where's the rest
of the money?
Cielo, where's the money?
I gave it to Ernesto.
What?
I did it for us, I swear!
- I swear
I did it for the family!
- No!
You gave Ernesto our money?
I can explain!
I can explain everything!
No! No!
Walter...
We can't come to the phone
right now.
Please leave a message.
Cielo, pick up if you're there.
It's happening again, Cielo.
Anti-Narcotics called and said
that the cartel people
want to kill Henry.
I don't know what to do.
They're sending agents
our house right now, but please
call me. Answer me.