It's them.
Mario!
1,500 gallons
are missing.
Where's the rest?
You won't get it.
Why is that?
Who's this man
with that little hat--?
I'm the one keeping it.
How come?
What's going on?
Mario, you and I
made a deal.
Where's the tank?
He doesn't know
where the tank is.
I'm the only one who knows,
so you'll have to
do business
with me.
Why don't you tell me
what you want?
Over here,
we just came
to pick what's ours.
Look, methylamine
is worth much more in
my hands
than in yours
or in anyone else's.
I need the
distribution.
- Distribution?
- Yes, sir.
This is my
You forget about
your product.
You just sell mine
and I'll give you
35%?
of my share.
Are you kidding?
They want to give me 35%
for the profits, guys.
That must be---
Come on, dude!
Why would I need you
if I have my own production?
Yes, I know
you do.
I've heard
about your
production.
I was told you get
a 70% purity.
When you're on
a good day.
What I do
has 99.1% of purity.
- So?
It's a cheap fake
versus the original
product.
The product.
Let's see if I got this.
You're telling me
I could kill you right now
and leave you here
in the desert. Right?
Then I'd get
the original product
out of the market.
Do you get me?
Look around you.
There's only us.
I really doubt
you'd want a world
full of fakes
when you could access
the original product.
My partner
tells me
that your
crew
switched to P2P.
You're using
colorants
to dye your meth
so that it looks
like mine.
I mean,
you're at doing
imitations.
You've had to do it
several times
to equal my product,
right?
What I'm offering you right
now
is access
to the original
product.
The best
one!
Direct distribution.
I'm making no deals with you
to be your errand boy.
Did you get me?
What for?
For a bunch of junkies
to get a better high?
A better high
means consumers
pay more.
More purity
means greater
production.
Millions of dollars
we wouldn't have to
waste
for having incapable
cooks.
I'm the best crystal cook.
No.
You're standing in front
of the two best crystal cooks
in Latin America.
With our skills,
you'll earn more
from that 35%
than you ever would on
your own.
Now, I have a doubt.
I'm just wondering
why we're so lucky.
Why cut us in?
Mario is retiring from
our crew
so his share of
the partnership
is available.
So if you want
it,
you can handle the
distribution.
Give Mario 5 million
dollars
of the 15 you
brought there.
Just think of it
as a finder's fee
for bringing us together.
We have 40 pounds
ready to ship.
I just need to know
one thing.
Are you ready?
Who the hell are you?
You know who I am.
Everyone here
knows who I am.
Say my name.
How the hell
would I know your name?
You do.
I'm the cook.
I'm the man
who killed Gustavo
Cortés.
No, that's bullshit.
The cartel killed him.
Are you sure?
That's what
I thought.
Now, say my
name.
You're...
...Heisenberg.
Exactly.
You're goddamn
right.
Walter, I have to hand it
to you.
I appreciate the kind words
and all that,
but I'm leaving
too.
Yes, I know.
We'll talk.
Maybe we should talk
about how and when
I'll get my share.
And we'll do that.
I know.
It's that I'm--
Listen, José.
Just give me some time.
I'll need a little help
getting things up and running
during this transition.
Can you at least do that for me?
Let's go now.
We'll talk later.
Walter,
before
splitting
I want to say two
things.
First,
I'll handle the costs
of the men in
prison.
Don't worry about them.
Second,
the bug
in your
brother-in-law's
office.
Anti-narcotics will
de a sweep
in any moment.
You have to get
that out.
Is that all, Mario?
No "Thanks"
for the five million dollars?
Or "sorry for chaining you"?
Walter, get the
bug.
Well, Mario,
I guess I'll see you around.
I don't
think so.
When I'm out,
I'm out.
Yes,
but I'm out too.
Be safe.
Is everything all right?
You tell me.
José, come on!
Go, go!
Stop!
Mrs. Cielo.
Peto Demoliciones.
I know whim
I'd demolish.
José, help me unhook this.
Excuse me.
What's this?
You really want
to know?
Why are you hiding it
in here?
Don't worry about
it.
Who are you hiding it from?
I told you not
to worry.
From the police?
Or from someone else?
Someone would kill for it?
Why don't you go to
the office?
I mean it,
go to the office.
I'll take care of
it
with José.
Ready?
Doctor, how are you?
What did you bring me?
It's just some biscuits.
- Really?
- Yes.
Try them.
- So?
- Absolutely delicious!
I'm not sharing those.
I want them all for me.
No, honey,
they're just
for you.
I brought them just
I knew you'd
like them.
- I love them.
- Really?
So tasty!
Come with me, doctor.
They're wonderful, God!
My colleagues
always criticize me.
They're upset
because I don't share
anything
with them.
They say I'm
selfish.
There, doctor.
Come.
All right, Doris.
So?
How's Alberto?
Don't get me started,
doctor.
I'm so upset.
- Why?
- You know what's the latest?
He wants to buy a boat.
Maybe one of these days
he moves to the sea
or hot land
or the desert.
No, no, no.
Definitely no.
He's not buying a boat.
End of story.
All right,
I'll let you
get to this.
See you, Doctor.
Enjoy it.
- Bye
- Thanks, Doris.
Your granddaughter
is going to need a second safe
if you decide to leave her
one more dollar.
How's the rest
of it?
Empty, as usual.
The families are pretty reliable
with the pickups.
Nobody
complaining
abut wanting it all at
once?
No.
No, they get it.
In this country
full of irresponsible people,
they prefer to get paid
little by little.
If not, they go nuts
and waste it all.
So I guess
this is it for a while.
Don't worry about the families.
They'll keep getting
their deliveries.
No.
I know times are tight.
I know this is a difficult time
for the country's economy.
Yes, yes.
But I'd really like to count
on your help,
sponsoring the race.
For instance,
we've already covered
the silver level.
We'd need the golden level.
The good thing
about this level
is your brand logo
would be on the shirts.
That's really good
because you know
that more than 200,000 people
watch this race.
Just do the math,
think about it
and I'll call you back.
Fine, fine.
Thank you,
Bye.
Damn it!
I'm sick of having to ask
for money.
It's so humiliating.
Just guess what
I've got here.
What's that?
Read
it.
Search warrant
on Mario Arboleda.
Finally some good news!
How long does it take you
to gather your team?
3 hours.
Let's move then
and get that--
Police!
Search warrant!
Open the door!
We have a search warrant!
Coming!
if you want me to read that,
I'm going to need my glasses.
Come in.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
This is no longer done
like before.
No.
Everything has changed.
Hey, José!
You're just in
time.
I was about to
start.
Why don't you start get
going
on the setting tank?
That would be a huge
help.
We left that stuff in
there
too long
after the last cook.
It needs to be
cleaned.
- Walter--
- For real.
When I say a long time,
it's like an eternity.
It's full of
residue,
dirt.
You know what we need
to invest in?
A power washer.
That's exactly what we
need.
Hey, Walter.
Can we just take a second
and talk about this?
Sure!
You know what I think
we need to talk about?
Doubling down.
- Doubling down?
- Yes, I've been thinking.
We're making 99
pounds
per week,
not 50.
José, what if...
Just what if
we start a second lab?
A second lab
ran by you.
Where you're the
cook!
Why not?
You deserve it.
José!
You're as good as
me.
What do you think?
I think nothing has changed.
I'm out.
I just want to get my money
and get out.
José, when you have
something,
when you do something
that is the
best...
That's not
something
yo get every day.
Excellence
is not around the corner.
And you have it.
You have that incredible talent.
Why waste that?
It's like not using
your potential.
Why would you do
such a thing?
I don't
know.
Just tell.
What will you do?
I don't know.
right now.
I'll figure it
out.
No, no, no,
tell me now!
Look at you!
José, please!
Look at you.
You have nothing in your life,
no one.
Yes, yes.
You have video games.
cars--
- Professor--
- Tell me the truth, José!
Think hard and tell me
what will happen
when you get tired
of doing nothing.
How soon would you start
using again?
Just tell me.
I know you're upset
about what happened
to that boy.
I'm just as upset as you are.
Are you?
Are you really upset?
How can you say that to me?
How do you dare!
I'm the one
who's the father here.
The only who can feel--
What do you want me to do?
Curl up in a ball
and cry?
Do I have to get locked
in a room
and get high
to prove it to you?
José, what happened
was horrible. It was...
It tears me up inside!
But what can I do?
Am I supposed to just lie down
and die with him?
It's done!
It makes me sick!
that it happened.
Just like everyone else
who died in our wake.
What Peto did
was infamous.
But let's be honest, José,
you and I
have done things
that are just as bad.
Yes.
Believe me I know.
Guido's death
and all the others'.
I don't know
if there's a hell,
but if there's,
you and I are into it.
Right?
But I'm not lying down
while that happens!
So you think
just because I don't cook
meth
I'm lying down?
Is that what you think?
Tell me, Walter.
How many more people
are going to die
because of us?
None.
José, you and I
are in control now.
No one else gets hurt.
That's bullshit!
You've told me
that
once and
again
and it's always
been a lie.
Always.
- Of course not
- Of course it has!
And you know
what?
I'm done.
I mean it.
So please,
give me my
money
and this is it for
us.
Fine.
Why?
Why do you want that money?
Because it's
mine.
It's my cut.
No!
No.
It's filthy blood money.
Where's your transparency?
Your moral?
Where's the pure José?
You shouldn't touch a dime
because it's dirty money!
You know what I'll do?
I'll save you from that.
I won't let you touch it.
Is that what you want?
Why can you be honest with me?
Tell me you want it
as much as I want it.
It's not wrong to want it.
José, stay.
Let's cook as usual.
I assure you
we'll earn
10 times more.
No, 20 times!
I promise!
You know what,
Walter?
Do whatever you want,
bitch.
You don't want to pay
me?
Don't.
I don't care.
- You do care.
- I don't care.
It's on you.
I'm done.
You're not done!
If you leave,
you get nothing!
José, listen to me!
I won't give you a dime
if you leave!
José!
Excuse me.
Boss!
You're the boos
now, Henry.
No, sir, you'll always be
the boss for me.
Thanks.
So how are you doing?
I just have a little
flu,
but I'm fine.
I thought you were
in the Caribbean, on a
yacht,
with some chicks,
your wife
preparing lunch.
The way it should
be,
right?
I'd have loved that,
but I've had too many farewells.
Besides, you know
that among high ranks
every moment is a good moment
to take some whisky.
Sure.
Sit and talk to me.
Speaking of high ranks,
they asked me to come
and talk to you.
What?
Did I screw it up?
Henry, just take it
as a piece of advice.
Any advice coming from up
there
is an order.
Talk to
me.
In any case, Henry,
you know I want you
to do a good job
in this office.
Yes, sir.
I think you're a great worker,
but I want you to know, Henry,
your job is no longer
a filed job.
You're in charge
of the anti-narcotics office
and that brings along
some responsibilities.
For instance,
reports, Henry.
You have to fill in reports
in a timely manner.
We're working on
that, boss.
Why spend so much time
and money
in a practically over case,
such as Gustavo Cortés'?
I understand
everything you're
saying
and I hope you'll
understand
what I think.
You have to
believe in me.
If I'm making these
decisions
is because I have evidence
that the blue meth
is back in the
streets.
I know Gustavo
Cortés' team
is working again.
And Mario Arboleda
has a lot to do with
that.
I believe you, Henry,
I do.
But?
What is it?
It's just one case
among hundreds.
You can have no preferences.
- I know. But I think--
-Henry, no preferences.
There's just one job now
and that's the one
that has to be done.
One more thing.
Why are you personally executing
the search warrants?
- What's that?
- Yes, I know.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
You're damn right it won't.
From now on
there's no budget
to go after that guy.
Understood?
All right, Henry.
Don't take it personally.
This is the way it is.
Get better.
- Thank you, boss.
- I'll be in touch.
Goodbye.
- Boss!
- Hi, Gómez.
I'm glad to see
you around, boss.
- Goodbye.
- Bye..
What was that?
That visit.
You know what I think?
The boss likes you.
There's something there.
He asked me for
your number.
- Take a seat.
- What happened?
Tell me.
We can't continue
going after Mario
Arboleda.
We have no budget
for that.
Let's put it this way.
Mario Arboleda
hasn't left his house.
He takes care
of his granddaughter.
He hasn't made us
lose track of him
or anything like that.
So what's the problem?
Has any of Gustavo Cortés'
men
talked
already?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Nothing, they're not saying
anything.
We have to make them talk.
Just make up
some sentence
reduction,
a trip to Cartagena.
Chicks, offer them chicks,
lots of chicks.
No, they're not saying anything.
It's so strange.
After so many
years
working for the
police,
this is the most
loyal group
I've seen.
Those people
must be getting a
monthly fee.
Have you checked
their bank accounts?
Sure.
They're not spending a cent.
No one's living
beyond their means.
These nine guys
are being represented
by one lawyer?
Yes, by Marín.
Marín.
Can we find out
more
about this guy?
We might get
something there.
You want me to trace a...?
to trace him?
Like the shit ain't deep enough
for you already?
Antonio said
we couldn't follow
Mario Arboleda.
HE didn't say anything
about anyone else.
Do it.
- Are you sure?
- Do it!
All right, boss.
Shall we get started?
Yes, sir.
Peto, I know
everything you'll see today,
all the processes,
the equipment,
will be absolutely strange
and unknown for you.
Well, not completely.
I guess you had basic chemistry
at school.
- No.
- No?
That's all right.
I'll go slowly,
I'll explain
everything in detail.
I promise you
I won't overwhelm you
with all the information,
knowledge, formulas
and all that.
- All right.
- Thank you..
I don't need you
to become Antoine Lavoisier
from one moment
to the other.
Who?
The father of modern chemistry.
What matters here, Peto,
is that I need
all your energy and attention.
Listening, Peto.
Listening.
That's the key for learning.
Do you get me?
And if you do so,
I'm sure you'll be ready soon.
Let's get started.
It's used to measure.
Erlenmeyer,
precipitation.
Gently, gently.
Careful, careful.
That one
and this tank
too.
Adjust.
No spilling.
Come on!
Pressure is important.
Are you ready?
Transparent.
Now the CO2 freezes the
liquid, crystallizing it,
which gives us
our finished
methamphetamine.
Now all that's left
is breaking it up,
weight it
and we're
done.
This is complicated.
It's going to take me
a few more times
to get a grasp on it.
I'm absolutely sure
about it.
You'll have to go over
this
many times.
Yes, sir.
How did I do?
Fine, Peto. Fine.
You applied yourself.
That's as much as I can
ask.
Yes.
You want us to discuss
money?
No, no, no,
don't worry.
I have to learn first.
We'll then talk about that.
Hi, Doris.
Good morning.
Guess what I
brought you?
It's tangerine
cake.
You'll love it.
Thank you, Doctor.
Doris, it has a happy
face
so that you have
a happy day.
- How are you?
- What's up?
Are you all
right?
Come with us.
- No, what's going on?
- Please.
I didn't tell
you.
I'm working
with a new guy.
I think it could
work.
he's a guy
that's interested in
learning
and also...
Brother, I've tried it.
I mean...
I swear I've tried it
as hard as I could
and it's all
like bumping
into a wall.
It's like...
It's as though I didn't exist.
That's bad, dude.
And I know
she's not happy.
I know it.
I try to help her.
But I don't know
what else to do.
I just don't...
I can find no way.
I'm so screwed!
I don't know when everything
got so fucked up, Henry.
- Coffee?
- Yes.
- Two sugars?
- Yes, yes.
And what
else?
- Cream, right?
- Cream.
Lactose free.
I'll be right back.
God!
Walter.
Your coffee.
Man!
Buddy, for real,
if I'm taking
too much of your time...
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
Don't worry.
I also feel--
It's a nightmare.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
No.
Thanks.
No problem.
Buddy, I really don't know
what to do.
I just--
Gentlemen
Gómez, how are you?
Excuse me,
please.
Sure, go.
What?
Tell me you have
good news.
I sweated the guy for 14 hours.
A record.
I'll give you your
medal then.
Tell me.
What happened?
- He'll do it.
- He'll do it?
He's giving us Mario
Arboleda?
Is he
- We're getting him.
- Good!
So what are you
waiting for?
Go and get me
that fucking Mario Arboleda!
[laughing
]
Grandpa!
I'm coming!
Hello?
Can you talk?
There's a small situation
with the money
but I don't want
to do this on the phone.
Can we meet?
I can come in a few
hours.
No, I can't meet you later.
Where are you now?
At the park
with my
granddaughter.
Where exactly?
The one in front of the
library.
Perfect, I'm not far.
I'll come to you.
- Wait for me.
- Okay.
My little girl.
Hold tight.
That's it, girl.
Hello?
Mario, they're coming for you.
They're coming right now!
Slow down, Walter.
Who?
Anti-narcotics!
Somebody flipped.
They have some kind
of bank surveillance.
I don't know.
Something about some lawyer.
Someone is talking
and they're coming for you
right now.
God!
How could Mario
use that clown of a lawyer?
"Doctor Marín",
That's bullshit.
Always consult with me
before using outside counsel.
All right, Saúl.
This is nonsense.
What can we do?
Besides pray
that he gets away?
I don't know.
Because if narcotics
catches him,
he'll flip
and it'll be the end.
- We're so screwed!
-No, no, no.
Mario would
never flip.
I'm sure.
He'll never open
his mouth.
Never say never.
This is the second time
anti-narcotics takes his money.
No, Saúl,
he won't flip.
He won't,
but his nine guys will.
Wait.
Hello?
It's him!
Wait, Mario,
I'll put you on speaker
with the brain trust.
The what?
Walter and José Miguel
are here.
I don't want Walter and José.
I want you.
I need you to help me.
Sure, better call Saúl.
I've got a bag
at the airport.
Passports, money, everything.
But there're eyes
everywhere now.
I can't get close.
I need you to pick that bag
and get it to me
as soon as possible.
Mario,
do you know
how thick the crap storm
is out there because of this?
I told you not to use
that lawyer.
He's a hack!
Shut up, Saúl.
I need that bag.
Get it!
Mario, it's
José.
I can do it.
Just tell me where the
bag is
and what to do.
No, José,
I pay Saúl.
He can do it just fine.
Yes, you pay me
and anti-narcotics knows
I represent you.
They're probably out there
waiting for me to move
and so something stupid.
Mario, I can go.
It's not a
problem.
No, José, no!
No, José.
I'll do it.
Besides, remember,
you're out.
I'll do it.
Tell me where the bag is.
Walter.
Before I hand this
over,
I need something from
you.
And what's that?
The names of your
nine men.
Why?
You're never
going to pay them off.
They affect me and
José.
We deserve to know.
The only thing left now
is get out of here.
Maybe you can
leave,
I can't just
can't.
leave.
I have a family,
people depending on me.
Hum.
You're welcome!
What?
I need those names,
Mario!
You owe me that.
I don't owe you
a damn thing!
All this falling apart like this
is on you.
So it's on me?
That's some kind
of logic
right there.
You're followed
by anti-narcotics
and it's on me?
- How's that?
- Asshole!
We had a good thing!
We had Gustavo Cortés,
we had a lab,
we had everything we needed
and it all ran
like clockwork!
Yes, sure!
You should have
shut your mouth,
cook and make as much money
as you ever needed.
It was perfect.
But you just had to blow it up.
You, your pride
and your fucking ego!
You just had to be the man.
Nothing else would be
good enough, right?
If you'd done your job,
known your place,
we'd all be fine right now
and everything would be great.
Damn!
I've just realized
Lidia has the names too.
I'm so sorry, Mario.
This could have been avoided.
Shut the fuck up, Walter.
Let me die in peace.