Hello...
I'm sorry.
The door was open.
Welcome!
Let me introduce you.
This is Walter, my husband.
- Pleased to meet you.
- You too.
Cielo told me you work
at Número Atómico lab.
That's right.
I've heard about the place.
What you do over there
sounds like Science Fiction.
Well, we just call it Science.
Yes, sure.
Exciting, isn't it?
Honestly, what I do
would bore you senseless.
Well, this is it, honey.
This is the house
I can't stop talking about.
What do you think?
Do you want to take a tour?
Sure.
Let's do something.
How about I give you
some privacy
so you check out the place?
She knows the style
perfectly well.
I'll go for a walk meanwhile.
- Sounds good.
- Fine.
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
What I like about this house
is...
I don't know.
The energy.
I love the garden!
And the fountain.
It's incredible, isn't it?
- And it has rooms as well.
- Really??
- Where people sleep.
- No kidding! That's good!
- Let's go upstairs.
- How many?
- Three.
That's all?
No, we need five
at least.
Do I look like I'm about to drop
a litter?
We need three at least, right?
Yes, sure.
Hugo, Paco and Luis.
I don't know, honey.
I feel we need something more...
- More what?
- I don't know. Bigger.
Spacious.
Honey, I swear I've already been
to every house in the city
and this is a good neighborhood.
It's the best house we can get
for our price range.
Then let's stretch
our price range.
How are we supposed
to stretch it?
No, I'm just saying
we should live the moment.
That's all.
Hey, are you in the mafia?
Did you win the lottery
and not tell me?
Cielo, we don't have to fear
the future.
Was can't just paralyze
or be too cautious.
We've got nowhere to go
but up.
So let's go up.
Hello?
Walter, it's us.
So.
Walk towards us.
Mario, I'm going to need
some kind of assurance.
Walter...
I assure you I could kill you
from way over here.
Walter.
Mario.
You've caused
too much trouble lately.
That's how things are now.
Put your arms out on the sides.
Please.
The hat.
You know I haven't slept
since Thursday?
I was out all night cleaning up
after you.
Though I'm old
and I get insomnia,
I need to sleep, Walter.
You said no half measures.
You gave me that advice.
It's funny how words
can be so open
to interpretation.
Let's go.
You got your car fixed?
No. Not yet.
Do it, it's important.
Sure, it's the car
my wife uses.
And that you use
to kill our people.
Has your condition worsened?
- Excuse me?
- Your medical condition,
your health,
has it grown worse?
Not that I know of.
Is there a ringing
in your ears?
Are you seeing bright lights
or hearing voices?
No, I'm quite well.
- Thanks for asking.
- No.
You're not well.
Clearly you are not.
No rational person
would do what you did.
What you did
was not intelligent.
Explain yourself.
My partner was about
to get himself shot.
I intervened.
Some worthless junkie.
For him you intervene
and put us all at risk?
Some contemptible junkie who
couldn't keep the peace
for eight hours?
That's right. He couldn't.
He was angry because
those two dealers of yours
had just murdered
an 11-year-old boy.
I heard about it.
He should have let me
take care of them.
maybe.
Then again, maybe he thought
it was you who gave the order.
Are you asking me
if I ordered the murder
of a child?
I'd never ask you that.
Where is José Miguel Rosas now?
I don't know.
Could be in Medellín,
Venezuela. I don't know.
the thing is he's not near.
He's got enough money
to last forever.
He knows
he needs to keep moving.
I don't think you'll find him.
I don't know, Walter.
It's what I do after all.
Find people.
Make them appear
and disappear.
The way I see it,
José Miguel Rosas doesn't exist.
He's out of the picture.
That's what you wanted
from the beginning.
Am I wrong?
Gustavo,
you've always struck me
as a very pragmatic man.
I'd like us to manage things
that way.
The best ting to do
would be to review
the options we have.
"We have"?
Right. That you have.
I think you have two.
May I?
You kill me right here and now.
You start looking
for José Miguel,
you'll find him
sooner or later.
You kill him.
End of story.
Just a revenge exercise
that seems pointless to me.
And option B?
I continue cooking.
You and I
forget about my ex-partner.
We forget this ever happened.
We consider this a lone hiccup
in an otherwise
long and fruitful
business arrangement.
I prefer option B.
You'd need a new assistant.
- Sure, I'll get one.
- No.
This time, I choose.
Sounds good.
Get your car fixed.
I will.
Excuse me.
Those are the new rules?
I can't open the door?
The new rules.
Guido.
Professor.
It's good to have you back.
It's good to be back.
- Shall we?
- Let's cook.
We're here!
- Ready?
- And the others?
The others are for me.
No, grandpas
don't play with balloons..
I do.
Besides, you have to tell me
why you want a rhino at home
if they're ugly.
No, they're nice.
Besides,
with such a big nose,
they'd break everything at home.
It's not a nose,
it's a horn.
You never stop learning.
Can I have a pink balloon?
Later, honey.
I need them for a job.
Some other day.
- Come in.
- No, I don't have time.
Sen grandpa a kiss.
- Hi. How are you?
- Hi. Fine.
I brought your car.
It's perfect now.
These guys are real genius.
There're no signs of the bump.
By the way,
I cleaned it
and polished it.
Thanks.
It was quite useful.
But you have to be careful.
You crashed because you left
in a hurry the other night
and I was worried.
Yes, I'm sorry.
It was just a mistake.
I was in a hurry-
I know, I'll get nowhere
if I hurry.
It was just to do something
for work.
Do you need to keep the car?
No, no, no.
What's more, I asked one
of the car sellers
to come with me
so I could leave you your car.
What?
Come.
- You bought a new car?
- Yes.
I just realized I was
spending too much on taxis.
Besides,
you have to enjoy life,
you never know
how long you'll last.
It's an expensive car.
No.
Not that much.
it's not showy,
ostentatious.
For an unemployed professor,
it is.
You think so?
But...
I think it's totally normal
for the owner of a car wash
to have such a car.
That justifies
the deal I offered you.
Doesn't it?
What happened?
What was that?
Quiet.
Come here.
Come, come.
Hi, Carlitos!
Do you have anything
you want to tell me?
Thank God you're here.
- They were keeping me prisoner.
- Prisoner?
Then that's why
you haven't sent us
the inputs, right?
Mario, please,
I don't work for them.
They stole my chemicals.
I couldn't do anything.
You know I'm a businessman.
- A businessman, I know.
- Of course.
The lady out front
knows how to drive?
Yes, why do you ask?
Because she's driving you
to hospital.
Untie her.
She's going to need her shoe.
And from now on
I strongly recommend you
to answer our calls.
Mexican.
Just that one.
The others are from here.
He was probably
looking for people
for that case in particular.
Neither them nor him
are good.
Anyway, we're talking
about people from the cartel.
No doubt about it.
They must be looking
for our weaknesses
because they must have heard
we're producing.
But they found none.
What about Rosas?
I'm making inquiries.
You can take your mask off now.
Let's activate this.
Yes, sir.
Does that guy ever leave?
I don't think so.
When exactly did that start?
It's new.
We had...
We had a little drama
with the person you replaced.
I'm sorry to hear that.
No, it'll be fine.
Things will continue
to smooth out.
But if you're at all worried
about working with me.
No, no, no, I'm not.
It's all right.
Because whatever my shortcomings
last time,
I intend for things to go
perfectly
from here on out to--
No, Guido, for real.
Don't worry. It's all right.
You're a great chemist.
I'll all be all right.
We'll do things your way.
That's it.
I just want to learn from you.
Thanks, Guido.
Four.
Guido.
Boss! Mr. Gustavo.
I should have called first.
- Do I interrupt?
- No, no, no, sir.
- Come in.
- Thanks.
Excuse me
You want some coffee,
green tea,
some liquor?
No, no, Guido.
No, thanks.
I'm fine.
In fact, I came here
to talk to you
about something serious
and rather pressing.
Yes, sure.
If push came to shove,
I was wondering how soon
you might be able
to take over the lab yourself.
You and an assistant.
Mr. Gustavo,
are you asking me
to be in charge of the lab?
Yes.
Why would push
come to shove?
Guido.
Has Walter ever talked to you
about why he got into this
particular line of work?
No, sir.
I assumed it was
because it pays so well.
That could be a reason.
But specifically,
has he ever spoken to you
about his health problems?
I'm not surprised.
He's a very private person.
What exactly are
his health problems?
He's dying of cancer, Guido.
He's doing this
to provide his family.
In my opinion,
he's got enough money.
They'll never want for anything.
He's accomplished his goal.
How long does he have?
We don't know.
Every time I ask him,
the conversation is not easy.
I understand.
I intend to keep Walter on
as long as he wants,
assuming he's physically
up to it.
But...
As he cannot or will not tell me
how long that might be,
I must prepare
for the worst-case scenario.
How soon would you be ready
to take over the lab, Guido?
I think that...
I suppose if we had at least
a few more cooks together...
You don't think
you're ready now?
No.
The things is
he's such a genius,
he's a master.
There's always
some more for me to learn.
But if you ask me
for a date,
I'd say one or two more cooks.
One.
I'd be ready with one more.
I guess.
I believe in you, Guido.
I know that when the time comes
to make a decision,
you'll be ready.
What's up, Guido?
Walter, I have a question.
Why do I get the impression
you're more curious
than usual today?
- No.
- No, no. Just ask me.
What I wanted to know was...
Is there any particular trick
to purging the catalyst bed?
No, it's pretty straightforward.
I'll show you when we get there
Thank you.
Mario, I'm busy.
I see.
I'm looking
for one of your clients.
- Which client?
- José Miguel Rosas
Why don't you look for him
on the internet
or on the phone book?
I need you to concentrate.
The sooner you tell me,
the sooner you can get back
to whatever the hell
this is exactly.
Mario,
let me tell you someth--
You're good right there.
I'll sit here
and we'll both be comfortable.
We all know why I tell you
I'm looking
for José Miguel Rosas, right?
And you pretending otherwise
only wastes my time
and serves to annoy me.
The problem is
there're rules
to this lawyer thing.
Is that right?
Yes, yes.
It's the attorney-client
privilege,
so I can give you information
just like that
because that could cost me
my license.
And I'm not just talking
about this client.
I offer you the same service.
So if I give up José,
then you'd be right to think
I could give you up as well,
don't you think?
So then where's the trust?
I trust the river flow
I'd throw Saúl Bueno in.
Yes, it's an argument.
So don't make me beat you
till your legs don't work.
Whose legs?
- The kicker's
or the kicked one?
- It's the same.
No, no, no.
I can't tell you.
I couldn't live with myself.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no!
Fine, fine, fine.
I can't "say" anything but...
But who's to say
that I wrote it down
in my day planner
and you just saw it
while searching my office
when I was not here?
That's good, right?
Don't touch anything
on my desk.
I'll make myself some coffee.
Agree?
I'm just looking out for you,
that's all.
Believe me, money laundering
isn't what it used to be.
I do miss those times.
They used such lively colors.
I still like them.
- Light colors.
- Stop, Saúl.
I'm not interested
in anything else.
I'm buying the car wash.
That's it.
End of story.
One look at this place
and you'll fall in love.
You'll thank me
for the rest of your life.
Come, Walter, Come.
Look.
Here it is!
Here it is.
What do you think?
Are you serious, Saúl?
Of course I'm serious!
Where else are you going to find
a cash-only business
that's this much fun?
This could easily be called
"Laundryfun"
- No. This won't work.
- No, no, no. Wait.
Don't say anything
until you see it.
Don't be so incredulous.
Let's get in and you'll see.
Listen to me.
Come.
This place is ideal.
You can have children's parties,
baptisms, communions, birthdays,
with moms and dads
and you can also organize
some orgies for teenagers.
Saúl, thanks.
Just leave it there.
No, no, I won't.
How come
they're tracing the car?
Is it bugged?
- I said "Maybe. Maybe.
- They're following me, Walter.
Mario, who's supposed
to be on my side,
threatened to break my legs.
I'm so nervous
I had to double
my whisky doses in the morning.
What are you getting me into?
I'm seriously rethinking
my pricing.
And that goes for you too.
Mario is no dummy.
Give us 17 hours
before he finds out
the address I gave him
goes nowhere.
So you guys talk your stuff,
do your thing
but make it snappy.
I'm going to look
for somewhere to pee.
Maybe the house of terror.
How are you holding up?
Just here.
You?
I got my job back.
At least until they kill me
and Guido takes over.
So he's their boy?
How long you think you've got?
I don't know.
He asks a lot of questions
about the cooking process.
I try to be as vague
as possible,
but it's not easy.
They watch me
day and night.
Maybe the only thing
that's saving me
is Guido's fastidiousness.
He won't be sure until he learns
each detail of the process.
But once he learns
the entire method...
So what do we do?
You know what we have to do.
There's got to be
some other way, Walter.
Maybe it's better for you
to just go to the cops.
You could tell them
you did it for your family
and give them
lots of information.
They'll be happy.
You could even make a deal
with the DEA.
They could take you
to thee U.S.,
change your name,
your surname.
Maybe just the surname.
Walter is American.
That would work there.
I can disappear.
I can live like this.
I've been doing it.
We made a good career,
but it's over now.
No! No!
I'll never go to the police!
I'll never go to the DEA!
We have to keep cooking, José.
That's the one thing
I'm certain of.
Gustavo can't stop production,
he can't afford to.
So if I'm the only chemist
that he's got,
then I've got leverage.
And leverage keeps me alive!
It keeps you alive too.
If I'm the only chemist
that he's got.
I can't do it.
I can't.
I'm no murderer,
you said so.
I'll do it.
But I need your help.
José, they watch me
all day.
I can't even get close
to Guido.
But if I could just shake Victor
for even an hour one night,
I could...
I think I may be able to make it
look like an accident.
There has to be some other way.
I wish there was,
but there isn't.
If it comes down to us and him,
then it's him.
José, you're the only edge
I've got.
As long as they don't know
you're in Bogotá,
you're my only edge.
But I need you to track Guido.
Get me his address
and I'll do the rest.
José, I saved your life.
Will you save mine?
So cute.
Such lovely little hands.
Yes.
Hello?
Tell me you have good news,
tell me you found him, please.
He lives behind Teusaquillo.
Route 20, number 25-12.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Yes, I'm here.
Route 20, number 25-12.
- Is he at home?
- Yes.
Anyone watching the place?
No, looks pretty calm.
There's no one here
after 6 PM.
Fine.
When are you doing it?
Tonight.
Don't do it.
This is not the same
as killing two guys
who deserved it.
This guy it's innocent.
It's not worth it.
There's no option.
Walter, go to the cops.
Listen to me.
Hey, we've got a problem!
There's some kind
of chemical leaking in your lab.
You have to come.
Sure.
- I'll follow you.
- No!
They told me to bring you.
Get on.
Hurry!
I don't know if it's a barrel
leak or what,
but you got something stinky
down there.
After you.
Walter, the sooner
you figure out what this is,
- the sooner we'll go home.
- No.
No, Mario,
please, don't do this.
Unfortunately, I do.
No, no, no. Let me cook.
I'll cook for free.
- I'll do anything!
- No.
If I could talk to Gustavo,
I could explain it to him.
- He'll understand.
- No.
Please!
I can convince him!
- No.
- Please! Please, Mario!
Shut up!
I can't talk to Gustavo.
- I'm sorry. I can't.
- I'll give you Rosas!
He's the problem.
You know it.
Without him,
we'd be all right.
I'll tell you where he is.
He's in Bogotá.
He's not near,
but he's not
where you're looking.
I need an address right now.
No, no, no,
I have no address.
He moves around.
But if you let me call him,
I--¡No, no, no!
It's my phone!
Calm down.
I'm just getting my phone.
I'll call him
and I'll have him meet me.
Hello.
Did you do it?
- No, you have to do it.
- What?
What?
No way,.
Listen to me.
You're closer than we are.
You'll have about 20 minutes
lead.
They've got me at the laundry.
They'll kill me!
So it, José!
José, do it!
Just what the hell
was that exactly?
You might want to hold off.
Why?
Because your boss
is going to need me.
Route 20, number 25-12.
You?
How can I help you?
No...
I had nothing to do
with their firing you.
They just called me.
I have money.
You want money?
I can give you anything.
What do you want?
Please, don't...
Please, don't.