THREE MONTHS AGO
I thought
I was going to see some nudes.
I didn't say
she painted nudes.
I said it was
an erotic exposition.
If this is eroticism,
I'm the Pope.
This painting isn't only
about the human body.
It is about daily life.
And if you look at it
with an ironic perspective
it is about
all the prejudices
and taboos about sex.
There it is.
If you wanted to get new ideas
trust me, I have
much more imagination than this.
Really, this artist had health
problems, so to speak.
It's a door.
- A door?
- Yes.
Any other doors
we can check out? Like...
the exit door, for example?
Yes?
No?
[Jose snorting)
I did like
the cow skull pictures.
Those were cool.
But a door?
I will say it again: a door.
Sometimes, you simply
get fixated on something
and do not even get why.
You open yourself up
and go with the flow
and go wherever the universe
wants to take you.
So the universe took this lady
to a door
and she got
all obsessed with it
and just had to paint it
once and again
until it was perfect.
No, I wouldn't say that.
Nothing's perfect.
- No?
- No.
You know what? I don't agree.
I do believe
there are perfect things.
That was so sweet.
I think I threw up
in my mouth a little bit.
You can't admit just
for once that I'm right.
Come on, Miss Curator.
What happened is very clear.
The old lady saw a door
and got so obsessed
that she painted it
a thousand times
until it was perfect.
No.
I believe that
the door was her home
and she loved it.
In my opinion
that's about making
that feeling last forever.
Give me a step.
Just one step, Henry, please.
I can't, I can't!
That's it. Take me up!
Come on, honey.
- You can do this. Try.
Just imagine
that pain is weakness
leaving your body, honey.
Pain is my foot
in your ass, María!
Okay.
Listen to me.
If you can get your leg up,
go for it.
I can bear it.
Let's see.
Take me up! No!
Take me up, stop pulling me!
Take me up! Take me up!
We're gonna let you rest
for a minute
and in some minutes
we're gonna try it again.
- Okay, Henry?
- No fucking minutes!
Take me up.
I'm done! I can't!
Take him up.
Easy. All right.
Come on, uncle Henry.
You can do it.
How else are you going
to get out of here?
Don't you have any friends?
Find something better to do
than staying here
being a pain in the ass!
Watching me hanging here
like the balls
of an old man in a Turkish bath.
Fuck!
Henry, calm down.
Junior just wants
to be supportive,
like the rest of us.
- Let's go.
- Never mind, mom.
Breathe.
I'm breathing, don't you see?
Cielo.
We got our first bill.
Baby, do me a favor.
Get ahead.
I've got to talk to your aunt.
Jesus, María.
Remember this is a secret
between Walter, you and I.
- Be careful, okay?
- Sorry.
Can you help us?
Yes, María, we can.
Prepare yourself
for the figure. Look.
They're gonna start
coming in weekly.
- Okay.
- You're sure you can do this?
Yeah.
- Relax.
- Thanks.
I'll do that.
What the hell, man?
What, I can't work a scale now?
Just say the words.
Say you think I'm stealing.
Move.
The phrase was
"You have to learn
to walk with who you are."
It was repeated
over an over again by somebody
who was close to me
and helped me a lot.
He was my sponsor when I
started coming to meetings.
And I like it because
it involves
something very important.
And that is
that we have to learn
to accept ourselves
the way we are.
But this idea of "walk"
is also interesting
because it tells me
to advance, to go on
to move forward.
Welcome, Jose.
And I think that
it's an important concept
to bear in mind.
I see we have
new people, a couple new faces,
which is good.
Maybe we can introduce
ourselves. Why don't you
raise your hands,
the new ones
so everybody knows who they are?
You, okay.
All right. Very good.
And you, okay.
Who wants to start us off?
How about you?
What's your name?
My name is Andrea.
Feel free to say
whatever you want
what you're thinking or feeling.
Honestly,
I don't want to be here.
It's good for you
to feel that, this rejection.
I invite you,
if you don't want to be here
to go out, take a walk, okay?
Talk to people.
Draw your own conclusions.
What matters here is that nobody
is forced to stay, okay?
Anybody else?
What's up?
My name is Jose.
Nice to meet you. Mauricio,
but everybody calls me Mono.
And this is
- I believe, Pedro?
- Right. I'm Pedro.
Nice to meet you, bro.
What's up, man?
How are you?
- I'm sorry, guys.
- No, go ahead.
It's for everybody.
I wanted to give you a heads up.
It's gonna get a little slower
smuggling product
with Grandpa Anus
breathing down my neck.
He's watching every move I make.
But don't worry.
I'll keep it flowing.
- Great.
- So?
How's it going?
How's it selling?
Mad volume?
Yeah! It's...
You know, bro, it's, um...
It's not so good.
What do you mean?
How much have you sold, bro?
Me? I sold a tenth.
One tee--?
One tenth?
To who?
To him.
You must be joking!
Man
I couldn't resist it.
Look, buddy, you know what?
It's not so easy
selling to these people.
Look, look at them.
They're trying
to better themselves
and we're trying
to get them back to a hole.
Yeah.
I agree with el Mono.
Here, you can sense
you can breathe
some positivism, man.
They're here
opening up their hearts
telling about their fam--
I feel remorse.
"I feel remorse."
You're kidding me, right?
I'm out risking my ass
to get product for you two
for you to come with this shit?
Now you're guardian angels
and can't sell?
Pussies!
You know what?
I want it back. All of it.
I'll sell it myself.
Come on, man.
Don't be like that, Jose.
But it's true, yo.
Selling to these
people is like...
like shooting a baby
in the face.
Yeah, man.
- It's not easy like you think.
- It's not easy?
I'll show you
exactly how easy it is.
Check this out.
Fucking pussies.
I told you.
Excuse me.
Hey. Sorry!
- No. Go ahead.
It's Andrea, right?
- Yeah.
- Pleasure. I'm Jose.
Wanna know something?
I don't really want to be here,
either.
- Shall I join you?
- Okay.
Smooth talker.
- Hi, mom.
- Hey.
Aunt's coming to dinner?
No.
Your dad is.
For real?
Hey.
How'd you get her
to sleep so quick?
Are you that boring?
I'm comforting.
I'm a comforting presence.
Look, Walter,
this is the certificate
of physical and mental fitness
signed by a doctor.
This was the only requirement
I needed to get
my driver's license.
So now
- I can drive my way.
- No way. Not yet.
You don't turn 16
for two more months.
I'm almost there.
We need to have
everything ready.
What do you mean "ready"?
Well, you know our old car
isn't so convenient for me.
And now
that I'll have my license
it'd be a good idea
to buy a new one.
I'd like a convertible.
Don't you want
some mango lemonade too?
We might also buy one of
those which have mini fridges
for the champagne bottles.
Who told you
we were going to buy you a car?
I heard you two talking
about my problems
with public transport.
Since when do you eavesdrop
other people's conversations?
This country is not prepared
to deal with people
who have reduced mobility.
Just listen to this manipulator!
I don't know how people
get to manage without a car.
- Are you talking about me?
- Yeah, maybe.
Mom doesn't let you
get even close to the car
so why don't you buy one?
Look, Junior.
That's not so easy.
Money doesn't grow on trees.
Besides, it's a decision
that can't be taken overnight.
I've been thinking about this
for a long time.
We should probably leave
this discussion for later.
Now your dad and I
have a couple things
we need to talk about, so--
The most important thing
is that it is aerodynamic.
I like red very much
and, if it's not convertible
at least,
it should have a roof hatch.
That should do for me.
Perfect! I'll write it down
so I don't forget.
- Leave her in the crib?
- Okay.
Well
here you are.
Ice Creams and Popsicles
Little Fridge Inc.?
What's that?
It's a loan-out.
- It's fine.
- Whose loan-out?
Listen, Walter.
Does your guy know the tax code
and regulations in this country?
There's very specific paperwork
that has to be submitted
and declared.
Yes, relax.
He's a qualified guy.
Completely qualified!
Who is he?
What's his name?
What are his qualifications?
What's his experience?
Walter, please, understand.
This money
has to be unimpeachable
when it reaches Henry and María.
And it is. It will be!
But how do I know that?
You can't even tell me
the man's name!
Really?
Do you really want to know?
Do you want me
to tell you the name?
Yes.
Welcome!
Mrs. Cielito.
I'm just gonna call you Cielito
from now on.
I like my customers
to feel comfortable.
To get familiar.
Besides, it's a lovely name.
"Cielo."
It's pretty obvious.
Walt never told me
how lucky he was.
Clearly, Walter's taste in women
is the same
as his taste in lawyers.
Only the very best!
With just the right amount
of dirty.
to do it more...
Sorry, no.
I like to joke
and it's patently obvious
that you are very classy.
Please, sit down.
Cielito.
All right.
Well...
Look, Cielito
so Walt tells me
that you have some doubts
and concerns
and I'm the right guy
to alleviate them.
Yes, I do have some concerns.
And if we're going
to go down this road
it's for the sake
of my brother-in-law.
Your brother-in-law.
I've heard about him.
An upright, correct
and faultless man.
And ruthless too.
There are no heroes
like him anymore
nowhere,
not even in the police.
At any rate
I need some assurances
that we're gonna go about this
in a safe
and, above all, cautious manner.
Of course.
Fair enough.
That's how we're gonna do it.
I'll walk you
through the process.
First step is something
we call money laundering.
How does it work?
Take your money,
represented by, say...
This. Here.
This is your money, all right?
Let's imagine these pencils--
I'm a
bookkeeper.
I actually know
what money laundering is.
You're a bookkeeper?
No way!
So?
And, as with most things
the devil is in the details.
So to begin with,
what are we saying?
Which will be the source
of this money?
That's simple.
Walt here actually
came up with a great story.
Brilliant, I'd say!
Ht thought gambling winnings.
Blackjack, right?
- Am I right?
- Yes.
- Some card counting?
Well, actually,
that was Cielo's idea.
- Really?
- Yes.
Cielito!
You grow more gorgeous
by the minute.
Well, there you have it.
What I'm gonna do
is generating
some false currency
transaction reports
as well as
the necessary W-2Gs.
I know a couple casino managers
who will jump at the chance
to report false losses.
It's a win-win for everyone.
Yeah, but you can't...
You can't sell that
for very long.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Way ahead of you. We declare
just enough
so as not to arouse suspicion.
Then Walt's one-time winnings
will become seed money
for an investment.
Investment in what?
Drum roll please.
Exactly!
What do we have?
A theme park!
for the whole family!
Or, at least,
a business inside the park.
7,000 square feet
of rollicking fun for everyone!
- I've already seen
the premises.
- An amusement park?
- A theme park?
- It's the latest fad, Walter.
It's always been in the market
although it hasn't been seen
in the market.
But it will be a revolution,
we will all enjoy.
All the family will have fun.
It's the latest craze!
What does it have to do
with Walt?
- It doesn't make any sense.
- Look, Cielito
it makes more sense
than you two being together.
I'm still trying to figure out
how did you do to get
such a beautiful sweet lady.
Do you even know Walt?
Tell me why
Walter, of all people
would buy such a business.
- It doesn't add up.
- It adds up perfectly.
Why?
Walt's a scientist.
And every scientist
inside, deep inside,
are like little kids.
Kids who love magic,
sleight of hand, illusion
tricks, the lab.
Walter has every right to
set the kid he has inside free.
Sure.
And I'm gonna meet
with my family
and tell them:
"Haven't I told you?
Overnight Walter
decided to invest
- in a business for kids."
- And teenagers.
You really think
I'm telling that
to the people who know him?
"Sure, that's always been
Walter's wish
he just kept it for himself."
Really? That's what we're
supposed to tell our family
our friends,
the government?
All right. Let me bottom line
this for you.
You don't need to be involved.
Why? Because I'm the one
doing this job.
I've been doing this
for a lot of years
successfully and without your
help, believe it or not.
So, we can call it a day.
Thank you very much.
It's been a great pleasure,
Cielito.
Thank you for stopping by.
You want a beer
or something?
Or something.
What do you mean?
Like beer.
I'm clean out of anything else
you may be thinking about.
Even if I wasn't,
we're not supposed to.
Yeah. I know, I know.
It's the only thing
I hear lately.
Over and over again.
No, no and no.
Don't you think
it's ridiculous
that society says beer is okay
and a little hit
of something sweet is wrong?
what's the point of shutting
yourself off
from something
that lifts you off the ground?
You can't imagine
how much energy I spend
fighting the urge not to use.
And I feel like crap
because of it.
I know. It's just...
- What? What is it?
- It's just...
I can't get caught using again.
See, that's exactly the thing.
Not to get caught again.
You ever try that
blue stuff that's going around?
No?
It's the bomb.
Just a little gas in the tank
and suddenly life
gets much more interesting,
all's worth it.
Things look so different.
And it's so little
that is very unlikely
that you get hooked.
Like I said,
I got nothing here.
What if
I could get some?
You wanna try it?
Kiss to mommy.
Mommy! Mommy!
Your Nana
brought you home early.
Mom, I thought we said
you picked up Byron from school
and kept him.
I was, but I passed by
and saw you were here.
So I stopped.
I thought you had a meeting.
I did, but we changed the time.
Mom, this is Jose.
He's from the meeting.
He's like a sponsor.
- Jose, this is mom.
- Hi.
Baby, don't forget
to wash your hands, okay?
Come here.
Have you no shame?
I can't believe it, Andrea!
I can't believe it!
Go up right away!
Jose, this is Byron.
You have a kid?
What's up, buddy?
Byron?
That's a cool name.
Here. Give it up.
Right on!
Byron is almost six.
You okay with kids?
What? Kids?
Yeah, I like them!
- He's cool.
- Well
Byron is gonna
go play in his room
while the big people talk.
- Say "Bye, Jose."
- Bye, Jose.
Bye, Byron.
How was school today?
Fine.
Safe and cautious.
That's all I'm asking.
And that lawyer of yours
is neither.
Yeah, at first sight, he may
come across like a circus clown.
At second too.
But he actually knows
what he's doing.
Safe and cautious
is you not being involved
in this at all.
It's late on that.
This is what happens when you
decide to pay our bills
with money from drug business.
Cielo, this isn't
just about what happened before.
My involvement in this
is ongoing. Understand?
I can't just quit.
I have something of a contract
with them.
It's all very safe,
structured and professional.
I can't simply go there
and say "I quit."
What do you do?
Where are you going?
Walter, if you're gonna
launder money
at least, do it right.
You worked here four years.
It's a business you understand.
It's a story
people will believe.
This is what we buy.
No theme parks nor shit.
I mean, you.
This is what you buy.
You heard what the man said,
buddy?
Yeah, man. It touched my soul.
Yeah, because it's true, pussy.
Hi.
Jose, right?
This is Pedro and I'm el Mono.
How's everything?
You've been waiting long?
Why are you so stupid?
Easy, buddy.
I thought we had to keep
the story until the very end.
How's that, man?
So you and that girl
- you do the deed yet?
- Do what, yo?
Sell her our top product.
What are you two
even doing here?
What do you mean?
You can't get
your nut up to sell.
What's the point of even
coming?
Homie, I'm on step five.
I no longer use and I admit
my mistakes before others
myself and even you,
if you want.
Really, man. Me too.
I'm also on step five.
You must be joking, right?
No, we're being serious.
Step five
is harmony, dedication,
discipline and perseverance.
You know what?
See you later, bitches.
You see that, Tripa?
Yeah, man. He gave in
to the worst of the vices.
We have to get him back.
Yes.
Byron.
You know?
I have magical powers.
Look.
Look at my thumb. Ready?
One, two and...
- That's not real.
- It is real.
All right, do you want
to see something that's real?
You see this piece of paper?
Look, it looks like a worm.
- Do it again!
- Let Jose eat his dinner.
No, it's okay.
Want to see it again?
Could you do a trick
with firecrackers?
Firecrackers?
I don't have
any firecrackers on me. Why?
Who does tricks
with firecrackers?
Tomás.
And how are those tricks?
Who's Tomás?
- He's my kid brother.
- I see.
And we don't talk about him.
Eat your pizza.
You're can't be serious!
That's what you want to buy?
Yes.
Saúl, people will believe it
at least.
I worked here for four years.
Yeah, with a green overalls
and a cap, right?
Hey, how come you guys
always get
with the air freshener?
Although you say
you don't want it.
Me, for example,
I'm allergic to that.
I end up sneezing
and smelling of strawberry.
You should respect customers.
It they don't want
air freshener,
they don't want it. Period.
I don't know, but I think
this makes a better story.
Much better
than your theme park, Saúl.
Is that you talking
or the "cielito"
you have back home?
Saúl, let's admit it!
Cielo has a point.
It makes more sense
investing my capital
right here, you know?
Based on her long years
of experience
in money laundering, I suppose.
Let me tell you something.
If you're committed enough
you can make any story work.
You see?
I once
convinced a woman
that I was a famous TV star.
And it worked. Why?
Because I believed it.
Capisci ?
Besides, I don't know.
This dump isn't gonna work
because it doesn't have
a Daniel.
There's no Daniel here.
What in God's name is a Daniel?
Daniel runs the theme park.
The guy who had the idea.
The one who had a vision.
That man saw
where others saw a dirt lot
the possibility of a park
with lights, rubber aliens
and magic.
You see? How do you think
Las Vegas was invented?
Because there was a dreamer.
Some Daniel that dreamed of it.
And when Daniel
had financial problems,
what did he do?
He went searching for
exactly the type of
situation we're offering.
Daniel will look the other way
to keep his great project,
his dream afloat.
In other words Daniel
can be trusted completely.
But this guy here?!
Just check him out!
You can't trust
someone like him.
Listen to him!
You buy this place, all you got
will be some hoses
water jets and nothing else,
why?
You got no Daniel here.
Move!
Early still.
If you're holding,
we can do something.
You know
that stuff we talked about
the other day?
That blue stuff
you told me about?
What?
What kind of mother are you?
What kind of mom gets wasted
with a little kid
to take care of?
- Listen.
- What do you know about me?
I take care of my baby
and I'll do anything for him!
And I strive every day
for him not to follow
Tomás' steps.
You're right.
Sorry.
They made him kill somebody.
Some dealer
from some outside crew
who was sticking his nose
in the neighborhood.
Some fat guy
who was selling there too.
Yo, they killed Gordo.
Shot him dead.
El Gordo called me before...
Before that. There were two men
acting funny.
Why didn't we go sell
to a different place?
- When was this?
- A few months back.
What else did he tell you?
He shot him dead.
Just because he was working
the wrong corner.
I won't let my boy
go through something like that.
Guess what.
People who say "Guess what"
and then actually
expect you to guess.
I hate those people.
I just heard
about a certain patient,
last name, Navarro
first name, Henry
who is going to be released
at the end of this week.
You like the news?
It's fantastic.
Are they planning on rolling me
out the front door
or they'll put me
on a greased plank
and slide me out the window?
- Honey, why do you say that?
- You know what?
I don't care what the insurance
company thinks.
I'm not leaving here
until I'm well.
Henry, this has nothing to do
with insurance.
All the doctors agree
in that you're healthy enough
- to go home.
I'm healthy enough?
Honey, you get stronger
every day.
You're fine.
You don't need
to be in a hospital.
María, I don't know
if you realize
the condition I'm in.
And in this condition...
I do need
to be in this hospital.
Okay?
Baby, you'll have
all the same equipment--
What?
What do you mean?
You'll do the same PT
you do here
but at your house,
which will be great
because you'll be home.
It's always better to be home.
Besides, I renovated our room.
A complete renovation.
Guess what?
I had them move the plasma in.
You'd always asked me to hang
the TV on the wall
and I'd always said no.
You only had to get shot
to get it, right?
I got you a new bed.
- You got a bed?
- Yes.
- A hospital bed?
- Well Henry, since--
Henry my ass!
You put a hospital bed
in my bedroom?
- Baby.
- Baby my ass!
You take that shit out of my
room right away, María!
- Henry, come on.
- "Henry, come on"?
"Henry, come on"?!
I leave this hospital
when I walk out of here.
You understand?
- You understand?!
- Yes.
A Daniel?
What's that?
An accomplice.
Someone who's in on the scheme
who knows about laundering
and who's simply paid
to play dumb
and look the other way.
Look. Fine.
I agree with you
the theme park is a hard sell.
But without a Daniel
the car wash isn't feasible.
It isn't really an option.
What about me?
- What about you?
- I'll be Daniel.
No. No way.
No, no!
I'm perfectly capable
of managing a small business!
A legal business, not this.
Who else could we trust?
- No!
- Walter, for God's sake!
- I'm in this already!
- Sorry?
And if I'm in it,
I'm going to do it right.
You are not in this!
How am I not in this?
We're married!
We are not married, no.
We're divorced.
Right?
I never actually filed
the papers.
Married couples
can't be compelled
to testify against one another.
Jose! Respirator.
Hello.
Yes?
Yes. All right.
Okay. I'll be there.
What was that?
An invitation.
Walter.
You're right on time!
- Please, come in.
- Thanks.
I hope you like bouillabaisse.
In short, it's nothing more
than a fish stew
with a fancy name.
It sounds like a cliché
but indeed, it's just exactly
like my mother used to make it.
Do you like to cook?
You can help me.
Do you mind?
Would you slice the garlic?
Very thin, please.
This is a French dish
that I love.
Why did you invite me here?
We're working together.
I thought it was important
that we spent
some time out of the office.
Now the garlic.
It always amazes me the way
the senses work
in connection to memory.
This stew is simply
an amalgam of ingredients.
If I took them separately
they don't remind me
of anything.
But this way
the smell of this stew
instantly brings me back
to my childhood.
How is that possible?
It all takes place
in the hippocampus.
The senses make the neurons
express signals
that go back
to the same part of the brain
where memory is stored.
Smell, for example
can be related
to a childhood memory.
That's something
called relational memory.
But don't quote me on that.
I'm rusty on my biology.
That's very interesting.
Walter.
I would like to help you.
Help me how?
When I first started out
I made a lot of mistakes.
Maybe more than I care to admit.
I wish I'd had someone
to advise me.
This life of ours
it can be overwhelming.
You are a wealthy man now.
And one must learn to be rich.
When a man is by himself
he can manage to be poor.
But being rich
is a totally different story.
What advice do you have for me?
Never make
the same mistake twice.
You Tomás?
Heard you were the man.
Yeah? What you want?
Meth. I need a tenth.
Three hundred.
For a tenth?
No, yo.
Hey, easy, buddy.
So what's up?
Hey!
Bounce, bro!
Bye!