You saved our lives. I
can't thank you enough.
I don't understand
what happened to us,
we were driving and
taking a look at the map.
My phone started ringing.
I didn't pay attention to the road and,
all of a sudden, we were in the ditch.
And then you found us here.
Your pants.
The thing is that I was
drinking coffee. With
the maneuver,
the coffee ended all over my pants.
And...
Like I said,
I can't thank you enough.
Exactly. Thank you very much,
bro.
And now what? Can't
we just dump them here?
Yes, of course. We just
dump them here so the man
with the tractor,
who already saw us, finds them!
Let's go!
Come on.
- Come on!
- Don't do that. You're going to flood it.
I'm not going to flood it!
Can't you stay positive?
Come on,
come on. Start this time.
- Come on!
- See? You flooded it. I told you.
I didn't flood it!
It's going to start!
And when it does,
we're going to your house.
No! Not my house! I can't take
that risk! What are you thinking?
Ok, shut up! Listen to me, José.
After we finish doing this,
we won't see each other never again.
And we will never ever talk
about this again. Understood?
Understood?
What? I can talk now?
I thought I had to raise my
hand to talk. Yes, I understood.
This is it. Come on.
- Come on!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
Come on,
let's go! Thanks for saving me, nan.
- So? Let's go!
- Easy, we have to warm it up.
Shit!
- Do I tie them up or what?
- Yes, of course! Hurry!
Ok, bro, but let's go! Drive!
Walter?
Yes.
Are you coming out?
I'm coming.
I have to tell you something really
funny that happened at school.
We had a teachers'
meeting last Thursday
because we had to
talk about certain things.
But, this time, we talked about
the photos for the school yearbook.
Last year,
we decided to allow senior students
to have the photo taken by any photographer
they wanted, they could hire anybody
so they are not forced to
hire the school photographer
who has been working
during 20 years...
So, all of the senior girls
went to a huge and elegant
place to have their photos taken
and they were all dressed
up and with a hairstyle...
So, Sandra,
the principal... You know Sandra, right?
Right,
she had to check all those photos
and she ended turning
down almost all of them.
Guess why.
Because of the cleavage.
- Do you want more bread?
- No, thanks, mom.
The thing is that even
the small-busted girls,
and we know them,
had a big cleavage showing.
Apparently,
there is some new brassiere for that,
but I don't know how it works.
Haven't you heard about it?
It's the Wonderbra.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's a new bra with
some push up action.
We are calling you
because we want to know if you are
interested in our long distance rates.
I get it.
We would like you to answer
this call as soon as possible.
- Yes, this is Walter Blanco.
- Bro--
You told me not to worry
because he was almost dead.
You know what?
He is as alive as you.
Sir,
I'm having breakfast with my family
and I can't talk right now because
I'm spending sacred time with them.
So please erase my
name from your database
because I'm not interested
in the service. Thank you.
Don't get nervous,
teacher! Don't get nervous, bro!
I can hear that man
groaning from here.
When will your Highness come?
I need you here to
solve this problem!
Calm down! I'll be
there after school.
After school?
You are insane! That's
too late. Come here now!
Call in sick, say you had an accident,
but come here now!
Mr., again,
I'm not interested in that service, thanks.
And please, don't call again.
But--
You can't believe these people.
They don't give up.
- Bye, love.
- Bye.
What's up? This is my house.
This is Jose's place.
Leave it at the tone.
Chiral.
The term derives from
the Greek word "hand".
And it means that your left hand
and your right hand
mirror each other.
One in front of the other.
Identical, but opposite.
Same thing happens with
two organic compounds
that are identical,
but opposite at the molecular level.
Although they are identical,
they don't always behave the same.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Some good example
is Thalidomide.
The right-handed isomer of
this drug is a good medicine
for pregnant women to
avoid morning sickness.
But if you give a pregnant woman
the left-handed isomer of the drug,
the baby could be born
with physical defects.
This is what
happened in the 1950's.
There exists some
investigation you could watch...
Well, so, let's say it again. Chiral,
mirroring.
Active, inactive, good, bad.
Sir,
is this going to be on the murder?
What?
Is this going to be on
the mid-term exam?
Chirality? No. I don't know.
You have to study it
anyway. And remember:
Knowledge is power.
Have a good day.
No, shit.
No, no, no.
Shit.
No, no, no!
What is he doing here? Shit!
Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Is he ok? Do you need some help?
He's my nephew,
he has some drug problems.
I need to take
him to the hospital.
What do we do?
The one in the RV is...?
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
Totally?
Yes,
bro! You can go and see it for yourself.
That's not a bad idea.
We should go see him to make sure
he doesn't rise and walk like Lazarus
on the neighborhood.
So what,
bro? This is all my fault?
You know what,
teacher? I've been through a lot.
So take it easy because
I'm getting sick of it.
All this shit is your fault.
Ok, stop it!
We need to move forward.
Tell me something
about this guy. Anything.
I don't know.
What do you mean?
Don't you know his name?
"Loco". They call him "Loco".
What kind of name is that?
They call him Loco! What
do you want me to do?
How long have you
been working with him?
- I worked with his cousin.
- Who is his cousin?
Was.
Emilio, the guy out in the RV.
Emilio worked with Loco.
Loco was one level higher.
He was the one that sold the
product to the big ones, you get it?
He was like... Like...
He was like those people that sell
the products to the supermarkets.
- A distributor?
- Right.
Loco is a distributor?
Is he dangerous?
Dangerous.
Well, let's see...
He tried to kill us yesterday,
so yes, he's dangerous.
I'm trying to say that
he is a businessman
and maybe he could act
out of mutual self-interest.
What?
Maybe he can listen to reason.
Maybe he does,
teacher. Go and ask him.
"Dear Loco, if we let you go,
do you promise not to come
back and cut us to pieces?"
I don't think he listens
that kind of reason.
I mean, he's Loco.
What was that?
The guy is awake, bro.
Marijuana?
"What I would do".
"I would do the Kardashians".
"Kardashians".
"I left school and
joined Los Monar--"
Los Monarcas?
No, be careful. Listen.
If I were him,
I would lie there faking being almost dead.
And I would wait for the
right moment to attack.
- You get it?
- So what do we do?
What are you doing? Jose,
where are you going? Jose!
- So what?
- Enough.
Can you stop making
the same question?
- You have to do something.
- We.
We have to do something,
and I'm opened to suggestions.
- No, bro, this is your fault.
- Don't blame me!
You brought those guys here!
Yes, of course.
And I came to you
begging to cook meth.
"Come on, teacher, please".
I want you to listen me carefully
and understand it once and for all.
I prefer to cook with my granny in a
wheelchair before cooking with you.
Teacher.
- And the phosphate gas?
- Phosphine gas.
- Same shit.
- They are not the same.
What about that?
I don't know. Can't
that gas still kill him?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean?
You're supposed to be the scientist,
bro!
Look,
that isn't the worst problem now.
In case you don't remember,
we have a body in the RV.
And that's like leaving
chicken under the sun.
We have to do something! And fast,
before somebody finds it!
I've been thinking.
I think our best option is
chemical disincorporation.
- What?
- We have to dissolve it in strong acid.
You are joking, right?
And who's going to do that?
- We'll do it together.
- No, bro.
I'm not good with dead bodies.
When I was a little kid,
I had a dog named Valentino.
And somebody killed it.
I was so traumatized that I
still dream about Valentino.
Enough!
We are in this fifty-fifty,
right?
I think it is fair
to do it together.
One of us deals with the body and the other
one deals with the guy in the basement.
And who decides the tasks? You do,
I guess.
We can flip a coin.
Do you have one?
No.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Right, I'll do the acid thing.
No! Rock-paper-scissors.
One, two, three,
rock, paper, scissors.
- I won! I'll do the acid thing.
- No. Two out of three.
Yeah, right.
What's up? This is my house.
This is Jose's place.
Leave it at the tone.
Teacher, pick up the phone.
It's me. I have a question
about the container, bro.
- What's up?
- What kind of plastic, bro?
Polyethylene.
And how the hell am I
supposed to know that?
Jose,
I told you. The container must have a
stamp at the bottom
that reads "L - D - P - E".
L - D - P - E.
No, not this one.
Right, got it.
But this doesn't seem to be very resistant,
man.
Any acid is going to
eat right through this.
- Not hydrofluoric acid.
- Why not?
You didn't pay attention
to any of my classes, right?
You know what? Thanks for the conversation,
it was pretty instructive.
And friendly.
Listen.
Let's talk about
the important issue.
Have you already done your part?
I'm getting prepared for it.
Bro, think about this: if we
take him to the hospital right now,
I bet they won't be
able to save him.
I don't even think
that they take him in
because he doesn't
have any health insurance.
So, basically...
You are doing him a favor,
right?
Who's there?
What are you doing with me?
Hey! Give me some
water! I'm thirsty.
You don't like the crust?
Where is Emilio?
Is he dead?
Answer me! Yes or no?
I'm a coward.
Where are you, Walter?
Very good, are you smoking weed?
Perfect, bro!
Walter, are you smoking my weed?
Yeah,
that's ok. Make yourself at home.
Take it easy, man.
- What did you buy?
- Nothing.
There wasn't any
container big enough.
Not big enough for a body.
You could have bought two.
Legs in one, torso in the other.
Do you think that's
funny? Do you?
Your head is messed up, bro.
So what? Have
you done it already?
You didn't do it?
Not yet.
What are you talking about?
I have to leave now.
Where are you going?
Listen, listen, listen.
I promise I'll do it
tomorrow. Ok? But now--
I have a doctor's appointment.
- A doctor's appointment?
- Yes.
- We have a deal.
- José...
Don't go to the basement.
The guy is awake.
- He's awake? But--
- He's awake.
What did we play
rock-paper-scissors for?
Walter,
rock-paper-scissors! That's sacred, man!
Shit!
Everything's fine?
Everything's really fine.
Look at its face. Hi, baby!
Smile!
Do you want to know?
- Yes.
It's a girl.
You remember this when she
is 15 and starts going to parties.
Let me check the blood sugar,
I'll be right back.
But don't worry,
everything's really fine.
Thank you.
Walter, who's José Miguel Rosas?
- Who?
- Don't play with me.
The guy that
called this morning.
He has a blog about music and it
says he studied at Los Monarcas.
Was he a student of yours?
Yes. He's nobody.
So, why is he looking for you?
Why does he call you?
Walter...
You came home at
two in the morning
and you didn't tell me
where you have been.
You spent the rest of
the night in the bathroom.
Can you please tell
me what's going on?
What do you have to
do with some junkie?
Nothing. He's a dealer.
What kind of dealer?
Marijuana. He
sells me marijuana.
What?
Not a lot, sometimes.
Walter, do you think you're 14?
For God's sake, your brother-in-law
is an anti-narcotics agent.
I want you to do me a favor.
This is a very special favor.
Could you stop breathing
down my neck all the time?
Please, darling. Seriously,
at least for this time. Just once.
Could you leave me alone?
Could you just give me a break?
Darling...
I would really appreciate it.
Just meat.
Just meat, José Miguel,
that's just meat.
Just meat, just meat, just meat.
Just meat.
Just meat, just meat.
Yes, this is the place.
- Can you wait for me?
- Yes.
[coughing and
groaning from fatigue]
Hello. José Miguel?
I'm talking to you.
This is private property!
What are you doing here?
- Relax, I want to say--
- No, no, I'm not interested.
Don't you touch me!
Please,
get out of here. Not touching.
Whatever you are selling,
I'm not interested.
Please, leave.
No. I'm here because the secretary
in Los Monarcas is a friend of mine.
She gave me your address.
Who are you?
I'm Cielo Blanco,
Walter Blanco's wife.
And he told me everything.
- Really?
- Yes.
I want you to know that my
brother-in-law is an anti-narcotics agent.
And I won't
hesitate to call him.
This is the one and only warning
I will give you. Understood?
Stop selling marijuana
to my husband.
Ok, right.
Ok, do me a favor and get
out of my property. Please.
- I will.
- Ok, everything's fine.
And I'm giving you some advice.
Be a musician,
because drugs won't take you anywhere.
Ok, thanks. Leave.
No, no, no. Please.
Shit!
Yeah! Why don't we do...
this shit at home
so I can sleep like
a baby at night?
Moreover, teacher,
why don't you send
your psycho wife in
so she can threaten
me in my own house?
That would be really cool.
That would be really amusing,
bro.
And why don't we talk about the
psycho you have in my basement?
Yes!
Let him live there, bro.
And don't forget to feed
him three times a day.
Teacher, you know what?
I want to thank you for
this amazing opportunity.
This is really amazing.
The truth is that...
I...
I have always wanted
to melt somebody in acid.
I have always wanted--
José.
So you have a brother who
is an anti-narcotics agent?
- What?
- You heard me.
Brother-in-law.
Well, that's better.
- How do you know that?
- Your wife told me.
- My wife?
- Yes, your wife.
She was here, out there. She
almost caught me moving Emilio, bro.
I see you are the one wearing
the pants in the relationship.
And why the hell did you tell
her that I'm selling you weed?
I don't know. Maybe
because that's better
than telling her that
I'm cooking crystal meth
and I killed some guy.
And you have another one pending,
don't forget about that.
Keep smoking that shit.
Yes,
I smoked a bowl. What is the problem?
You can come here
and smoke my weed,
but I can't smoke
a bowl of meth?
No,
man. This is my house and I set the rules.
I do whatever I want to do.
And change that expression,
don't look me like that.
When are you
going to do your part?
I have the worst job to do!
The worst job? Do you want
to know about the worst job?
Try dragging 150 pounds
of rotten meat up the stairs.
I barely got him in
the bathtub. Barely!
Bathtub?
Yes,
the bathtub. And that's another thing.
Why do you make me go to every
store in town to buy a plastic container
when here I have a bathtub
that is perfect
for what we need?
You idiot!
What are you doing?
What were you asking me?
Yes, you asked me why I sent you
to buy that plastic container. Right?
Well, the hydrofluoric acid
doesn't eat through plastic.
However,
it will dissolve any other element.
Metal, glass, wood,
ceramic...
That's why I asked
you to buy polyethylene.
I run faster than you!
What is that?
Mom, look what I found!
- What is it?
- I think it's a mask.