Walter.
Yo, I wanted to tell you
that I liked your idea in there.
I think it's pretty much
how things should be done.
Thanks.
Dude, wait.
I remember you told me
it was your birthday.
So I...
Here.
The slip's inside
if you want to change it
for other you like more.
Happy birthday, bro.
Hi.
I was at Henry and María's,
visiting the kids.
I talked to Junior
for quite a while.
And he's fine, he...
He's continuously asking
what happens
'cause he can't quite get it.
He is obsessed with knowing
but he's fine.
How about you?
How are you?
Big money is coming in
in a couple of days.
Are we okay with that?
Let's go to bed.
Good night.
I wanna show you something.
Look.
Do you like it?
It's peculiar,
but it has something to it.
Above all, what it has
is that it's a birthday present.
And the person who gave it to me
not long ago,
wanted to kill me.
It's true.
Not many days ago
he had a gun
pointed at me here
and he was this close
to pulling the trigger.
And I don't know why he didn't.
But, suddenly, as if by magic
he changed his mind.
And he doesn't hate me anymore.
Now he has
a very different opinion
about me.
Weird, right?
And just now when I was
on my way there
I thought maybe you'll feel
exactly the same.
I don't know why
but I feel that soon
you'll have
another opinion of me.
You'll think different of me.
See you later.
My baby.
Sorry, sir.
Reporting a missing child.
Hey.
- That is a real surprise,
Walter!
- What's up, buddy?
- How are you?
- Fine. Very good.
All right.
Listen, I'm sorry to drop
in on you out of the blue.
No, never mind, man.
- You sure?
- Sure.
Aren't you too busy?
If you have things to do,
we can take a rain check.
No, no.
I'm just settling
into the new digs
here.
But it's cool, isn't it?
It's very spacious
and you have a hell of a view.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, it's cool.
At least, it's better
than the boxes we have, right?
What will I do
with the proletariat here?
Henry.
I want to congratulate you
on this appointment.
Very good.
- No, Walter.
- Yes, yes.
Well, thanks.
Thank you.
Although I must confess
I need to be out there.
That thing
of chasing dirt-balls
is like an addiction,
brother.
Of course, being a
boss
also has its appeal,
right?
Yes, sure.
- See you later, boss.
- Bye.
Gómez, thanks.
- Bye, Walter. Good day.
- Later.
Hey. Whoa.
Look at that.
No way!
Is that new?
- Yes, it is.
- Really?
Yes, I mean, it's...
That's beautiful.
So classy.
Was it a birthday
present?
Yeah. Well, I mean,
not-- not really.
I bought it for myself.
Look at
you.
New car, new
watch.
You're treating yourself.
What?
Am I acting like a gangster now?
No, no, no,
you know what that is?
Boosting one's
self-esteem.
With all the curve balls
that were thrown at you
this year, brother,
you deserve it.
- Hell yeah, right?
- Sure!
As long as you
got the money
to spend, that is.
- Yes or no?
- Yes.
Come on, sit down.
- Thanks.
- How's it going?
Fine, everything in order.
So how's Cielo?
Um...
I think she's getting better,
you know?
She went
to the car wash this morning.
She said
she needed to, you know
keep her mind occupied, and--
That's good.
Great.
- Yeah, she went back to work.
- That's good, yeah.
I mean,
as long as you're all
right
with her being on her
own and--
No, no, in fact
I'm right there with her
most of the time.
And the guys there
keep an eye on her when I'm not.
Good. That's
good.
Yes, right.
And what about
the whole idea of seeing
a professional,
a psychologist
or one of those
shrinks?
Remember I told you
María was happy
with the one she's
seeing?
Says they come in
like zombies, brother
and come out like larks,
you know what I'm saying?
Actually,
she already found someone.
A Pedro or something...
Pedro...
I don't know why I'm drawing
a blank on his last name.
He's an expert.
He's supposed to be top notch.
You must've heard of him.
Well, the thing is--
I'm glad you're on it.
That's not something
you wanna let fester.
No. No, way.
You can't risk it.
Henry, um...
I really just wanted
to thank you
for having
Valentina and Junior
at your house
for watching them--
There's nothing to
thank, buddy.
Yes, there is.
We're glad to have
them home.
No, but it's a burden
and you have your own problems.
No burden at all!
Those kids are so
sweet.
We love them, buddy.
Thanks.
I'd like to come and see them.
Tonight's all right?
What do you mean?
You are asking
for my permission
to go see your own
kids?
Are you nuts or what?
You go tonight
and we'll have
a scotch together, okay?
Thanks.
Unbelievable.
Walter.
Something else
on your mind there?
Remember
what I told you, right?
Whatever I need,
I'm here.
If you need to talk,
if you're in trouble
I'm here,
all right?
I think Cielo
doesn't love me anymore.
And I don't know what to do.
She says
that I'm a bad influence
on the kids and--
How can she say so?
That I'm not good
for them--
She thinks I'm a bad father.
You're a bad--?
No, no, no, that--
Being a bad father
is one thing
Having marital problems
is a different story.
Every couple has
problems.
It's like, um...
I mean, I...
I'm not
an expert on parenting
and you know it,
but if you ask me
from where
I'm sitting, brother
I think you're great
with the kids.
You're a provider,
aren't you?
You provide them
with food and a home.
You're no drunkard.
You're not--
You're at their beck and call.
There's no doubt
you love them.
- Yes.
- And you know--
You know
what?
The guts you showed
going toe-to-toe
with cancer
the way you got over
that illness, buddy
that's an example
to your kids.
That's an inspiration to me,
you know?
Really.
I've made mistakes, Henry.
Everybody makes
mistakes!
That's life, brother.
- Want something to drink?
- Okay.
Yeah? You want a coffee?
Yeah. Okay.
- I'll order it.
- No, no, no!
Henry, please.
Buddy, I don't want them
to see me like this.
Relax, I'll go
for it.
How do you like it?
- With...?
- Two of sugar.
Two of sugar.
Relax, buddy.
Just take a moment,
think about it
and get it together.
I'll be right back.
- I'm sorry, brother.
- Feel at home.
And there's no need
to be sorry.
No way!
I'll be right back, okay?
Thanks.
Walter.
Here's your
coffee.
You two
are really great together.
Congratulations.
Take it from me.
Remember, buddy
it's always darkest
just before the dawn.
I really appreciate
your help, buddy.
Mario, what are you doing?
I can't be here.
- Keep still!
- Let go of me!
Why did you bring me here?
I've got to get my daughter
from school!
What am I doing here?
What is this place?
- Shut up!
- Why are we here?
- Sit down.
- Let me go!
- I can't be here!
- Sit down, damn it!
Let me go, I don't see
why I have to be here.
Why did you bring me here?
I don't have to be here!
Sit the fuck down!
Give me your phone.
Let's get to the point.
Here's your script.
You have about 30 seconds to--
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna dial
the Anti-narcotics
chief
Henry Navarro
and you're gonna pass
along
this information.
Listen to me, Lidia.
If you yell for help
I am gonna pull out
my pistol
and shoot you in the head.
And the same goes
for panicking
or breaking down into
tears.
Look at me,
not at them.
If you make Navarro
suspicious in any way
what's gonna happen
next?
You'll shoot me.
Where?
- In the head.
- With what?
With your gun.
It's a pistol actually,
not a gun.
All
right.
Computer's set?
Yeah, it's all set.
Anti-narcotics.
Hi, I'm Lidia Barrera.
I need to talk
to agent Henry Navarro
please.
Tell him it's regarding
Madrigal Electromotive.
Hold the line, please.
I'll put you through.
Mrs. Lidia, how are you?
How can I help you?
Mr. Navarro, how are you doing?
I just wanted
to report something.
I was in our warehouse
supervising
a shipment of methylamine
when I noticed a device
on one of our barrels.
What kind of device?
It looks like some kind
of a tracking device.
So I was just wondering
if maybe your people
put it there
when they were here.
You very well know
that Madrigal's willing to help
with the investigation
we don't want to interfere.
Maybe you could
give me some guidance?
Well, I'll tell you
what we're gonna do.
Set that barrel aside for me
and I'll look into it
and get back to you.
And in the meantime,
mum's the word, all right?
Yeah, thank you.
Okay, thanks for the call.
Gómez.
What is
it?
Hey, you don't know anything
about GPS trackers
on a Madrigal barrel, do you?
No. Nobody from my team
planted anything.
Why?
I don't know.
I figured as much.
Thanks.
No, I know nothing,
but I didn't do it!
I didn't plant that thing!
Believe me!
It wasn't me!
I didn't do it, Mario!
I'm not so stupid!
Mario! Let me go!
Mario!
Shut up!
Like I told you.
That old hag
wanted to make fun of us.
So now what?
We're fucked up.
We can't get close
to the warehouse.
His look-in authorization
is gonna be due
in around twelve hours.
We'll use Lidia's security code
to gain access
and we take every barrel
we can get our hands on.
Well, what about her?
You two drive the barrels
back tonight.
I'll deal with her.
No! No, no, no.
Please!
This was not me!
I didn't put no GPS!
You've got to believe me.
Mario, you know me,
I'm not so stupid.
Yo, honestly, I believe her.
It sounds like
she's telling the truth to me.
Kid, you still have learn
a lot about women, trust me.
I'm sorry, Jose.
No, no, please!
Mario, you can't do this!
I swear I didn't do anything!
I put no GPS on that barrel!
Don't hurt me!
Giraldo, come here,
tell me something.
Tell me you guys
weren't so lame-brained
to put a GPS tracker
on a barrel in Madrigal.
Yes, sir, it was us.
But, man, tell me
whatever made you put
that thing
on the outside of a barrel?
We didn't have time
to go in
with hazard suits,
sir.
But how many barrels you tag?
All of
them.
That's why
we ran out of time, sir.
Okay, buddy. Okay.
Never mind.
Next time,
a little communication,
all right?
Yes, sir.
I mean it.
We've got to work on
that.
It won't happen again, sir.
Okay. You may go.
I told you, it wasn't me.
We can't touch
any of those barrels.
As regards her, it's the same.
You can't keep
with the idea of killing me.
Don't be idiot. I saved you!
If I hadn't spotted
the tracker on the barrel
we'd all be in jail right now!
She's right.
She'll turn a badge on us
the first chance she gets,
trust me.
Once, the woman
put a hit out on me.
Seriously?
You still need methylamine
and I can help you.
But you've got to promise
your partner
will stop threatening me.
Let's talk.
About
what?
All of those
barrels
are already marked.
Who said anything
about barrels?
I'm talking about
an ocean of methylamine.
Leave me alone with her.
Mario.
Let's go.
The man knows what he's doing.
Asshole.
So, let's
hear it.
What do you
have to say?
Not without a guarantee
that I won't be killed anyway.
You have my word.
Not good enough.
I need a guarantee.
There's no guarantee
here.
You'll have to trust,
like the rest of us did.
Is it true
that you put a hit
out on Mario?
I was scared
about what they
could say,
he and those men
he has in custody.
They're nine of them.
They know everything
about me.
Probably about you too.
Assuming
you're the master chemist
they're always talking about.
How much methylamine
are we talking about,
literally?
Then we'll discuss
my commission.
No shit!
First things first.
Methylamine tankers usually
go through this road,
the main one.
But now it's blocked
because of a strike.
Those poor people usually do.
The miners
or the coffee growers.
Now we're using
this secondary road.
This is
a particularly secluded area.
That's where you do it.
Where we do what?
What do you mean, exactly?
Get your product.
"Get your product" meaning what?
Robbing the methylamine?
You said so.
You do what you have to.
I only tell you where it is.
How many in the crew?
Just the conductors.
We'll have to
kill them.
Fuck, yo.
Why do we always
have to kill people?
Calm down, Mario.
I have done this
long enough to know
there are
two kinds of heists.
Those where the guys
get away with it
and those that leave
witnesses.
Come on,
Say "anti-narcotics."
Honey, don't teach her that.
She'd better learn to
say
"aunt María."
But she just said
"an-ti-nar-co-tics."
Yeah, sure,
I'm sure she did.
Then take her
to work with you.
You wanna go?
Catch crooks out there?
Yes? You do?
Hey, what about Junior?
He's all depressed
and melancholic?
Yeah, poor
thing.
He feels
his parents
treat him
like he's a baby there.
No wonder.
They treat Valentina
much better than the poor kid.
- Shut up.
- No, really.
Shut it, honey!
Junior, sweetie,
do you want me
to fix you a sandwich
or you prefer
to order some pizza?
- No, thanks, auntie.
- You sure?
Kid, come here.
Come and sit here with us.
Let's have a chat.
What is it?
Wanna watch a movie?
No. And you
can keep talking about me now.
Sweetie.
Junior.
I think we should focus
on the local market.
Work with customers from Bogotá
and go one step at a time.
You mean switch back
to a pseudo cook.
It's a backward step.
It's going back.
You're the chemist.
Admit it.
It's gonna cut down
on our output.
Changing
the production system
means losing
what we invested
in our new lab equipment.
And making less money
is better than making nothing.
Yeah?
Excuse me
but why don't you tell us why?
Why is making nothing
not an option?
Because, considering
the risk we're taking
I'd rather stay put
and do nothing.
Here you go again.
I know where you're going.
So let's go there.
It's because
of your nine guys in lockup?
Whose silence we have to buy?
You broke it, you pay for it!
And we've talked about this
plenty already.
We better talk about it
a little more.
Because what it sounds
like you're telling me
is that, from now on
we have no choice
but to do this pseudo cook
and give
whichever profit we make
to your
guys.
What's next then?
Say it.
We embark
on that risky operation
suggested
by the least reliable woman
in the world?
We kill
a bunch of innocent people
only to follow your scheme?
Let's call a spade a spade.
It's your plan better
than mine?
And yours is better than mine?
Okay, stop it!
What if we
can rip off that train
and no one ever knows
it got robbed?
This may be it.
This might be the place.
Trucks will come
from that direction.
I checked it out
and there are no farms
or businesses.
I think we can fake the accident
here on this crossroads.
Yes.
Shall we measure it?
Twenty, ten feet.
Here's the first tanker.
Each tanker
- is sixty feet.
- Gotcha.
I like these slopes.
There'll be no escape route
for the tankers.
Around here it'll be
the end of the first tanker.
Okay.
Distance...
Here's the next one.
Fifty, fifty-two
fifty-six, sixty.
Exactly here it's the end
of the second tanker.
- Sounds fine, right?
- Yes.
- Okay, let's do it here.
- This is the place.
There you go, perfect.
Keep straight, straight.
- Slightly to the right!
- To the right!
- There!
- This way, this way!
- That way, that way!
Right there! Let go!
- Right there! Let go!
- That's perfect!
- How does it look like?
Good.
All right, Peto,
open it up!
Come one, Peto, move it!
You're very slow.
Listen to me:
the day of the operation
I need that hose down
in fifteen seconds.
Will you be able to do it?
Yes, sir, of course.
- You sure?
- Yes, sir.
- Boss, can I ask you something?
- Go ahead.
I get why we want
the tank for the methylamine.
But why
this other one
for the water?
Jose, it's your idea.
You wanna fill him in?
All right.
It's very simple.
We're stealing the methylamine
from the tankers
but they can't leave empty.
If on their way
they run into a weigh bridge
the train company's gonna know
it got robbed.
So while we steal
the methylamine
we fill the tankers with water
so the guys won't realize
until they reach base.
Anyway, they'll know
we robbed them
'cause they'll get water
instead of methylamine.
No, that's the point.
They won't get water,
but watered-down methylamine
which is a different thing.
So the guys from Madrigal
will think
it was the providers
who ripped them off.
Shit happens.
I've heard stories like
that.
They buy some machinery
and what they get
it's a lot of
stones.
- That's right.
- Exactly.
That's why it's important
to keep it a secret.
Some guys who work for us
don't know
all these details.
So mum's the word, okay?
- Yeah, sure.
- Hey! "Yes, sir."
Yes, sir.
So kid, show me you have guts.
We have to change the weight
with nobody noticing it
- and very quickly.
- Understood.
Jose, we have to be
very accurate.
Methylamine
is lighter than water
so we'll have to replace
just nine-tenths of it.
And check out the hose nozzles
'cause there'll be some spillage
we'll have to account for.
I'll be paying attention
to that.
Damn, you guys
thought of everything.
That's how we work.
Junior, open the door.
Dear, please.
Just come out and talk to me.
I'm staying!
That's all I have to say!
What's going on?
You got what you wanted.
Congratulations.
Junior, open up.
Come on, Junior.
I'm not gonna ask twice.
- What?
- You know what.
In fact, I have no idea
of what's happening.
But you do know
what you have to do.
Are you kicking me out
of my own house?
- No, Junior.
- You seriously doing that?
Whatever makes you
think that?
Junior, we love you.
And this is your house
as much as it is ours.
But I talked to you
and explained
your mom and I
need some time alone.
- You didn't.
- Yes, I did!
- You haven't explained shit.
- Junior.
Why can't I stay here?
This is not gonna be a debate
nor a negotiation.
Dad, explain to me.
I want one good reason--
Because we're your parents,
damn it!
And we're asking you to!
That's reason enough right now!
Now, come on!
To your uncle's house!
He's hopping mad,
but I'm sure
it'll pass soon.
So don't worry.
Walter.
Stop trying to play peacemaker
with me.
I won't change my mind
about you.
I don't accept
that.
You're my wife.
No.
I'm not your wife anymore.
I'm your hostage.
But since you insist
on keeping me imprisoned
I'll make you a deal.
I will launder your money
I'll keep your secrets
but the kids will stay
at Henry and María's
where they have a chance
of being safe.
Think you've seen
too many movies.
I don't know how else
to explain it to you.
Our children are not in danger.
Walter, a couple of days ago,
you told me
that a man
held a gun to your head.
You said it with pride.
So there's nothing you can say
that'll make me change my mind.
I know there'll come a day
that somebody
will knock on that door
looking to harm you
or me or all of us.
And when that day comes
the children cannot be here.
You agree to that.
Agree
and I promise I will be
whatever kind of partner
you want me to be.
Okay.
By the way
you're seeing
a therapist.
Name, Pedro.
Last name, up to you.
And where were you?
Out burying bodies?
No, organizing
a truck robbery.
Yeah?
I've got the data we need.
Write this down.
Come on, forward!
Go on, go on!
There!
Fernando, take the bike.
Around sixteen
feet ahead.
Around there!
Leave it there!
And now lie down
with your head that way
towards the back!
That's it!
There
you go!
All right, you ready?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Mario!
Ready?
All clear!
Ready!
Jose, Peto,
you ready?
There they come! Hide!
The trucks are coming!
Places, everyone! Go!
Stop, please! Stop!
Stop, stop!
What happened?
A guy on a bike got in my way
and I ran straight into him.
- Please, help me!
- What do you mean?
Let me see.
- He was thrown up to there?
- Yeah, I hit him bad.
Joaco, come here, move!
Help me out here.
What is it?
Buddy, help me, please.
What happened?
A ran into a guy on a bike.
- You killed him?
- No.
Okay, relax, buddy.
How you feeling?
Let's go!
Guys, let's go!
- It's okay, dude.
Calm down.
How are you feeling?
I ache all over.
How are things going there?
Good.
I ache all over!
Okay, let's pick him up.
No, no way!
He must have internal bleeding.
Murderer!
Why don't we take him
to a hospital?
I already called an ambulance.
- We'll have to wait.
- Wait?
You heard him?
The trucks are there.
We can use one of them.
My car's blocking the way.
Then move it,
remove it from there.
- It won't start.
- What's the problem?
I don't know.
It just won't start.
How's everything there?
We're connected already.
We're gonna start emptying.
This guy
did you give him anything?
- Give him water.
- I have some.
No, wait, don't worry.
I'll get it.
Let's pick him
up.
Come on, I'll help you.
There you go.
Let's pick him up,
dude.
There you go.
No, buddy, he's in bad shape.
You hurt him, bro.
No, no.
Move a little, come
on.
I can't, I can't.
What's with the water, dude?
Coming, coming!
Hurry up!
Give me a status.
Good. We're at 500 gallons
and counting.
Water is going in now.
Jose!
Emptying starting.
Come on, come on!
Calm down, brother.
I've got kids. Help me!
Yes, I know.
Calm down.
I'm good at mechanics.
Let's wait
for the ambulance.
I'll remove the truck.
Come on,
let's go.
Don't leave me alone!
He knows, he'll help you.
I'll show you
where's the problem.
Lift it up, lift it.
It's there, right there.
Go to the other side,
come on.
Yes, go to the other side.
You can check there first, okay.
Right on!
Hold him, hold him.
All
right.
Okay, it worked.
See? I told you.
A jeep's coming
from the other way.
Buddy, a jeep's coming.
We're not done yet.
Sir, please, we need help.
This guy's hurt,
we need to take him
to a hospital.
There's no
chance.
If they get
the victim
into the jeep
the tankers' drivers
will go back to their positions.
I need more time!
He can take the victim!
Come here, buddy.
He's arguing
with the driver
about what to do.
They're getting
the victim
into the jeep.
Then let them take him!
If they take him,
our whole plan fails.
When they reach
the hospital
and see he's not wounded
they'll call Highway Police
and report the accident.
That's why we have
an ambulance.
Then send the ambulance in!
You're in bad shape, buddy.
Cooperate a little.
Come on, get up.
Guys, wait a minute!
It's best
if the doctors
move him.
Yes, you may hurt me worse.
No, he's gonna bleed to death.
No, no.
Wait, look at his leg.
Look how it is.
He'll die on us.
Wait,
we can't move him.
The ambulance's here!
Everybody calm down!
The ambulance's here.
Don't worry, brother.
You'll have to be patient.
He almost
didn't make it.
Look at this man's leg.
I'm not sure
if it's safe to move him.
So we let him bleed to death?
Does he have
health insurance?
I don't.
I can't take him then.
But that's inhuman.
Wait a minute.
With or without insurance
we'll take him.
But I may get into trouble.
What?
I'm gonna get this on video.
If you let this guy die
your face will be
all over the news.
- Come on.
- Come on, do it.
- Whose car is that?
- Me.
- Can you move it?
- Sure, dude.
Let's go get a stretcher.
Can we be of any help?
We'll bring a stretcher.
They're getting
the victim
into the ambulance.
We have to beat a retreat.
We're not done yet.
I need more time.
We're out of time.
- We're almost there!
- No, there's no more time.
Thank God we could help
the guy from the bike.
But now we'll have
to remove that truck
so that we can go through.
It's not gonna be easy
'cause it won't start.
No, the guy with the jeep
can pull your truck
so that we move it
and unblock the way.
Right, we can give it
a shot with a winch.
- You sure?
- That's the point, yes.
Come on, dude.
It's so heavy!
It's overloaded.
It has a soul of its own!
- Let's do it.
- You've got leeway.
- I'll tell you.
- There you go.
They're heading
to the truck.
It seems
they're gonna tow it.
Go, go.
Go, go, pull, pull.
Now backwards,
backwards.
Hold it!
Hold it steady!
Walter, they already
moved the truck.
We've got to flee.
We're near
the nine thousand gallons.
No, now!
Come on, come on.
Okay, buddy.
I think we're all set here.
Thank you very much
for all your help.
Hope that guy gets well soon.
See you.
Sir, can I help you
with anything else?
You need a ride
somewhere?
No, I'll stay here.
I called Highway Police
so I'll wait for them.
Thanks, anyway.
Good luck.
Get off now!
No! One more second!
Walter, now!
Jose, that's it, get off!
Get off!
- Yes.
- Now!
- Hell, yeah!
- We did it!
- Son of a bitch!
- Well done!
- Bravo!
- Very good, Peto!
Well done, Peto.
Fuck!
You almost didn't jump!
Let's flood this town
with meth, goddam it!
Peto, what are you doing? No!