How's it coming?
Very, very well.
- It's a flurry of deliveries.
- Yes, sir.
Feels like Christmas morning.
Don Gustavo...
this is very exciting.
I'm glad.
And if you have any questions
about the price that we pay,
which is understandable,
I guarantee you that what we
have here is the best.
Great quality.
I want you to have
what you need.
I do.
I doff my proverbial cap to you,
sir.
When do you think
we'll be up and running?
Within a month, I'd say.
Two weeks.
Yeah, two weeks.
Perfect.
By the way,
that sample
you asked me to run,
I ran it, and it is quite good.
Thank you very much, Guido.
You can give that to Victor...
to discard.
Is that our competition?
I'm sorry?
It really is quite good.
The purity...
I'm speaking, of course,
strictly in chemical terms.
And I can't, as of yet,
account for the blue color.
You don't have
any competition,
not as far as I'm concerned.
After all,
how pure can pure be?
Of course, I told you
I can guarantee you
a purity of 96 per cent.
It's a hard-earned
figure, 96.
Fine by me.
However,
this other product
is higher than that.
It's 99, maybe even
a touch beyond that.
I'd need an instrument
called a gas chromatograph...
and, and...
What I mean, Don Gustavo,
is that last 3 per cent, it may
not sound like a lot,
but it is, it's tremendous.
Who ever did that
is way ahead of us,
ahead of the gringos
and the Mexicans,
the one who synthesized it.
For our purposes,
96 per cent will do just fine.
Please, don't let this
trouble you.
Yeah. It's just
being a chemist
I'd love to know
who synthesized it, is all.
It's just professional
curiosity.
A man who wants
to work with me.
A trained chemist,
like yourself.
But I don't consider him
a professional.
With all due respect,
Don Gustavo,
if the person who did that
is not a professional
I don't know what that makes me.
There are other considerations.
His is the best I've
ever seen,
hands down.
Truely. He's a genius.
No, please, don't.
Please, don't.
Yes, sir. Carrera 20
number 25-12.
I just heard the one shot.
Just the one single
like a backfire.
No, the neighbours
didn't hear anything either.
We talked
and no one heard fighting
or anything like that.
Yes, sir.
He's dead.
Thank you,
we are waiting for you.
Sorry, did you know him?
You don't want
to touch anything.
Police are on their way.
What the hell happened?
What did you do?
Drive.
What the hell happened?
Look at me. What the hell
happened?
He's gone.
Shit!
You do a sweep?
I couldn't. People there.
People? You got yourself seen
by these people?
So what?
Just another looky-loo.
I guess I'd better
get this over with.
- Hey.
- Geez, I woke you up.
I should have called ahead.
I needed to get up anyway.
Come in.
No, no. It's kind of my
only time to run errands.
I just needed to--
My bills.
Cielo, thank you,
big time, as always.
They seem to be getting
bigger instead of smaller,
and I'm not really sure what
that's all about.
Tell me if this is getting
to be too much for you guys.
It's absolutely fine.
Okay. Thanks.
Hey, what's with that car?
It's Walter's new car.
Walter's new car?
Wow.
A new car
plus he's paying Henry's bill?
He must be doing great
with that gambling thing.
- We're not talking about that.
- No, easy.
Does this mean
what I think it means?
What? What do you mean?
Come on! You and Walter?
He's spending the night here.
All right.
Okay. I'm not pressing.
You'll tell me when you're
ready. I think that it's great.
I'm out of here. Okay.
A big howdy-do
to Mr. I'm-Not-Here.
- Bye.
Hi! I thought
you were sleeping.
Where were you?
At the store
buying things for breakfast.
Dressed like that?
Would you rather
have no breakfast?
No, no, no.
Give me a hand with the eggs?
It's about eight.
- We should start--
- Shut up!
We need to start a cook at eight
to keep to our schedule--
Gus' schedule.
And as angry as he may be,
I don't believe he's willing
to forfeit an entire batch.
That just might
make him angrier.
Please, Mario, come on.
Let us cook.
Isn't that what this
whole thing is about?
That's right, genius.
We ain't missing no cook.
Just for the record
we should wear masks.
I insist on putting on masks.
What is this jerk doing?
I'm sure he will forget
the aluminum.
You see? No aluminum.
Gustavo.
I want to talk about Guido.
Guido was a good man,
he was a great chemist.
I always respected him.
He didn't deserve what happened.
This is a big injustice.
But I would shoot him
if I had to.
If I had to do it
again tomorrow
I would,
and the day after tomorrow.
You had me choosing
between me
and Guido and Jose
and Guido got the worst part.
It's a fact.
This is all your fault.
It's not mine nor Jose's.
Guido's death is on you.
Gustavo, let's be reasonable,
what did you expect me to do?
To sit tight
waiting for you
to kill us?
Without defending ourselves?
Did you really think
I wasn't going
to fight back?
That I wouldn't take
extreme measures to defend
ourselves?
That was a misjudgment,
a bad call, and you know it.
Gustavo.
Please, think.
I don't care what
you're planning.
No matter what you're trying
to prove here
please don't loose sight
of what's going on here.
Without us, Jose and me,
you won't have anyone
to cook your product.
Victor here
is not the right person
I can assure you.
He has no idea what he's doing.
I've been watching him for
weeks, I know every step of it.
Is that so?
You think you could do it?
If you know that much,
why don't you explain
the details of this procedure?
Tell us!
Tell me,
is the catalytic hydrogenation
protic or aprotic?
Please, tell me,
I seem to have forgotten.
If the reduction
is not stereoespecific
why do we get
a enantiomericly pure product?
Tell me!
I'm talking about the phenyl,
a hydroxyl,
two methylaminopropanes,
each one, of course,
with a chiral center in the
carbons...
one and two
of the propane chain, right?
Tell me!
The reduction
in our methamphetamine
which chiral center does it
eliminate?
Please, help me, Victor,
I can't seem to remember it!
Gustavo,
please, let us work.
It's clear your professor here,
elementary first,
is not up to the task.
That is called cooking,
no matter how
you choose to call it.
It's a recepe.
You just need to follow
the steps, and I know them.
Is that what you want, Gustavo?
A fast food cook?
Why don't you set up
a hot dog stand
up on the street?
You want to compete with the
Mexicans with this? Come on.
Good luck to you!
I want to know
what your new cook will do
when he gets
a damaged precursor.
Will he even realize it?
He won't have a clue!
What will he do
in the raining season,
when the temperature increases
and so does the humidity,
and the product gets all cloudy?
How will he fix that?
Tell me!
No, Gustavo.
Gustavo, if you kill us,
you will have nothing.
Just a highly equiped basement
that's worth eight million
dollars
for which you'll have no use.
Without Jose and me
this equipment is worth nothing.
No one will make a profit here.
Your clients won't buy that
shit!
The distribution chain
will break, and you know it.
Gustavo, if you kill me
you'll have nothing.
If you kill Jose, you loose me.
I know you are a smart guy
you won't sacrifice reason
for a tantrum.
Gustavo, let us work.
We're here, we are ready,
we are motivated.
We can simply
pick up where we left off.
Gustavo, please.
So?
Cooking time!
We're closed!
- Closed!
Open.
- It did.
- Look at the time, man.
Tell Saul.
No, no Miss,
he's not in,
but you can leave a message.
I wouldn't know.
I'll see what I can do.
Please hold.
Saul, Walter's wife calling.
- Saul, there's a call for you!
- Really?
Walter Blanco's wife.
What the hell does she want?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
I'm looking for bugs.
I think we are clear.
Tell her I'll call
in ten minutes
from a safe phone.
He's nowhere to be found.
I called his house. I called
every number I have for him.
#Yeah, I'm sure he's
fine.
You're sure? As in you know
where he is?
Well, I'm not the man's keeper.
#Clearly something
is going on here.
Why would he leave
his car in my driveway?
People carpool to work, right?
#It's good for the environment.
#He carpools?
Why would he leave
his keys laying around?
Well, be both know
he's kind of a genius
a mad scientist,
these people get distracted.
Maybe the keys fell off
and he couldn't find them
and so he took a cab.
No, no, no, look, Saul,
that's absurd.
I'm looking for some help here.
I need to find him.
Look, Walter is fine, okay?
I guarantee that 100 per cent.
100 per cent. Idiot!
You got a passport, right?
That's great.
We may have to fly out of here.
Fly!
Walter.
Walter!
Yes, hi, Miss.
I need the number
for a locksmith.
No, listen, please,
I can't get into de house,
I can't get into de car,
they stole my purse
with everything inside.
Please, help me!
Don't you have
any way of proving
that this is your house?
I just told you,
they stole my purse.
I had my wallet inside
and all my papers.
Look, the baby is hungry.
Yes, honey.
Are you all right?
Not now, God.
Hold the child
for a moment, please.
Hold her.
What's wrong?
I have asthma.
My inhaler is inside.
Perfect!
Thank you.
Yes, honey, I will feed you.
There, there.
What do we do?
Do I send you the money?
No, that's fine, Miss.
- That's fine, easy.
- Really?
Sure, no problem.
Sir, again, thank you so much.
- My God repay you.
- Be well.
Thank you. You are an angel!
Yes, honey,
I will give you some food.
Hey, there! I'm back!
How was P.T.?
I heard it was very good.
I need some water
for the flowers.
I'm really liking
this new therapist.
He keeps me in the loop,
always has time
for a phone call.
He keeps me posted.
You can see he cares.
I heard you broke
new ground today.
I broke new ground?
That's what he said. Tell me.
I walked 5 meters in 20 minutes.
And I had maybe this much
less shit in my pants.
That's new ground?
So if you and him
changed the meaning of
the entire language,
yeah, I guess
I broke new ground.
Call it
a figure of speech,
it's a way of looking at it.
But I am seeing progress.
Definite progress.
You're ordering a new rock?
It's not a rock.
It's a mineral.
It's a nice one.
I need the thing.
- Number one or two?
- Number two.
Number two. Coming right up.
Number two.
Let me help you there.
We'll just lay this down.
There. All right.
Here we go.
Will you just stay there?
No.
Come on, then.
Hold that.
No.
All right.
Hold that.
- What do we do?
- Let's pick it up.
One, two and--
There.
- There it is.
- That's it.
I'll get the chemicals.
Mario, you should wear a mask.
You'll see if he wears a mask.
I never used this stuff.
You sure it'll do the job?
Trust us.
There.
That can go
into the records
as waste without any problem.
Clean and legal.
- Great.
- So?
We just have to finish up
cleaning and cook.
- Don't ask for my help.
- Don't worry
we got that.
Each one to his own.
You've always been bad
at cleaning.
I didn't like to do it
when I lived alone
nor when I lived
with my parents, ever.
In life you have to change,
Jose.
- Grow up.
- That's not what I meant.
Since I met you
I never cleaned so much
in my life.
I would have liked
not to have to clean so much.
I guess that's what
they pay us for.
I gues we are the World's
most expensive cleaning crew.
There's worst things than that.
Like what?
Sure.
Can I get you anything else?
- Can I get some more fries?
- Yes, sir.
Jose, how are you?
I'm starving.
I don't understand
how you are not hungry
after all this time.
I don't understand
how you can eat.
Like this.
Are we talking or not?
Really, Jose,
tell me how you feel
after everything that's gone
through.
I'm eating, okay?
You did the only thing
that you could.
I hope you understand that.
Understand it or not,
what's done is done.
I can't bring that man back.
Now we have to think.
Thoughts?
- Thoughts?
- Sure.
We have to know what
our next move might be.
Our next move.
What next move?
You can stop repeating
everything I say.
Jose, it's very important
that we are perfectly focused
on what we are going to do next
given the fact that
at the first opportunity
Gustavo will kill us.
What, that wasn't
an opportunity just now?
He didn't do it, did he?
No. We bought ourselves some
time.
Some time.
So you think
we are still fucked?
We bought ourselves some time.
The question is how much.
He'll be looking
for another chemist.
He's not going to find
another chemist.
Where is he going to find
another chemist?
It's not just about somebody
being able
to run a lab that big.
Someone he can trust,
someone he knows will
keep their mouths shut.
Yeah. Good luck with that.
Bet it took him years
to find Guido.
Bet he's sorry now.
Are you sure you're okay?
Come on.
At least now
we all
understand each other.
I mean him and us, we get it.
What do you mean?
We're all on the same page.
Clear as shit.
Really?
What page is that?
The one that says...
if I can't kill you,
I'll fuck you up
and you'll shit wish you were
dead.
Miss, can I look at the
desserts?
- Hi!
- Hello.
Don't worry.
It's parked over a couple of
blocks down.
How so?
Junior was about to get up,
and he would have seen it,
so I wanted to avoid
a lot of questions.
That was smart.
Did you buy some clothes?
- Sort of.
- Do you have your keys?
- Here.
- Thanks.
You okay?
Right as rain.
Good.
Here are the keys.
The car is parked--
You know where the butcher's is?
- About a block down.
- Sure. Thanks.
Good day.
You too.
Come here!