- Come here.
- What do you want?
Walk.
Please, don't hurt me.
I'll do as you say.
Open the door.
Here are the keys.
We don't need them.
No, no, no!
Don't please!
"Compulsive gambling".
Addiction to games.
Learn causes
and consequences.
Gambling made me lose
many things in my life.
Mi family, my friends.
It was like a robbery,
only I was the thief.
It's amazing,
the stories you tell yourself
to justify it.
Just to play one more hand.
At anything:
dices, cards, slots.
Anything I could gamble at.
No, María, that's out deal.
Don't worry.
No, you're not paying
for anything.
We'll take care of
everything, okay?
We're meeting to say a word
about the bills.
We just want everyone
to know about Walter.
In therapy they call it
"socialize the problem".
Okay, fine.
Kisses. Bye.
Well...
Tonight's the night.
There's no turning back.
All right.
Let's do this.
So, this is the deal.
First I assign point values,
correlate to the effect
of removal.
You're going to split the 8s?
- May I continue?
- I'm sorry.
The mathematical principle,
known as the Kelly Criterion,
upon which I devised
my own strategy
is not dissimilar
to the MIT system.
No, no, no, wait.
You're not teaching them.
Focus.
You said you wanted me
to be thorough.
- No, just play.
- No.
- Play. You're taking too long.
- it's not that simple.
I have to be able
to explain all this.
No, here you have to look
professional.
Pretend you're in a movie
and you're an actor.
- Just act. Do it!
- No, no, no, Don't.
Don't be--
- For real. Believe me!
I've studied
every detail of this.
But you've lost
half of the hands played.
Because it's not that easy.
I know how to count the cards.
That's what it's about.
But it doesn't always work.
If it always worked,
I would be in a casino.
Walter, please,
they have to buy this story.
You know how they'd buy
this story?
If I didn't play.
I'm in recovery.
I shouldn't even be playing.
What you're doing is like
giving meth to an addict.
That's true.
You're right.
- Of course.
- It makes absolute sense.
- You can't touch any card.
- No.
Perfect!
The first point is solved.
The first point?
There's more?
Of course.
We're not leaving anything
at chance.
Here's what we have to say.
What's this?
- Well...
- Is it a script?
Yes, there're
our dialogues.
This is like a novella script?
So you're a writer
all of a sudden?
No, but you can learn a lot
on the Internet.
- This is ridiculous!
- No! No.
- You're nuts!
- Hey, it's not ridiculous.
It's necessary!
Henry is a cop.
He's used
to doing interrogations
and he knows
when someone is lying or not.
We can't tell him
a stupid story.
We can't sell him
a full-of-hole story
about how we suddenly have
enough money to buy a car wash.
Hold on.
Am I supposed
to memorize this?
Don't complain!
You've memorized worse things.
- Boring chemical stuff--
- No, no, no.
Be respectful with chemistry.
It has nothing to do with this.
Please, Walter!
This story has to be believable!
Cielo, you told this story
to María.
I know María
and I'm sure she told Henry.
Well, for the first time
in her entire life
María hasn't said anything.
Henry has no idea.
He thinks the insurance
is paying for his treatment,
not us.
I don't get it.
Why do we
have to keep this secret
is we have the perfect alibi?
Gambling. The brilliant system
I invented.
I'll tell you why.
When you were ill,
did you let anyone help you?
Did you take money
from Edgar and Marcela?
Because I seem to recall
that you'd rather sell drugs
than take help.
So why would Henry
think otherwise?
Fine.
- Fine, I give up.
- Perfect.
- Happy?
- Good.
Guys, we have good news.
Walter and I
are buying a car wash.
Yay!
The next logical question Henry
will probably ask is:
Where are you getting
the money from?
To which I'll say:
"We want to tell you
the whole story.
It's a doozy,
so hold on to your hats."
What hats?
That's not in the script.
No, I know.
But...
- It just came out.
- It just came out?
It just came from inside.
- Fine Whatever. Go on.
- Okay.
That's where you will take over,
starting with your diagnosis,
pages 1 and 2.
Please,
concentrate on the cancer.
- I will.
- That makes the public
like you.
What public?
María, Henry and Junior.
- Yes.
- They're our public.
- Yes, I'm sorry.
- Okay.
After that, per pages 3 and 4.
Please, that part.
Go.
"Despair and fear
made me act like..."
- Like an idiot?
- Yes.
- No.
- Yes, an idiot. Come on.
I terribly, terribly
regret my ac--
No, saying terribly twice
doesn't sound good.
You have to sound
like you regret it.
But the tone is not okay.
I don't like it.
Just look for another word.
Improvise.
What matters is that you look
regretful and embarrassed.
That's the part
that doesn't fit at all.
Why am I so regretful
and embarrassed?
I don't get it.
- Don't you?
- No.
Do I have to explain to you
that part?
Cielo, supposedly,
I did this for my family, so...
No, stick to the script.
This story
makes me look like an asshole.
Like a weak guy
who doesn't make decisions,
who loses control.
I'm the villain.
No, this is story
that also has defects.
- And we both look bad.
- Do we?
Where are your defects?
You don't look bad
in this story!
It's implied.
It's implied, sure.
Just tell me one ting.
Where is it implied
you slept with your boss?
Or did you leave that out?
You know what?
For a fired schoolteacher
who cooks crystal meth,
an illegal drug,
I'd say you're coming out
pretty much ahead.
Don't you think so?
I don't think so!
I don't want Junior
thinking less of me.
No.
Don't worry about that.
You'll be like a prince
for Junior.
You'll be the cool one
in the story.
I'm just the bitch
that made
his poor dad's life impossible.
You're the victim of this bitch!
Cielo...
Cielo, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I put you
through all of this.
I'm really sorry.
This is all my fault.
I really regret all this.
That's the tone
I like!
See?
Didn't that sound good?
Can I add it to the script?
Give me the pen.
Come on.
So then
comes the part
where I say
how proud I'm of you
because you're in therapy
and then comes the end.
Just a suggestion.
You might look down on the floor
with remorse.
There's remorse again!
Just cut that out.
Fine, I know
you can't feel that.
- Then just look at your feet.
- Yes, I prefer that.
Fine.
So then,
I'll take María's hand.
How could you get her
hand?
Just look where she is.
Will you get over me?
- We're in the wring places.
- Then move.
Jesus!
So I'll take María's
hand and I'll tell her:
"It's such a relief to tell you.
We're just so glad we have
a strong family to help us
through this."
In that moment, maybe,
I could tear up a little.
It all depends
on how I'm feeling.
You'll cry
in that precise moment?
I don't know.
It's just an idea.
Through which eye?
Left? Right?
It's just an idea!
Don't make fun of me!
No, I'm not making fun.
I just want to know.
- One or two tears?
- This has to be convincing,
Walter,
I'm doing the best I can here.
I have to be meticulous.
You know what I think?
Maybe lying doesn't come
as easily to me as
it does to you.
María, why do you push me here?
I'm sorry!
- Hello, guys.
- Hi, aunt.
- Welcome!
- What's up, uncle?
What's up, boy?
- How are you?
- Fine. Super!
Hello.
You look good.
Thank you.
What do you have there?
You have no idea
what I cooked.
I might get an honest-to-God
meal here for once?
Your aunt María, she's cute,
but she could burn water.
Yes, I know.
So funny.
I'll head
to the kitchen.
Go show the boys
your new rock collection.
It's not rocks, María.
It's minerals.
Mi-ne-rals.
You want to see my collection?
Really?
Yes, sure.
Let's go.
Do I help you?
No, no.
Don't worry. Look.
This is how you do it.
I'll just turn around.
Look.
Uncle, what's this?
That's my favorite one.
That's Rhodonite.
It's manganese inosilicate.
What makes it this color?
That's the manganese part.
It oxides like rust.
In fact, it's more complicated
than that, Henry.
Manganese can have an oxidation
state of between -3 and +7,
which takes it through a range
of colors.
Purple, green, blue.
But its most stable state
is +2, which is usually
pale pink.
Feels like plastic!
Must be so cool
to be you.
You have a very nice collection.
I love it!
Do you?
Yes.
I'm glad you like it.
Hey, boy,
give me that file, will you?
You've got to check this out.
- This one?
- Yes, yes.
Come, I'll show you.
Put this there.
Hold on, Henry.
It's not a disturbing image
of a dead body, is it?
- No, no.
It's disturbing,
but not the way you think.
Just check it out and see.
You'll fall flat on your ass.
Like when you miss
your crutches.
No, you'll fall on your face.
Watch it.
No, it's just...
It was more or less this way.
Just look.
White wine, night
and old songs
Did he record
this on his own?
And she laughed at me
You see?
Sweet liar
Look at his glasses.
That's the best part.
Fucking spring
That comes
after an arousing dream
If I suddenly wake up
- Uncle, who's this guy?
- This guy?
That's out number one
public enemy.
It's despairing
Because love hurts
So good!
It's such a relief
to finally tell you.
We're just so glad that we have
a strong family
to help us through this.
Calm down.
The worst is over now.
No, I don't...
I don't even know
what to tell you.
Just look at Walter!
Walter, you're such a stud.
How much did you exactly win?
Let's say
it's enough to buy a car wash
and pay for all the taxes,
which are pretty much.
Maybe even pay for a couple of
reasonable college educations.
But why did you stop?
You could have bought me
a convertible.
No, Junior.
Look, the truth is...
And this goes for you too,
I'm terribly,
terribly regretful and
embarrassed for my behavior.
Excuse me,
I have to go to the bathroom.
Wow!
Walter!
Did you drown in the bathroom
or what?
Did I take too long?
I'm sorry.
Hey, man,
let me tell you something.
I'm really surprised
about what you've just told us.
Sure, I understand.
I'm sorry.
We should have told you before,
but this is quite delicate
and Cielo and I
thought we should wait
for the right moment.
Sure.
It mustn't have been easy
to talk about it.
No, no, no.
Of course not.
hey, Walter.
I want you to know
you can always bend my ear,
you know?
If you have any problem
or if you just want to talk,
I'll be there.
For whatever you need.
Thanks, for real.
I really appreciate it.
And...
The same goes for you.
If you ever
want to talk about something,
either personal or...
Even some technical question
about your work,
I can help you with that.
I'd be pleased to.
You can count on me.
Sometimes just talking something
through,
really makes a difference.
We're not talking
about an improvised lab.
This is a big ass operation.
Massive production.
At least...
220 pound per week or more.
Who is this person?
What do you know about him?
Well...
Not precisely.
We just know
he's a weird guy
and that he's deader than a
Texas salad bar.
That's all.
But I'm totally sure
he's my guy.
Your guy?
There's this mystery man
I've been chasing
for the better part of a year.
Cooks the purest meth
that I've ever seen.
He accomplished a 99% of purity.
Not even Mexicans and Americans
can do that.
You know what they call him?
- "Jaisenber".
- Jaisenber?
The physicist?.
The physicist, yes.
The one who helped Hitler.
- Yes, I know him.
- Precisely.
Anyway, I figure with a handle
like that,
my guy's got to be
some sort of an egghead.
I asked you to look at this
to see if you can find
any logic in all these formulas.
For what I read,
these people
cook with phenylacetone.
Right?
Yes, that's it.
Here it is.
Didn't Americans use that
to cook meth
in the 60s?
Especially to make
blue crystals,
which his what I'm looking for.
There's something
that called my attention.
"Two sticks of dairy free
soy margarine,
two cups of sugar,
a bit of salt..."
What's that?
It's a recipe for vegans' mores.
- No way.
- Yes, yes.
Guido Bermúdez
is really special.
Give it to me.
I'll show you something.
There's all kinds of crazy crap
in there.
But there's one thing
that called my attention.
This dedicatory.
"To W.B.
Silent master.
My inspiration."
W.B.?
Who could be W.B.?
Wilson Borja?
Wilberto Buitrago?
You get me?
Walter Blanco.
You got me.
And I give in.
Asshole!
For real,
who could be W.B.?
Give it to me.
I think I remember...
Here!
It's a poem.
"Proverbs of hell".
"The road of excess
leads to the palace of wisdom.
Prudence is a rich ugly old maid
courted by Incapacity.
He who desires but acts not,
breeds pestilence."
Guess who wrote this?
William Blake.
An English poet.
No way!
No, but...
How did you guess that?
How did you see that?
I've been reading this
every day.
Mystery solved.
That's it.
W.B. William Blake. Of course!
Thank you, really.
I was going to start
following other leads
make a mess.
Thank you.
Henry, this Guido,
the one who wrote these notes,
You think he's Jaisenber?
Yes, I think so.
And it makes me mad.
Why is that?
I'd have liked
to catch him myself.
I wanted to be the one to slap
the handcuffs on him.
I understand
what you're feeling.
But you know what?
Don't worry.
Generally,
when a big guy falls,
other more dangerous come up.
That's no consolation.
Listen, Henry.
What about the person
who killed Guido?
You have any leads?
That's not our problem,
it's APD's.
They say they've got
some fingerprints
and an eyewitness
saw a person of interest.
But they know nothing yet.
They'll find him eventually.
Yes, sure.
No doubt.
José!
José Miguel!
Jose!
Here!
I need to talk to you.
Go ahead.
Would you stop doing
what you're doing, please?
I need your attention!
When I'm done.
That dude's next.
Okay?
What the hell?
It's urgent.
- Come here!
- Don't be so exaggerated.
José, Guido's murder
is being investigated.
So? That's their job.
It's normal.
And I have it on good authority
that they found fingerprints
at the scene.
Not mine.
- I'm going back to work.
- No!
How can you be
so sure?
Because I've been here at home
and you're the only one
who came to bother me.
Your brother-in-law's got
such a hardon for me
that if those
were my fingerprints
I wouldn't be here.
I didn't touch anything.
Absolutely anything.
The casing!
- Did you pick the casing?
- No.
José.
Tell me exactly what happened
from the moment you got there.
I what to know exactly
what happened.
I went there,
did my stuff and left.
No! I want details.
You drove there.
Get off the car and then?
Focus, damn it!
You went to his door.
Did you knock or ring the bell?
- Knocked.
- Fine, that's fine.
When Guido opened,
did he recognize you?
Did you talk? Did you get in
or shot him from outside?
What did you do?
José. José!
Argh!
Who wants to make
200 bucks?
- Let's go.
- Assholes!
Look, the boy's probably right.
If they had anything on him,
he'd be locked up already.
What about Henry's?
He suspects.
He knows José is involved
in the sale of blue meth.
That's the only lead he had
before the attack.
What if he ties
the loose ends?
He goes after him.
How?
On his Rascal Scooter?
I'm sorry.
That might have sounded
insensitive.
Anyway,
if he goes after José,
I'll sue his ass
for police brutality,
harassment and 16 other things.
The history that those two
have together being what it is,
you got to figure
your brother-in-law
is smart enough
not to go down
that particular road.
- There's nothing
to worry about.
- You think so?
Listen, Saúl.
What else should I not worry
about?
Should I not worry that Gustavo
plans to murder me
at the first chance he gets?
Should I not worry
that my drug-addicted partner
doesn't seem to care
whether he lives or dies?
You should see his house.
It's full of hobos.
Now how long
before Gustavo decides
that he's too big of a risk?
How long before he sends
that grunting dead-eyed cretin
sucker-punching me in the face.
Are you talking about...?
That's a good description.
Mario.
You know what that guy
is capable of.
When did this stop
being a business?
Why am I the only person
capable of behaving
in a professional manner?
This is way too dangerous.
Saúl, how can I
protect my family,
José, myself?
How?
Just a little question.
My name never came up
with those guys, right?
Meanwhile, we're buying
this stupid car wash
to launder the money
and my wife doesn't say a word.
She's telling herself
that I work in this little lab
where there's no blood
and when my contract is up
I'll just hang it all up,
tip my hat, and walk away.
When did everything
get so screwed up?
I won't say you're wrong
because to be realistic,
you're in a little trouble.
But what I do tell you
is that you're in condition
of buying a clean slate.
- A clean slate?
- Yes.
This is a last resort
back pocket kind of thing,
but if you really got
to protect yourself,
then you should think
of disappearing.
I know a guy,
a disappearer.
Some Copperfield
who can do the job.
It's expensive,
and when I say "expensive"
I mean expensive.
But you'll have the chance
of starting a new life
somewhere else.
Costa Rica, Argentina.
Like a witness protection
program
kind of thing?
But without
having witnessed anything.
New name, new life,
everything new.
You'd be absolutely lost.
But once you make the decision,
there's no chance
of coming back.
None.
What do you say?
- You want his card?
- No.
No, there has to be
another way, Saúl!
I don't know.
We have to make everything
go back to normal. Otherwise...
Sooner or later
someone else will die.
And it can't be me.
Me neither.
All the air we breathe
is mixed
in those invisible waves.
It's in the Internet signal,
when the computer vibrates,
in that transparent little light
of the remote.
It's a room full of threads.
There're invisible waves.
Shut up!
That's cancer.
And in microwaves.
That gets in your body too.
Those signals--
Wake up, bitches!
Don't stop the party!
Hey, bitch!
Will you make sure
there's pizza here
when I get back?
Sure! I can do that!
I need these people
up and partying
when I get back.
- Sure!
- Understood?
But who's paying for it?
- No problem.
I'll be right back.
- Great!!
- Stand up!
- Wake up, come on!
As I was telling you,
those waves...
Those waves
are killing us.
We're trees.
Like this. Trees.
Listen to me, dude.
Cancer is psychologic.
You cause
your own cancer
with so much stress
and sadness.
You worry about problems.
I rather let drug kill me,
not cancer.
I don't want that.
Buy pizza and anything you need.
- Cool!
- For everyone.
- Cool, dude.
- I'll be right back.
- Look! Pizza!
- Wake up, bitches!
- All flavors and colors!
Hey, bitches!
Christmas's here!
Take it!
Wake up.
José, wake up!
Wake up!
What's up?
What's up with your ear?
Downstairs now!
What the hell?
Where's everybody?
I invited your guests
to leave.
- Fine.
- You know who this is?
No idea.
You ought to.
He's been here for three days.
Okay.
He stole your money.
38 millions look familiar?
This is it?
That's it.
Thanks.
You want to know what's next
for Miss Pissed In His Pants?
- No.
- Sure?
I'm sure.
Don't you even want to guess?
Mario, you're going to kill him.
So now what?
Is this the part
where I'm supposed to beg you
not to do it?
And then what? I'm supposed
to promise to straighten up
or some other crap.
Is that what your little show
was all about?
You're on thin ice,
you little shit head.
Mario,
you're not going to kill him.
You know how come I know?
You put a blinder on him.
If you were going to kill him,
You wouldn't mind
him seeing you.
I'm going back to bed.
Close the door, please.
Good luck.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I was taking care of something.
- How's your ear?
- Mending.
Tell me.
José Miguel Rosas
is increasingly incautious.
He's a risk,
a liability.
I know him and Walter
are a team.
Walter won't like it,
but something's got to be done.
- Leave a message.
- José.
I don't know
how many messages I've left you.
Why don't you answer
my fucking calls?
I'm at your house.
If you're in there, open,
freaking irresponsible!
José!
José Miguel!
Where is José?
What?
Won't you ask me
where we're going?
No.