What are you looking for?
How can I help you?
I have DVDs,
I have some CDs,
porno 3D. The latest.
Do you want to see them?
Tell me. Can I help you?
You are talking to Tigre.
Tell me.
I'm looking for this place.
Who sent you?
Sir.
Go up the stairs
to the bottom.
Ask for Gancho.
Who are you looking for?
How does it look?
You mean, in do I see it?
- Yes.
- You look pregnant.
Any lawman
worth his salt
is going to spot that, yeah.
Assuming that's a deal breaker?
Yes. It's a deal breaker.
You won't buy it then.
I have to buy something.
I need protection.
The thing is
which is the right one.
Here.
I'll show you one
of my favorites.
The best of the best.
"Topo Gigio".
.38 Special, snub nose.
It's the same
as the other one but smaller.
This can do wonders.
It's smaller
and it doesn't show.
A revolver
is the best thing, man.
It won't jam.
- I don't know.
- Listen,
I'm not just trying
to sell this to you,
this is not a selling technic.
I've used this gun.
If you could see
the hole it left on the front.
And even bigger on the back.
I'm not feeling it.
I don't know.
It seems fragile.
Fragile? If you could see
people laying on the floor
after three of four shots.
Plus, I will give it to you
with hollow-point bullets,
not the other ones
that have less power.
- Don't you have anything
bigger?
- Sure.
They're not stronger,
they just have more bullets.
In this one you can have
up to ten bullets,
you put them in here.
And one on the barrel.
Like this one or this one.
But let me tell you one thing.
If you've got six bullets
and you can't get out
of the problem you're in,
that means you're in
a big shooting.
Some seven or eight other
bullets
won't do shit.
Is this the correct side?
If you're right-handed,
it is.
Maybe it'll feel
better on the left side.
No, no, no, no.
Never.
You don't want to cross draw,
not unless
you're going to be sitting,
you know, store clerks,
card gamers and such.
But you never cross draw.
I feel the urge
to ask you something,
even though I know better.
I've been providing my services
for the past 30-odd years.
But I do have to ask you,
we strictly talking
defense here?
Yes, absolutely defense.
You don't look like a crook.
You could simply buy it legally.
If you did have to use it,
wouldn't it still be better
to use one
that couldn't be traced?
That's true.
I believe that in this country
one needs to defend oneself.
You can't let someone
fuck you over.
If someone wants to fuck you,
you take that
and you fuck him up first.
Some call it a moral right,
and I do include myself
within that class.
I'll take it.
Honey.
Can I have another coffee,
please?
Sure.
- Jose!
- Hi!
What's up, brother?
What noise.
Dude, it sounds
like an earthquake out there.
Yeah. New sound system.
Check it out.
Whoa! Bodacious subwoofers, yo!
Serious cannons.
18-inchers,
six of them, aluminum columns,
so they're really, really like,
sonically neutral.
Tweeters are killers, too.
Dig all them lines
jumping around.
Psychedelic.
See that, Mono?
It's kind of like a fish tank.
Kind of like just want
to stare at them.
Yeah, man.
We can bet on which light
gets up there the most.
Don't be stupid, Mono.
This is a temple of Art and
Music.
It's got, like,
parametric equalization.
Automatically
adjusts the levels
to changes in, like,
air pressure and whatnot.
It's a totally digital
vacuum tube amp
which is by far the best
anti-distortion-wise.
It's 120 decibels
without breaking a sweat.
You learned the catalog by
heart.
It's the first thing
he learns since kindergarden.
Because his head is toast.
That's why they say:
say no to drugs.
No to drugs.
Hey.
Hold on to your hats, bitches.
I saw Andrea
at a meeting yesterday.
And?
She asked about you.
Okay.
No.
No, man, no.
No, I...
12 steps and all that.
Seriously?
Yeah, man.
Pass.
Yeah, man, 12 steps.
Come on.
Maybe just a little bump.
I can control it.
Sure, if Mono can control it,
so can I.
You ever played
Zombie District?
It's great!
Those bitches, look.
You cap them in the head.
The way them bitches
get all cranial.
The Japanese take it by a long
shot.
Please, brother.
You're fronting.
No, man, seriously,
the Japanese
are way sicker
than the gringos.
The chicks, they are smoking.
The zombies... uf.
You are sicker than the
Japanese.
How can you look at a zombie?
Come on.
Zombies must be a good fuck.
But then who cleans up?
Imagine all the scratching and
shit!
They must feel that.
I was thinking
about another thing.
What happens if a zombie
bites a vegetarian?
That sounded deep.
A paradox.
He will get rabies
and start eating
all the fruits and vegetables.
That's really
dangerous.
Can you imagine that?
He starts eating one fruit--
And eats them all!
Jose, what do you think
will happen
to the vegetarian zombies?
Agree, totally.
Hey, man,
what's the matter with you?
Why are you looking so funny?
It's too quiet in here.
Silence...
This is too empty.
You know what this place needs?
What is it, honey? You okay?
Can't you sleep?
Actually, yes, Maria.
This is me sleeping.
What's it look like?
Looks like you're
looking at a rock
at... 3:00 in the morning.
Rock?
For, like, the tenth time.
This is not a rock.
This is a mineral.
Okay. Got it.
This is a kyanite
of the silicate family.
Your kyanite
is very pretty, honey.
Comes from the Greek "kianos".
It's methamorphic.
Found in the Central
Cordillera.
Would you like some more detail?
You keep acting like you
give a shit,
I can give it to you.
I'm not going
to fight with you.
You know, when last
I counted, Maria,
there were four bedrooms
in this house.
You know, I mean, if I'm keeping
you awake and all that.
See you tomorrow.
You have reached Walter Blanco.
Please, leave a message.
Walter, are you there?
Well... okay.
Could you call me back, please?
Henry's bills are really
starting to pile up here.
I haven't received a check
from you in quite a while.
- Shit!
- Second order of business
is the car wash.
Take the next step here.
We need to look
into buying this car wash.
Hello, Cielo?
What are you doing?
What do you mean? Wait. Are you
screening all my calls?
What are you thinking, leaving a
message like that on my machine?
You have to be careful.
Why? What did I say?
You just left recorded proof
of our intention
to buy a car wash.
Now you think that was wise?
Walt, it is a car wash,
not a brothel.
I mean, if we can't
even say what it is,
why are we buying it at all?
Cielo, please, just--
- Hey, Mom.
- Hold on. Hey, hon.
Your breakfast is in the oven.
- It's still warm.
- Thank you.
I'm telling you,
if you're not willing
to pull the trigger on this,
I am more than happy
to call Saul myself.
No, no, no, no, no.
I will handle it, okay?
Look, a flying scorpion.
What?
Look, I have to go.
I'm going to work.
Wow--
I could so use a brain
transplant right now.
Tripa.
What is it, man?
Wake up, bitch.
I need to get
all these people up.
No, no, no. I didn't say that.
- Tripa.
- Listen here.
- Yes.
Here's some money.
Just go out and get
everybody some breakfast.
Stock up on liquor while you're
at it. Keep this party going.
I want this place kicking
when I get back.
You got it, bro.
Come on, damn it.
Wake up and party!
Come on! Party!
Hello.
You the new guy?
All set?
You got something for me?
201.6.
What's the count?
Give it a second weigh
if you would, please.
New policy.
"New policy"?
What's that, Mario?
Any particular reason?
Don't you trust us anymore?
What, Walter?
Any problem?
Where's Gustavo?
- Why?
- Because I would like to speak
with him.
Because,
the way we left things,
I would like
the chance to clear the air.
We need to be able
to work here.
Walter,
you're never
going to see him again.
Look who woke up hungry.
Are you hungry?
There.
Drink that up!
Another motor wash.
That's ten today.
That's five.
What, honey?
Just a few more minutes,
and we're on our way home.
Mama's just
doing her work here.
That's it! Come on!
Way to go, Henry,
one more step!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on, honey!
- Keep it going!
- Come on, honey.
I am going!
Use that anger!
- Come on, that's it.
- Come on, honey.
You are almost there, Henry!
Just eight more steps.
Seven. Come on!
- Six! That's it.
It's all up in here, Henry,
it's all up in here.
- Keep it up.
- Come on, honey.
- Come on, that's it!
- No, come on.
Come on!
- That's it.
- Henry, that's it!
Three more, Henry.
Two, two, two, Henry.
Two more, Henry, and--
- Two! It's all in here.
Henry, it's all in here.
That's it, man.
- All right, buddy!
- Yes, honey!
Excellent!
This is the man!
Very nice.
Very nice. Very nice.
You're a good man.
Thanks.
It's an honor, my friend.
An honor.
Same time tomorrow?
- Yes.
- If I'm still alive.
What do you mean?
Sure you'll be!
I'll walk you out.
Thanks a lot.
See you tomorrow.
Great, honey!
Great session.
Lots of positive energy.
We need that all the time.
Yes.
It's great to see him
like that, but--
One day at a time.
We are doing great.
I know.
You've got a real way with him.
You know how to get to him.
You want to go full-time?
We've got a spare bedroom.
Be patient. We're doing fine.
- I'll see you tomorrow, right?
- Sure.
- See you.
- Bye.
That was great.
You had a great day.
You made progress.
Did you work up an appetite?
I have a great recipe,
you'll love it.
You want some?
Get out.
Henry...
Henry what? Get out.
Okay.
Let me know, okay?
About time!
I was starving.
What's up with the pie,
man? It ain't cut.
That's the gimmick.
What gimmick?
This place.
They don't cut their pizza,
and they pass the savings
on to you.
How much can it be to cut
a damn pizza?
Maybe it's, like,
democratic, bro, you know?
It's like on your Birthday,
you cut a slice
the size you want.
Yeah. It's democratic.
Birthdays.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
You got some, like, scissors?
I will cut this bitch up good.
Who is it?
- Hey, would you mind?
- Uf.
Jose, I figure you make,
like, 10 million pizzas a year.
Each pizza takes,
like, 10 seconds to cut.
In man hours, that's--
A lot?
Hey, man.
- Who is it?
- No, it's... Andrea.
What about the scissors?
What about Byron?
Honey, wait in the car, okay?
Let the grownups speak.
Little man.
About this.
I get this in my mailbox.
This was you?
Is someone gonna come
looking for this?
No.
What exactly am I
supposed to do with this?
I don't know,
Buy a house with Byron.
Get out of that shit hole
of a neighborhood.
Or you can go out
and spend it on glass,
but I got to believe
you won't do that.
Bye, Jose.
- Hello.
- Go home, Walter.
- Good day.
- Good morning.
Delivery for Henry Navarro.
Yes, it's here.
Can I have a signature, please?
These bricks are heavy.
Rocks.
Want me to wheel them
inside for you?
Thank you.
Okay.
- There's the living room.
- Thanks.
Is that my minerals?
Yes, sir.
How many boxes?
I don't know, three, four,
a hundred, a million.
Did you check them for damage?
They're rocks, Henry.
No, they're minerals.
Check if they're all right,
will you?
Those delivery jackoffs,
I'm telling you--
I'm not getting ass raped
by those bastards, all right?
- You going out?
- Yes, honey.
I need you to look after
your little sister.
Where are you going
all dressed up?
Can't your mother dress up
for a change?
You can if you're going
to see dad.
Are you going over there?
Maybe.
The bottle is in the fridge.
You heat it up.
Asshole, look at that!
What's with all the soap?
You think that's free?
Stop wasting it.
Look,
tell your brother that if he
doesn't show up tomorrow,
I'm going to have to fire him.
- Yes, sir.
- And no more excuses.
- Hello.
- Yes?
- Don Ramiro Clavijo?
- Yes.
Hello, Cielo Restrepo.
Excuse me.
You want to buy my car wash.
I do. And I am prepared
to talk numbers right now.
Do you think
this is an easy job?
You are willing to get down
on your hands and knees
and scrub like a house maid
with all the chemicals
eating into your nice skin
and stinging in your eyes?
Well, I know a thing or two
about scrubbing.
Any other advice for me?
Because I am serious about this.
Good.
I am serious, too.
I have worked 30 years
of building this business
from nothing,
with my own hands
and my own sweat and blood.
So, with that in mind, is there
a figure you can quote me?
19.000 million pesos.
How about 1.500 million?
Where do you come up
with this number?
On a typical day,
you manage 19 cars per hour.
Extrapolating,
I added the extra revenues
for hand waxes and detailing,
subtracted
your overhead
and salary and maintenance,
which I obtained
from comparable businesses.
Giving me an estimate
of your annual cash flow here,
to which I added
the market value
of your real estate,
giving me a total estimated
value of 1.400 million.
On top of which
I generously
added an extra 100 million pesos
so as not to be insulting.
The price is
40.000 million pesos.
Mister Clavijo, please.
This is the price
for Walter Blanco.
You don't think
I know who you are?
I remember.
Well, I have not
pretended to be any--
Your husband, he quit
without giving me notice.
He broke my air fresheners.
He cursed at me.
And now he wants to buy
my car wash.
But he's not man enough
to come in here
and face me himself.
Instead, he sends his woman.
Excuse me?
Walter Blanco wants
to buy my car wash.
The price he pays
is 40.000 million pesos.
But he doesn't have
to send you, he should come.
I don't do business with women.
Now, please be
kind enough to leave,
I have things to do.
Hi. Have you recently
lost a loved one
on an aviation disaster?
Have you suffered injury,
shock to the senses,
or property damage
as a result of airplane debris
or, God forbid,
falling body parts?
Don't miss this week's specials
in "Tell Saul".
You'll learn a lot
about your rights.
If you need advising,
I'd be glad
to help you through your loss
even though
it will never fill the hole
in your heart.
You deserve justice.
So "Tell Saul".
You might want to learn
how to tail better
if you're planning
on making a habit of it.
May I sit?
Can we have something stronger?
On me.
You make a hell
of a lot more than I do.
What alcohol do you have?
Rum, liquor.
Two rums, double.
There were some actions that I
took which I want you to
understand.
I didn't want any of this
to happen.
Everything I did
I did out of loyalty
to my partner,
and then, later, of course,
it was purely
out of self-defense.
Thanks.
I hope you can
appreciate that, Mario.
I appreciate that when
you were going to kill me
you were simply
following orders.
And I harbor no ill will.
Great.
Well, there's a load
off my mind.
I'm trying to tell you--
I get it. Drink up.
Hell of a last couple of weeks.
Makes a man wonder
exactly where he stands.
I cannot be alone
in feeling this way.
Not after what happened
to Victor.
Walter, what's with the piece?
Right hip
inside your waistband.
You wear it if it
makes you feel better,
but if push comes to shove,
it's not going to help.
Do I have
to come right out and say this?
You and I,
we're in the same boat.
Drink your drink.
If it happened to Victor,
it could happen to you.
To any of us.
And what the hell was that
anyway?
A message?
He cuts a man's throat
just to send a message?
You won.
You got the job.
Do yourself a favor
and learn to take yes
for an answer.
Yeah, I got the job,
but for how long?
Mario...
Get me in a room with him.
That's all I'm asking.
I'll do the rest.
You done?
Yes.
Thanks for the drink.
I'm sorry.
This won't happen again.
See you next time.
Bye.
Thanks, Rosa.
We'll be here.
Come on.
Jose, that was epic.
- Epic. Thanks.
- Seriously,
where
are you two going?
Mono, get back inside.
Come on.
Tripa, let's get inside.
No, man, I've been awake for,
like, three straight days.
I can't take it.
It's not
like I ain't got the space.
You crash here.
I think I've got a canary.
I think I'm, like,
supposed to feed it.
Whatever, you little bitch.
Tripa!
Come on, get back inside.
Thanks, man.
I'm kind of
pushing flowers here, yo.
Look, man...
I ain't proud of it,
You know we got man love for
you. Now that you're back in the
mix
Come on, you're staying,
Tripa.
It's like nothing
but good days ahead.
- Come on.
- Plenty of time. No, man.
I'm good for now.
- Man.
- There's...
There's time for that.
Plenty of time to pace it
out is all I'm saying.
I was thinking,
like, next week?
Yeah, sure, man.
Next week.
We are cool.