We interrupt
our schedule programming
to bring you this breaking news.
We've received several calls
from concerned viewers
informing us about
what seems to be an air crash.
Possibly two aircrafts collided
in Bogotá's sky,
in Teusaquillo area.
We got calls
from several witnesses
which claim they saw
an explosion over their heads
followed by falling debris
from the sky.
Investigators experts on crashes
are expected on site
this very afternoon.
It seems these aircrafts
were being re-routed or vectored
through the airspace,
which is standard procedure
according to a spokesman
for the air forces.
The collision was
between a charter flight
operating out of Rionegro
bound to Villavicencio
and a commercial jet
that belonged
to Andinas Airlines
bound to the Caribbean.
I thought it was
just hail falling.
But no, they were
heavy hailstones.
I was so scared.
And I didn't know
how my neighbors were.
- Do you live near here?
- Yes, madam.
I live in the house
next door and...
How long did the
authorities
take to get here?
Did they find
survivors?
Well, they came here gradually.
But I'm worried
about my neighbors,
if they are okay.
Experts in air collisions...
After several days
of investigation,
the final death toll
now stands at 92.
After investigating
for several days,
the final death toll
now stands at 92.
This strange mid-air collision
has left many wondering
how such an accident
could take place
in a system
with so many safeguards
and, on the other hand,
how efficient the air security
of our country is.
The answer is simple:
a human mistake.
The first investigation results
indicate that the collision
that crashed flights ST 9666
and ARA 787,
was caused by improper
air traffic control.
It was confirmed
the cause of the accident
was a fateful mistake
by an air traffic controller:
Diego Maldonado.
A human mistake.
According to
the first investigations,
the collision that caused
the crash of flights ST 9666...
A 19-year veteran engineer
of the air traffic
control center in Bogotá.
The engineer Maldonado
had recently returned to work
after a five-week absence
due to a personal loss.
It's now known
that four weeks ago,
Maldonado lost a daughter
to a drug overdose.
Apparently his daughter,
Juana Maldonado, aged 26,
had a long history
of substance abuse.
Friends of the family say
the death of his only child
hit the engineer
particularly hard.
Coming as it did
little more than a month before.
Many are questioning the
timing of his return to work
and are wondering
how much blame truly lies
with those who let
a grieving father
come back to his work
as an air traffic controller,
without the psychological tests
needed to confirm
he was apt to work again.
We talked to some...
These days, I just find it
really hard to concentrate.
The images I had to see
were horrible.
They're stuck in my brain.
They keep coming and going.
Every time I remember it,
I feel nauseous.
Thanks, anyone else?
Guys, let me remind you,
this is a space
for you to talk,
to pour your hearts out.
Many of you shared classes
with Claudia, with Sebastián,
with Ricardo...
So please, make the most
out of this moment.
Me, please.
I just wanted to say
that I've been thinking
these days
why this happened to Sebastián.
I mean,
if there's a God and all,
how did He let him die?
Not just him, many
other innocent people
died for no reason.
Sebastián was the
smartest kid in class.
I still see him there...
...sitting at the front row
raising his hand.
Since I learned
he was one of the crash victims,
I've been having insomnia,
I haven't slept at all.
Just thinking...
how he felt
at the time of the explosion.
Boom!
How did Claudia feel?
How did Ricardo feel...?
- Thanks, Clara.
Thanks.
Go ahead.
A cousin of mine
found a seat,
an airliner seat,
that had fallen
next to his bike.
The most horrible part of it
is that...
...there was still
a pair of legs bucked into them.
I'm not lying,
human legs.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes...
I was just moved.
Sure.
Now it's the faculty's turn
to share
because this tragedy
certainly didn't only affect you
it affected us as well.
Mr. Blanco...
you didn't teach
the students that died,
but I'm sure you knew them.
Would you like to say something?
No.
By they way, welcome back.
Thanks, thanks.
It's very good to have you
back.
Well, the truth is...
...I would want to say
that we should look
on the bright side of all this.
First of all,
nobody on the ground was killed.
Taking the magnitude
of this event into account
over a populated urban center
that right there
has to be a minor miracle.
Besides,
neither plane was full.
One of them
was two-thirds full.
I mean, casualty-wise,
it's less than the average
of accidents in Colombia.
I mean, more than half
of the accidents in Colombia
are much worse than this one.
The Cúcuta accident in 1988
was much worse:
143 victims.
In 1989, if you recall,
the bomb Pablo Escobar planted
resulted in:
107 travelers,
plus 3 victims on land.
In 1993,
25 miles from Medellín,
133 victims.
And the worst one of all:
Buga, 160 victims.
But do any of you remember
those accidents
I just mentioned?
No, right?
You know why?
Because people forget
and move on.
And that's exactly
what we should do.
Overcome this and move on.
That is what human beings do:
we survive and move on.
Well, that was all.
Thanks a lot.
On my first meeting
with my clients,
I always tell them
I'm so sorry
for the situation
they're in.
Tell me something, Cielo,
Does your husband
go along with this?
Does he know we're here?
I don't know, I guess,
we're not separated.
Has he moved out?
He must be moving out right now.
I hope he'll be out
by the end of the day.
In the meantime,
my kids and I are staying
with my sister
and my brother in law.
So, you're the one
who moved out?
Well, yes, temporarily.
Only so he could pack his stuff.
In fact, he was supposed
to leave last week,
but then came the plane crash...
No, God.
You had to go through
that?
Yes, the house is located
right beneath the flight path.
But, well, anyway,
it's time for us
to go back home
because I don't want to trouble
my sister and my brother in law
any more,
I'm sure we're driving
them up a wall.
I don't want to drag them
into this any more.
I think it's better
for everyone.
Well, as I see it,
you want to maintain
residency
in the house you've lived
all your life.
Yes.
It puts you in a better
position in regards to custody.
Two children, right?
Valentina and Walter Jr.
He's a teenager,
he's in high school.
Valentina and Walter.
They need to stay with me.
How long have you
been married?
Sixteen, almost seventeen years.
I understand
it's not an apartment,
it's a house that
you live in?
Do you own it or rent it?
We have maybe 15 years on it.
Definitely mortgage.
What about other
debts or assets?
Well, I mean...
I'd like you to describe
for me, briefly,
your husband's
financial situation.
No, look, in fact...
I'm not trying to get
any economic benefit
from all this.
No, no, no, it's not that.
I just intend that every one
of my clients gets
detailed accounting
of what they owe
and, well, what belongs
to them.
Let me be honest
with you, Cielo,
no stone will be left
unturned.
You'd be amazed with how
many things husbands hide,
and the wives
never find out.
Walter!
Hey, buddy.
Cielo gave me the keys
so...
...I could help her,
you know...
This is it?
What a week!
You know what?
It reminds me when Pablo Escobar
brought the plane down.
There's a kind of
uncertainty,
people doesn't know
what to think of this.
Don't you feel
it?
I think this week
should be named
by the Guinness Book of Records
as the weirdest week
in the world, right?
Hey, am I talking too
much?
Yes, yes, I
know I am.
You know what?
I don't know how to deal
with this situation
between you and Cielo.
It's none of my
business,
you know?
I don't want to tell you
what to do, or anything.
Here's an idea!
For example,
there's something we
a tactical retreat.
You know what I mean?
You regroup, you get
your act together,
so what you'll get
is Cielo to feel your absence
and that is what...
Forget it, man.
No, no, no,
I'll take this one with me.
Take it with you?
No, man, you're nuts.
Give me that.
Holy cow...!
What do you have here?
Holy sh--
A thousand million pesos
in cash.
You crack me up, man!
That's the spirit!
A thousand million, ha, ha, ha!
Man!
Hi, there!
So this path takes us
to the question,
the big question.
Who of everyone here,
is here for self-improvement?
Yes?
Anyone else?
Many of you want to be better.
That's your first mistake.
Let me ask you
a different question.
You want to be better or worse
for whom?
Or for what?
I'd say, the question we should
ask ourselves is:
why can't we accept ourselves?
Some more chocolate?
Hi, you reached the Blancos.
We can't come
to the phone right now.
Please,
leave us a message.
Hello, everyone.
I was just checking in
and maybe tell you
where I'm staying
in case you need anything.
Anyhow, you know
you can always reach me
on my cell.
Just in case,
I'm at a motel in La Soledad.
You know what?
It's actually
a nice neighborhood...
If you're done,
will you please clear the table?
Well, it's not a luxury hotel...
It's more of a residency,
really,
but it's fine, it's...
it's very independent
and has everything I need.
Besides, we're relatively close.
Hello?
Hello, yes.
What's up, dad?
Yes, yes, I'm fine.
Will you tell me
what's going on?
Nobody's telling me
jackshit around here.
Morgan!
No, whatever.
Let me help you.
There you go.
Hey, tell me,
your aunt...
how's she taking
all this?
Fine, I guess.
You make sure you say hello
to her for me, will you?
Why don't you do it yourself?
It's your house.
No, I'd better not.
Things are going
to be like this...
for good?
What do you
mean?
Dad, please, don't play dumb.
You know what I mean.
Will you keep acting as
if you were not a member
of this family?
Junior, I'll always be part
of your family.
Yeah, but...
...I feel I had a dad...
...hired by the hour.
Well, take it as a kind
of modern service.
It's not funny.
I've got to go now.
No, no, wait, please.
I'm sorry.
Everything's going
to be fine.
I just need you
to give us some more time.
Bye.
He dropped him in
and left in the taxi.
- How's tricks?
- How's what?
Tricks. It's an expression
you guys use.
Hi, honey.
How was your
day?
Why do you have to treat him
like this?
You don't even talk to him!
Hey, cool down, okay?
Sorry.
Don't speak ill of his dad.
Don't turn him
against his dad.
Walk in his shoes for a second.
He has no idea what's going on.
He's dying of curiosity.
He doesn't know why
his mom is not speaking his dad
overnight.
- María, please.
- I mean it.
If you don't talk to me,
I can't help you, Cielo.
Do you want to help
me?
Don't poke your
nose into this.
I'd appreciate
that, honestly.
What do you mean?
You're calling me "nosey"?
Hey, I just want to help.
Cielo.
I just want to help,
which is very different.
So now,
facing this purifying fire...
...we'll listen to the voice
one more time.
Not a voice from the outside,
but the voice...
...each one of us
has within ourselves.
That voice that talks to us
all the time?
It drills us, it points at us,
it questions us.
How good are we?
Am I good enough
to be a businessman?
To be the president
of the republic?
Maybe these days
that's not the best example
but...
What I mean is that the voice
is there...
...talking to us.
And there comes a time when
you have to answer yourself.
What am I good at?
How good am I at it?
Am I good enough
to accept myself?
Just the way I am?
Simply me,
who I am.
I don't know, I say yes.
I say yes to myself.
But what does
the voice tells you?
What do you answer
to that voice?
You, Jose, for example?
What do you answer
to your voice?
Can you hear it?
Come on, man!
Use this!
If you feel like telling me
all I'm saying
is stupid,
that I'm full of shit,
Say it!
You know that,
bro?
I feel like
asking...
What makes you the expert?
I never said I was that.
No, you didn't,
but you're the one
sitting there
telling us to be
happy,
to learn to accept
ourselves,
and blah, blah, blah,
blah,
and to be honest,
I feel I'm at church, bro.
At mass.
Why? Because of the sermon?
You know why?
Because I'm sick
of the people who like
giving sermons
and think they are better
than anybody else,
and look down on people
simply because you
are different.
I understand.
Religious people,
vegetarians,
even sportsmen are
like that.
They can't wait to rub it
on your face
and that makes them
feel better persons.
See, I've got
this friend...
I've got a friend
who says...
...you only need
one had habit
to be given to vice.
But if you're not
given to vice,
that doesn't make you
virtuous.
Right?
So, I wonder, Camilo, if...
...if you're really
one of us
or you're just there
watching us
from the cheap seats.
You know what?
I've got news for you.
I am one of you.
You are?
Have you ever
really hurt anyone in your life?
And I don't mean just
I don't know, letting your mom
or wife down.
but did you ever really
hurt someone
you really love?
I killed my daughter.
No, well...
Bro, I didn't want
to...
No, no, don't worry.
That's what
we're here for, right?
Talking about these stuff.
June 18th, 1999,
my birthday.
I wanted to celebrate myself,
I deserved it.
I was alcoholic back then,
and a cocaine addict.
I was using a lot and...
The night before
I'd bought 3 grams,
three good, heavy grams?
Good old school cocaine.
Cocaine wasn't an issue,
I had enough.
But I was out of vodka.
So I decided to start
an argument with my wife
demanding her to go get me
a bottle of vodka
because I deserved it.
I had worked a lot
and I was celebrating.
"No, no, you go!"
Unfortunately, at the time
there were no delivery service.
So, well, I was pissed.
Without thinking,
I took the car keys,
jumped in...
...put it in reverse
and hit the gas.
I didn't notice Carolina,
my 6 year old daughter,
playing at the end
of the driveway.
How do you not
hate yourself?
To be honest, I don't hate
myself as much as before.
I hate myself less and less.
For a long time
the only thing I did,
you know what was it, Jose?
Precisely that.
I blamed myself, hated myself.
And that only led me
to go on drinking and using,
and destroying myself.
And destroying
everything around me.
I was more devastated and sad
every day.
Woe is me!
But you know what?
One day I decided
that I couldn't go on like this,
that I couldn't live my life,
what was left of it,
feeling so miserable.
And I decided
that I had to do something,
I had to find a new way.
What way?
The way to change, Jose.
That way.
Cielo!
Can we talk?
Yes, sure, come in.
Honey.
Do you want to start?
Yes.
Are these the divorce documents?
Why are you doing this to me?
When did we get to this point?
What is this?
Is it to punish me?
No, I am not
punishing you.
Yes, you are punishing me!
Cielo.
We are happily married.
I'm happily married--
I'm happy.
It's just we are...
I love you, you know that.
And I would do anything for you.
Would you even consider...?
Telling the truth?
Would you?
Are you calling me
a liar again?
So we're going down that road?
You bring me
the divorce documents.
You come in here,
as if nothing has happened,
and both of us
should be solving this,
together.
We're a team, Cielo.
You haven't heard my side yet.
You haven't heard
any of it at all
- No, I've heard enough.
- No.
You're a drug dealer?
What?
Drug dealer?
Yes.
I've been thinking
and I can't find
an explanation.
How else could you possibly
make that kind of money
in such a short time?
Marijuana.
You're dealing marijuana
with that boy,
Jose Miguel.
No?
Is it worse?
Cocaine?
It's methamphetamine.
That's what Henry
mentioned to you the other day,
that they're beginning
to produce it here.
But wait a second.
I'm just a manufacturer.
I'm not a dealer.
There's a big difference.
What does that mean?
That you do it but you
don't sell it?
Yes, exactly.
And you think that doesn't mean
you've got blood in
your hands anyway?
No, Cielo, wait.
Cielo, please, don't go.
Please, wait a second.
Cielo, this is
much more complicated
than what it seems.
There are a lot of angles
to this, okay?
So please,
let's just sit back down
and talk it through.
Please.
I'm going to make you
a deal, Walt.
I won't tell Henry,
or your children
or anybody else.
Nobody will hear it
from me.
But only if you grant me
this divorce
and stay out of
our lives
once for all.
No, Cielo.
Let me get the hell out of
here before I throw up.
Jose, take care.
Thanks for
everything.
- Camilo.
- Walter.
Come in.
You know what it is?
Little friction.
Couples in general...
Besides, it's recent.
Strictly temporary.
We're just...
We're just taking
a little break.
That's you, over there.
Jose, mm...
Saúl is keeping
your money for you,
so as soon
as you're feeling better...
I'm better.
You're better? Really?
So, therapy,
the rehab, it helped?
Yes, I'm not using.
I'm clean.
Good!
That's very good.
Congratulations.
Look, I think we should
stop thinking
about how bad things got.
I mean, the consequences
of it all.
Let's focus,
let's be optimistic
and try to get our lives
back together again
and on the straight and narrow.
You been following
this airplane crash?
Yes.
Did you know
it was Juana's dad
who crashed them together?
The man was so torn up
after what happened
that--
Okay, look, let me stop you
right there, all right?
You are not responsible
for this whatsoever.
I am very up-to-date
on this thing,
probably far more
than you are.
Look, there are many factors
at play here.
Yes? For instance?
I mean, for example
the collision radar on the jet
didn't work.
That's public record.
You can look that up on line
if you want.
But it goes deeper than that.
It's the whole
technological system
that is completely obsolete.
You know who's responsible?
The government.
Look, Mr. Blanco,
you...
... You either run from
things or you face them.
That simple.
What do you mean by that?
It's something I leaned
in the rehab center.
In fact, it's pretty brief.
It's not about changing,
it's about accepting
who you really are.
I accept who I am.
And who are you?
I'm the bad guy, bro.
Gentleman, is everything okay?
Everything's great.
Thanks a lot. Very good service.
Very well.
Are you enjoying
yourself, sir?
A lot.
It's good to see you
here again, Walter.
- Thanks a lot.
- May I?
Please.
I have an offer that will be
of interest to you, Walter.
I actually am not here to...
I mean...
I'm here
because I think I owe you
the courtesy
and respect to tell you
personally...
...that I decided
I'm leaving this.
I'm done.
Please, know
this has nothing to do
with you personally.
On the contrary.
I find you
extraordinarily professional.
I appreciate
the way you do business.
In fact, this decision
only has got to do with me.
I feel...
...I have to make a change
in my life.
I don't know, I'm at something
of a crossroads...
and it's brought me
to the realization
that I don't what
to be a criminal.
No offence
to any people who are.
That's simply not who I am.
Notwithstanding,
I'd like you to hear my
offer.
Sure.
But it won't change my mind.
Three million dollars
for three months of your time.
Dollars?
May I take this as a "yes"?
I have money.
I have more money
than I know how to spend.
What I don't have is my family.
The answer is still no.
Fine.
Then...
...enjoy your evening.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
Welcome to Colombia!
You come from Mexico,
I can tell for the suitcases.
You're kind of
rockers?
Like in... rock!
English?
I speak English.
It's so hot, bro.
It's been hot these days?
Very well, sirs,
this is your hotel.
It's only 40
thousand pesos.
Yes, well, the thing is
the airport surcharge
is not included
and the Sunday night
fee, either.