"You are with me. I am with you."
[young Osha] "Always one,
but born as two."
[Mother Aniseya] Ascension is
about walking through fear.
It is about sacrificing
a part of yourself.
I want to be a Jedi, Mama. I do.
[Mother Aniseya] We must let them
test the girls.
And what happens if the Jedi discover
how you created them?
I won't let it happen.
- [young Mae] Osha!
- Mae!
- [young Osha screams]
- [Sol] No!
I got you.
Mae started a fire
that killed her entire family.
- Mama! Mama!
- [Sol grunts]
The Jedi got what they deserved.
They invaded our home.
[ship whooshes]
Have you told me everything
that happened on Brendok?
You were very young.
Hello? Is anybody there? Can you hear me?
[Jedi over comms] Identify yourself.
- My name is...
- [blaster fires]
[Sol] Oh, Mae.
I've had 16 years to think
about what I would say to you.
So you're going to listen.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
- [device beeping]
- [Indara] Right there. Right there.
[detector whirs]
[Sol grunts]
[device beeps]
[beeps]
[device beeping]
[detector whirs]
[beeping]
[speaking Shyriiwook]
[thunder rumbling]
[device beeping]
[♪ gentle music playing]
You must eat, Padawan.
I'm not hungry.
[speaking Shyriiwook]
It's unwise to insult a Wookiee's cooking.
I'm just sick of eating Nuna legs.
And I want to go home to Coruscant.
I know. But we're on a mission.
We've been here for seven weeks.
And there's no one here,
and if we were going to find something,
we probably would've found it by now.
A hundred years ago,
this planet was catalogued as lifeless
because of a hyperspace disaster.
Yet this planet, Brendok, is thriving.
So there's some plants here. Big deal.
Calm yourself, Padawan.
Do not center around your anxieties.
Well, if only I knew
that what we were doing
was somehow important or meaningful...
We are looking for a vergence.
What's a vergence?
A concentration of Force energy
centered around a location.
A vergence could create life
like what we see on this planet.
It's a power that should be studied.
Protected.
Nothing could be more important
to the Jedi.
This is a noble mission.
[speaking Shyriiwook]
[detector whirring]
[sighs]
[device beeping]
My Padawan is too distracted to appreciate
the significance of a vergence.
Nor are we sure
that it's the cause of life on Brendok.
[Sol grunts]
He was disturbed. Unbalanced.
You were disturbed.
[Sol grunts lightly]
Do not confuse Torbin's feelings
with your own.
[Sol scoffs]
I do not tell him answers
to ease his mind.
I teach him
to seek the answers for himself.
You disagree?
- [Sol sighs]
- That's why I have a Padawan
and you do not.
- [Sol groans]
- [Indara chuckles]
[speaking Shyriiwook]
We'll split up then.
Sol, follow the river.
We haven't covered the Northlands yet.
- Meet us back at the camp.
- Okay.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[speeder bike whirring]
[grunts]
[panting]
[♪ gentle music playing]
[young Osha] Mae?
How did you know I was here?
[young Mae] When I can't find you,
I look here.
[young Osha] The bunta tree's
so beautiful.
[warbling]
Let it go, Mae!
Stop!
[warbling stops]
Why do you always
have to do things like that?
Why do you always run off alone?
[♪ uneasy music playing]
"You are with me. I am with you."
Oshie!
"I am with you"?
"Always one, but born as two."
[young Mae] "As above sits the stars...
"and below lies the sea...
"I give you you..."
[Koril] What are you doing here?
How many times have I told you?
It is not safe out here.
[young Mae] Sorry, Mother Koril.
There will be consequences
for breaking the rules.
- [young Osha] It isn't fair.
- [Koril] The rules are for your safety.
Now follow me. Quickly.
- [comms beeps]
- Indara. Can you read me?
We are not alone.
Indara, can you read me?
[♪ unsettling music playing]
- [system beeps]
- [door powering up]
[system buzzes]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[door buzzes]
[♪ fervent music playing]
[grunting]
[Mother Aniseya] Girls!
Your enemies will not warn you
before they attack!
Get up.
Block me!
[warbling]
[breathing heavily]
[warbling stops]
Excellent, Mae.
Osha, I expect more from you.
[creaking]
Girls, to your room.
[witches vocalizing]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
A Force cult. Here?
I think they are witches.
- Nightsisters?
- [speaking Shyriiwook]
We do not have all the information.
Besides,
Nightsisters don't raise younglings.
Let alone train them.
They do not treat the girls like children.
We should return to the ship.
Ask the Council for guidance.
I fear for the girls' safety.
The witches prepare
for a ceremony tonight.
What if the girls are in danger?
Indara, I know you would defer
to the Council, but I insist.
Come with me. See what I have seen.
[speeder bikes whirring]
[speaking Shyriiwook]
It's an old platform elevator.
This must be an old mining site.
- Kelnacca, slice the controls.
- [speaking Shyriiwook]
I'm going in alone.
- [system trilling]
- Master, we must escort you.
It's too risky to go in as a group.
They'll take it as a threat.
There are over 50 of them.
Fifty women, and only two children.
We should go as a team.
[system beeping]
- Fine.
- [elevator powers up]
But we must be vigilant.
- [system buzzes]
- [elevator thudding]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Indara] Good evening.
I am Master Indara,
and these are my colleagues,
Sol, Kelnacca, and my Padawan, Torbin.
I am Aniseya, mother of this coven.
These women are under my protection.
You're trespassing.
Forgive our intrusion.
We thought this planet was uninhabited.
The all-knowing Jedi
were ignorant of their surroundings?
I find that hard to believe. [echoing]
[breathing heavily]
[echoing] Torbin, Jedi Padawan...
Son of paupers from the planet Bonadan.
You've traveled so far,
only to become trapped on this planet.
[Torbin breathing heavily]
You are a strong and good Jedi.
[echoing] You are a strong and good Jedi.
[Mother Aniseya] But you have
natural desires you suppress.
Tell me...
Do you wish to escape this planet?
[echoing] Do you wish
to escape this planet?
I can help you.
Do you wish to escape this planet?
[Indara] Osha. May we meet your sister?
[Mother Aniseya] You wish
to return to Coruscant.
[echoing]
Your Master denies you.
I would not keep you from what you want.
I would always let you have what you need.
[echoing]
Why not ask me? [echoing]
Go on. Go on.
Go on.
Ask. Ask me. Ask.
Ask me.
[Torbin breathes deeply]
I want to return to Coruscant.
Kneel.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
- [speaking Shyriiwook]
- [gasping]
[Mother Aniseya] If you want your Padawan
returned to his right mind,
I suggest you all leave. Now.
Mama! I wanna show them
what you've taught me.
Please let me take the test.
Mother Aniseya,
you cannot deny that Jedi have the right
to test potential Padawans.
With your permission, of course.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[♪ music builds, dramatic chord plays]
[Torbin gasps, breathes heavily]
[Mother Aniseya] The scouts will
bring Osha to your camp at midday.
We appreciate your cooperation.
[Indara] That was clever.
Suggesting we test the girls.
Buys me time
to ask the Council for guidance.
Indara, I feel a connection to Osha.
Sol, testing the twins
is not something we can take seriously.
Osha's too old to join the Order.
I feel she is meant to be my Padawan.
Her coven will never let her leave.
- They are so insular... So strange.
- [Sol sighs]
They marked her sister with dark magic.
Ceremonial markings are customary
in many cultures in the galaxy.
But Osha did not have one.
- I worry she's not safe.
- That's true.
She may have resisted being marked.
There's no way to know.
Then who is protecting this child
if not the Jedi?
I believe she wants to leave with us.
Do not confuse what Osha wants
with what you want.
[breathing deeply]
[Koril] We're here.
[Torbin] This won't take long, Mae.
- [device clicks]
- What is that?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just need to take a sample
of your blood.
Is that okay?
- [device clicking]
- Ow.
In this test,
you must divine what images appear
on the testing screen...
What do you want me to do?
- Tell us what you see.
- [device beeps]
A spaceship.
[device beeps]
A castle.
- [device beeps]
- A planet.
A necklace.
The image hasn't appeared yet.
Can I go back to my family now?
Last night before we entered your home,
what was everyone doing in the courtyard?
Ascension.
[Indara] What is that?
Is your marking a part of Ascension?
Do you like it?
It's very beautiful.
Ascension must be very important
to include a marking like that.
Mama says "Ascension"
means Osha and I will lead the coven.
That's why I have a marking like Mama.
But you're children.
How can you become the leaders?
I... don't know.
Mama said,
"Everyone must walk through fear.
"Everyone must be sacrificed
to fulfill their destiny."
Thank you for explaining that to me.
Can I go now?
[Indara] Mm.
[♪ uneasy music playing]
[sighs]
Mae was instructed to fail.
- Mm.
- [Sol] With your permission,
I would like to try a different approach
with the other child.
You may.
There are other children there?
Thousands like us.
But you must have the courage
to say what you want.
[young Osha] I want to be a Jedi.
[Sol] Then you must have the courage
to tell the truth.
We should continue the test.
[device beeps]
A planet.
[Sol] Correct.
[♪ stirring music playing]
What now, Master?
You should run the girls' blood samples.
- I've contacted Council for instruction.
- And then?
You, Sol, and Kelnacca
continue the field work.
I'll wait here
until Coruscant makes contact with us.
[system beeping]
Osha passed.
I will meet you at the camp
when I hear their answer.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[breathing heavily]
Something is wrong.
[branch snaps]
The Council said no.
[sighs]
They will not sanction
bringing the twins to Coruscant.
Or separating them from their coven.
But there's something dangerous
about those women.
You saw what they were capable of.
You can feel the twins are not safe.
They say that we have interfered
too much already.
Will they let us come home at least?
No.
- [sighs]
- Let me talk to the Council.
They've already made their decision, Sol.
- [Sol] But Osha passed.
- After you coached her.
Do not alter this little girl's destiny
because you have formed
an emotional attachment to her.
That is not what's happening here.
[sighs]
I want to do what's best for Osha.
- You don't get to decide that.
- [device beeps]
[speaking Shyriiwook]
[Torbin] It's the twins'
blood test results.
[device trilling]
The M-Count very high.
Extremely high.
Very Force sensitive.
- Wait. Their symbionts are the same.
- [device beeps]
They are twins.
No, no, exactly the same.
Even identical twins
would have different symbionts.
This is impossible
without some kind of manipulation.
The twins were artificially created?
[Indara] Maybe by tapping
into a power dense enough
to split one consciousness
into two bodies?
Only a vergence
could create that type of power.
This is it.
Torbin, stop!
Don't you see?
We just need proof of a vergence
and those girls are the proof.
- [speeder bike powers up]
- This is our ticket home.
Stop him!
Kelnacca and I will take the ship.
[speeder bike whirs]
What's wrong with you?
[young Osha and Mae shout]
- Go and take a walk, Mae.
- [shouts]
Take a walk with Mother Koril.
- But Mama!
- [Mother Aniseya] Now!
[young Mae] What's wrong with you?
Mama! Mama!
[♪ tense music playing]
[speeder bikes whirring]
I wanna be a Jedi, Mama.
I do.
[♪ gentle music playing]
I must discuss this situation
with everyone here.
But we will consider
your wish when we do so.
I love you, Mama.
I love you.
Now go. [sniffles]
No! I don't wanna go.
You wanna stop Osha from leaving?
Then stop her.
[♪ ominous music playing]
The Jedi will not warn you
before they attack.
- [warbling]
- [Koril grunts]
- [young Mae grunts]
- [Koril pants]
Good girl. Get mad.
[witches chattering]
[Rane] She is a child.
The girl has yet to discover
the power she holds.
It's not her decision to make.
But is it ours?
You cannot allow Osha to go.
She has chosen it.
It's what she wants.
You would sacrifice our future
for the wish of a child?
My children are our future.
Her wish must be considered.
You may be their mother,
but you are also our leader.
Right now I choose mother.
[screaming]
[tool clatters]
[young Mae] No one can get in or out!
Witches! Arm yourselves!
[witch] Hurry. This way.
[Sol] Torbin!
I think they've locked the girls inside.
The elevator's been disabled.
[warbling]
[young Mae] You can't go.
We're stuck here now.
- [warbling stops]
- Follow me.
[♪ tense music playing]
You cannot let them in your head again.
Do you understand?
- I need you to help me get the girls.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- [system beeps]
- Hey, give it back!
[door beeps]
Mae, let me out.
- I won't let it happen.
- Mae, please.
No. Mae.
[Indara] There's no way
that we can land the ship there.
If I can get close enough,
- do you think you can make the jump?
- [speaking Shyriiwook]
Go. We must stop him
before he starts a conflict.
Go!
[witches chattering]
[witch 1] Spread into position.
Get everyone in the common room.
Prepare for battle.
What is happening?
The Jedi have breached the fortress again.
[scout] Come with me.
I told you we cannot use violence.
And I told you I would die
before I let the Jedi take my children.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[glass breaks]
What are you doing?
[breathing heavily]
[electricity crackling]
Mama! Mama!
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ tense music playing]
Take another step
and it will be your last.
It was foolish to come back here, Jedi.
We come with noble intentions.
You wish to know
if we will allow Osha to join you.
To be raised
by an institution instead of a family.
The twins, where did they come from?
How were they created?
[bowstring creaks]
Someday, those noble intentions
you all have
will destroy every Jedi in the galaxy.
- Easy, Torbin.
- Fire! Help! Mama! Help!
Osha!
Help me!
[female singer vocalizing]
- No!
- [lightsaber ignites]
[lightsaber ignites]
[gasps]
Mama!
[lightsaber retracts]
[Mother Aniseya breathes heavily]
I was going to let Osha go.
- [exhales sharply]
- It's what she wants.
It's what she wants. [breathes shakily]
She chose you.
- [body thuds]
- No!
Mama! Mama!
[young Mae crying]
Mama! Mama! [cries]
Mae. [yelling] Run!
[lightsaber ignites]
[system trills]
[lightsaber humming]
[Koril grunting]
[Sol grunts]
- [lightsaber humming]
- [weapons firing]
[Koril and Sol grunting]
[yelling] Fight me! [pants]
[sighs]
[breathing shakily]
[Koril grunting]
[explosions booming]
[gasps]
- [gasps]
- [witches screaming]
- [Sol grunts]
- [Koril pants]
- [lightsaber retracts]
- The twins! They're locked inside!
[♪ tense music playing]
It's happening again.
[Koril] You should not
have brought him here.
No. My mind is fortified!
[Koril] Not you.
[Kelnacca speaking Shyriiwook]
[lightsaber ignites]
[female singer vocalizing]
[witches vocalizing]
[lightsaber ignites]
[all grunting]
No, no, no, no, no!
[warbling]
[screams]
[lightsabers crackling]
[Torbin grunting]
[screams]
[screaming]
[grunting]
Kelnacca!
Kelnacca, no!
[both grunting]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Sol shouts, grunts]
[choking]
[witches vocalizing]
[both grunting]
- [groaning]
- [warbling]
[panting]
- [groaning]
- [warbling continues]
[witches vocalizing]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[witches groan]
- [warbling stops]
- [gasps]
[speaking Shyriiwook]
Get the twins.
Master, I...
Get them now. Now!
[electricity crackling]
- [young Mae] Osha!
- Mae!
Mae!
[young Mae] Osha!
Osha! Mae!
Where's Mama?
Mama's dead.
What have you done?
[rumbling]
[yelps]
What have you done?
- Mae! Osha!
- [rumbling]
- [grunts]
- Osha!
- Mae! Mae!
- [young Mae] Osha! [screams]
- Osha!
- Mae!
[strained grunting]
- [young Mae] Osha!
[grunts]
- Osha!
- Mae!
[grunting]
- [young Osha screams]
- [Sol] No!
[young Osha yelps]
[grunts]
Help me! [pants]
[pants] I got you.
[ship whooshing]
[speaking Shyriiwook]
[Torbin] Master...
I'm sorry.
Kelnacca, send a message to Coruscant.
We're going home.
I warned you not to interfere.
I warned both of you.
I wanted the twins to be safe.
With no thought of the consequences.
I had to make a choice.
[both grunting]
Master! Master!
[breathing heavily]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Torbin] What will we tell the Council?
[Sol breathing heavily]
We will tell the Council the truth.
Yeah.
Mae burned down the witches' fortress
and everyone was lost.
Indara, I must face the Council...
Why would you do that to her?
After everything
this little girl has lost tonight,
you'd take away her dream as well?
Before you throw yourself
at the mercy of the Council,
ask yourself why you made this choice.
[young Osha] Mama? Mama!
You're okay, Osha.
Where am I?
We are on our way to Coruscant.
What happened?
[♪ somber music continues]
Mae started a fire.
[♪ downtempo music playing
"The Power of Two"]
♪ Parts of me will die with you ♪
♪ And I think it's gonna be
the good parts ♪
♪ Don't wanna feel at all ♪
♪ Thick skin, big scars ♪
♪ Thought I was tethered to you ♪
♪ You cut it straight to the truth ♪
♪ And we still one in the same ♪
♪ So all my pain is your pain ♪
♪ You thought your soul was a necklace ♪
♪ That you could wear and take off ♪
♪ That you could rip then break off ♪
♪ That you could trade in the dark ♪
♪ But you're my ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ And you feel the same
when they say you're to blame ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ Like war with myself
it's a losing game ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ Twin ♪
♪ Thought I had a life with you ♪
♪ You know the power of two ♪
♪ The power of two ♪
♪ But tell me where was your heart ♪
♪ When you ripped destiny apart? ♪
♪ Thought I was tethered to you ♪
♪ You cut it straight to the truth ♪
♪ And we still one in the same ♪
♪ So all my pain is your pain ♪
♪ You thought your soul was a necklace ♪
♪ That you could wear and take off ♪
♪ That you could rip then break off ♪
♪ That you could trade in the dark ♪
♪ But your my ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ And you feel the same
when they say you're to blame ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ Like war with myself
it's a losing game ♪
♪ The power of two ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ Can you feel the same
when they say you're to blame? ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ Like war with myself
it's a losing game ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I feel the shame
when they call me your name ♪
♪ Ooooooh ♪
♪ And you feel the same
when they say you're to blame ♪
♪ Twin flame ♪
♪ I'm at war with myself
it's a losing game ♪
[song ends]