[Vernestra] Osha has a twin sister?
[Sol] Her name is Mae.
She was presumed dead 16 years ago.
But I believe she is responsible
for Indara's murder.
Go investigate.
She wants to kill four Jedi.
Indara, Torbin, Kelnacca, and you.
[Jecki] How well do you know Osha?
[Sol] Brendok.
I was there when her sister started a fire
that killed her entire family.
I will stop them.
No one's taking me.
- The Jedi are bad.
- The Jedi are good.
What have you done?
[bridge rattles]
- Osha!
- Mae!
- No!
- [Osha yelps]
[Mae] I have two Jedi to kill
after Torbin.
And I will kill one of them
without a weapon and please the Master.
Oshie?
- Osha's alive.
- I know.
Khofar. A relaxing forest retreat
in the Outer Rim.
[growling]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[creatures chittering, chirping]
[♪ mysterious music continues]
[object clanking]
[sizzling]
[♪ ominous music playing]
Keep each movement tight yet subtle.
Diminish areas of vulnerability.
Maximize your defenses
without need to strike.
[chiming]
That's our time.
Daro, Rena, I want to see
your opening stance before you leave.
[Jecki] Osha.
I came to say goodbye.
You're not staying?
[Osha] I've done what I needed to do.
- Thank you.
- For what?
For helping me find my sister.
Prove my innocence. Clear my name.
I was just doing my duty.
I may never have known for certain
Mae was alive.
And thanks to you,
I've seen her with my own eyes.
Even if I failed to stop her.
I figured you'd stay
until we apprehended her.
I mean, you must be curious,
after all this time.
Mae is the Jedi's problem now.
And I'm not a Jedi.
Don't tell me you'll miss me.
[both chuckle]
You care about Mae.
You mourn the years lost
between the two of you.
Someone must find Mae
before she does any more harm.
But it's not me.
I just... I can't.
Next time I'm on Coruscant, though,
I'll look you up.
And we'll go to a cantina
and trade stories about Master Sol.
Did you say goodbye to him?
I've caused him enough trouble.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[ship rumbling]
[Qimir] Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
I wouldn't just take off, if I were you.
Khofar is massively uncharted.
I know bounty hunters
who won't set foot in these forests.
Oh, but you have?
Yes, I have.
To find the Wookiee. And it was hard.
That is one Jedi
who doesn't wanna be found.
- [♪ uneasy music playing]
- [creatures screeching]
You went in there
and risked your life for my Master?
No. I risked my life to help you.
Admit it. You need me.
You know, your sister being alive
doesn't change anything.
You need to kill the Wookiee.
You made a deal.
There's three hours of sunlight left.
Let's get going.
Okay. Follow me.
[♪ uneasy music continues]
[Jedi 1] Who is she?
[Jedi 2] No idea.
[Holden] She is fast, but weak.
Her emotions guide
her every choice in combat.
- Yet there is skill there.
- [Sol] Yes.
Someone has trained her.
But who?
She doesn't know her Master's identity.
But she fears him.
An apprentice
who doesn't know their Master?
It's absurd.
Could this be a splinter Order?
Or something worse?
- [group muttering]
- If they're a splinter Order, we'd know.
This girl could become a major threat.
She is not disciplined.
Yet, she eluded you.
And she killed two Jedi Masters.
[holoprojector beeping]
Yes, but Mae targeted these three...
Four. Including you, Sol.
The four Jedi stationed on her home planet
when she was a child.
How odd.
She turns up all these years later,
trained by one of our own.
You think a Jedi taught her?
Even a hologram can tell me that.
We must alert the High Council.
The High Council would be obliged
to inform the Senate.
A scandal like this
would inspire fear and mistrust.
We should handle this ourselves.
We must learn who trained her.
Master Holden, extract Kelnacca
from his post on Khofar and intercept Mae.
[Holden] And if she doesn't
come peacefully?
[Vernestra] I'm not expecting it
to come to that.
This meeting is adjourned.
[holoprojector beeps]
Master Vernestra, please.
[inhales sharply] Why didn't you
tell me about this?
- I did! As soon as I knew...
- No, Sol.
Sixteen years ago,
why didn't you tell me there was a chance
this poor girl survived?
If I thought there was,
of course I would have.
But I saw her fall.
No one could've survived that.
Let me be the one to bring her in.
Your personal connection with her
and her sister is not a benefit here.
Mae's objective is not solely her own.
You must know that.
I fear Mae is only a small part
of her Master's larger plan.
A plan that is difficult to see.
Some sort of shift.
Something to tip the scales.
If she resists arrest
and Holden neutralizes her...
It won't come to that.
Then her Master will truly be lost to us.
She will not surrender
without getting something in return.
Do we have something she wants?
[Qimir] How do you kill a Jedi
without a weapon?
It has to be some sort of test, right?
You engage unarmed, but can you
use their saber if you disarm them?
Or is that cheating?
I'm just curious how you're gonna
do it this time. You've failed so much.
I didn't fail.
I killed Indara and I killed Torbin.
But you killed them "your way."
You have to kill the Wookiee
without a weapon.
- Your Master wants you to...
- What kind of deal did you make with him?
I didn't. Uh, we didn't exactly.
I... I just owe him.
You know how he is, he collects people.
I've never seen his face. Have you?
You know I haven't.
Oh, look, there it is. The perimeter.
I can't believe my sister's Jedi scum.
What was she like when you spoke to her?
She seemed in over her head, honestly.
She seemed really fond
of that one Jedi Master.
What was his name again? Sol?
Anyways, let's get going.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
I'm glad we got you serviced.
It's like the day we met!
[Pip beeping]
Yeah, I would do that
if I had the tools, Pip.
- But I don't have those, all right?
- Osha!
[Pip beeping]
Sol.
I went to find you
and Jecki said you already left.
I'm sorry I didn't say goodbye.
I need your help.
I need you
to come with me on this mission.
You want me to rejoin the Jedi?
Well, not officially.
Oh.
You need me, so you can get to her.
Sol, I can't.
When I told Mae you were alive,
her eyes softened.
She became a different person.
If you come,
they will allow us both to go.
I don't want Mae to get hurt.
I know you don't, either.
There is still good in her.
The part of her that loves you.
She's a murderer.
But she is still your family.
Fine.
[exhales softly]
But I am not wearing that civilian robe.
The Order stationed
Master Kelnacca on Khofar,
but no one has heard from him
in over a year.
He's been unresponsive
to our warning transmissions.
Communication towers in the area
may be down.
[Pip beeping]
- Due to the difficulty of this mission...
- [sniffing]
- ...I advise all of you to stick together.
- [Pip beeping]
Shh.
[roars]
[mechanical whirring]
[yelps, snorts]
[whispering] Hey! I'm so sorry.
[grunts, sighs]
[sniffs]
Who is that?
That's Bazil.
Is he, or they, with us?
[Yord clears throat]
Any questions, civilian?
No. No. Very comprehensive briefing, Yord.
Hmm.
[ship whooshes]
[♪ captivating music playing]
We're looking for a Wookiee.
He's big and hairy.
- [device translates alien language]
- [speaking alien language]
You're gonna need
to hand that blaster over.
Well, it's mine now.
It's actually
the property of the Jedi Order.
So, I'm afraid I'm going to have
to insist that you hand it over.
[alien speaking alien language]
The locals say he ventured off
into the forest and never came back.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
Kelnacca is in there.
[wind blowing]
[Osha] How do we find him?
We have a tracker.
[Bazil sniffing]
[breathes deeply, snarls]
[♪ exciting music playing]
Yord. Yord. Yord. Do you understand
what the Bazil is saying?
His name is Bazil. And yes.
Although most Padawans
want to learn Shyriiwook,
I took it upon myself to learn a language
a little more nuanced.
Okay, well, if you're upset
I'm on this mission, join the club.
I'm not upset.
I am concerned for your safety.
Yord, I need to ask you a favor.
Sol thinks that Mae can be saved.
Master Sol is a wise Jedi.
He must have reason to suspect
Mae will listen to what you have to say.
But if it comes to it,
and she doesn't listen to me,
you need to stop her.
I won't be able to do it.
- Osha...
- Please.
I can't hesitate a second time.
I've known you since we were younglings.
Mae has always been your wound.
Maybe Sol brought you here to face her,
but maybe he brought you here
to face yourself.
We need to catch up.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[creatures chittering]
Come on.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Bazil sniffing]
[Bazil speaks Tynnan]
- [growls]
- [Jedi] What is it?
[Bazil speaks Tynnan]
He says there's something wrong here.
Something rotten.
Keep up the pace, keep down the volume.
We don't know, and we don't want to know
what lives out here.
[Pip beeping]
[Jecki] Osha.
[creature chitters]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[creature snarls]
[creature screeches, snarls]
Sol!
[creature snarls]
[creature chitters]
[screeching]
Stand down!
- [umbramoth screeches]
- [lightsaber ignites]
I have it.
[umbramoth screeching]
- [lightsaber hums]
- [umbramoth thuds]
- It went straight for the saber.
- It's attracted to light.
[panting] Let's move.
It'll be dark soon.
[umbramoth chitters]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
What is it?
Um...
I was able to sense that creature.
But I disturbed it, and now it's dead.
It's always an honor to get
to witness anything or anyone
transform into the Force.
Although you've had more experience
with death than I have.
Well, I could never accept death
as a true Jedi should.
A true Jedi?
I couldn't accept what I'd lost.
How unfair it felt.
The resentment that I felt for my sister,
even though I missed her,
at the same time.
We're not defined by what we lose.
We're defined by what we survive.
You've survived a lot.
[♪ gentle music playing]
Come on, it's not too far.
Probably ten minutes south of here.
We're just gonna make it.
[Qimir panting]
No. No, no, no. You can't stop now.
[Mae panting]
I have to fight a Wookiee after this trek.
I'd like to rest for a minute,
if that's all right with you.
It's not, but okay.
[breathing heavily]
It's not a test.
What?
He calls it the "final lesson."
He says, "Your final lesson
is one you teach yourself.
"You will kill a Jedi without a weapon."
Attacking a defenseless person goes
against everything the Jedi stands for.
How do you kill someone
like that? Unarmed?
It's not a test. It's impossible.
It's...
It's not impossible. You know that.
I want this more than anything,
but it's impossible.
And if I don't do it, he'll kill me.
You don't even care.
I care.
Here.
I'm gonna find you more water.
You're right.
You need to rest.
You're losing your nerve.
And we can't have that, can we?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I don't see him.
- What?
- Bazil.
Great, he's vanished again.
[sighs] I swear, we need a tracker
just to track our tracker.
Sol!
- We've lost Bazil...
- [Mae screaming]
[Mae] Help!
[Qimir] Mae!
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[yelping]
Help! Help!
[Qimir panting]
Mae. Mae! Mae! Help!
[Qimir grunts]
You know, after running through
that forest for an extremely long time,
I realized something.
I don't need to do this anymore.
I don't need to kill a Jedi
without a weapon.
- I don't need to keep this deal.
- What?
Hey! Cut me down!
You were wrong.
Osha being alive changes everything.
My loyalty is to Osha. Not your Master.
What are you...
What are you doing? [grunts]
What I'm going to do
is surrender myself to Kelnacca.
- And then turn myself in to the Jedi.
- No. No, no, no. No, stop. Stop.
It's ten minutes south, right?
The Jedi will put you in prison.
Not after I tell them who I know.
He'll kill you.
He'd have to find me first.
And I don't know if even he could make it
all the way over here without a guide.
I'll have to admit it.
I did need you.
[Qimir grunts]
Mae! Mae!
[♪ mysterious music playing]
She couldn't have gone far.
Where could she be?
I don't know.
- Where is Bazil?
- I don't know, Padawan.
[♪ mysterious music continues]
What is it?
[panting] It's nothing.
You wouldn't let me confront Mae on Olega?
You weren't ready.
But I'm ready now?
This is different.
I feel different.
I sense things again in a way
that gives me the courage to face her.
You're not going to face her.
You're going to face your past.
[Sol breathes heavily]
Both of us will.
Once we get Mae safely to the ship,
I'll explain everything.
I promise.
[Mae panting]
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Mae grunts]
[Bazil sniffing]
Hey, little buddy.
[Bazil roars]
[Bazil calls out]
He's found Mae.
[calls out, roars]
[calling out]
[Jecki] Go, go, go!
[Yord] Osha.
- Stay behind us.
- [Jedi] This way.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Bazil calling out]
[Jedi] Through here. Quickly.
[panting] Master Kelnacca!
[♪ uneasy music playing]
He's here.
[breathing shakily]
[Jedi] Over there!
[Jecki] Master Kelnacca!
[♪ tense music playing]
[Jedi] In the name
of the Galactic Republic,
and the Order of the Jedi,
anyone inside that domicile
should come out with your hands
where we can see them.
That means you, Mae Aniseya.
[rumbling]
[♪ tense music continues]
What is that?
Identify yourself.
Stand down.
[Mae panting]
[lightsaber ignites]
[lightsabers ignite]
Osha, run!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ mysterious music playing]