Extract Kelnacca from his post on Khofar
and intercept Mae.
I need your help.
I need you
to come with me on this mission.
Kelnacca is in there.
[Osha] How do we find him?
[Yord] We have a tracker.
If it comes to it,
and she doesn't listen to me,
you need to stop her.
I can't hesitate a second time.
We're not defined by what we lose.
We're defined by what we survive.
You've survived a lot.
Keep down the volume.
We don't want to know what lives out here.
-Sol!
-[umbramoth screeches]
-[lightsaber ignites]
-[screeching]
-[lightsaber hums]
-[umbramoth thuds]
You were wrong.
Osha being alive changes everything.
-I'll turn myself over to the Jedi.
-He'll kill you.
[Mae] He'd have to find me first.
He's here.
[lightsaber ignites]
[lightsabers ignite]
Osha, run!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[groans softly]
[gasps]
Pip?
[Pip beeping]
You're all right?
Shh.
[distant lightsabers humming]
-[grunts]
-[Pip beeping]
[gasps]
[♪ dramatic chord plays]
[panting]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[lightsabers clashing]
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[grunting]
[Jedi 1 groans]
[lightsabers crackling]
[lightsabers sputtering]
[Yord grunts]
[lightsabers clashing]
[Yord shouts, groans]
[lightsabers crackle, hum]
[grunting]
[Jedi 2 groans]
[groans]
[lightsaber humming]
[grunts, panting]
[♪ ominous music playing]
Osha, run!
[♪ tense music playing]
[breathes shakily]
[panting]
[Pip beeping]
-[rustling]
-[Pip beeps]
[panting]
[leaves rustling]
[lightsaber ignites]
[Osha panting]
[lightsaber retracts]
[♪ tense music playing]
[trees snap]
Civilian to the ship.
[Osha grunts]
Civilian, to the ship.
[lightsaber humming]
[♪ dramatic choral music playing]
[chittering]
Bazil! Come on, let's follow him.
-[chitters]
-Yord! We have to go back.
[sighs]
-You're injured.
-I'm fine.
Sol gave me an order.
Osha. I don't want to
have to subdue you but I will.
Come on.
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[stranger] Master Sol.
Who are you?
[stranger] You... don't remember me?
I sense something familiar.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[lightsabers clashing]
[stranger breathing heavily]
[panting]
You carry a Jedi weapon.
But you are no Jedi.
[♪ tense music playing]
-[Jecki shouts]
-[Mae grunts]
[both grunting]
[Mae shouts]
You're under arrest for the murder
of Master Indara,
-the murder of...
-[screams]
[Jecki grunting]
[Jecki panting]
-The murder of Master Torbin...
-[grunting]
...the murder of Master Kelnacca,
and the fire that killed your family.
[Mae screams]
[grunting]
[lightsabers clashing]
[lightsaber retracts]
[stranger breathing heavily]
You trained Mae.
Show your face.
[stranger] And let you read my thoughts?
No. No. No.
What Master hides his face from his pupil?
[stranger] You tell me.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[grunting]
[Jecki shouts]
[Jecki screams]
-Jecki.
-Jecki is a Jedi.
She can take care of herself.
I need to get you to safety.
That thing is too dangerous.
[lightsabers clashing]
[gasps, panting]
[lightsaber ignites]
[panting]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What is he, Yord?
I don't know.
He doesn't follow the rules of combat.
And there's no method
to his movements, it...
It doesn't make sense.
He gets into your head and he stays there.
My mother could do that.
Get inside a Jedi's head.
I saw it once.
We have to keep moving.
-[Pip beeping]
-Where's Bazil?
Come on! Keep moving.
[both grunting]
[breathing shakily]
[Jecki grunting]
[grunts]
[beeps]
You took Master Kelnacca's saber?
[wind blowing]
-[lightsaber ignites]
-[stranger shouts]
[lightsabers clashing]
[Jecki grunts]
[stranger] Mae, you can learn
from this Padawan.
She's a loyal pupil.
[grunting]
[lightsaber sputters]
[lightsabers crackling]
[grunting]
[panting]
[lightsabers clashing]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Jecki shouting]
[lightsaber sizzles]
Yord.
[lightsaber humming]
Turn off your saber.
Do it. The light attracts them.
[Yord] Attracts what?
[rustling, chittering]
[lightsaber retracts]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[softly] We go slowly.
[panting]
[♪ tense music playing]
-[stranger] Coward.
-[yelps]
You were going to betray me.
[Mae shouts]
Forgive me.
Master, I was weak.
[stranger] You've always been weak.
[Mae yelps]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-[stranger breathing heavily]
-[lightsaber hums]
-[stranger grunts]
-[Jecki shouts]
[grunting]
[Mae panting]
[gasps, grunts]
[Jecki shouts]
-[panting]
-[lightsabers clashing]
[little Mae] Osha.
Osha. What is it?
We have to go back.
Please, don't.
He's gonna kill them.
He's gonna kill them all.
[rustling, chittering]
[umbramoths screeching]
Follow me.
Run!
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[lightsabers clashing]
[grunting]
[Jecki screams]
[shouts]
No!
[♪ ominous music playing]
[lightsaber retracts]
[gasps]
Jecki.
Was that its name?
[breathing heavily]
She was a child.
You brought her here.
Hello.
[gasping]
You really didn't know it was me?
Not even deep down?
-[lightsabers clashing]
-[grunting]
-[lightsaber retracts]
-[Mae gasping]
You attack me while my back is turned?
Not very Jedi of you.
-[grunts, panting]
-[lightsaber retracts]
What are you?
I have no name.
But the Jedi like you
might call me... Sith.
[panting]
Why risk discovery?
Well, I...
I did wear a mask.
What do you want?
Freedom.
[Mae yelps]
The freedom to wield my power
the way I like.
Without having to answer to Jedi like you.
[breathing heavily]
I want a pupil,
an Acolyte.
-But this one...
-[gasping]
went back on our deal.
She exposed me.
So, now I have to kill
every single last one of you.
[Mae grunting, panting]
I don't make the rules.
The Jedi do.
And the Jedi say I can't exist.
They see my face, they all die.
Aw, look at you two.
Right back where you started.
[lightsabers humming]
-[grunting]
-[lightsabers crackling]
You.
Surprise.
[Yord shouting]
[neck cracks]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Mae grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[shouts]
[both grunting]
[shouting]
[groaning]
[lightsaber ignites]
[Osha] Sol!
Osha.
This is your Master?
You trust him
even after everything he did to you?
His mind is twisted by darkness.
I've accepted my darkness.
What have you done with yours?
[umbramoth chittering]
[Pip beeping]
Sol.
[umbramoths chittering]
The Jedi do not attack the unarmed.
[sighs] Rules, rules, rules.
If you never follow them,
you never have to break them.
[umbramoths chittering]
-I love you, Pip.
-[Pip beeping]
-[stranger grunts]
-[grunting]
[umbramoths chittering]
[grunting]
[umbramoths screeching]
Why did he say that?
Sol?
Why did he say I shouldn't trust you?
What did you do?
Please, Osha.
I'll explain.
[Sol thuds]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
Osha.
What have you done?
I... I did what I needed to do.
For you.
For our family.
Everything you've ever done
has been for yourself.
All of these lives lost tonight.
Again. All because of you.
The Jedi got what they deserved.
Those Jedi were more my family
than you ever were.
Have you forgotten who we are?
Where we come from?
They invaded our home.
Invaded?
Mae, no.
You're the violent one.
You started that fire.
And I would have been dead too
if it weren't for the Jedi.
They've brainwashed you.
They've turned you against me.
But it's okay, Osha.
I can help you.
I can help you return to yourself.
[Mae breathing shakily]
I love you.
Don't choose them again.
Please choose me.
Choose us.
[♪ gentle music playing]
We both survived.
All we have is each other now.
[Mae gasps, pants]
You're a criminal, Mae.
You must pay for your crimes.
What're you doing?
[Osha] What I came here to do. Arrest you.
Don't do this.
You did this to yourself.
You followed a false Master.
So did you.
[Osha panting]
Leave Sol out of this.
He stole you from us.
He saved my life.
And what kind of life is that, huh?
A life without purpose?
Without love, without family.
He led you nowhere. He's...
[Osha grunts]
[panting]
You never could block.
[lightsaber ignites]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[female chorus vocalizing]
[umbramoths screeching]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[lightsaber retracts]
[Bazil chittering]
[sniffs]
[chittering]
[coughing]
Sol? Are you all right?
Where is she?
Who?
Your sister.
She's gone.
We must get to the ship.
Here.
Let me help you.
[Sol grunts]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[panting]
Let's go.
[aliens speaking alien language]
[creatures shrieking, chittering]
[sniffing]
[chittering]
[♪ uneasy music playing]
What extraordinary beings we are.
Even in the revelation of our triumph,
you see the depth of our despair.