[Sol] The twins... how were they created?
I fear for the girls' safety.
Only a vergence
could create that type of power.
[gasps]
[witches groan]
[Torbin] What will we tell the Council?
Mae burned down the witches' fortress
and everyone was lost.
[Vernestra] How odd.
Turns up all these years later,
trained by one of our own.
I fear Mae is only a small part
of her Master's larger plan.
[Mae] He says, "Your final lesson
is one you teach yourself.
"You will kill a Jedi without a weapon."
Have you forgotten who we are?
Where we come from?
They've brainwashed you.
[Sol] We need to find your Master.
But first, you and I are going to talk.
Below the surface of consciousness
are powerful emotions.
Anger. Fear.
Desire.
That's the path to the dark side.
[stranger]
A sensory deprivation headpiece.
Try it on. So it's just you and the Force.
And what you bring with you.
[Osha breathing heavily]
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[chuckles lightly]
[Osha gasps, breathes heavily]
Osha?
[Osha gasping]
[breathing shakily]
No!
[shuddering]
[Osha gasping]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[inhales sharply]
[shuddering]
[stranger grunts, inhales sharply]
[yells, breathing heavily]
Mae. I saw Mae.
She had her hand outstretched.
She was killing Sol.
Where is she?
She had a saber in her hand.
But she didn't use it.
This is the future you saw.
She can kill with no weapon.
But the future isn't fixed.
I can still stop her.
With what ship? I'm taking mine.
And going where, exactly?
I've seen where they are.
So we go together.
And see who gets to her first.
[Mae] Where are we?
[sighs] Brendok.
Why?
[Sol] I will contact Master Vernestra.
The Jedi will meet us here.
Why?
There is a vergence on this planet.
Now that you and Osha are both alive,
I can prove it.
Prove it?
Prove what?
That murdering our mother was justified?
What happened to you,
- to your coven was an accident.
- [whirring]
An accident?
- If it was an accident...
- [whirring]
...then why didn't you tell Osha?
Why did you lie to her?
Why did you blame it on me?
You started that fire.
You locked everyone in.
Because the Jedi invaded our home.
[Pip beeping]
Everyone in there died
because of the four of you.
It was right for us to intervene.
[Pip beeping]
My biggest regret
is that I wasn't able to save you both.
You and Osha are not twins.
You're not even sisters.
[restraints hum]
You're... [shouts]
- [Pip crackles]
- [Sol grunting]
[Sol groans]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Bazil sniffs, chitters]
[Mae panting]
[Pip beeping]
- [chimes]
- [Mae] The escape ship!
[Bazil grunts]
Mae!
See you in hell, Jedi.
[Pip beeping]
[system beeps, powers up]
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
- [breathes heavily]
- [ship whooshing]
[button clicks]
- [system beeps]
- [mechanical whirring]
[ship whooshes]
[Pip beeping]
- I wish this thing had a hyperdrive.
- [ship accelerating]
[♪ rousing music playing]
[Pip beeping]
He's too big to follow us in here.
[♪ thrilling music playing]
[Pip beeping]
- [grunts]
- [ship accelerating]
[grunting]
[speaks Tynnan]
[system beeping]
[♪ thrilling music continues]
[Pip beeping]
[asteroids thudding]
[system beeping]
[ship accelerating]
[cables snap]
[alarm blares]
[ship rumbles]
[speaking Tynnan]
[Mae] Brace yourself, Pip.
[Pip beeping]
[alarm blaring]
[ship crashing]
Master Vernestra, uh,
Senator Rayencourt's here to see you.
Where is he?
Um, he's in there.
You let him in the control room?
[Mog] Hmm.
[Vernestra] Senator.
Apologies for my intrusion.
[Vernestra] Not at all.
I was surprised when they said
you were traveling through hyperspace.
How is your stomach?
It's my head, actually. And I'm fine.
This must be urgent to wait for me here.
I've heard some disturbing things.
What have you heard?
That you are running
a murder investigation
without reporting it to the Senate.
I'm keeping this internal for the moment.
I have the authority
to take independent action
if there's no larger threat.
How can you know
there is no larger threat?
[Vernestra] All the victims were Jedi.
There are multiple victims?
I am very close
to apprehending the suspect.
Is the suspect a Jedi?
Very close. Thank you for your concern.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
You don't like me.
You think my campaign
for an external review of the Jedi
is a personal vendetta.
If you want my honest opinion, yes.
Good. Here's mine.
I think the Jedi are a massive system
of unchecked power, posing as a religion,
a delusional cult that claims
to control the uncontrollable.
- We don't control the Force.
- [Rayencourt] Not the Force.
Your emotions.
You project an image
of goodness and restraint,
but it's only a matter of time
before one of you snaps.
And when, not "if", that happens,
who will be strong enough to stop him?
That's certainly an opinion
and not one shared
by the rest of the Senate.
The majority of my colleagues
can't imagine a galaxy without the Jedi.
And I can understand why.
When you're looking up to heroes,
you don't have to face
what's right in front of you.
Is that all, Senator?
I have reported your lack of transparency
to Chancellor Drellik.
He may invite you
to a Senate tribunal for an update.
I hope, for your sake,
you have this suspect in custody by then.
Good luck.
No, what is it you say?
"May the Force be with you."
[door closes]
[chittering]
[stranger] So you're really not going
to tell me where we're going.
[Osha] We go together
or we don't go at all.
That seems fair.
Did I give you the impression
that I was a fair person?
Yes, you did.
You made a deal with my sister
and you expected her to uphold it.
That's fair. And so is this.
Osha.
You should be trained.
Would you ever consider?
No.
Last chance.
I told you, I'm not my sister.
You're definitely not.
Mae made that deal
without even thinking about it.
[♪ uneasy music playing]
[ship whooshing]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[creature squawking]
[system beeps]
[system beeping]
[♪ somber music playing]
[clicks]
[system beeping]
[♪ uneasy music playing]
- [breathes deeply]
- [Force whirring]
[whirring stops]
[Bazil sniffing]
I know he is,
but I need to get a message to him.
It's urgent.
[man over comms] This is highly
unorthodox, but I shall see what I can do.
[comms beeps]
Master Vernestra, we found Master Sol.
He's turned his transponder
beacon back on.
- Where is he?
- Brendok.
[sighs]
Prepare my ship.
Gather as many Knights as you can
without raising alarm.
You anticipate a confrontation?
A resolution.
[ship whooshes]
[♪ tense music playing]
[stranger over comms]
All the way back home.
- [beeps]
- [system powers down]
[clicks]
[Osha] There's no spaceport,
but there's a landing site
near our fortress.
[system beeping]
They're already there.
[system beeps]
[ship rumbling]
[♪ intriguing music playing]
[shouting] Mae!
[little Mae] Mama!
No!
[♪ solemn music playing]
Getting this elevator operational
is the only way in.
Unless you want to climb.
[stranger] Are you sure?
[♪ eerie music playing]
[♪ solemn music playing]
[female singer vocalizing]
[sighs]
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts, breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[shouting] Mae!
- [gasps]
- [Pip beeping]
[Pip beeping]
[wires crackling]
[system beeping]
[elevator powers up]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Sol breathing heavily]
[shouting] Mae!
[stranger] Thank you
for leading me to her.
We make a great team.
[lightsaber ignites]
[lightsabers humming]
[♪ tense music playing]
[both grunting]
[stranger breathing heavily]
[lightsabers clashing]
[stranger grunts]
[breathes heavily]
I will destroy you if I must.
[stranger] Not if she gets you first.
[lightsaber hums]
[lightsaber ignites]
[lightsabers humming]
[both grunting]
[lightsaber ignites]
[stranger grunts]
[lightsabers humming]
[lightsaber retracts]
[♪ triumphant music playing]
[stranger grunts]
[lightsaber ignites]
[♪ tense music playing]
- [lightsaber clicks, ignites]
- [stranger grunting]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Mae] Osha.
Listen to me.
All of this death.
Everything that happened here,
all because you didn't want me
to become a Jedi.
I didn't do this.
- Sol lied to you. He blamed me...
- Sol never blamed you.
He tried to teach me to accept
that someone that I love
could be capable
of this level of destruction.
And I failed.
I could never learn
to calm my negative emotions.
My hatred of you,
my grief over our mother.
So I never became a Jedi.
And, I guess,
in the end you got what you wanted.
Sol killed our mother.
I saw it with my own eyes.
He's lied to you.
Every day since you left our home.
How could he teach you
to control your negative emotions?
He's the reason you have them.
You didn't fail.
He did.
[breathing heavily]
[Osha yells, grunts]
[both grunting]
[♪ thrilling music playing]
- Pip!
- [Pip beeping]
[female singer vocalizing]
[screams, panting]
[panting]
[both grunting]
[lightsabers clashing]
- [stranger breathing heavily]
- [ship whooshing]
[lightsaber humming]
Now you pay for what you've done.
[stranger] Oh, they're not here for me.
[both grunting]
[female singer vocalizing]
[ship whooshing]
[stranger grunts]
[lightsabers clashing]
[both grunting]
[lightsabers crackling]
[lightsabers screeching]
[lightsabers humming]
[lightsaber sizzling]
[stranger breathing heavily]
[lightsaber thuds]
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[lightsaber humming]
[Mae grunting]
[Sol panting]
[breathing heavily]
[stranger] Good, Mae.
Feel your anger.
This is the source of your pain.
Strike him down
and your journey will be complete.
[♪ ominous music playing]
No.
I want him to confess what he did.
I want him to face the High Council.
The Senate. The Republic.
I want him to pay for his crimes.
I did the right thing.
I wanted to protect you both.
From what?
You are not twins.
You and Osha are the same person.
I don't know how your mother did it.
But it has something to do
with a vergence on this planet.
How she did what?
She created life.
Your lives.
I believe she used the Force
to create you and Osha.
Do you have any idea
what kind of power that is?
In the history of the galaxy,
very few have been that powerful.
And you killed her.
You killed our mother.
I...
[sighs] Yes.
[sighs]
I did.
[Osha breathes shakily]
Is that true?
I was protecting you.
It was the right thing to do.
If it was the right thing to do,
why didn't you tell the Jedi?
Without Mae, there was no proof
you were created in this way.
Why didn't you tell me?
They would have sent you away.
You were too old to train.
They never
would have let you become a Jedi.
I did what I thought was best for you.
Of course, I wanted to tell you
so many times, but I couldn't.
Stop talking.
I kept this from you
so you could have the life
you'd always dreamed of.
I did everything because I... [chokes]
[chokes]
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[choking]
[Force whirring]
Stop talking.
[♪ somber music playing]
[Sol choking]
[lightsaber rattling]
Osha.
It's okay.
[Sol groaning]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[sobbing]
[breathing heavily]
[♪ uneasy music playing]
- [lightsaber ignites]
- [Osha screams]
[sinister music playing]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Force whirring]
[gasps] You!
You're alive.
I know where they are. Follow me.
[Bazil speaking Tynnan]
Bazil, you're all right. What a relief!
- [lightsaber humming]
- Osha, we need to leave.
- Come with me.
- [lightsaber retracts]
I know a way out.
[♪ tense music playing]
[door beeping]
- [Force whirs]
- [system beeps]
[Jedi] This way.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[♪ tense music playing]
We have to climb down there.
[Osha] Are you sure?
Trust me.
When I fell,
I got sucked into this core tunnel.
Come this way.
[♪ solemn music playing]
[Mother Aniseya] No!
[little Mae] Mama!
[little Osha] What have you done?
[Koril] You should not
have brought him here.
- [Kelnacca speaking Shyriiwook]
- [Sol] Kelnacca, no!
[Indara] Get the twins. Get them now.
You two, search the premises.
[Jedi 1] Yes, Master.
The rest of you set up
a five klick perimeter.
They couldn't have gotten far.
[Jedi 2] This way.
Use the tracker.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Osha] You did all this
when you were little?
[Mae] Yeah.
Then what did you do?
[♪ tense music playing]
[Bazil chitters]
[Bazil sniffs, speaks Tynnan]
[both panting]
[♪ gentle music playing]
I sat here. And I waited.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
I'm sorry I started that fire.
[Osha crying]
"You are with me. I am with you."
Who taught us that rhyme?
I thought you made it up.
[Force whirring]
[stranger] If I can find you,
so can the Jedi.
[speaks Tynnan]
[♪ rousing music playing]
We'll explain what Sol did.
- They'll have to...
- [stranger] Even after everything,
you put your faith in the Jedi?
Osha, when they find out
how powerful you are...
You will meet the same fate as our mother.
What do we do?
What do you want, Osha?
[♪ pensive music playing]
Let my sister go
and I will train with you.
Are you sure?
The Jedi will use me to find you.
[Bazil sniffing]
[Bazil speaks Tynnan]
[Jedi] Go! Go!
[Bazil chittering]
[stranger] I can attempt
to wipe her memory.
Remove any trace of you or me.
Permanently.
[Bazil speaking Tynnan distantly]
Do it.
Quickly.
I can't lose you again.
You're not.
You're going to do
what you were meant to do.
But I won't stop you this time.
[♪ rousing music playing]
Wait.
[breathes deeply]
[sobbing]
I will find you.
I know you will.
[sobbing]
"You are with me."
"I am with you." [sniffles]
[Osha] "Always one."
"Born as two."
[Force whirs]
[Osha] "As above sits the stars..."
"And below lies the..."
[whirring stops]
[Osha sniffles]
"I give you you."
"And you give..."
"You... You give..."
[Bazil sniffs, speaks Tynnan]
Don't move.
Lay down any weapons that you have
and surrender.
You're under arrest.
What did I do?
[Pip beeping]
Remove her restraints.
[restraints beep]
Leave us.
[door closes]
Please sit, Mae.
Do you know why you're here?
They say I... I killed someone.
But I... I don't remember.
What do you remember?
A fire.
It...
It destroyed my... my home.
I'm seeing a man.
He... He killed my mother.
So I run away.
There's someone that I need to tell,
but I can't... I can't find her.
Your last memory
is from when you were eight years old.
That man who killed your mother
was a Jedi.
He was my friend.
He was a kind, brilliant,
compassionate man.
And he did a terrible thing.
Sixteen years ago, four Jedi
were stationed on the planet Brendok.
There they discovered
a Force cult of witches.
A conflict ensued.
There were many casualties.
Afterwards, the Jedi conspired
to keep their actions secret.
Recently, when the truth
threatened to come out,
a rogue Jedi named Sol
killed his accomplices
to maintain the cover story.
I'm sorry, my friend.
Speaking on behalf of the High Council,
we wholly condemn
the actions of Master Sol.
I think in light
of these events, Chancellor,
we cannot wait for a full Senate vote.
An external review of the Jedi
must begin immediately.
- [group chattering]
- I can assure you,
while this is a terrible tragedy,
it was the work of one flawed man.
And where is Master Sol now?
He was found dead on Brendok.
At the scene of his original crime.
I believe he ended his own life.
[♪ mournful music playing]
Sol made a mistake.
A mistake he lived with
for so long it twisted his mind.
He justified every selfish step
with the love he had for your sister.
My sister?
Does the name Osha mean anything?
You poor girl.
You've been through so much.
The Jedi have failed you.
I am going to make this right.
- But I need your help.
- [Mae] With what?
I need you to help me find someone.
Who?
A pupil of mine before he turned to evil.
[♪ somber music playing]
[♪ tense violin music playing]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Sorry to disturb you, Master.
We need to talk.
[♪ haunting music playing]
[witches singing]
♪ The power of one ♪
♪ The power of two ♪
♪ The power of many ♪
♪ The power of one ♪
♪ The power of two ♪
♪ The power of many ♪
♪ The power of one ♪
♪ The power of two
The power of many ♪
- ♪ The power of many ♪
- ♪ The power of two ♪
♪ The power of one ♪
♪ The power of two ♪
♪ The power of many ♪
♪ The power of one
The power of two ♪
- ♪ The power of many ♪
- [witch vocalizing]