APPLAUSE
Hello, hello, everybody.
Thank you so much, thank you.
Thanks very much.
We're back!
APPLAUSE
We're back! We're back
with a new-look Top Gear.
We have changed everything.
And to give you a taste of what you
can expect over the coming weeks,
we have prepared a little montage.
Tally-ho, tally-ho, chaps.
They are all over me!
At Twickenham, for England!
We might actually just
be in with a chance.
Let's do this for
Carroll Shelby, come on!
You will find
the source of the River Nile.
Here we are, ladies, at
the bowling club. Oh, lovely.
And, stop. Oh, I am so on board.
There's nobody driving!
The last to arrive will cross
into Mexico...
Hello. I've accidentally
painted a gentleman's
sausage on a storm drain.
'Oh, my.'
Big jump, whoa!
APPLAUSE
We haven't changed anything,
have we? No. Not really.
Wait, I have bought a new jacket.
You have new shoes.
I'm in my 50s now. James, to be
fair, you were born in your 50s.
To be honest,
James turned 50 just last week.
Yeah.
APPLAUSE
Why are you applauding?
All he had to do to get to 50
was not die,
and the speed he drives,
that's not difficult.
Anyway, we have a tremendous series
coming up, some amazing races,
some incredible challenges
and, of course, some brilliant cars.
And we start with
the best of them all.
The Pagani Zonda is
my favourite supercar.
But it's been around
for a decade now,
and for the last few years,
Pagani have been promising again
and again that they will replace it
with a brand-new car.
And now, finally, they have.
It's called the Huayra.
It costs £800,000 and it has
a top speed of 230 miles per hour.
The name Huayra comes from
the South American god of wind.
Probably not what you want to hear.
What you DO want to hear is that
it has six-litre twin-turbo V12,
made especially for it by AMG.
And once petrol is applied,
it makes 730 brake horsepower.
And what you do want to hear and see
is what that does.
Aaaargh, ha-ha!
It spins its wheels all the time!
I'm in a monster!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, dear God! 0 to 60 in 3.2 seconds
and then on into space!
That is 180.
That is savage. Savage, savage thing.
I can't get enough of that.
I'm going to do that again.
The drama isn't just
restricted to the speed.
Because inside the Huayra,
it looks like a Victorian's idea
of the 23rd century.
And the detail is beyond obsessive -
every single nut and bolt
is made from titanium.
The name badge takes 24 hours
to carve out
from a solid piece of aluminium.
Each wheel, also hewn from
a single aluminium block,
takes five days to make.
And look at this gear shifter.
All the mechanism is exposed so
you can see the workings.
It's made from 67 different parts,
all arranged
just so you can hear that mechanical
clunk of a gear being selected.
You don't even need to use it - you
can use the paddles by the wheel -
but they have put that there because
it makes it more of an occasion.
This fanatical attention to detail
goes on and on and on.
Even the body is more high-tech
than the one
you'll
find on a Formula One car.
It's made from carbotanium.
I even know what that means!
Now somebody's told me.
It's a blend of carbon fibre
and titanium,
which is incredibly light but is
actually stiffer than carbon fibre
and doesn't shatter
when you crash.
That makes things safer
should you suddenly find
all 730bhp
propelling you towards a hedge.
Not every element, though,
is quite so cutting edge.
Pagani haven't gone with
a fashionable twin plate clutch
that so many cars use,
because they do make for
faster changes.
They have gone instead for
a more traditional single plate
clutch because it's smaller
and a whole 100 kilograms lighter.
In fact, the Huayra
weighs just 1,350 kilograms
and has the power-to-weight ratio
of 541 brake horsepower per tonne,
which is more than you get
from a Bugatti Veyron.
But where the Bugatti Veyron
is four-wheel drive,
this is only rear-wheel drive,
and, rather worryingly, we have now
come to the part of the film
where we must see what it's like
going round corners.
I understand the more infantile
viewers, of which there are many,
will now want to see me
sliding the back end around.
So, here goes.
Amazingly, you can corner this car
like a halfwit
and come out the other side alive.
And that's because, in the Huayra,
the black art of aerodynamics is
watching over you.
You see those flaps on the outside?
There are two at the back and two
the front. They measure how fast
you're going
and then deploy
to keep everything stable.
That's astonishing!
All from the back wheels -
I'm in love!
But the handling is not
all down to the magic flaps.
It doesn't feel big,
like a Lambo,
and it's all been set
up so well
and made so stable that even I can
corner it hard without hiding in
the glove box, whimpering.
Oh, God,
this is properly put together.
The Zonda was always going to be
a difficult act to follow,
but the Huayra has pulled it off.
It drives better, it looks better
and it hasn't lost any of the drama.
On top of that, it also has something
that its main rivals,
Ferrari and Lamborghini,
no longer possess.
This car, and this may get
a bit Culture Show now, I know,
has still got its innocence.
Ferrari and Lamborghini haven't.
One is owned by Audi,
the other is a commercial machine
for selling hats and keyrings.
Pagani is where those companies
were 30 years ago -
no corporate culture,
no branded teddy bears,
they just want to make
a bedroom wall pin-up poster.
With a touch of the madness
we saw in the Lamborghinis
of a few decades ago.
And you can feel that!
There might be some people watching
right now who could actually
afford one of these things.
And it is the job of you, me
and everybody else to stand around
and join together in a chorus,
"Do it, do it, do it!"
APPLAUSE
Wow. That is an amazing-looking
thing. Crazy but wonderful. Amazing.
Now, do you know, do you know
which of the world's cities
has placed the largest number
of orders for this car? No.
Wakefield. Is it?
No, I made that up.
Is it really as fast as it looks?
Yes, yes! You know
the straight between Chicago
and Hammerhead? Yeah. In this,
it's not as long as you think.
It's just there. Is it not?
So I can't relax. "Oh, there!"
It is just one corner,
it is amazingly insanely fast.
Now, obviously, we must find out
how fast it goes around our track,
and that of course means handing it
over to our tame racing driver.
Some say that we have at least
thought of a new way
of introducing him.
But we haven't.
It's The Stig!
And he's off,
surprisingly gentle at first,
but then the tyres light up,
the spoilers spring into action.
Coming up to the first corner,
and he is...he's indicating,
seems unnecessary,
but he is keeping it all in shape.
Just about.
MUSIC PLAYS
Should explain that, since
the Olympics, The Stig has become
obsessed with national anthems.
He's around Chicago
and fires in towards Hammerhead.
Hammond was right,
that took no time at all.
Under-braking and takes it easy
through the left and right.
Now, hard on the power. Do you hear
those turbo waste-gates fluttering?
Now, follow through - surely he
can't use all the power there.
He did. He double-breaks
as he passes the tyres,
presumably with his left foot
or the middle one.
Just two corners left.
God, he's coming in fast.
Steady, Stig, up to Gambon.
He's very smooth through there.
And across the line.
APPLAUSE
Right, the Pagani, Pagani...
Hu...in. Huayra.
Huuuugh. It's a stupid name.
Why is it stupid?
It hasn't got any consonants
in it.
Consonants are the meat of language.
If you had no consonants in your
name,
you'd be...I-a.
And I'd be...Eey.
People have waited a long time for
us to come back, and that's it.
Anyway, the fastest car
we have ever had around the track is
the Ariel Atom V8 1.15.1.
Now, are you seriously suggesting
that this is faster than that?
I would say it is in with a shout
of being as fast, yes.
Well, you're wrong. Oh.
Because, the Pagani did it in 1...
13.8. I am not joking.
APPLAUSE
It's genuinely staggering.
I can't see that time being beaten
ever, to be honest.
Anyway, it is time to do
the news, and it's good news,
because the Dacia Sandero is on sale
in the UK and taking the nation
by storm.
Great! Now, the Mercedes SLS,
there it is.
There is a new black version of it,
there's a picture of it there,
and it's yellow.
It has 60 more horsepower than the
standard, more speed, more violence.
Dear God, is the brochure
written in bullet holes?
No, the brochure is carved into your
face with a hunting knife. Is it?
Subtle.
I wonder if they have addressed
the problem with the old one -
you could never get it sideways.
This one doesn't go in
a straight line.
It's funny, weirdly - my friend
just bought a black series Mercedes,
and every time I see him,
I say, "How is it going?"
And he pretends it's great.
"It's fine!
"I'm enjoying it!" "But you've
aged 30 years in a week."
"I know! But I really like it!"
That's like saying, "I've got
a new attack dog, and it's great!
"You don't know when it's going
to attack, or who! I love it."
That's what that is. It's a big
yellow attack dog. It's very silly.
Now, may I talk about
50 Shades Of Grey?
Really?
Can I just honestly ask,
who here has read it? Be honest,
who here has read it?
We're noticing a trend.
It's mainly a women thing,
I'm guessing, yes?
Men don't really have an equivalent,
until now.
I have found the male equivalent
of 50 Shades Of Grey.
Tremendous Tractors.
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
Come on, you're going
to love it the most!
Why would you not read that?
It is all in here, isn't it? "Spikes!
"These move through the ground
to cover the seeds
after they drop.
"This has chunky treads,
to grip bumpy or sloppy ground."
Hammond... This is
absolutely marvellous.
I think you're reading more into it
than is actually there.
"It cuts the stocks and threshes them
up to knock the grain right out."
I'm coming over all flushed.
It's just a book about tractors.
And the best thing is,
there's a series of them -
there's Dazzling Diggers, Amazing
Aeroplanes, Enormous Erections.
What? I made that last one up.
"Spreads the straw behind it as
the grain spills from the spout...
"..for farmland can be rough!"
I've gone somewhere else.
You've gone cross-eyed,
is what you've gone.
Right, Volkswagen... Volkswagen
named the Touareg, the big 4x4,
after the Tuaregene North African tribesmen.
It must have seemed like
a very good name at the time,
because they're a tough,
romantic nomadic people,
eking a simple living
from the harsh desert.
Unfortunately, it turns out that
today, the Touareg are running guns
from Libya into Mali and fighting
there alongside hardline Islamists.
I think we can be pretty sure
there will be some high-level
very urgent meetings at VW this week.
They're certainly dropping plans
now for the new hatchback,
the Baader-Meinhof.
"This van, the new
VW Lord's Resistance Army..."
That's the one with the independent
rear access, or IRA. Stop it! Yes.
If you think about it,
you only need one letter
to drop off the back of your Polo
and you will have VW PLO.
It turns out every single Volkswagen
is named after
a terrorist organisation!
Right, there is a new Corvette out,
and they have brought back
the Stingray name.
All-new chassis, so it has perfect
50-50 weight distribution, 450 brake
horsepower from a 6.2 litre V8,
which means 0 to 60
will be under four seconds.
And the best thing is it makes you
27% more attractive
to your sister.
Now, you know those dot-matrix signs
on motorways?
The overhead gantries that are used
to warn you about impending doom?
Well, sometimes, there is
no impending doom,
so they put up other messages.
I was driving along other day,
and one said,
"Have you prepared your car
for winter?"
And I thought,
"When I bought it from Mercedes,
"I rather hoped they'd done
that already."
How do you prepare your car
for winter?
We genuinely don't know.
Does anyone have any ideas how you
would prepare a car for winter?
Winter tyres!
Winter tyres - you could conceivably
put winter tyres on,
but you only need them for, what,
half a day? And they cost
about £150 each.
In the olden, olden, olden days,
you probably did have
to prepare your car for winter.
Perhaps that's the problem - the
man writing the sign is stuck in
1953. Yes.
Is it you? Have you been
moonlighting writing signs?
"Don't forget to line your engine
block with some stout canvas."
It was you!
Can I direct you to your jacket?
Before you say I'm locked in 1953,
Mr Toad.
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
I'm the only modern one here.
Really?
You may remember,
a while back on Top Gear,
we met the Race2Recovery team,
a group of injured soldiers
who were planning to take on
the toughest race in the world- The Dakar.
I remember thinking,
that is very noble,
but it's impossible, because Mark
Thatcher had four functioning limbs,
he never made it,
so the idea that they would was,
in my mind, preposterous.
The race was over 8,500 kilometres
across South America,
it took two weeks, 30 percent
of the entrants didn't finish.
But, and this is amazing news,
last Sunday, they did!
APPLAUSE
Philip Gillespie, Matt O'Hare
and the rest of the team,
deep, deep respect from all of us
here, that is amazing.
Tremendous. Right,
that is the end of the news.
I would like to move things on
swiftly to the Bentley Continental.
There are various versions
available - you can have one with a
top speed of 187, top speed of 194,
a top speed of 198,
but what if none of these top speeds
are quite what you're after?
Well, Bentley has a solution.
And here it is.
The Continental GT Speed.
This is not to be confused
with the previous
Bentley Continental GT Speed,
or the Bentley Continental GT
Supersports or in fact any other
Bentley Continental that looks
exactly the same as this one.
No, this one is a bit special.
What this is is
the fastest Bentley ever built,
because it will do
205 miles per hour.
It will also go from 0 to 60
in just four seconds.
And to deliver that kind
of performance,
the standard issue six-litre
twin-turbo engine has been stoked
to produce 616 horsepower.
To ensure that all that power is
delivered in an orderly fashion,
this car has been fitted with a new
eight-speed automatic gearbox.
To help it stand out next
to a regular Continental GT,
the speed has been given
a few signature flourishes.
Such as
this black mesh radiator grille,
these rifled exhausts,
and inside, a gorgeous
dark-tinted aluminium fascia.
It costs just over £150,000, and at
this point, you may be thinking,
"So what?
"Why do we need another fast
Bentley anyway?"
I thought exactly the same,
until I drove it.
Up until now, every Continental GT
has been, to my mind,
just a sort of big posh car
built to the numbers.
Built to an easy directive.
But this car, finally feels,
I think, like a Bentley should.
It's not the magnitude of the
power that is important,
it's the way it is turned into
speed.
You sort of get a discreet
"ahem" from the butler
and then this big aristocratic
whomp in the kidneys.
The ride in a Bentley,
I think, should be reasonably firm
but forgiving and supple,
and that's what you get here.
You feel very much in control.
You can read the road
through the wheels
and through the steering wheel,
but it doesn't batter you
in any way.
Likewise, that new eight-speed
gearbox is an absolute peach.
It's also intelligent -
it will skip gears,
it will go from fourth to eighth
if that's what is required.
The Continental has
been around for ten years now,
and what this version feels like
is a decade of engineering
coming together to make
something rather special.
So to find out
how good it really is,
we decided to take it somewhere more
demanding than a Welsh B road.
So, since it
has four-wheel-drive...
Yes, we're going to unleash her
£150,000 Bentley on a full-blown
stage of
the World Rally Championship.
Specifically, here, on a 15-mile
stage of the gruelling Welsh Rally.
This is Top Gear
consumer journalism.
I've never driven a rally stage
and I'm not going to now.
I'm giving the job to rally ace
Kris Meeke...
who you may remember from our race
between a rally car
and Olympic gold-medal skele-bob
pilot Amy Williams.
On that occasion, my job was to sit
next to him and not look scared.
Today, though, I would have to give
Kris directions,
which meant getting to grips with
the mystifying world of pace notes.
Basically, the number before the R,
the R is a right,
the number is the severity of
the bend. One is a slight bend
and the six is a real hard bend,
so the numbers are graded
one through to six.
The numbers between the corners
are the distance,
so 40 is 40 metres, the C that you
were calling is a crest,
and the arrow is into, so that'll be
crest into one right over crest.
So how do I do this and look out
the window at the same time?
You don't look out, you have to feel
the corners through your backside.
So your brain needs to be
200-300 metres ahead of my driving.
If it goes wrong, and we have
a crash, who says sorry first?
First thing I will do
is check your pulse
to see if you're still living,
then I'll ask you to apologise.
Besides the complexity of the pace
notes, there was another worry.
A World Rally car is
purpose-built for the job.
It weighs just 1,200 kilograms
and has bespoke brakes
to help it stop.
Its gearbox is made to soak up
the punishment.
Its roll cage is designed to keep
the occupants in one piece.
By contrast, all we have changed on
our 2.3-tonne Bentley was the seats.
The seats are good.
I think that's good thinking,
but most of other things about this
car are bad, aren't they, for rally?
Too big.
Yeah. A Bentley on a rally
is a stupid idea.
It has all the horsepower you need
to get it up to speed,
but we're trying to stop
2.3 tonnes on road tyres,
so we don't have the grip.
And you haven't got the handbrake.
You have the electric handbrake,
which is no good.
It's not, but we will have to do
a little bit of man manoeuvring
around the hairpins.
Are you a bit scared about driving
this rally course?
I am a little bit.
You should be even more scared.
And on those final words of
comfort...
..we took our place
on the start line.
You see that bloke's
moustache there? Yes.
That tells me everything
is going to be all right.
So if you count me down,
do a five. Yeah.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Four right. 40.
You need to be quicker, James,
come on. 40 metres. Four right.
Suddenly, I knew what it felt like
to be a rabbit
caught in the headlights.
Next, James, come on!
Left, left plus two left.
James, I can't go up the road
if you don't call out the notes!
One right. One right?
Repeat, repeat!
Then three right and then 40 metres.
Five right into six left
then 40 metres into five right.
This is a five, you're too late,
James, come on!
Right, square right.
Sorry, square left.
James, either get it right
or shut up!
'The red mist had descended
on Kris.
'A fog of doubt had enveloped me,
'but it seemed he wasn't going to
back off.'
Oof!
Next one! One right.
Bloody hell!
Four right.
On the plus side, the Bentley's
four-wheel drive was superb.
The power phenomenal.
And Kris was majestic.
Especially in the tight bends
where the Bentley's electric
parking brake was useless.
Going into large hairpin right.
That's where you needed
the handbrake. Yeah.
Ten miles in, and I was giving Kris
proper backup.
Five right.
Severe six right. OK.
That's a bit better, James.
Through water.
40, four left.
Got it. The finish, James.
Two left. Tight.
Man in road. Two left, over a crest.
Jesus!
APPLAUSE
So, James May, James May...
the big question is, were you last?
No.
We beat a proper WRC rally car
by two seconds.
So you were second to last?
Yeah. First of the winners.
I have to say, though,
obviously I would like to mock you
for your hopeless co-driving skills,
but watching this
on that rally circuit,
a deeply impressive spectacle,
it really was.
Yeah, it is a deeply impressive car.
It's weird, I've never been
a fan of the Continental,
but I drove the little V8 engine one
last year
and I thought that was pretty
good as well. Yeah, absolutely.
They have done a great deal
to improve the car over the years.
But the trouble is,
they haven't really done anything to
improve the people who buy them. No.
I mean,
they do all that engineering work
and then they sell it
to Mario Balotelli. Exactly.
Who? I knew you didn't know.
He's that Manchester City player
with the blond Brazilian
on his head.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anyway, it is now time to put a star
in our reasonably priced car.
My guest tonight is best known as a
ginger man who is intent on bringing
suffering and misery to countless
millions of innocent souls.
Don't worry,
I'm not talking about Mick Hucknall.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome, from Homeland,
Damian Lewis!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
You're here! Thank you. How are you?
Pretty great. Have a seat.
Thank you. Have a seat.
Thank you. Thank you.
I want to talk about Homeland,
obviously,
I know everybody wants to do that,
but...
I keep reading that
you don't know how it ends,
but you must do, really.
Well... I could tell you,
but I'd have to kill you!
I don't know how it ends,
because THEY don't know how it ends.
It sounds a little avoiding
to say that,
but honestly, the writers
write incredibly spontaneously.
They're actually sitting down
this week to work out what happens
next season. You're in a wood now.
It's a bit of a surprise
I'm still alive, I think. Yeah.
Now they've got the headache
of me still being alive,
they've got to work out what
to do with me.
Obama's a fan, isn't he? The
President of America is a hug fan
and invited my wife
and I to the White House.
You are kidding. Sat...
convinced we would be sitting,
you know, by the revolving doors,
you know,
just on the way to the toilet,
consistently being
hit on the back of the head as...
old people went to pee.
And then actually we sat
at the table opposite him.
The programme I'm surprised
you haven't been on yet -
Match Of The Day. You're a big
football fan, aren't you?
I do like a bit of footy, yeah.
You are a...
I'm a Liverpool fan. Can I ask...
SPORADIC CHEERS
As you can tell from
my deep Scouse accent!
..have you never played in
one of those pro-am celebrity...?
I've actually twice had
the extraordinary experience
of playing at Old Trafford
in front of 70,000 people.
And last time I played, actually,
I was playing in the centre midfield
for England against
the rest of the world
with Jamie Redknapp.
It was just me and Jamie
marshalling midfield
behind Shearer and Sheringham.
And I clattered into Zizou,
Zinedine Zidane,
after about 15 minutes, and I didn't
realise how angry he was.
Jamie Redknapp kept following me
around the pitch, saying,
"Dame, Dame, calm down!"
And I said, "What do you mean?"
He said,
"They haven't come to see YOU play!"
And then in the 30th minute,
in front of 75,000 people,
what does Zidane do?
He rolled his foot over the ball
a few times,
went to the touchline,
stood there with the ball,
looked up at me
as I came charging in, like this,
going to tackle Zidane,
looked at me and went...
poked it straight
through my legs...
to spontaneous laughter.
I've never been laughed at
by 70,000 people.
It would shrivel up,
and there'd be space for things,
that's for damn sure.
But it was an amazing experience.
Cars. Cars.
I gather your first car
was an Alfa Romeo? Yes, it was.
It wasn't a Spider,
it wasn't a sexy Alfa Romeo.
I bought my Alfa Romeo for a grand
on a forecourt in Balham High Road.
No! Yeah. And it wasn't even
at a car dealership.
It was like a junk shop
with four cars in front of it,
just lined up on the pavement.
I used to live in Balham
and I know exact...
You bought an Alfa from that man?
It was just off the pavement.
I was pulling out of the car park
at the Royal Shakespeare Company
where I'd been working
for a couple of years.
I put my foot to the brake, it went
straight to the floor. No, no!
I just rolled out
straight across the road,
bang into the opposite wall.
Normally, the Alfa Romeo prevents
that happening by breaking down
on the way TO
the Royal Shakespeare Company.
So if you'd gone through the woe
and the misery of
a very, very unreliable car,
presumably your next one
was more sensible, more reliable?
It was a TVR. There you go.
Which one? The Chimaera.
TVR stands
for Total Vehicle Reliability.
LAUGHTER
It's amazing fun, though, the TVR,
when you get it going
and you throw it around
the country lanes.
I thought you were a bike man
more than cars.
I do, well, I have had motorbikes.
I went and got my test
and then totally fell in love
with the ultimate hairdresser's
chopper bike.
Which was the Yamaha Virago 1,000cc
high-handlebarred...
An Easy Rider bike! Chopper.
Easy Rider. Quite.
Did you never fall off a bike?
That's what would stop me getting on
one, the terrible pain that would
result. No idea.
I had a couple of prangs
and then I had a bad one
just outside Pentonville Prison
on the Caledonian Road
when a cabbie pulled out
and I just went straight
into his windscreen.
And I was out cold,
woke up in a sort of cinematic
cliche of a circle of faces
as I came to. And also to feel this
really hard grip on my wrist.
That's the first thing I remember,
just thinking,
"That doesn't feel good. Someone's
really holding onto me tight."
Turned out the guy who was in the
back of the taxi was a male nurse
from the Royal Free Hospital who'd
taken a taxi because he was pissed.
He then said to me later,
he said, "It was good I managed to
get you into the recovery position."
I said, "Yeah, but why were you
holding onto my wrists so hard?"
He said, "Because I couldn't tell
if you were actually dying
"or if I was just too pissed
I couldn't find your pulse!"
So it was just like...
My God, come back! Holding onto me.
Normally, these days,
when people have accidents,
the first thing they see
is somebody videoing them.
That is today's version, isn't it?
It is today's version. Ten iPhones.
Yeah, exactly.
Now, obviously, you came here to do
your lap. Yes. Which wasn't easy.
The sight that greeted us
this morning...
let's have a look at the pictures
we've got. This is our track.
That is what... Yeah.
With light sleet.
So, realistically, you were never
going to set the fastest time.
You know, it's quite nerve-wracking
coming to do this
for the first time.
You think, what's my limit?
At what point do I just follow
through a bit, you know?
And will that be
on the first corner?
And when I saw the weather,
it was oddly relaxing.
You were thinking, now I can't win,
so it doesn't matter?
Yeah, then I thought...
Then everyone was going, it's going
to be great fun, it's quite icy
out there,
you'll be able to lose the back end
and throw it around a bit.
I was going, how do you know I'm
going to be able to do any of that?
Well, who'd like to see him
doing a bit of that?
AUDIENCE: Yes!
These are some of the practice laps.
Let's just run the tape here.
Now, this is the follow-through. The
fastest part, that's pretty ballsy.
And...
I wouldn't want to go off there,
because it's pretty fast.
Second to last corner, yep.
Well held!
Is it well held?
Yes, it is well held!
And that one is...?
I do like your determination to keep
going. Because of the camera!
More rally driving, I think, today.
Very good, though.
Eventually, you did manage
to get a lap in. Yes.
Who here would like to see that?
Yes! Let's go.
And they're off!
Determined.
Coming up to the first corner,
just wet there,
nothing much to worry about.
Now there's something
to worry about!
Ooh. That's slightly scary
when the back does that.
Keep it on the throttle, Damo!
Look at that!
Change gear now. Now!
Braking's not easy into
the Hammerhead at the best of times.
In those conditions...
Ooh, a dab of handbrake!
I see a dab of handbrake
and a bit of under... Change gear!
The Skandi flick. I believe.
It was a Skandi flick.
No racing driver should have to
put his windscreen wipers on.
Do you know what I mean?
When they're rallying,
that is quite normal.
I wouldn't want to be going over
there at anything more...
Can he make it all the way
through the tyres?
Yup!
Back into the fast bit. Now, can he
get to the second last corner right?
Yes... No!
Yes!
Into Gambon. Looking good.
Oh, no! No!
That was a lot of fun.
That was tremendous!
That does look like a lot of fun. It
was a lot of fun. It was terrific.
So where do you think you've come?
So far, the slowest man we've ever
had round here was John Prescott.
In a 1.56.7. Yes.
Damian Lewis, you did it in...
Two minutes...
..nine seconds...
..point one!
But...
APPLAUSE
Should we have
a separate board for snow?
So I think you're the fastest person
we've ever had in the snow.
So we'll put you up there.
It's good!
I have to say, actually... Great.
I do have to say, that is
the slowest lap we've ever had.
But, and I'm sure everyone
will agree with me on this,
by far and away
the most entertaining.
Ladies and gentlemen, Damian Lewis!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Now, so far in this programme,
James has been rallying
in a £150,000 Bentley,
and I've raced around our track
in an £800,000 Pagani.
So someone's got to bring it all
back down to earth.
Yes, and unfortunately
that person is Jeremy.
Yes, as usual, it falls to me
to be the voice of reason
and common sense.
With this, the Peel P50,
the smallest car ever made.
Until now. Because I have created,
behold, this!
Now, I know. I know.
Incredulity is often
the first response.
But let me talk you through it.
Because underneath the handcrafted
aluminium bodywork,
you have the engine and the running
gear from a quad bike.
But you will note it has lights
and indicators and a number plate.
It's passed
all the Government tests,
which means you can drive it
on the road.
Are you seriously suggesting that
that is an actual car?
I promise it's a real car. What's it
called? Ah! Well, that's brilliant.
Because it's shorter and narrower
than a Peel P50,
I've called it the P45.
Now I'm going to test it.
What, you're going to test a car
that you built? Yes.
So what are we going to do next
week? VW tests its new Golf?
Shut up! I'm going to be completely
unbiased, as you shall see.
I began on the track.
And having determined very quickly
that the P45 was exquisite
in every way,
I took it onto the public highway.
I should make it plain this is
Base L model that I'm driving now,
but there are some optional extras.
CAR BACKFIRES
Urgh! Nothing wrong.
Edit that out.
There is, for instance,
the deluxe wash wipe option
which costs just £1.99.
Good.
And also, for just £500, this does
come with satellite navigation.
There's the sat nav. You see?
You just hold it up
and see where you're going.
The P45 is designed to deal
with all eventualities.
I'm relaxed.
So, I decided to join the main road.
Yes, look at this! Look at this!
Very brilliant.
CAR BACKFIRES
Oh! Oh my God!
If you're watching this in the edit,
make sure that doesn't go
on television.
I don't want people thinking
it's a death trap.
CAR BACKFIRES AND JEREMY SCREAMS
It happened again!
Edit that out as well.
I can't believe how quiet
the roads are this morning.
I'm barely seeing
any traffic at all.
As I neared Guildford,
I did find a jam,
but this was no problem
for the super-narrow P45.
The speed machine is coming through!
Ah! Oh! Oh! Nothing wrong!
Oh, yes!
This is incredible.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you are witnessing
the birth of the future.
I'm just staggered that
Ford, General Motors, Toyota,
all the automotive giants, haven't
thought to make a car like this.
And yet, a poky little motoring show
on BBC...
Ow!
This is the way to drive the P45,
with your face on the windscreen,
then it can't smash into it.
So, for local commuting,
my car is faultless.
But what if
you want to go further afield?
To find out,
I pulled into a petrol station
and without even getting out,
I brimmed its tank.
Good.
Damn!
I only have a 1.7-litre fuel tank,
but the minimum delivery
here is two litres.
Discreetly, I squirted
the difference into a bin.
(I didn't see anything.)
Then I fired up the two-stroke,
100cc engine
and set off to London.
Technically, I'm legally allowed
to drive the P45 on motorways
and dual carriageways.
So to see how it gets on,
I'm about to join the fearsome A3.
Here we go.
Ooh.
Aarghhh!
Arghh! I've never been frightened
of a Citroen Picasso before
and I just was!
Aarghhh! A van!
Arghh! I've got a weave on!
Ohhh!
Oh, yes! Help me! HELP! HELP!
How fast is that now?
34! Arghh! Lorry, lorry,
lorry, lorry!
Ohhh! A lot of poo shot out then!
So while this may be
completely legal,
it's also
completely terrifying.
However, the advantage of a car
this small is that
you don't have to take
it on dual carriageways.
In fact, you don't have to use
the main roads at all.
What you do instead is you drive it
to the railway station,
but instead of leaving it in the car
park to be vandalised and stolen,
you take it on the train with you.
Now, I will be honest.
None of the train companies
we contacted would play ball,
so I'm using the coach instead.
Coach is good.
Coach is better than a train.
Fewer diseases on a coach.
And of course,
when you get to the big city,
you don't have to use
the tube or the bus,
because you have your car WITH you.
Ah.
ENGINE SPLUTTERS
Oh, dear.
I don't think...
ENGINE CUTS OUT
Ah.
ENGINE FAILS TO START
Just cut the cameras.
In London, I went for
a little drive.
Yes!
All sorts of hand signals
available. If I want to go...
left, right, somebody annoys me.
And then I went shopping.
And with the P45,
there's no need to pay.
Or waste time
looking for a parking space.
Oh, dear.
Of course,
a Peel P50 also fits in a lift,
but because it has no reverse gear,
you can't back it out again.
Unless there's a newsreader to hand.
This, though,
does have a reverse gear.
So...here we go.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep,
beep, beep, beep, beep...
I know what you're thinking.
There's no way you'd be allowed
to drive around here
with a two-stroke engine
belching fumes into the faces
of all the baby children.
But here's the thing.
The P45 is a hybrid.
So when you come inside,
you can disconnect the petrol engine
and connect up
a couple of electric motors.
A very simple job.
You take off a wheel,
connect a free-wheeling hub...
It takes a couple of guys...minutes.
There are a couple of drawbacks.
Number one,
the top speed is now 3mph.
Number two, the batteries will
only last an hour.
But I'm a man and I can't
think of any shopping expedition
that could possibly take
longer than that.
Shoes, I've got some,
I don't need any of those.
I've got a chair.
There's nothing I want to buy.
Eventually, I bought
a present for James.
Then I decided to find out
just how quiet my car is
in electric mode,
so I took it here.
This is extraordinary.
Nobody's looking up.
Nobody's noticing me.
The only trouble is that
libraries are more interesting
than shopping centres.
Whoa. History Of Germany.
Can't be that big just to say,
"We lost a lot."
An hour simply flew by.
Get out of the way, student.
Soon, the batteries were flat.
Oh, no.
HE SIGHS
Now, if this were a Peel P50,
I could simply pick it up
and carry it out.
But I'm afraid the P45
is a bit heavier.
A lot heavier. Weighs a tonne.
There's only one thing for it.
ENGINE STARTS
ENGINE REVS
This is so embarrassing.
Sorry. Sorry, everybody.
I'm so sorry. Really, I'm so sorry.
That night, I was due
to go to a show.
Oh, yes!
Stupid idiot!
And as I was running late,
I decided to take a short cut.
Look here. "Cyclists not allowed."
Good.
I'm not a cyclist, so here I come.
Hello...
GLASS SHATTERS
ENGINE REVS
Come on. Quickly...
GLASS SHATTERS
I'm really sorry.
'Soon, I was in the West End...'
Arghh!
'..and nearing the theatre.'
This is the joy of a P45.
Everything is a drive-through.
Hello. One, please.
Thank you very much.
THUD
Ooh...
There you go.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
The show was ace!
# Radio ga ga, video goo goo... #
Not a single gay man on that stage.
# All we need is... #
However, my seating arrangements
were a bit cramped.
MUSIC DROWNS SPEECH
INDISTINCT
Oh, no! Cut! Cut!
The next morning,
it was clear to me that the P45
was completely excellent, but would
it make commercial sense
to put it into production?
To find out, I'd set up
an important business meeting.
To make sure I look my best,
I'm wearing a suit, as you can see.
I've washed my hair
and now I'm going to give the car
a wash and brush-up as well.
Now, here we go. Yes.
Arghh! It's not warm!
It's extremely cold!
Oh, yes! People pay many pounds
for this in countries...
Oh, it's gone quite badly.
What's happened here?
A terrible thing has happened.
SHOUTING
A bad thing has happened.
I've got completely wedged.
ALARM BEEPS
With the P45 untangled, I headed
off to my big business meeting.
First of all, I'd like to
apologise for my...wet sleeves
and my bloodshot eye -
I got soap in it.
We'll gloss over that.
Right, erm...
Cars are getting bigger, these days.
I've got a picture of an original
Ford Cortina,
which I'm sure you won't remember,
Deborah! (LAUGHS)
And the modern Mondeo,
which is bigger.
And it's the same story with
the Golf and the same story
with the Fiesta, and it's ridiculous
when we live in a country
as cramped and overcrowded as ours.
So cars should be getting smaller.
And that is where this comes in.
This is my creation.
The P45.
The idea is you can drive
this to a railway station
and then you pop
it on a train or a coach,
go to the next city
and you can use it there as well.
It's road legal...
Can I make sure, cos I might
have missed something?
You started off apologising
why your arms were wet
and then didn't explain why.
Because they've got water on them.
I actually do travel back and forth
from the West Country on the train.
You say you can take that with you.
That looks quite big
to get on a train.
That's because train companies
put seats in their carriages,
which they needn't do with this.
If you just produced a carriage,
you could drive in and sit there.
Hold on a minute. At the moment,
you can't get it on a train?
Not as such. No. So you've got
to rely on the train companies
redesigning their trains for you
to get this on the train?
Well, redesigning is quite easy -
you just take the seats out.
OK. I, erm...
Jeremy,
is this your first business venture?
Yes.
What would it cost to have
one of these on the road?
£8,000. £8,000?
What would you make them for?
It'll cost £4,000 to build.
By children or will you get adults?
Can you really get children
to work in a factory?
Cos that would be
brilliant if you could.
EVAN DAVIS: Jeremy has asked
if he could get children
to work in a factory.
You must come and have a look.
Theo Paphitis decides to take
a closer look.
Jeremy. It's shit. It isn't!
It is. Total and utter shit.
Theo Paphitis thinks Jeremy's car
still needs work.
I don't understand why you're not
seeing what I'm seeing here.
DEBORAH: We are, Jeremy.
I can see exactly what
you're looking at.
It's just that I can see
that it's loopy and you can't.
How much of YOUR money have you
invested in this? None at all.
That is the best thing that
you've done yet.
Do you have a plan? Do you have any
idea of the size of the market,
how you're going to sell it
to that market?
Yes. So, size of the market?
1,600 a month.
1,600 a month? Or a year.
Well, Jeremy.
I'm going to make you an offer.
That's the ticket!
£1 for 1%.
Why would anybody buy this?
It's got stripes on it.
I couldn't invest in you.
I'm sorry. I'm out.
Jeremy, I have to say one thing.
It is the smartest
I've ever seen you.
So congratulations for that.
You've made, clearly, a real effort.
However, I can't invest
in ridiculous things.
So on that basis, Jeremy, I'm going
to have to tell you I'm out.
Jeremy, it's rubbish. It's useless.
You're wasting your time.
I can't invest in this. So I'm out.
Theo Paphitis is out,
which means Jeremy's only chance
is Duncan Bannatyne.
Well, Jeremy.
I'm the last Dragon in.
I tried to tempt them
by making an offer,
hoping they would come in with me.
Sorry, I can't understand
a word you're saying.
That is... I'm out.
Jeremy has insulted Duncan
Bannatyne,
and now he too is out.
All the Dragons have given him
his P45.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Well, I'm sorry...
I'm unbowed by their negativity.
How can they not realise this is
a car you NEVER need to park?
You can go to the theatre in it,
shopping, your arms are free
so you can reach things from
the shelves.
You never need get out of it.
Which is ironic, because the first
thing anyone will want to do
on getting in, is get out of it.
LAUGHTER
And it's a death trap.
I feel like Vincent van Gogh.
You've only got one ear? No.
Nobody recognised his genius
until AFTER he died.
So what you're saying is,
for this to be a commercial success,
you have to be dead?
LAUGHTER
Yes.
And on that bombshell,
it is time to end.
Thank you for watching. They'll see
you next week. Good night!