You know how we go on a family trip
-once or twice a year?
-[Sheila] Mm-hm.
So, I'm thinking Vail.
Vail.
[Kris]
I am so excited to surprise the kids.
It's just the perfect place
to take the family.
[Kourtney] Scott's asking if he can come.
I think Scott should come.
I feel like it's a good opportunity to see
if he can handle
coming on family vacations.
You just need to keep it together, dude.
[Scott]
Well, you got yourself a deal, kid.
[Kris] Welcome to Vail.
[Khloé] Oh, my god, guys.
[Todd] Look at this, baby Rob.
[Kim] I can't believe Rob isn't here.
[Khloé] Rob is just a pussy.
He proposed in front of her whole family.
We wake up to my brother
just getting engaged.
[Khloé] He hasn't told us anything.
That's so [bleep] up that he did that.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Morning. Hi.
-These are so cute.
-[Sheila] So cute.
[tinkling]
A little rescue St. Bernard.
Okay, let me see what's going on here.
See the drama.
[Sheila] Huh?
You all right?
I guess Rob got engaged last night.
-What?
-Yeah.
[pensive music]
[sighs]
I'll tell you, never a dull moment.
How are you?
I mean, are you all right?
[Kris]
No, but that's why we're just wandering.
I wake up to a gazillion text messages,
which is never good news,
and I'm reading through them
and realize Rob got engaged last night.
He got engaged.
And it's sort of coming out of left field.
Like I… I think I'm just in shock.
[Sheila] How did he tell you?
-Like what…
-[Kris] He didn't.
It was just all over the Internet.
-[Sheila] Oh, I'm sorry.
-It's wild.
-[Sheila] No, it's not right.
-[Kris] He asked for her mom's
hand in marriage
and I'm like, we don't even…
he's never even mentioned it to us.
-[Sheila] You gonna call him?
-[Kris] No. Mm-mm.
I'm not gonna call him.
I don't… I mean,
he should've called me and said--
I understand.
[Kris] I didn't do anything to him
except give him an amazing life.
[pensive music]
[Sheila]
Put one foot in front of the other.
-Take each day one at a time.
-[Kris] Yeah.
[sighs]
[Kris] To hear that Rob got engaged
through social media
is a bit disappointing, to say the least.
He should've told me first,
or even talked to the family about it,
or mentioned it to his sisters.
But I had no idea.
[phone ringing]
-[Corey] I love you. I love you so much.
-[chuckles]
Are you guys on the lift?
Who are you on the lift with?
-[Corey] The instructor.
-[instructor] Hi.
He's doing unbelievably, he's killing it.
[Corey] I've been down about five times.
I'm doing pretty good.
I'm warming up but I'm doing all right.
Yeah, I got the best skis.
I don't know
if I'm gonna separate from them.
-Oh.
-I like…
-My boots and skis are so cool.
-[Sheila speaks indistinctly]
What?
-I said my boots and my skis…
-Yeah.
-…are so cool. I like 'em.
-Good, babe.
I feel so bad that I'm so distracted
while Corey's trying to tell me
about his skiing
because he's having such a good time.
I think I'm just still in shock
and just trying to digest
this whole situation with Rob.
-[Corey] You don't sound too excited.
-I am. So excited.
[Corey] All right, bye-bye.
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
Okay.
[Kendall] What shoes are you wearing, T?
[Tyga] I have on tennis shoes.
[Kylie] This is about to be an adventure.
I'm already tired.
[giggles]
We have not been to Vail in so many years,
and this trip is super important to us,
so just because we got
a little bit of this negative news,
I don't want it ruining our trip.
So, we are going to ignore
and go skiing
and enjoy the rest of our trip.
All right, team, we out.
[Kylie] We out.
[upbeat techno music]
[Khloé]
Northie. Oh, my god, you look so cute.
What's wrong with you, boy?
[Kourtney]
I think it's colder than I thought.
[Kendall] We're gonna go skiing.
[man] Welcome to Vail. Have a great day.
[Khloé squeals, giggles]
[Kendall] Oh. You okay?
I thought it was gonna go without me.
[light music]
[Khloé] Okay, kind of don't want
to do this anymore.
-[Tyga] This is pretty high.
-Now I'm getting scared.
God, and my helmet didn't fit.
Is this a bad sign?
-[Kendall] I'm scared too.
-You're scared too?
Oh, my god, if a Jenner is scared,
then, we've got a problem.
[Kim] Scott, it was, like, 75 degrees.
[Khloé] 75?
[laughs]
No, that's what they told us.
[wind gusting]
[light music]
[Scott] This trip is definitely
the most time
Kourtney and I have spent together
since we've broken up,
and it's definitely a little different
because, you know,
Kourtney and I aren't together anymore.
So, I don't really know how to act.
I mean,
I miss my family and I miss
being around Kourtney
so it's… it's a lot of things
to get used to.
[light music]
[Khloé] So are we ready to rock and roll?
It's cold.
Can I see my girl ski?
[Kim] Yeah?
Do we have matching ski socks?
[Kourtney] Wow, P! Look at you.
[Kendall screaming]
[Kylie] Go, T, go.
[upbeat music]
Comin' in hot.
[Khloé]
If you knock me down, I'm gonna kill you.
We made it.
[lively music]
-Look.
-Oh, this is fabulous.
[both laugh]
-This is fantastic.
-It's so good.
Whoo. Oh.
-[Kris] Randy, how was it?
-Oh, it was beautiful.
So good after all those years.
-[Kris] How long has it been?
-15.
Stop. Stop it.
-[Kris] There they are.
-[Sheila] Oh, look who's there.
Hi. Did you go up?
-[Kylie] Oh, my gosh…
-Hey, Scott.
-Hi.
-[Tyga] How you doing?
-[Sheila] Where are they?
-How are you, guys?
[Khloé] Oh, my god.
You look like you're on Sesame Street.
Oh, my god, look at Mom, Scott.
-[Scott] Purple haze.
-Come here, let me touch you.
[laughs]
[Kim] So he came, he brought the ring,
and then, like,
all of her whole family was there,
and he just did it.
[indistinct chatter]
It's just so bizarre.
He has not spoken to any of us.
He must legitimately hate
our whole family.
Everyone's calling us, like, our friends,
like, asking if it's true,
and they want to congratulate Rob,
and it's kind of embarrassing
for us to not know.
[Kim]
Like, of course, do whatever you want,
like, do what makes you happy.
I got married once
and didn't tell my whole family.
But I don't know,
it just seems so not like him.
[Kim] Kourt, that was Roxy,
and she basically said that…
Rob said he's loving his life…
[Khloé] He was the same with Adrienne,
the same with Rita.
[Tyga] What are you gonna do?
Nothing you can do.
The best thing is to sit back
and just let them be.
Yeah.
Like, everything you're going through,
like, I've been through worse
with her, you know?
Tyga did have a relationship with Chyna,
so I appreciate his perspective
on the situation,
but he also has to understand
where we're coming from as well.
Rob, even after the fact,
hasn't said anything to us.
[Kim] I would literally never post
a photo with you,
just to like, not hurt her feelings
because, like, obviously,
that did hurt her feelings,
you know, that, like…
my little sister is, like,
you know, with her baby dad.
Like, I'm very, like…
Like, I understand it,
how she could've been hurt,
like, totally, like, I'm never…
[Tyga] But it also has nothing to do
with you though, you know?
-It's like…
-Totally.
[Tyga]
That's life, you know what I mean? Like…
People have to find out for themselves
-and go their own way, you know?
-[Kim] Totally.
She's not a bad person,
you know what I mean?
She's not a bad person at all.
When she posted something about Kylie,
I went so crazy on my brother
because I was, like,
"The way we…" And I know
everything was on speaker.
I was like, "The way we were raised,
that is now your girlfriend."
[Tyga] Okay, it's, like, if he was, like,
not posting anything from jump,
like, about Kylie, or, like,
not doing none of this stuff,
you were only doing it
because you was just trying to,
like, get at me.
And just be in the mix all day.
It's not funny, you know what I'm saying?
It's just the overall one-up factor.
It's like, "Yo, I won."
Why was he able to propose
in front of her whole family,
-but he can't include us?
-I don't know.
[tense music]
[Khloé] I feel like
Rob is deliberately excluding us
from so many things.
And he almost, like, likes this wedge
that's being put between us all,
which is bizarre to me,
'cause we didn't grow up that way.
But whenever Rob needs something,
he'll come back crawling.
Rob is full of bull [bleep].
And I can't handle it.
[dramatic music]
You were only doing it
because you was just trying to,
like, get at me
and just be in the mix all day.
It's not funny, you know what I'm saying?
-It's the overall…
-Package.
…one-up factor. It's like, "Yo, I won."
-[Kylie] Yeah.
-'Cause in her mind, like--
This is your sister you're talking about.
Have some respect.
Should I call her?
-[Tyga] No, you shouldn't call her.
-[Kourtney] Why?
Because… You should, Kim should call her.
[Kourtney] She knows I'm the rational one.
Kim, you're the only person
that can patch all this stuff up,
and you know it. You're gonna have to.
Would you go to the wedding?
[pensive music]
-[Tyga] You have to, right?
-[Kylie] Would you go to the wedding?
-[Kim] Look, guys…
-Mom has to.
[pensive music continues]
We're not going to his wedding
if he has a wedding.
[Kourtney] But I mean, how many weddings
have we been to in this family
and they don't mean [bleep]?
So, let's all get over it.
[upbeat music]
-[Scott] Let's go.
-[Khloé] Let's see you [bleep] like us.
[Corey] Which way we going?
All right.
[Khloé] Oh, yeah.
[Corey] Whoa.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Corey] Whoa.
[Khloé] So good.
[Kourtney]
Watching Corey gives me a heart attack.
-[Scott] I know, it's scary.
-[all laugh]
[Corey grunts]
[all laugh]
[Corey] I'm okay.
-[Kourtney] Who wiped out?
-[Corey] Now I feel safe.
I'm feeling good. I was going too fast.
[Kourtney] You needed to stop?
I think I'm just beat at this point.
[Corey panting]
[Corey]
All right, I got to pull it together.
I got to get my Scott [bleep] together.
You know, Scott's just too cool.
Look how he stands. He just stands like…
He don't look like he even working.
[Scott] If you jerk off a little
in the middle, it really helps out.
[Kourtney] Coming through, Khlo.
Open it up, open it up, open it up. Oh.
-[Kim] I'm coming.
-[Khloé shrieks]
-Yeah.
-[all cheering]
[upbeat music]
[Kendall] Wait, you guys,
it doesn't just take like that.
-You have to, like, wait for me to focus.
-[Scott] What do you mean?
Okay, do it.
-[Kendall] Oh.
-[camera shutter clicks]
. [Kendall laughs]
-[Kendall] He's really modeling.
-[Tyga speaks indistinctly]
[girl] Kendall.
[Scott in girly voice]
Kendall.
Let's put it out there.
-[laughs]
-[Scott] Let me see--
So all you have to do is
focus with this big one.
-[Scott] Focus…
-On me.
[girl] Kendall.
[Scott]
Well, you got to get, like, a better view.
-Go, like, by the door.
-[Kendall] Okay.
Just go outside.
[chuckles]
-[Kendall] Who-- Where are they?
-They're, like, right down there.
-[Kendall] No, Scott.
-[Scott] Here's Kendall.
[girl 1] Kendall.
[Scott]
Here's who you've been waiting for.
-[girl 2] Oh, my god.
-[Scott] Here's Kenny. Here's Kendall.
-[girl 1] Kendall.
-[Scott] Say hi. Tyga performs in 20.
-[girl 2] Tyga.
-[girl 3] I love you.
-[laughs]
-[girl 1] Come down and perform.
-[girl 2] Tyga.
-Tyga.
-[girl 3] I love you.
I can't believe you're really performing
in 20 minutes.
-That's what I'm not doing.
-[chuckles]
[Scott] Yo, tell them to flash us.
Are they old enough?
How old are you guys? Flash us.
[girls laugh]
[laughs]
[girl 1] Tyga.
-[Scott laughs]
-[girl 2] I love you.
Adventure Ridge.
See, those are the names of all the runs.
-Oh, okay.
-[Kris] Hi.
-[Corey] Watch your step.
[Kris] This is nice.
I haven't been up here in so long.
It's so pretty.
I've set up an amazing dinner
on top of the mountain
at the most beautiful restaurant.
I wanna take the family up
and enjoy the sunset.
[Kris] Here we are.
[Sheila] Oh, we're here.
-Wow.
-[Kris] It's so good.
[Sheila] Thank you.
Look at the sun setting.
-[Sheila] Wow.
-[Randy] Are you serious?
[Sheila]
Look at this. You're on top of the world.
Wow.
[Kris] It's stunning.
[Sheila] Look at that sunset.
Honest to God.
-We love you guys.
-[Corey] Love you too.
-[Kris] Love you.
-To the best trip.
And good night.
[phone chiming]
[Kris] You've got to be kidding me.
"Hi, Kris.
I saw that Rob and Angela, aka Chyna,
got engaged and I was wondering
if you can forward my e-mail below
over to Rob for consideration.
As you already know,
I'm the best wedding videographer
-in Northern California."
-[Randy] No.
"I just thought
I would reach out first, thanks."
That's crazy.
[Kris] Oh, my god.
[waiter] So are we waiting for
a few others to show up for dinner?
[Kris]
That's the 10-million-dollar question.
[line ringing]
-[Kim] Hi.
-[Kris] Hi.
[Kim]
I'm throwing everyone else under the bus.
No one else is on their way.
[somber music]
I'm dressed and ready to go.
I was totally on my way.
And I just think by the time
we get there, it's so dark already…
Okay, well, until we start doing
these family vacations,
so it's really a family vacation,
then I'm not doing this anymore.
[Kim] I swear, I was literally on my way.
We all should've done it together.
I love you and I promise
I'll make it up to you. I swear.
I've gone to so much trouble,
and if my kids don't give a [bleep],
then I don't give a [bleep].
I don't care anymore.
[Kris] They're just idiots.
[upbeat music]
-[woman] Hey.
-Opa. Opa.
[Scott] Work it.
[indistinct chatter]
[Scott]
Do we actually wanna go bowling or no?
Yeah, why not?
-[Khloé] Oh, hey.
-[Kendall] Care to join us?
-I can. Where is…
-[Khloé] Fancy Nancy strikes again.
-[Kourtney] Are you not going to Mom's?
-No, I felt so guilty.
[Kourtney]
Why didn't you go meet with Mom?
Because it was gonna be too dark
-and this sounded better, to be honest.
-[Tyga] What?
[Kim] My mom planned this big dinner
at the top of a mountain.
And truly, I woke up
this morning, worked out,
then went skiing,
then, you know, took my daughter skiing,
so I've had a full day.
So we decided to just eat
at the restaurant
that's right inside of the hotel.
It's just easier.
She's also there with her friends,
so I don't think she would mind.
Like, I don't know
why she's so disappointed.
[Kourtney] Should one of us call Rob?
I don't want to call our brother.
[Kourtney]
That's how you're feeling, but guess what?
How many are there of us?
You feel like
you don't want to talk to him.
-Good for you.
-You feel like you wanna talk to him?
[Kourtney] I feel like I'd like to--
Actually, I really,
really don't even care.
So, at a normal…
[Kylie] How the [bleep] are you gonna say
you don't even care?
[Tyga] She's gonna carry on the legacy.
If she has a boy?
I could change my kids' last name.
What the [bleep].
I'm sitting right here, you sick [bleep].
[Kourtney laughs]
[Tyga] Wait, all, all your guys' kids'
last name is Disick, right?
This bitch just said,
"I'm gonna try to change 'em."
No, I said I could
-change my kids' last name.
-[Scott] You could?
What the [bleep] is wrong with you?
So that she couldn't have the last name.
It's a joke.
[Todd] I remember you guys saying,
you know what,
we're gonna try snowboarding,
and then Kourtney decided to fall,
and what happened?
-[Kourtney] Break my arm.
-You broke your arm.
[Kourtney] Within, like,
the first five minutes of snowboarding.
-Full cast?
-[Kourtney] Yeah, full cast.
-Yeah, I did.
-[Khloé] No, that's not a real story.
-[Scott] No. She swears it's real.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
Ask Kim if that's real.
[Scott] Kim, is that really true?
Kourtney actually says that she fell.
[Kourtney] That I had a full cast.
We thought that…
[Scott] Right. Okay, thank you.
-I rest my case.
-[Kourtney] We did.
[Kim] I don't know if it's true.
It was like 30 years ago.
[all laugh]
I know Kourt had a ton of anxiety
in regards to Scott coming on this trip,
which I totally understand,
but the more that we're on this trip,
and Scott is really proving himself,
I could just see
that her guards are getting let down,
and Kourtney's now having more fun,
and I could see those nerves
are completely leaving her.
Who the [bleep] are you waving at?
-[Kourtney] Those kids.
-[Scott] They didn't wave at you.
-[Kourtney] Yeah, they were.
-No, they weren't.
[Scott] Now they realize who you are.
-[Kourtney] Good.
-Are you insane?
-No.
-Those kids didn't wave at you.
-They were waving at us.
-No, they didn't.
-Yeah, they were.
-I'm gonna ask them.
[Tyga] Let's cheers.
-[Kendall and Khloé] To what?
-[Tyga] To, um…
just cheers to being blessed, having a…
-a great family.
-[Khloé] "Being blessed
-and having a great family."
-Yeah.
And you guys really don't realize that,
I'm on the outside looking in, but, like,
you guys have a really solid family.
-The family value is so strong, you know?
-Yeah.
[Tyga] Like, it's just a great thing.
Not a lot of people have
families like that,
-you know, so, like…
-[Khloé] Cheers to family.
Toast to Kris Jenner.
[Kourtney]
Toast to Kris Jenner for setting up
-this secret trip for us.
-[Khloé] Yes.
[Kendall] Even though she's not here,
she can feel it.
And just, like, doing this for all of us.
-[bleep]
-[Khloé] Doing the damn thing.
[Kourtney] Doing the damn thing.
[Khloé chuckles]
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
Wait, this is, like,
the nicest bowling alley I've ever seen.
Back here?
[Khloé] Mother[bleep].
How do you…
[Scott] Where's the pin master? Who's up?
[Khloé] Come on, Kim. I believe in you.
[upbeat music]
-[all cheering]
-Yeah, Kim.
[Khloé] What?
-There you go.
-[Kourtney] Can I do it?
[Khloé] Yeah.
[laughs]
Oh, yeah, Ye.
[all laughing, yelling]
[Khloé] I told you. It's rigged.
All right.
-Whoa.
-Oh, oh.
[Khloé] Oh, yeah.
-Whoo!
-Yeah.
[Scott] I got a strike.
[Khloé] Oh, you did?
I didn't even get to see you get a strike.
This is [bleep] bull [bleep].
[Khloé] No. Yeah.
This girl's twerking all over town now.
I'm over here striking 'em out.
[Khloé] Ow.
-Did it work?
-Yeah.
-[Khloé on recording] Oh, yeah.
-[Scott on recording] Oh, come on.
[Khloé] Who's winning?
-[Kendall] Ye.
-[Khloé] Pablo? Pablo.
Pablo, Pablo, Pablo.
-[Khloé] How are you on the trip?
-[Scott] Good.
Especially now that your boobs are
directly in my face.
"Let me ask you, how are you feeling?"
[Khloé] Do you get uncomfortable
that we're all drinking?
[Scott]
Nah. I don't care about that [bleep].
Like, is it rude?
No.
I, I would think it would be weird
if people didn't.
[Scott] I don't not drink, but…
I know, but not around Kourt, right?
Yeah.
-[Khloé] Why, 'cause there's too much…
-[Scott] No, I just told her I wouldn't.
-Oh, right, but she knows you do.
-Yeah.
[Khloé] Hmm.
[Scott] I don't lie to her
about anything anymore.
-[Khloé] Good.
-[Scott] Ever.
Even if she asks me,
like, the weirdest [bleep].
Hmm, easier that way,
-you don't have to remember.
-Ah, never.
[Khloé] Does it bother you
that she drinks now?
[Scott] No, [bleep] it,
I always want her to lighten up.
[Khloé] Yeah, but just, like,
is it awkward ever?
[Scott] I mean, of course.
But I can't imagine you not being here.
[Scott] Yeah, no, I mean, listen,
it's been, like, amazing
to be able to be around everybody,
and the kids, especially.
[pensive music]
[Scott] One of the biggest issues
between Kourtney and I for a long time
was me drinking, and a lot of times,
I think I get overly emotional
when I drink,
and that's a lot of the times
when Kourtney and I would fight.
And I told her, on this trip,
I just wouldn't drink.
I just want her to see
that I can keep it together.
-[Kourtney] Scott?
-Huh?
-[Kourtney] Avocado?
-[Scott] Oh, thanks.
Oh, she made you a plate. Oh, wow, ho…
Amazing, you talk to me for two minutes,
-she makes me a plate.
-[Khloé laughs]
-[Khloé] She made you food.
-[Scott] It's unbelievable.
[Khloé] Get another one, Pab.
-[Scott] Oh. Shoot.
-[Khloé] Oh!
[all cheering]
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] Scott.
-[Scott] Huh?
-Hey.
-[Scott] Holy [bleep].
You, like, have a glam room on a ski trip.
Don't you guys feel like
this is gonna, like,
-kind of make you look a little insane?
-We are insane.
Ooh, "Rob Kardashian,
'My family didn't know
jack about my engagement.'"
[tense music]
[Kim]
This is on TMZ, so it's all of our faces.
-[phone chimes]
-And it says,
"Rob Kardashian blindsided his family
not giving them the heads up
or even a hint about his engagement.
Sources familiar with the situation
tell us Rob went to great lengths
to keep Kim and company in the dark.
The women are not taking kindly
to being squeezed out.
And as reported, none of the women jumped
on social media to congratulate him."
-Why would we congratulate him?
-[phone chimes]
And no one should congratulate them.
That's so desperate
and fake of whoever does first
'cause I know someone's gonna break.
[Kylie] Tyga tweeted something.
-[Khloé] Saying what?
-[Kylie] He said,
"Everyone deserves to be happy.
What someone does for their happiness
is not my concern
as long as it's not interfering
with my happiness."
All the comments are like,
"Don't care anymore."
They're not bashing him anymore.
They're just like,
"Oh, okay, he doesn't care?
Good, we don't care."
People are trying to make it
this big feud and it's just…
it is what it is. Like, we just want Rob
to be happy.
I just feel like the world thinks
that we care so much
and they're making it this huge,
big deal, when in reality,
none of us really care.
We just want Rob to be able to tell us
when he's gonna do
something so big like this.
[Kylie] If people know
that we actually don't care…
[Khloé] As soon as no one cares
about them, it's gonna fizzle out.
[chuckles]
-God.
-[Kylie] No matter what we do,
we can't control what…
what's gonna happen between them.
I know that Kylie feels like
silence sometimes can, you know,
drag it on longer, and I agree.
Part of me wants to address this.
But then, on the other hand, like,
I do wanna talk to my brother first.
But at this point,
I don't really know what to do.
At the end of the day, it's his life, and…
[Khloé] His problem.
[tense music]
[upbeat music]
[Kendall] Where's Kylie?
We're so late, let's go.
[Kendall] As much fun as I'm having,
I have to get home
because I have a trip for work.
And I know Tyga's getting on a plane
'cause he has to go on tour.
So I'm just gonna hop
on the plane with him
and Kylie to prepare for that.
[Kendall] Bye, guys, love you.
[light music]
Bye, Mom, I love you. Bye.
[electronic music]
-Khloé?
-Yeah.
One time, we were on this, um, houseboat.
-Oh, jeez.
-And your dad went,
-went jet skiing.
-Yeah.
But he, like, two hours later,
never came back.
-Oh, god, I remember that.
-And we all could not find him.
And I was, like,
three, four months pregnant.
-That's so scary.
-[Kris] Yeah, it was scary.
And they were trying to calm me down,
and I'm like, "You guys don't understand,
my baby's not gonna have a dad."
-Oh, baby.
-I was like, "Oh, my god."
God, I wonder where Kylie gets
her dramatics from.
Oh.
I wonder where you get
your dramatics from.
I was thinking the exact same thing,
but I was…
-You were on the other boat barking.
-I was gonna keep my mouth shut.
[laughs]
[electronic music]
[background chatter]
Kourt, did you get the video I sent you,
-of, uh…
-[Kourtney] Mase?
-Yeah. Cute, huh?
-Yeah.
[Khloé]
You two are sitting next to each other?
[Khloé] [bleep] getting real.
[Scott] Oh, yeah.
-[Kourtney] Hey, Mom.
-Hi.
-[Kourtney] Is she sleeping?
-Yeah.
-Hi.
Since we, uh, missed
the dinner the other night,
when you wanted us to all come out,
I just want to say that,
you know, we're really sorry.
[light music]
It's something to really appreciate
having this,
like, big family and a big support system.
Sometimes we take it for granted.
And I know my mom planned this dinner,
and she's probably so upset about Rob,
and I feel like we should have gone,
and I feel really guilty
'cause we should just like be there
and be this, like,
emotional support for her
and have a good time.
[Kim] This has been such a fun trip.
Don't you guys think?
-[Kris] Yeah.
-So fun.
-[Randy] Yeah, super fun.
-[Khloé] The best.
Guys, let's have a toast.
Let's have a toast…
[Randy]
Toast to the hostess with the mostest.
-Cheers.
-[Kanye] Cheers.
[Khloé] North…
I wish I was you right now.
Aw, she's snoring.
[Khloé] She is snoring.
[light music]
I'm gonna put ice on your brother's booty,
I hope you know.
[Penelope] Why?
Because your brother put ice
down my boobies.
-[Khloé] You good?
-[Penelope] I'm gonna put something on.
[Khloé] What?
Ooh.
That was delicious.
Oh, so good.
It was worth it. I had a burger…
[Khloé] Oh, come here, Mase.
I got to tell you something.
Why does everybody
call sisters now sisters?
[Kris] 'Cause they, they do it?
-[Khloé] Hey, come here--
-Well, if you're in Sydney,
-it's sister this, sister that.
-[Khloé] Mason, come here.
-Let me throw a snowball at you.
-[Mason speaks indistinctly]
-[Khloé] Yeah.
-Oh.
[Khloé] Don't you dare.
-Don't you… Oh!
-Oh, jeez.
[Scott laughs]
[Khloé]
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Oh.
I wanna eat it so bad.
-[Mason] Eat it.
-[Khloé] No.
[quirky music]
Oh.
[grunts]
-[Kourtney] Wait, hold on.
-[Kris] You get this.
And then I'll jump in and we'll get it.
Here, here, here.
Perfect. One, two, three.
[electronic music]
[Kourtney] There's nothing like
walking through, like, a small town.
I think you're right.
[Kourtney] All right, Gorsuch it up.
[Kim]
Look at how cute these are, seriously.
-These flame pants?
-Yeah, and these?
Oh, not the… not the rhinestones.
They are cute if we were snowboarders.
[Kim] Were you so nervous
for Scott to come?
Like, I've been telling everyone I'm…
Like, Scott was amazing on this trip.
Yeah, I'm, like, really glad
I let him come
'cause I feel like
it's all about, like, the memories
and, like, for the kids
to, like, have him here.
[Kim] Totally.
And I feel like he's been…
-[Kim] He's been so good.
-…so good.
[Kim] Yeah.
And he's been totally fine.
Yeah, I know, he's been, like, amazing.
-Yeah.
-I was, like, so proud.
[Kourtney]
Yeah, I'm glad that he could be here.
It was a great decision
having Scott come on the trip.
And I think it's great for him
to know that…
he is always going to be
a part of our family.
Oh, this is so cute.
Do you like this on me or no?
[Kourtney] No.
Oh, well, that took care of that.
[Kourtney] Mom, you don't even ski.
[Kris] Oh, right. You're right.
[both laugh]
[Kris] Okay.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] I just heard
that you canceled Kocktails.
How do you feel?
Well, I was just pissed about the show.
It wasn't my vision anymore.
I don't think you should stop it.
Like, I'm a person
that's really particular about production
and the table has to be like this.
But when I was at Adidas,
when we were gonna do the first shoe,
I didn't wanna put it out.
I didn't like the shoe.
But I worked through it,
made the 350, and now I have,
like, better opportunities.
Like, I always wanted
to do Kocktails on my app.
-But can you call it Kocktails with Khloé?
-But don't stop.
Oh, I'm not gonna call it Kocktails.
[Kanye] Dicktails with Khloé.
Seriously. Tails from the [bleep].
-[bleep] and Roll.
-[Khloé] [bleep] and Roll.
[phone chimes]
Rob just wrote me, by the way,
and said, "Call me when you're alone."
[tense music]
-Rob?
-Yeah.
I didn't respond.
[Khloé] There's no loyalty
or family unity with him.
-It's bizarre.
-He's just… That's his personality.
[Khloé] I hate that other people know more
about our family than we know.
As long as we know,
we could be a united front,
but if we don't know,
then there's cracks in the foundation,
and everything's gonna go to [bleep].
Caitlyn did it and now Rob's doing it.
He's the weak link in the bunch,
and he needs to be cut.
Let's get a new link.
[tense music]
There's no loyalty
or family unity with him.
-It's bizarre.
-He's just…
That's his personality.
He's the weak link in the bunch,
and he needs to be cut.
Let's get a new link.
The mom whole animosity is at you two.
And that's what I don't, I don't like.
Did you see what she just wrote
about all of us
and how we weren't invited to the wedding?
[Khloé] Why does she even comment?
Both me and Kim have been in situations
where we were with someone
that all of our friends hated.
And family.
[dramatic music]
[Kim] I've definitely been
in a situation before
where my family hasn't always approved,
so I know what he must feel,
and he probably doesn't wanna reach out,
thinking that we are being judgmental,
so I think maybe
I should make the first move?
I think I wanna write Rob
to put an end to…
[clicks tongue]
…like, the beef.
I commend Kim
for wanting to reach out to Rob.
I mean, I… it's huge on her part.
I wouldn't reach out
just because I'm stubborn,
and I just don't really give a [bleep].
I think I would even start
and explain like,
"Look, I'm not, like, an idiot, like--"
-I have no tolerance for him.
-[Kim] 'Cause I know your--
It's nuts that Rob doesn't care
to say something.
Like, you're our brother.
The psychic wrote me
that exact thing today.
Who said that?
The psychic texted me and says,
"Hey, I'm in the airport,
and I see on the magazines,
and I'm… Like, on the TV
of what's going on…
and your brother…"
Well, why does he need
to see that if he's a psychic?
[all laugh]
[upbeat music]
[Scott] I got to tell you,
you look very sexy
-with your beard trimmed down.
-[Todd] You like that?
[Scott laughing]
[Todd] Thank you, thank you.
So, do you, like… Do you know how long
the sled, the, uh, sled riders…
[Scott] Snowmobiling?
-[Scott] It's probably up to us…
-[Todd] It's probably an hour…
-…whenever you're bored.
-[Todd] I feel like I remember doing this.
So you go, like… up to, like,
a beautiful, like, summit,
where you can see,
like, a beautiful view--
[Scott] You don't think anybody's
gonna take pics and Snapchat?
I mean, what else is there to do
when you're on a…
-[Scott] Nothing.
-Nothing.
And then, I think there's probably,
like, a big open field,
where you just, let loose and go,
like, 60 miles an hour and have fun.
[Scott] Dude, you just sold
the living hell out of that.
-[Todd] Right?
-Do you work for the snowmobile company?
[Todd] So, I'm actually offering coupons
for next season if you get it now--
And guess what, you can save
15 percent if you switch to…
-[Todd] If you go to Kawasaki, yeah.
-…snowmobiles.
[Todd] There's about 62 more horsepower
in the Kawasaki versus the Yamaha.
-And fuel efficiency is far superior.
-[Todd] Really.
[Randy] I'm not gonna go
60 miles an hour on it.
-And I don't think I'm going up the thing.
-Just do every… Just go fast.
The faster you go, the safer you are.
You gotta jump [bleep].
You gotta go fast, all right?
-[Todd] He's right.
-[Scott] Maybe you should stay home.
-I'm getting worried.
-[all laugh]
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Hold on.
[man] And personal preference,
would you like the open face…
-What do you think, the open face or this?
-…or would you like closed face?
-Maybe the closed face.
-I want a closed face.
Today, we're all going snowmobiling.
[Kim] I love doing all these fun
family activities together.
It's been like the perfect trip.
-[Kris chuckles]
-[smooches]
[Scott] Mase, you ready?
Let's head out.
[Kim] Okay, look. I'm gonna sit here,
and you can sit with me, okay?
-[Scott] Good.
-[Kourtney] How'd you get the water in?
[Scott]
Here, you want me to give you some?
-[instructor] Everybody ready?
-[Kanye] Yeah, we ready.
[engines rev]
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Whoa. Whoa.
[Kim] What's wrong, sweetie?
[North] But I'm singing.
[Kim] Oh, you're singing.
Oh, I thought you were crying.
[engine revving]
[Kim] I won.
I think the snowmobiling is definitely
one of the highlights of the trip.
It's really, really quite amazing
for all of us
to be in like one pack together
going up this beautiful mountain.
It's a really great time to get out
of your own head, I think,
and just be able to let go
of everything else that's happening.
[Kourtney] Two, three…
Boom.
[man] Come on, Mason, follow me.
[Scott] Yeah, Marty.
Kid's loose.
[Khloé laughing]
[Scott] Having fun?
[Mason] Yeah.
-[Scott] Are you going full throttle?
-[Mason] Uh-huh.
-As fast as you can?
-Yeah.
-You're going all the way, right?
-Uh-huh.
-All right, don't let off.
-Okay.
[Scott] Here, put your fingers all here
and not just your thumb.
-[Mason] Okay.
-All right, lean into the turns a bit.
[Mason] Okay.
[engine rumbling]
[upbeat music]
[Kris] It's so interesting
because back in the day,
when your mom and I used to take
-all of you guys skiing…
-[Todd] Mm-hm.
…it would take us literally
an hour and a half
-to get you guys dressed.
-Mm-hm.
First, you put on the long johns…
then we put on a cotton turtleneck,
a sweater over that, overalls,
the ski socks.
-I mean, 75 pieces of clothing.
-[Todd chuckles]
I really wish… We had so much fun today,
but I really wish
Kendall and Kylie would've come.
I always miss whoever's not here,
just like I miss it
when Rob isn't here all the time.
[pensive music]
[Kris] I haven't spoken to Rob
since I heard the news
about his engagement,
and it's hard because, you know what?
He's my son
and I want him to be really, really happy.
That's all that we've got in life.
But when it comes to Rob,
and this whole situation,
I just don't know what to do.
It's making me a little bit sad.
That's what moms do.
Moms worry
and moms love…
Yeah.
…and moms miss their kids.
[upbeat music]
[Todd] We have to go
to the living room or be down here?
[Khloé] Upstairs.
[Todd] So, upstairs.
-Where'd Scott go?
-[Kourtney] He went to bed.
Oh, come on.
He said he wants to wake up early
in the morning and so do I.
[Khloé] Are you leaving… Oh.
But I'm not leaving yet.
[Khloé] Oh, yeah.
Is that your little foreplay?
You almost… Just the tip,
and then, you shoved it on in.
[Kourtney]
I just touched your little [bleep].
You did, but you got me
raging waters, girl.
-Yeah. Girls and guys.
-Okay. Okay.
Should, should we stand over there?
-[Todd] Yeah, but I can stand behind you.
-[Khloé] Yeah, no.
Ready, set…
[chuckles]
[laughing]
-[Khloé] There's so much pressure.
-[Kanye] Tell them that I'm gonna play.
I'm gonna play one round.
[all laughing]
[Kim]
We have had so much fun here in Vail,
and, when we used to come years ago,
all the kids would, like, play kid games
and then, downstairs,
the adults would play adult games
that we couldn't be around for.
So it's fun that now we're older
and we're playing games.
Let's see what it comes down
to at the end.
I can't hear. What?
[Kim] The fact that,
with our own kids and our own families,
we can really carry on these traditions,
just makes it so special
and it's the best way to end the trip.
[Kourtney]
Good game. Girls win, obviously.
Obviously.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] Yay, we're here.
The Chocolate Factory.
-[Todd] Yay.
-[Khloé] Yay.
-[Sheila] Ice cream.
-Do you want chocolate sprinkles
-or rainbow sprinkles?
-[Mason] Um, chocolate.
[Scott] Look at this.
Do you want a necklace?
-[Kourtney] Can we taste a birthday cake?
-[woman] Yeah.
-So good.
-[Kourtney] Are you sure?
-Uh-huh.
-Okay, birthday cake, please.
[happy music]
[Kourtney] I was definitely really nervous
about, you know,
Scott coming on this trip,
but I think it's nice
that we can all hang out together
and, like, have fun.
I'm not stressed out.
Like, I think it's just nice
that we can all just be, like,
one big family.
[Randy] What do you wanna do?
Go… go to the river and party.
[all laughing]
[upbeat music]
Oh, my god, thanks, Mom.
[Kris]
They only had one, but I thought of you.
-Thanks, Mom.
-[Kris] For relaxing.
-Lay at home in your sock shirt.
-Oh, and it's so cozy.
Right?
Ooh, Mom.
That's a good one, thank you.
Thank you, cutie.
[Kourtney] Hey, guys?
-[Khloé] Chimichanga. Jolly good.
-[Kris] Jolly good.
Oh, the brownies look so good.
We were thinking
of staying tomorrow and skiing.
[upbeat music]
[Todd] Who's staying? You?
Me and Scott and the kids.
[Corey] That'll be fun, Kourt.
[Kourtney] Yeah.
[gentle music]
[Kourtney] We were thinking
of staying tomorrow and skiing.
[Todd] Who's staying? You?
Me and Scott and the kids.
[indistinct chatter]
It makes me really happy
to know that Kourtney and Scott
are having so much fun
that they wanna stay another day.
I'm just hopeful that maybe
this is the new Scott
who really enjoys life,
and it's all about family.
I hope it's gonna last.
Think we're gonna ice skate tonight.
That's fun.
[Kris] Really fun.
What time are you being picked up?
Now. Kim and Kanye are already in the car.
[Todd] Thanks for coming, guys.
[Kris] Oh, thanks for having us, Todd.
-Listen, any time.
-Y'all be safe, everybody.
Okay, bye. Love you. Thanks for planning
such an amazing trip.
I love you, honey.
-[Randy] You're not leaving.
-Yes, I am.
[Khloé] I'm out of here.
[upbeat music]
North's at Kanye's. Hey, North.
-[North] No. No, no.
-[Kanye] Mommy's calling you.
[growling, chuckling]
[North giggles]
[North] I want to watch a… a girl movie.
-Oh, okay.
-A girl movie.
Here. Give it to Mom.
Whoa.
I need a little help.
[Kim] Okay, here, I got it.
[Kris]
So, Kanye, how'd you like that town?
[Kanye] That we just went to?
It's a sweet town.
[Khloé] I thought that this was
the perfect time of year.
Me too.
-I love not being cold.
-[Khloé] Me too.
-[Kris] I wasn't on the mountain, so--
-I would choose hot over cold any day.
Kind of surprised
Kourtney ended up staying.
We haven't been to Vail
in so long, and they both…
I mean, we're having
a good time, and the kids.
She wants the kids to, like,
get those memories.
She said it was really good for them.
Scott was in such a good mood today,
yesterday, and the day before.
I've never seen him have so much fun.
Like, he was doing everything
he loves to do.
I'm just happy everyone's getting along.
That's all I care about.
The only thing
that will always be missing is Rob.
[Khloé] Mm-hm.
[pensive music]
[Kim] Minus the little Rob drama,
it was such a good trip.
Like, everyone was having fun.
This trip has been so amazing,
even though there's been
some drama with Rob.
So now that we're, you know,
on our way home
and back to reality,
I, you know, I reached out to Rob.
I think it's time that we talked.
So now, you know,
I'm just waiting for him to respond
and the ball is really in his court.
[Kim] On the next episode…
Friday is the Lip Kit launch.
I know, it's so soon.
[Kylie] I am stressing out right now.
I really hope
that everything goes perfect.
[loud gasp]
Oh, [bleep].
[Kylie] Oh, my god, you guys, you guys.
You guys obviously know.
We should've just at least got a text.
If you guys really wanted to know,
you guys would've said, "Is this true?"
[Khloé] You [bleep] idiot,
what do you want me to do?
Hold a press conference?
And then there's one more thing
I have to talk to you guys about.