[upbeat music]
We're gonna play charades
and we're gonna do movie titles,
but we're making them into porn titles.
No, I don't like that.
-Okurrr.
-[Kourtney] It's wack.
Can I just do the charades, please?
This is the worst game night
I've ever been invited to.
-[Kourtney] Yeah. This game night…
-And definitely my last.
-…is wack.
-This is not a [bleep]
-game though.
-[Khloé] Where should I do it?
-Are you guys re--
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-This game's working out good.
-You got to look at me
to play this game.
-It is silent.
-That's what happens.
-This is so exciting.
-Go.
[Jonathan] Two words.
-[Kourtney] First word.
-[Kim] First word.
-[Jonathan] Titties.
-Tits.
-[Kourtney] Second word.
-[Kim] Committee.
[laughs]
[Kourtney] Hair.
[Jonathan] Slick.
-Tittie Slick?
-[Kim] Tittie Slickers.
-[laughs]
-[Jonathan] Oh, Tittie Slickers.
-That's funny.
-You're so…
-so creative.
-[Khloé cackles]
-[squealing]
-[laughter]
Trying to get…
You did it! You did it!
I didn't do [bleep].
-What did I do?
-[Khloé] Exactly.
[Jonathan] She actually didn't do
one part of that game.
[Khloé] You did nothing.
You better be careful.
-An earring and the hair.
-Not the earring.
The hair's not mine, so I don't care.
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
-[woman 1] All right, you ready?
-Yeah.
[crowd clamoring, yelling]
We're right there in the Forum Club.
[woman 1] And you go left.
[crowd cheering]
Tonight, Kanye is revealing his new video
for the song Famous.
He's been working on this video
for a really long time.
You know, I've seen this whole journey
and the whole making of
and process of this video.
It's gonna be so much fun,
I can't wait to see people's reactions.
[crowd chanting]
Kanye!
[Kanye] I want to thank
all y'all and my family.
My wife.
[crowd cheering]
Y'all supporting ideas and truth.
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[female fan] I love you, Kanye!
[indistinct chatter]
[distorted, overlapping voices]
[Rihanna] ♪ Man, I can understand
How it might be ♪
♪ Kinda hard to love a girl like me ♪
That's crazy.
♪ I don't blame you much
For wanting to be free ♪
♪ I just wanted you to know ♪
[crowd cheering]
[Kanye] ♪ Swizz told me
Let the beat rock ♪
♪ For all my Southside [bleep]
That know me best ♪
♪ I feel like me and Taylor
Might still have sex, why? ♪
-♪ I made that… ♪
-[crowd] …bitch famous!
-♪ Damn, I made that… ♪
When Kanye decided to make
a video for Famous,
he had, like, so many different ideas
and he thought,
why not do,
like, the craziest one, and have
some of the most famous,
or notorious people, in bed together.
He saw it more of, like,
there's so much craziness
around everything,
that this was, like,
their peaceful resting time.
["Famous" by Kanye West playing]
[Khloé] It is crazy high energy.
I know everybody is loving
the video, loving the song.
I think everyone's reaction,
how everybody is just dancing
and, like, just going crazy…
♪ I just wanted you to know ♪
[crowd cheering]
[crowd chanting]
Yeezy, Yeezy, Yeezy, Yeezy…
I'm, like, dying to see
what Twitter is, like, talking about.
Every single time, man.
Oh, my god. Damn.
Babe, look at these images online.
-Sorry.
-It's crazy.
The video is incredibly controversial.
Kanye loves to shock people
and to do things
that gets everybody talking.
But Kanye is also so good
at how he does that, he's so creative.
Wait, Caitlyn just called me.
[line ringing]
-[Caitlyn] Hello?
-Hey.
It was so good.
Has anyone been calling you?
No, I haven't heard anything.
I'm in Aspen right now.
It went so amazing.
Kanye broke the Internet tonight.
Like, for real, for real.
Most important,
you looked really good, so…
Oh, that's good.
[Kim] It was so realistic
and you looked so pretty in it.
The only person we told
about the Famous video is Caitlyn.
She didn't quite know everything about it
or really what it was,
but she trusts Kanye.
So, Caitlyn was happy to be a part of it.
You look amazing.
I'm gonna send you a picture
and zoom in. Okay, bye.
Bye.
[Kim] That went well.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] I love this room.
-[Khloé] You do?
-Yeah, and I love
how you have
all the fresh flowers all the time.
[Kris]
I should have fresh flowers in my room.
Well, why don't you?
-[Kim] You don't?
-[Kris] Nope.
What a tragedy.
[Kris]
So wait, has anybody reached out today?
About the video?
I mean, everyone had
something to say. It was, like…
-[Kim] It like, literally…
-[Khloé] He was the male version of Kim,
-breaking the Internet.
-That, like, broke the Internet.
Like, for sure.
I was speechless watching it,
'cause I didn't know what to--
I didn't know
what I was gonna be looking at.
To see that up on the screen, that big,
it was kind of crazy,
creepy, powerful, magnificent,
everything all at the same time.
It's artistic.
How did he pick each person?
Like, how did he decide,
"This is my list"?
Every person is a strong fixture
in Kanye's life.
Like, Anna Wintour put him
on the cover of Vogue.
-Taylor Swift.
-[Khloé] Taylor Swift…
[Kim] And then, you know,
Rihanna's in the song.
-[Kris] Yeah.
-And then, Chris Brown
right next to her.
-And then…
-[Khloé] George Bush.
[Kim] Amber, Ray J, Bill Cosby,
Donald Trump, and Caitlyn.
[Kris] Why Caitlyn?
[Kim] He just, like, likes people
that are authentic,
that do what they wanna do.
I guess I didn't realize how much time
Kim has been spending with Caitlyn.
And I had no idea
that Caitlyn was going to be in the video.
It was shocking.
[imitates gunshots]
Actually, I don't like guns,
so I don't wanna ever make that motion.
Oh, my god.
[chuckles]
It wasn't loaded.
[upbeat music]
Yes. That's…
-[Jonathan] No, you really do.
-[Khloé] This is our appetizer.
[Kris] Okay.
[Khloé] Who did your glam today?
There's, like, something where I'm like,
so envious of you right now.
-Really?
-[Khloé] Yeah.
I'm talking about, like,
your body, everything.
Like, it's really kind of [bleep] with me.
-What? You're, like…
-[Khloé] Yeah. Like…
-…the skinniest person ever.
-[Jonathan] Now it's [bleep] with you?
-It should have been [bleep] with you…
-[Khloé] No, but there's…
…three years ago. Now, you're on.
-[Khloé] No, but it was [bleep] with me.
-Yeah, you're good.
It was my whole life,
it's [bleep] with me.
Then I had
about two and a half solid years
where she was pregnant and I was good.
And now, she's, like, back.
You didn't think
she was gonna get this back?
Like, she has this…
which I don't-- I don't have this,
'cause she has big tits and a small waist,
-and a big ass.
-[Kim] I wish my--
I literally took a screengrab
of your… of your shirt,
when we were in New York.
Your boobs were, like, fully,
-perfectly perky, up. I have--
-[Khloé] There's no boobs.
-There's no cleavage. Look at that.
-I wish.
-[Khloé] I wish.
I have no waist because I have no tits.
If I get tits, I'll have a waist.
Ever since I've lost weight,
you lose weight everywhere,
so I've lost some extra cleavage
that once helped these things look
a little bigger.
Now, I feel a good more bottom heavy
than top heavy,
and I want to have, like…
you know, the hourglass thing going on.
It's really now, like,
I'm, like, really irritated.
-Well…
-[Khloé] I had the best workout
this morning and now I feel like
I need to go work out again.
-Why, what'd you do?
-Just look at Kim.
[Jonathan] Inspiration.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] You're just such a hater.
[Scott] How am I a hater? On what?
-On everything.
-Tell me which part.
I had no idea that I was such a hater.
Just 'cause I try to help you.
I won't help again.
Okay.
In London, I was trying to help you
with your outfits.
[Kourtney] No, you said,
"Everyone's texting me, congratulating me
that you're pregnant with my kid,
because you look pregnant in this photo."
-You said that to somebody?
-That's not a hater.
I always try to give you compliments
and tell you what looks good
and what doesn't.
Being a hater is saying, "Hey, do you--"
Oh, you said,
"Do you edit your Snapchats?"
-I never said that.
-[Kourtney] Yeah, you did.
You said, "Do you edit your Snapchats?"
I said, "You can't edit Snapchats."
-"And no, I don't take time to do that."
-[Scott] I never asked that.
-Yeah, you did.
-I said Instas.
Mm-mm. You said Snapchats.
I don't even know about Snapchat.
You could edit it?
I don't edit mine.
I don't think you can.
[Kourtney] Drinking that Haterade.
So, I finally made my plans
for the summer.
-Are the kids gonna be in camp?
-[Kourtney clears throat]
-[Kourtney] No.
-[Kris] What are you gonna do?
We're gonna go out of town for a month.
For a month?
Mm-hm. Like, three weeks.
Are you going?
I'm trying to understand what she's doing.
-[Kris] Is Scott going?
-No.
I'll send you guys an itinerary,
but it's top secret, for now.
It's the middle of the summer
and it's, like, really important to me
to take time with my kids
and just get out of town, and live life.
I have an idea of some places
that we wanna go,
but I haven't really figured out exactly
what we're going to do.
I just wanna see
where the summer takes us.
Okay, listen.
We're gonna have the best summer ever,
and you're gonna go on an amazing vacation
with the three kids.
And you should be looking at this like,
"Wow, she's taking the kids
on a vacation."
They could be stuck at home.
Like, walking around the house
driving you crazy.
-And you could be babysitting.
-I like that.
[dramatic music]
There's 11 other months out of the year
you can do that.
You know, hearing Kourtney say
that she's gonna go on
some month-long vacation,
I realize that Kourtney and I
aren't together,
but we do spend, like,
every day together with the kids.
It does feel like a very, very long time.
She's just annoying.
[Scott] She's just so rude.
[imitates Kourtney]
Like, let me find out and tell you
the day before.
-She's just playing with you.
-No, she's not.
[upbeat music]
Your last fragrance launch was in 2014.
So, critical time right now
to really build a brand new signature.
-[Kim] Mm-hm.
-You've evolved. You've changed.
[Kim] Yeah, I think new name,
-new logo.
-Yeah,
-we should.
-Like, it could be Kim Kardashian West,
-you know, instead of…
-[Kris] Yeah.
-With a new logo and, like…
-[Kris] That's great.
[publicist 1] Absolutely.
So, everyone will know,
like, the Kim Kardashian stuff
and Kim Kardashian West is all,
like, the new stuff.
I am so excited to relaunch my fragrance.
It's, like, a whole new team,
and I just loved working
on all of my fragrances before,
and I'm excited to have a new one.
I mean, I love, like, obviously,
Elizabeth Taylor
and what she's done
with her fragrance business,
-even, you know…
-[publicist 2] It's tremendous business.
-…after her passing.
-Yes.
[Scott] Yo.
-[Kris] Hey.
-[publicist 2] Hi.
What's, uh… what's happening over here
-at this big table?
-[laughter]
Our big business meeting.
-Fragrance meeting.
Oh, it smells good in here.
-[laughter]
-[gasps]
-I was kidding. It's the pastries.
-[publicist 1] Well put.
[publicist 2] Well put.
If you're nice to me, I might do
-a Scott Disick men's cologne.
-Yes.
I'd love to get something, that, uh, says,
"I like you, but still, [bleep] off"
at the same time.
-[laughter]
-Okay.
-Wait, what are you doing?
-[publicist 1] I think it sounds like
-the best seller.
-I thought we were hanging out today.
-Were we?
-[Scott] Yeah.
Whatever. I mean, it's cool.
I'll just wait for a little bit.
Kourtney and the kids
just left town a couple of days ago.
And it already feels like
they've been gone about a year.
It's definitely difficult. I mean,
I'm used to seeing my kids
every single day.
Any time I have too much time on my hands,
I'm not exactly sure what to do.
-So, it's hard.
-[Kim] I feel really bad
I have so many meetings. Can we, uh…
I thought you said yesterday
we'll go run around.
Go to Maria's.
[Kim] I know, but I totally forgot.
Please don't be mad at me.
-Please, please, please.
-[Scott] I'm not mad. It just…
it felt like you made plans.
[Kim]
I know, but this house meeting came up.
-[Scott] All right. Bye.
-[Kim] Bye.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé]
I've just got to tailor up some jeans.
[Monica] Okay.
[Khloé] 'Cause I'm so thin.
You are too skinny, please stop.
And because I'm so thin,
I don't have boobies anymore.
Well, we wanna get boobs one day.
Wait, I'm obsessed with your boobs.
I don't think you need boobs.
[Monica]
And you have that bra that literally…
-makes your boobs--
-[Khloé] I know, but not everyone wants
to wear a bra all the time.
I thought about getting my boobs done
for years.
Never really that serious about it,
because I've always had
somewhat decent-sized boobs.
But now I'm thinking,
"Okay, well, maybe I want
to get my boobs done."
I got these. Do you know
they sell these with nipples?
I don't want big boobs, I just want…
-Oh, my god.
-What in the hell?
-[Monica laughs]
-[Khloé and Monica] Hi.
[Scott] What are you holding on there?
Monica and I were just talking
about boobs.
-Those are nice boobs.
-You came into a…
-really good conversation.
-[Khloé] You really scared me.
I want more, like, full…
what is it, like, full circumference.
-[Monica] But you are a "C."
-You want a little more
-side boob.
-[Khloé] I'm really a "B" now.
[Scott]
If you're gonna be so bottom heavy,
-you got to be top too.
-Right. Like,
-don't you think I need bigger boobs?
-Yeah.
She's like a big booty ho
-video vixen.
-Yeah.
[Scott] She needs to be up and popping.
-[Monica] Well, let's try the dress on.
-Yeah.
-[Scott] Let's get those titties popping.
-[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Ooh, let me see what's popping.
-Ooh! Getting them titties on.
-[Khloé] The other one? Give it to me.
[Scott] Pop that bad boy in here.
Now that's proportional.
[Scott] Pow, pow!
[Khloé] But Scott, you don't think
my butt shrunk?
I mean, it's still out there
and living the dream.
[Monica] I have these.
That's kind of just, put it on the side,
so it just gives it a little…
-[Khloé] Oh!
-Ooh. Shake and bake.
Scott, that's very inappropriate.
[Scott] I want to make sure
that you're good.
I know how you like it rough.
[chuckles]
I don't think it looks bad
the way it is, Khlo.
I have fake boobs in here right now.
Like I said, I don't think it looks bad.
Look, if you saw me
at a wedding like this,
-would you be like…
-[Scott] If you were with a date
-or without a date?
-No, either…
-Would you be like…
-Either way, I'd be like, "Damn!"
"…I wish that bitch was on my arm."
[Scott] On my [bleep], not arm.
-Okay.
-[Monica] You are not allowed
at my fittings anymore.
Monica, I love you
and I think you do an amazing job.
Just let her get a little tittie on.
[laughs]
Oh, my god.
-I mean, [bleep] it.
-[Khloé] I hate him.
Okay, let me throw these on.
Oh, my god!
-Kim K.
-Hi, guys.
[Khloé] Do you like these boobs?
[Kim] Why on earth
would you want to get your boobs done?
I think it, like,
so suits you and fits you.
Do you know how much
of a confidence builder this is?
What are you doing in here?
This… Kourtney…
This is, like, really inappropriate.
-For who, Khloé or me?
-[Khloé] No, Scott…
-[Kim] Both of you.
-Scott and I do this
all the time.
[laughs]
Obviously, these implants are not
the real thing,
but I love the way they look.
[chuckles]
[Scott] Wow. Now you're talking.
Get the--
But you got to hold them up, right.
All of a sudden,
you can dance like a stripper.
Get it, girl. Show me
what you're working with.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Should I try to go up here?
I've never been this way.
I just want to experiment.
But do you know where you're going?
Oh, don't tell me
there's a lot of traffic right here.
[phone ringing]
[Kim] Hi.
[Caitlyn] Kimmy.
Caitlyn.
Baby, how ya doin'?
Good. I'm just riding
around town with Khloé.
[Khloé] Hey, Cait.
Baby, I haven't seen you forever.
Yeah, we texted the other day.
Oh, just briefly.
-Briefly, yeah.
-[Caitlyn] Yeah.
But anyway, Kim, I got a, uh, a request.
-Yeah?
-[Caitlyn] Are you ready?
-Yes, I'm ready.
-All right.
I got to do the ESPYs next week.
I was thinking,
why don't I give Kim a call
and see what she would come up with?
Okay. I can definitely help you
find something.
I know how important
the ESPYs are to Caitlyn,
so, of course, I want
to help her pick out an outfit.
I've always said, just make sure
you represent and dress appropriately.
[Caitlyn] The ESPYs, you can do any--
You can go formal, full-length.
Basically, anything that you want to do.
-Okay. I will figure it out.
-Yeah.
Oh! We're working together.
Kim Kardashian, my stylist.
Next time, Khloé, you can do it.
[both] Okay.
I'm a little more ratchet
than… than Kim is.
-[Caitlyn] I love that.
-[both chuckle]
-Okay.
-[Caitlyn chuckles]
[Caitlyn]
All right. I'll talk to you guys later.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
Love you. Bye.
She has no idea what ratchet is.
-No clue.
[both laugh]
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Whoa. Is this like
a whole workout room?
Dude, this place is no joke.
I'm getting buff over here.
[Khloé] I didn't know
you even knew how to do that.
[exhales sharply]
Oh, my god.
I'm gonna be huge
by the time I leave here.
[Scott chuckles]
That toilet doesn't look,
like, super comfy.
-[Khloé] It is.
-[Scott] Is it?
[Khloé] Why are you, like,
going through everything?
Ever since Kourt has left town
with the kids,
Scott has been over quite a bit.
And it's a little stressful.
[chuckles]
-[Scott] Let me ask you a question.
-[Khloé] Mm?
[Scott]
You got to get rid of some of this.
Why don't you throw this bad boy up there?
No, no, because those two go together
-as a piece.
-[Scott] What do you mean?
As a horse and carriage?
-Holy [bleep], this thing is heavy.
-It's real.
[quirky music]
[gasping nervously]
[Khloé gasps]
No, no. No, no. It stands up.
[Scott] Where is it supposed to go?
[Khloé] Stand. Yeah.
[Scott] I just broke
at least a hundred dollars
worth of this thing.
[Khloé] Okay. No, no. I got it.
You, literally, are no help.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Nope. No more touching.
[Scott] A lot of fun stuff in here.
Oh, my god.
Is this table
not really centered to the TV,
or it's centered to the wall?
Centered to the [bleep] thing,
I don't know!
It's centered to something!
What the [bleep]?
[Khloé] I can't handle this right now!
Seriously, what else
-is wrong with this room?
-Wait. Let me just…
-let me just fix it.
-No. For what?
Here's the [bleep] edge.
-What the [bleep] do you want me to do?
-Okay, okay.
All right, here. How about this?
How about you look down
and take a look at the speakers?
-No. I don't give…
-And then look at that side,
-and then look at that side.
-…a [bleep]. I've been fine here
-for how long?
-[Scott] That speakers half-closed
-and that's not.
-[bleep] that
because you're [bleep] stressing me out.
-So, no. We're not doing that anymore.
-I'd be stressed out too,
if my table was sideways.
I love Scott,
and I want to be there for him,
and I want to support him,
but he has got to stop touching
my [bleep].
Because I just want to kill him.
Like, I am too OCD for this.
Clearly, he has no idea
what to do with his time.
[Khloé] You have got to get out.
[upbeat music]
Is this a hairless peach?
[Scott] You're asking me
if that's a hairless peach?
What do you think I'm gonna think about?
This one went and got a Brazilian.
This is obviously a nectarine.
How the [bleep]
was I supposed to know that?
-What's the difference?
-Obviously, you're not
-a fruit specialist.
-Wait, I've got a-- Oh, my god.
-You're gonna Google a nectarine?
-[phone chimes]
Nectarine versus peaches.
[Khloé] "A peach and a nectarine are
very similar.
Genetically, there's not much difference
between the two.
-The main difference is that…
-[Scott] One's hairless?
a peach has fuzz on its skin,
while a nectarine does not."
-I'm not an idiot.
-[Khloé] Oh, wait, "Nectarines are
a bit more likely
to be affected by diseases,
-such as brown rot and bacterial spots."
-[Scott] The nectarine?
Well, it's 'cause it's got no bush.
-Right. There's nothing to protect it.
-Right.
You wonder why in the '80s
the girls weren't getting STDs
like they were today.
[Khloé chuckles]
You know, this is gonna be, like,
the longest I'm away from the kids
and Kourt, ever.
[Khloé] How do you feel?
Oh, I'm kind of anxious.
[Scott]
I'm supposed to do some appearances.
I just feel like I, like,
want to book my time,
so like, I don't think
about missing the kids and Kourtney.
-But at the same time--
-[Khloé] But are you gonna be
on your best behavior?
-Worse!
-Oh, my god. You probably are.
Well, I mean, it's hard to be
on amazing behavior
when you're at a nightclub or at a party.
Just make sure you're doing
whatever you think is best.
Well, I usually would do it strictly
because of money.
-[Khloé] Right. So, do you…
-'Cause I like money.
…need the money?
I could probably make money
other ways that are healthier.
Why don't you try that first?
You could go into your hobby
of flipping houses.
I could work on my houses.
I'm still gonna miss the kids.
I just feel like if I went to Europe
and I did some parties,
I probably would totally not think
about anything.
[Khloé] Kourt and the kids have been gone
about a week now.
In the past, when Scott had downtime,
he would book parties
and club appearances,
and nothing good ever came out of that.
So for him to even be thinking
of booking a club appearance again
really has me worried.
Think it through, and don't just do it
'cause you're bored.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] That one's, like, a little too big.
-I don't think you'd want to go that size.
-Which one?
-This one or this one?
-[Kim] Let me see them both.
This one feels heavier,
but the shape might be better.
The one on the left looks, like, bigger.
[Kim] That's all you've ever wanted,
is cleavage.
Look at that. That's amazing.
-That's, like, huge.
-[Khloé] That's amazing, right?
You would never go that big, would you?
-You talkin' to me?
-[Kim] I don't think they look bad.
[Khloé]
I totally look like an Instagram whore.
Whore. Boring.
It really is a tougher way to live.
Oh, my god, I'm finally you.
[gasps]
Oh, my god.
[Kim] I mean, Khloé looks beautiful
no matter what.
I love small boobs,
but, like, I've always had big boobs.
I think Khloé doesn't get
how hard it is to workout
when you really have, like, big boobs,
like, bouncing around everywhere.
So I wanted to work out with Khloé
so that she can really test out
her bigger boobs.
[Don] How's everybody's body feeling?
-[Khloé] Fabulous.
-[Kim] Really tired.
All right, what are we doing today?
[Don] Let's start here
on the ball for the warm-up.
You just get some blood flow right now.
Pull it, knee up, drop.
Good. Two up. Three up.
Look at how big my boobs…
Do a little jump up this time.
Up, two, up. Good.
I've always wanted, like,
cleavage in a sports bra.
Like, I love those girls at the gym
that just got big ol' boobs.
And I never really have that.
So, I'm digging
this whole cleavage-in-a-sports-bra thing.
-[Don] Nine, eight…
-[Kim] Oh, my god, you're way heavier
than usual.
-[Don] …seven, six…
-Shut up.
-[Kim] You do.
-[Don] …five…
I do feel like the boobs pass the test.
So, I don't feel like it hurts
to go get a consultation,
see what my options are,
and just to see, like,
how serious I am
about this whole boob job thing.
I mean, we're in LA.
I feel like people get their boobs done
like they fill up a car with gas.
-[Khloé] Don, thank you, sir.
-Thank you.
[Kim]
So how was it? Really different, right?
No, not that different,
but, you know… we'll see.
[upbeat music]
-[Tomer] Just want to walk through it?
-[Scott] Yes, let's just go through it.
This has head-on city light views,
it's got about a 180-degree view.
[Tomer] It's a mid-century house.
They've owned it for about 52 years.
You've got really high ceilings in here.
I mean, once they get everything out,
you'll be able to see, but…
-Yeah, the views are crazy.
-[Scott] This is nice out here.
The view and the land
and how private it is
and the private street is what makes it.
I'm happy that Khloé gave me
that little push
just to remember that I got to work,
instead of doing all these club gigs,
because it's not the best thing
in the world for me.
[Scott] Big pool, big view.
And you'd have a whole yard here.
And then all this just needs to be redone.
Everything needs to slide.
It has potential.
I think in the past,
it was very difficult for me
to be positive with my time
if I wasn't spending time with my kids.
But now I realize that they are
the most important thing in my life.
And there's gonna
be times when they're gone,
and I'm gonna need to fill my time
with positive things.
-[Khloé] How are you feeling?
-[Scott] I feel good. I mean,
I miss the kids, and I miss Kourtney,
but I feel good.
As long as I'm thinking about work
and, like, you know,
pounding the pavement…
-Pounding the pavement.
-…I feel fine and I'm happy.
And I love houses, and I love decorating,
so it's, like, I'm excited,
and it's a lot better
than sitting in a nightclub all night.
[Khloé] Yeah, it's like a whole--
-it's a whole shebang.
-It's a whole shabooble.
-[Khloé] Shabooble.
-This is just like a booba-aloosk.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
-[Caitlyn] Look who it is.
-[Kim] Hello.
My little girl.
-How are you doing?
-Hi.
-[Caitlyn] I appreciate,
Michael, you coming through
in very short notice.
-It was only what?
-[Kim] That's what Michael does,
-you know?
-A week and…
-[Caitlyn] That's what he does.
-So, let's, um…
-let's get started.
-[Caitlyn] Yeah.
I say we try some clothes on.
[Kim] Tonight is the night of the ESPYs
so Michael Costello and I
are gonna go through
all of the outfits with Caitlyn
just to make sure
that she has the perfect look
and we get her out the door
looking amazing.
-[Caitlyn] Are you ready?
-[Michael] We're ready.
[Kim] Should we let Snapchatters
-pick your outfit?
-All right, now this is a very Kim dress.
This is what I would call this,
-a Kim…
-Yes!
-[Michael] Well?
-[Kim] Should we Snapchat?
Yeah, I just don't have
the Snapchat thing going.
[Kim] Yeah. I could do it.
Let me shoot it
and then see if we like it.
-[man] See what it looks like.
-[Kim] Turn around
and we'll make the train perfect.
At the count of three,
start walking into the room.
One, two, three. Go.
This could be an option.
[Michael] You'll like this one,
the white one that she's gonna try on.
[Caitlyn] Are you ready?
-[Michael] I'm ready.
-[Kim] Yes.
[Caitlyn vocalizing]
[Kim] Wow!
-Go for this.
-[Caitlyn] I know you like the black one.
[Kim] Wear whatever makes you feel
the most comfortable…
-I feel comfortable.
-[Kim] …and the prettiest.
Yeah. I like this.
[Kim] Sorry to be annoying,
but do you have underwear on?
'Cause you see the underwear.
Oh, you need that.
-[Caitlyn] What?
-No, it's fine if you need it.
-I was just saying--
-[Caitlyn] Yeah, I know.
-We can play with that.
-I was just saying, that line.
Just cut a little bit in the back
or a little bit on the sides
just to not, like, dig in.
[Caitlyn]
No, I can wear different ones. All right.
Let me take these off.
[Kim] And what shoes
are you planning on wearing?
Well, I'm gonna wear these just because…
-I don't have any…
-[Kim] Why? No.
-Let me look.
-I don't have any that are…
-[Kim] Let me look.
-I got to be walking around
-so much, these are comfortable.
-[Kim] Well, this is an awards show.
You have to step it up.
Comfortable is for daytime.
This is like Dancing with the Stars.
Just try one on each foot.
[Kim] Why do you own them
if you won't wear them?
This is the event.
This is the time you're gonna wear them.
Roll your eyes.
[Michael] Did you show Kim the jewelry?
[Caitlyn]
-I'm wearing it.
-No, we're not doing the ring.
Oh. No ring?
-[Kim] No ring.
-What if I wear the ring on this side?
-[Kim] You're over-accessorizing.
-[Ronda] No. This and that.
-Over-accessorizing. Okay.
-[Kim] Yeah. Yeah.
Caitlyn is just not used to really putting
whole looks together all the time.
Or maybe she's so excited
that she finally has
the chance to wear
every accessory under the sun.
But she needs to, like, tone it down.
[Caitlyn] The final look.
Are you ready?
-[Kim] Yes!
-[Michael] Yay!
-[Caitlyn vocalizes]
-[Michael whistles]
-[laughter]
-Get that off.
[Caitlyn] Don't you like the crown?
-[Kim] I love it.
-[Michael] I love it.
-[Ronda] Oh.
-All right, let's take it off. I know.
It was so good too.
-[Kim] Gorgeous.
-Thank you, babe.
I still don't cosign the shoes.
-It's gonna be okay.
-[Michael] Beautiful.
-[Caitlyn] Are we ready?
-[Ronda] We're ready.
Let's do the ESPYs.
-[Caitlyn] Bye.
-[Ronda] Bye.
[upbeat music]
[Kevin] This is, like, double hotness.
-How are you?
-I feel like I died and went to heaven.
[Malika] It's your lucky day.
Do you want to go in
and not stand in the doorway?
[Kevin] Um, yeah.
[Malika] I'm the dental assistant.
[Kevin] Well, I can see
you've been very active lately.
[laughter]
Wait. You can tell that
through someone's teeth?
-[Khloé] Uh-uh.
-[Kevin] Um, yeah.
What's this little hair right here?
-[Khloé] Uh…
-[laughter]
[Kevin]
Okay, I'm gonna send in the cleaner.
-McGolly?
-Send in the…
Send in the cleaner.
[phone chimes]
Oh. Wait. Look what my mom sent me.
She's so pissed that, like, Kim
was dressing Caitlyn for the ESPYs.
Like, she's, like, really upset about it.
-Are you kidding? "Not loyal."
-[Khloé] No. Read hashtag.
"Hashtag not loyal."
[Malika]
"Mom, do not write to me in hashtags."
-[laughs]
-I was literally, like,
-"Who texts this?"
-Okay, you're such a jerk
for not addressing the real problem.
The first thing you say is, "Mom
-don't talk to me in hashtags"?
-Well, 'cause it makes her…
sound like she's, like, kidding.
No, she's not kidding. She's… she's…
she's being sarcastic, but she's pissed,
with all these question marks.
I know, but she ruins it
with the hashtags.
It's not out of character of my mom
to, like, go on a rant via text.
I feel like we all do that.
But I can't really understand
her tone right now,
and I don't fully understand…
[chuckles]
…why she's so angry
and why we're speaking in hashtags.
I don't know what to say.
I just feel like I need to, now tell Kim.
I mean, if she's kind of spiraling,
like, you should talk to her.
No. I'll talk to her.
I don't have a problem with that at all.
I just want to tell Kim, you know,
"Mom's really upset with you.
Like, Mom's pissed."
I don't think Kim has any idea.
[in sing-song tone]
Ooh… trouble.
[cheerful music]
[Jonathan] Those daggers are crazy.
-And they're shorter right now.
-Is this the sharpest
-they've ever been?
-If you had a baby,
you wouldn't be able to have those.
-[Kim] You can't wipe.
-Do you know the things I do?
I give massages,
-I do everything.
-[Jonathan] With this?
-Yeah.
-You could scramble
eggs and stuff. You're like,
-"Hold on…"
-Let me see.
-[Khloé] I could still massage you.
-[Kim] Ooh. Wait, but they're spiky.
-Like, they're hard.
-It's 'cause it's the first day.
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] Wait.
So, Mom is, like, fuming with you.
Wait. Why?
[Khloé] She was texting me with hashtags.
She was "hashtag disloyal."
Hashtag… And I said,
"Please don't text me with hashtags."
[Jonathan]
That's the weirdest thing I've ever heard.
She thinks you're a traitor,
and she thinks that you…
[chuckles]
…went against the family with Caitlyn.
[dramatic music]
[Khloé] She's pissed.
-[Jonathan] Want to call her?
-Yeah.
[line ringing]
[Jonathan] I cannot believe this.
[Khloé]
She's pissed. She was, like, really upset.
-[Kris] What are you doing?
-Mom, it's Khloé.
-Are you okay?
-[Kris] Yeah.
Wait. Why are you pissed off at me?
-Hashtag pissed.
-Oh, hashtag disloyal.
-[Kris] Kim?
-What?
You are a [bleep] traitor
that you would have the nerve
to go to help Caitlyn to pick a gown.
Like, what is going on?
[Kim] She said, "Fashion emergency.
I have nothing to wear."
Okay, here's the problem.
Why do you need to show up to help…
But last time I heard,
you guys are all good.
That's what you don't get.
I don't say anything to you
until I feel abandoned.
And that right now, I'm feeling abandoned.
Mom, I would never abandon you.
-If I even knew that you really thought--
-[Kris] But you've abandoned me.
You have taken somebody else and said,
"Okay, her feelings don't matter.
Everything that…"
-I truly didn't think…
-You know what?
-…that you would care.
-I can't teach you…
I'm just gonna try to stay neutral
and not get involved.
I don't want you to be neutral.
[voice breaking]
From my children that I gave birth to,
I want loyalty.
I don't want [bleep] neutral.
Oh, she's really upset.
[Kris] Neutral isn't what I signed up for.
[in normal voice]
That's what you don't get.
I'm trying to be as gracious as I can.
I'm trying to be
as understanding as I can.
I'm betrayed.
I've been [bleep] over on so many levels
that your head would spin.
[Kim] Okay, Mom--
-[Kris] I'm not going to…
-Oh, my god.
…[bleep] play this game anymore, okay?
We're all shocked. Like, I had--
Truly, like, I had no idea
she was this upset.
I would never intentionally do anything
to hurt her like this.
[Kris] I would lay in front of a bullet
for any one of you.
Kim totally hears you out,
and I think, moving forward,
it'll be really different.
But I don't think, like,
we ever heard this extreme of it.
[Kris] I never would put that out there.
So I say nothing.
Because I don't want you to be conflicted.
But enough is enough.
You hurt my feelings.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Hi, guys.
[Jonathan]
Oh, what's up? What are you doin'?
-What? 'Cause I have sunglasses?
-[Khloé] No, you look beautiful.
-Can I use this?
-I was with Malika
at the dentist when mom was texting me
all that crazy stuff.
-Oh, you were?
-[Jonathan] We got
-the aftermath.
-Like, she was like…
[Kim]
Like, screaming at the top of her lungs.
I was trying to keep the peace.
I… I didn't think it was a big deal.
I really didn't know there was, like…
I didn't know she really felt that way.
[Khloé] Have you spoken to her since?
No.
[Kim] The ESPYs was
Caitlyn's first public appearance
last year.
I didn't really consider
that it might still be
a really sensitive subject for my mom
and bring up these emotions
and it would be this painful.
She always tries to do a really good job
at not bringing drama to us,
especially if it's, like,
in her personal life.
I totally feel so guilty. I feel so bad.
Like, I obviously want, like,
Mom to know that she's, like,
my number one.
Like, I just want to take her out
for a fun day
or, like, something that she would, like,
actually think is, like, fun.
[Jonathan] Right.
[cheerful music]
[Khloé] Hi.
[Dr. Fisher] Good to see you again.
Nice to see you.
-[Kim] Hi.
-How are you?
-Good. How are you?
-Good to see you also.
-Wow.
-Doesn't Kim look so business?
I look so whorish
and Kim looks so business.
I should wear those with my black outfit.
[Dr. Fisher] You know,
I could really get some attention.
-You could borrow mine.
-[Dr. Fisher chuckles]
Okay, let's go look at some tits.
-Okay. Are we going? Okay.
-Easy as that.
[Khloé] I set up a consultation
with Garth Fisher, who is a family friend.
Also, I think, like,
the king of boob jobs.
He's literally done
hundreds of thousands of boobs
and just knows what he's doing.
[Dr. Fisher] Let me grab a few implants.
[Khloé] Garth, where are the good boobs?
-Okay, there are the good boobs.
-[Dr. Fisher] These are…
Okay. The ones--
Those are before
and after reconstruction cases.
[Khloé] I think I love the fullness of--
And, like, these don't look
-super fake to me.
-Right.
[Dr. Fisher] I think you're probably
gonna be around, you know, 350.
-Something like that.
-[Khloé] Okay.
-And that's, like, a "C"? Okay.
-Yeah. Full "C."
Kimberly likes the size of my boobs.
I just wish I had more cleavage.
[Dr. Fisher]
There's different styles of implants.
It just depends on what you want to do.
-I don't like the, too…
-Yeah.
…like, Playmate. Like, I don't like
really, like, circular boobs.
-[Dr. Fisher] Okay.
-I like-- I know you do,
like, the best, like, natural shape.
I want them to look natural.
I don't want them, you know?
Some boobs look hard.
-Yeah, I can make 'em look--
-[Kim] Like, two tennis balls.
-Like, that's the worst.
-[Dr. Fisher] Right.
Like, how can you guarantee that,
like, they're not gonna be hard?
You can never guarantee that.
What happens when you put this
in your body,
your body forms scar tissue around it
because it's a foreign object.
And everybody gets that in the world,
-no matter where you go.
-Mm-hm.
It's something that's kind
of a nuisance, annoying,
and sometimes,
you know, painful, sometimes.
So we hope it doesn't happen, but…
Okay.
[Khloé] How long is the recovery process?
Like, when can I work out again?
You should wait a month.
Because you don't want
to increase the risk
of having scar tissue forming in there.
[Dr. Fisher] Because you're gonna have
a raw surface inside.
Ugh, it's so hard.
Like, I really don't know.
Do I think I would like my boobs bigger?
Yeah. It's just
the seriousness of a surgery.
So I don't know.
I'm nervous.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] I love when you eat those cookies
around my house. Makes me so happy.
'Cause it just gets crumbs everywhere.
[Kim] You ate her hand.
Wow.
[Kim] Have you thought
any more about the procedure?
So, like, before I went to Garth's, Kim,
it didn't seem, like, that scary
-of a deal to me.
-[Kim] Yeah.
I mean, he says himself, he's like,
"I can't guarantee you won't,
like, capsulate."
No doctor can guarantee that.
He was like, "We have a 95% rate
that that hasn't happened."
I know, but…
[Khloé] But I'm not in a rush.
I still want to think about it,
-marinate with it, and just see.
-[Kim] Yeah.
Like, I'm not in a rush to do it.
Yeah.
For me, I do want my boobs done,
in the sense that I want bigger boobs.
It's a serious surgery.
I'm gonna be changing a part of my body,
and I need to make sure I'm planning
for healing time and downtime
and not just rush into something.
It's not that I'm never gonna get
my boobs done.
I'm just… not getting them,
like, today or tomorrow.
[chuckles]
[Khloé] No rush.
No rush.
[upbeat music]
-Wow, this is so beautiful.
-Oh, my god, it's beautiful.
What a gorgeous, beautiful view.
The view's crazy
from, like, every direction.
[Kim] I do feel bad
that I hurt my mom's feelings.
So Khloé and I set up this whole…
fun Beverly Hills day for my mom.
[Kris]
This is definitely the Pretty Woman suite.
My mom loves Pretty Woman,
and the Regent Beverly Wilshire is
the hotel that they filmed it in.
We're all gonna have lunch in the suite
that was their main suite in the movie.
And I just want her to know
we support her no matter what.
This is a dream.
You guys, this is so fun.
-[Kim] Thank you so much.
-[Khloé] Ooh, yummy!
Don't you love this hotel suite?
[Kris] Yes.
We wanted you to have a fun, pampered day,
as like, an apology
for upsetting you so much
with, like, me dressing Caitlyn.
[chuckles softly]
I mean, I would just never want you
to feel betrayed,
like, by your own daughter.
I obviously didn't know,
you know, how serious it was.
You always act so strong
and that it just never bothers you, so…
I mean, I would just never want you
to feel betrayed,
like, by your own daughter.
I obviously didn't know,
you know, how serious it was.
You always act so strong
and that it just never bothers you, so…
I felt really bad
about getting so angry at you.
-I really did.
-[Khloé] Why? You should be honest.
[Kris] It took me by surprise.
Even my emotion surprised me.
I don't know. I think…
just if I had known, I think
I would've had time to…
-absorb that.
-Mm-hm.
[Kris] Because sometimes
that stuff's hard for me.
I don't even have anybody to talk to
that's been through anything similar.
You know how you guys can talk
to your girlfriends?
But as a wife
who was with somebody for all that time,
that's a lot of memories
and a lot of years
and a lot of Christmas Eves
and a lot of Father's Day
and Mother's Day and Easters and…
[Kris] So, I don't really think about it
day to day.
But for some reason, that hit me,
I guess, just the wrong way, like, crazy.
[Kris] Going through this whole process
with Caitlyn has been challenging.
I've always wanted to be there for my kids
and have kind of pushed my feelings
down below the surface
so that I don't have to feel anything.
And that's always been kind of my MO.
And I think that sometimes,
you have to feel
what's going on inside.
And I just exploded,
because I finally was feeling
what I needed to feel for so many years.
And it just all came out in one moment.
I would never go do something like this
in the middle of the day.
So this is really fun.
[Khloé] This is so cute.
Kim wanted you to experience
your favorite movie
and feel like you're Julia Roberts
and she's Richard Gere.
[Kris] I think we should go boot shopping
in honor of Julia.
WWJD?
-[Kris] Yeah. Yeah.
-What Would Julia Do?
[Kris] What Would Julia Do?
[Kris and Kim laugh]
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Ooh.
-[Kris] Hi. How are you?
-[woman] How are you, ladies?
[Kris] This store is so beautiful.
What is this?
-To die. It's a jumpsuit.
-Yeah, it's pretty fab.
-Wow.
-[Kim] I love those little velvet shoes.
You don't love those, like,
-the little velvet?
-[Kris] I do. I do.
-Do you have an eight and a half?
-[woman] Eight and a half?
In the velvet shoes?
[Kris] You guys are the best.
Thank you.
Mm…
-Yeah.
-[Kris] Thank you, Khlo.
[crowd cheering]
[Kris] Hi, guys!
[cheering continues]
[man] You're the best mom ever.
-Thank you.
-She is.
[Kim] Next on
Keeping Up with the Kardashians…
We won!
[Kris] Look what I found.
We miss Scott being the Lord.
I never knew
you guys wanted the Lord back so bad.
[Khloé] You are now Duke Disick.
What's going on with my brother?
He just deleted
all of the pictures of Chyna.
[Khloé] He hasn't spoken to her in days.
-[Kourtney] Why?
-How dare you leave a preg--
I don't give a [bleep].
You still need to check on her.
Rob, why did you disappear?
[dramatic music]