[Scott] Look at this. You want a necklace?
Scott and I had one extra night in Vail.
I think realizing Scott can come
on our family vacations was big.
[Randy] What do you wanna do?
Go… go to the room and party.
[laughter]
You guys, Rob proposed
in front of her whole family
at her house last night.
[Rob] It happened, like, spontaneously,
so that's why you guys weren't
in the loop.
Do you understand
that that was hurtful to us
that we found out about your engagement
-on social media?
-Yes, I understand.
There's one more thing I have
to talk to you guys about,
but I don't want you guys to get mad.
[Kourtney] You're having a baby.
-Yeah.
-Congratulations.
I know Khloé's probably feeling--
[Khloé] Congratulations.
I personally don't know what the next step
for all of us is.
I mean, that's up to Rob.
[upbeat music]
What do you think life is like
with three kids?
-Different than two?
-[clears throat]
Or same as two?
No, it's different, I think.
Why? Are you thinking
about having a third?
Kanye has said it every single day
-for, like, the last week.
-Really?
And I was like, I don't think
I can carry another one.
I just feel like…
[groans]
I'll never be the same down there.
Kanye says it, like, feels the same.
Wait, tell me.
Do you think it's different?
-Dude, 100 percent things change.
-[Kim gasps]
Like, it's like throwing
a hot dog through a hallway?
No, it's not about that.
-I heard that ought to feel.
-I feel like me and Kanye
don't care about that. It's like,
the fact that, like…
something that big has come
in and out of there,
like, things are
just different internally.
There's just, like, bumps and curves
that, like, you know
what I'm saying? Like…
-Oh, my god.
-It's just not the same.
It's like the same house,
but the furniture's been rearranged.
-Correct. Like, exactly.
-Huh.
The front door is still the same,
but inside, all of your couches
have been spread apart
and mixed and matched
like a hurricane hit.
Yeah, that's a good analogy.
[bleep] my life.
[Kim laughs]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
Oh, you dropped it.
[Khloé] Are you gonna dive?
Go, Gabbana, go.
Go, go, dive.
Dive, dive, dive! You can do it.
You can do it!
Dive! Yeah, go under.
You did it! Good girl!
So, have you told anybody
about Rob and Chyna?
No. I have no one to tell,
nor do I care to be, like,
-the person that…
-Tells?
Yeah, and also there's so much,
like, drama with them.
I don't want them to get mad
if we do say something,
so I'm acting like nothing's happening.
But how do you feel?
[pensive music]
I mean, it's Rob's life.
I don't know.
[Khloé] How do you feel?
I feel like children
are a blessing from God.
[Khloé] Okay.
And that, you know,
it's God's plan and, like,
I just want him to be happy, really.
My brother and I have always had
such a strong connection,
and we've always been so close.
So what bothers me is not that
he's engaged,
not that he's having a baby,
but that Rob has completely
just disconnected from me.
He hasn't spoken to me
since he told us Chyna was pregnant.
He's not including me in his new life,
so how could I be happy
for someone or something
that I know nothing about?
[Kourtney] Hopefully,
it's all for the right reasons.
I mean, I've never really known her.
Like, I've never had
a relationship with her.
-Mm-hmm.
-So I don't know
the type of person she is.
She must be somewhat of a good person
for Rob to like her.
'Cause Rob's funny and charming.
Yeah.
I like this, um, fabric.
It's called something magical,
such as terrycloth.
I know. I have it on my couches.
-[Kourtney] My shade…
-Very exclusive.
[upbeat music]
[camera shutter clicking]
[Kim] That looks so cool.
The arm looks so pretty.
[Kim] "VIP only."
This is so exciting.
I love the gold.
[Kourtney] We have one more look.
Gold leaf in my hair
and gold leaf on my hands.
Oh, cool.
[Kim] So Kanye is shooting
the video for "Highlights"
this weekend in Iceland.
He just really wants me there
when he's shooting the video.
Every time Kanye and I have a project
that each other's working on,
we definitely try to be there
just to give, like,
moral support and input.
We really do feed off each other a lot,
so I know it's really important to him
that I come to Iceland.
-[Kourtney] That'll be fun.
-[Kim] Yeah.
And I really want you to go with me.
[Kourtney] Um, it's during my birthday.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-I think I would still go.
[Kim] Yeah, why not?
Make it a birthday trip.
Yeah.
-Jonathan and Simon would come.
-Yeah.
I always get anxious to, like,
travel and not bring the kids,
but that's my favorite song
from the album.
I feel like it would be fun.
[Kourtney] I've always wanted
to go to Iceland,
but I just don't know
how I'm going to feel
being away from my kids on my birthday.
But I wanna be adventurous
and do things that are different,
so I think it's fine to do
this quick trip to Iceland,
and just, like, live life and have fun.
Someone was saying
that the radiation on airplanes,
that, like, it's not good
to bring your kids
if you don't have to.
-[Kim] Nothing's good, you know.
-[Kourtney] No, I know.
-Yeah, just don't breathe.
-Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] How much do you think
you weigh right now?
[Lamar] Too much.
-[Khloé] Like 300 pounds?
-No.
Two… sixty?
[Khloé] Okay. Well, I wasn't,
like, that far off.
[chuckles]
What's your ideal weight?
Two forty-five.
[Khloé] Okay. Well,
you can't just sit at home
and eat Twinkies and soda and lose weight.
If that was the case,
I would've been super skinny years ago.
[Lamar] You are skinny.
-Thanks, Lam.
-You're welcome.
Is Robert Arthur Kardashian
getting married?
-He says he's getting married.
-[Lamar] When?
[Khloé] I don't know when.
-He hasn't told us anything.
-Why not?
Rob has disconnected himself from us,
apparently, mainly me.
He doesn't talk to me.
I hear he talks to my sisters way more.
I just hope he's focused.
-Marriage ain't easy, honey child.
-[Khloé] It's not?
Your marriage wasn't easy?
[laughs]
[Lamar] I've been there before.
Mm. True.
Call Rob.
I mean… he probably
won't answer my phone call.
Do you wanna try?
-Yeah.
-Move your big leg.
[line ringing]
He won't answer.
-[Khloé] Oh.
-[Rob] Yo.
'Sup, water bug?
[Rob] 'Sup, water bug?
I am really surprised
that Rob answered the call,
'cause even though Lamar's calling him,
it's from my phone.
It does make me smile
'cause at least I know he…
is finally gonna answer
one of my phone calls.
[Rob] I'm just running around.
I'm just buying ice cream.
I got strawberry shortcake in the house.
I'm gonna tear that [bleep] up
when I get in the house.
How is that helping your diet?
[chuckles]
-It accelerates your metabolism.
-Mm-hmm.
[Lamar] You getting married soon, daddio?
[Rob] Yeah. I don't know how soon,
but first comes love,
then comes marriage, you know.
When you gonna come see me, bro?
[Rob] Whenever.
[Lamar] Can we go out to eat
sometime this week?
[Rob] Yeah, whenever you want.
I have always loved Lamar
and Rob's relationship and bond,
and I want them to hang out,
but, you know,
I still want my time with Rob.
[Khloé] He hasn't had
any one-on-one time with me.
Rob hasn't attempted
to do anything with me.
[Rob] We can go out Friday.
[Lamar] Friday? Okay.
[Khloé] Is that all?
It says "poor connection." That's a sign.
Do you wanna say bye?
-So I'm gonna see you Friday.
-[Lamar] All right, bro.
It's done.
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Hey, my hearty.
-[Kourtney] Who is that?
-Hi, Northy.
Oh!
[Scott] Hi, buddy.
Okay, you wanna pick shorts?
P, let me have a hug first
'cause I haven't even had one yet.
-Let's see.
-[Penelope] No.
You want a hug?
P, you're not gonna give me a hug,
-even though North is?
-[Kourtney] Shorts or pants?
Kid's not even my daughter.
[Penelope] That's not your daughter.
[Scott] Who is?
[in British accent]
Who is my daughter?
-Me.
-[Scott] Now my daughter,
better come over here and give me a hug.
-Come here.
-[Scott] I'll meet you in the middle.
[Penelope] Okay.
[Scott in normal voice]
I'm waiting.
Paloosh.
[Penelope] No!
Belly buster, belly buster.
Now I'm your daughter.
-[Scott] Bug?
-Hmm?
What are you gonna do for your birthday?
Um, I think I'm going to Iceland
-with Kim and Kanye.
-To Iceland?
[Kourtney] To Iceland.
Icelandia.
-That's quite a trip, isn't it?
-[Kim] Icelandic.
[Scott] So why Iceland?
-[Kim] Kanye's gonna shoot a video there.
-Okay.
And I don't know.
We've just never been.
It's, like, on my bucket list.
-Are you taking the kids?
-[Kourtney] No.
But I'm sad to not be with the kids
on my birthday.
Are you gonna be there
on your actual birthday?
-Yes.
-Oh.
-[Mason] Oh, cool.
-That's weird.
[Scott] I've been with you
on your birthday
-for the past ten years.
-Hey, Dad.
[Scott] It's weird.
I know Kourtney and I aren't together,
but I figured she was gonna do
something locally,
and I'd be there to at least,
you know, wish her a happy birthday
and give her a hug or give her a gift.
We've been together
for each other's birthdays forever, so,
you know, it's just a little sad
for me to hear.
[upbeat music]
We are heading to Iceland
for Kanye's music video.
[Kim] Kourtney's coming, Jonathan, Simon,
Kourtney's friend, Nicole.
We're just gonna make it
a really fun trip.
I think this will be the perfect place
to spend Kourtney's birthday,
'cause it's a place
that's totally on our bucket list
that we never thought we'd ever go to.
[Simon] There it is, Reykjavik.
[bright music]
[man 1] Hello, Western people.
[indistinct chattering]
[Simon] Look how beautiful that is.
[Kourtney] Yeah, I got to look.
[Simon] Take it in.
It's beautiful.
-Hi.
-[man 2] Hello.
-[Simon] Hi. Good morning.
Guys, we're definitely
gonna need to sleep, like,
-a few hours.
-[Kourtney] It's 1:30
in the morning in LA.
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Kris?
[Kris] Hi.
Hi.
-Hi. Can I have a hug?
-I can barely see you
with all that camo on.
I know. Well, it's a disguise.
You blend right in.
-[Kris] What's going on?
-[Scott] Sure got
a lot of magazine covers in here.
I know.
The kids have been busy.
Evidently.
So I had something I wanted
to run past you.
-Huh.
-Kourtney and I have spent
every birthday together…
between mine and hers
for the past ten years.
-Aw.
-And her birthday's coming up.
Do I just say, like, screw it
and just, like,
fly to Iceland and surprise her and, like…
Hmm.
The thing that I hear her say
is that she just wants you to be
a good person and a great dad,
and to do it first for yourself
and then for your kids,
-and then for her, kind of like.
-Right. I know she says that.
-You know what I mean?
-But, like, let's say if,
in a year from now, or ten years from now,
we worked things out, like,
I would have hated
to have missed a birthday.
-You know what I mean?
-Yeah.
You know what would be
the best birthday present ever?
Just be that fun dad
and that responsible dad
that she's always praying
-that you will turn into.
-Yeah.
[Scott] I don't know.
I don't really know what to do.
One of the things
that Kourtney and I argued about
when we were together was that…
I never really fought enough for her,
so now I'm thinking,
should I go to Iceland?
Because maybe now, she would appreciate me
putting in some effort.
It's just hard sometimes.
Like, you know, when you've had
all these memories, and then…
they are stopping, you know, one by one.
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[Knútur] Hi. Welcome.
Hi. Thank you.
-Knútur Ármann. I'm the farmer.
-[Kourtney and Jonathan] Hi.
[woman 1] We call it tomato schnapps.
Ooh, how exciting, guys.
[Kim] We have the day off here
before Kanye's shoot,
and I wanna see
what Iceland's really known for.
They have this amazing
organic tomato farm,
and it is Kourtney's birthday.
She's all about all the organic stuff,
so I figured we should just check it out
and see what it's about.
[Knútur] Welcome to my farm.
-[Kourtney] Thank you.
-[Jonathan] It's beautiful.
[Knútur] Here, we try to grow
what's healthy, tasty,
good, fresh tomatoes as possible.
[Kourtney]
Wait. Is that all bees in there?
Yeah. The flowers,
they need to be pollinate.
Otherwise, we will not have many tomatoes.
And to help us to do that,
we have the bumblebees.
About 600 active bumblebees.
-[Kim] Oh, my…
-Oh, my god, hold on.
-[gasps]
-[Jonathan screams]
Sorry.
[Kourtney yelps]
Are these the killer bees?
No, no, no. These are bumblebees.
They are very friendly.
[Kourtney]
Kim used to be friends with bees
-when she was little.
-[man laughs]
I used to really like bees.
[upbeat music]
-Cheers.
-[Knútur murmurs]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[laughter]
Yes, guys.
This is called living.
I just put basil in your drink.
[Kim] Wait. Can you believe
it's your birthday week?
-Are you so excited?
-[Kourtney] Mm-hmm.
But if you think about it,
for the last ten years,
like, we've all been in, like, Mexico
or, like, something with you guys.
[Kourtney] True.
I feel like Iceland's a good change.
I'm definitely happy that I came,
and that I'm doing something different
for my birthday,
but I feel like I'm a little bit homesick.
I definitely miss my kids so much.
But I'm just gonna try to make
the most of it while I'm here.
Aren't you going to the video shoot?
Yeah.
-[Kim] Do you wanna come?
-I don't know.
[Simon] How far is the shoot?
[Kim] It's 90 minutes,
but it's atop of a glacier.
-[Kanye] Do I have to take a helicopter?
-[Kim] It's a helicopter.
I'm not so much a helicopter person.
But you're gonna do it anyway?
Yeah, I got to do it for the shoot.
[Kanye] It's hard to shoot these videos.
Like, I was in Scotland,
took a helicopter over.
It was below the wind chill.
You know, on the side of a rock.
You step two steps over, you could die.
-Kill yourself, yup.
-And I was just sitting there,
I was like,
"Man, people don't give a [bleep]
about videos like that anymore,
and people don't appreciate, like,
all the work you put into it."
-[Kim] Yeah.
-I need to do
some [bleep] on green screen.
[laughter]
[Knútur] This is a tomato ice cream.
Everything is made out of tomato.
-[Simon] Tomato ice cream.
-That's the tomato on top.
[Jonathan] Yeah, yeah,
that's the tomato on top.
[laughter]
Do you have cappuccino
without a tomato blend?
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
What up, man? How you doing, son?
-[man 3] Can I get a photo?
-Yeah, let's take it, yeah.
[man 3] Okay. I appreciate it. Thank you.
-[Kourtney] What? It smells?
-[laughter]
-[Simon] Someone tooted?
-[Nicole] There was a toot.
[Simon] Well, it's definitely one of us.
-[both laugh]
-Jonathan.
Just 'cause my shirt's the color of tomato
doesn't mean I [bleep] farted.
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
[Malika] K.K. heart.
-You look pretty.
-Thank you.
[Malika] I love your eyebrows.
They're thicker.
-Oh.
-Hold on.
Okay, that's fine.
[Malika] What's going on with you?
I'm a little frustrated
'cause I was with Lam,
and he was FaceTiming Rob,
and they were, like, talking, and like,
"Oh, I wanna see you, let's hang out."
Blah, blah, blah.
Rob is making such an effort
to hang out with Lam,
but yet Rob still hasn't seen me,
nor will he talk to me.
So it's a little…
Like, I'm a little annoyed
-by that.
-Mm-hmm.
But, okay, so what do I have to do?
You feel left out?
No. I don't care to do what they're doing.
I just feel like I'm owed,
like, a conversation
ever since he's moved out of here.
It's like, okay, so you do have time.
I just wish you guys could break the ice.
I don't see why…
Break the ice,
like we don't know each other.
[Malika] No, well, that's how
you guys are acting.
It's, like, ver-- I'm sorry,
even to hear it is, like, very strange.
Mm-hm. It's so weird.
I don't get it.
[Malika] I feel like there's, like,
this one little thing
that needs to be done to fix it.
If I'm not invited to hang out
or do something,
what am I supposed to do?
What's the plan, man?
Yeah, I don't know.
[upbeat music]
[phone ringing]
-[Jonathan] Who's that?
-The kids.
-[Kourtney gasps]
-Hi, Mommy.
Hi, little angel.
-Look who it is.
-Hi, P.
[Penelope] Hi.
[Kourtney] Hi, I miss you.
P, I'm in Iceland.
It's freezing here and it was snowing.
[Kourtney] Where's Mase?
[Mason] I'm going to the bathroom!
-Oh.
-[laughter]
[Kourtney] You guys,
I'm getting in the car.
I'm gonna call you from the car, okay?
-Love you.
-[Penelope] Love you.
[Kourtney] Bye. Are we ready?
[Simon] The car's pulling up, I think.
[Kourtney] All right.
Kim, have fun at the fitting.
Thank you.
Kanye and I are gonna go to his fitting
for his shoot tomorrow,
and I'm gonna meet up
with everyone a little bit later.
I don't wanna ditch Kourt
on her birthday week,
but I am here to support Kanye,
so I wanna be with him.
And I'm just trying to juggle it all.
I think you look better without it.
Oh, that's not the point.
[laughs]
[Jonathan] We're going to the car?
-We're going, yeah.
-So let's go.
[Kourtney] All right. Bye, Kim.
Ooh!
[Kourtney yelps]
We're literally blowing away.
[upbeat music]
Do you think that people go
on romantic retreats to Iceland?
I mean, anywhere can be romantic.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Jonathan] That's pretty.
-Thank you.
How about that video
on TMZ at the airport?
-[Simon] Yeah.
-Who?
-[Simon] Rob. Wild.
-[Kourtney] Oh, I didn't see it.
[Jonathan] He's, like, so normal.
-[Simon] Yeah.
-[Jonathan] He's like…
-[Simon] Giggling.
-He's, like, chattering
-with them outside…
-[Kourtney] Stop.
-No, no, like full interview.
-[Kourtney chuckles]
It's like crazy.
He says, "Yeah, hello, all right."
[Simon] Can you let me in on a secret?
Why would we not be happy for Chyna?
She's made… turned Rob
into, like, a new man.
This is the only issue, I think,
why everyone cared,
was because she, like,
bashed Kylie and stuff like that,
when they first got together.
-Nonstop.
-But I feel like
that was her, like, relationship,
and they have a kid together,
and, like, who wouldn't feel that way?
-I think it would…
-She's really funny. Like…
-Chyna?
-Yeah, she's a laugher.
I remember her with Kim, she was so…
She used to be, "I love her.
Oh, you're so funny."
She used to giggle, and then, like,
everything went sour so fast…
I mean, I remember them doing
those sexy mirror pictures
-in their… in the bathroom.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
-Why did she stop…
-I used to, like…
-…talking to her?
-…go on walks with her
in the neighborhood.
-Okay.
-Scott and I would hang out
with Chyna and Tyga.
-When he moved into our neighborhood.
-Right.
We would go just hang out at their house.
We'd all go to dinner together
with the kids.
In the past, Kim and I
were friends with Chyna,
but I think that for everyone else, like,
they're gonna have to get
to know her from scratch.
And I know not everybody feels
the same way that I do right now,
but because it's my brother,
and she's going to be family,
I think that we just need
to figure it out.
-Good for him.
-I hope they get married.
-That wedding will be wild.
-[Jonathan] Oh, my god.
[Simon] His sense of humor is beyond.
-[Jonathan] That's funny.
-[laughs]
He is, like, wild.
-So quirky.
-[Kourtney] He is.
He's the funniest ever.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
-[Kourtney] Guys, look.
-[Jonathan] Wow.
This is unreal.
This is… beyond.
-Guys, how is it?
-[Kourtney] Wait.
-[Simon] Beautiful.
-You have to start, though,
from the beginning.
Yeah, we will. We're just taking a pic.
So I just left Kanye at his fitting,
and I'm meeting up
with the group at the Blue Lagoon.
This place is so amazing.
I am so excited to be here.
It's like the Fountain of Youth,
supposedly.
[Kim] What is this that I'm stepping on?
That's the slimy stuff.
[Jonathan] That's the stuff
that goes on your face.
[Kourtney] I keep grabbing it
off the walls.
[Jonathan] It is all over my face.
I thought it was clear.
-[Simon] Oh, god, it feels so…
-[Jonathan] Does it look clear to you?
-[laughter]
-No, it's… it's turquoise.
-[Jonathan] What?
-[Kim] It's like…
it's, like, the color of the water.
-[Jonathan] Are you serious?
-Yeah, it's like
-a green… it looks white.
-[Simon] Are you guys dipping
into the water?
[Kim] Should we FaceTime Scott
and show him?
[Kourtney] Sure.
[line ringing]
-[Nicole] Oh.
-Oh.
[Jonathan] Wow, okay.
-[Kourtney chuckles]
-What's going on with you guys?
-Um…
-[line ringing]
We're just doing our best to co-parent.
[Kim] Yeah, that's the most important.
And getting along.
[Kim] Yeah.
[somber music]
I know that Scott was
a little bit disappointed
that I wasn't going to be
spending my birthday
with him and the kids,
but I do think part of figuring out
how to co-parent is realizing
that experiences together are great,
but we are going to have some experiences
not together, as well,
and I think that's equally as important.
-He gets so carried away…
-Sensitive, yeah.
-…and ahead of himself.
-[Kim] Yeah.
I just feel like I don't wanna just
-spend time with him one on one…
-I was like, "Don't…"
…because that's not…
What is that gonna benefit anybody?
[Kim] Yeah.
That's just not what I want right now
-and it's not what's good.
-[Kim] Yeah.
[Kourtney] All right,
should we go get our drinks?
[Kim] You guys, don't you think
we should all take a pic.
-Yeah.
-I wanted to show cleavage
-and I was like…
-Yeah.
-Got it.
-Wait, Kourt,
you're blocking my boobs.
-We keep moving.
-[laughter]
Get up.
One, two, three.
I don't have any cleavage to show.
All right, should we go back?
Oh, it's coming.
[all] Cheers.
-[Simon] Oh.
-Oh, spilled a little bit.
[Kourtney] Oh!
[Jonathan] Oh, wow,
that is [bleep] delicious.
[upbeat music]
[phone line ringing]
-[Kim] Hello.
-Hey.
How's Iceland?
[Kim] Like, one second it looks normal,
and then the next second it's like
so chillingly ice cold, it's unbearable.
[Scott] Kourt, is she, all right?
-Like, not lonely…
-[Kim] Yeah, she's doing good.
-Okay.
-We're all having fun, like…
All right, 'cause I feel bad,
like, you know,
part of me really, really,
really wants to surprise her,
just to be with her
or be near her for her birthday,
but we're not together.
Uh, she has her own life. I just…
[Kim] I think it's better
if you don't come.
She's having such a good time
with Jonathan
-and Simon and Nicole…
-Oh. Oh…
Hearing that Kourt's having
some fabulous time in Iceland
and knowing I'm not there is definitely
a little hard to hear.
I mean, at the end of the day,
I want Kourt to be happy
and I want her to have
the best time she can have.
But it's always gonna hurt a little bit
when somebody's having a great time
when you're not with the person.
[sighs]
Okay.
Um, all right. I guess
just let her know I love her.
-[Kim] Okay, I'll tell her.
-Okay.
-[Kim] Okay, bye.
-All right, bye.
[upbeat music]
[camera shutters clicking]
[Jonathan] God, this is a nice restaurant.
Everybody's blond except us.
-[chuckling]
-Ooh!
Can anyone buy a broad a drink?
We gettin' drunk tonight?
[Kourtney] Yes.
That's a birthday request.
[Jonathan] Oh, my god,
it's five minutes till your birthday.
Let's go to the bar and do a shot.
We're going to the bar.
-Let's get shots at the bar…
-You guys go get…
-Yes, let's do that.
-Okay.
So do you want me to go with you
at 9:30 in the morning?
-[Kanye] Yeah.
-Or I was thinking,
I would come with Kourtney and them, like,
at the end of the day.
Kanye's video shoot is tomorrow,
but it's also Kourtney's actual birthday.
I really do wanna be there
for Kanye's video,
but I also feel bad
'cause I did invite Kourtney,
so I do wanna celebrate and not leave her.
I just feel torn
'cause I wanna be at both places.
[Kanye] Yeah, okay, it's fine.
I'm gonna wake up early to…
I got to wake up early anyways.
-[Nicole and Jonathan] Happy birthday.
-[Simon chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] So, it's real weird.
Nicole, I couldn't remember,
Nicole, your name,
like I have Alzheimer's.
Shh…
[Jonathan gasps]
Oh, my god!
[hotel staff] Sorry, guys.
The hot tubs have been turned off.
We've received some complaints about it.
We're gonna have to ask you to leave.
Wait, can we get you to say that again?
I want to get that on SnapChat.
[camera shutter clicks]
Just go to bed.
[Nicole] We're going to bed.
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] Oh, wow, that is sick.
Holy, beautiful.
Kanye is already up at the glacier,
shooting his music video,
but first, we're gonna run around
and do a couple activities
for Kourtney's birthday.
[Kourtney]
One of my favorite things to do…
Uh, you're interrupting me…
is to see churches in other cities.
[laughing]
[Simon] This doesn't feel very churchy.
It feels like Kim's house.
[crowd whooping]
[upbeat music]
[indistinct chattering]
[Jonathan]
This is what all the hype is about?
[Kourtney] Yeah!
[Kim] For some reason,
Miss Organic, Gluten-free
really wants to go to this hot dog stand.
[Kim] I don't really get it,
but Kourtney should spend
her birthday the way she wants.
[crowd singing]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Kourtney ♪
[crowd cheering]
You guys are so cute, thank you.
How does it feel to be 37?
Doesn't feel any different.
-It doesn't?
-Feel like I'm 21 still.
Well, you look it too,
so that's the good news.
[Kourtney] Um, I got flowers from Scott.
[Kim] He's so sweet.
Scott really did wanna come
and celebrate
Kourtney's birthday with her,
but I'm glad he sent her
a really nice gift,
but, you know, kept his distance.
I thought that was really sweet
and super mature.
I was gonna give you your present,
but I thought,
"Maybe not at the hot dog stand."
No.
[laughs]
[upbeat music]
[Lamar] What's up, broheim?
Yeah, I'm good.
-[Rob sighs]
-[Lamar] Thanks, bro.
-Use that napkin.
-[Lamar] Hmm?
I said, "Use that napkin."
[Rob chuckles]
-That was good.
-Turkey tacos?
Taco Tuesdays. Today's Tuesday?
No, it's Thursday. Taco Thursday.
-How's everything with you?
-I can't complain.
I'm living, I'm healthy.
How's your love life?
It's amazing.
[chuckles]
-You gonna tie the knot?
-Mm-hmm.
I don't know when, but…
not gonna move as quick as you did.
Nah. You don't wanna do that.
Have you talked to Khlo Money?
-Yeah, we talk about you all the time.
-[Rob chuckles]
'Cause I… I haven't talked to her.
Maybe we should all go out to eat.
Whenever I talk to her,
it just leads to crazy…
Her and I yelling at each other,
no matter what.
No, seriously though,
you should talk to your sister.
I mean, time goes by so fast, man.
[Rob] Yeah, it does.
I need to hit her up.
I need to talk to her.
[upbeat music]
[crowd singing on video]
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ Dear Kourtney ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
That was good,
-with all the people singing.
-[Jonathan] Yeah, that was cute.
-So fun.
-[Kourtney] It was so cute.
We may not make the video shoot though
'cause we've been so late.
So do I, but we're so late. I mean,
it's up to them
if they're still shooting and let us go.
[Kim] Pascal,
I wanna try to make the video.
[Pascal] We're going to Rangá Hotel.
But we need to go straight to the video.
[Kim] We don't have time
to go to the hotel.
[Pascal] The hotel is where
the heliport is,
and from the heliport,
you fly to the glacier.
I came here for Kanye's video shoot
and this is really important to him.
I'm starting to freak out
because I just don't wanna
disappoint Kanye.
[tense music]
[Kim] Kanye's video shoot
is in this really crazy, remote place.
It's like an hour-and-a-half drive,
then a 30-minute helicopter ride.
I'm just nervous
that I'm not gonna make it
to Kanye's shoot in time.
[Kim] When we get to the glacier,
Kanye is already done shooting,
and I'm, like, heartbroken.
He's being nice, and kissed me,
and it's all good, but, like,
I just know he's more, probably,
disappointed in me.
[Kanye] Which heli are we getting in?
That one over there?
[upbeat music]
[paparazzi clamoring]
[Scott] Hello, my "Khlo-verfield."
[Khloé in British accent]
Hello, Lord.
[Scott] That's some ensemble.
[in normal voice]
What I'm wearing?
[Scott] For the Blu Jam.
[Khloé] What are you getting?
I don't know, I'm freaking out.
[Khloé] It's way too many options.
What is… How is this…
I can't say this word.
[waiter] "Chilaquiles."
[Khloé] Okay, I'm gonna get that then.
[Scott] I'll have that too,
but no sour cream.
Thanks so much. I just talked to Kourt,
I sent her flowers for her birthday.
-In Iceland? That's nice.
-Yeah.
Are you sad that you're not
with Kourt on her birthday?
Yeah, obviously. And, I mean…
I was, like, gonna go there
and just, like,
-try to surprise her.
-[Khloé] Oh, that's right.
-What happened to that?
-But then…
You know how she is,
I would get there and she'd be like…
"What are you doing here exactly?"
Well, she's not the person
that's even gonna scream for joy anyway.
[Scott] Ever. Even when we were together.
When we bought her a puppy
at three years old,
my mom said she goes, "What's next?"
Yeah, that's just Kourt.
Scott is normally so consumed
about his own feelings
and his own thoughts.
And finally, I think he's being
really aware of Kourtney's feelings,
so I think it's, like,
a real sign of maturity
that Scott just sent her flowers
and was respectful of her space,
and chose to stay home.
[Khloé] Did you hear that Rob and Lamar
are hanging out again?
When have you spoken to Rob last?
Last, I wrote him
and I said, "I love you,"
you know, and "Be good."
Caitlyn texted me yesterday and said
all she does is try to reach out to Rob,
and Rob doesn't respond.
It's like, well, I don't talk
to Rob either.
[Scott] That must be hard for you though
because, I mean, he went
from living at your house,
never leaving the house for years,
and now all of a sudden, like…
[Khloé] It's [bleep] weird.
[upbeat music]
Oh, thank you.
[Jonathan] Can't wait to take
a little nap for an hour.
-You did?
-I need a… No.
I need a little, I need a little…
-A little nap?
-Just a 15-minute,
or, you know…
[Simon] My heart's still pounding
from the helicopter.
[Jonathan] Why he mad?
He's annoyed
that I didn't see him perform.
I feel so bad, I feel so guilty.
The one thing I was out here to do,
I missed.
-So today was my fault.
-For what? What happened?
I think he thinks, like,
"Kourt and her friends are coming,
-and they'll just hang out."
-Yeah.
"We might see them, but, you know…"
But now it's like,
"Oh, babe, I might see you."
[chuckles]
You know?
Like, we flew all the way
out here for him,
and I did say from the beginning,
my number one priority is the video.
I usually have my [bleep] together,
so I'm…
just really kind of disappointed
in myself.
And I just… I don't know
what the right thing to do is.
[light music]
[Kourtney] So do you think we're getting
some Northern Lights action tonight?
[Simon] I pray.
Whoa.
People fly to Iceland
just to see the Northern Lights.
[Kourtney] It's not guaranteed
that you can see them,
but we're hoping,
hoping, hoping
that we will get to see them.
[Kim] Wow, that is un… That's beautiful.
[Kourtney chuckles]
The wine is over there, guys.
I double dog dare one of you to jump in.
[laughter]
-[Kim] Is this the wine?
-[Kourtney] Yes!
Guys, is there a chance
that we're gonna see some kind
-of colored sky tonight?
-Nope.
-[Jonathan] Zero?
-Zero chance.
-Where's the moon?
-The moon's, like fully covered.
[Kourtney]
Even though it was hard to leave the kids,
I'm glad that Kim and Kanye,
you know, took me
on this adventure with them.
[Kourtney] Kanye.
Here, I feel like you'll like this.
-It's, like, hot red wine.
-[Kanye] Nah, I'm okay.
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Kanye] Kim! You're not waiting for me?
Okay, I'm getting in the car.
You wanna get in the car?
[Kanye] Yeah, I'm down to go in the car.
[Kourtney] Okay, a quick toast.
Where's Kim and Kanye?
They went in the car.
[Kourtney] They went on the bus?
They're the worst people to travel with!
The Wests suck!
[Kim] I feel bad.
Today was a mistake.
I'd love to, like, come to the studio.
I do feel so bad about missing the video.
We have one more night here,
so I just want a night
of the two of us alone,
and I really do wanna see
how the video is going,
and I just wanna do what I can
to make up for it.
-We made it to Iceland…
-You're so sweet.
…but we didn't make it
to the Northern Lights.
But our northern light is you, tonight.
Happy birthday, Kourtney.
-[laughter]
-Oh, my god.
[all cheering]
[electronic music]
[knocking on door]
[Lamar] Khloé, look who I found.
[Rob grunts]
[chuckles]
Hey, Khlo.
Long time no see.
[Khloé] This is kind of awkward,
just having, like,
Rob and Lamar walk into the theater
like nothing has happened.
[tense music]
[Lamar] Khloé, look who I found.
Long time no see.
This is bangin', you know? Smell it.
-Oh, that's…
-That's gross, Lamar.
Are you trying to do
something funny right now?
No, no, I'm trying to get you to smell it.
-Smell my cologne.
-[sniffs, chuckles]
-[Rob] You smell really good.
-[scoffs]
-[Lamar] You like it?
-[Rob] Yeah, I do.
[Khloé] I am so happy
that Rob is finally willing to talk,
but it's super awkward at first.
Very awkward.
We need to get over this initial moment.
-Anyway…
-[coughs]
The smoking still going good for you?
-[Lamar] I mean, you know…
-Sounds like it.
I felt like something was in my throat.
It's called nicotine.
[Khloé] I mean, he's already out drinking,
that's what he was doing all last night.
[exhales sharply]
See, this is what we were
talking about the other day
when you said why I don't call Khloé?
-[Lamar] Yeah.
-It's 'cause…
a simple conversation could turn into a…
a crazy…
You guys, oh, my god, I swear.
-Like, I don't really know.
-[Lamar] What?
[Khloé] What's the point of this?
[Lamar] Um, do you wanna go out
with Rob, soon, to dinner?
And Blac Chyna?
[Khloé] No, that's not part of the plan.
It's not Blac Chyna, too.
-Why not?
-No. 'Cause I'm not
going from "A" to "Z."
[Khloé] I need to talk to Rob first.
Rob and I just need to have
a private conversation
and just have a talk
and let's hash things out
so we could just move on
and get out of this awkward space.
I think we should all get dinner together,
or hang out here at the house.
Drink.
-No.
-[Rob] Get… no.
-Only agua.
-Mm-hmm.
[Rob] No, but seriously,
we should all definitely do something.
[smacks lips]
Yes, Rob, I would love to do that
with the two of you.
Yeah, maybe just the two of us.
[Rob] I get it.
It's cool.
Good.
[Khloé] Rob and I have a long way to go,
but I want my relationship
back with my brother,
so, I don't know.
This is off to a good start.
[Lamar smacking lips]
[Khloé] You're just gonna
keep eating this candy, huh?
My blood sugar's low.
No, it's not. That's the problem.
It is, I can tell how I feel.
[Khloé] You're like a child.
[Rob] That's disgusting.
He's just a slob.
-[Khloé] Lamar.
-Damn.
[Lamar] [bleep] put that on there.
Oh, my god.
[upbeat music]
Ooh.
[Kim] Iceland was fun.
Did you have a good birthday?
[Kourtney] Yeah, I had the best birthday.
It was definitely, like,
a place to remember.
And Simon and Jonathan are always fun.
[Kim] So much fun.
Wait, so where did you guys go last night?
[Kim] We went to the studio.
He had to record a song.
[Kourtney]
Did anyone else go, or just you two?
[Kim] No, he just wanted me to hang out.
But I thought the trip was really fun.
-Um…
-I loved the Blue Lagoon.
-That was, like, the best.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[bleating]
[Kourtney] Do you guys wanna feed
some animals?
-P, wanna go on a pony ride?
-[Penelope] Uh-huh.
P's going on the pony.
You wanna go, Mase, or no?
-No.
-[Scott] All right.
Be careful with her. She's a special one.
[Scott] Yeah, P. You look pretty up there.
I told Kourt if I'm not gonna be
with her in Iceland,
at least let's all do something together
when we're home,
and I planned a little getaway
at Underwood Farms
and hang with the kids, laugh a little,
kind of have some kind of memory
to go back to.
-How was Iceland, by the way?
-[Kourtney] Amazing.
What did you do there?
[Kourtney] We went to a tomato farm.
You had to go to Iceland
to go to a tomato farm?
[Scott] I definitely wanted to be there
and it was just one more thing
I didn't wanna miss.
I mean, it's difficult being not together
with someone you've been with for so long
and somebody that you're still
close friends with,
and I guess this is just one more thing
that, you know, you got to get used to.
[Kourtney] Ready for the cow ride, guys?
Okay, I'm going in, um, Molly Moo.
Scott, which one are you going in?
[Scott] Can I drive the tractor?
[Kourtney] No, there's no way
that you're not getting in it.
[Scott] I can't get in this thing.
Yeah, you can. I squeezed my butt in.
What… Are you… My legs don't go in here.
There's a bigger one, look.
[Scott] God…
-Oh, this is like, oh…
-[Kourtney] Yeah!
-Living the dream.
-[Scott whoops]
[Scott] American Airlines,
all the way up front.
Living the dream.
[Kim] Next on Keeping Up
with the Kardashians…
I have to do Fergie's video about MILFS.
What's going on with the stalker?
He's out of the psychiatric ward.
He didn't just get released, he escaped.
Kylie needs a wake-up call.
[Kylie] What's on my car?
I did an interview for GQ.
[Kim] I've had it with people
blatantly treating my husband
a certain way
and making him look a certain way,
and I'm gonna say how I feel.
He really did wanna do the right thing.