[Khloé] You guys.
Rob proposed in front of her whole family
at her house last night.
And you don't even tell your sisters?
We basically wake up to the news
that my brother is engaged.
"None of the women jumped
on social media to congratulate him."
Why would we congratulate him?
We were thinking
of staying tomorrow and skiing.
Me and Scott and the kids.
It makes me really happy
to know that Kourtney and Scott
are having so much fun
that they wanna stay another day.
[upbeat music]
-[Scott groans]
-Hi.
[Scott] Snapchat?
[playful music]
Oh, my god.
And this is all Snapchat?
Yeah, these are fun
and I can record them for the kids.
But how many different things are there?
Tons? Or do you have to download--
-And they change daily.
-Oh…
Mase loves doing them.
I'm sure. He's six.
Like, how this offends you…
[chuckles]
You waste a lot of time
of your life on it.
[Kourtney chuckles]
-That doesn't offend.
-That took one second in glam.
It didn't. A hundred percent
didn't take one second.
-No, literally.
-No.
Do you know how many people say to me
that my snaps are, like, the best?
What are they gonna say, they suck?
I don't ask them.
[Scott laughs]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] How do you spell, like, "Damn!"
Is it, like, D-A-Y, "Daymn."
Oh! D-A-Y-U-M.
A-Y. Dayum. U-M.
-[Malika] How was Vail?
-Vail was super fun.
Went skiing, had some fun,
like, restaurant nights.
Your brother doesn't miss
going on vacation with his family, like--
He was invited.
And he said he was coming
and he ditched it.
It's his life to choose.
Do you feel like he won't do it
because he feels like you guys, like,
he can't bring her?
I don't know what she would do
on our family trips.
I don't know, if she's about to be family,
you might want to start thinking about it.
[Khloé] I'm not struggling
that Rob got engaged.
I'm offended that Rob
hasn't said anything to us.
And I think the most frustrating part
is Rob and I were always super close.
So I feel like the fact
that he hasn't said anything yet,
it just, I mean, it hurts my feelings,
and I just want Rob to reach out to me.
It's still new.
You guys might be able to grow to,
like, a very family, like, way.
Crazier things have happened.
Mm-hm.
My stepdad turned into a girl.
Somehow, Lamar's back in our lives.
Full-time. Like, crazier things
have happened.
Crazier things have happened.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] Ooh, Dad got you something.
-[babbling]
-[Scott] And I got you little toys too.
[Mason] Popcorn!
[Kourtney] I think this trip to Vail
has been a big step for my family.
I think realizing that Scott can come
on our family vacations was big.
I'm glad that we had
that one extra night in Vail,
but there's a lot going on in LA,
so time to get back to reality.
[phone chimes]
Rob just texted me, Kim, and Khloé.
"I just had a long talk
with Mom in person,
and I realized that there are
a lot of things
we need to talk about,
and I'd like to talk to you
three in person.
I love you very much
and I want you in my life.
Let's talk as soon as possible. Rob."
I am happy that Rob has reached out.
The last thing I want
is drama with my own brother,
and I want to figure out a way
so that everybody can get along
and be a happy family.
You realize, if they get married,
her name is gonna be "Blac Kardashian."
Yep.
How random is that?
-[laughs]
-Finally, somebody said it.
[upbeat music]
[Kylie] Hello, Mother.
Hi.
So what does "carpe diem" mean?
[Kris] I think it means, like, Zen.
[Kylie] It means "seize the day."
How come I don't know that?
You went to school a long time ago.
-[phone chimes]
-That's for sure.
Look what I just got.
Another new dog?
Ooh. Is that the final?
That's really cool.
[Kylie] I am so lucky and blessed
to have found my passion,
which is my cosmetic line.
I am having another
one of my Lip Kit restocks,
and it's a lot of hard work,
but it's so much fun.
I love every minute of it.
Friday is the Lip Kit launch.
I know. It's so soon.
You good?
Yeah.
I am a little nervous
about my next Lip Kit restock
because last time,
my website was over capacity
and it crashed.
[Kylie] There were
so many negative comments,
and when people don't like something,
it really affects me more than
anything else I've ever done.
I just want to make everything perfect.
[Kris] I think you should actually give
all of your sisters one and me.
Are you gonna give a Lip Kit to your dad?
[Kylie] Mm-hm.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] What the [bleep] is that?
That is the bowl
that I asked you if I could get,
-and you said yes.
-And what did I say?
-No, I said no.
-[Kris] You said yes.
It's a copy?
[Khloé] That's the exact
[bleep] bowl I have.
-You said could you have mine…
-[Kourtney] Copy.
-…I said no.
-I asked.
Okay, you're forgiven, then.
I really think I'm gonna cancel Dubai.
What are you going to Dubai for?
[Kris] I'm going for business.
Now I'm just rethinking the whole thing.
But why?
I just think it's not
the greatest time to be away
and what if somebody needs me here?
But why isn't it a great time to be away?
Just to go so far away
with so many changes going on.
[Kris] I have a trip coming up,
for business,
that includes going to Dubai
and the Maldives,
but I've had an opportunity
to sit down with Rob
and understand everything that's going on,
but no one else in the family has.
So I feel extremely irresponsible
for leaving town.
I just wanna be here for Rob,
if he needs me.
You're always encouraging us
to see our obligations through.
[Khloé] You've left me with him before.
I think you'll be fine.
Rob wants to just explain to his sisters
a little bit more about the situation,
but it makes me really anxious
not to be there.
[upbeat music]
[Kylie] Everyone seems
so excited to see me!
[Kris] All right, let's scoot,
-scoot this way.
-I was.
[Kourtney] I'm wearing
my Kylie Lip Kit today.
-What color? Candy?
-Mm-hm.
[Kylie] It's super cute.
Khloé, I have an orange shade.
Well, you didn't give it to me,
so, you know…
Well, it's not out yet.
[Khloé] Oh, but Jordyn gets to wear it.
Okurrr.
-[Corey laughs]
-Well, whatever.
[Kourtney]
Mom, who did your makeup yesterday?
[Kris] Joyce.
-[Khloé] You looked so good.
-[Kourtney] The best I've seen
-you look in a long time.
-I thought you looked so cute.
Well, good, I'll get booed more often.
[Kris] I was so upset
I didn't know what to do,
so I'm texting Kim,
"I just got booed. What do I do?"
[Khloé] I was saying to Kourt, like,
when I was at the basketball game
and I got booed,
like, it's just one person
and then, like, the…
It's like the wave.
One person starts, like,
who the [bleep] wants to do the wave?
But everyone just copies.
I was, like, very upset.
If you're gonna get booed,
at least look good
and you looked good.
[Kylie] Hearing my mom talk about
how she got booed at an appearance,
I so feel for her.
And that's the worst feeling ever.
Stories like that just stress me out,
and that's why I don't like
to deal with this kind of stuff.
Thank you.
Mom, I'm having really bad anxiety lately.
[Corey] What are you doing
when you notice it the most?
When I'm working a lot.
[Jonathan] Are you just overwhelmed,
or you just feel like
you have too much going on?
It's really hard to explain,
but it's, like, something in your mind,
that how your brain works,
like, you overthink a lot.
[Kris] Kourtney had that for a long time.
[Kourtney]
I had, like, a therapist on call,
and I would just talk to her
on the phone for an hour
and talk about everything,
like, sometimes daily.
I always talk about it.
I'm talking about it right now.
I totally forget that Kylie's 18 years old
and that she is doing so much.
And then on top of it being really famous
and having her every move watched
and judged is pretty insane.
[Kourtney] When you're really anxious,
you're not supposed to drink caffeine,
alcohol or have excessive sweets.
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] That's horrible.
[upbeat music]
Ready? Kris, this is Diala Makki.
-Hi. How are you?
-Pleased to meet you.
And my good friend as well.
[indistinct chatter]
[Diala] You have five grandchildren now?
I do.
[Diala] And your daughters are getting
more successful day by day.
Is… is it more difficult
to spend time together now as a family?
Do you have to work harder
at getting everybody…
I know you hijacked your family
and put them on a plane
and took them on a vacation.
I did. I did. I said "Be there or else."
I really need to be focused
on my business trip.
-Thank you.
-[woman 1] Thank you so much.
But at the same time,
I can't help but wonder what's going on,
and I just wish I was at home.
-Bye, guys.
-Bye.
[Kris] All right, where are we going?
Great.
-I'm obsessed with watches.
-[woman 2] Me too.
-And I love…
-[phone ringing]
Hello.
[Rob] It's Rob.
Hi.
What are you doing?
Oh, wow. Okay.
All right, well, I'm just about to go…
Okay, bye. Love you.
Okay, that was Rob.
Rob calls me to tell me
that he's gonna meet his sisters,
and it makes me extremely nervous.
I really pray that they will
solve their differences
and see things eye to eye.
-I just need a glass of water.
-[camera shutter clicking]
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] You know I shot
my cover yesterday.
Yeah, how was it?
Great. I love Yu Tsai.
How crazy is he?
Like, he tells you what to do.
"Smile. Keep that smile."
Then he's like, "Okay, now, stop smiling."
And then he's like,
"But smile through your eyes."
I would think that you
would not like that personality.
-No, I loved it.
-[phone chimes]
[Kourtney] Why is Kylie having
a talk with Scott right now?
I don't know. About what?
I don't know. He said, "I'm with Kylie.
We're having a talk."
About what?
-I didn't ask.
-Oh, that's what I just asked you.
[Kourtney] I feel like she was
just, like, in an anxious mood.
She kept saying to me,
"I'm so anxious. I'm so anxious."
And so, I was like, you know,
"Working out helps a lot.
Work out with me."
Oh, I mean, for me, like,
workouts took away so much of my anxiety.
-Same.
-That's my place of solitude.
Me too. I'm like, I have to work out.
Just mentally, what it does for you
and that release.
-What up, girl?
-[dog panting]
[Kourtney] I had such a good workout
with Don the other day.
Oh, I love him.
Like, he's so nice.
This guy works out all day long.
He has the most energy I've ever seen.
He's not fazed by you and I whatsoever.
I forgot to tell him. But he was like,
"I wanna come to your shoot."
Who, Don?
Who, Don wants to?
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Mase.
Mase.
-What?
-[Khloé] Hello.
[Rob] Oh, what's up?
[Mason] Nothing.
So what's up?
Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
Oh, a new sweatsuit finally.
-Same one.
-[Khloé chuckles]
[Rob] Same one I wore ten days in a row.
Where's Kourt?
Kourtney?
Rob and I can't be left alone together
for too long.
Kourtney.
[Khloé] This is uncomfortable.
I love my brother,
but I haven't seen Rob in…
I feel like a really long time,
so I can't lie, it's a little awkward.
And it's almost like we don't
wanna be left alone together,
which is kind of weird.
How was Vail?
It was good.
[Khloé] Good memories.
[Rob] Mm… I was supposed to go.
I know you were.
No one told me it was a ski trip.
-Okay.
-[Rob] So…
No one told you it was a ski trip.
Mom says we were flying
an hour and a half away.
I had a stylist come over
and get me all shorts.
You always find some loophole excuse.
I'm not gonna go on a ski trip
with no… with nothing.
-Sorry.
-[Rob] No, it's…
There's plenty… There's plenty of time
in the year to go on a family trip.
Well, if that's your mentality,
then things will never happen.
There is plenty of time
in this year to go on a--
So there's plenty of time for you to do
what you gotta do, right?
-[Rob] Hey.
-[Kourtney] Oh. Oh. Oh.
[laughing]
[chuckles]
-Do we wanna sit in here?
-[Rob] It's your house.
-You decide where to sit.
-You can't leave Rob and I
-alone together for too long.
-Wait, have you seen
-my movie theater room?
-[Rob] No.
-We'll go check it out.
-Check it out after.
-[Rob] We'll check it out now.
-While waiting for Kim.
[Kourtney] The playroom
and the movie theater are downstairs.
-[Kim] Hi. What are you doing?
-You look thin.
-I look thin?
-Yeah.
What do you think
he's gonna talk to us about?
[Kim sighs]
[Khloé] We were left alone together
for too long,
and I had an attitude,
so I'm not gonna talk a lot.
-It's like--
-Yeah, I think you just have to,
like, you know what? It's not your life.
I'm gonna refrain from talking.
Yeah. Just be quiet.
Khloé and Rob have, like, this, you know,
history of growing up so close together.
[Kim] So Khloé is obviously
taking this harder
than all of us.
And I really do feel bad for her.
[Kim] Hey.
My favorite sister.
[Rob chuckles]
Khloé should probably sit over there.
Why? Because I'm too close to you?
-You're in close reach.
-It's just better.
-Like I'm gonna hit you?
-[Kourtney] Let's just switch.
What are you gonna say?
[chuckles]
I know you guys obviously know
what happened,
just based on, whatever.
-[Kim] Social media.
-Social media.
But everything that happened,
I'm very happy about.
It was something that I--
So, like, did you get on, like, one knee?
[chuckles]
I gave her the ring,
and then I got on the knee after.
It happened, like, spontaneously,
so that's why you guys
weren't in the loop,
because I was gonna do this regardless.
I just didn't know when,
and it just ended up happening.
We wanna be honest with you.
We felt like we should have just
at least got a text and say,
"Hey, guys. I know you're seeing this
on social media. It's true."
People were asking us and we were like,
"We don't even know if it's true."
If you guys really were concerned
and wanted to know,
you guys would have said, "Is this true?
-Congratulations…
-Well, we felt,
-…you just got engaged."
-I'm not finding things out.
Obviously, well, you think
I'm just gonna post
some fake [bleep]
because I'm a media whore?
-Never in my life.
-Why would I say congratulations
if I don't know if it's true or not?
It's the first time I ever proposed
to someone in my life.
Why would I joke with that?
I don't joke with that.
-We understand, you know--
-[Rob] It's a two-way street.
You guys could easily
have picked up the phone and called me.
No, I'm not gonna talk to you guys
when you guys are in a room
with Tyga in… on a ski trip.
But yet you put it on social media.
That's not the point.
You act like I'm supposed
to just call you guys and just say,
"Oh, this and that,"
-when you hate this girl.
-[Kim] We would've appreciated that.
-So it's like, it's crazy.
-But we love you.
-That's great. And she makes me happy.
-So we would have appreciated that.
-And she loves me.
-And we're happy for you.
-Right. So we…
-[Rob] And I'm happy. And that's it.
Of course, we would be happy for you.
But we're allowed to be hurt
that you didn't tell us,
-but we're also…
-[Rob] But that's why…
You're allowed to do it in your own way.
[Kim] We see that you're happy,
and that's all that matters to us, really.
Like, we obviously have tried
to get you out of the house
for years, you know,
and that hasn't worked.
And so, if someone else can do that,
like, we are really, you know,
thankful for that.
Do you understand that
that was hurtful to us
that we found out about your engagement
on social media?
Yes, I understand,
but I didn't understand…
I didn't… I wasn't even thinking that
at the time.
It happened so fast,
but I get I upset you guys.
I get I'm your brother, your only brother.
You would like to know
when something important
like this happens.
I apologize
'cause I wasn't trying to be rude.
So…
[exhales]
And then there's one more thing
I have to talk to you guys about.
I don't want you guys to get mad.
[nervous chuckle]
[tense music]
[Rob] There's one more thing
I have to talk to you guys about,
but I don't want you guys to get mad.
[nervous chuckle]
[Kourtney] What?
You're having a baby.
[sighs]
Yeah.
[tense music]
-[Rob] Just so you know…
-[Kim] Are you being serious?
[Rob] No, I'm being Bible.
I'm being deadass,
but you have to understand
I've been trying to do this.
I'm not even kidding.
This was, like, really my decision.
It, like, really wasn't hers.
On Dad's grave, on everything, I'm Bible.
Did you tell Mom?
Yeah, Mom knows.
She didn't want me to say anything to Mom
and you guys until she was three months,
but I want Mom and you guys involved
'cause I think it would be worse,
since obviously the engagement thing,
how you all reacted
and then she starts to show
or something, but…
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Congrats.
I know Khloé's probably feeling--
[Khloé] Congratulations.
[Rob] Thank you.
[Khloé]
I don't know my emotions right now.
I know I feel… I feel more empty
and more unresolved
than anything else, and…
I'm, like, internally sad.
[Kourtney] Are you excited?
I'm excited, yes, but I know you guys,
probably feel really weird.
I mean, I don't expect you guys
to be all happy, but…
I'm sure you guys will eventually.
So…
She's not a bad girl at all.
She's really loyal and she helps me a lot
with trying to get back on track
and it's just good.
So, obviously, I want you all a part of it
because it's gonna happen,
so there definitely needs to be a talk
between all you guys,
'cause she's not going anywhere.
She knows I'm gonna be in her life.
She knows you guys aren't going anywhere.
I don't want it to be where it's just,
like, y'all don't have a relationship.
That's just weird.
[tense music]
[Khloé] I do think a baby is a blessing.
I think that if this is gonna get Rob
to get his [bleep] together, cool,
but I personally don't know
what the next steps
for Rob and his girlfriend
and all of us are.
I mean, that's up to Rob.
Obviously, things aren't gonna be,
like, perfect overnight.
-No, I know, but I just wanted--
-And, you know, I think
-we should talk, you know.
-Yeah.
It has to start somewhere,
and that's why I started
with Mom and then you guys,
and I'll have my talk
with Kendall and Kylie,
but I wouldn't make a decision like this
if I wasn't all the way sure
with everything.
-What?
-[Kourtney] That's exciting.
Babies are a blessing.
Who would have thought Rob
would've been the one to join the…
North and Saint and everybody?
[Kourtney]
Who is that little guy? Come on.
[Kim] Hi.
-[thumps]
-Ow!
[upbeat music]
Hey. Today is Freestyle Friday,
so we're not doing
the motivational quote thing right now.
We're just gonna jump into the workout…
-All right.
-…and get it done.
-Freestyle Friday!
-[Kourtney] It's Friday!
-[phone chimes]
-[Khloé] "Could not send."
Kourtney, what the [bleep] is up
with your Wi-Fi?
You have this big-ass house
and you can't afford a Wi-Fi box out here?
It's not about affording,
it's about radiation.
You're gonna die anyway.
You understand that, right?
Die with a good Snapchat going through.
What the [bleep]?
[Kylie] Hey.
Kylie is here.
[Khloé squeals]
You made it to the family workout.
Kylie is here!
-[Khloé squealing]
-Hi, you guys.
[Khloé exclaiming]
Kylie, get ready to crush your anxiety.
Crush it.
[Kourtney] Khloé and I have
a lot going on in our lives.
We have, like, the best lives
and also the most [bleep] up lives
at the same time.
So, this is what gets us through our days.
-[Don] Here we go.
-Okay.
[Don] Three, two, one. Let's go.
One. Twenty seconds. Two.
I'm so surprised you could jump rope.
-Kim can't.
-[Don] Two…
They had to cut the jump rope over her.
She just swings the rope around.
Good. Drop your ropes right there.
[panting]
Okay, guys,
I don't know if I'm gonna finish this.
[Don] It's just the warm-up.
I need to get home and take a shower
and get ready for the day.
Do one quarter and just try it.
I kind of wanna leave.
[Khloé] Just do at least one quarter.
[sighs]
[Don] One leg up, we're going 30 seconds.
One, drop. Two, slow it down.
[Khloé] Kylie really just seems
like her head is not here this morning.
-You only did one quarter.
-[Kylie] I know.
There's three more to do
and possibly overtime.
[Don] You at least got to do half.
You know, Kylie being so young
and there's so much pressure
and focus on her life,
I could definitely understand
why she feels anxious a ton of the time.
But I know Kylie just has to find
what it is that will take away
that anxiety.
[Kylie] I love you, guys.
Think about if you did four,
how good you would feel.
[Khloé] Love you.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Excuse me, can I help you?
[Mason] No.
[Khloé] Well, that's not how you shut it.
Put the stick back.
-Which one?
-That big one. Now pull it out.
Pull the drawer out.
There you go.
Everything has a home.
You have a home.
I do and you're in my home.
It's been real.
[Mason] It's been so good.
[Kourtney] Should we call Mom
and tell her we talked to Rob?
[Khloé] She's obviously known.
That's obviously why she was
tripping out like that
and not wanting to go,
and I think if she just knows
that we're cool,
then she'll feel better.
Yeah.
[phone ringing]
[Kris] Hello.
Hi, Mom.
-[Kris] Hi there, pussycat.
-Ooh.
How is Dubai going?
[Kris] The jet lag is always
a challenge for me,
but other than that, it's all good.
-What's going on?
-Well, nothing.
Kourt and I wanted to call you
because now we obviously talked to Rob,
and we now know why you were
so hesitant about leaving
and that we're all good over here,
and there's nothing you could do
if you stayed here,
so don't worry about that.
[Kris] What did he say
when you talked to him?
You know, just a lot, a lot to digest. Um…
[dramatic music]
You know, there's nothing we can do,
what's done is done, so…
[Kris] Yeah.
I don't know.
My mom was planning
on going to the Maldives
right after her Dubai trip.
She wants to be here for Rob,
but Rob and all of us sisters, we're good.
There's no reason
why she has to rush back home.
If anything, she needs this vacation
and she deserves this vacation.
[Kris] Thanks for letting me know.
I'm fine now that you called
and you guys are there,
and it makes me feel better,
I love you, guys, and I'll be home soon.
-Bye, guys.
-[Khloé] Bye.
Love you.
[upbeat music]
[percussive music]
This looks nice.
I feel like we're on Fantasy Island.
[light music]
I was really anxious to leave town
at a time when my family really needs me,
but I got a call from the kids,
and everything's all good
with the girls and Rob.
[Kris] It just gives me the confirmation
that I really needed to take a minute
away from the situation and relax.
[Kris] Wow, this is so cool.
-Cheers.
-Cheers, baby.
[Kris] This is peaceful.
This makes you like
you're one of the fish.
Yeah.
-Look at the teeth.
-[Kris laughs]
[Corey] Why have rabbit teeth as a fish?
[Kris gasps]
Here comes the whole school.
They all travel together.
-Yeah.
-It's like my kids.
Okay, if you were Kylie,
what fish would you be?
[Corey] I'm gonna pick out Kylie for you.
[Kris] Okay. It has to be, like, big lips.
[both laugh]
-And Kendall.
-That's Kendall right here.
-[Corey] It's pretty.
-Uh-huh.
-There goes Kim.
-[Corey] Hello.
This is the paparazzi
and they're trying to find Kim.
[both laughing]
[Corey] Oh, look at this one.
Look at this one.
[Kris] That could be Rob.
I kind of miss the kids.
[Corey] We're almost home, baby.
Back to Hidden Hills.
Sometimes in life,
you just need to take a minute
and walk away from a situation
in order to see things more clearly.
I'm having another grandchild,
and I'm Rob's mom,
and I need to just be as loving
and positive as possible for him
because that's what they need right now.
[Corey exclaiming]
Those two are pissed off.
[Corey] He's probably getting
after his bitch.
He like, "Girl, where the [bleep]
you been swimming at all night?"
[both laughing]
You, okay, it's… it's time to go.
We've been under the water way too long.
I'm getting a little worried about you.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] This is nice.
I've never been out here.
Me neither.
It's kind of cool
that it has, like, a ledge.
[Kim] I know.
[Kylie] Hey, Bambi, come here, Boots.
[Kourtney] Oh.
Ew. This dog smells so bad.
She farted.
[Kourtney] I think you feed them
-weird food.
-[Kylie] No.
I honestly just can't imagine
having a pet.
[dog whimpers]
So how's your anxiety?
I don't know, I just feel like
I've been dealing
with anxiety for so long.
-[Kylie] It's just a thing.
-Like, you just get overwhelmed.
Yeah, some people are born for this life
and some people aren't,
and I just know
I'm not supposed to be famous.
Like, I can feel it deep down inside.
Some people are born for this life
and some people aren't,
and I just know
I'm not supposed to be famous.
Like, I can feel it deep down inside.
-[Kim] Really?
-Yeah.
That makes me so sad.
-I'm not supposed to be famous.
-I'm not either, for sure.
-Yeah.
-I am.
-[Kourtney] I think you are.
-[Kylie] I know you are.
Because you can handle it.
I can handle it,
I just don't give a [bleep].
I can't handle it, and I give a [bleep].
I care too much, I read too many things.
No, but I was like that.
At the beginning,
I would go out, I'd come home,
and I'd sit home
on the computer all night long.
Yup.
[Kim] I do sympathize with Kylie.
It does take really thick skin
to not read the comments.
And it took me
up until about two years ago
for me to get that way.
So I can understand that she is,
like, in the height of it all
and she has so much attention around her,
but your life is just so much better
when you don't pay
too much attention to it.
I used to literally spend all my days,
like, just worried about media and, like,
I was just so obsessed.
And then what happened?
You just stopped caring
and you realized
you couldn't please everybody?
Kanye didn't care,
so being around someone that, like,
-doesn't care as much…
-Doesn't care.
…you just let it go.
I couldn't even tell you the last time
I looked at a magazine,
-and I wouldn't even care.
-[Kourtney] Me neither.
[upbeat music]
[Kylie] I'm surprised to hear that Kim
struggled with being famous
in the past too,
and it does give me a little hope
that if she got through it, I can, too.
Yeah, it's just been like this
for too long.
Like, I'm way too young for this.
But don't you think that, like,
you're like a normal person at a party?
-Not really.
-Yeah.
I just don't like parties at all.
I know. On the way walking you
to the car, you're like,
"By the way, I hate parties."
I hate parties.
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
Hi.
[man 1] We are here.
[Kylie] Should we talk about Lip Kit,
and go through
some of the stuff right now?
[Kris] Yeah.
So this is what they're getting.
The box is epic.
And then Kylie's note,
"Thank you so much
for purchasing your Kylie Lip Kit.
I hope you enjoy using it.
And I wanna thank you
for joining me on my journey."
Kylie, this is so good.
We have 25 minutes to go.
[Kylie mutters]
I know. I'm getting nervous.
[tense music]
[Kylie] I am stressing out right now
because today's the day
of my Lip Kit restock
and I really hope
that everything goes perfect
so that no one
has anything negative to say.
So I'm gonna post photo before,
and I'm gonna say,
"All six shades are now available
on kyliecosmetics.com," right?
-Yes.
-Yeah, kyliecosmetics.com.
-[woman 3] Yeah.
-You guys,
we're, like just a few minutes.
[all exclaiming]
Okay, guys, showtime, go time.
[Kris] Let's do this.
[Kylie] I'm scared, I'm scared.
[woman 4] This is how many people
are on the site right now.
[Kris] Fourteen thousand?
[Laura] Fourteen thousand.
-Wow.
-[Laura] We're up.
People have a feeling,
they have a feeling.
[woman 5] I'm having,
like, heart palpitations.
I know. Me too. I think
I'm gonna cry or something.
Okay, it's 8:59.
[Kris] Oh, look how people
are starting to jump on.
[Kylie] All right,
tell me when I can post.
-[Laura] It's 9:00, it's 9:00.
-Tell me. I just shared it.
-[Kylie] I did it.
-[Laura] It's 9:00.
[gasps]
[Kris] What?
[Kylie] It stopped. I think they literally
-just broke it.
-[Kris] What?
-[Kylie] It just stopped.
-[man 2] No, no, no, no, no.
[Kris] Is it broken already?
[tense music]
-Oh, [bleep].
-Oh, my god, you guys, you guys.
[Kylie] It stopped. I think they literally
-just broke it.
-[Kris] What?
-[Kylie] It just stopped.
-[man 2] No, no, no, no, no.
[Kris] Is it broken already?
Oh, [bleep].
[Kylie] Oh, my god, you guys, you guys.
[Kris] Is it our site
or it's Shopify's site?
[man 2] It's the site.
-The site's down?
-[Laura] Shopify…
Shopify can't get in.
This is so stressful.
[Laura] Let's get Ryan on the phone.
[phone ringing]
Hey, Ryan. Um…
I can't get into the back end
of the Shopify admin. Can you?
[Ryan] We're looking at that right now
but the site is open.
The IT guy, he says
you'll be able to log in
once we remove the cache.
-So they're doing it right now.
-Cash?
-I think they need to clear theirs…
-Different "cache."
-Okay.
-[Laura] Okay.
-[Kylie] Oh, my god.
-[Kris] You're up?
-[Laura] I'm up over here.
-[Kris] Okay.
-So it hasn't crashed yet?
-[both] No.
The customer's
not experiencing any problems.
-It's just our end, Kris.
-Okay.
-So we're selling product?
-[Laura] Yeah.
[Kris] So almost 30,000 people
are on the site.
[Kylie] Amazing.
[man 2] What's it saying on social?
-[woman 5] "Bam, bitches."
-[Kris] "Bam?"
"Thank you for improving the site.
I got Posie and Koko easy.
It was such a pain last time."
-[people cheering]
-Oh, yay!
[Kylie] I just posted on Twitter.
Go get it, honey.
We're up over 70.
[exclaiming]
[Kris] Hundred thousand.
-Congratulations, Kylie.
-Yay, congratulations.
[Kris] Whoo!
Oh, now it's… now it's sold out.
In less than 30 minutes.
-[man] That was it.
-[all cheering]
That is really… it makes me happy.
-[Kris] Congrats.
-[woman 5] It paid off.
-[Kylie] Thank you.
-You're welcome.
This is just so exciting.
[Laura] Oh, my god, you're gonna all cry!
-I'm so proud of you.
-[chuckles, sniffles]
Proud of you, my girl.
I am so happy everything went perfectly.
The website didn't crash,
everybody's happy, except for the people
that weren't able to get it this time.
But other than that,
I'm just focusing on the positive.
Kylie, I think
you've just launched an empire.
[Kris] Congratulations, everybody.
[all cheering]
We kind of [bleep] rock.
-[Kris chuckles]
-Amazing.
[all cheering]
[upbeat music]
What kind of couch is this?
[Khloé chuckles]
-There's, like, no back to it.
-I know.
Well, there is
if you take this pillow away.
What happened to your couch
that was comfortable?
[Kris] I gave it away.
Look, and then
I can't even move my head back
'cause there's no back support.
Okay, well, I don't know
if you've noticed or not,
but everybody moved out of here,
and I had to do something.
[phone chimes]
Wait, Kylie and Chyna,
they were upstairs, Mom?
Yeah.
I'm just so confused.
[Khloé] Seeing this picture
of Kylie and Chyna together,
I legit thought
it was Photoshopped at first.
I was like, "What am I looking at
right now?"
Well, Rob came over to have a talk.
Why didn't you tell me that?
I haven't gotten a chance to talk to you.
Kylie and Blac Chyna?
[tense music]
It feels so good to have had
the conversation with Rob and Chyna.
I said, "Look,
I just want Rob to be joyful
and happy and productive and…"
He goes, "Mom, I'm really happy.
This is what I want." So…
Just being with them and hearing
what they had to say,
and to see how in love
they are is amazing.
He's a grown man,
and he needs to make his own decisions,
and I need to let go a little bit.
-[phone ringing]
-[Khloé sighs]
Did you forget to tell me something?
[Kylie chuckles]
I just am seeing screen grabs
from Twitter,
and I'm like, "What?"
[Khloé] This is crazy. How was it?
[Kylie] Should I just tell you
when you get here, the whole story?
-[Khloé] You are a beast.
-[Kylie] Let's talk when you get here.
-I love you.
-M'kay. Love you, too. Bye.
It makes me so happy
that Kylie was able to be so mature
and sit down with her brother and Chyna
and really get some
of the past issues talked about.
The next step, I think,
is really for my other kids
to follow in Kylie's footsteps.
[upbeat music]
[Harry] What's new, Khloé?
Oh.
[sighs]
[Khloé] Not much.
So tired.
But that's not new.
Uh-huh.
[playful music]
Oh, what's new with you?
[Harry snickers]
This is the worst conversation, Khloé.
[laughs]
Who cares about small talk?
Yeah, true.
Make me so uncomfortable.
So, Kylie, are you gonna tell us?
Yes.
[Khloé] I need to hear what happened
with you and Chyna today.
So pretty much, um, Rob called me
about the whole situation,
and I was just like,
"Look, I'm done. I'm over it."
And he was like,
"Just come in for the meeting."
Her and Mom were going back
and forth for a while.
Were they fighting or they were fine?
I mean, Mom was being kind of like Mom.
-[Khloé] No.
-Like, for sure.
-No.
-Yeah.
That's scary.
She was like, "I don't have
a problem with you guys,
I don't have a problem
with any of the sisters.
I swear I didn't do this out of spite.
Like, it just happened." This and that.
And then her and I were talking
about, like, Tyga a lot,
and, like, what went down
in the beginning,
because she was just like,
"You know, he would still text me."
And I already knew that.
Like, T told me everything.
Like, I saw all their text messages,
like, whatever.
I do think I'm still working
on finding ways
to let go of the things
that people say about me.
[Kylie] So I just told Rob
I want to talk to Chyna
because there's so much
misunderstanding going on
between her and I over social media.
[Kylie] We just talked a lot.
As I was talking to Chyna,
she had as much to say to me
as I had to say to her,
and I feel like a weight
has just been lifted off
both of our shoulders.
And I feel like that's all we needed.
And then I was like,
"We have to take a Snapchat
so the world knows."
-You said that?
-Yeah.
And then I just did the…
"We've been best friends the whole time."
I swear, I thought that was
a Photoshopped picture.
Everyone did.
So you guys are cool now?
[pensive music]
So that's that?
Yeah.
I think, at this point,
we all need to be one big happy family,
'cause some things we just can't control.
Like other people's lives.
And honestly,
I think you guys should talk.
It's like, people need to make up
and get over things, and, like--
I'm just gonna start
minding my own business.
No, because family is family.
I don't know why I would have
a sit-down with Chyna
'cause I don't have any issues with Chyna.
I find it weird that Rob doesn't think
him and I should have a sit-down
before anything else
because that's where the issue is,
is between Robert and myself,
and Rob can't just go into hiding.
[Khloé] I think the more space
Rob leaves between us,
it's… it's not just gonna fix itself.
Robert and I need to talk
about what happened,
how did we get to this place,
and how we could fix it
so we could never go back here again.
Who wants to have beef with someone?
-I don't.
-[Kylie] It's, like, tiring.
I don't like having a beef with anyone.
Beef is not fun, you know?
I just don't like beef.
I haven't had beef in years.
[laughs]
"I don't like beef."
[Kylie chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Who shut the door?
Who shut the door?
Did Kris Jenner do that to you?
Do you remember her? You lived with her
-for a minute.
-[Kris] Hi.
Yeah, but is it the same dog?
Because Gabbana,
I feel like, was more gray.
She's just happier,
so her hair turned back dark.
That's exactly why I went to the Maldives.
I wanted to be happier,
I had too much gray hair.
[Khloé] How was it?
It was really, really fun.
-We just, like, chilled.
-That's good.
I just needed a minute because…
I just felt really overwhelmed,
and I didn't wanna just come
right back home
before I took some time
for myself to breathe.
-Mm-hm.
-[Kris] And just…
digest everything that's been going on.
Especially after Vail.
Vail was a lot for me.
I just think that all of us
have been so caught up with,
like, all this Rob drama.
It's just overwhelming.
You know, there's this huge part of me
that just wants him to be happy.
[Kris] Khloé and Rob have always
been two peas in a pod
and best friends.
And it just breaks my heart
that there's any divide
between the two of them
whatsoever, especially over relationships.
I think I cried myself
to sleep for three years
just praying he would feel and get better.
I was telling Kourtney and Kim, it's like,
wait till your kids grow up and, you know,
you face some real-life challenges
with everyone.
And then you realize
what a mom really goes through
even when her kids are adults.
The next step, I think,
is really for Khloé to hopefully
have a great conversation
with Chyna and Rob,
and I think that
the more we all heal together
and bond together,
the better life we're all gonna have.
[dramatic music]
[Kim] Coming up next week…
Kanye's shooting the video in Iceland.
This is unreal.
Are you sad that you're not
with Kourt on her birthday?
[Scott] Yeah, obviously.
[Kim] We need to go straight to the video.
We don't have time to go to the hotel.
I'm starting to freak out.
I'm not gonna make it
to Kanye's shoot in time.
We may not make the video shoot.
[Lamar] You should talk to your sister.
[Rob] Whenever I talk to her,
it just leads to yelling at each other.
[Lamar] Look who I found.