Did you invite Rob?
Yeah, he said, "I'd love to,
but, because of Chyna, I'm not coming."
Have you talked to Khloé lately?
-No.
-She's had a hard year.
And she misses her brother.
[Khloé] No [bleep] way!
I was just checking to see how you are
and see if I could see you soon.
[Khloé] This is the best phone call ever.
[Khloé] Oh, Robbie.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kourtney] Kylie.
-Ooh, girl.
-[Kourtney] What are you doing?
[Kylie on phone] Ooh, girl.
-[Kourtney] Is that funny?
-[Kylie] Yeah.
In two years, you'll be 39.
Are you gonna be
going to Vegas when I'm 21?
If I could work at Spearmint Rhino,
-I'll come with you.
-Okay.
You got to strip club it up
when you're in Vegas.
-Yeah.
-We went to one, one time,
and Khloé was hanging the strippers
upside down by their ankles,
-holding them like this.
-There's no way.
And then Malika, the strippers had Malika
by her ankles and were shaking her.
Like, upside down.
And I was eating chicken fingers
in the corner.
-Oh, my god, when was this?
-Tyga was there. And Chyna.
[both] Oh, my god.
That is so crazy.
-Life is crazy.
-Yeah.
[theme music]
[upbeat music playing]
[Scott] So what's shaking?
[chuckles]
What's shaking?
What do you want to do for your birthday?
[Khloé] Well, I'm not doing anything.
-I never do anything.
-[Scott] Yeah, you do.
What have I done for my birthday
for the past two years?
-Just answer the question.
-[Scott] I'm trying to think.
Twenty-five, you were fat,
so you probably
just tried to eat yourself.
-[chuckles]
-Uh, 26, you were slimming down.
[Khloé] One year, Kourtney threw
a pajama party for me at her house.
What year was this?
It was the year that I thought
I was turning an age,
but I guess I missed a year,
so that year was not a good one for me.
-[Kendall chuckles]
-And I had a balloon.
-One balloon.
-[Kendall] We can make it so poppin'.
"Poppin'".
[Kendall] Yo, do you want to, like,
get a yacht from Marina del Rey,
and you sail to Malibu?
That's a great birthday
for people who enjoy water.
-Oh, right.
-[Scott] Oh, right.
-I absolutely hate water.
-[Scott] She needs a flotation device.
I'm gonna lookup
"penis flotation devices".
[Kendall] Do you want to, like, bowl?
Roller skating?
Are you kidding? I would kill myself.
[Khloé] I love everybody else's birthdays,
I don't love my own birthday.
Really just because there's been
plenty of years
where my birthday just has been,
kind of like, dark clouds around it.
So I'd rather do nothing
and have no expectations.
[Scott] How old are you turning?
-[Kendall] Twenty?
-I'm only kidding.
I know you don't talk
about age anymore, it's just…
where you are in your body?
-Mm-hmm.
-[Kendall chuckles]
I like that. In my eyes, you're about 25.
[Kendall] Why are you
so nervous about your--
Did-- You already turned 30.
Are you turning 31 or are you turning 30?
First of all, listen.
[chuckles]
I'm not afraid of my age.
Looking your age up right now.
[laughs]
That's not fair.
-I'm Googling!
-No, I…
No, I wouldn't Google you.
Here, let me tell you,
you are in your prime now.
Do you want me to show you
what you looked like
-when you were 25?
-Oh, I remember.
-That's it.
-[Kendall laughs]
You want to be this girl?
[Scott] You want to celebrate that,
or you want to celebrate now?
I hate birthdays.
[upbeat music playing]
[Jonathan] I've never seen
this part of the house.
-I've only been here at night.
-[Khloé] At night, it's great.
'Cause it has all the twinkle lights,
-that's my favorite.
-[Jonathan] Beautiful.
By the way, this is paradise.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[Jonathan] So anyway,
I'm addicted to this yogurt
that Kim and Corey brought me to
in Beverly Hills and I--
[Kourtney groans]
-But it's only--
-Go Greek?
-[Jonathan] I love it.
-[Kourtney] Do you know what
the best thing on top of it is?
The honey…
lavender… something.
[Jonathan] I think you're just,
like, pushing honey,
'cause Kim told me
you're doing some honey thing.
-I am. I'm doing--
-So you're like the honey ambassador.
-What is this thing?
-I'm doing this
-Manuka Doctor's skincare line.
-[Jonathan] What does Manuka do?
[Kourtney] Which, I'm just nervous,
because I have to do a London trip,
and I have to present at an awards show,
which I'm used to doing
with Kim and Khloé.
Like, I love doing everything
all together,
but I just feel like,
to do interviews by myself,
like, to have a meet and greet.
I'm like, "Does anybody really care?"
-Like…
-What?
Speaking in public by myself is,
like, a huge no for me.
[Kourtney] I failed two classes in college
because I wouldn't give a speech.
Like, doing anything with my sisters,
I'm totally fine, and we're all together.
But just, like,
knowing that it's all about me,
I just don't like being
the center of attention.
-People care.
-Just me, by myself…
You're so insecure. What's wrong with you?
-[Kourtney] I'm not.
-They do care.
[Kourtney] I don't know.
But, seriously, if you want
to do interview questions
we could, like, practice
and, like, snap you out of this.
And I will come out of PR retirement.
-Yes.
-[Jonathan] Just to help you.
-Okay.
-'Cause it's, like,
-my specialty.
-[Kourtney] I'm into it.
-A little practice.
-All right, well,
-let's set up a time.
-[Kourtney] Okay.
Have your people call my people.
-I will.
-[Jonathan chuckles]
[chuckles]
I really will.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] Haven't been to lunch
with you guys in a while.
Isn't it gross to think
of how many people's mouths
have been on these things?
I didn't really think of it
until right now.
[chuckling]
But, yeah, that's…
-nasty.
-That's disgusting.
[Scott] Did you end up
seeing Rob the other day?
-[Khloé] Yeah, he came over.
-And?
[Khloé] It was nice. We just talked.
-It was a nice conversation.
-[Scott] Where? At your house?
-Yeah, he came into my house.
-And everything was…
-you felt good, right?
-Yeah. Like, I was just--
Like, I just told him,
I was like, you know, like,
"When I married Lamar, like,
it was really awkward
and I had to put myself, and like,
make myself uncomfortable
so the family was comfortable."
It was my job to bring Lamar in
and make everyone fall in love with him.
-It's still his job…
-[Scott] Totally.
…to bring her around,
and that's what I was saying.
Are you aware of what happened
over the weekend?
No, what happened over the weekend?
[Scott] Are you serious?
-What happened over the weekend?
-[Khloé] Yeah, what happened
over the weekend? Why would I say--
I guess they got into, like,
a really big fight.
I've heard they've been
having problems recently.
And I'm sure he's stressed out enough
with just everything else.
I know from firsthand
how difficult it was growing up…
overnight, you know what I mean?
Like, he's had a pretty easy life,
and now, he technically has to take care
of a woman and a new child,
and a stepchild, basically, and it's like…
I mean, I would think
that's a lot of pressure, but--
[Khloé] Yeah.
-I don't know.
-What was their fight about?
Oh, I mean, I think it's something
maybe you should ask him.
It seems pretty personal.
[Khloé] I mean, I don't mind calling him
and saying something.
[line ringing]
-Hey, Rob.
-[Rob] What's up?
[Khloé] What's going on?
How's Chyna?
[Rob] Um, I'm out of her house
and we're not living together.
[Khloé] Why?
[Rob] I, honesty, I'm so over it.
If I don't care, then that's exactly
where she wants me to be,
and I'm completely content with that.
And I'm just preparing myself.
Well, you feel unappreciated, and, like,
I don't think she realizes
maybe the effect it has on you,
but, you also can't put all that
on her shoulders, you know?
You've got to do your own thing,
you've got to be strong
on your own two feet.
And you got to, like, do you for you,
so no matter what, you'll always be okay.
[Rob] I'm not doing nothing wrong.
-But, like, you--
-[Rob] I'm doing exactly what she wants.
So, I don't know what I need to do.
It's just a lot of this [bleep]
I don't know. I just don't…
[Khloé] Hello?
I love that my brother has been so happy,
and out and about, and living his life,
but hearing how upset he is,
I am really concerned
that Rob will go backwards.
I don't want him to have made
all this progress,
and then, if they're arguing,
or something bad happens,
he's gonna go and retreat.
-What are they doing?
-He said that he's giving her space.
He doesn't know how to act.
You know, she's hormonal.
It's a new relationship
where it's still weird anyway.
[sighs]
That's just a lot.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kourtney] You comfy?
[Penelope] Mm-hmm.
-Hey.
-The food god is here
to bless your food before you eat.
-Oh, good.
-♪ Ah ♪
What's up?
What's going on? Hi, P.
-I came here to help you.
-[Penelope mumbles]
For Manuka?
How exciting.
[Jonathan] Wow, look at you, J. Lo.
If you took me out of PR retirement,
we need to go over your questions.
[Kourtney] Okay, so what questions?
I'm gonna throw you off…
-Okay.
-…left and right.
So just remember,
you're gonna be on your own,
no sisters. 'Cause I swear,
I used to do this with Kim
back in the day.
-No way.
-And she'd be like…
"What should I say?"
I'm like, "Let's go over this."
-[Jonathan] Like, literally.
-[Kourtney] Oh, my god.
-All right, Kourt.
-Yeah?
So how'd you get involved
with Manuka Honey?
-Well, I posted it on my app…
-Mm-hmm.
…and they were looking
for a brand ambassador…
-Boring. Boring.
-…for their…
-That's so boring.
-…skincare.
-What do you want me to say?
I want to buy it. Make it more exciting.
Be like, "I've loved honey my whole life,
and I was, like, putting it on my--"
-"I put it on my [bleep]…"
-Yeah.
"…to make it shine
like the top of the Chrysler Building.
I want my nips to be
a little hard, you put it on."
[Jonathan] Can you just
demonstrate where you put it?
-Because people love visual.
-This is a skincare line.
[Jonathan] Yeah. People love visual.
-It's honey. Honey's freaky.
-It's for your face.
Oh, it's not for your body?
-No, but--
-[Jonathan] At all?
-I was putting the honey…
-Can you use it on your body?
-…on my body.
-And?
-[Kourtney] Mm…
-[Jonathan] What's it like?
-You know…
-[Jonathan] Don't smile.
[Kourtney] No, I was thinking
-of a real answer.
-Give a good answer.
It's just, like,
a really good consistency.
You have to answer
in a really full answer.
This pretend interview
was supposed to make me feel
so much better and more prepared,
but Jonathan is making me feel
so much worse
and so much more anxious about it.
Right now, you need some work.
[Jonathan] Poosh, how did Momma
do on the interview?
One to ten, give me a number.
[Penelope] No.
-[Kourtney] No?
-Everything is "no", by the way.
-Really, P?
-[Jonathan] Nothing.
[Penelope] No.
[laughs]
"No."
[upbeat music playing]
-[Kris] Hey.
-[Kendall] Hi.
How are you, honey? You look really cute.
[Kendall] Thanks.
Have you eaten today?
Why, every time,
I could say, like,
"Oh, my god, my nail broke",
and you'd say, "Have you eaten today?"
This is crazy.
I just had an acai bowl.
Strawberries are really bad right now.
-Are they out of season?
-I don't know.
Siri, where are you?
Hey, Siri.
Come on, Siri.
-Siri.
-Mom.
-[phone chimes]
-[male Siri] Hey, there.
Oh. What is the best season
for strawberries?
[male Siri] Hmm. Here is
what I found on the Web
for "What is the best season
for strawberries?"
Can you read it to me, Siri?
[male Siri] Who, me?
[Kris] Yes, you.
Okay. So what are we gonna do
for Khloé's birthday?
Hello?
That's a really good question,
since we have, like, no time left.
She was saying how…
she doesn't want to do anything.
But I feel she needs to do something.
-She never does anything.
-Okay.
I had a million suggestions,
she wasn't into any of them.
She was into nothing.
So I say we just do something
without telling her, or, like…
Hi. How are you?
-What up, girl?
-[Kendall] What up?
-[Kendall chuckles]
-What's shaking?
-We're talking about…
-We're just talking about…
-…Khloé's birthday.
-…um, Khloé's birthday.
[Scott] I think we should put
an ice skating rink over her pool.
-[Kendall] But it's summer.
-What about a foam party?
-[Kendall] Yes…
-At her house, the pool,
the whole thing's foam,
we do a Jell-O pit,
Jell-O fighting.
Like everybody's gonna do Jell-O shots?
For-- No. They're gonna
[bleep] wrestle in Jell-O.
Is that not the vibe we're going for?
-[Kendall] I don't think so.
-No. I think--
-I'm thinking more…
-Or maybe I hang out
-with different people.
-…party under the stars,
dance floor, appetizers, have a sushi bar.
[Scott] I mean, I think
that sounds pretty fun.
[Kris] Khloé is so loving,
and has such a big heart,
and she's so good at making sure
that everyone else feels
special and loved.
So I think it's really important this year
to come together
and start celebrating Khloé.
Because she has had a tough year.
Should we get some male strippers for her?
Yes.
-[Scott] I think so.
-Oh, my god.
-All right, well, I'm gonna--
-[Scott] Do you like that?
I'll make that call. I'll make that
-happen right now.
-[Kendall] Yeah, do that. Do it.
-I'm gonna…
-[Scott] Wow.
I am not so into those glasses.
-[Kendall laughs]
-Why?
Very Harry Potter-ish.
-Yeah, I like them.
-I don't love them.
I think you're better than that.
[laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] Are you wearing
full-blown underwear?
[Kourtney] Yeah, I have my period.
Like, granny panties?
Why are you wearing those
'cause you have your period?
-'Cause--
-What do you wear out
-in your period?
-What do you mean?
-Like, what…
-I don't wear tampons.
-What?
-I just don't think that's healthy.
Hold on, let me-- Look at me.
Let me see your-- No, other way.
-You're wearing a pad?
-Yeah.
How do you not look like
you have, like, a whole--
-Well, it's not like this thick.
-I just don't…
The one-- You should've seen
the one in Iceland.
-It was this long.
-Ew!
-And it was this thick.
-[laughs]
And it had two sets of wings. Two sets.
-For how big of a vagina?
-I have no idea.
That is the most…
-disgusting thing.
-I have, like, thin…
thin ones.
-[Don] How we feeling?
-[Kourtney] Good.
[Don] Okay, let's warm-up.
Let's just go up and down for ten.
Just take off, grab 'em.
[Khloé] Are you feeling any better
about your press tour?
[Kourtney] No, I'm still kind
of nervous without you guys.
[Khloé] You act like
you've never done an interview.
-[Kourtney] I know.
-[panting]
Don't you get nervous, when you did, like,
Howard Stern and all that stuff?
[Khloé] Howard Stern is crazy.
I was so nervous.
Any [bleep] story our family has,
they're gonna ask.
But you're doing more business.
Howard Stern,
that's more personal-oriented.
[Kourtney] Yeah, I mean, I'm not
doing any crazy stuff like that.
It's all beauty-related.
[Khloé] The great thing is,
you control your interviews
and you could then throw
a question back at them.
-Everything is about you.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
Khloé's right. I am in control,
and I don't have to say anything
I don't want to say.
She's giving me
much more helpful advice than Jonathan.
I have done this for so many years,
I just don't know why I get so nervous.
[Khloé] What are you nervous about?
Like, what questions is
someone gonna ask you?
-I don't know.
-I guess Scott questions.
No, I actually don't care
about Scott questions.
I can answer any Scott question easily.
-I don't care about that.
-Do I kind of have a muscle
if I do this? No?
Okay. Can't hold it that much longer.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] Oh, hey. Isn't this,
like, your ideal weather?
-You love it hot.
-That's you.
I feel like I've seen this before,
but I can't figure it out,
so I'm trying to--
It's just this that you've seen before.
[Khloé] I know. I love that cape, though.
-It's Kendall's.
-Ooh.
-Can I have it next?
-Yep.
I did shorten it, 'cause it was so long.
-And she doesn't know that…
-[Khloé] That's so mean.
…but I only tucked it, so you can untuck.
Mom loaned me this Valentino dress
that I wore at your wedding,
and I tailored the whole thing,
like, sucked it to me,
and I never told Mom 'cause I was scared.
And then she asked for it back,
and she was like,
"It can't fit me,
I've gained so much weight,"
but I was scared to tell her
-that I really tailored…
-Oh, my god. You have…
-…the whole thing
-…to confess today.
No, it's okay.
[Khloé] Oh, my. Hi.
-Hi, how are you?
-[Kim] South of France.
-Oh.
-[Kim] This is like…
-I haven't seen you.
-…an Italian getup.
My Italian getup?
[in Italian accent]
It seems very Italian.
[Kim in normal voice]
Wait, can we discuss…
Your glasses are a little crooked.
Oh.
[chuckles]
How about that?
[Khloé sighs]
So…
I'm trying to find Rob.
I've called him, I've texted him,
he's not responding.
But he responded to Victory today.
He told Victory he was at his house.
Oh, so he's not at Chyna's house.
-Mm-mm.
-They're still not
-talking to each other?
-Mm-mm.
-[Khloé] How long is that gonna go on for?
-I don't know.
But I talked to Chyna and it scared me
because it was everything
that we had experienced with him.
She was experiencing the same thing.
So, she wrote me last night, and she said,
"Can I see you tomorrow?"
"I just really need to talk to you."
-You know, "Rob won't talk…"
-[Khloé] And that's today?
"…to me." Yeah, she was supposed
-to come over at 9:30.
-Rob won't talk to her?
-[Kris] Yeah.
-Why won't Rob talk to her?
I don't know, I haven't gotten
into the whole song and dance.
Is he ever gonna see his kid, though,
or is she… is she gonna take it?
You don't-- You really think they're over?
He seems, like, when I talked to him,
he was very much, like, in love with her.
Am I missing something?
How long have they not been speaking for?
[Kris] I don't know.
I know when my brother hurts,
how badly he does hurt.
The more they're fighting
and the longer things are bothering him,
the more depressed he gets.
He'll go into hiding again, go missing.
Like, I don't want Rob to live
that life anymore.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kris] Khloé?
[Khloé] Hi, Mom.
[Kris] Hey, what are you doing out here?
Sitting. It's so sunny in here.
It is sunny in here.
I love this ping-pong table.
Thank you.
Like, this is really beautiful and chic.
It makes you want to play ping-pong.
-[Khloé] Mm.
-[Kris] So here's the deal.
I wanted to come over
and talk to you in person
because we've all been trying
to figure out
what to do for your birthday.
Nobody can think of what to do
and I thought,
I'm just gonna come over here and ask you
what would be your dream birthday party
that we could all do
to celebrate with you?
I just don't really feel, like,
it has to be something so great.
Like, it's just another day.
-Like, no.
-Well, it's your birthday.
Why doesn't everyone just, like, call me
and wish me a happy birthday this year?
No. Because… no.
I just feel like…
my birthdays, I get more anxiety about
because they've always been a dark cloud,
like, looms over it.
Like, it's always, like, something like,
negative or, like, a letdown.
That's why we want to make it
special this year.
And acknowledge it, and have a party,
and make it a celebration.
And make it about how we celebrate Khloé.
Come up with a couple of things
that would make you really happy to do
and to be with everybody,
and then we'll do the rest.
How about that?
-Okay.
-Okay, good.
It'll be really fun.
[Khloé] My mom is right.
There's been a lot
of negativity in the past,
so I'm gonna take control
over this energy,
and I am just gonna put
in the atmosphere that,
"No, we're gonna have a party,
and it's gonna be
one of the best parties
I've ever had in my life."
[Kris] Oh, and we need a birthday list.
'Cause I know you probably have
a list going on somewhere.
So register,
-and then send me a link.
-A birthday list for?
A birthday list for friends,
or are we talking about gifts?
Gifts. Like, what you want
for your birthday.
-What's your wish list?
-No, I'm not four.
[Kris chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] Where the hell's Kourtney?
-[Reign] Mama.
-[Khloé] What?
-[Khloé] Kourt?
-[Kourtney] What?
Do you ever think you and the Lord
are gonna get back together?
-Do I ever?
-[Khloé] Yeah.
You know you are, right?
I don't know. I just don't know
what is in God's plan.
Some days I'm like, "Ah, never."
And then some days, I'm like,
"Okay, maybe in the future."
-Like--
-I don't think tomorrow.
It's not in tomorrow's plan…
-[Khloé] No, not in tomorrow's plan.
-…I'll tell you that.
[Khloé] Have you guys spoken
to Rob at all?
[Kourtney] Nope, not once.
Well, apparently, Chyna called Mom to say,
"Rob has been sleeping all-day
until 3:00 again,
and he doesn't wake up,
and he's not motivated,
he's up under me all the time."
She's like, "It's annoying, it's frust--"
Like, they were the same issues
he had before.
And I know everyone was like,
"Oh, my god, Chyna saved him."
"Like, he's good now."
When you're in love, you do get,
like, that high, which is great,
but now it's, like, reality time.
And I told Rob this. I said, "You know,
you have some issues
that you've always had."
"And I'm happy that Chyna got
you out of the house,
but all relationships fight,
so you guys will be okay again,
but you have to deal with your issues."
Totally, as he should.
I just want Rob to know
that, no matter what,
like, we'll always be there for him.
He has to know he could call one of us,
like he could come to my house,
I'm not gonna ask questions,
-just go in back into your room.
-I want him to feel that way.
Like, I want him to feel
like he always has someone
to turn to, you know?
[Khloé] I want my brother to know
that we're all in support
of whatever makes Rob happy.
And, I think, if Rob knows that we're all
supportive and onboard,
Rob will feel more comfortable
to talk to us about some things,
and maybe if we could give him advice,
it will help his relationship.
Some tensions
between Rob and Chyna will just diminish.
-Do you want to call him and say "Hi"?
-[Kim] Yeah.
[line ringing]
[automated voice] I'm sorry, the person
you are trying to reach has
a voice mailbox.
[tense music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Kourtney] Rob?
[Kim] Where is he?
[Kourtney] There's nothing but a scale.
[Kim] Ricky?
Where is he? That's so weird.
He wouldn't be here after all that.
[Kim] We really wanted to check on Rob
'cause we haven't heard from him.
So, kind of worried about him,
and just want to make sure he's okay.
[Kourtney] Should we write him a note?
"Rob, we want you to be happy,
and we're here to support you
in any way we can."
-K, what do you want to say?
-Call us. Love you.
All right
[sighs]
[Kim] I called Chyna.
-[Kourtney] Mm-hm.
-[Kim] Just to be like,
"Hey, like, I get it."
"You know, you guys are, like,
not vibing, but I just want you
to know, like…
I'm here if you need to like,
talk about anything."
She's like, "Honestly, I used
to think it was all you guys."
-[Kourtney] Yeah?
-Like… 'Cause that's like,
the way that it is,
like, perceived or whatever.
Now, she's like, "I just need someone
to talk to 'cause it's really hard…
to, um…
-deal with him."
-Mm-hmm.
She's like, "I just want someone
that's like, motivated,
and that'll, like, get up
and like, do something."
-Yeah, but he's depressed.
-Yeah.
And so I said, you know, she's like,
"I could see now that it's, like,
you guys all tried to help him."
And I was like, "Yeah, and we thought
you were gonna help." You know?
But I also said, like,
"Don't give him false hope
if you don't, like,
want to be with him, you know?"
[Kourtney] Yeah.
I think there's always
two sides to every story,
and I want to be supportive of both.
I mean, Chyna's now family,
and you know, I want her to be calm
and feel like she has a support system.
You know, I do want her to feel
like she has me to talk to,
and to, you know,
vent to if she needs something,
just like my brother can.
And I just want everything to be cool
and I think they just need to talk.
-[Kourtney] It's been real, Rob.
-[Kim] Hopefully, he'll call us.
[upbeat music playing]
[reporter] Hey, Kourtney. Kourtney!
[photographers clamoring]
I'm finally in London.
And I have a full, crazy day
of photoshoots, interviews.
I'm presenting
at the Glamour Women of the Year Awards.
And I'm excited, I'm just
definitely really nervous.
[indistinct chattering]
[host] Please welcome, Manuka Doctor's
brand ambassador, Kourtney Kardashian.
[crowd cheers, applauds]
[Kourtney]
I have the worst stage fright, and like,
I just can't get on the stage
and talk by myself.
Thank you, guys,
and I am doing my tit lift.
So you got to get really in there,
-that's the trick.
-[crowd laughing]
Way down in.
With more than three million subscribers
to her You… YouTube channel…
[dramatic music playing]
I cannot believe that I'm stumbling
during my speech.
This is exactly why I don't give speeches.
I just want to sneak out the back door.
With more than three million subscribers
to her You… YouTube channel…
I cannot believe
that I'm stumbling during my speech.
I just need to take a deep breath
and finish this up,
and never give a speech again.
…a best-selling book,
and a cookbook on its way,
this woman is a millennial mogul.
The inaugural Manuka Doctor
YouTuber of the Year Award goes to
Tanya Burr.
[audience cheering, applauding]
Thank God, that's done.
And now, I have a photoshoot,
press interviews and a cocktail party,
and I'm doing it all by myself.
[camera shutters clicking]
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat music playing]
[photographer] Get a nice
little movement right in there.
That's it. Stroke in there.
[man] Beautiful.
Do a nice big pose.
Cute. And that's it.
[woman] That is stunning.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
You guys are gonna put
croissants in front of me?
[laughter]
[interviewer] So I'm your first interview.
[Kourtney] Yeah.
[interviewer]
So, if you had to swap styles
with one of your sisters,
who would you choose?
Um…
I would say, Kylie,
because I think she's really--
First of all, she does her own makeup…
-Does she?
-…perfectly.
[Kourtney] And she's so up on
all the trends.
Brilliant.
[Kourtney]
I was really anxious and nervous,
but I'm getting more and more comfortable.
-Hi.
-[glasses clinking]
Thanks, everyone, for coming
and I'm so happy to be in the UK.
I want you all to know
that I brought this amazing weather.
[laughter]
[camera shutters clicking]
-[man] Thank you. Thanks, love.
-It looks so cute over the shoulder.
[indistinct chattering]
[Kourtney] Do you have Snapchat?
You'll never take a photo…
-[laughs]
-…any other way now.
I feel really confident,
and I'm actually enjoying
doing all this press.
[Kourtney] It's actually really fun,
so I'm really proud of myself.
-Amazing. Thank you.
-Thank you.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Do you want cheese bread?
[Khloé] Sure.
I'll do a whole shebang.
[Kim] I called Chyna and I was like,
"Girl, I feel you."
Like, her and Rob are, like,
fighting and whatever.
I get it, you know what I mean?
Like, he's not
the easiest person on the planet
to deal with.
So, maybe if she felt like
we were all, like,
inviting her to your party,
then she would feel,
like, more accepted, 'cause it's like…
You know what I mean? Imagine
if you were in her shoes.
I'll call her.
Would she wanna go even if Rob…
-wasn't coming?
-Yeah, I mean, if I was like,
"Hey, I'm going, come."
Like, I'm sure she would love
to hear that,
like, you want her to go, too.
You know what I mean?
I think she feels like you don't like her.
[Khloé] I don't know her.
Obviously, when Rob first told me
about his relationship with Chyna,
how I first found out,
it just wasn't on good terms.
But I don't really know Chyna.
I've never hung out with her one on one,
I've never had her phone number,
none of that.
And I want to change that.
I want to change the energy
within the family,
I wanna make everything just happy,
and that we're all just
accepting of one another.
[line ringing]
-[Chyna] Hello?
-Hey.
Hi, hey.
What are you doing? How are you feeling?
[Chyna] Hey, I'm doing good.
I just, literally, like,
got King from school
and about to make some broth and chicken.
Oh, that's good.
[Chyna] Yeah.
[Kim] Well, I'm sitting here with Khloé.
-[Chyna] Hi. Hey, Khlo.
-How are you?
-How you doing?
-I'm good, thank you.
-How are you?
-Good. Yeah, good.
Um, well, I am having a birthday party,
and I wanted you to know,
like, I know you and Rob are,
like, kind of, like, fighting or whatever.
And I wanted you to know
that if he doesn't want to come,
like, you are still invited to come.
[Chyna] All right, okay. Yes.
Thank you. Yay, I'm so down.
I am so happy that Chyna has agreed
to come to my birthday party.
I think this is a great step
in such a positive direction,
and I hope, with us inviting Chyna,
Rob does decide to come.
[Khloé] I would love if Rob came.
You know, it's my brother,
I wish he would be there.
[Chyna] Yeah.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Khloé] Hello.
-[Rob] Hey.
-[Khloé] Hi, Robbie Rob.
-[Rob] I was just--
I spilled some, like, fish in my car.
Ew.
That's gonna be… brutal.
I heard Rob and Chyna
finally spoke to one another,
so I really wanted to stop by
to see how Rob is doing.
Do you know I completely just knew
how to get here from memory?
I've only been here one time.
[Khloé] I pulled over
and was just like, "Wait."
[Rob] It's confusing the first time.
[Khloé] Cute. Cute.
Ooh, that's a nice backyard.
-[Khloé] Rob, oh, très chic.
-[Rob] Yep.
[Khloé] Oh, a lemon tree?
What? Rob, this is so cute.
What are you smiling for?
'Cause it's my license picture
-that I didn't want to--
-Oh, I want to see.
-That, uh… that I…
-Let me see.
-…wore a hat, so I'm like…
-[chuckles]
-Look, it's so bad.
-Why'd you wear a hat?
'Cause I just wanted to get it over with.
No, but you know you can't wear
a hat in your picture.
No, I know. I just didn't care,
'cause I'ma go back there
and retake the picture when I'm feelin'…
-when I'm feeling better.
-Spiffy?
Oh, my-- You got to get out of here.
-What?
-[Rob chuckles]
-[Khloé] Kimberly.
-What?
Uh, how much are you?
I know, the neighbor did kind
of look at me like…
-You literally look like Rob--
-…a hooker city.
-Yeah, he probably thought…
-I did feel, like, uncomfortable
-for one second.
-…like Rob paid for you.
Like, Kim, I literally
just dropped my jaw when I saw you from…
[chuckles] Well…
-Chillax.
-[Rob] It wasn't a bad "wow."
[Khloé] Anyway, what's going on?
How's everything on the home front?
[Rob] I mean, it's been tough.
It's really just--
It takes either one person to man up.
Obviously, that's gonna have
to be me.
But at the same time, I'm not
gonna argue with a female.
We had a good talk
the other night, so, we'll see.
[Khloé] I'm the one who said
arguments are normal.
-It's gonna happen.
-[Rob] Okay, but at that second
it happened, I took it seriously,
-and I took it to heart.
-And that's--
-And I was like, "All right."
-'Cause you're sensitive.
I don't even-- I don't know.
You have to worry about Rob,
and how you could be strong
and better for you, and now your baby.
[Rob] Yeah, well, I'm fine.
[Khloé] Don't you want to get
-you're [bleep] together?
-[Rob] I do.
My plan is not to have a kid with somebody
and not be with the person.
That's just bizarre to me.
[Khloé] I know Rob and Chyna
have a long way to go,
but I'm really happy
that they are working things out.
Relationships are hard no matter what.
And as long as Rob is trying,
and starts really engaging
and communicating,
that's all I could ask for,
but he has to figure it out
and this is, like, baby steps to his life.
What are you doing on Monday, Rob?
[Khloé] Are you coming
to my birthday party?
[Rob] I'm not sure. I don't know.
Where else are you gonna be?
There's alcohol, there's food.
There's games, there's a photo booth.
And I invited Chyna.
Well, it'll probably make me want to go.
It's always helpful to go with somebody.
[Khloé] Yeah.
I mean, I get it.
[Khloé] Uh… Kim, your selfie book is here?
[Kim] You guys, look what Rob reads.
[Khloé] It's not a reading book.
There's no words in it.
There are words, you ass [bleep].
"Kim Kardashian."
[Kim on recording]
Guys, look what Rob reads.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Kris] There's the birthday girl.
-[Khloé] Hi, guys.
-Hey.
-[Tracey] Happy birthday.
-Hi, Mom.
-Hi.
-You look beautiful.
-[Khloé] Hi, guys.
I am super excited for my birthday party,
now that it's here and, like,
you know, can't turn back.
Ready to go inside?
[indistinct chattering]
[Khloé] Oh! This is so cute.
I decided on Dave &amp; Buster's,
because they serve alcohol and play games.
The best of both worlds.
[Khloé] Did you invite people?
[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Khloé] Where's everyone?
It's 7:40.
[Kourtney] The party started at 7:00.
[Khloé] There's nobody here.
Holy [bleep], Dave &amp; Buster's is huge.
I didn't realize how big this place was.
[Khloé] How many people did you invite?
[Khloé] I really hope people show up.
Relax.
Allie's on her way.
[Kourtney] There, Scott just walked in.
And here's North and Kim.
[gasps]
Hi!
Oh, my goodness. Thank you.
-Happy birthday.
-Hi. Thank you for coming.
[Kourtney] Stop. Uh-uh.
-Did you guys plan this?
-We're matching?
-[woman] Is that planned?
-[Scott] Yeah.
You didn't tell me
you got us matching ones.
I just got all the dope ones.
-Hi.
-Hey.
[indistinct chattering]
[party music playing]
[Khloé squeals]
To Khloé's birthday.
Happy birthday, Khloé!
[all cheering]
[Kim] Go, go, go!
[Kourtney] Okay. Okay.
[Kris] Oh, my god.
[camera shutter clicking]
-Happy birthday!
-Thank you!
[Scott] Is Rob coming?
I keep asking him,
but I don't get a response.
[Kris] I don't know. Let's FaceTime him.
He's never going to answer.
Have you talked to Rob?
Not in, like, a week.
[Kris] I just want everything
to go perfectly tonight,
and it would really mean
a lot to Khloé if Rob comes.
So, I'm praying he shows up.
[Malika] Is Rob coming?
[Khloé] I don't know. I invited him.
There's Crissy and John.
-And me!
-Let me get out of the way.
We're having so much fun
celebrating Khloé's birthday,
but Khloé really misses Rob.
[Kourtney]
It's definitely not the same without him.
[Kourtney whoops]
[woman] Rob!
[Kourtney whooping]
Oh, my god, it means like, the world to me
to have my brother at my birthday.
I can't remember the last time
my brother was at a family holiday.
So, to have him here… it's pretty awesome.
-Oh, my god, hi.
-[Chyna] Hey.
-Rob!
-[Rob] Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
-How are you?
-[Khloé whoops]
-I love you.
-Good. I love you.
-[Rob] What's up?
-Man, you good?
Good.
I can't believe they're here.
I am overjoyed.
[Kris] I'm so happy you're here.
-Say hi to Kanye.
-Hey, man.
[indistinct chatter]
It's such a special family day,
and we're all here celebrating.
We're so used to not having Rob,
and there's a sadness.
There's always a sadness
in the air when Rob's not here.
And so, tonight,
we don't have the sadness.
[Rob] Happy birthday. Love you.
-Hey.
-[both giggling]
-You're our…
-[laughter]
-[Khloé] Did you guys talk?
-[Rob] Yeah.
-Yeah, we talked.
-Are you guys okay?
Yeah. Did you say hi to her?
No.
Come here.
-Oh, my god.
-[Rob] Chyna.
[Khloé] Oh, my god.
-[Chyna] Happy birthday,
-[Khloé] Hi, thank you.
Happy birthday. You look bomb.
-Thank you.
-[Chyna] You look bomb.
-Oh.
-I'm so round, right?
[Khloé] But you're just belly.
[Chyna] All belly, I know.
Earlier it was like smaller,
it's like it grew.
[Khloé] Thank you.
I'm so glad you invite-- I was invited.
I was, like, "Yay."
I'm happy you're here.
Thank you for coming.
You're so sweet.
I am grateful that Chyna came
to my birthday party,
'cause I think without her,
Rob wouldn't have come here.
And it shows me how much
Chyna does care about Rob,
because that's an intimidating situation
to walk into.
[Chyna] I'm trying to think,
I'm like five months now,
I'm wondering, like, how much bigger
am I gonna get, you think?
-[Kim] Bigger.
-[Chyna laughs]
[Kim] I'm so happy
that Rob and Chyna finally came.
And I'm just glad
that they can work it out,
'cause you know, it's like,
they have a baby on the way.
I just want everything to be
cool. At the end of the day,
we just want both of them to be happy.
-Mom, Rob.
-[Kris] Oh, my god.
[Rob mutters]
I want to take a picture with Khloé
'cause it's her birthday.
[Chyna] Khloé, can we go
in the photo booth with you?
-Yeah, let's go.
-Go in the photo booth. Go.
This has honestly been
one of the best birthdays
that I've had in so many years.
I'm just happy that I had this party,
that everybody came here,
that my brother and Chyna came.
And I hope this is the new tradition
for my birthdays to come.
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct shouting]
[Khloé yelling indistinctly]
[Rob] Hey.
-[screams]
-That's awkward.
-Are you ready to be a daddy?
-Yeah.
[Chyna] Mm. Give me some tongue.
[Chyna] This season on Rob &amp; Chyna…
Do you know where the baby is right now?
-Right here?
-[laughs]
[Scott] I feel like this is the first time
we've hit the streets together
in a long time.
It's almost like he was in jail.
-[Rob] Hey, do this one.
-Oh, that's nice.
[laughs]
[Rob] It's a big change
to go from being inside
for like, four years,
to now being outside.
You was waiting for me?
[laughs]
Y'all trying to go to the strip club
-where it all started?
-[all] Yeah!
♪ Let's go ♪
[all shouting, laughing]
[all] Cheers!
[Chyna] Oh! Oh! Oh!
-Just relax.
-[screams]
[Rob] Yo, who this hitting
your phone over and over?
Why you want to keep
going through my phone
like you don't trust me?
I just don't get why you even care.
What are you still texting
other females about?
-[Rob on phone] What?
-I'm not [bleep] playing with you.
Why the [bleep]
are you still texting bitches?
[Chyna] What are the flowers for?
I just wanted to apologize.
[Chyna] I don't know
why he thinking it's a game.
[Rob] The whole argument is too much.
She's too hot and I'm too hot.
Everybody argues in a new relationship.
I know you've been through a lot,
but you put that wall up
to protect yourself.
[Rob] We're just two different people.
I don't expect her to be like me.
I don't even know that you know
exactly who you are.
-Yeah.
-What could I do to help?
[Chyna] What really triggers you
to go into a dark hole?
[Kim] Depression is a serious issue.
What's gonna happen
when this baby is born?
You really want to spend
the rest of your life with me?