[upbeat music]
[Cordell] What you doing this weekend?
Why? Are you trying to take me on a date?
Yeah, my birthday's this weekend.
[Khloé laughs]
How old are you turning?
That doesn't really matter.
-[Khloé] Okay, okurrr.
-[laughs]
-What are you doing for your birthday?
-[Cordell] I'm taking you out to eat.
Oh-- Okay.
What you want? some crab or some steak?
[Khloé laughs]
[Cordell] For real. I'm serious, though.
[Khloé] You want to be with me
on your birthday?
[Cordell] Yeah, you want to give me
your number or something?
What do I got to do?
-I got to work for it?
-Yeah, you got to work for it.
[Cordell]
I'm gonna talk to your assistant then.
[Khloé laughs]
[Snoop Dogg]
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls.
Today, I have a very, very beautiful,
special, lovely guest…
[whispers]
Khloé Kardashian.
-Oh, why, thank you.
-See how I said your last name?
-Kardash…
-I never heard it that way.
I've heard people say it
this way, that way,
but I never heard them say… "Kardashian."
Well, you always put
your own twist on things.
That is good. Kardashian!
[laughter]
[Snoop Dogg] So, Khloé,
the Kardashian empire is gigantic now,
and it's loving and it's fun, it's happy
and it's all ages and sizes and colors.
You got your baby sisters.
You got your sisters that's right by you.
That's, like, it's just so much style.
-[Khloé] We're not stopping, Snoop.
-For real.
And it feels good to see you doing it
because I like to pass it on
to my family. Like…
It's good to keep family in the business
and to be rightful-minded
while you're doing it.
We don't have to argue and fight
and we don't have to agree
-to everything that we do or don't like…
-Right.
…but we can always be family.
Yeah. Your son just asked me out
on a date.
-No, he didn't.
-[laughter]
-Is he old enough?
-He won't tell me his age.
-I'm not gonna tell you, either.
-He said, "Steak or crab?"
-[Snoop Dogg] Was he serious?
-Mm-hm.
-[Snoop Dogg] Mm.
-[laughs]
I'm proud of him
for even making an effort,
to put even put forth the effort to try
for something that's so high up
in the sky.
Boy, I love him
for reaching for the stars.
[laughter]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] You look so skinny. It's, like…
-[Kim] Really?
-[Khloé] Like… Oh, my god.
I don't like people like you.
-You're skinnier than me.
-[Khloé] No.
Like, I just don't have hips like yours.
I got to have a baby just to have hips.
Yeah, you should.
Can you actually have two for me?
You get really good hips
-if you pop two out at once.
-Yeah, but…
[bleep].
I just, you know, Kanye said
I could have their embryo.
Is that weird to most people?
It would be
'cause I would steal that child.
-Yeah, that's the problem.
-[Khloé] Why would you?
Because it's mine.
-[Khloé] Technically not. I birthed it.
-No, no.
No. That's what a surrogate is for.
But I'm not a surrogate.
[Kim]
I'll let you do it and then I'll steal it.
[Khloé] We can just be, like,
-a wolf pack and like…
-Right. It's like you're not
-leaving anybody.
-…raise them all…
Yeah, it's not like I'm gonna take the kid
-somewhere else.
-[Jonathan] You're both in Calabasas.
-Well, I know.
-They're all gonna be together
-and we could raise them as a little pack.
-Once you have a kid, you'll understand.
[Khloé] But you don't even want them.
Yeah, I do.
Lately, I've been thinking
I would love to maybe have another baby,
but, like, I had
two really difficult pregnancies
and really difficult deliveries.
[Kim groans]
It hurts so bad.
[breathing heavily]
-Don't cry. It's gonna be okay.
-It just hurts so badly,
I, like, could never do this again.
So, getting pregnant again,
it's something that does…
concern me.
What if you decide not to have them?
-You'd rather--
-[Kim] Well, after three years, at 40,
I'm not gonna pay
to keep them in this freezer.
-[Khloé] Can I pay?
-I'm gonna have to ask Kanye, seriously.
He already said yes,
-I asked him at the birthday party!
-But I think he thought you were joking.
You can't ask him in a party environment
with some drinks…
-He wasn't drinking, it was like…
-[Kim] It has to be, like,
-with attorneys and a sit-down.
-…children's party… No.
It has to be, like, a full sit-down.
If you had an attorney involved,
they're gonna change his mind.
[Khloé] Your kids are just so cute.
[Kim] Saint is such a doll.
-You have no idea.
-[Jonathan] No, we do.
That's why I want one of your embryos.
Yeah, yours are good.
[upbeat music]
[Kris gasps]
-[Kris] Kenny!
-[Kendall] How are ya?
-[Kris] My baby!
-[Kendall] What are all these glasses?
-You can have some, too.
-[Kendall] Oh, you're gonna get
-makeup all over.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
-How are you?
-[Corey] Good to see you.
-Good.
-Thanks for coming.
[Kendall]
I am at will.i.am's studio today,
and we are shooting the remake
for the "Where is the Love?" video.
Will reached out to me
and I definitely wanted
to be a part of it.
It is a direct response
to the gun violence
that's been happening recently.
[will.i.am]
The lyrics that we wrote in 2001,
you could just put them in
what's happening right now.
The vocals we will be recording today…
[Kendall] Oh, my god, I'm singing?
-No, no, not "singing" singing.
-Oh, my god.
[laughs]
[will.i.am] Just lip-syncing.
I'm lip-syncing.
-Yeah.
-[Kendall] I literally was like,
-why wouldn't someone warn me?
-[will.i.am laughs]
So yeah, you'll lip-sync
the words of the part,
and we'll have, like, images of things
that have gone wrong in the world,
and then there's this question mark
that people hold up
to question, like,
the world that we live in,
how can these things happen?
[Kendall] I love it. Shall we?
[will.i.am] Yeah, yeah, let's go.
["Where Is the Love?"
by Black Eyed Peas playing]
♪ Mama, Mama, Mama, tell us ♪
♪ What the hell is going on? ♪
♪ 'Cause people got me
Got me questioning ♪
♪ Where is the love? ♪
♪ Yo, what's going on
With the world, Mama? ♪
♪ Where is the love? ♪
♪ Overseas, yeah
They're trying to stop terrorism ♪
♪ Where is the love? ♪
♪ But if you only got love
For your own race ♪
♪ Where is the love? ♪
♪ Then you're gonna leave space
For others to discriminate ♪
♪ Where is the love? ♪
♪ And to discriminate
Only generates hate ♪
[will.i.am] Super fresh.
[Kendall in sing-song tone]
Genius!
[will.i.am] Awesome.
[Kendall]
I love Will. He's super inspiring.
And this is such a huge message.
I think it's very crazy
what's going on in the world.
It definitely makes me
more eager to kind of get out,
make statements, and be
a part of something like this.
-Thank you so much. Thank you.
-[Kendall] ♪ Where is the love? ♪
Thanks for having me be a part of this.
I'm so, like, happy to be a part of this.
[Corey] Yeah, Will, good job, man.
-Thanks, man.
-Bye, guys. Thank you.
[Corey] Great job.
[upbeat music]
[Faye] Oh, is this silk?
-Yeah.
-I thought it was cotton.
-No, silk Dolce.
-[gasps]
-Oh, that's even better.
-No, what's even better
-is this art.
-Christ, it's fantastic.
-[Faye] Do you love it?
-[Kris] Faye…
can I just tell you you have
the most amazing taste
in the entire world?
This is something
that's, like, taken to another level.
[Faye] I love this artist.
This reminds me of the wedding.
Oh, my gosh. You got married right there.
-[Faye] I know. Right here.
-Right there.
-[Kris] We'll have that memory forever.
-[Faye] Forever.
-[Kris] Speaking of memories…
-Yes.
I had the best idea.
I want to have a videographer
interview my mom
and have her spell out her whole life.
-Like…
-That is the best.
[Kris]
"What was your first childhood memory?"
And what she misses,
and what she would do over again,
or does she have regrets, and just…
-[Faye] Love it.
-…really talk about her life
and give us a little bit of history
that we can hang on to.
Yes, I think that's a great idea.
My mom is my best friend, and she's lived
a very beautiful, incredible, long life,
and has so many interesting stories
about things
that I can't possibly begin
to tell my kids,
because I can't remember it all.
-[Faye] When are you gonna do it?
-[Kris] As soon as possible.
I don't wanna ever have
my regret be that I didn't do it.
I've never met a woman
who's so conservative.
Sometimes, when we get into conversations,
do you ever notice she…
-Sometimes she's shocked…
-[chuckles]
-…that we've ever said something…
-[Kris] She's shocked, and then
she'll give you a gummy and say,
-"Eat this, you're gonna love it."
-[chuckles]
-"You're gonna love it."
-[laughs]
[upbeat music]
[Dr. Crane] Hey, Kris.
[Kris] Hi.
-Hi, Kim. How are you?
-[Kim] Hi. How are you?
-How are you?
-[Kris] Good to see you.
You both look… you look as young as ever.
Well, I've only known you
since I'm 17 years old, so…
I hear you've been thinking
about pregnancy.
-Yeah.
-[Kris] Do you think
that her body could withstand
another pregnancy?
[Kim] I want to check with my doctor
and see how everything's looking…
to see if it's even possible
to get pregnant again.
Here's what I think.
[Dr. Crane]
Your pregnancies, you had toxemia.
-[Kim] Mm-hm.
-[Dr. Crane] You had a retained placenta.
Very traumatic.
-You know.
-Yeah.
We're always worried
about the next serious complication.
I think the potential fear
of the whole situation is legitimate.
You never know that you might not have
the same type of problem
that could be more serious this time.
[tense music]
You're always taking
a little bit of a chance.
-Yeah.
-[Dr. Crane] There are situations
where a retained placenta
could be life and death.
[tense music continues]
You could bleed to death.
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] Oh, hi.
-[Kendall] Hi.
-Oh, we're so…
-Oh, my goodness!
Wow, we coordinated,
and we didn't even have to try.
That's 'cause we're sisters.
-Cute. Yeah.
-[Khloé] Aren't we?
How the hell are you, "happershrand"?
Remember the Black Eyed Peas song,
"Where is the Love?"
-Mm-hm.
-[Kendall] will.i.am remixed it
-and did a whole video to it.
-For what?
So I did… For everything that's happening,
Black Lives Matter, all of that stuff.
It's so sad. It's one thing
after another after another.
It makes me feel like the world is ending.
I don't know if we have more access
to viewing everything, like,
we're just more aware…
-[Kendall] Yeah.
-…of stuff or…
But we've had access to viewing everything
for years now, and it hasn't been
-this bad.
-Yeah, but the older you get,
the more aware you become of things.
-True.
-And like social media wasn't as big
a few years ago.
We should do something.
With our platforms, how many people
we have access to,
it's probably really silly to not.
But, like, what are you
most passionate about?
Is it, like, the gun laws?
Yeah, I mean, I feel like
that's kind of step one, no?
I think gun laws, forever,
have needed to be changed.
Movie theater killings,
all that stuff, that's, all things
-that were preventable, like…
-Yeah, totally.
[Kendall] I'm very passionate
about stricter gun laws.
I've never really made a statement,
but having such a big platform,
I feel obligated to take action now,
especially with everything
that's going on.
It's such a hard thing to try and, like,
change one human being.
You can't go and like, be like,
"I'm gonna change your soul."
-Mm-hm.
-Like, you know what I mean?
It's harder to get a car
than it is to buy a gun,
-which is wild.
-That's so wild.
But I think, like,
it starts with one person.
-One person has to make a change…
-[Kendall] Uh-huh.
-…somewhere…
-Mm-hm.
…and if you could bring awareness
to just one other person, like,
that follows you, or believes in you,
or likes you,
I think that's all you could ask for.
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] But I think if we all
as a family, did one cause
and really brought awareness to it,
I think it will move mountains.
Kim loves that. Like, Kim's always been
really passionate about it,
so I think our next step is maybe
having, like, a little family powwow.
Yeah. Are you supposed to have
one braid popping out?
-I have, like, a few braids.
-[Kendall] Oh.
I thought it was like
part of your, like, extensions,
or something,
that was just, like, coming out.
-Like my weave? No.
-[Kendall] Yeah. Yeah.
[upbeat music]
-[Kourtney] Hey.
-Hey.
-Why you're looking at me crazy?
-[Kourtney] Oh, no.
-My makeup? You're investigating?
-[Kourtney] No.
-[Dr. Huang] Hi, guys.
-[both] Hi.
-Kourtney, how are you?
-How are you?
-Kim, how are you?
-Hi.
-Good to see you.
-You too.
[Dr. Huang] All right.
-How's the family?
-[Kim] Good.
-He's so big.
-[Dr. Huang] Oh, my gosh,
-congratulations.
-[Kim] He weighs almost as much
-as my daughter. He's huge.
-[Dr. Huang] Adorable.
-Happy kid.
-He's so cute that I feel like,
oh, my god, I need to have another one.
[Dr. Huang]
Okay, so this is why you're here today?
Yeah.
So I didn't get good news from Dr. Crane,
and, you know, it's super disappointing.
I really wanna have another baby,
and Dr. Huang is
the best fertility specialist.
So, I just want to get a second opinion
and see what he has to say.
[Dr. Huang]
In my evaluation of your pregnancies,
there's the risk of postpartum hemorrhage.
-Mm-hm.
-[Dr. Huang] Right? So, you know,
we don't want to carry
that same risk of having you
get pregnant, deliver the babies,
then need blood transfusion
or, God forbid,
if we can't stop the bleeding,
uh, do a hysterectomy.
Your first pregnancy,
you had placenta accreta
and preeclampsia.
When you have one pregnancy
with preeclampsia,
it does increase your risk
about 25 to 30 percent
of having a subsequent pregnancy
with preeclampsia.
You getting pregnant again would be
a high-risk pregnancy.
The other option then,
would be to consider
using a gestational surrogate.
You know, if you were trying
to safeguard you,
and being around for these, you know,
kids that you have,
then doing what's safe is the best thing.
Using a surrogate is not
an unreasonable option.
If the two doctors
that I trust have told me
that it would not be safe for me
to get pregnant again,
I have to listen to that,
but because I don't know anyone
that's been a surrogate,
anyone that's used a surrogate,
I didn't really think of that
as an option for me.
[Kim] I don't know. I need…
I just want to, like, weigh my options.
[Dr. Huang] The question is,
how can we do this safely,
because if our goal is to grow your family
like you want to,
then a surrogate makes sense.
[upbeat music]
Well, what are you leaning towards?
Like, do you think
you would be pregnant again
or have a surrogate?
[Kim]
Obviously, I do want to have my own baby.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-You know?
But I feel like I truly don't know
if my body can handle it one more time.
You should talk to somebody
maybe who's used a surrogate.
Yeah.
Just think of a surrogate
the whole way through.
Somebody, like, would you,
like I would be…
Yeah, like, what are you eating?
-Right.
-What are you this? What are you that?
[Kim] I mean, there's just a lot of fears
that I have about surrogacy
and a lot of, like, unanswered questions.
Like, I just don't have
the information on it.
I don't know how I'm gonna feel about it.
I never have given it that much thought,
that I just… it's something that does…
concern me.
If you use a surrogate,
nobody has to know, the whole time.
You could have a baby for a year,
-and nobody would even know.
-[chuckles]
Not that that's a reason
to have a surrogate,
but if you have to, that is a benefit.
Like, who's in that little stroller?
Yeah.
[soft upbeat music]
-[dog barking]
-[Scott] Should we go out here
-with the sun?
-Sure.
I wouldn't mind getting a little rays.
[Khloé] Kind of breezy.
Oh, look who it is!
[Khloé] Oh, my god, you look so pretty!
-What's going on out here?
-[Khloé] Wow.
-Where are you going?
-Just over here to say hi.
-[Khloé] You look so pretty.
-Thank you.
-You look good.
-[Scott] I feel like
you guys get so decked out.
-I'm so decked out right now.
-Me and you don't.
In my Bible shirt…
-[Scott] But I feel like you and Kim…
-…and my flats that I wear every second.
[Kris] So cute. So wait,
I wanted to run something by you guys.
-Let's hear it.
-[Kris] I've been thinking a lot about…
life and my mom.
Wouldn't it be great
if I had somebody interview Mary Jo
about her life on camera
so that we have these amazing memories
about this person that none of us know
as well as we know each other,
because we all grew up together.
We didn't grow up with her
in her life, in her childhood.
[Khloé] That is such a good idea.
[Kris]
I want to ask her if she'd be into it.
She's in San Diego. Call her right now.
-[Khloé] Okay.
-[dog barking]
[line rings]
-[MJ] Hello.
-Hi, MJ.
[MJ] Hi.
-[Khloé] What are you doing?
-[Scott] Oh, she's the best.
I went to lunch
with Frankie, my boyfriend,
-and his wife.
-What?
-[laughs]
-[Khloé] How was your lunch?
-Good?
-Is she a side girl?
My mom wanted
to ask you something, hold on.
Did you just catch that?
-[Khloé] What?
-Hey, Mom, are you a side chick?
[MJ] Am I a what?
[Kris] A side chick.
I don't know these terms.
Yes, I think I'm a side chick.
[Scott] Oh!
He's going to introduce me to the wife.
-[laughter]
-Oh, thank God. Lucky you.
-Is she being serious?
-[Kris] She's kidding.
Hey, Mom, I wanted
to run something by you.
Wouldn't it be great if you came up here,
and I got somebody
to ask you questions on camera
and then we would interview you…
No, give this, give this to me,
give this to me.
-[Kris] Never mind.
-[Khloé] Hi, MJ.
-[Scott] I think there's a word for it.
-[MJ] Oh, it's called a legacy, uh, video.
[Khloé]
Yeah, we want a legacy video of you.
Okay, could I have
hair and makeup, please?
-[Khloé] Of course.
-[laughs]
-[Scott] Of course, the best.
-[MJ] I look so horrible.
[Kris] So you're in, Mom, if we set it up?
Yeah, we want a legacy video of you.
Please say yes.
I'll come up when you're ready.
-[Khloé] Yay!
-Okay.
We'll do it.
[Kris and Khloé] All right. Love you.
-[MJ] Love you, bunnies.
-[Khloé] Bye.
Like, the cutest thing in the world.
[Khloé] But why don't you interview her?
You videotape her so you have more like…
of, like, a family feel.
You don't want some stranger
interviewing her.
Well, I'll be there, but I think
I need a professional.
You should interview her.
[Kris] No, I'd rather not.
I don't know why my mom is so against her
being the interviewer for MJ.
I feel like this can't go any other way.
I don't want to hire
some random interviewer
to interview MJ,
'cause I don't think we're gonna get
raw, deep, good stories.
[Scott] I've known her 11 years.
-I could ask from 11.
-[Kris] Your questions.
-Oh, that's a good idea.
-I have my questions already.
[Kris] Okay.
Work on your questions!
It's gonna be a big deal!
[upbeat music]
-[Kendall] Who are ya?
-[Rob sighs]
[Kendall]
You smell nice. Do you want to see around?
-This is your brand-new home?
-[Kendall] Yes.
So, this is gonna be
the family living room.
-[Rob] Okay.
-[Kendall] I don't know the difference
between a family and living room.
-And then, I'm making a puzzle…
-Oh, nice.
…because I'm really cool.
-[Rob] Oh, Lion King puzzle?
-[Kendall] Yeah.
The guest rooms aren't done.
These are just, like…
this is just [bleep] we had.
Khloé had that bed in storage,
so she just gave it to me.
[Rob] This…
[laughs]
[Kendall] What, it was yours or something?
You can keep-- No, it doesn't--
It doesn't matter.
-[Kendall] What?
-No, what it was…
It was just…
I put it in her storage. It's all good.
-It's brand… It's brand-new.
-[Kendall] Oh. She just gave it to me.
And then…
-this is my favorite part.
-This is a dope ass room.
I call it the boys' room.
Yeah, this is where probably
I would be all the time.
What's this?
"Chrissy Teigen leaves Twitter
-after gun…"
-[Kendall] "…control tweet."
Um, Khloé and I were talking,
and I've been looking
for, like, gun control organizations
to get involved with.
-[Rob] Yeah.
-'Cause I'm, like,
we have such a nice platform
to, like, bring awareness to things.
Yeah. Gun control's,
like, a very serious thing
in America, in the world.
But if you get involved
with that type of stuff,
you're definitely gonna,
like, get some backlash.
Be a lot of people that have
completely different views,
that are opposite than you.
So, you're gonna get a lot of hate.
[tense music]
Kim received a lot of backlash
-when she spoke on it.
-Really?
Yeah, you're a young, powerful woman,
so you got to…
just be prepared
for the negativity as well.
[Kendall] That's crazy.
"Conservatives are saying
that Matt Damon is a hypocrite
because his character
in a movie carries firearms."
Is that a joke?
People get crazy with anything.
If you say something
that's completely right,
you're still gonna hear
a bunch of [bleep].
I feel like if I get involved,
it's gonna do more damage
than actually help.
[upbeat music]
[Kendall] Put your right hand out
like you're gonna shake my hand.
-[Kendall] Wait, wait, wait.
-[Khloé chuckles]
That's so trippy.
Who taught you to do that?
Okay, wait, then another one.
Everyone just curl in.
Keep going, keep going.
[Kim] This deserves a Snapchat.
-Guess the fingers.
-Oh, I think they'll know my fingers.
My nail is so…
[Khloé]
I think they're gonna know my finger.
[Kim] Do you guys know you can change
the color of your letters?
-I had no idea.
-[Kendall] Yeah.
Duh. I don't even know Snapchat.
Dodo bird.
Khloé was telling me
that you really wanted to get involved
-in something.
-[Kendall] Mm-hm.
I was telling her that you do
a lot of stuff for, like,
gun awareness and gun violence.
I was saying we should ask you.
I work with this organization, Everytown…
-[Kendall] Mm-hm.
-…and I set up a lunch
with some gun violence victims.
Some family members
that have been affected
that I think would really love
to meet you guys,
'cause they really do appreciate
people like us speaking out.
I've been meeting
with Everytown, an organization that…
is fighting to change
all the gun control laws.
There are so many loopholes in the system,
and I just feel really passionately about…
how our gun control laws have to change.
You guys should meet with them
and see what they're all about
and see if it's something
that fits for you.
[Khloé] I'm down for it.
I wanna do this
and I wanna be a part of it,
but it just makes me nervous,
like, what people are gonna think of it.
You don't know who's gonna, like,
actually be for it and who's not.
That's why a lot of people
don't get involved, I've learned,
is because you do…
you can get a lot of backlash.
[Kendall]
It's kinda difficult, 'cause I know
that we are public figures.
And seeing how controversial it could be
to speak out about something
you're passionate about,
I just think I don't want
the attention of someone not agreeing
with what I'm saying to take away
from the fact
that there's actual gun issues
that need to be handled.
It might bring more harm than good.
I feel like, in life,
I've gotten a lot of backlash
and I've gotten a lot of hate,
so I'm gonna just stick up
for what I believe in and what I want.
It's something that you believe in,
so you have to be confident in it
and go for it.
But at the same time, like… I don't know.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] This tan is everything.
Thanks. It's actually a real tan,
for once in my life.
It's very becoming.
I haven't had a real tan
in about three years.
Yeah. Me, neither.
[Khloé] Um, we are…
Do you even know about this,
the legacy video
that we want to shoot with MJ?
-I don't.
-I love that it has a name now.
-It's a legacy video.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
So, Mom wanted to do this video with MJ.
So, I came up with a few questions
-that we could ask.
-Can I see?
Why don't we have
Anderson Cooper be the mediator
and ask MJ all the questions?
[Kris] She would die.
Okay, that's so impersonal,
and MJ will give…
like, she would love that her grandkids
are asking her questions.
-And it's way more sentimental.
-Totally.
And she will be
way more inclined to give, like,
deep, emotional answers,
rather than Anderson.
-Oh, here we go.
-She'll feel guarded,
-and MJ's not…
-Anderson is hot.
[Kris] Like, she loves Anderson.
[Kim]
Why don't you wanna do the interview?
[emotional music]
It just makes me sad.
[Kris] I don't want to cry
through the whole thing, you know,
because it's like
the story of someone's life,
but at the end of their life.
I just feel like, I…
I don't know what I will do
when something happens to her.
I'm especially emotional
when it comes to my mom,
because I realize
that one day she won't be here.
So, I would rather not be the person
interviewing my mom, because I know
that I'm going to be an emotional wreck.
I think you will regret it later
if you don't.
If you ever watch this,
you're gonna wanna, like,
hear your voice or things
that you really are interested about,
'cause you're gonna have
way different questions
than I have.
-It's okay to share emotion.
-Totally.
I share too much emotion sometimes…
But you don't want
to interview her at all.
I would love to…
You know what, I think is…
just because we're sitting here
discussing it,
now I'm really thinking about it.
I think we should share.
I think if we each took an hour,
it would be a lot easier
and it would give her a change of scenery.
[Kris] I understand what Khloé's saying,
but I don't want to be that emotional.
I think it will be a more meaningful tape
with me doing it,
as long as I can just keep it together.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] I'm redecorating this room.
-I'm keeping those sconces.
-[Kim] Yeah.
The hallway looks
so much cleaner without them.
-[Kim] Way better.
-[Kourtney] But I also want it
to look like a home.
I don't want it to look like…
-[Kim] A monastery?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Kim] So, Dr. Huang set up
someone that has used
a surrogate before. Her name's Natalie.
[dramatic music]
I want to talk to someone
that's used a surrogate
that also has carried a child before
so that she would know the difference.
I want to explore every avenue,
just do all the research
that I possibly can
to figure out what all of my options are.
Hi.
-Hi. How are you?
-How are you?
-I'm Natalie.
-[Kim] Hi. I'm Kim.
-Nice to meet you.
-[Kim] Nice to meet you.
-Hi. Kourtney.
-This is my sister.
-[Natalie] Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
[Kim] So you had
-a baby naturally.
-Yes.
And then you used a surrogate
and had twins.
Yeah. I was diagnosed with breast cancer,
and my oldest was six months old,
so if I wanted more kids, this was it.
-Yeah.
-[Natalie] And so,
I then had twins via surrogate.
-And were they your egg?
-[Natalie] Yes.
-And your husband's sperm?
-Yeah.
They are my husband's, yeah.
They're genetically ours.
Yeah, and do you have a relationship
with the surrogate now?
-We don't.
-Was that her first time?
[Natalie] No, it was her third.
Someone has to really understand
what they're taking on,
and if you've done it before,
it makes a huge difference.
I'm more worried that, like,
'cause I gave birth to two,
there's a sense in me that feels like
because I went through all that pain
for these two babies,
like, I know we, like,
did this together. You know what I mean?
-[Natalie] Yeah.
-Like, we went
through hell and back together.
This little baby was just…
Like, there's no one
that would feel your love.
Like, they're literally near your heart.
Like, they're inside of you,
and there's no one else
that could be as close to your heart
as your babies.
[Kim] My bond with my kids is so strong.
I think my biggest fear is
just that, like,
if I had had a surrogate,
what I just don't know…
Like, would I love them the same?
That's, like, the main thing
that I keep on thinking about.
That scares me.
There's not a day where I have any thought
that my love for my kids are different.
That my connection
to my kids are different.
-Wow.
-You know, you get to carry one
and have them close to you,
but the other is
'cause you so desperately wanted them
in your family.
Yeah, but, like, I don't want
to take the easy way out.
It's not taking the easy way out.
-Mm-hm.
-[Natalie] It's actually saying,
"I want to raise my kids."
It's actually the hard way out.
It's you saying you're not gonna do it.
-Yeah.
-You say you're gonna let
somebody else do that for you
because you want to be with your kids.
[Kim] This is really reassuring.
So she's giving me a lot of hope.
I mean, it's still a lot
for me to think about,
so I really want to, like,
talk it over with my husband.
I have to see
just what I believe God is, like,
putting in my life
and what's meant to be for me.
-[Kim] Thank you so much.
-My pleasure.
Thank you for sharing your story.
Just a lot to think about.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] So nice out here.
[Kris] It is really pretty.
[Kim] Hi.
Today is the lunch with Everytown,
and I'm really glad that my mom
and my other sisters are going to join.
-Hi. Lucy McBath.
-Hi.
-So nice to meet you.
-Mother of Jordan Davis.
-[Lucy] Hi.
-I'm Kris. How are you?
Hi. How are you?
The more we can get this message out,
the better, and I just…
I want them to see something
that I've been really passionate about.
[Christopher]
So, I just wanted to thank everyone
for coming together to share stories,
to talk about
why this work matters so much.
We also wanted to thank
the Kardashian family for coming here.
Thank you for all the work
that you guys have done.
Um, I know that this has been an issue
that you've been speaking out on.
-[applause]
-[Kim] Where is Kendall?
I thought she was gonna be here.
[dramatic music]
-[applause]
-[Kim] Where is Kendall?
I thought she was gonna be here.
I know Kendall had some reservations
about supporting the cause
due to backlash.
I would say if you're passionate
about something,
get behind it 100 percent.
[bleep] the backlash.
Who cares?
So I hope that she does show up.
I wanted to kick it off to Lucy
to welcome and share her story
and some of the work that she's doing
and, um, that she's proud of.
[Kendall] Sorry I'm late.
[chuckles]
And there's another little Jenner Kendall.
[laughter]
-[Kendall] Oh, I'm at the head.
-[Kris] Yeah, you are.
[Kendall chuckles]
Hi.
Everybody, thank you so much
for coming here.
We're very honored
to have you here with us.
[Lucy] I'm the mother of Jordan Davis.
He's the young man
that was shot and killed in Jacksonville.
One that the country has deemed
"the loud music case."
Moms Demand Action
for Gun Sense in America were
really the ones to give me a platform
to really be able to fight,
not just for Jordan,
but for all Americans that are dying
senselessly around the country.
My mom, Dawn, was the principal
that was killed
in the Sandy Hook school shooting.
[Nza-ari] I lost a close friend
to gun violence
when, um, I was in high school.
Gun violence is just ravaging
our community.
My son and their brother
was murdered last year
outside our family home
by a friend from high school
that he had not seen for four years.
He, um, shot him seven times
and left him to die.
My dad, he was at a work training event
in San Bernardino last December
when, um, his co-workers shot the place,
and he, along with 13 other people, died.
The weekend before the shooting,
we were speaking about workplace violence,
and I had no idea that four days later,
my dad would be gone.
[Richard] Chris was our only child.
He was everything to us,
and the only thing
that's important to me now…
is try to prevent more families
from losing their children like ours did.
Every day that goes by
without us taking our best efforts
to reduce gun violence
in this country means
that more people die for no good reason.
Anything we can do, we're glad, you know,
to be here and just to spread the word.
Hearing all these personal stories
from the people
that actually had to suffer from it
just makes me want to get more involved
in Everytown.
I think it'd be
a little irresponsible of me
to take this platform for granted.
And I think that I need to appreciate it
and use it,
so, I'm just gonna kind of go for it.
[Kim] So handsome.
[Kendall and Kris] Thank you.
They say, "Not one more,"
which is what our goal is,
that not one more person has to die…
-[Khloé] Thank you.
-[Richard] …in this country
for reasons that we can prevent.
[Kim] We should all take a group picture,
and start getting
a good message out there.
Can we all squeeze in? Okay.
-[woman 1] One, two, three.
-[camera shutter clicks]
[Kim] Is everyone okay
if I post this to social media?
-[woman 1] Sure, yeah.
-[woman 2] Please do.
[upbeat music]
[chuckles]
Okay, bye.
Can I just tell you one little thing?
Mm?
It's a little distracting
talking to you with a grill.
I knew you were gonna say that.
I don't know whether
to look at your grill or your boobs.
I'm really so confused today.
It's just the first time
I'm wearing it, so…
Mm.
So there's this woman
that Dr. Huang had me meet with
that had a baby with a surrogate.
I just wanted to know
what her experience was.
Like, is she…
Does she love the baby the same?
Does it feel the same?
Like, is she just as happy? You know?
[Kim] I know what it's like
to have a lot of siblings
and having, like, all of our fun holidays
and what a fun life that is.
[Robert]
There's Kourtney and Robert and Khloé.
There we have all four of you.
How beautiful.
[Kim] I think it's, like,
the best support system to have siblings,
so I would love to have one more at least.
So I've kind of come
to the conclusion in my mind
that, okay, I can't carry another one.
And now I just want
to, like, explore surrogacy.
I just think that that scares me for you.
So there is this woman
that Dr. Huang had me meet with
that had a baby with a surrogate.
I just wanted to know
what her experience was.
Like, is she…
Does she love the baby the same?
Does it feel the same?
Like, is she just as happy? You know?
So I've kind of come to the conclusion
in my mind
that, okay, I can't carry another one.
And now I just want to, like,
explore surrogacy.
I just think that that scares me for you.
Like, what if she gives birth
and then grabs the baby
and makes a run for it?
-Well, I don't think she can.
-Oh.
Also, the best thing is
I could have… a new baby
and have no one know
and live my life for a good year
before we announce it.
But I don't know if it's for me.
-Yeah?
-I really don't know.
[upbeat music]
Wait, do you ever post anything
to your private and public?
-[Kendall] Yeah, always.
-[MJ] I'm gonna grab my phone.
So cute.
[MJ] That's what everyone's doing,
-so I might as well do it too.
-[laughter]
[Khloé] Oh, my goodness!
-[Kourtney] Oh, my gosh.
-[Khloé] Stop.
-[Kourtney] That is so small.
-[Khloé] Wait, I want to see her.
[Kendall muttering]
So cute.
That dog is so cute.
-[smooches]
-[Kris] Hey, guys.
Hi, Kenny.
Do you guys want to chat for a second
-about how this is gonna go?
-Okay.
Um, I'm gonna start out by myself.
I decide to ask my mom
the questions after all,
but I'm nervous.
I don't want to make this a sad
or emotional experience for my mom.
I'm gonna start slow
and hopefully get through the interviews.
Oh, whoa. This is cool.
-[Kris] Okay, Mom, you ready to do this?
-[MJ] Yeah.
-What year were you born?
-'34.
1934 or 1834?
-19. Uh-huh.
-1934.
And your mom was how old when she had you?
Probably 19.
-Wow.
-[Kris] Really?
[Kris] So, like, Kylie's age.
Yeah, but in those days,
you know, that's what happened.
[Kris] How old were you
when you got kissed the first time?
[MJ] 15.
And who did you kiss?
Do you remember his name?
-Yeah, I married him.
-[Kylie] Oh, how amazing.
-Her first kiss she married.
-[Khloé] That's so cute.
But we were only married two months.
-Two months?
-Yeah.
Less than Kimmy.
[laughter]
-What's your biggest fear?
-Biggest fear.
[MJ] I try not to fear.
What's your biggest fear?
[emotional music]
[voice breaking]
I don't wanna say it.
Why did you ask me that?
I can't believe I'm crying.
Just losing someone.
[Khloé] Oh, my god, I'm gonna cry.
This is exactly what I was afraid of.
[MJ] What's your biggest fear?
[emotional music]
[voice breaking]
I don't wanna say it.
Why did you ask me that?
I can't believe I'm crying.
Just losing someone.
[Khloé] Oh, my god, I'm gonna cry.
[emotional music continues]
Just emotional.
[Khloé] What are you upset about?
It makes me realize
that she's not gonna always be here
and she's not gonna live
that much longer and…
Yeah, but most people don't have
the opportunity
to even get, like,
these questions answered,
-do you know?
-Yeah, I know.
So I think it's, like, a blessing.
[Kris]
Losing her… It's gonna be really hard…
[sniffles]
…when she's not here.
But… And I'm glad we're doing this, but…
And it's hard to lose a parent.
But you can't think like that.
-Like, you can't be…
-[Kris] No, you can't…
but when you're talking
about someone's life…
[Khloé] But she's had, like, a great life,
-you know?
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] And…
At least she's had 82 years.
You get to have these memories,
and you get to do this.
Many people… Like my dad,
they didn't have the opp--
-You don't get to talk about anything,
-[Kris] Yeah.
-You know?
-So…
-[Kris sniffles]
[Khloé] We're lucky.
[Kris] I know that Khloé's right.
I'm just an emotional person who,
when I start talking to somebody I love,
especially about memories and…
anything about life,
I just get real mushy.
So, I just need to get
one of my kids to take over,
so I can pull it together.
[Kim] Are we ready?
I'll start with the first question.
If you could only save one grandchild…
-[MJ gasps]
-…who would it be?
-Oh, my god.
-[MJ] Oh, no.
I declare the fifth.
[laughter]
Okay, the fifth grandchild?
[laughing]
How many people have you slept with?
[MJ] Oh, that's a good question.
-Four.
-Four total?
-No, four that I remember.
-[Kendall] Remember, yeah.
[laughing]
[Kourtney] Were you a party animal?
Uh, between husbands,
I went out a lot with the girls
and went to bars
and learned to salsa and all that.
Do you have any favorite sayings
or quotes that you live by?
[MJ] Always try harder.
Do your best.
That's all we can do.
[Kourtney] What is the best thing
about growing older?
[MJ] I figure if you make it this far,
it's all good.
[chuckles]
[Kris] It's pretty awesome seeing my kids
interview MJ about her life.
And about her story and her memories
and just have it on film
as something that will last forever.
[Kourtney] Okay, I think we're good.
[Kendall] Yeah, we'll let Khloé do it now.
[Khloé]
Mom, why don't you come back out with me.
[Kris] I would love to.
[Khloé] Where'd you get your style from?
[MJ] Probably my mom.
And I think, you know, I love the movies,
and I think I got it from that.
'Cause we always say we get it from you,
because you gave it to my mom.
Do you wish you had a boyfriend right now?
Most of the guys that would be my age…
-are gone, number one.
-You don't, you don't have to date
anyone your age.
-Look at Kris Jenner.
-[MJ] Well, yeah.
[laughter]
What is your most treasured possession?
I don't know. I don't like possessions.
I'm not hoarding things for that reason.
I hoard them for sentimental reasons.
[MJ] I do have a garage full of the things
you've sent over to my house…
[laughs]
…like chairs and things you want to hoard.
[Kris] They're all gone.
Well, I save what I want to.
What do you think is
the most precious thing
that you've kept?
Well, now, let me think.
Your baby pictures?
-Aww…
-[MJ chuckles]
-If you could have one superpower…
-That I could fly
so I could go back and forth quicker…
to see you.
[Kris]
What's your idea of perfect happiness?
Well, being around all my kids
and, uh, seeing everyone happy.
[MJ] I'm very happy to be here.
Yeah, I like waking up
in the morning and saying,
-"Thank you, God. One more day."
-[Khloé] Aww.
-[MJ] Yeah. Don't you?
-[Khloé] Mm-hm.
We're lucky.
-Super lucky.
-Yeah.
Blessed.
All right.
-We're out.
-[laughs]
-Give me a hug.
-Okay.
-[Kris] I love you, Mom.
-Love you too.
I'm so happy
-that I did this.
-I love you, MJ.
[Kris] Khloé was right.
It's definitely a lot more sentimental
and personal this way.
[Kris] Thank God we have that on tape.
-Yeah. I told you.
-You know, forever.
I know it's emotional, but…
most people don't get to do
this kind of stuff.
I know. Thank you.
-[Kris] Love you.
-Love you too.
-Oh, thank you.
-[Kris] Thank you.
[Kris]
Sometimes, the young ones are smarter
than the older ones.
[Kim] Next on
Keeping Up with the Kardashians…
-Have you read any baby books?
-No.
Do you know how to take care of a baby?
No.
[chuckles]
-[Rob] Is that okay, little girl?
-Poor guy just gave his kid pinkeye.
Kim, are you not coming to my meeting?
[Kim on phone] What meeting?
[Khloé] You always talk [bleep] about Mom.
"Oh, she's a horrible manager."
You're taking over for Mom
when you're acting just like Mom.
[Alexa] Your mom, I think,
was just in an accident.
[siren wailing]
[tense music]