[upbeat music]
[music stops]
[Kourtney] Hey, Kyles.
Oh, Kylie, you could be in my Snap.
And you're gonna say, "Yeah,
I saw her go in the guest room."
[Kendall] She's gonna find us
in, like, bed together.
[chuckles]
[Kourtney] One, two, three.
Hey, Kyles, have you seen Kenny?
Hey, Snap.
I literally just saw her go over there.
[Kourtney] Maybe she went this way.
[playful music]
Wait, who is she in here with?
What the…
What? Okay, wait, hold on.
-[laughs]
-[Kendall] Did it work?
[Kourtney in video]
Wait, who is she in here with?
-What the…
-[Kendall] It's so weird.
[Scott] So what's taking you guys so long?
[Kourtney] What the…
[laughter]
-I'm still the one.
-Yeah.
-That's exactly what you do.
-[Kourtney] Okay, now what?
-I don't know.
-Now, do I say…
-[Kendall] We could get like--
-Kylie!
[Kendall] Let's get, like,
a video of Scott,
like, just walking out of the house,
and you're like,
"Yeah, that's right, you."
-And you go…
-[Kourtney] That's right!
-[Scott] Okay, I'm leaving.
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Scott] So, this is my back.
-[Kourtney] Just keep walking straight.
You are so sick.
You're so inappropriate.
Like, what is wrong with you?
Everybody knows I'm inappropriate.
-[Kendall] Oh, it's so good.
-[laughter]
-[Kourtney] You're so…
-Okay.
[Scott] I love you, guys.
-Bye, love you!
-[Kendall laughs]
[electronic music]
[upbeat music]
-[Malika] Hi, Khloé.
-Hi.
I'm so afraid to step on your floor.
I feel like I'll dirty everything.
[Khloé] I feel like it's already dirty.
-[line ringing]
-[doctor] Hello?
Hi, it's Khloé Kardashian. How are you?
[doctor] I'm well, how are you?
I'm good. So, Lamar's coming in
to see you at, um, five today.
And he was just in a coma a few months ago
and he's on a ton of medications
for that stuff,
but they vary every week,
so it was hard for me
to fill out that form.
[doctor] I'll give him
the best care possible.
And we'll reach out to you after.
to gonna give you a heads-up.
Okay, thank you so much. Bye.
Sorry.
Don't apologize. You're so kind.
Got his nails done this morning.
He's in a massage right now.
He's gonna go to the eye doctor at five,
and then a dermatologist
is making a house call
to his house
'cause his skin is breaking out.
Bam.
I don't know what he would do without you.
He doesn't know.
Lamar has definitely come a long way
since his whole hospital situation.
I mean, I have put
a lot of my life on hold
to try to help Lamar
and get him on a great track.
But, you know, internally
there's still so much that
Lamar has to fix about himself.
[pensive music]
I thought you were calling
a doctor for yourself.
For something, like,
oh, God, forgot my gynecologist
wants to make an appointment with me,
and then it's like
9,000 things about yellow.
I just want him to focus
on positive things,
-so I don't care.
-Yeah.
[Khloé] Um, did you have fun last night?
[Malika] I had the best time in the world.
I'm so mad you didn't come
with us, though.
[Khloé] Well, I was getting a tan.
I know. That's very important.
I wanted to know, so Kendall
is doing a fashion show in Cuba.
I don't know how much time
she can spend with us,
but let's go out there to Cuba.
-Us, as in you and me?
-[Khloé] Yeah, you and I,
and we'll go and, like,
chill with Kendall,
like, whatever we can do.
So I think it's gonna be super cool
since it's still, like, new
that we're allowed to go there.
-Everything is still, like, 1950s.
-[Malika] Yeah.
Like, the style of everything,
'cause all I hear
is that people are buying
property over there to like--
Oh, God, am I gonna have
to stop you from buying a house?
No, I don't want to buy a house.
I mean, all these developers
are buying hotels and this to make,
like, 'cause it's gonna be
a huge tourist attraction.
-It will be really fun.
-I would… I, honestly,
it's on my bucket list,
so it would make me
really, really happy.
Kim and Kourt are coming, too,
but I'm happy you're down to go.
-Oh, I'm down.
-[Khloé] You're always my wingman.
You know what, babe?
-I'm your lifer.
-Yeah.
That's what that is.
I'm super excited about this trip.
I've always wanted
the opportunity to go to Cuba.
And I need to start pushing
myself to do things
that are more for me,
instead of for everybody else.
-So, we're going to Cuba.
-[Malika] Cuba!
-Yeah!
-[Khloé] It's gonna be exciting.
[Malika] I'm excited.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Like, you guys take
everything from me
and that's, like, a known fact,
but you have the balls, though,
to take something
that's so identifiable to me
and my personality and my home, right?
And this started by me saying to her,
"Oh, my god, you didn't give Mom
that Marilyn Monroe painting
that's in her kitchen?"
"Oh, I thought you gave it to her."
"She has the same exact one."
You have… Is that the exact same print?
-Are you [bleep] out of your--
-[Kris] I don't want…
I don't even want it
if it's the same print.
Mom, I'm obsessed with Marilyn.
And I… it's, like, my thing.
I have the Larry Schiller one…
[Kim] Like, I looked at the
Larry Schiller ones years ago,
but I knew that was
Khloé's thing. I love Marilyn.
[Khloé] Mom?
[Kris] Oh, sorry.
Okay, well, uh, this Cuba trip,
Kim, Kourt and the kids,
and Malika, and Kanye,
and all of them were all--
We decided we all want to go.
We think it's gonna be so much fun.
Like, if they're doing
this Chanel fashion show
and everything there, like,
it's got to be safe and--
Kendall's supposed to walk in Chanel.
-[Kim] I know.
-But I will tell you guys
-[Khloé mutters]
-…that there's no Internet…
If we're with our whole family,
who needs to call anyone?
Uh… me.
Why wouldn't you come?
I'm not going to Cuba. I… I can't.
If there's no communication…
I have work to do.
[Kris] The girls wanting to go to Cuba
is a little stressful for me.
I feel very anxious about not being able
to communicate with them
while they're gone.
You don't communicate
either way. Can't reach you…
[laughs mockingly]
[Kris] You guys can go down
to Cuba, have fun.
It's, like, going to be legendary.
It's gonna be so much fun.
And I heard the sangria is to die for.
I think the only thing
I'm gonna really enjoy
about you guys being in Cuba,
I can have some peace and quiet.
All right, guys, well, I'll enjoy my time,
and you guys let me know
when you get back,
because you certainly
can't send me an email
when you land.
Hasta luego.
[Kim and Khloé laugh]
[upbeat music]
[plane engine buzzing]
[Khloé] Oh, my god. This way!
KoKo, I got a jellyfish stung.
What? You got stung by a jellyfish?
-[Mason] Uh-huh.
-Where?
-[Mason] Right here.
-[Malika] No way.
I did, too, before.
-Where's my huggie?
-[Malika] So, what did you do?
[Kourtney] We put vinegar on it.
[Khloé] Masey, guess what?
One time, I got stung
by a jellyfish two times.
-Aw, Mase.
-Say KoKo.
[Reign babbles]
KoKo! Hi, Reigny.
[Kourtney] It sucks that Kendall
couldn't make the trip.
The whole reason
we were even going to Cuba
was because Kendall was walking
in the Chanel show there,
but because of last-minute changes,
Kendall has dropped out,
so since we all have our travel plans,
we're all still going, and I'm so excited.
-Is Kim coming?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-Oh…
-[Kourtney] Not here, though.
-She's meeting us there.
-[Khloé] Oh, it's just us?
So we're gonna party on this plane?
What are you talking about?
[Kourtney] And Kim and Kanye
are in New York,
so they are going to meet us in Cuba.
[rumbling]
Khloé, did you guys spray
yourself with DEET?
Yeah, I brought us, like,
refills enough for four days.
I don't mess with, like, real bug spray,
but I'm not taking a chance.
We, like, doused ourselves,
'cause I don't want to get the Zika.
-[Malika] Yeah.
-[Penelope] Oh no.
[Kourtney] That is Cuba.
Never been, but we're going
as a family together,
this is so exciting.
Are you excited for Cuba? Are you?
-Yeah.
-What are you--
We're on a world tour.
[Khloé] So Scott couldn't get into Cuba?
He wanted to come,
but he told me the night before.
And he was like,
"I'm getting a jet. Let's go."
Is he coming?
I don't think that
he could get his traveling.
It's like really hard,
I guess, to get a visa.
Scott decided at the last minute
that he really wanted to come to Cuba,
but you need, like, visas
and all this paperwork
to be filled out that takes,
like, weeks and weeks,
so he wasn't able to make it.
Were you fine with him coming?
Yep.
I said, "Come on down to Cuba town."
[Khloé] Yeah!
-We're landing already?
-[Penelope] Already?
[Khloé] Five more minutes, we're landing!
I am annoyed, like,
that I don't have contact
to anybody that's not with us.
Like, the fact that I can't use
my phone does disturb me.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-It bothers me
and that's my prerogative,
like, Kim has her husband
and her babies with her,
you have all your babies with you,
and then it's just me and Malika.
Like, we want to be able
to talk to our friends
or whatever.
-And I want to be--
-[Kourtney] Guess what?
-No, but you get…
-Friends schmrends.
[Khloé] That's why you guys
aren't tripping out
about your cell phones.
You guys are with all your family.
[Kourtney] Right.
It's definitely scary
to go to another country
and then not have any access to back home.
Lamar knows that it's not easy to reach me
because our cell phones
don't work in Cuba.
And there's, like, one hotel
in all of Cuba that has Wi-Fi.
That's just a nerve-racking thought.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Hi.
[Malika] Very excited.
-Malika, how pretty is it here?
-It's amazing.
We got the car that I wanted.
Yes.
Mase, look at this. Hi.
[woman] Hi.
I'm just so excited.
I love getting out of town,
I love seeing new places.
Cuba is now open to Americans.
Like, I'm just so excited,
I feel like, to witness
such a piece of history.
And we got your seats in here, guys.
And be able to bring our kids
and, like, all go together
and make memories.
[Khloé] Oh, I've already been bitten
and I have Zikia or whatever
the [bleep] it is.
Where did you put the DEET,
Khlo? I can spray you.
-You have it, in your purse.
-You just need to be overloaded.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-Nice to meet you.
-My name is Mandy.
-Hello.
My nickname Mandy
'cause last name Armando.
Armando.
[car engine starts]
[Khloé] I love this car.
1957 Chevy. First time here?
-[Malika] Really? Sure.
-Yes.
[Armando] Havana is beautiful.
[Khloé] Oh, I'm so excited.
[upbeat music]
-[Khloé] Oh, my goodness.
-[Malika] Oh, my God!
Look at the goats.
So the goats are, like,
people's dogs, almost.
[Khloé] Yeah, they're one with nature.
All the colors are so pretty,
on all the buildings.
Yes, in Cuba the people like the colors.
I love it.
Hello.
-This is the neighborhood.
-People are so nice.
-I love it.
-[Malika] You meet people
in United States and they look
at you like you're crazy.
-This is live. Cuban real life.
-Yes, that's what I like, is real life.
[Khloé] I love so many things about Cuba.
I love that there's history and culture.
People are outside,
and they're walking the streets
and everyone is, like,
enjoying other people.
Hello!
[bus horn honks]
We're friends with everyone.
[Khloé] Just seeing the pride
on everyone's faces,
it's refreshing to see that.
[Malika] We should set a goal.
To walk away from this trip
saying it's one of the most
amazing trips we've ever had.
Yeah, so far, so good.
-We're in Cuba.
-[Malika] So far, so good.
-[Malika] What's this over here?
-[Armando] This is a plantation
-of bananas.
-Really?
-Mangos, banana, avocado…
-Yum.
All the things we like.
We're such tourists. [laughs]
They're so cool.
[upbeat music]
[Malika] Let's party.
-[Khloé] Hola.
-[Malika] Thank you.
We'll see you tomorrow, Armando.
-Bye, have a good night.
-[Khloé] Thank you.
-Say bye.
-Bye.
[upbeat music]
[Kanye mutters]
[indistinct chattering]
-Do you see a pink car?
-[North] Yep.
Who is this?
[Kim] We are coming from New York.
We're a few hours behind everyone else.
I am so excited to be here in Cuba.
Kanye's super excited.
He's never been, so it's fun
to take him someplace
that he hasn't been to.
And it's also fun
that we're bringing both kids.
-[thunder rumbles]
-[North gasps] A lightning.
[Kim] A lightning.
[Kanye] Isn't this like a dream come true
to go to Cuba with your husband and kids?
Yeah. It's pretty cool.
[North] Daddy, 'scuse me.
[Kanye] What are you asking me, North?
[North] Did you see the lightning?
[Kanye] I know.
Isn't the lightning so crazy?
Crazy, crazy lightning.
Let's go like this. Whoo!
[North whoops]
No, wait till the lightning…
[North whooping]
-No, we gotta see lightning.
-No, wait.
-Wait for the lightning.
-[North whoops quietly]
-[thunder rumbles]
-[Kim and Kanye gasp, whoop]
-[North] Whoo!
-See? She's like, "What?"
[North whoops]
-What?
-[North] Whoo!
-[thunder rumbles]
-[all whooping]
[Kim] When we first get to Cuba,
it really is exactly how I imagined it.
Like, nothing's really changed in decades
and it's so amazing,
and I'm so glad we came at this time.
-[Khloé] It's so beautiful.
-Yeah.
[Khloé] Come here, Mase Dumbledore.
[chanting] Dumbledore! Dumbledore!
-Spotless door.
-Mason is a Dumbledore!
Mase, why did you, like,
make a peef on your juje?
They made my butt liberated.
[Khloé laughs]
Kourt, what are we doing?
We are walking the streets of Cuba
with my friend, mi amiga.
-Berta.
-[Khloé] Hi, Berta.
Hi. And is your name?
Kourtney.
-Nice to meet you.
I love to just be free,
especially in other countries and cities,
and just, like, explore.
That was their house. Did you see
inside the window of their house?
No, Kourt.
This is life. This is life, Khloé.
This is life in Cuba.
It's so fun to be able
to just walk the streets
and talk to local people
and see how other people live.
And it feels like we're living life.
[Malika] Dorothy, you're not
in Canada anymore.
-[Khloé] Canada?
-Kansas.
[laughter]
[Malika] This is fun, see?
[indistinct chatter]
[Kim] How cool.
[Malika] Hi.
What?
[Kanye] Yo, can you come here?
I think when you film,
you should film it with the camera in it.
You know what I mean, like…
Get the full view.
-This is Kourtney, Mason…
-How are you?
-Malika.
-[Malika] Hi.
-[Kourtney] He films everything.
-[Khloé] I was just like,
"Who is filming us with that,
like, VHS camera?"
-[Kim] He just likes to film.
-Like what is happening?
Well, he films… he films me.
Kanye always has his eye out
for a young generation
of, like, really creative people.
And Kanye's been working
with this young filmmaker
who is videoing everything
that Kanye's been doing.
So he's here in Cuba
just to capture our trip.
[Khloé] Kourt, what are you drinking?
I might have sangria.
It's, like, my favorite.
[Khloé] I'm sure it has to be
good here, right?
You guys, the pres who dropped the mic,
this is where he came
and he sat here, Obam.
-At this table?
-Obama sat at this table.
And when Michelle needed
to use the restroom,
they put a toilet seat over it,
because there's nothing to sit on,
you just gotta cop a squat
and pray for the best.
You guys, copping a squat is my thing.
-[Khloé] I know.
-[Kourtney] They don't know.
[Khloé] Well, they're going to…
Are all sangrias like this?
-What a fun beverage.
-[Malika] How is it, Kim?
-Good.
-So she called me.
-[Malika] Mm-hm.
-[Khloé] And was like,
"We need to talk to you about Lamar."
And I was like, "Okay."
And she was like, "I am really sorry,
I don't know what to say.
Lamar just asked for cash."
So she's giving it… She has
to get it to him in the morning.
-Do you guys want some?
-No, thank you.
[Khloé] I am his, like, advisor,
if he's… something's wrong.
-But, like, technically…
-I just feel so bad.
…he's of sound…
-You feel so bad for what?
-Like… you.
Khloé, you can't do…
You've done everything you can do.
You can't control him.
You want to try and be the best,
but honey,
if he wants to run himself
back into the gutter,
he's gonna do just that.
But who's with him that's even
gonna, like, let him…
[Malika] He may ditch everyone.
We don't know exactly what he's thinking.
It doesn't mean
that someone's gonna let him.
Or is he just gonna run away
while we're here?
[tense music]
I already know why he was, like,
waiting for me to leave town,
waiting for me.
And he knows my phone doesn't work.
-Yeah.
-He doesn't know
that I got Wi-Fi in the room.
What a [bleep]. He was waiting for this.
This is what he used to do
when you would leave town?
Every time I'd leave town,
when we were married,
did this happen.
I just didn't think he would
still do the same thing.
[Kourtney] Can you pass the olives, Kim?
[Khloé chuckles]
-Do you like Kourtney's outfit?
-[Kanye] Yeah.
Is this like the dress you wore
to your first Met appearance?
Yes, this print right here? Yeah.
Your appearance.
-[Kanye] Your first appearance.
-Appearance.
-Yes, please.
-[indistinct muttering]
How did you feel about your blue eyes?
-How did I feel about them?
-He can hardly see.
Oh, you could?
No, they were…
they were thick plastic things.
I don't understand that question.
No, no, let me just tell you,
the question is,
"How did you feel about your blue eyes?"
That's like if Kim had on
a blonde wig and I said,
"How did you feel about your blonde hair?"
[Khloé] That's
a passive-aggressive question.
It didn't sound like you liked them.
No, it's like, did you like the look?
[Kanye] How do you feel about your choker
that you're wearing?
[laughing]
[Malika] Do you know
what I love about you?
What?
There are often moments
that I just want to say
exactly what I'm thinking and I don't.
[chuckles]
[Khloé] Yeah.
You guys, Kanye and I
got into a fight in Iceland.
[Khloé] What about?
About this whole topic.
-[Khloé] Thank you.
-[waiter] You're welcome.
So everybody got the same thing?
Basically.
But back to…
Okay, I'll answer the question.
I felt very good about my contacts.
-[Khloé chuckles]
-I felt very…
No, I could tell Kim was into it.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
So, let's do this, gang. Let's earmark.
So, Claire, get some stickys, honey,
take all the products.
-[Claire] Okay.
-[Kris] We'd like to give
all of the Kardashian
beauty stuff that we have
to the, um, underprivileged women…
-[Claire] Mm-hm.
-…downtown for Mother's Day.
Let's look and compete for these ladies.
If there's product here…
Ooh, boy.
This is what happens
when they went to Cuba?
-[Claire] It's outrageous.
-[Kris] Oy, boy.
Matt, where's Khloé's assistant?
-[Matt] I can track her down.
-Yeah.
So maybe she could come get her stuff.
Okay, I think we're good.
[upbeat music]
I haven't been here in so long,
it feels good.
I was able to email Kim, like, twice.
I haven't talked to them
since they've been in Cuba.
They're not posting anything.
So I was just hoping that they were okay.
Even though I already knew
the communication would be bad,
it's like crickets over there.
I can't believe that they're out there
having this great time
and probably not giving me
a second thought.
And I'm sitting on pins and needles,
waiting to hear anything.
I didn't realize
how much I miss them, you know?
When you don't know
that they're right there to call
or just, you know, pop a text.
The texting is what's crazy.
I didn't realize how much I relied on that
for communication.
[upbeat music]
What up, bro?
Look at the pink and purple car, Bubs.
[Kourtney] Do they have seats
in these or no?
We could all ride here.
[Kourtney] Okay.
I almost didn't come to Cuba because,
like, all of the old-fashioned cars,
you can't put car seats in them
because there's no seat belts at all,
so there's nothing to strap
the seats into.
But, in Cuba, like, nobody's in a rush,
and it just seems like everybody
is much safer, like, with the driving.
Everyone's just taking their time
in getting places safely.
Northy, I'm videotaping.
Say hello.
Hi.
This gives me life, guys.
[Kanye] Are you having so much fun?
Mm-hm.
[Kanye] Do you like
your little diamonds in your ears?
[siren blaring]
[Kanye] Oh, I get it.
-[Kim] What?
-[Kanye] I just asked her,
"Do you like your diamonds in your ears?"
[Kourtney] Yeah?
[Kanye] So now I understand the question.
I just asked, "Do you like your diamonds?"
[Kourtney] What did she say?
[Kanye] She didn't…
She didn't respond to me.
[Kourtney] Did she say,
"Dad, are you trying to say
-you don't like my diamonds?"
-[Kanye] No. But now I understand.
This is the way you talk to children.
And 'cause you communicate
-with children the most--
-No, I swear to God…
I swear to God, last night,
I was laying in bed.
In the middle of the night,
I woke up and I was thinking,
-"That's how I talk to kids."
-[Kanye] Yeah.
Look at the lion, Mase.
The lion statue.
Why is the lion important?
[Armando speaking Spanish]
[Armando] The symbol is power.
It symbolizes power.
-The lion.
-'Cause lions are strong,
-right?
-Yes, strong.
Hi.
You say hi to, like, everyone.
Yeah, we're supposed to say hi
to everyone.
'Cause we're in a new place,
so we got to make friends.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Out we go.
We're at the museum.
-[North] What is this?
-[Kanye] Ooh!
It's a museum, Northy.
-What's up, brother?
-[man] What's up?
[Kanye] What's up?
[woman speaking Spanish]
[man speaking Spanish]
Everything is direct
and made by real artists.
They make everything here. They…
-[Robert] Please.
-Come on, guys, let's walk.
[child crying]
When we all are traveling
to different countries,
we love to check out art.
And so we are at Fábrica de Arte Cubano,
which is a huge studio set up
by one of the biggest artists in Havana.
And this place was built
to set up an artist community.
[North] Feet!
-Daddy, look at his feet.
-[Kanye chuckles]
-[Kim] Yeah.
-Crazy feet.
[North] What are the nails colored?
The nails are kind of a beige color,
-like a shark tooth.
-Beige?
[North] Looks like green.
[Kanye] It… It is like a green too.
I was gonna say green also.
You're so good with color.
-Are you gonna be an artist?
-[North] No.
What are you gonna be when you're big?
[North] Um, a bunny.
-A bunny?
-That's much better.
-[North] I love bunnies.
-[Kanye chuckles]
-I love bunnies so much.
-[North] No, I love them.
[Kanye] No, I love bunnies.
[X-Alfonso speaking Spanish]
Now, we're coming from the shop area.
This is made with engine gaskets.
Rubber gaskets.
[Kourtney] Look, P, clothes.
Let's walk around over here.
[Robert] All is handmade, of course.
[X-Alfonso] This is a…
[Robert] Concert and music hall.
[upbeat music]
[museum guide]
This is the fine art gallery.
His whole studio with, like, tons of art,
it's dedicated to music, and film,
and all these different artistic outlets.
It's really amazing to see
the artists use what they have
accessible to them on the island.
[Khloé] Let's hide you
so no one could see you.
Okay?
-It was very interesting.
-You are always welcome.
Muchas gracias.
[Kanye] Thank you so much.
[Khloé] Bye, thank you.
[upbeat Cuban music]
[Kourtney] How cool. Look at the old cars,
like, driving on the freeway
here. It's like Dick Tracy.
[Kanye] It's so legendary.
Look at that castle over there, Mase.
[Kim] Everything's so cool, right?
[Kanye] And I really feel
like I'm in a movie, bro.
And I like these weird colors.
I love, like, really, like,
-weird colors like this. Yeah.
-[Kim] It's a cool blue, yeah.
It's, like, really cool
to be out here in Cuba
where all of the colors and everything
are really, like, so beautiful.
Like, that's dope.
That building's pretty dope.
The whole city is very easy vibe,
anyway, like all those weird tones.
It feels like we're in a dream.
I need to shoot a music video out here.
[Kourtney] Look at that cool tunnel…
with the blue star.
Like, we need to take photos
at those stands.
And then we can go through the tunnel
-like this.
-[Kanye whooping]
That's what… I do that
when I'm in a convertible.
[whoops]
[electronic music]
[Khloé] Yay, we're going on an adventure.
Look at all these cars, guys.
[car horns honking]
-All the colors are so pretty.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
[Kim] Look at… We're gonna pass the tunnel
and we can scream the whole time.
[Khloé] One, two, three.
[all screaming]
[whooping]
We did it.
[Kourtney] P, you want to try this?
-[Khloé] Go ahead.
-[Kourtney] Hold this. Hold it.
-[ringing]
-[all exclaim]
[Kourtney] Okay, Northy's turn.
-[ringing]
-[Kanye whoops]
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Kim laughs]
You're like your daddy.
You got to overdo it.
[Grethel] So these are, uh,
some of the Havana Club products.
We are at Havana Club
and I'm so excited to see
a rum distillery
because Cuba makes the best rum,
and just to smoke cigars, drink some rum,
be like really Cuban for the day.
[Grethel] From this one on
is part of our iconic collection.
The one that you're going to try
is our very, very special product here,
the extra-aged rum Máximo.
It's a work of our grand rum master
José Pablo Navarro.
He has been working
for the brand for 42 years.
-Pablo?
-José Pablo Navarro.
José Pablo.
-What's his name?
-Pablo, Pablo, Pablo.
-Pablo. One more Pablo.
-[Kourtney giggles]
[Grethel] Okay, follow me.
[Kim] Even though
I'm not that big of a drinker,
I'm enjoying all the memories
that we're gonna have
and it's really cool just to, like,
soak up what the culture is here.
Rum doesn't age in the bottle.
It ages only…
-[Khloé] In a barrel.
-…in the, uh… in the barrel.
So, once it's in a bottle,
it can't age anymore?
-[Grethel] No, not in the case of rum.
-Interesting.
[Grethel] So, uh,
the tasting we do with, uh, cigars
and rum is called sobremesa.
Sobremesa is something you do,
generally, after you eat dinner.
Okay.
[Grethel] It's that you chill
at the table. You share with your friends,
you share a drink, a cigar, dessert…
Americans don't do that enough.
Americans are rushing
and always wanting
to go to the next place.
I like it.
I like this Cub… this Cuban moment.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] I think
that last one's the best.
-Come on over, "ropa."
-Check what I missed, right?
-Is that it?
-[Khloé] I like that one.
[Kanye] I'm actually super into this
because I like fire and I like alcohol.
-Right up your alley today.
-[Kanye] I really like cigars.
[Malika] Hey, Kimmy, I see you.
[coughs]
[Grethel] Oh, oh, one thing.
-Don't inhale the air, okay?
-Yeah, she told me,
after I did ten times.
-What is the point of this then?
-[laughter]
-[Kim] Does anyone want mine?
-Khloé does.
[Khloé] Not really.
[Kourtney] Did you get a good video?
[dramatic music]
I'm trying to make an effort
to be in the moment,
but being away from the hotel
and being unreachable
is just not, like, a settling feeling.
[upbeat music]
[Malika] Aren't the buildings pretty?
-[Penelope] Right now?
-[Malika] Yeah.
Okay, on the left now,
is the cemetery of Havana.
It's the biggest cemetery
in Latin America.
The name is Necropolis of Columbus.
That's crazy.
[Malika] That's a beautiful
church, Armando.
This is the San Francisco de Paula Church.
-Oh, it's so pretty.
-This church…
This church used for maternity hospital
in 17th century.
Wow.
[Armando] It's beautiful building.
[Khloé] Beautiful building.
I can probably ride through this town
all day long, just, like, looking.
[Khloé] Yeah, it's so cute.
Don't you feel like if you
had someone with you in LA
and you had to drive them around,
wouldn't you just say,
"This is the Valley"?
Right.
[upbeat music]
What if I just, like,
dipped myself in the water?
Mm-hm. That would be perfect.
That it would be,
like, super wet and cool.
[photographer] Amazing. Stay right there.
[upbeat music]
[camera shutter clicking]
I am doing a photoshoot
for one of my new lip kit colors,
and it's just so exciting
to be a part of something
that I have always wanted
since I was little.
[female staff] He always tried to escape.
[Kris] Hey, Kylie.
[camera shutter clicking]
[Kris] Oh, that looks great.
You look so cute and pretty.
Everyone's been in Cuba now for a few days
and I have a little more
free time on my hands.
Now I can focus on Kylie a little bit.
[Kris] Have you heard from your sisters?
[camera shutter clicks]
[Kylie] No.
[camera shutter clicking]
I haven't heard from anybody
in, like, two days.
[tense music]
[camera shutter clicking]
M'kay.
I mean, you want to have
a conversation? What's up?
[Kris] I'm just not used
to not hearing from anybody.
[Kylie] My mom shows up.
I didn't invite her.
All my sisters are in Cuba,
and she doesn't know
what to do with herself,
so she's harassing me.
It feels really awkward not being able
to talk to anybody or check in.
[Kylie] Mom, you're acting a little crazy.
M'kay.
[chill music]
[Khloé] Yay, Mase! We're here.
-We are the judges.
-Mase, we're here.
That's how… Ain't that how
you enter in convertibles?
-[Kim] Yup.
-Look at the water, Mase.
Cannon.
[Kourtney] Look at the cannons.
Hi.
What's in your hand, my bubs?
[whoops] What is that?
[Kanye] Is that, like, a magic stick?
-♪ You've got the magic… ♪
-Babe, don't say that.
-[Kanye] What is it?
-I'm saying that…
-Oh, sorry.
-You know what that is?
What is a magic stick?
-[bleep].
-Oh, sorry.
Oh, come on, Bubs. Do you see the water?
[Kourtney] They all wanted
to sit next to KoKo.
-It's good to be an aunt.
-[Khloé] You know what?
Don't have kids, don't need them.
Khlo, Kanye and I
had a discovery in the car.
-What?
-[Kourtney] He said that he realized…
'cause he said to North,
-"Hey, North, do you like your diamonds?"
-[Reign] KoKo.
And then he said, "The way that I talk
is how I talk to a kid."
And I said, "I swear I woke up
in the middle of the night
and thought that to myself."
And I said to Kanye, 'cause he's like,
"I would never say anything intentionally
to hurt your feelings."
I think you two
are just not vibing right now.
No, no, we are. We are.
[Kanye] So what's worse?
Uh, intentionally trying to hurt me
or talking to me like a child? [chuckles]
That's the way I like to be communicated
with anyway, mostly.
-Yeah. I keep it simple.
-[Kanye] Yeah.
I get it. [chuckles]
[Kim] You know they have, like,
potato rations here,
so, like, you can only get
a certain amount,
-'cause there's not a lot.
-[Khloé] Thank you.
[Kanye chuckles]
[Kourtney] Khloé went out
of town and Lamar kept asking, like,
"When are you leaving?
When are you leaving?"
And the day she left, he asked for cash.
For what?
[Kourtney] What do you think?
[Khloé] What?
[Kourtney] Just telling him about Lamar.
But you're so upset, but…
But doesn't he want to start
playing ball again?
[Khloé] He never wanted
to stop playing ball,
but you just can't live
that lifestyle and do that.
And I tell him, without discouraging him,
I'm like, you know, like…
Let's, like, focus on coaching,
like, Kobe just retired.
But his motor skills
are not what they used to be.
[Kanye] Yeah.
He was such a great athlete
and didn't even try.
Like, that's him not trying.
When he got off the Clippers
is when he started doing that.
And he didn't finish his therapy
to get better.
And that was his choice.
He told me and Malika when we were there.
I was like,
"Why are you sleeping all day?"
And, like, Malika was there,
like, "You got to get up,
it's a beautiful day. Like,
go on a walk or something."
And he was like, "I just have
thoughts now, at night."
[dramatic music]
And I was like,
"Well, what do you think about?
Like, that's why I said
you need to go to a counselor,
'cause I don't know how to help that.
I don't have those thoughts
and I want you to get better."
[Kim] It's really hard
to see Khloé so stressed out.
And I wish she wouldn't put
that much weight
of this whole situation on her shoulders,
but I think that's just who she is.
I wish she would just enjoy herself…
and wouldn't put herself through that.
[somber music]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Do you like the car, Mase?
-[Mason] Yeah.
-So awesome, right?
[Mason] Mm-hm.
Hola! Estas muy bonita.
[Khloé] Kourtney went to school,
um, and she's a Spanish minor.
-School? Spanish? Yeah.
-Yeah.
Sí.
Kourtney, do you remember
your Spanish, sí?
Habla? Hablo?
Is it hablo?
-[Mason] Hablo.
-Hablo, or habla, say, too.
[speaking Spanish]
-I don't know what that means.
-Is it?
Sí.
[Kourtney] I love Cuba.
The architecture is incredible.
The buildings, the colors,
like, there's so much life here.
Maybe tomorrow, guys,
we should only speak in Spanish.
Very interesting.
-[Malika laughs]
-Say muy interesante.
[murmurs]
-Comó estás?
-[Kourtney chuckles]
Muy bien. Hey.
-[in English] Speaking Spanish.
-[Kourtney chuckles]
[Armando] Oh, good.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Kylie?
[Kylie] Hey.
Do you want me to teach you
how to make my famous pasta primavera?
Yeah.
[Kris] Oh. Well…
[smooches]
I just know you've been wanting
to hang out with me.
-You do?
-Mm-hm.
Okay, so I'll tell you
what we're going to do.
I can tell that my mom needs
a little extra attention right now.
I feel like my mom complains a lot
that she has too many children,
but I think she can't function without us.
Okay, so let me get in here
and get my pan.
Are you not…
are you not tying this for me?
Oh. You're so needy today.
I love when you're needy.
-Really?
-Yeah.
'Cause it means you still
want to hang out with me
and you still need me.
You're not all grown up, yet.
So this gets sautéed, with the garlic,
for about five minutes.
And you put the carrots in first,
because they're the most dense,
and they're hard.
-[Kylie] Yeah.
-You know?
Do you know why you cut bread with this?
-No. Oh, yeah.
-'Cause it's got
a "seregated" edge.
It's more like a bread knife.
-Or would you like…
-[Corey laughs]
Segregated.
-It's not segregated.
-Oh.
[both laugh]
-"Seregated."
-[Kylie] Mom.
-Yeah?
-It's "serrated."
-Serrated. Serrated.
-[chuckles]
-You're so funny.
I think you're kind of right.
Look at what I'm doing.
You open up each piece of bread…
[Corey] I really love y'all two together,
'cause the way you look at her,
I can already tell
you really listen to your mother,
-which is great.
-She does.
I… I really feel like you're the only one
that listens to me.
She really, like, honors
what you have to say,
and I like that.
I know you've been missing
everyone in Cuba,
so I wanted to spend time with you.
-Make me feel better?
-[Kylie] Pasta's ready.
I love spending time with you,
especially when we can do
something we both like.
Kylie is the cutest,
most sensitive child in the world.
And I think she can feel
that I'm missing the other kids so much,
that she wants to come over
and keep me company,
and that means everything.
I love a good colander,
'cause you can get a facial.
-Look. Facial, facial.
-I do the same thing.
-Honestly.
-Are we the same person?
I've never seen anyone else do that.
I think we are.
Now grate it all over.
-Doesn't that look pretty?
-[Kylie] Mm-hm.
[upbeat techno music]
[Kourtney] So pretty.
[Kourtney] I read Old Man and the Sea
in high school.
Thank you.
[driver mutters]
Kim and I are going to see
Ernest Hemingway's house.
We're excited, just because we studied
and read Ernest Hemingway,
and it's cool to see how people live.
Welcome to our museum. My name is Isbel.
I'm going to be your guide.
And that's the house of Hemingway.
In 1928, it was the first time
Hemingway visit Cuba.
Only 48 hours, but was enough.
He was in love.
When Hemingway received a special guest,
he used to ring the bell to say "welcome."
[bell rings]
Today, for you.
[Kourtney] Are those
his magazines and books?
[Isbel] Yes. Everything is authentic.
Furniture, paintings, animals on the wall.
He was a hunter.
As you can notice,
it's not luxury in the house.
Everything is simple,
but nice and practical.
That was Hemingway's style.
You want to walk around
and see the rest of the rooms?
-[Kourtney] Sure.
-[Isbel] His private bathroom,
only for Hemingway.
One of the most interesting
things here is on the wall.
That's Hemingway's handwriting.
You see the scale there?
He'd check his weight almost every day
-and take notes on the wall.
-[Kim] It's like me.
-[Isbel] You do the same?
-[Kim] Yeah, I do.
That's cool.
[Kim] This house is so cool.
It's such a part of Cuban history
that I wish Khloé could see this.
I just want her to, like,
live life and enjoy herself,
and not worry about it all.
Which just breaks my heart,
'cause it's like the same cycle
all over again.
It just really sucks.
-[Isbel] First time in Cuba?
-[Kourtney] Mm-hm.
-[Isbel] Not the last, I hope.
-[Kourtney] No, we love it.
It's so beautiful.
All right, muchas gracias.
-[chuckles]
-[Isbel] You're welcome.
[Kourtney] Next on Keeping Up
with the Kardashians…
Kanye is making her an entire…
You can't salsa dance without dresses.
[Kourtney] Oh, yeah.
Cuba looks so cool.
I got a serious case of FOMO for Cuba.
-[horn honks]
-Ladies!
-Ay, caramba!
-[Kris and Kylie chuckling]
It's about a business decision.
My mom's job is to get us deals,
but everything
has to be carefully played out.
When you're dealing with family,
it's not about a business decision.