[upbeat music]
[Kim groans]
An agent texted me two days ago
and said, "Hey, there's this new player.
He really is into your sister."
And I go, "Which one?"
And then he goes, "Kendall."
And then Kendall and I Googled him,
we decided she's not into him, whatever.
So then he says, "Okay,
is the other sister, Kylie, down to talk?"
Yeah, it's just like
going through the rotation.
-And Kendall was like, "How dumb are you?"
-[laughs]
[Stephanie] That's so gross.
Malika, she's, like, the best sidekick,
'cause she's down for whatever,
but I saw Malika do
some crazy things last night.
I feel like this weekend, like,
was a lot of sinning.
A lot of sinning,
we all need to go to church.
I need holy water.
[Kim] I haven't sinned in years.
You… you're married.
You don't want this life.
-[Khloé] Trust me.
-No, I'm just saying, like--
-You don't want to go here.
-I don't have the urge,
so that's good. You know?
Like, living a content life…
is so good and fulfilling.
That's really nice for you.
[chuckles]
[Stephanie laughs]
[laughter]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] When I drive up here, I'm like,
"Oh, it's so boring up here,"
and then when I come here,
I realize how peaceful and amazing it is.
-This is so nice.
-[Kourtney] Hello.
-[Khloé] Hello.
-[Jonathan] You kind of match
-with the whole couch.
-[Kourtney] I know.
-That was my plan.
-[Jonathan] I love it.
Was Kylie at Mother's Day?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-What went on?
So, I didn't go to Mother's Day
because Rob hasn't been
to Mother's Day in the last three years,
so I'll bow this one out.
[Khloé] I think there's a lot of tension
and a lot of unfinished business,
things that are just not resolved
with my brother.
So I was more than happy
to sleep in on Mother's Day
and let my brother take this holiday.
And 'cause I heard Chyna was going.
-No one ever told me…
-She came…
-…she actually came.
-…on Mother's Day.
-So, she showed up and…
-We all… She brought King.
The kids had a blast.
-They had so much fun. Right.
-Forget about the kids.
Tell us about Chyna.
I mean, you know,
it's like, everyone was
totally fine, got along.
[Jonathan] And was she, like,
sitting and just like, chilling?
Yeah, they had… I felt her belly.
-[Khloé] Kourtney.
-She said she's feeling great,
like, you know?
I mean, my brother's having his first kid.
[dramatic music]
Like, what am I gonna do
except support him?
We love Rob so much,
and just having him around,
I think it was great.
We need to make sure
that we're all getting along,
because we don't want a baby coming
into this world with all this tension.
Kourtney is the most politically
correct person right now.
No. She's not over the top.
Like, she's not like,
"Hey, Happy Mother's Day!"
"Oh, my god, I can't wait to see you."
[Kourtney] But, I mean, why would she be?
It's probably hard for Chyna, you know?
Oh, boy. That's weird. Very, very weird.
[Jonathan]
You're really giving J.Lo vibes today.
[Khloé] Me?
-[Jonathan] Yeah.
-Oh, my god.
[Jonathan]
I haven't seen you in person for a while.
-You're really skinny.
-Why? So, what does that mean?
-I'm skinny?
-[Jonathan] Your face looks good.
[clicks tongue]
[upbeat music]
Seat belt, please.
-What'd you just do?
-Nothing.
Why'd you just fart, yo?
What's wrong with you?
-No, I didn't, yo.
-Yes, you did.
Lamar, you smell. Why do you do that?
That's disgusting.
It's better out than going in.
No. For who? Do that by yourself. God.
[Lamar] I want McDonald's.
No. You're on a diet.
How's McDonald's helping you?
Do you still take
your medicine every morning?
[soft music]
[Khloé] Ever since coming back from Cuba,
I've been so worried about Lamar.
I really want to keep Lamar
in, like, a positive space
and keep him busy with positive things,
and surrounded by positive people.
Look at the hairs on that mane.
Oh, cute.
Look, is the baby with it?
Look at the little baby.
-Want to go out and pet it?
-No.
[Khloé] Why not?
-[Khloé clicks tongue]
-I'm scared of horses.
It's in a cage, what's it gonna do to you?
One almost attacked me.
[Lamar] I will never forget.
That [bleep] went wild.
[mimics horse neighing]
I ran so fast.
[laughs]
[upbeat techno music]
-[phone chimes]
-What are you doing?
Just taking a Snap.
-Snapchat.
-[Scott] And you needed to…
get up on the dance floor?
-I brought food for you.
-Food?
Yeah, I got that… I went to Blue Table,
and I haven't been in so long.
I got that sandwich
you used to always get back in the day.
I don't think I can eat it anymore.
[Scott] Why?
'Cause it has cheese.
I'm doing non-dairy,
and it has gluten in the bread.
[quirky music]
But you were fine eating this
for years and years and years.
No.
This used to be your favorite sandwich.
I've known Kourtney for a very long time.
And all of a sudden,
she thinks she's allergic to everything.
[Scott] You're not allergic.
Nothing will happen to you.
It actually does smell good,
but I'm not gonna have it.
Look at this.
Oh, look at it just… "Hello."
-I'm not gonna have it though.
-[Scott] "Eat me."
-Stop.
-"Eat me."
-[Kourtney] No.
-Have a bite. You're fine.
It's in your head, all these diet,
and allergies, and gluten, and dairy.
[Scott] You can eat this.
I saw you eat this for years
and you were fine.
I also saw you eat this
when you were pregnant with our children
and they came out perfect.
-So?
-[Penelope] I need two marshes.
[Kourtney] Two marshes?
-[Scott] Are they gluten-free?
-They are.
Gluten-free, dairy-free,
vegan marshmallows,
and they're the best.
Sounds like you're putting
nothing in yourself,
but sounds great.
I'll have one too, P.
[Scott] Whoa! There's Mom's lunch.
-Mm-mm.
-What?
[Scott] Mase, come here. I need backup.
[Mason giggles]
[Penelope squeals]
Thank you. Bring her over here.
[Penelope giggling]
Give me the marshmallow out of your mouth.
-[giggling continues]
-[Scott sucks air]
-[Penelope giggling]
-[Scott] I'm gonna get that thing.
-Swallow it, P.
-[Scott] No!
-[grunts]
-[Kourtney] Swallow it.
[Scott] She's quick.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Oh.
[gasps softly]
[Kris] I'll get you some napkins.
-[Lamar speaks indistinctly]
-[Kris] It's all right.
-Please.
-It's all right.
[Khloé] If this was anybody else,
she would cuss them out,
-"What the [bleep]?"
-[Kris] Damn right.
[Khloé] You have her wrapped
around your little finger.
Sauce all over her gray rug,
and she doesn't even flinch.
It's okay, Lammy, I got you.
[Khloé]
Has my mom ever gotten me a napkin ever?
No. Or got on her knees
to clean up after us? Never.
[Kris] It's all right. How are the kids?
[Lamar] They got so big.
Right? Tall.
Yeah, he played ball, so he just,
you know, he's in his own world.
[Kris]
Have you tried to play basketball again?
Just for fun?
-Like, dribble the ball, or…
-[Lamar] Yeah.
-Bounce it around for a minute?
-Mm-hm.
You know, Kourtney has
that basketball court.
-[Lamar] Yeah.
-Right down the street.
No. Imma go to this, um,
training facility in Santa Barbara.
A lot of pros and, um…
guys that would be pros work out there.
-[Kris] Oh, really?
-Yeah.
[dramatic music]
Basketball is obviously
Lamar's passion and love,
and anything that's positive
and uplifting, I'm all for,
but Lamar hasn't followed through recently
with so many things.
Like, I need to see some consistency
and a little effort on Lamar's part.
Going to a basketball camp is a big step,
and I don't want
to set him up for failure.
[Kris] And so you would just train?
[Lamar] Yeah.
[Kris] That sounds really cool.
[Lamar]
Yeah, I'm looking forward to going.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] Your hair looks cute.
[Kim] The braid?
-Who did it?
-[Kim] Cesar.
Yeah.
Cute, right? Your makeup looks good.
Last night was awful.
Like, I couldn't even
Snapchat myself. I had to…
-It would take, like…
-I hate it
-when you can't Snap yourself.
-[Kourtney] It was, like,
would take ten times to do a Snap
-because it was so bad.
-Yeah.
[Kim]
Did I tell you what Chyna wrote to me?
[Kourtney] What did she write?
She basically told me
that she's doing animated emojis.
They showed Chyna hers,
Chyna sent me hers,
and there was one of her kicking a tiger.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-[Kim] Like, for Tyga.
And she said, "Oh, I told them
to take that out."
"I don't want to put that one in."
So it'll be interesting to see…
She acted like she had the power.
I think it's super cool of Chyna
to just give me the heads-up,
just so we all know
what's going on with each other,
since, you know, she's having
a baby with my brother.
I really do appreciate that.
How was she
when you guys went to hang out?
She's so friendly.
Like, if you hung out with her,
she just would be like,
"Oh, do you want this product
for your skin? Oh, my friend…
I know exactly where to get it, hold on.
Let me get it for you."
[Kourtney]
If Chyna's coming out with ChyMojis,
it's nice that she's running it by Kim,
who was, like,
the original KIMOJI inventor.
The more time
that the family can spend with Chyna,
hopefully, everybody can,
like, accept that she's going
to be a part of our family.
She's, like, totally normal,
like, as if nothing, like, ever happened.
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[chitters]
-[Malika] KK.
-[Khloé] Hi.
[Malika] Oh, yeah, comfort.
That's a pretty color on you.
Especially on that couch.
-Thank you.
-Um…
I need to call Elizabeth.
Because Lam wants,
you know, he still wants to go
to that basketball camp in Santa Barbara.
And I don't mind if he goes,
but I said to him,
"Why don't you go
to your boxing class five days a week
-that I've set up for you?"
-[Malika] Mm-hm.
"Consistent. Go five days a week.
And if you could follow through
five days a week
for one week, I'll think about it."
I think that's a lovely compromise.
He hasn't gone to one workout.
[Khloé] I am just so conflicted right now,
and I feel guilty about it.
I want the best for Lamar.
I love that he would be spending
his time in such a positive way.
But, you know,
with everything going on lately,
there's just not a lot of trust there.
There's nothing wrong with helping someone
when they're in need.
But you don't want to make a habit
of giving, giving, and giving to someone
that has only proven
that they're not ready to do it.
Yeah.
[upbeat techno music]
[Scott] Hey.
[Khloé]
Why would this be so complicated for,
like, a normal person to use?
Look at this cool little watch I got.
-I don't know what it does yet.
-[Scott] You know what time it is?
But I just want…
It's like, I'm just learning
-how to work this.
-Holy [bleep].
You really got some closet on you, kid.
Thank you.
It must feel good.
Coming up in here is like,
"Damn. I done made it."
Let me ask you a question.
Do you not think it's a little ridiculous
how obsessed Kourtney is
with all these allergies?
Yeah, well, honestly,
I don't think… I don't know.
Some of the things, like…
They change every day, number one,
which is not normal
when you're really allergic to something.
-I think it's, like, her hobby.
-Right.
"Once in a while, it's not so bad."
I go, "No, not once in a while."
Like, it doesn't work like that.
-No middle ground.
-[Khloé] There's no logic.
[Scott] I know,
for a fact, Kourtney's not allergic
to all these things.
The worst part about it is,
I really can't tolerate lactose.
I got a real allergy. She doesn't.
The next time we're over at the house,
I think we swap out her drink
of what she usually drinks
and then just watch her.
-Regular soy and almond.
-But what if…
What if she really can't have it?
I've seen her eat ice cream
in front of me.
I've seen her eat pizza,
I've seen her eat every crap
there is when no one's looking.
-What the [bleep] does this do?
-She made this up in her mind!
Are you really trying
to, like, connect this watch
-to your phone thing right now?
-Well, I just, it's…
What are you even gonna do
with it, by the way?
Kourtney could be allergic to that.
What kind of rubber is this?
Yeah, she can't have
that around her hands.
[Khloé mimics beeping noise]
Imagine a spaceship just came in?
[chuckles softly]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé]
Oh, my chairs came, by my new table.
Okay, well, these are gray.
-Correct?
-[Malika] Yeah.
When you guys ordered
these chairs outside,
did you guys check
that you ordered black, question mark?
[Khloé]
These are not black whatsoever, period.
-[phone chimes]
-[sighs]
I'm tired of waiting
for things to come into my house
and they always come wrong.
I feel you.
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Lamar's friend] Hi.
[Khloé]
Hi. Did you talk to Mr. Odom yesterday?
-[Lamar's friend] I did.
-[Khloé] Okay.
[Lamar's friend] The basketball camp is
right in the heart of Santa Barbara.
It's run by this doctor
who turned sports guru.
[Khloé] I'm on the phone
with a dear friend of Lamar's,
and he knows very much
about this basketball camp
and he's been through it all
with me and Lamar,
and so he knows exactly
where I'm coming from
and the information that I need
to figure out what to do.
[Lamar's friend]
I talked to Lamar recently.
I said I'm really bummed
you're not taking
everything else seriously.
Like, I'm seeing you going out,
you're not doing counseling.
He just doesn't have a lot of motivation.
-[Khloé] That's an understatement.
-[Lamar's friend] Now,
maybe this is a start.
Why I liked it is
'cause there's nothing to do up there.
You know, Santa Barbara closes early.
It's a very healthy environment.
I'm obviously supportive
if it's something that's healthy,
and even if it's something
that, you know, would get him in shape
and make him feel good
about himself, I'm all for that.
[Khloé]
I do feel better that this is something
that he thinks Lamar should go and do.
I just want this to actually go
as smoothly as I pray it goes.
Well, I will figure this out
and I'll, uh, text you
with some information soon.
-[Lamar's friend] All right.
-Okay.
-[Khloé] Bye.
-You got a hair.
-I need to take a nap.
-Okay.
Okay, I'm gonna start now.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
[chuckles softly]
[upbeat music]
[Yu Tsai] Do you need coffee, tea
-or anything?
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Yu Tsai] Tea?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
You don't even know the drama yesterday
that was happening.
What? What happened?
Like, um, did you see
the ChyMojis or whatever?
I didn't see them, but I heard about them.
Yesterday, Chyna's emojis come out,
and there's just some
that we all don't even know
what to think about.
[Kourtney] It really threw me off.
There was, like, one of, um,
her slapping Kylie.
-Did you see it?
-No, I didn't see them.
[Mario] Is it for sure Kylie though?
[Kourtney] That's, like,
what everyone was saying online.
Just when everybody was trying
to be really accepting
and welcoming Chyna
into the family, this comes out,
and I think that we all are
just, like, confused.
It says, "Surely, that's not Kylie…
Blac Chyna slaps Jenner look-alike
in daring new emoji."
And then, look,
there's a picture of her without…
[Kourtney] Totally.
-The lips.
-[Mario] The big lips, yeah.
[Kourtney] It sent me over the edge.
Everything with Rob,
I always try to be super calm,
but I was just, like, in a mood.
So I was gonna call Chyna,
and then Kylie was like,
"No, just call Rob.
Like, it's too crazy to call Chyna."
And I'm like, "I don't want to yell
at a pregnant person."
[Mario] So, wait, what did you say to Rob?
[Kourtney] I yelled at him.
[Kourtney] This is the first time
that made me question
Chyna's intentions.
Like, I usually don't let
any of this kind of stuff bother me.
But for some reason,
this just sets me off.
I just had to call Rob. And Rob's like,
"It's not Kylie.
When has she ever slapped Kylie?"
And I'm like, "I don't know."
But, you know, I just really upset him.
But didn't he see that,
didn't he see them, the emojis?
[Kourtney] Yeah, but he's like,
"What do you care
if she's, like, doing this?"
"Everyone has emojis."
I'm like, "I don't care
that she has them."
"I care that it was Kylie."
[phone ringing]
-Hey, Khlo.
-[Khloé] You okay?
What is going on with all the Kimojis?
And I showed Mario Kylie,
and he's like, "That is for sure Kylie."
[Khloé]
It's all online, saying it's Kylie!
[Kourtney] I went off on him yesterday.
He's like, "I'm gonna go
on the red carpet tonight,
and I'm gonna tell everybody
how I have the worst,
most unsupportive, disgusting family."
Like, ridiculous.
But I think that it's stupid
to take it there.
[Khloé] I actually have a good tweet
that I'm gonna do. It's a subliminal.
What? Your subliminal tweets
are not subliminal.
[chuckles]
[Khloé] Okay, I'm out.
[Kourtney] Okay, love you.
[upbeat techno music]
[Kylie]
Khlo, I really need food. I'm like…
[Khloé] So eat,
there's so much food in my fridge.
-[Kylie] I don't know what to eat.
-[Khloé] I don't know what's wrong
-with you.
-[Kylie] Maybe I'll try
some chicken risotto.
I kind of want a sweet potato too.
[Khloé] Okay.
There's only so much I can do
with one hand.
[Kylie]
Let's cut this open and see what it is.
What is that?
It's chicken of some sort.
Doesn't look like chicken to me.
Oh, it doesn't? Well, I don't eat
anything else but chicken.
All right.
[Khloé]
My text was ruthless yesterday, huh?
[tense music]
-Yeah.
-[Khloé] This emoji situation.
Can you believe
Kourt got so upset yesterday?
[Kylie] Yeah, so upset.
And for Kourtney to get upset,
you know it's a big deal.
Mm-hm.
[Khloé] Aren't you upset
that Chyna made an emoji about you?
You think that looks like me,
with the thick brows
and side bang and purple lips?
[Kylie] I've never worn
that hairstyle before, right?
[Khloé] You've worn every hairstyle.
I really think it looks like this girl
that she hates
that she had a public fight with.
There's so much misunderstanding going on.
I know everyone is really upset,
but I talked to Chyna,
and I really don't think
the emojis are of me.
I'm really tired of my family
fighting with Rob
over every little thing.
He is expecting a baby,
and it's time for everyone
to just be happy for him.
I just found out it's a lot easier
when, like, everyone gets along.
[Khloé] I know I'll talk
to him again, it's my brother.
[Kylie] So, who is this person
that cooks all this for you?
Mr. Odom's chef.
-[Khloé chuckles]
-Mm-hm.
[Khloé] Um…
Yesterday, I called Lam, and I was like,
"I'm looking for house rentals
in Santa Barbara."
[Kylie] Oh, wow.
[Khloé] And then, he was like,
"I'm having really bad cravings."
And I was like,
"You should talk to someone.
Like, I don't know how to help you.
Like, I wish I did."
[Kylie] That's crazy.
[Khloé] I want this for Lamar.
Lamar has been really honest about,
you know, the thoughts he's been having,
but at the same time,
my answer to that is, like,
"I think you should see someone
that could help you with this."
But Lamar won't do that.
And so that's really, again, frustrating.
You can't do anything
if the person's not willing
to take control of their life
and get help.
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Have you gotten
into the new house yet or not?
[Kylie] No, but now I'm in escrow.
Are you gonna be able to gate
your property now?
Yeah. And then, eventually,
if I get older
and I just always have those properties,
I could tear down the whole thing
and, like, build a house.
Maybe you could attach the two houses.
-Yeah, like, something.
-And just make a compound,
and then it just comes through the middle.
So what did you need me for?
I need you to help me
'cause I really truthfully believe
that Kourtney has made up in her head
that she's highly allergic
-to every single thing…
-[laughs]
-…on the face of the planet.
-I know.
[Scott]
Now that Khloé's not gonna participate
with switching out all the foods
to "the allergic stuff,"
I've decided Kylie needs to be
my accomplice here.
I mean, I trust her,
and we'll see what happens.
She's just lost it.
I don't even think
she knows what gluten is.
I don't. Do you?
-No.
-Does anybody?
I'm sure.
So, my point is, I'm saying,
I want you to distract her,
I want to replace
everything she has with regular dairy,
regular gluten, regular soy,
and then we'll see the end result.
Okay.
That's it. Plain and simple.
Plain and simple.
[techno music]
[Scott] So, let's find her,
and then you distract her.
And then I'll come back
and get the groceries.
[Kylie]
Smells like a gluten-free grilled cheese.
[Scott] Yeah, aka, horse [bleep].
-[Kylie] Kourtney?
-[Kourtney] Hi.
[Kylie] Hey.
-[Kourtney] Cutting P's nails.
-[Scott gasps]
[Scott] Hi, Paloosh.
So you're getting your nails done?
Mm-hm.
You have a little gray hair.
Do you want me to pull it out?
[Kourtney] No.
-You like it? Okay.
-[Kourtney] Live for them.
All right, I'm gonna go downstairs
and eat some food.
[Scott] I'll be back.
You never eat here.
-I have my lunch. It's salad.
-[Kourtney] Oh.
[sniffles]
I know it's all psychological
with Kourtney thinking
that she has all these allergies.
And she makes up
these elaborate stories, like…
[gasps]
"Oh, well, this one time I had gluten,
and I had a little goosebump on my arm."
I'm like, "Maybe that's just
'cause you're wearing a T-shirt,
and you're in the middle
of a ski mountain."
So I definitely think this is some place
where I can prove to her
that it's not real, then.
[mischievous music]
-[Kourtney] Why is Scott being so weird?
-[phone chiming]
Should we go down there?
Mm…
[mischievous music continues]
[Kylie] I'm just gonna tell you.
-What?
-'Cause I feel awkward.
-But he's… he's…
He's switching your food downstairs.
My food?
'Cause he thinks that your gluten allergy
-is, like, a joke, so he…
-Yeah, he does.
So he's switching all of them.
Scott just doesn't understand
why me and the kids
have to be gluten-free, dairy-free,
and it may not seem like a big deal,
but it's, like, it's an allergy, so…
I… It's just annoying.
By the way, like,
he should know of anyone.
-He's lactose intolerant.
-And I just want to tell you,
'cause, like, I don't know
if you're, like, really allergic
and something might happen.
He, like, doesn't believe me,
so he'll go against my ways.
Yeah.
Okay, don't tell him that I know.
[Kylie] Okay.
Blood.
-Blood is thicker than water.
-Okay.
[upbeat music]
-Hi, guys. How are you?
-[Scott] Hey.
-[Leon] How are you, babe?
-Good to see you.
I'm gonna sit over here.
So I can gaze into your eyes.
What took you so long?
-There was a lot of traffic.
-[Kim] I was at a doctor's--
There was, like,
coming from Beverly Hills.
-Like, there's so much…
-[Scott] So much.
-[Kim] …traffic here all the time.
-Rodeo was, like, shut down.
[Scott]
'Cause we were over there shopping.
-[Leon] Yeah.
-I was, like, right near there.
[waiter speaking indistinctly]
Uh, we'll take some Brussels sprouts,
sounds good.
-[Leon] Yeah.
-[Scott] So, you know,
I've heard Kourtney talk about
all these little emojis
about Chyna and whatnot.
And I said to Kourt,
I go, "But in all honesty, like,
there is such a bigger picture here
we do need to think about."
"Like, your brother,
whether what terms everyone's on with him,
is gonna have a child with this woman
for the rest of his life."
"That's it."
-[Leon] Yeah.
-[Scott] Like, forget it, who cares?
-Like, there's a bigger picture.
-Yeah.
[Scott]
And I told Kourtney and she was like,
"All right, I'm still annoyed."
[Kim] I think that Scott is right.
We all love my brother,
we're so happy for him
that he's, you know, having a baby,
so, I think I need to talk to Kourtney.
She needs to just,
like, sit back, be supportive,
so everyone is happy.
It's like, what do we do to keep it,
-like, just calm…
-Civil?
Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Where can I take
a good selfie in the mirror?
-This one?
-I don't know.
I've never done one there.
[Kim] Kourtney, you do this here
on a daily basis.
[camera shutter clicking]
[Kourtney] Can we go outside?
[Kim]
So, did you get a chance to talk to Rob?
I haven't really talked to him
since we got into that fight
-when I yelled at him.
-Yeah, I cannot believe
you haven't talked to him since then,
and I cannot believe
he hasn't cared enough to call you.
[Kim] I feel like this is so ridiculous,
and I think we all just need
to, like, get over it.
You know?
Well, it's like, even, like,
I know what it's like to be,
like, having your first baby
and people aren't supportive.
Took, like, years for people
to like Scott.
True. But I just wanted to at least,
like, get you guys on the phone
so we could not
-have any kind of drama.
-Yeah.
Do you want me to call?
Call and see if he answers.
[line ringing]
[Kourtney] I think Kim is right.
I mean, I should've asked Rob
what was going on
instead of just getting so angry
and assume that certain things were true.
And I just want to hear what Rob says.
I'm hoping that he wants to…
make it a peaceful situation as well.
[line ringing]
[Kourtney] He's not answering.
[automated message] I'm sorry, the person
you are trying to reach
has a voice mailbox--
[Kim] So what do we do
if Rob's not gonna answer?
[Kourtney] I don't know.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Here we are, guys.
[Kourtney] Mase, do you mind switching?
P, you didn't tell Lovey what you did.
[Kris] What'd you do?
Just look at her
and tell me if you can notice.
-[Kourtney] Wanna go under the table?
-[Kris gasps]
I just noticed.
Did you get your ears pierced?
P, we're gonna switch
so you can sit here, okay?
[Kris] Let me look at you.
Wait, no feet on the table, Kourt.
-Up. Pick her up.
-[Kourtney] Here.
They're so beautiful.
[Kourtney] Let me look at them
to make sure they look okay.
-Did it hurt?
-[Penelope] No.
I didn't cry.
-[Kourtney] She didn't even move.
-[Kris] You didn't cry?
-[Kourtney] Nothing, right?
-What?
Just a little bit.
Mase, what do you feel like?
Gluten-free pasta?
-[Mason] Yeah.
-[Kourtney] Okay.
So, Scott was over the other day
and saying that,
like, our allergies aren't real
and that we don't need to be on that diet.
So anyways, he came over and, like,
switched out our non-dairy milk
with real milk.
But then Kylie told me
before we even had it.
Did you tell him that you found out?
-Mm-mm.
-[chuckles]
I feel like I could pretend
to be really sick.
That's a good one.
I think you should say
that you're super sick
and you have to go to the doctor's.
[chuckles]
Scott, in a million years,
would never think that I would get sick,
so it is, like, a great opportunity
to just get to make him feel bad,
because he just needs
to learn a lesson to, like,
get out of my business
about, like, what I'm eating.
That is amazing. Payback is a bitch.
Hey, watch your language.
Oh, my god.
Between the food and the non-cussing,
I would go crazy.
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
-[Khloé] Hi.
-[Lamar's friend] Hey, Khloé.
[Khloé] I know exactly who that is.
[Lamar's friend]
Do you know if he's shady?
I know he was around
during, like, a bizarre time,
but I don't know for sure.
One of Lamar's friends has called me
and is, you know,
notifying me that Lamar is hanging out
with bad guys again.
And it saddens me.
I know Lamar wants better,
I know Lamar wants to excel
and be on a good path,
but he just can't help it.
[Khloé] I'm just at a loss of,
like, so what do we do anyway?
I've tried every single thing.
[Lamar's friend] I know you have.
Nothing's gonna wake him up.
That's where the biggest problem is.
I thought he was really gonna change,
but, like, this is Lamar.
[upbeat music]
-[Scott] Kris. What is going on?
-[Kris] Yeah?
God, I thought you'd never get here.
[Scott] What do you mean "never get here?"
I just drove
100 miles an hour to get here.
You've got to come see Kourtney
because I don't know what's wrong,
and one of us has to take her
to the hospital.
[Scott] What's the problem?
[Kris] Honey, are you okay?
[Kourtney grunts weakly]
[Kris] I think she's eaten something
that she's not…
that's not agreeing with her.
[tense music]
She's fine. Are you guys kidding?
Kourtney sucks at this.
And I don't wanna be
her partner in crime anymore.
I mean, this is epic,
but Kourtney's like, "Whatever."
She's just not a very good actor.
[Scott] Hello? She's fine.
-[Kourtney yells]
-What-- What's wrong with you?
[Kris laughs]
There's nothing wrong with this kid.
[Scott] This is ridiculous.
She doesn't look sick,
she's just decked out,
hair and makeup.
I mean, looks like
she's going to the Oscars.
Don't mess with me and my food.
[mischievous music]
[Scott] How did you catch it?
-[Kourtney] Kylie.
-Kylie told you?
But just because it's like, it's a choice.
But I don't think it's fair
to tell everyone
you're allergic to all these things.
And then go have a glass of milk
or eat a big ice cream,
and be like, "Oh, it's a cheat day."
You can't cheat on allergies.
[Scott] The fact that she thinks
that she can take "off days"
of being allergic,
that doesn't work in America, lady.
Or anywhere else in this world.
It's absolutely ridiculous,
and I'm appalled.
Listen. Some people choose to be vegans,
some people choose to be vegetarian.
-Great.
-We are choosing to be
-dairy-free.
-[Scott] You're choosing to lie
and say you're allergic.
-That's fair too.
-[Kris] It's her choice. She's--
-Okay, okay. So I…
-Maybe just don't use the word "allergic."
[Kourtney]
Since Scott is being ridiculous,
I won't call
my diet restrictions an allergy,
since that seems to be offending Scott.
I'll just say
that it's, like, a healthy lifestyle.
-[Kris] Okay.
-I…
-I agree.
-Mom, you have so many different styles
-going on in your house…
-[Scott] Here we go.
-…of decor.
-[Scott] First of all,
-step outside of here…
-20 years.
…you'll see a mid-century room,
then you'll see
a colonial and Old English,
and a horse stable on the other side.
I'm almost allergic
to how many different styles
-you have in this house.
-[Kris and Kourtney chuckle]
I… I just can't.
-I can't. I can't.
-[Kourtney] No, but it's so mean.
I wish you guys well. I really do.
I hope you work things out,
but I'm gonna go back.
[Scott] With what, her allergies?
-Or the whole break-up thing?
-I need a vodka.
[door closes]
[upbeat music]
[Rob] Hey, Kimbo.
[Kim] Ricky.
-Just came here to see…
-[Kim] Aren't slides,
-like, your favorite?
-[grunts]
[chuckles]
It's the only shoes I wear.
I love them.
I need new ones.
Well, I called you over here
because I just wanted to,
like, get Kourt on the phone for a sec,
because I feel like your fight with her,
obviously, you guys should talk about it.
-Okay.
-[line ringing]
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-[Kim] Hi.
I'm here with Rob, and I know you guys,
like, haven't spoken
since your little fight.
[Kourtney] Okay, yeah.
And I think we all just need
to, like, get over it and move on.
[Rob] It's just that the assumptions,
like, the negative assumptions…
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-[Rob] It's just not necessary.
It's just, talk to me normally and calmly.
'Cause I don't come screaming
at any of you guys
for anything that you guys have done ever
in your life…
[Kourtney] But that's what siblings do.
What?
[Kourtney]
And then we make up two seconds later.
[sighs]
[Kourtney]
I apologize for just making accusations.
Nah, it's all good. I just,
we don't need to be fighting
over some pettiest,
dumbest [bleep] in the world, so…
[Kourtney] I agree.
There's no reason for there
to be any drama, really.
I mean, Rob has come such a long way
and he's had such positive improvements.
I think Kourtney and I,
we just want him to feel, like,
we love him and we're supporting him.
And I'm just glad
that they can work it out,
'cause at the end of the day,
we just want to be a family
that will always be there
to support each other no matter what.
[Kourtney] I'm excited
for this new chapter in your life,
and I'm excited for you
to join Club Kourtney and Kim.
That's right, it's a really good club.
-[Kourtney] And, um…
-It's, like, the best club.
Yay.
[upbeat music]
-I did that. And that.
-[Kourtney] Ooh.
[gasps]
Mase, that guy's the best.
With that heart.
[Mason] I'm gonna make them mermen.
[Kourtney] That's so good.
Well, I love this mermaid.
-[Khloé] Do you know all these states?
-No.
[Khloé] You're not even looking at them.
-[Mason speaking indistinctly]
-How was your night? What did you do?
[Khloé] Honestly, Kim, I…
I don't want to talk about it.
It was, like, five steps backwards.
I don't even know what to do.
[tense music]
-How crazy.
-[Khloé] And I said,
"You know, like,
you could die right now, right?"
[Khloé] Lamar and I talked about…
the demons he's been battling recently.
And he doesn't realize
how erratic I think he's acting,
'cause it… he can't help it.
And I'm just like,
"God, I thought all this was over."
[Kim]
I'll go over there today if you want,
and I can talk to him, or I can, like,
have Kanye come and help talk to him.
[tense music continues]
Like, why do I treat him
better than I treat myself?
[Kim]
I mean, I feel like maybe you shouldn't…
put so much energy into it.
You know, you'll always be there,
but you can't, you know,
baby him and be his, like, mom.
Like, with Scott, like, it's like,
I don't tell him, "Don't do this or that."
And it feels so good to let it go,
but it's hard because, at the same time,
you don't want the person to die.
Well, that's just what's gonna happen.
[somber music]
I feel really strongly
there's only one outcome.
You know, I've always hoped
that Lamar seeing
everyone that rallied around him
during a dark time
and everyone who's rooting
for a comeback story
and everyone that wants
to see Lamar do well
and just succeed in life,
just win at the game of life.
I think that's where,
I always put all my eggs into that basket.
And it… whether it be my personal family,
or the fans of the world,
or just everyone that's praying for him,
it really is so moving how much everyone…
was rooting for Lamar.
Except him. So it is disappointing.
I just think, in your mind,
you have to be, like,
prepared for the worst.
And try your best.
[calm music]
You know you gave me these jeans
a long time ago?
Oh, my god. Those are the jeans
that I wore when I was in Spain.
I love them. They're a 27,
but, like, they fit me.
So, like, they would never fit me,
but my goal was just to see--
-These would never fit you.
-[Kim] I know, I know.
But I'm saying,
like, in, like, six months.
What are we gonna do
about, like, Khloé and Lamar?
I feel like she just, like,
did so much thinking,
like, this was it and, like,
they're gonna get back together.
And, like, she's gonna,
like, help save him.
I don't think she thought that.
-Really?
-[Kourtney] No.
I think, deep down inside,
she thought, like,
-"What if this works out?"
-I don't.
-I don't. I don't.
-Really?
-Oh, I so think that.
-[Kourtney] She…
I don't think she thinks,
"I want to spend my life
with him and have kids with him."
Because, like, where's the trust?
-And where's…
-The normalcy?
I just don't think
that's the situation she wants.
Yeah, but I think she feels,
like, tied to him.
[Kourtney] Of course.
She feels tied to him,
and she feels responsible,
and she feels like she's all he has.
Yeah, totally.
[Kourtney] When it comes to Lamar,
I know that Khloé has,
you know, been through it all with him.
Khloé has given everything,
she's tried everything.
You know, I can give her
as much advice as I can,
but, like, there's only so much
that she can do.
[Kim] Next on
Keeping Up with the Kardashians…
I don't want to send him
the wrong message.
Scott invited me
to his birthday party in Las Vegas.
[Kourtney] Ah, ah! Ah, ah, ah, ah!
So have you talked to Khloé lately?
-No.
-She misses her brother.
She should be careful what she says.
And you all aren't welcoming
of this relationship,
-so it's not that easy.
-I've missed you.
Why won't you even look at me?
[Rob groans]