I've tried every single thing.
I thought he was really gonna change,
but, like, this is Lamar.
[Khloé] Why do I treat him
better than I treat myself?
I feel like you shouldn't put
so much energy into it.
There's one more thing I have
to talk to you guys about,
but I don't want you guys to get mad.
-[Kim] You're having a baby.
-[Rob] Yeah.
I know Khloé's probably feeling--
[Khloé] Congratulations.
So, have you told anybody
about Rob and Chyna?
-No.
-How do you feel?
I mean, it's Rob's life.
[Khloé] How do you feel?
[Kourtney] I just want him to be happy.
[Khloé] My brother and I have always had
such a strong connection.
What bothers me is that Rob has
completely just disconnected from me.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé groans]
[Kourtney] I'm better
at basketball than Khloé.
[Don] You get one shot.
-[Kourtney groans]
-[Khloé] That's not… You're better?
[laughs]
[Khloé] You know what I hate?
So, yesterday on the red carpet,
what's up with my inner thighs?
Nothing. I didn't see anything.
Yeah, they're [bleep] nasty,
and someone wrote,
"What kind of ho works out every day
and doesn't have good thighs?"
And I was like, "You're right.
I agree with you,
what kind of ho does work out every day
and doesn't have good inner thighs?"
[laughs]
[Don] What happened?
What's wrong with your inner thighs?
I will show you my picture.
-I'm so pissed at my legs.
-Let me see it.
[Kourtney] If a ho eats Popeyes, then…
We had Popeyes once on the airplane.
When was the last time we had Popeyes?
-[Don] Let me just take a look.
-[Khloé] You ass [bleep].
-They're right though.
-Have you seen this?
I don't know what she's talking about.
I mean, maybe I'm looking
at something wrong.
-[Khloé] That inner thing.
-Yeah, what are you…
Oh, right there?
Yes, I want it to be hard.
I swear, when I was fatter,
I had more muscle definition.
[Don] Well, come on,
let's take care of it right now.
[Khloé] Oh, [bleep] balls,
we're gonna die.
[laughs]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Hi!
Oh, my goodness, it's my favorite girl.
Hi!
Are you so excited
to come to lunch with Lovey?
-Huh?
-Mm-hm.
[Kris] Yeah? Wanna sit in your chair?
-No.
-Okay, this is fun.
-I like that top.
Thank you.
Have… Look, I have the pants on, too.
-[Scott] Really?
-Yeah.
Oh, I like those.
I wanna get some stuff like that.
-Dolce.
-[Scott clears throat]
Might be a little much for me,
but I like it.
Thanks.
I had the craziest appointment
at my doctor's today.
'Cause I've been struggling with just,
you know, getting older.
And it was so interesting
because your body can really break down
if you're not careful,
and we really need
to take care of ourselves.
So, what? Do you feel tired?
Is that why you went?
Yeah, just kind of, like,
not great, tired.
Like, welcome to 60, thank you.
Yeah, but, I mean, you look good
and you're running around.
I mean, you do more than
most people do in their 30s.
The problem is there's no reason to be,
like, 20 pounds overweight.
You're not 20 pounds overweight.
Aw, thank you.
My life is always crazy,
and I'm constantly
under a lot of pressure
and have a lot going on,
so I need to figure out a way
to increase my energy,
and just be able to have
a little more stamina during the day
because I'm exhausted
and I need to step it up.
At the end of the thing, the doctor goes,
"Well, I'm going to give you this kit.
And I need you to go home
and basically collect a stool sample."
Oy. You realize we're at lunch, right?
Yes, but I just don't think
I can play with my poop like that.
I don't think I wanna hear you
play with your poop like that.
And then I have to mail it…
[Scott] My daughter's three,
I don't think she even wants to.
She has pooped before.
-I pretend women don't.
-Really?
Yeah, I don't like to hear that stuff.
Have you ever been in a room
when a girl has pooped?
Absolutely not.
No. Not at all.
-[Kris] Okay.
-Gross.
No. Right, Poosh?
[upbeat music]
[Scott] Hey, KoKo.
[laughs]
You sounded like Jonathan Cheban.
Jonathan says that. "Hey, KoKo."
[Scott] You, like, blend into this chair.
-I dress--
-I almost can't find you.
I dress according to theme.
I'm a chameleon.
What's going on?
You know it's my birthday this weekend.
-Or did you not?
-No, I did.
Are you gonna be involved,
is the question,
now that me and Kourtney aren't together?
Uh, hello.
Yup, I'm going.
-True family.
-[Khloé] Yup.
[Khloé] I am super excited
that Scott invited me
to his birthday party in Vegas.
This could not have come at a better time.
[Khloé] I definitely need
a good distraction right now.
This is gonna be, like, super fun
and I'm excited.
-Are you going to 1 OAK?
-[Scott] Yeah.
Oh, PS, I wanted to have
a family dinner at Nobu
on Thursday night here in Malibu,
and the next day we'll go to Vegas
and it'll be like a big party.
I have a busy week.
-Do you?
-Thursday, Nobu.
Vegas, Friday.
Then I have a spray tan at 8:45.
-Oh, my god.
-I know.
-Things are filling up quick.
-Filling up.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Hey, Don.
[Don] Uh-oh! Look who we have here.
Have you ever trained my mom?
I haven't gave her the full matrix yet.
[Kris] Oh, [bleep].
Wait, I need to Snapchat this.
-Why? Do I have camel toe?
-No.
Ta-da.
[Kris chuckles]
-So, this is the day.
-[Kris] Yeah.
I'm trying to find workouts
because I really wanna stay strong.
-Okay.
-And I need cardio,
and I need to keep it going, you know?
[Kourtney]
Yeah, so you can feel your best.
My mom hasn't been really
into working out lately.
[Kourtney] And she has been complaining
about not feeling well
and just feeling low energy.
[Don] So we'll do a warm up first,
get some blood flowing,
and then we'll stretch everything out.
-[Kris] Okay.
-[Kourtney] I'm happy
that she wants to get back into it,
because one of the biggest things
that helps Khloé and I
is working out.
Let's go for a basic jog.
We start down here.
-Oh, a jog.
-Yeah, here we go.
We're just going there.
Your pace, your flow.
Over there, you're going over there.
Over there.
Kourtney, I used to do track
in high school.
-You did?
-Yup.
You know what? I still got it.
[Don whoops]
Let's go. One up,
then drop all the way down.
Don't stop, Mom. Come on, you can do this.
[Kris] Whoo! Baby.
I set the pace.
You have to keep up with me.
Easy.
[Don] Okay, I see you showing off now.
[Kris laughs]
-[Don] Last one for the abs.
-Last one?
Three, two, one.
Let's do three sets. Flip back over.
What?
That was one set.
We're not done?
-Each quarter has three sets.
-Oh, [bleep].
[laughter]
[Kris laughs]
-Come on.
-[Don] Let's go.
[Kris] I got this.
-Let's go.
-[Kourtney] Do it, Mom.
[pants]
Three up, then right back down.
Four up, there you go.
Five up.
One, up, drop, good.
Four. Do it.
Five. Knees up.
I have not really been exercising
to the extent that I used to.
I guess I shouldn't have been so surprised
that this is such a challenge.
Two sets down, one to go.
[Kris groans loudly]
Second quarter, second quarter.
[Kris grunts]
Here we go.
[Kris] But you know what?
I'm not gonna let anything stop me
from giving this everything I have,
and I'm gonna push through this workout.
-[Don] How you doing?
-[Kris] Really great.
[Don] Good. That's a wrap.
[Don whoops]
[Kris] Oh, my god.
My legs, they have a mind of their own.
-[Don laughs]
-They're running away!
[Kris] I can't control them.
Help, get me back.
I can't help myself!
[upbeat music]
-[Elizabeth over phone] Hi.
-[Khloé] Hey.
[Elizabeth] So, you decided
that you're ready to do this.
I just wanna make sure
that it's bulletproof,
that no matter our marital status,
I still could help Lamar
if, God forbid, this were to happen again.
[Elizabeth on phone]
If this happens again,
and Lamar is not in sound mind
and Lamar is on life support,
you get to make the decision regardless…
-Of marital status. Yeah.
-[Elizabeth] Yes.
[Khloé] Perfect. Thank you.
[Elizabeth] You're welcome.
I'll talk to you later.
-[Khloé] Okay. Bye.
-[Elizabeth] Okay. Bye.
[Kourtney] What's happening?
You're getting a divorce again?
What I was just talking to Elizabeth about
was Lamar asked
that, if anything were to happen
to him again, that I always be,
like, his medical advisor
and, like, make all those decisions
'cause he has no one else to trust.
And I said, "But when we get a divorce,
I legally don't have those rights."
So, we met with lawyers.
That, if anything were to happen,
regardless of our marital status,
I will still help him.
And so I heard they were done,
so I just called Elizabeth
to confirm they were done,
and then we'll re-file.
-Yeah.
-Like, this…
how long am I gonna sit in this for?
[Kourtney] Yeah, no.
This is ridiculous.
I'm finalizing my divorce papers
today with my lawyer…
again, for the second time.
[Khloé] Lamar and I have spoken about it,
we're both on board.
So, we are going to file tomorrow,
and so it might be public,
but we don't really anticipate much.
-[Lamar] All right.
-Okay?
[Lamar] Yeah.
Okay.
Regardless if Lamar and I
have spoken about it
and that we're on the same page,
it's still bittersweet.
[Khloé] I was holding out, you know,
to help Lamar,
but Lamar's not helping himself,
so I have to do what's best for me.
And I have to move on and just be done,
like there's no reason to hold on to this.
[Khloé] It will always be love
and I will always,
like, love Lamar
and, like, be his friend, but…
it's time for me to start
the next chapter of my life.
[upbeat music]
[Kris moaning]
-Okay. How are your headaches?
-[Khloé] Fine.
But I mainly give them to myself, I think.
I just stress myself out.
[Kris] That's not good.
I've been doing that my whole life.
-Now, that's not good.
-Take a page out of my book
-and don't do it.
-[Khloé] That's not good.
[Kourtney] Khlo. Come to the kitchen.
-The boss is calling.
-Oh.
I'm the boss.
[Khloé] Not of me.
[Kris] You gonna go to Scott's birthday?
-[Khloé] Yup. Hey, boss.
-[Kourtney] Hey.
-Are you gonna go?
-I don't know.
I said I'll have to decide last minute.
-See what's going on…
-[Kris] You should go.
…with the kids.
[Kourtney] Scott invited me
to his birthday party in Las Vegas.
And I'm just not sure if I wanna go.
I mean, I'm so happy that Scott and I
are getting along so well
and that we're co-parenting,
but I think hanging out
with Scott without the kids,
Scott can just take any little thing
and run with it,
and think that, like,
we're getting back together tomorrow.
[Kourtney] Right now, I can't even wrap
my head around that idea.
There's so much work
that would be involved,
and I'm so not even there yet.
[Kris] Wait, so when are you going?
[Khloé] I have a shoot on Friday,
so I would have to leave after my shoot.
But that's when he told me
he was leaving anyway.
And he said the plane
was gonna come back right after.
Yeah, 'cause he said
he has something the next day.
What does he have the next day?
[Kourtney] Atlantic City pool party.
-What?
-[Kris] That's wild.
You are cute.
You're cute.
[upbeat music]
Hey!
What is this, off-season?
[chuckles]
Yeah.
-What are you icing your leg for?
-[laughs]
I was working out
with Kourtney and Khloé with that Don guy.
I ran 20… 35 laps.
[Scott] That's ridiculous. Like, for what?
Well, just I'm going through
this sluggish stage,
and I used to be in such great shape
and now I cannot get it together.
I've been really good
about showing up for my workouts with Don.
[Kris] And he's really tough.
I don't think I've ever been so tired
and exhausted in my life.
But it's really gonna pay off.
I just know it is.
[Kris] No pain, no gain.
I mean, I just wanna feel good
and be healthy.
[Scott] Water aerobics.
You could do the big move
from Dirty Dancing,
Corey could hold you up, spin you around.
-[Kris chuckles]
-That's normal.
[laughs]
Oh, my god.
I understand Kris wants to keep her youth
and keep her body looking good,
but now she's starting to work out
with Kourtney and Khloé?
They're little animals
and they work out every single day.
[Scott] Of course, you're gonna go
break a knee or something.
She's not 20 years old anymore.
Why are you trying to be
something you're not?
Everyone loves you as you are.
Don't think you need to try
to keep up with them.
They're psychotic. You look beautiful.
You're, like, the hottest
60-year-old on the planet.
That's a known fact.
You look about 40, but you are 60.
You can't be running 5,000 laps
in a tennis court with a bunch of kids.
You'll kill yourself.
-[Kris] Yeah.
-I mean, at least your outfit looks nice
and everything matches.
Thank you.
Other than different sweats to the shoes,
-but okay.
-I know.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Scott] P was telling me last night
how many different names she had.
She goes, "Sometimes I go by P,
sometimes KiKi calls me Peepaleep."
-[Kim chuckles]
-"Sometimes I go by Poosh,
sometimes I go by Poosh-kaloosh."
[Kim] Yeah, North goes…
She calls her Peepaleep now.
-That's cute.
-'Cause she heard me say it.
-Hi.
-[Kourtney] Hey.
By the way, are you guys aware
that your mom thinks she's, like, 30?
-[Kourtney chuckles]
-She's not though.
She's 60. She's got a lot of pressure.
She just wants to look good, and she does.
She looks better than any
other 60-year-old alive.
But she… Honestly, what is she thinking
to come over here
and jump into you and Khloé's workout?
[Kourtney] She wanted to do that.
[Scott] Yeah, but I feel like
you should've said,
"Hey, we've been doing
this workout a long time.
Pace yourself."
Yeah.
[Kourtney] I mean, Scott is right,
and I think sometimes we just forget
that my mom maybe can't keep up with us.
But I've seen her
do these kind of workouts,
like, our whole lives,
so it's just easy to forget.
[Kourtney]
But I do love working out with my mom,
so I really do wanna find something
that we can do together.
[Scott] All I'm saying is
maybe you could do
something that's more up her alley.
I don't think she needs to, like,
break down on the side of the road
like an old car at this point.
Girls got to work out.
[laughs]
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Hey, Khloé.
This is the most beautiful room.
-Thank you.
-And I love that picture of you.
-Mike shot that.
-Stop.
-[Khloé] In Saint Barts.
-[Kris] Right, I remember that.
Look at your body.
I gave birth to that thing.
-You did.
-[Kris laughs]
-Not that size, but yeah.
-[Kris] Oh, my god.
[Khloé] Um… Have you talked to Rob lately?
[Kris] Aw…
You guys haven't seen each other
in such a long time.
-[Khloé] I know.
-That makes me really sad.
It makes me really sad.
I text Rob just the other day
for the first time in, like, weeks.
And I was like,
"Hey, um, you know I love you
and I miss you,
and I really hope Chyna's pregnancy
is going well."
And he just, "I love you, too."
But, like, there's no, like,
effort on his part.
Like, he has never reached out to me once.
It's just weird
'cause Kourtney, Kim, Kendall, Kylie,
like, no matter what we're doing,
we always text or FaceTime where…
[Kris] Yeah, make sure
you guys stay connected.
But no matter how busy we are,
or how in love we are,
or how sad we are,
like, we turn to each other.
So, it's so weird that we don't talk,
and that's bizarre.
[somber music]
[Khloé] Rob and I grew up inseparable.
And I feel like no matter
where I've been in my life,
Rob's always been someone
that I lean onto.
And especially now I'm going through
so much this week,
I'm really missing his support
and just him being there,
and just even for me to go to his room
and hang out with him.
You would think, like,
with him starting a family,
he would wanna talk about stuff.
I hate to see my kids in this place.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Gabbana!
All you do is follow me everywhere!
[Khloé sighs]
Oh, I hate everyone today.
Honestly, it's too much
for one soul to bear.
Oh, I see it.
"Khloé Kardashian files
for divorce again."
How do you feel?
[phone chimes]
Don't try to act like you care.
[Kim] No, I thought you were like,
"Oh, who cares?"
We've been going around
this circle ten times.
What?
Nobody cares but me.
I'm, like, the only person who does care.
No one gives a [bleep]
and I understand why.
Whatever.
I don't think no one gives a [bleep].
I think we, like, dropped everything
to, like, help you, you know.
I think as far as your decision
to wanna get a divorce again,
I think it's, like, inevitable
and I think that you should.
I think that you shouldn't, like,
live your life, you know,
-just like waiting to see…
-I don't need anybody… I don't…
I don't need anybody to care.
-I really…
-No, but it's not…
But it's not that we don't care.
I just think it's, like,
the best decision.
So I'm like, don't wanna rock the boat
and talk too deep about it
in case you change your mind.
[Kim] I think Khloé acts
like she doesn't need the help
and she's so strong
and she doesn't want the help,
but then, she really does need it.
[Kim] So it's just hard to know how to be.
But I don't want Khloé to ever think
that we don't care.
It is for my best interest but is it hard?
It's so hard.
[sighs]
[upbeat music]
North, what's your name?
-Bugs.
-"Bugs"?
What's your other name?
West.
[Khloé] West?
Mommy's name is West.
Yes. And what else is Mommy's name?
-Kim.
-Where's your dad?
Um… Mommy?
Yeah?
-Where is my dad?
-[chuckles]
He is at home, resting with Sainty.
"At home, resting with Sainty."
[Khloé chuckles]
Thank you.
[North] Where are we going now?
We're going to Nobu
for Scott's birthday.
[upbeat music]
Hi.
Oh! The birthday boy!
-Happy birthday.
-Love you.
[Kris] Oh, that was awkward.
I'm trying to go like this, and it's like…
[smooches]
[Kim] I have been looking
for a good picture of us all day.
We have nothing good together?
Like, there was some funny things
that was like…
-Nothing, like, real?
-"…Scott and Kim.
They're gonna leave everyone
and get married."
Like the same funny things.
Like they say
about every single one of them.
Like, Khloé did it and I did it.
[light music]
Happy birthday, Scott.
-[chuckles]
-Oh, this is a video?
[Scott] I was giving, like, my look.
[Khloé] Happy birthday.
Thank you. Mwah.
[Scott] You know, I'm really impressed
that, in the middle of filing for divorce,
Khloé can get herself up
and still come to my birthday dinner
and be supportive and be loving.
She really is one of the strongest women
I know and have ever met.
Can you pass me some of that shrimp?
Why don't you have
the field greens salad here?
-It's real good.
-[Khloé] I am.
So, Scott, how's your birthday going?
It's been a little bit
of a hectic day, but…
now it's nice to just be able to,
like, relax and calm down.
Been pretty good.
[Khloé] Good. Are you excited for Vegas?
I'm excited that everybody's
coming and stuff
and we'll all be together.
Who's all going tomorrow?
Semel.
And then just basically us.
JJ and his wife. Benny and his wife.
Chris, Cheyenne, Mickey, and that's it.
-And then, uh…
-[Khloé] Yeah.
Are you guys going or no?
[Kourtney] I don't know.
I feel like this table's so big.
I could have invited some people.
-Did you invite Rob?
-[Scott] Yeah.
He said, "I'd love to, but…
because of Chyna, I… I'm not coming."
[dramatic music]
Khloé and Rob have been best friends
since the day Rob was born,
and I hate to see them in a situation
where they're not talking
to each other because,
with everything else that's going on,
Khloé needs him now more than ever.
[dramatic music]
[Khloé] Did you invite Rob?
[Scott] Yeah.
He said, "I'd love to, but…
because of Chyna, I… I'm not coming."
Kourt, why don't you give Scott
one of his presents?
[Scott] Ah, I don't wanna. I don't wanna.
Your birthday,
we wanna celebrate with you.
[Kourtney] Open the bottom one from us.
-Mason made you a card.
-[Scott] Oh.
Did you see this card my son made?
You took some real time.
And what, did you shoot
a BB gun through it, too,
while you were at it?
[laughs]
Oh, I love these.
Oh, my god.
These seriously got to be huge for you.
Could you get these made with my… with a…
-[man mutters indistinctly]
-[laughter]
I do love having the whole family
join me for my birthday.
[Scott] I'm having a great time.
Thank you, guys!
You know, it's really nice to feel
that we're all still close,
and we can all still do things together.
[all] ♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
[Kris whoops]
-[all] ♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
-Look, look, look.
You want to blow out
the candles for me, Poosh?
You want to help me?
-[all] ♪ Happy birthday, dear Scott ♪
-Wow.
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
-[Khloé] Yay!
-[all cheering]
[all whooping]
[Kris] Whoa!
[Khloé] Yeah!
[upbeat music]
[phone chimes]
Just cheese.
And just one pizza.
It's just us.
-And North will have a piece.
-[phone chimes]
Caroline's coming over to bring you pizza.
-That's cute.
-Yeah.
Um…
I feel really bad that, like,
Khloé is feeling really, like,
that we don't care or, like, do anything.
I mean, I feel like we just need
to, like… do something nice for her,
like, even if it's, like,
a fun spa day at home
or go get her favorite food.
Like, just a fun something for her,
to where she feels like we care.
[Kourtney] Yeah.
I know you're contemplating
-going to Vegas.
-Mm-hm.
But I really feel like
you should really consider going
'cause Khloé really wants to go.
[Kourtney] Mm-hm.
I want her to have a fun time,
and if she's in the mood to go,
you know, have a great time,
like, she's definitely been there for me.
But I also have to do what's best for me.
I'm not saying I'm not going.
I just don't want to send him
the wrong message
because, like, he'll take any little thing
and run with it.
And I feel like I did my own thing
for my birthday, like, I went to Iceland,
and I don't wanna always have
to do everything together.
I guess I just feel bad for Khloé.
I really don't know
if I feel like going to Vegas,
but I do know that Khloé
really wants to go,
and I think she needs a fun night out.
So, it's just hard
because I really just
don't know what to do.
[upbeat techno music]
-[Scott] Yo.
-[Khloé] Hello.
-[Kourtney] What up?
-Kourt, this is Scott.
-[Kourtney] What up? What up?
-What up, girl?
You're looking too good up in here.
-[Kourtney] I know.
-Damn.
-[Kourtney chuckles]
-Oh, no.
I'm about to try
to holla at this chick, ya dig?
Good luck.
I've decided to go to Vegas
for Scott's birthday
because Khloé really wants to go
and she needs a fun night out,
and I think that's, like,
one of the ways I can be there for her.
We are going to Vegas, baby.
Scott's birthday.
[giggles]
♪ You're not invited ♪
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Yeah!
[Scott] Feel like every day
is my birthday.
Like, you know what I'm saying?
[Scott] All right, I'll see y'all
on the other side, boy.
[Scott cackles]
[Khloé] So, Scott, what's the plan?
[Scott] I'd like to have a little, like,
pre-game sex with Kourtney
before we go to dinner.
[Khloé] Okay. Perfect.
[Scott] Then a little birthday sex,
like, after I'm in the club.
-[Khloé] Okay.
-And then just--
[Malika] Any plans
that might include us, or no?
-Oh, no, nothing involves any of you.
-[Malika] Okay, just checking.
You're all just here just so
I could be with Kourtney.
[Khloé] Dear Lord Jesus, please make…
Have us have a safe flight to Vegas.
In Jesus' name, we pray. Amen.
-[Malika] Amen.
-Jesus' name. Amen.
If at some point this plane
started going down,
-could we make out or have sex?
-[Kourtney] No.
-[Malika] It's your last shot.
-[Scott] Your last shot
at everything, 30,000 feet up,
you're never gonna have
anything ever again?
-You still wouldn't?
-Nope.
-Still wouldn't.
-This chick is solid.
[upbeat music]
-Got a lot of good energy up in here.
-[man] Uh-huh.
-All right.
-Happy birthday.
-Happy birthday, Scott.
-Happy birthday, buddy.
[man] Not everybody
get excited all at once.
[chuckles]
[Scott] What is Khloé doing?
She has her earphones on?
[Kourtney] Yeah.
Khlo, what… what…
like, this is what goes on?
You're just, like, at my birthday dinner
and just, like,
having a whole other, like--
Are you really
in my conversation right now?
'Cause I have not bothered
one person here.
Obviously, that's the problem,
I want you to
'cause you're, like,
the life of the party.
I am the life of the party,
but right now, I'm doing something else.
And then when I get off,
then I'll be the life of the party again.
All right, let me know when you're ready.
Right, so I'll let you know.
Come on, dear… Come here.
-No, no, no.
-This is my birthday.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
-[laughter]
-Do I have to move down
to the end of the table?
I know Kourt is really concerned
about sending the wrong message to Scott,
but I think all of us,
and Kourtney herself,
would feel really weird
if Scott actually stopped
flirting with her.
[Khloé] I mean, look at them.
They're so comfortable around each other.
And I don't care
if they're together or not,
this is just gonna be their dynamic.
[Scott] Man, this is one
miserable [bleep] table.
We're chilling. What do you want us to do,
dance on the table?
I mean, if I had it my way, yeah.
[Scott] Should we go to the club?
Whoo! Vegas!
[camera shutters clicking]
[women cheering]
[crowd clamoring]
[upbeat music]
Everybody say, "Happy birthday, Scott."
[all] Happy birthday!
[crowd cheering]
[dance music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
[Kourtney] Ah, ah! Ah, ah, ah, ah!
I'll get her. I'll break her down.
-You all right, Mom?
-Yeah.
Do you wanna make out?
I'm so happy that Scott and I
are getting along so well
and that we're having
so much fun just being silly.
And I think I was maybe
overanalyzing the situation
because there's no reason
we just can't all have fun together.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] You look really good.
"Thanks, Mom, you look good, too."
-[Rob] You look good, too, Mom.
-[Kris chuckles]
Do you want something to eat, Rob?
[Rob] Uh, I'm all right.
[Kris] There's a chicken
and broccoli plate here for you.
-Doesn't that look yummy?
-[Penelope] Mm-hm.
So healthy.
Thanks.
[Kris] You want another napkin, Boo?
Let's put it like this.
This is what I used to do to Rob
when he was little.
Yeah.
[Kris chuckles]
[Kris] Um…
So have you talked to Khloé lately?
-No.
-[Kris] Hm.
You're her best friend.
And she hasn't talked to you
in a really long time.
Doubt I'm her best friend.
You're her best friend.
-You really are.
-[chuckles]
She loves you so much
and she misses her brother.
Well, she should be careful
what she says and…
'cause she does this all to herself.
I get that you're in
this new relationship,
that's amazing for you.
-Mm-hm.
-But it doesn't mean
that you can't still be close
to all of us.
That's how life works.
No, I know, but y'all aren't, like,
that welcoming of this relationship,
so you can't expect me to just be like,
"Oh, let's all hang out
and everything's cool and fine."
It's not that easy.
[Kris] Khloé has always
been there for Rob,
and she needs him now more than ever.
[Kris] So, this is his turn
to be there for her.
My hope is just that Rob
realizes how important this is
and that he makes it right.
[upbeat music]
I get that you're in
this new relationship,
that's amazing for you.
-Mm-hm.
-But it doesn't mean
that you can't still be close
to all of us.
That's how life works.
No, I know, but y'all aren't, like,
that welcoming of this relationship,
so you can't expect me to just be like,
"Oh, let's all hang out
and everything's cool and fine."
It's not that easy.
Don't you think that having a baby
is one of the most amazing things
that can happen to you in your life?
And that's what you wanna
share with everybody,
and, like, the family
and let us share the journey with you.
It's nice
if you still have a bond with your family
because we all love you so much.
And I want you and Khloé to be okay
and happy and connected.
It's your sister.
[smacks lips]
Mom…
You know, she's had a hard year
and going through…
a bad time with all the Lamar stuff still.
And she couldn't need her family
more than she does now.
And that includes you.
So, if you made an effort
just to kind of mend the feelings
that are hurt
and just try
to get back on track with everyone,
it would be so easy
if you would just make the first move.
No, I know.
I get it.
I'll reach out to Khloé.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] I'm really happy
that Rob is gonna reach out to Khloé.
And I think once they're reunited,
it's gonna be good.
[line ringing]
[Khloé] No [bleep] way.
Who the [bleep] is this?
Uh, it's your brother.
[Khloé] No [bleep] way!
You finally called me.
-How is everything?
-I'm good, I'm good.
I'm just moving along
-and I'm--
-[Khloé] How's Chyna doing?
-Getting bigger and bigger.
-[Khloé] That's a good thing.
I was just checking to see how you are
and see if I could see you soon.
[Khloé] What?
This is the best phone call ever!
-Yeah. Yeah.
-[Khloé] When do you wanna see me?
Uh, maybe tomorrow or this week or…
[Khloé] Oh, my god, that soon?
This is so exciting.
But will you really and don't just say it?
Yes, yes, yes.
[Khloé] Okay, I don't know why
you've been avoiding me,
but there's really no reason
and Dad would not be happy
with either one of us right now.
I agree.
-[Khloé] I love you.
-[Rob] Love you.
-[Khloé] Bye.
-Bye.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] This is a great backyard
for a party.
[Kim] I know.
So, I had Khloé's pajamas
dropped off at her house.
So she could just wear them here.
Cute.
[Kim] Kourtney and I
wanna do something for Khloé.
Something super chill at the house.
Just like a little pampering Khloé moment
so that she feels loved.
-What the hell is going on?
-Hey, Khlo.
[Kim] Hi.
[Khloé] Why are we here
and why are we all wearing these,
the outfits?
You're my second and most honored sister.
Heir of all I possess.
-Who's your first?
-It's Kim.
She's my first sister that I've ever had.
But you're the honored sister,
the heir of all I possess.
The "heir of all you possess"?
[Kourtney] It's just from a book
that I read to the kids.
-Oh, I thought you meant…
-No one takes it
-too literally…
-…you are leaving me
-everything in your will.
-…literally or seriously, okay?
I doubt you're the type of person
who has a will.
-[Kim] What?
-Kourtney seems like,
"When you die, you just die.
No one should care about,
like, material possessions."
[Khloé] No, really, what's happening?
[Kourtney] I just wanted you
to feel adored…
-Mm-hm.
-…admired, loved, and cared about.
[Khloé] I do feel… but why?
What happened?
Well, what hasn't happened?
-Yeah.
-True story.
That is the question.
True story.
[Kim] You've been through a lot lately.
You just re-filed for divorce.
[Kim] And even though you act strong
and, like, together,
it's just, like, sometimes you need TLC.
This is a pampering session
to just keep you going.
Thank you, guys.
This just shows that, you know,
my sisters do love me
and they are aware
of everything I'm going through.
I do not have a clue
what I would do without them.
[Khloé] When you have people
that you know you can depend on,
even though you're going through [bleep],
you just know everything's
gonna be okay eventually.
Do you guys wanna know who the hottest guy
-in the world is?
-Who?
[Khloé] There's this guy
that became famous
because of his mug shot.
What if we find him
and try to set him up with Khloé?
[Khloé] Like, he's just, like,
such a hot man.
Kourtney, how hot is this guy?
Ooh, he is hot.
What did he go to jail for,
is the question?
"Single charge.
Felon in possession of a firearm.
He had to go
to a transitional housing facility."
-Honestly…
-[Kourtney] Damn!
…having a man on house arrest
is the best man to have.
They can't go anywhere.
I'll be Bonnie. He can be Clyde.
Ooh!
[upbeat music]
[Scott] This doesn't seem that safe.
[Kourtney] You could probably do
a good butt thing.
-[Velcro ripping]
-[Scott] Oh… Oh, yeah.
[Kourtney] I'm sweating like a beast.
Okay, and one. Two.
Pull it out now, three.
I think Don told me he does Pilates.
-[clanking]
-Whoa!
What in the [bleep]?
Could've taken my head off.
Who knew Pilates was so dangerous?
What are you doing now?
Do you even think
you're doing anything right?
Oh, [bleep].
Looks like you're about to give birth.
Well, that's what I thought
these were for.
Here we go, coming round.
Mason number three or four,
where are you? Hello?
I took Scott's advice to heart
and got my mom a Pilates machine.
It'll be great for my mom.
And it's actually something
that I've really been wanting to do.
So it's good for both of us.
-Feeling good.
-Good.
[Kris] What in the world?
Hey, Mom.
-I can't believe…
-[Kourtney] Do you know Don?
…you guys did this.
Do you know Don does Pilates?
And Pilates is gentle on your body,
but it's also such a great workout.
[Kris] Oh, my god, fantastic.
This is supposed to transform your body.
But don't forget, you got to take it easy.
[Kris] Wait, look at the…
you put your feet in these.
-[laughs]
-Oh, this is by Balanced Body?
-Thank you so much!
-[Scott] Yeah.
Your body is gonna be so on "fuegs."
-I'm excited.
-This is where your new chapter
of your life starts.
-Right here in this garage.
-In this garage.
[Kris] I push myself pretty hard,
-so I appreciate it.
-[Scott] Yeah.
And this is something
we could do together.
I may not be able to go zero to 60,
but this is the perfect balance
for my body.
[Kris] It's fantastic that I have a family
that really wants me
to be the best that I can be.
And I think that the fact
that they've gone this far
to surprise me means a lot.
This is so cool.
I have, like, my own Pilates studio.
I could charge you to come over.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Well, well, well.
-[Rob] Gabbana.
-What do we have here?
[Khloé] I got dressed up for you.
Got my whole arm wet for you.
[Khloé] No, two hands.
-Wait, I'm wet.
-It's okay.
[Rob groans]
[Khloé] Oh, Robbie.
You could give a normal hug.
Like, two hands is fine.
[Khloé] Would you like to sit
in my office?
So serious. What's happening?
I've missed you.
Well, why won't you even look at me?
Talk to me.
[Rob groans]
[upbeat music]
I've missed you.
Well, why won't you even look at me?
Talk to me.
[Rob groans]
So I heard you and Scott
are having a baby or something.
-Rob, don't be weird.
-Okay.
[Khloé] I've been calling you,
I've texted you.
[laughs]
No, you have not.
Do you want to look at our text messages?
I'm pretty sure the last text messages,
uh, you blocked me.
That was when we were fighting.
And then I said, "I love you, I miss you,
I hope Chyna's having a good pregnancy."
-Yeah.
-And then you wrote,
"I love you, too," and that was it.
-When is she supposed to have a baby?
-In November.
You excited or nervous?
I'm excited, I'm not nervous.
[dog barks in distance]
Um, so, like, the more
you guys come around,
the easier it's gonna get,
but if the more you guys stay away,
it's just gonna stay this weird place.
-Or even make it weirder.
-[Rob] Yeah.
I just feel like the situation
is just, like,
not very welcoming for her to feel like,
"Oh, I should go be BFF with so and so."
No, I think it should be natural anyway,
but--
You know, obviously, I hang out
with her all the time, or--
I know it's gonna be different,
like, obviously you have her.
And even if that's your…
like, you don't have to bring her around,
like, that's totally your choice, but…
it's also not fair for you
to, like, eliminate yourself
from our lives.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Like, my life at least.
Like, you and I had such
a close relationship,
and then for you just to,
like, disappear, that's like…
No, I wouldn't wanna do that.
And I would like to be there for you.
Well, good.
I just want everyone to be happy, so,
you know, I need everyone else to be,
like, on the same page.
We'll get everyone together.
[tapping on table]
[chuckles]
[Khloé] It feels so good
to have my brother back and in my life.
Just, I feel so much more safe and just,
like, at peace that he is here
and someone that I could talk to
and call and lean on,
and just be that silly,
goofy brother that I always have.
[Khloé] Me not talking to you
for months, that's weird.
-Yeah.
-Like, that's never happened
ever in my life before.
Well…
I love you.
[chuckles softly]
I love you, too.
I'm really tired.
Want to take a nap together?
-Mm…
-[both laugh]
[Kim] Next on Keeping Up
with the Kardashians…
[Kourtney] I'm at the Women
of the Year Awards.
I just can't get on the stage and talk.
What would be your dream birthday party
that we could all do
to celebrate with you?
Why doesn't everyone
just, like, call me and wish me
-a happy birthday this year?
-No.
I'm so glad you invited…
I was invited, I was like, "Yay."
Hey, Rob. How's Chyna?
[Rob] Um, I'm out of her house
and we're not living together.