-[Khloé] Hi, Mom.
-Hi.
[Kris] This is so great.
Lamar's recovery has been a miracle.
He is now getting out of the hospital
and he is able to move into his own home.
[Kris] This is such a great space.
[Khloé] I got these texts from Caitlyn.
She tells me to get a life and to shut up.
I'm like, "You shut up
and you get a [bleep] life."
[Caitlyn on phone] You don't go on
Howard Stern and call me a liar.
You were her dad
since she was five years old.
So tell me about you.
I'm a 32-year-old man that lives alone.
-[Scott] We'll see where things go.
-[Kris] Where's Scott?
[Kourtney]
Scott and Tyga have been hanging out
at his house. All day and night.
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney]
It pisses me off that people like Tyga,
who should know better,
that are close to our family,
that don't just, like,
find some other friends.
It's not like Kanye's
calling him and saying,
"Come to the studio," every night,
"Come to my show," you know?
It's Tyga calling him
to hang out and go to parties.
[Kris] Yeah.
I think Kourtney has to accept the fact
that it's really Scott
that she should be mad at,
and she can't keep putting
the blame on other people.
[Kourtney] So, it just…
-It still bothers me.
-Yeah.
You guys, Baby Yeezys
are gonna be launched in August.
-The black ones and the…
-[Khloé] Oh, my god, how cute.
…like, original blue and cream mix.
[Kim] And so I was like,
"Well, have you guys thought about pink?"
-So, "You guys are gonna be…
-I think pink would be so cute.
…wearing them all in the show?"
"The new ones in the show?"
Kanye is having
his Yeezy Season Three fashion show
at Madison Square Garden.
Kanye really wants the whole family there,
and I do too.
And I think it's really cool
that he's opening up
a fashion show to the public,
which has never been done before.
So I can't wait for all of us to go
and just have a good time.
[Kris] I was thinking
about getting a private plane
on Monday morning.
-[Kourtney] I'm going with Kim on Tuesday.
-Honey, we got a plane.
[chuckles]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
-[phone rings]
-[Khloé] Hello?
Hola, Lamar.
Hold on. You wanna say hi
to Kylie and Kourt?
Hi, Lam.
[Lamar] Hey, Kourt.
Miss you.
[Lamar] Miss you too.
[Khloé] How was therapy today?
[Lamar] It was good. I ran
on the treadmill for 10 minutes today.
No, you didn't.
[Lamar] Yes, I did.
That's so good.
Lamar, that's awesome. Congratulations.
[Khloé] Lamar is constantly progressing,
getting better,
and I'm so, so proud of him.
I know a lot of this stuff
is probably really frustrating for Lamar,
but it just takes time.
And I am a full believer
in his ability to fully recover.
-[Lamar] All right.
-Okay.
I'll just talk to you later.
-[Lamar] Bye-bye.
-Bye.
That's crazy.
Right, Kylie?
-[Kylie] What?
-Okurrr.
[clucking]
Don't be scared.
Okurrr.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] What are you doing in here?
[Khloé] Ooh, the leopard.
[Kim] The leo-pard.
We are, like, in the same color tones.
Uh, it's called black.
[chuckles]
-There's no tone.
-And… No, your brown boots.
Oh. Yes, Gina.
-[Kim] Yes.
-Mm.
[Khloé] What's going on?
[Kim] Nothing. Just getting ready
and packing for New York.
[Khloé]
You're gonna need that jacket there.
At… Like, I wasn't prepared
to really leave the house just yet.
-Mm-hm.
-And I don't really wanna be seen.
But I feel like
all the coats will cover me.
-[Khloé] The coats.
-And it's all about just,
like, hiding under coats.
I mean, you're really not that big.
[Khloé]
How exciting about the show, though.
I'm so excited.
It's supposed to be so good.
It's at Madison Square Garden.
So crazy.
[Kim] Yeah, you have to come.
What am I gonna do,
just, like, come and, like,
leave Lam, and, like, I have Kocktails--
No. Like, bring him.
[chuckles]
I can't just, like,
bring Lamar to New York.
Why not?
[Khloé]
Like, he has not been in public yet.
He hasn't been on a plane
or been around people.
Like, it's just way more anxiety for me,
I think, than for anybody else.
[Khloé] Lamar has not traveled
since his accident.
Lamar has not been to New York in years.
New York is
a very negative place for Lamar.
I am just flooded with anxiety.
[sighs]
It's a lot.
When I was sitting there
with him at his house,
he was like, "Honestly,
like, Kanye's music,
like, helped me so much.
Like, that's when I realized, like, okay,
I could start, like, thinking again
and things were coming back to me
and I could start, like, articulating it."
[Khloé] He loves that. He's always, like,
"Ah, Kanye saved me."
That's so sweet.
[Kim] There was a moment when Lamar
couldn't really express himself
and he couldn't really talk,
but he could hear
what we were saying to him.
And Kanye really felt, like,
we can cure him through music,
like, we can get him to talk.
He would go to the hospital,
and he would, like, rap and sing.
And I think Lamar started
to get his, like, function back
and started to talk,
once he started to listen
to a lot of music.
[Khloé] You're doing so well.
Good job.
I think Lamar wants to go
and support Kanye,
and this will be just
such a powerful moment for them, I think.
But, like, what's the plan?
[Kim]
Like, shouldn't he get out at some point?
[Khloé] No. I mean, I'm doing Kocktails
because I wasn't planning on going.
[Kim] Well, see if he even wants to go.
[upbeat music]
[Kylie] How's your app going and stuff?
[Kourtney] Good, I think.
[Kylie] How's Scott?
I don't think he's been okay lately.
After his hanging out with Tyga
and all that.
So, I almost wanna, like, call Tyga
and just literally go off on him.
I have a tendency to, like,
shift some blame from, like, Scott
onto the people that are around him,
to where, like, I'm never be able
to be cool with you again. So…
[Kylie] I mean…
I don't know about going off on him
'cause he's really sensitive.
[Kylie] I know Kourtney gets mad
at Tyga sometimes.
But Tyga always feels like
he's in the middle of Scott and Kourtney.
I think I should just say, like,
"Do you ever think about how your actions,
like, affect other people?"
Like, "Stop being so selfish."
[upbeat music]
[Malika] What's up?
Wait, please, please,
I like my toes licked but not by dogs.
I hate when she does that too.
You wanna like it, but you're like,
"You're a dog. Ugh."
No, because she has a soft tongue too.
Babe, you got a good tongue.
-[Khloé] Yeah, it's bizarre.
-I'm just saying.
[dog whines]
I think you should get Lamar a dog.
-Not a puppy.
-No, no, no.
He doesn't need to take care of anything.
It just needs to be, like, a companion.
So, obviously,
Kanye's fashion show is, like, known,
and the whole family
keeps talking about it
and talking about it.
And I was never planning on going.
-Who's gonna watch Lamar?
-[Khloé] Exactly.
So then Kim was like,
"Well, why don't you bring Lamar?"
And I was like, "Bring Lamar?"
And, mind you, I just found out
that it's for, like, 14,000 people.
It's just a lot to handle no matter what.
[Malika] It is very natural for you
to be protective.
You should be, but you also have to let
the reins go a little bit,
to see how he's progressing.
You won't know that until you try.
Yeah, of course. But Lamar's…
It's like when you're starving
and you go to a restaurant,
don't you order way more
than you could eat?
His eyes are bigger
than his stomach right now.
[Khloé] I'm just trying to protect him.
[Malika] I'm thinking on the other side is
think about what his life has been like.
He's been very secluded.
I think it's time.
I actually agree with Kim.
[Khloé] I am really overprotective,
and I know how much Lamar wants
to go to New York.
But, still, I'm scared,
'cause I don't know how Lamar's
gonna handle the situation.
I really just have to decide
what I think is best…
for Lam at the end of the day.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] Hello.
[Kris] Hi.
I've had, like, a headache
since the middle of the night last night.
It's really weird.
[Kris] Did you hear
that Scott has an appearance
at 1 Oak in New York while we're there?
[Kim] Yeah, so he called me
because he wanted a ride on the plane.
So I was, like, "Yeah, for sure, come."
And then, like,
you know, I can maybe, like,
hang out with him, keep an eye on him,
just, like, help him with, like, sobriety.
If we're hanging out,
he's not gonna, like, be wasted.
-Yeah.
-And I'm like, "We'll all hang out
and go to dinner when we land,
and, like, be busy,"
so that he's not, you know,
in, like, party mode.
Yeah.
He did say he wanted to go
to the fashion show,
-so…
-Oh, good.
[Kim] You know, it was really important
for us to invite Scott
because I want him to feel like
if he needs to feel busy,
that it's with us instead of partying
and resorting back to maybe,
like, unhealthy behavior.
So I wanna invite him
to all the things that we're doing.
-[Kim] Look that way.
-Oh.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-Maybe not your head at that angle.
-Oh.
-No, you can be on your phone.
No, no, no, just, like, middle. Yeah.
What are we doing?
[upbeat music]
Oh, I love these hoops.
Are we kidding?
-I know.
-Finally.
Who do I have to blow
to get these earrings?
[woman 1] Hmm. I'll find out.
[Khloé]
Okay. "How are you? I'm so excited."
Um…
[woman 2] Are you starting to get nervous?
-You are.
-[Khloé] Again. I am.
I wanna ask him,
"So how do you feel about Caitlyn?"
-[woman 2] Are you guys better?
-No. I haven't spoken to her.
After she said,
"You little piece of [bleep]."
"[bleep] you. Dah-dah-dah, I'm upset."
And then she's like, "I think
we need to have a girl's dinner
and have a little hug."
I'm like, "Nuh-uh."
It really… Like, when you say
you're sorry,
it actually is a sign of strength.
It's not a weakness.
You could just say "I'm sorry."
Caitlyn is upset with me
because of my Howard Stern interview
which I sincerely
don't understand what I did wrong.
All I ever said was the truth,
and the truth is
that Caitlyn was never fully honest
about her transitioning. End of story.
I just have so much going on
in my life right now,
and I just don't, I don't need
to deal with this.
[knocks on door]
-Come in.
-[man] We're ready to go to set.
-I'm ready.
-[woman] And we're walking.
[Khloé and woman] And we're walking.
[Khloé] Hello.
[upbeat music]
[electronic music]
[car horns honking]
[camera shutter clicking]
Let me see, Kourt.
Have a look, please. Have a good look.
Yeah.
Oh, my. Oh, my.
[Kanye whoops]
-Hey. Hey, look at my crew.
-[Caitlyn] Hey.
Come on, I need a picture.
-[Kanye] It's… Hey.
-Yeah, here we go.
[Kim] Caitlyn just got to New York,
and she's in her fitting,
and it's really exciting.
I just really hope
that Khloé and Lamar can come.
Kanye and I both really want them
to be a part of this.
-[Kanye] Kourtney, come here, come here.
-[Caitlyn] Come on, Kourt.
-Kourtney, I made that for you.
-Yes.
Well, but it's coming home with me.
-[Kanye whoops]
-You can borrow it.
[Kim] This is the first time that Kanye
is really dressing the whole family.
He and Olivier from Balmain
collaborated and made these pieces that…
They're like one-of-a-kind.
And I think it's, like, so cool
that they put so much work
into really getting looks
for every single family member.
[upbeat music]
-This one's the best one.
-[Jonathan] Okay, that's cool.
-Yo, yo… yo, get…
-Let her change--
Yeah, but I deserve it. I deserve it.
You deserve it
'cause you went to design school.
[Kanye] Let's photograph this next look.
[indistinct chatter]
[Kim] I don't want to show my knees.
[light music]
I just gave birth
a few months ago to Saint,
and I'm not really ready
to go out in public yet,
'cause there's always so much pressure
under the public eye,
but I would never miss
Kanye's show for the world.
I'm so excited for the show.
[loud, overlapping chatter]
Who knew you'd be so helpful
for me in life.
Got to take care of each other.
I never thought in a million years…
-You'll like that one.
-that I'd be sharing makeup with Cait.
[loud, overlapping chatter]
[upbeat music]
[lively music]
[Corey] You look pretty.
Thanks, babe.
-Hi.
-[Kris] Hi. Hi, sweetie.
-How are you?
-[Caitlyn] Hi.
-[Corey] What's up?
-Hi.
-What's going on, man?
-How are you?
-[Kourtney] Okay.
-[Kris] Great.
[Caitlyn] I haven't been
to the house in a while,
and you've done a nice job
with everything.
[indistinct chatter]
-With my house?
-[Caitlyn] Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh. Where's Scott?
He's here.
-He's at the hotel.
-[Kris] Where?
-Doing what?
-Hanging out.
[Kourtney]
Kim has invited him to every single thing.
She's, like, "Do you wanna come
to the album thing?
Do you wanna…" I already…
I wrote Kim days ago and said,
"No Tyga, no Scott at the show."
-[Jonathan] She invited both.
-Of course.
[all laughing]
But Kim's, like, "What do you care?
Just invite Scott to stuff
if it's gonna, like,
keep him out of trouble.
Better him hanging out
with all of us than…
-[Jonathan] Getting into…
-Whatever."
-There's no rhyme or reason at this point.
-[Kourtney] So… Yeah.
[Jonathan]
If he wants to be in trouble, he will be.
Exactly.
[Kourtney]
Kim may have the best intentions,
but that doesn't mean
that it's going to go
the way that she's thinking it's gonna go.
And I'm really just hoping
that there's no drama
because we're really there
to support Kanye.
Hey, you want to go to the bathroom?
I think I'm good.
-[Kourtney] I have to go to the bathroom.
-Okay. Let's go.
[Caitlyn chuckles]
You guys know that I've peed
in the Delano lobby.
-[Jonathan] When?
-[Kris] I've heard this story
a million times,
and I wouldn't keep repeating it.
And I peed in my BMW
because I had seven ice teas.
[Kris] No wonder you couldn't sell it.
[upbeat music]
How was therapy today?
Good.
You're just chilling, right?
You're… You don't have anxiety. Only I do.
Great.
[light music]
I've decided to go to New York with Lamar
'cause I think this is
something he truly wants to do,
and at the end of the day,
I want Lamar to be happy.
I still feel
a ton of anxiety and pressure,
but if this makes him happy,
and if I could keep him safe,
then that's a match made in heaven.
[Kim]
Just relax. I got the perfect outfit.
-I've got it custom-made for you, okay?
-Thank you.
-[Kim] Okay, relax. Calm down.
-He said thank you.
-Have fun. Okay. I got to go.
-[Khloé] Okay. Love you. Bye.
[Kim] Bye.
I'm nervous. Like, this is nerve-racking.
You haven't been in public ever.
I have more anxiety than you do, I'm sure,
but it's because I don't think
you understand.
I can understand.
[Khloé] I know. I know you wanna go.
I know all that, but it's a lot.
That's all I'm saying.
[sighs]
[upbeat music]
[Kim]
Oh, my god, I miss being in New York.
Knock, knock.
[knock on door]
[Caitlyn] Whew.
-[Caitlyn] Look at that.
-You know La La.
-Oh, yes. How are you doing?
-Oh, hi.
Good to see you.
-How are you?
-It's so nice to see you.
-[Caitlyn] Nice to see you. Hey, baby.
-[Kim] Hi.
It is hot in here.
Well, after Christmas,
it's so good that you're here in New York
so you have all these coats
-you can actually wear.
-[Kim] I know. I know.
That's what… I was just telling La La.
She asked where I got this,
and I was like,
"One of my Christmas presents."
-Yeah.
-[Kim] You look nice.
Well, thank you.
How's the show coming along?
[Kim] Really good, really hectic.
Lamar's coming into town.
-Right.
-[Kim] Isn't that exciting?
[Caitlyn] Extraordinarily exciting.
[Kim]
Her husband played with him for years.
-Yeah, right.
-[La La] Yeah, he was.
He saw something on the news about you,
and he was a little confused,
so I had to, like, explain it to him.
I was like, "Well, it's Caitlyn now."
And he was like, "What?"
I know Khloé tried to explain it to him
a couple of times,
but at that point, I don't think
he was getting anything.
[Kim]
Yeah. Have you talked to Khloé at all?
She hasn't been talking to me lately.
[Kim] I know. I was gonna say,
-didn't you guys get into a big fight?
-I know. Yeah.
[tense music]
[Kim] This is a really big week.
Lamar's already dealing with the pressure
of being in an environment where there's
a lot of people.
And this is, you know,
it might be really difficult for him.
And Khloé and Caitlyn are
kind of on the outs.
So everyone has to put
our differences aside
for this week and just be cool.
She called me a liar with Howard Stern.
[Caitlyn] I didn't lie to anybody.
I hope Khloé will spend some time with me.
And she didn't reach out to me at all
at that time either.
-I mean…
-And she has a big hang-up
that "she's the kid,"
so the adult should reach out to the kid,
or you're the one transitioning,
so you should have reached out to her.
It's just how she feels.
I just hope that Caitlyn and Khloé
get a chance to move past the drama
because otherwise,
it could just be a disaster.
[Kim] It's not wrong or right,
but I just think that, like,
at some point, talk to Khloé.
[light music]
[Kourtney] Hey.
[background chatter]
[Benjamin] Where were you guys today?
-[Simon] Kourtney, can I say?
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Simon]
Kourtney got, like, ambushed by Tyga
and, like, five other men
who came around her
and were like, "I hope there's not beef."
And Kourtney was like,
"No, we're fine. We're not fine,
but we are fine."
Tyga's been hanging out with Scott.
They've been going to clubs together.
-[Jonathan] Hi. Hi.
-Yeah. Hi.
-Hollywood.
-Why Hollywood?
-[Simon] What did you get to drink?
-[Kourtney] I don't know.
-I might just have a beer.
-Whoa. It's that time?
Thank you.
[indistinct chatter]
Where's Scott?
-At the hotel.
-[Jonathan] Oh, why doesn't he hang out?
When is he staying till? Tell me
just so I know when the misery ends.
I don't know.
Where'd he go last night?
I'm not sure.
[Kourtney]
He was writing me all night, like,
"Can we watch a movie? Can we hang out?"
And he's like, "If I hang out with you
then I won't go out."
Like, I can't, it can't be on me.
[Kourtney] I can't live my life worried
that my actions could cause Scott
to spiral.
I just really need to live my life for me
and hope that he's doing
the best that he can do.
[indistinct chatter]
It's so good.
-[Nicole] Is it warm?
-No, it's so good.
-Cheers.
[Kourtney]
This is why my voice is annoying.
Because when I talk screaming talk…
-"Yeah, guys. Like…"
-[Jonathan] Ha.
-Oh, my god.
-[all laugh]
[bleep] kills me.
[laughs]
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Okurrr.
[Kim] Do you think
people will think I dyed my hair?
[make-up artist] Mm.
All the white people will.
The black people will know.
[chuckles]
-[Khloé] Kim.
-[Kim] Yeah?
Uh, one thing, Lam is really nervous
about meeting Caitlyn.
[Kim] Well, I had a whole talk
with Caitlyn yesterday about it.
-[Khloé] About Lam?
-And I was just like,
"You know, you have to, like,
take it in baby steps."
Like, he… I don't know.
You know,
he could definitely comprehend it.
[Kim] But, you know, he might not be able
to grasp it all at once.
He said to me the other day,
"Bruce", something.
And I had to say there is
no Bruce anymore, it's Caitlyn.
[Khloé] After our New York fight,
we, like, have not spoken.
[tense music]
I don't really care
to see Caitlyn right now
because the last time
me and Caitlyn spoke,
we were fighting over text.
I'm already so nervous about
how Lamar's gonna handle the situation.
I feel very overwhelmed.
So this'll be fun, seeing her today.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Ready?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Ready.
-Are you ready?
-As ready as I'm gonna be.
[Lamar] Your hair is strutting, Mama.
[Khloé and Lamar chuckle]
[Khloé] Ooh.
-[Lamar] Hey, Keeks.
-[woman] You look so good.
[Kim] You look so good.
[Kim] Today is the big day.
We're all getting ready
for the Yeezy show.
I am so excited that Khloé and Lamar
pulled through and came to New York.
I really think
that Lamar's gonna enjoy being out,
and it'll make him feel
super normal again.
[Khloé] Yeah, Lam,
check yourself out in that mirror.
Northy, gorgeous.
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] How do you feel being in New York?
-Actually, great.
-That's good.
I ain't been in New York for…
-years.
-A long time.
Oh.
Is that paparazzi?
-[both] Mm-hm.
-Yo, what the [bleep]
is he doing, man?
You're going out with that?
No, I'm just doing it on purpose, just to…
Why would I give them a shot?
I can't even think right now.
I'm stressing out. I can tell.
-[Lamar] Mm.
-Ready?
[Lamar] Nothing's stressing me out
on Kanye's day today.
Ain't about me.
[Khloé]
If you ever get uncomfortable or anything,
you'll tell me, right?
[inhales sharply]
This is a social atmosphere.
-I know but--
-Social scene, baby.
If it gets too much for you.
You haven't…
been around this many people
in a long time.
I wanna make sure your brain,
like, doesn't get,
aah, like, in overdrive.
I'm too smooth for that [bleep].
-Oh, my god.
-You know what I mean?
[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] This is so exciting, guys.
Now, he is actually performing--
No, he's playing the whole album
while the show's going on.
-Oh, I got you.
-[Kourtney] Hey, Pops, guys.
Ooh, I'm gonna cover myself.
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[Kylie] [bleep]
Okay. We're safe. We're safe.
[Kylie] Scott said he's not coming?
Nope. He just said.
-[sniffs]
-Why?
"I don't think so."
"I'm not making more drama
and wanna be out of the press."
[Kylie] What did he say?
"Uh, it's just going to say
me and you are back."
-[male friend] Is he out here?
-Yeah.
[tense music]
[Kourtney]
I think Kim will be disappointed
that Scott isn't coming to Kanye's show.
And, you know,
he always has a million excuses,
and sometimes,
it's like it's too overwhelming.
And, like, I get it that it's a huge day,
but we're all here to support Kanye.
I'm excited to see L.O.
Ah.
-I forgot about that.
-I forgot about that, guys.
[electronic music]
It's just Kanye Legendary.
[Melanie]
Should I just pretend this is Kanye?
[Kris]
No. No, that's why when you said cream--
Put some holes in it.
[Kris] When you said cream…
[Kim] Babe, do you like your blonde?
[Kanye] I do. I love it.
I can't get comfortable.
I have to go, like…
[Khloé] Hi.
-[Kendall] Lammy. Oh, Lammy.
-[Lamar] Hey.
-[Kendall] Oh, my god. Family.
-Oh, my god.
-Hi. You look so cute.
-[Kourtney] Kanye, I want you to know
we're very hyped.
We're singing all of your songs.
[Kourtney] We know every word.
-[Kendall] I love you so much.
-[Kanye] Thank you so much.
-How you doing?
-Hello, gorge.
There is…
[indistinct chatter]
-[Caitlyn] I love you, buddy.
-[Lamar] I love you too.
-[Caitlyn] I'm so happy you're here.
-[Lamar] Thank you.
Made my day.
[Khloé]
This is Lamar's first time out in public.
This is the first time
Lamar is meeting Caitlyn.
I feel very overwhelmed for Lamar.
So I don't have time
for all this Caitlyn drama
between her and I.
I'm just gonna let bygones be bygones
and try to get rid
of all this negative [bleep].
-[Khloé] You okay?
-[Lamar] Yeah.
Our whole point is that
even if, like,
even if they're super positive,
-you just don't have to answer anyone.
-[Khloé] You don't have to talk
-to everyone.
-You know, just, like…
It's not, like,
interview time or anything.
-You know what I mean?
-[Lamar] Yeah.
[Kanye]
Hey, guys, we got, we got to start.
[Kim] All right, we got to start.
Get Mom and we'll all walk together.
This is the most epic day.
[Khloé] I've been worried
about so many other details
when it comes to this New York trip.
And all of a sudden, I realize,
that we really are
at Madison Square Garden.
[Kanye]
Okay, everybody gotta come this way.
This is, like, for 15,000 people,
and that's a lot for Lamar to handle.
It's a lot for me to handle.
I'm just incredibly anxious
and nervous, like,
"Aah. There are too many people."
Like, because it's too loud.
Like, I don't know.
-[Kendall] This way.
-Okay, go.
Come on, Lammy.
[Khloé] Lammy, you just stay with Ye.
-[Kanye] Pasquale?
-[Pasquale] Yeah?
-[Kanye] Are we good?
-[Pasquale] Yeah, good to go.
[Kanye] Okay, go ahead, babe.
[electronic music]
[Kanye] Are we good?
[Kim] All right, let's go.
[audience cheering]
[audience whistling]
[audience cheering, applauding]
[Kim] Kanye and Lamar walking out
with the spotlight on them,
and you hear everyone
in Madison Square Garden
just cheering.
[cheering continues]
It feels so emotional and powerful.
Kylie is crying, everyone just has chills.
[Jonathan] Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
[Caitlyn] I was thinking,
the last time Lamar was here, he was
probably playing in a basketball game.
He's just been through so much.
[audience whistling]
[Kim] You know, it's been
a really long road with Lamar.
So many ups and downs.
And I'm just so happy
that I'm here to witness him
walk out on his own and just be here.
Okay?
[audience cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
[Kanye] Yeah.
[audience cheering]
So I'm gonna play y'all the new album
so if y'all like any of the songs,
feel free to dance.
♪ High as light ♪
[Young Thug]
♪ Tell my baby I'm back in town ♪
[Kanye] ♪ High, high ♪
♪ My light ♪
[Young Thug]
♪ Tell everybody I'm back in town ♪
[Kanye] ♪ Highlight ♪
[Young Thug]
♪ Tell my baby I'm back in town ♪
-[Kanye] ♪ Highlight ♪
-[Young Thug] ♪ Town ♪
♪ We only makin' the highlights ♪
♪ Tell my mama, tell my mama ♪
[audience cheering]
♪ We only makin' the highlights ♪
♪ Tell my mama, tell my mama ♪
♪ That I only want my whole life ♪
♪ To only be highlights ♪
♪ One life ♪
-♪ One night ♪
-♪ Uh ♪
♪ Highlights ♪
-♪ Living the life 'til I die ♪
-♪ That's all I need ♪
[Kim] Being in Madison Square Garden
and to know that there has never been
a fashion show like this before
and seeing Kanye's
whole vision of his new collection
and to see all these amazing models
just be so proud to represent his line
and to have fashion and music
just all kind of blend together
is a really cool, special moment.
[Kanye] ♪ You want a boss or an R&amp;B ♪
♪ With a six pack? ♪
♪ Yeah, I need every bad up in Equinox ♪
[Kourtney] This show is so, like,
I'm blown away.
The setup of the stage
and the clothes and being able
to hear the music
and we're all so excited and dancing
and having so much fun.
It's just such an amazing show.
♪ Oh, no, no, no ♪
[audience cheering]
[Kanye] I really appreciate y'all coming
and supporting this event.
It feels so good to see
all of New York City
standing behind the crazy [bleep]
from the interviews.
[audience cheering]
[Kanye] I love you, guys.
[upbeat music]
Ooh, I need a drink.
Amazing.
[camera shutters clicking]
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you. It was so good.
[Rosie]
He said to me, like, three days ago,
"Can we go to the Kanye West
fashion show?"
I'm like, "Honey, I don't know anything
about fashion shows."
I text my publicist, she's like,
"Yeah, it's in two days."
So I'm like, "I don't know what to wear."
Ta-da. Hope you enjoy your night,
and nice to meet you.
-And, uh, carry on.
-[Caitlyn] Fight the good fight.
You too, man.
[Rosie] It did annoy me
that you've been a woman for three months
and you have more style
than I ever had at 53.
But that's okay, I'm working through it.
[upbeat music]
[phone rings]
Is that a little girl named Poosh?
[Penelope] Mommy, where are you?
I'm in the car with KoKo and Lamar.
[Penelope] I need KoKo.
[Kourtney] Okay, hold on.
-Hi, sister.
-[Penelope] Hi.
You wanna say hi to Lam?
[Penelope] Yeah.
Hey, sister.
[Penelope] Hey, Lam.
How you doing?
Are you being a good girl?
-[Penelope] Yeah.
-All right.
-[Kourtney] All right, Poosh.
-She said…
-[Kourtney] I love you.
-[Penelope] Bye.
[smooches]
-[Khloé] Lammy, that was fun.
-[Kourtney] That was fun.
[Lamar] Caitlyn was in the spot tonight.
[Khloé chuckles]
How did that feel?
[Kourtney] Yeah.
[Lamar] Weird.
[Kourtney] I remember the first time
meeting her, I thought it was so weird.
[Khloé] It's weird.
I called her Bruce
the first couple sentences.
I mean, understandable.
Did you then call her Caitlyn?
Yeah, I tried to correct myself.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Hi.
-We were just asking about you.
-Oh, hello.
-[Kris] There you are. I just texted you.
-Hi.
-[Kris] What is the address here?
-[Kourtney] Was that unbelievable?
-[Kris] West 55th?
-[Simon] The show? Mind-blowing.
-Yeah.
[Kris] I mean, who sells out
Madison Square Garden
for a fashion show?
How did you feel tonight,
coming into the stadium
when everybody was cheering?
-[Kris] That was wild.
-Good. Yeah, it was.
-Hi.
-Hello, how you doing?
[tense music]
[Kris]
Like, how many bags do you have, really?
-This is Balmain.
-[Kris] Stop.
[Caitlyn]
So, Lamar, you missed all the fun.
-Like what?
-What?
A lot's happened. We got to talk.
All these months,
and now we finally get to see you again.
Yeah, a lot's happened.
[Caitlyn and Lamar laugh]
But I'm here.
[dramatic music]
Honestly, I was very emotional
to see you there today.
Yeah.
-All good stuff.
-[Lamar] Yep.
Life is good, isn't it?
It's beautiful.
[Lamar] It's beautiful.
It beats the alternative.
[Kourtney] Mm-hm.
[Khloé]
I feel like a weight has been lifted off
of my shoulders.
Lamar and Caitlyn met, and I mean,
he was super mellow and calm.
I think I was way more nervous
than he was.
Lamar handled everything perfectly.
[Kris] So I want to tell you guys
something about
Khloé and Lamar's relationship.
[Khloé] Oh, my god.
-So I was over…
-[Khloé] Can you tell me first
-before you have…
-Uh, no.
-…to say it publicly?
-[Kris] So I was over at the house,
and Khloé and Lamar were talking
about conspiracy theories,
and I didn't realize… I knew Khloé,
like, she thinks
there's mermaids and aliens
-and all these wild things.
-[Khloé] There are.
-And leprechauns.
-But so does he.
-[Khloé] Well, what's your point?
[Kris] I just wanted to say
-that that was adorable.
-[Khloé] Oh, that was it?
-That you guys connect on--
-And Corey was teary-eyed over that?
[all laugh]
You guys, it's been magical,
but I'm done. Yeah.
-Okay. Okay. Yeah.
-[Caitlyn] A long time
-since the last time we talked.
-[Lamar] Yes.
A lot has… A lot of water's flown
-under the bridge.
-Bye, Cait.
-Yes.
-Okay.
-Bye-bye.
-[Caitlyn] I'll finally get my hug?
Yeah, you get your hug right now.
Okay, good. Good.
Seawater under the bridge, Cait.
[Caitlyn] A lot of water.
A lot of wonder… Well, whatever.
At the end of the day,
I'm always going to love Caitlyn.
We might not see eye to eye all the time,
or any of the time, but,
I know Caitlyn loves me.
We're family. I think that's
what family does best.
We go up and down, and…
But we are still always gonna be there
for one another.
[Caitlyn]
So happy to see you there tonight.
-Thank you.
-It's just like…
I was crying the whole time.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
[electronic music]
[Kourtney] You know what's crazy?
Just, we were saying,
can you believe Lamar is here?
-When we left you in the hospital…
-Mm-hm.
in Vegas,
we didn't think we would see you again.
[somber music]
And we were hysterically crying
on the airplane.
We couldn't even talk.
Can you believe that from that moment…
-Till now.
-…like, we've gotten here…
Mm-hm.
…to where you're
at this huge Madison Square Garden
-with, like, 30,000 people?
-Yeah.
[Khloé] Like, screaming
when you walked through the door too.
-[Kourtney] Yeah.
-[Khloé] That's major.
I swear that people's prayers for you,
-like, saved your life.
-Mm-hm.
Like, the world
-praying for you…
-Mm-hm. Yeah.
-I agree.
-…saved your life.
It's a great question, Kourt.
Yeah.
[Khloé] Do you appreciate everything,
-you think?
-I do.
Wait. But you never had, like, a moment
where you saw heaven and stuff like that?
[Lamar sighs]
No, I kept having real dreams,
in-depth dreams.
[Kourtney] With people you know and stuff?
Some people that have passed on.
-Oh, really?
-I think he went to heaven
from the conversations he has with me.
Yeah.
And since they told me
he was basically dead.
[chuckles]
Maybe those people were just with you.
I mean, that's what it is.
Yeah.
-Telling you to stay.
-Talking to you and…
[sniffs]
That's what it is.
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] It's so peaceful in here,
I could fall asleep.
This lighting is amazing.
I'm literally, like…
[Kim] Ugh. I can't believe
Scott has not texted me back.
Where is he? How have I not seen him
-one day this week?
-[Simon] He's psychotic.
So first of all,
whole entire plane flight,
he's like, "I'm coming, I'm excited."
And then, he was at the hotel
the first night,
and he asked Kourtney
to hang out with him.
And Kourtney's like, "I'm in New York."
-"I wanna go see my friends."
-Right.
-[Jonathan] But he went out that night.
-[Kim] So…
-So I guess he went out.
-[Simon] He went out that night.
With his guy friends.
[Kim] I was, like, "Don't drink, be good.
Remember what we talked about."
So then, yesterday,
he never wrote me back.
I go, "Okay, are you rested?"
"Because you're gonna look so handsome
at the show next to Kourt."
Nothing. Never wrote me back.
-Just nothing?
-[Kim] He's just MIA.
[Simon] He went out that night,
the night before the show.
Jake's cousin saw him at Up&amp;Down.
My friend saw him at 1 Oak last night too.
[Simon] I just don't understand why Scott,
like, doesn't wanna make his life better.
-Yeah.
-[Jonathan] He's got everything.
-You couldn't ask for anything more.
-[Simon] Everything.
[Jonathan] It's, like, amazing.
But he said
he's not happy inside, you know?
[indistinct chatter]
[Kim] I can only do so much for Scott.
I can't control him
and I'm not gonna try to.
You can try so hard to help people,
but you really can't change them.
It's easier, sometimes,
just to sit back, be supportive,
but let them do what they wanna do.
He just needs to figure this out
on his own.
-It's so sad.
-It's dark.
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat music]
Yeah.
[Caitlyn]
Ooh. Borrowing all the magazines?
Oh, these are my interior design ones.
[Caitlyn] No flying magazines?
-Like, airplane stuff?
-[Kris] Oh.
No, but there's a safety card here
you can read.
[Khloé] I really wanted to, like, mend
that bridge with Caitlyn
and extend the olive branch
and invite her on the plane
back to LA with us.
[Lamar] How long was I in the coma?
[Khloé] You were in a coma for four days.
Lam sees a hearse and says,
"Was I supposed to be
in one of those?" But, like…
[serene music]
-Yeah.
-No.
-No, I mean, he was--
-God is good.
-[Lamar] God is great.
-God is good but I kind of want him
to be a little more free.
[serene music continues]
You're very rare.
Like, bad things can happen
if you go back to that life.
-You know, like I was talking about it.
-This is, like, a second chance
-for life.
-Yeah.
[Lamar] The last time I came to New York,
my cousin was killed.
And then the day after that,
I got into a car accident…
[Khloé] Yeah.
-…and that kid died in front of me.
-[Khloé] Yeah.
So I do.
There's a thin line
between life and death.
[Khloé] Yeah.
-[Caitlyn] How are you doing?
-[Lamar] Good.
Thanks to this lovely young lady.
[Khloé chuckles]
[Caitlyn]
Well, she certainly was there for you.
-[Lamar] Yeah.
-Yeah.
Khloé was showing me some pictures.
Of when I was in the hospital.
Let me see the pictures?
[emotional music]
[Khloé] October 14th.
To get to a hospital and hear
that someone has four hours to live
and there's nothing you can really do,
it's horrible.
[emotional music continues]
Lamar wasn't able to walk.
He had no facial recognition.
He did not know people's names.
[Khloé] But now Lam is walking perfectly.
High five.
Person who wasn't walking
a month and a half ago.
[Caitlyn] Into Madison Square Garden.
Into Madison Square Garden, baby.
[Lamar] I gotta get back out there
with a ball in my hand.
[Khloé]
When something as tragic as this happens,
it does make you hold onto life
and think about things.
You're more in the moment
and you don't take things for granted
as much as, maybe, you once did.
Isn't my friend Melanie nice?
The best.
[Khloé laughs]
Melanie Griffith?
[Kris] She married Don Johnson twice.
She did?
If you're lucky, that could be you, Lamar.
-[Kris] Okay?
-Yeah. If you're lucky.
[Kourtney]
Wait, why did she marry him twice?
Because they got a divorce
and then they decided
they shouldn't be divorced.
If you guys ever got married,
can we just skip the wedding part?
No.
[Khloé] Oh. I was gonna say "sure."
But we're definitely
getting out of this marriage,
'cause it's been a little tainted.
Call… call if you hear me.
[all laughing]
Just sayin', okay.
[Khloé]
I'm just saying we need to cut our ties
and we can figure it back out.
-You know?
-Agreed.
[Kim] On the next episode…
Did you hear that Rob bought a house?
Yeah, Khloé's kind of, like, freaked.
[Kris] It's his money.
[Khloé] It's not his money
-'cause I know--
-Yes, it is.
I'm just allergic to [bleep]. Oh.
-[Rob] Yo.
-[Kris] Welcome home.
[Kourtney] Can I just say
I don't like this rug in here?
-[Kris] Okay.
-[Kourtney] Let's remove the stuff…
Kourtney's just, like, taking over.
I just feel like they had worked
so hard all day
-and we were just trying to--
-What do you want me to do,
come over and lie?