[upbeat music]
[Kourtney] I'm so excited for Miami.
When are we going
to get good Miami outfits?
I know. I need some good outfits.
I should see if Monica can come this week.
-[Khloé] No, I'm texting Monica.
-No, no, no,
but I'm leaving before you.
[Khloé] Hey, Moni, I'm going to Miami
for a full Kardashian extravaganza,
and I will need divine looks.
Exclamation point.
How does your thing work?
-What do you mean?
-Mine doesn't. Watch.
-[phone chimes]
-[Kourtney] Hi.
Exclamation.
[chuckles]
You say exclamation point.
Oh, [bleeps] idiot.
[laughs]
-Point. Wait.
-[Khloé] What?
[Kourtney] Monica, exclamation point.
Nope.
[Khloé] It can't read tone.
It just reads your words.
[Kourtney] I leave town for three weeks.
Would love to do some Miami looks.
Exclamation point.
[phone chimes]
See?
I don't know why yours does that.
[Kourtney] Right. Think I'm gonna take…
Spending the day with bae.
-[screams]
-Bae and day, they rhyme.
Day, bae.
Bae, day.
-Oh, really.
-[laughs]
Do you have this much fun
when you're with Kim?
Hell to the no.
[laughter]
[theme music]
[upbeat music]
[Teddy] Lay down, put your right arm there
and then roll yourself back.
-Okay.
-Nice and easy.
Arms down by your side. Inhale,
and then you're just gonna push
the carriage all the way up.
-[Scott] Wow.
-Hey, Scotty.
-And lower those heels.
-Hi. How are you?
Good afternoon, sir. How are you?
-How you doing? Nice to see you.
-Nice to see you. Likewise.
Yeah. Flat heel, push away,
all the way and drive your hips
all the way down,
-press all the way up.
-Ay-ay-ay.
[Teddy] This is not child birthing,
but it's kind of close. A little wide.
-Lucky you're there and I'm here.
-[Kris] Aren't you gonna try it?
-This ain't for me.
-Press away, a little burn.
Yeah.
There we go. Slow down.
This is like a bad porno
with a venereal disease.
-All the way down.
-[laughs]
-[Teddy] Wider.
-[Kris] Wider?
Harder, wider,
faster, slower, don't burn me.
-Ow, it hurts when I pee. Ooh!
-Last one.
-[laughs]
-Scott makes me laugh.
So it makes me really happy
when he chooses to spend time with me
rather than some of his friends
that might not be
the best influence on him.
-Don't get too nervous.
-Okay.
-Don't worry. I'm not…
-Oh, [bleep].
-[Kris] Oh, no way!
-[Teddy] Don't worry, buddy.
-[Scott] I'm not wearing boxers.
-[Teddy] Thank God.
-[whoops]
-Two different workouts.
-Press away.
-[chuckles]
-Wow.
-[Kris laughs]
This is something.
[Teddy] Push the heels
and stretch the legs
all the way out to me, make a circle.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
-[Teddy] And one, and two.
-I'm a guy for a reason.
I don't want to…
I'm gonna have a kid here.
Vulnerability.
I'm not having a child!
[laughter]
-[Teddy] Oh, drop it.
-Oy!
And the leg's gonna go back,
-it's gonna go back.
-[Scott] What?
-This is dangerous!
-I'm right here.
This does not feel safe!
[laughter]
-[Teddy] That's what she said.
-What's happening?
This is called "enjoyment."
-Roll it down. One.
-This is enjoyment?
-[Teddy] I don't think so.
-I feel like I'm gonna die.
-[Teddy laughs]
-[Scott] I don't like this.
-Hold the knees, open stretch.
-Oh, my god!
[laughter]
[Scott] Oh, how enjoyable is this?
-Okay, down here.
-That was the best.
[Scott] I'm not gonna lie.
I'm one of the better people
on these things.
[Kris] You know what's funny?
It creeps up on you. Like, you get sore.
Oh, my god, I can't wait!
That sounds amazing!
I can't wait to hurt!
[Kris] You want to wake your body up.
-So, I want him to come over.
-[Scott] I will be here.
-[Teddy] You can do some Pilates.
-You know, Scottie,
you're always telling me
that you have nobody
-to hang out with these days.
-I don't.
I'm doing lunch
with my girlfriends next week,
-and you're welcome to come.
-I'm there.
-My friends love you.
-[Scott] Okay.
[upbeat music]
[Jonathan] I love
that you're never hot or cold.
Like, you could wear this,
and it'll be 200.
-It's…
-Wait. That is, like…
Seriously, you have to say that.
That's, like, what everyone says. Okay.
I love that you're never, like,
hot or cold.
Like, it's 90 degrees,
and you're wearing full jean jacket.
And in New York, when it's two degrees,
you'll wear, like, a little skirt.
[Kim] #NeverReallyOutside.
-#InMyOwnEnvironment.
-[Jonathan] Yup.
You know what's so crazy,
is I've been having, like, anxiety lately.
-About what?
-Like, every last thing.
Like, even driving here. I try to drive,
like, not on the…
all the way on the freeway,
because what if
a car flips over and hits me?
-[Kim] I think of, like…
-I can't believe
-this is happening to you.
-… every freak accident.
Leaving Caitlyn's house
and driving down the hill,
I was like, "I don't care if North is 25.
I'm not letting her drive up
this hill and down by herself."
Oh, you're turning into,
like, a worrywart?
-Everything?
-[Kim] Like, totally worrying.
-I'm not this person.
-No, I know you're not.
Like, this is on stilts,
and that bothers me.
I think, like, we can get crushed.
You're… Now you're going crazy.
No, it's what I think of every single day.
-That's terrible.
-Yeah.
[upbeat music]
[phone ringing]
[Scott] Hey.
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-[Scott] What's up?
I just wanted to see
when you were coming over later.
Oh, um, I'll probably be
a little bit later
just 'cause I'm going to do something
in the city for a little bit.
[Kourtney] What are you going to do?
[Scott] Your mom asked me
to go have tea with her and girlfriends.
[Kourtney] Okay.
I don't think
it's the weirdest thing, do you?
[Kourtney] Um…
It's just… it's random.
Going into this whole tea party…
sounds okay.
I mean, I have no idea
what I'm gonna talk about
with all these ladies
for this amount of time,
but I'm sure I'll figure it out.
-[Kris] … Kathy. Hello there.
-[Scott] Wow. You guys
-look very fancy.
-Hey, there.
-I had no idea.
-How are you?
-[Scott] Hi. How you doing?
-[Kyle] What's happening?
At least put your sunglasses on
so we're chic.
Oh, are you supposed to wear
sunglasses here?
[Kris] Well, when you're having tea.
-Really? Okay.
-Honestly, I don't know.
I'll take mine off.
But you should leave yours on.
I try to see my girlfriends
every week or so.
We're always hanging out,
and why not invite Scott?
He's the life of the party.
So, Kylie just went to a new gynecologist,
-and he said to her.
-Oh, awesome.
I can't wait to hear about this.
-That's right.
-[Scott] I didn't think…
Let's talk about
all of your daughters' vaginas.
[Kris] You have to learn
how to take care of your body.
-As a female, it's a lot different…
-Scott--
…than when you're a male.
Is this comfortable, this table?
That's why it's called
-"high tea".
-[Scott] It goes low into me.
-Get it?
-No, it's crushing my tea.
[Kris] So what else?
You have some gossip for us?
[Scott] I wish I did. I have nothing.
[Kris] If you're gonna come to tea,
you have to have really good gossip.
-Okay, so…
-[Kris] Did you sell your house?
-No.
-Rob was looking for a house one time,
and I got really mad
because Rob didn't like the house I liked.
I said, "Well, this is just [bleep]."
She literally wants to buy everything.
-It's unbelievable.
-[chuckles]
If I send her anything, she's like,
"Oh, my god, that's so amazing.
Is there two of them?"
[laughter]
[Kyle] I feel like
we should do a girl's trip.
[Kris] Definitely, or…
-Nice. I'll be there.
-Girl's trip.
-[Kris] Nice.
-[laughter]
I was a little nervous coming into this,
but everybody's so nice
and so not intimidating.
And I feel like I'm definitely
getting along even better
than I thought with all of her friends.
-[waiter] Arnold Palmers?
-Right here…
for our other girlfriend, Scott.
[laughter]
-That's what I'm here for.
-[Kyle] I know.
But I will say, I really admire
hanging out with you guys
because it's not all about texting
-and being on your phones.
-[laughter]
But it's beautiful.
Like, I actually get to listen
and hear things.
-[Kyle] We're old school.
-I need to get to this meeting.
I love you guys…
[Kyle] Next time we're gonna
have more gossip for you.
-[Faye] Definitely.
-[Scott] Yeah, I love it.
-See you soon.
-[Kris] Love you, Scott.
Can't wait to plan the trip
-to Mexico for all of us.
-Are you coming?
-[Kyle] We're going to Punta Mita.
-What do you mean?
Somebody's got to supervise.
Yeah, he's definitely coming with us.
-[Kyle] We do need an escort.
-Well, or a pool boy.
[laughter]
[upbeat music]
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[Russell] Beautiful, Kendall.
Gorgeous. Beautiful, Kendall.
Very strong. Beautiful.
Bring the legs out.
Yes, beautiful.
[line ringing]
[Kris] Hey, Kendall.
Hey, Mom.
[Kendall] What are you doing?
[Kris] Gonna go into a couple of meetings.
Oh, okay. Um…
[Kendall] Do you want to know
the craziest thing?
So have you ever had sleep paralysis?
-[Kris] What does that mean?
-I don't know.
It's like you wake up,
and your brain is aw--
Like your mind is awake,
but your body's still asleep,
so you can't move. Like, you just wake up,
-and you're fully paralyzed.
-[Kris] That's terrible.
Terrifying.
You feel like
you're never gonna move again.
[Kendall] I'm freaking out
because recently,
I wake up in the middle
of the night and I can't move.
I looked it up online,
and it's a weird thing
called sleep paralysis.
It's so scary when it happens.
You literally feel like you're
never gonna get out of it.
[Kendall] It mainly happens on planes.
[Kris] I think you've just got
incredible anxiety
-about traveling.
-Yeah.
[Kris] You know?
And you can't have a fear
of getting on a plane
because of your anxiety attacks.
-But it's…
-[Kris] Yeah, you gotta…
No, no, I'm done arguing with people
because everyone says
I'm fine, but I don't feel fine.
And I promise you, one day,
when I'm rushed to the hospital,
then you guys are gonna wake up,
because I promise you this is not--
[Kris] Kendall, I believe you.
[Kendall] Okay.
[Kris] I don't want you to live
with this anxious feeling
-all the time. That's terrible.
-Yeah, and I'm kind of freaking out.
It's so weird, 'cause I get,
like, super light-headed…
when I'm on planes too.
And I feel like I'm gonna faint.
-[Kris] Yeah.
-[Kendall] I don't know what to do,
'cause I'm, like, freaking out
about even flying home.
[Kris] All right, just take a deep breath.
[upbeat music]
[Scott] What is going on here?
[Kris] Hi, Scott.
-Hello.
-We're doing water aerobics.
And would love for you to join.
[Scott] Um…
Initially, when Kris asked me
if I wanted to come over
and swim in the pool,
you know, I thought, no big deal.
I didn't really think
it was gonna be, like,
water aerobics.
[Kris] We're just getting started.
[Scott] All right.
It's a little weird,
and I definitely don't know
what I've gotten myself into.
I'm Tracy, and I was told
that you guys love it hard.
-[Lisa] Yeah, oh, yeah, we do.
-What?
-Yeah, we do.
-We do?
[Tracy] If you don't like it hard,
what's gonna happen is you're going to…
turn a little blue, it's gonna be good.
Hey, Scott, why don't you be,
like, the… leader.
[Lisa] I want to look at you from behind.
-[all cheering]
-Yes.
I think there's enough going on,
I don't need
-to be in the middle.
-[Tracy] Everybody ready?
-Yeah.
-[Lisa] Yes.
Close your eyes and feel it.
-[Scott] Oh, wow.
-Reverse.
[Kris] Scott's into it.
[Tracy] Three, four.
-Okey dokey.
-[Tracy] Five, come on, six.
Out your mouth, push it.
-[Scott] Oh, god.
-[Tracy whoops]
-[woman] Is it your…
-Roll, Scott,
-come on, roll.
-[Tracy] Give me your hips.
[chuckles]
You know…
[Scotts] Pretty sure I have no idea
what's, uh, happening.
I mean, it's a little bit of a weird life
that I lead here.
I don't think this is for guys.
-Come on.
-[laughter]
This is like a stripper class.
You could give somebody
a lap dance when this is over.
[Tracy] This is all for your tight tush.
Squeeze, nice and tight.
Scott, either you're gonna
do it or you're not.
[Scott] I didn't know
water aerobics was this sexual.
Two, get back to thrust.
[Tracy whoops]
Thrust, thrust, thrust, thrust.
I just don't know
if it's the most appropriate thing
in the world to be half-naked
with Kourtney's mom
and all of her friends
doing all these weird,
exotic dance moves
that you'd see in a strip club.
It's a little embarrassing,
I'm not gonna lie.
Squeeze your butt cheeks like
you're holding a credit card.
[Tracy] Shake it out,
come on, booty rolls.
-[Tracy whoops]
-[Heather] Do you care if I pee a little?
-[Tracy] No peeing in the pool.
-[laughter]
[Heather] Well, I'm trying to hold it
while you're doing the jumping jacks.
I have had two kids.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Come do a selfie with me.
-No.
-[Kris] You never do selfies with me.
One day, when I'm not here
you're gonna regret it…
-I hate selfies.
-… because it's gonna be like,
"I wish I had a picture of me and my mom
doing selfies in the kitchen."
-Wait.
-I feel like I just took
-a picture with a fan.
-Okay. I am a fan.
I actually like these,
will you send 'em to me?
[squeals]
My hair.
-You can send 'em to yourself.
-Wait, let's take more.
Oh, whoa.
-This is a new world for me.
-[camera shutter clicking]
Get it, Kendall.
[Kendall] I'm gonna caption it
"Pictures with fans."
[Kris] I'm your biggest fan.
-Mm. Since when?
-You're my favorite.
[sighs]
[Kris] Do you want
to go over your schedule?
[Kendall] I mean, I guess.
You have a week in Paris,
Milan, and then London.
I… I don't know
if I'm gonna be able to do that.
Well, you're already booked
to do that, honey.
I can't travel that much.
-Well…
-[Kendall] I'm, like, scared.
I'm freaking out because of these…
[bleep] paralysis things.
I'm scared to fall asleep
because it keeps happening to me.
It's almost like…
it almost feels like my heart stops.
Okay.
The nature of what you do for a living
and your career is flying
around the world.
You have designers
that have already booked you
and are counting on you to show up.
I'm just telling you…
I think that my health is a bigger deal.
[Kris] Kendall basically lives
on an airplane.
So, the anxiety on an airplane
and the sleep paralysis is a huge problem.
Sometimes, it's been so bad
that she's been paralyzed
from even getting on an airplane.
[Kendall] I want to get off the plane.
[Kris] Kendall, don't cry.
And I've had to get on a plane,
fly from LA to London
just to get her from London to New York.
So, it's becoming a real problem.
It's genuinely frightening
and I don't know how much of it I can do.
[upbeat music]
[Kim] What a life changer
that you got rid of the camel…
-Yeah, but I'm not sure if I like it.
-[Kim] … drapes.
I love it. This makes it, like, chicer.
They couldn't be this camel color
with the lines in them.
-You liked it all?
-Well, I mean, it was just…
it was easy and it looked finished, but…
-I mean, it looks clean.
-All of that was here when I moved in.
[Kim] It looks cleaner, a little brighter.
It's not like you really need
to black this room out,
-so it doesn't really matter.
-[Kim] Yeah.
So, Scott, why on earth
are you hanging out with my mom,
going to tea parties
and doing water aerobics?
First of all, it wasn't a tea party.
-[Kim] It was a tea party.
-It was "high tea."
-Was Lisa Miles there?
-A tea party…
[Scott] No, Lisa was at water aerobics.
Lisa wasn't at high tea, she was busy.
She texted me for your number today.
Like, since when were you interested
in water aerobics?
[Kim] Yeah, that's a little odd.
You never worked out a day in your life
since I met you.
The only difference
between them and all of you
is they don't sit on their phones
-the whole time.
-Saggier skin?
-[laughs]
-Their skin's a drop saggier.
It's just so not like you.
Just not your, like, steez.
I knew this whole water aerobics thing
was gonna come back and haunt me.
I mean, I didn't want to be, like
a full-blown cougar stalker.
It's definitely not the most normal thing
on the planet.
So maybe I shouldn't hang out
with the cougar squad.
[Kourtney] I don't want you to feel bad.
[Scott] I think you do.
I was just interested
in what exactly goes down.
I don't know, listen,
I mean, we talked about…
Menopause. I'm just kidding.
[laughs]
[upbeat music]
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[paparazzi clamoring]
Tonight, I am going
to the launch of Skyspace LA,
and I'm super excited to go.
It's really nice to have this event here,
just 'cause I don't have to travel alone.
[crowd cheering]
Hello, everybody,
and welcome to OUE Skyspace LA.
I am so excited to be here.
I brought all my friends out
and we are gonna ride this slide,
and we are so excited
for Travis Scott to perform.
And, yeah, I just hope
everyone has an amazing time.
[cheering and applause]
-[Kendall] I'm shaking.
-You were perfect.
You did it.
-[Kendall] We're getting on the slide.
-[Kim] I can't.
[Kim] Go now. Kendall!
-[Kendall squeals]
-Kendall!
I'm coming!
[screams]
I hate it, I hate…
-I got you going down, Kendall.
-I did it!
Very proud.
I'm really glad to just spend some time
with Kendall at her event.
We both travel so much,
but she has a few days here in LA,
so I'm glad to just be here
and watch her do her thing.
[Kim] Pretty view.
[Kendall] God, I'm so tired.
[Kim] You are?
-What's been going on?
-[Kendall] This stupid
sleep paralysis thing is,
like, really getting to me.
-[Kim] Sleep paralysis?
-[Carla] What is that?
It's, like, you're asleep and then, like,
the middle of the night…
basically your mind wakes up
but your body's still asleep.
So, like, you wake up,
but nothing can move.
-You can't speak, nothing.
-Wait, what?
-[Carla] Who's had this?
-[Kendall] Me.
It's the scariest thing
in the entire world.
You literally think
you're never gonna be able to…
[Carla] And you can't
pull your body up, right?
[Kendall] You can't do anything.
You're freaking out.
Like, 'cause all you wanna do
is be able to move.
So you're laying there
and you're trying to move,
but I think the key is to try and relax.
Nothing.
I mean, I thought I was having anxiety.
This is, like, so much scarier.
I've never heard of sleep paralysis,
and I think it sounds like
such a crazy experience.
And I feel so bad
that she has been going through this.
This is the most chilled out green room.
[Kim] Mm-hm.
[Carla] Go to sleep, Kendall. Take a nap.
Yeah, I only got, like,
two hours of sleep.
[Kim] Me too.
-So annoying.
-[Kim] It's been months living like that.
[Liz] Kim, how do you do that?
-I would die.
-[Kim] I know.
-It's so…
-That's the craziest thing
-I've ever heard.
-[chuckles]
[upbeat music]
[knocking on door]
-[Kris] Hey, how are you?
-What's happening?
-Good.
-The house looks great.
[Scott] You're just
hanging around in a gown.
I like it. It matches
the tones of the walls.
I wanted to point out,
she said I was kicking her out,
and she made me feel guilty about it.
-Every single time she comes…
-[Scott] It's beautiful here.
Well, don't make me feel guilty.
-[bleep]
-[laughs]
Should we go sit down?
-[Kim] Yeah, we can go over here.
-[Scott] Yeah.
So, you called me the other day
to ask me a question,
and you just seemed very anxious.
Yeah.
[Kris] And I don't know
where it's coming from.
Kendall has got the same thing,
-remember the other day?
-[Scott] She can't get on the plane.
[Kris] She thinks that,
-you know, like, she wakes up…
-[Kim] She told me about it.
It's awful. I mean, I'll never forget
flying to Paris to fly home with her.
It was almost like she jumped on me
and, like, fell asleep cuddling
because she was so happy
to have me there on the plane.
She could finally relax.
So I think that she feels very scared
and not in control of her situation.
And you're feeling not in control.
-[Kris] Emotionally.
-My mind does go crazy.
When you get in your own head, it's scary.
And you don't want to let it get
to the next step,
like, Kendall's at the next step.
-Yeah.
-And that's debilitating,
because she can't do what she needs to do,
and she can't live life.
Yeah.
It's really ironic that Kim and Kendall
are going through similar things.
Maybe there's a way
that they could help each other
manage their anxiety
so that they would feel like
they had the support of one another.
I think that we should find somebody
for you two to talk to so that
this doesn't get bigger
than it already is.
[upbeat music]
[phone ringing]
[Scott] Hey.
[Kris] Hey, what happened to you?
[Scott] Um, I had to go
to, like, this closing
for a house that I'm buying.
[Kris] Well, it definitely bugged me
that you didn't show up.
Kris asked me if I wanted to come over
and eat with her friends.
You know, I definitely know it's not cool
to flake on anybody,
but I guess I gotta start hanging out
with some people my own age.
[Kris] I had a place for you.
We sat there waiting.
And we were looking forward
to you coming, you know,
it's just manners
to call somebody and say,
"Hey" or, you know, pop me a text
and tell me something came up
because I was counting on it.
[Scott] I mean, I guess
I'll know now for the future.
[Kris] All right, kiddo.
Well, I'll see you soon
-and I love you.
-[Scott] Okay. All right. I love you.
-[Kris] Okay, bye.
-All right, bye.
[light music]
-[Kim] Do you want a muffin?
-[Kendall] No.
[Kim] Um, are you going
to France on, uh, Friday?
[Kendall] I don't know, man.
I'm afraid to, like,
get on a plane. It's so crazy.
I'm, like, supposed to be gone
and, like, traveling.
-And like…
-[Kim] You can do it.
[doorbell dings]
[Kim groans]
-[Kim] Hi. How are you?
-Hi. I'm good, how are you?
-I'm Michelle.
-Good. Hi, I'm Kim.
-Nice to meet you.
-Here, we can go over here.
-Okay.
My mom found this therapist
who specializes in anxiety.
Since Kendall and I
really aren't therapy people,
I think it's better for us
to do it together
and just see if it helps us.
I mean, I really pride myself in, like,
fully having my [bleep]
together all the time.
And with how bad things are for Kendall,
she has to get this under control.
This is Kendall.
-Kendall, this is Michelle.
-[Kendall and Michelle] Hi.
-Nice to meet you, Michelle.
-How are you?
-I'm good. How are you?
-[Kim] We're anxious.
[Michelle] Well, good thing I'm here.
So I guess I just want to kind
of get to know a little bit
about what typically makes
you guys anxious.
Sometimes, I literally
randomly get panic attacks
-when I'm flying or traveling…
-Mm-hm.
…or by myself. Mainly on planes, though.
Like, I had a crazy panic attack
and I was FaceTiming my mom
crying, like, on the plane.
And like, I have weird sleep paralysis
happen to me when I'm on planes now.
And this is all new.
So I'm, like… I don't even know
if there's a way around any of it.
There's not a whole lot you can do,
like, sort of in the moment.
It's kind of riding the wave.
It's more about
sort of preparing yourself.
And so, there's coping skills.
One of my favorite ones is
something called "interoceptive exposure."
Basically, just trying to mimic
the panic attack symptoms
when you're just kind of calm like this.
Oh.
[Michelle] The theory behind it is that
if you know what a panic attack is
and you know how to calm yourself down,
you're less likely to have a panic attack
and they're less scary
when you're having them.
Oh, my god, no,
this is so scary. Okay, pass.
I'm not about to, like,
actually… Oh, my god, no.
The therapist is trying to get me
to make a panic attack happen.
But every time I think
about my anxiety at all,
it only makes it worse.
I wanna get this under control,
but not like this.
If you know what a panic attack is
and you know how to calm yourself down,
you're less likely to have a panic attack
and they're less scary
when you're having them.
Oh, my god, no,
this is so scary. Okay, pass.
I'm not about to, like,
actually… Oh, my god, no.
Just remind yourself when
you're on that plane that it will end.
-You're not dying.
-[Kim] Um…
My anxiety's really different.
Like, if I get in a car, I'm like,
what if I drive, like, you know,
on this side of the freeway
-and then a car flips over…
-[Kendall] Oh!
-[kim] … and hits me this way?
-[Kendall] Same!
I mean, I'm always afraid
of a car accident.
Like, always.
[Michelle] Do you think you think
about that more often
than the average person?
-Yeah, definitely.
-[Michelle] Yeah.
Any idea why?
I don't know.
I think about it all the time.
[Michelle] Mm-hm.
Like, it drives me crazy.
The interesting thing
about anxiety disorders is
even though they're all
different symptoms--
So you have the panic attacks
and you just sit here and ruminate…
The treatment is very similar.
We could take a drive, we could…
I could show you
what that might look like.
We can, like, key--
[Kendall] I'm not gonna go for that.
We're gonna spin you in the car.
Does that work for you?
-Okay. Yeah.
-[Michelle] Yeah, does that work?
-Okay, cool.
-[Kendall] All righty then,
I'm gonna go home. Well, thank you.
-Nice to meet you.
-Awesome. You're welcome. You too.
I know this is really difficult
for Kendall,
but I am disappointed
'cause I feel like
it's fixable if she works on it.
Okay.
[Michelle] So what we're trying
to accomplish is…
experiencing those thoughts.
So I'm gonna have you tell me
what thoughts are going
through your head as we're driving.
I'm kind of nervous to induce my anxiety,
but if it's, like, an exercise
that she thinks will help,
I'm totally willing to try it.
I just want to get past my anxiety
and figure out a way just to live life
like I was before.
I just heard a story about, like, kids
that threw a rock in a window…
-Mm-hm.
-… and, like, the woman
-that they hit is brain damaged.
-Mm-hm.
And then I'm like,
"Ugh, that could be anyone."
-It, like, breaks my heart.
-Mm-hm.
You know the average person
doesn't think that way, right?
-[Kim] Yeah.
-Yeah, okay. Just checking.
Well, we call these intrusive thoughts.
They're just pop-ins.
They jump in your head
and is related to being responsible
for another human being. And that's scary.
That's overwhelming
-to a lot of moms.
-[Kim] Yeah.
So if you can, since you typically avoid
driving near the center divider,
if we can get over,
my suggestion is
let's get all the way over.
[Kim] Okay.
[signal light clicking]
So are you having any thoughts that…
you'll get hit or anything like that?
-A little bit.
-Yeah.
-[Kim] It's just more like…
I'm extra aware what those cars are doing.
Mm-hm. So…
and do you ever tell yourself,
like, "No, I'll be fine"
or anything like that?
-No, it just… I let it pass.
-Okay, got it. Good.
[Michelle] That's really
what you want to do,
and that's generally
what I teach people to do,
is really just tolerating those thoughts.
It's like, try not to be super aware that,
you know, it's that fine line between,
um, being hypervigilant
and, and kind of living your normal life,
making sure I'm aware of what's going on
and then also,
like, not changing
my behaviors too much for that.
[Kim] I mean, I've never had anxiety.
I've never had anything
to where I've not really been in control
and so, I think this is just,
like, a slipup
and I have to take back my life.
Yes, all of these bad things could happen.
Um… But again, we don't wanna
necessarily change our lives
because of it.
-Totally.
-[Michelle] So…
[upbeat music]
[Khloé] Oh, Scott, Scott, Scott.
That's me. Mm-hm.
First of all, I love your shorts.
-[Scott] Thanks.
-[Khloé] And secondly,
what happened to your leg?
-I fell off a scooter.
-What scooter?
[Scott] One of Mason's.
-That's really bad.
-I don't want to talk about it.
-That was ridiculous.
-Anyway…
[Khloé] I heard that you are now
flaking hanging out with Kris Jenner.
[breathes deeply]
[Scott] I just think
it's getting a little bit weird
that I'm with her and her friends,
-like, every other day.
-[Khloé] Who cares?
Going to dinner, going to lunches,
pool exercising, pool aerobics,
I mean, what's next?
But aren't you having fun with her?
Totally! But Kourtney kind of gave me
a little [bleep] about it.
-'Cause Kourtney's a hater.
-[Scott] It's not only Kourtney.
-Was it Nancy?
-Nance.
-Nancy.
-Fancy Nancy, AKA Kimmy K,
has been bothering me, too.
Like, "Why are you always with my mom,
and all of her friends, and all the… "
Why do you care?
Maybe I'm liking it too much
and I'm scared.
I think my mom is super cool.
I love her friends,
and I know that all of us,
especially Kourt, would agree,
that my mom and her friends
are definitely a better influence
for Scott than some of his other friends.
It's, like, a great, positive…
thing for him to be around.
I feel like you're more freaked out
'cause you feel like
you're going to cougar town.
-Like, it's fine.
-Right.
I really think you're being crazy,
and I think that you should appreciate
that you're a hit
and that these old broads love you.
And also, like, if we were to compare
to who you were hanging out
with prior to, like…
these broads,
I think you're doing pretty well.
Listen, I… I agree.
I'd rather be hanging out
with your mom and her friends
than people that don't
actually care about me.
-Right.
-They are fun.
I guess you bring up a good point.
You know, I definitely do feel bad
about pushing Kris and her friends away,
'cause I know that they were
only trying to be there for me,
and I feel like she always has been
and I really have a nice time with them.
I shouldn't be scared to admit it.
You got to hang out with the cougars.
[Scott] I like the cougs. Trust me, I do.
-You keep them young.
-Forever young.
-Forever sprung.
-Ew.
[Khloé] Hi, my baby.
-[Scott] Off of me.
-[Khloé] She's a nice girl.
You let other girls lick you, why not her?
Excuse me?
[smooches]
[Khloé] My baby.
[upbeat music]
[Kris] Look how cute this picture is
of your dad and me and Auntie Joyce
and Uncle Larry.
It's almost like
we were all color-coordinated.
[Kim] Saint kind of looks like Robert.
-[Kris] Robert, your brother?
-[Kim] Mm-hm.
It's so wild how fashion…
has so much to do with the memories.
It's like, I remember that outfit.
I had the nerve to wear
a 101 Dalmatians sweater.
Like, out in public
and it wasn't Halloween.
[Kris] Oh, my god, look at your dad.
[Kris laughs]
-[Kim] That mustache.
-[Kris] That's a major 'stache.
Don't you, like, wonder, like,
what would our lives be like,
though, if my dad was here?
Like, don't you think
our lives would've been,
like, so different?
[Kris] I think about it all the time
because I feel like,
in some way, he is still here.
Your lives would be fuller, for sure.
[Kris] He would be so proud
of you guys right now.
[Kim] He totally would.
-He would be so…
-He would be like…
-… impressed.
-… really excited that, like,
Rob is ventured back over
and everyone is, like, all together.
-[Kris] Getting along.
-[Kim] Mm-hm.
[camera shutter clicks]
[Kim] My dad lived his life to the fullest
and I have all these photos now
that I could look back at.
I know he never lived in fear
and I don't want to ruin
all of the memories for my kids
because of my own anxiety.
The last thing my dad said to me was,
"I know you'll be okay
and you are strong."
So, I would never want
to not live up to that.
[upbeat music]
Look how he set up
over here for the painting.
[Kris] Hi!
-How are you?
-[Brandon] Good, how are you?
[Kris] Wine and cheese, ladies?
-[Faye] Love that.
-[Kris] This is so cute.
Let's definitely grab some wine.
-[Faye] Definitely.
-Right?
-'Cause that helps, for sure.
-[Kris] Okay.
[Lisa] We're putting our aprons on?
[Brandon] Please, put your aprons on.
-[Scott] Oh, hello.
-Hi.
[all] Hi.
-What's shaking?
-[Lisa] What are you doing here?
-We're painting.
-Coming to painting class.
Are you crazy?
I'm not gonna miss out on this.
[chuckling]
Okay.
I've gone back and forth thinking
about if I'm gonna hang out
with these lovely women or not…
and the truth is,
I don't care what people think.
Age really is just a number
and I love all these ladies, so…
I'm not gonna break bonds
with these people
that have only been there for me.
And, you know, these ladies need the Lord.
-Can I have a little bit?
-Do you guys have an extra easel
-by any chance?
-[Scott] Of course they do.
[Brandon] So, here's the base.
Kind of a slight little smiley face.
You see how I kind of angled it?
-[all] Yeah.
-Right. Just do that.
[Scott] Wow.
I like this color. That is a nice palette
-you got there.
-Yeah, are you sure?
-That is nice.
-[Kyle] That's like a teal.
Right. I would almost go
-with a nice turquoise.
-[Lisa] Mm-hm.
-[Kris] Okay.
-[Scott] Beautiful.
-Beautiful little line up.
-[Faye] Are you seriously gonna,
like, build a studio in your house?
Is that gonna be the next thing
that you're gonna do?
I'm thinking about…
Well, I'm gonna have Scott do it.
[Lisa] Oh, it's gonna go
in Scott's house, huh?
You're gonna have the artist's studio?
No idea.
Why don't you do sculpting
and do that scene
from Ghost where you, like,
-build that big, phallic symbol?
-[Kris] Oh, we could do sculpting next.
-Right.
-Can somebody make me some green?
-I'll make you some green.
-I need some green!
I need olive green.
[Scott] Oh, you're doing
a very, very nice little job
over there, I'm not gonna lie.
-Ta-da!
-It's beautiful.
-Beautiful, guys!
-Yay!
-[Lisa] Yours is really good.
-[Kyle] Oh, that's pretty.
[Kris] Thanks for coming, Scott.
I love having you in the class.
-Oh, yeah.
-[Kris] That made it fun.
Just one of the girls, you know?
Yeah, well, you look good in a dress.
Thanks.
[Scott] I also wanted to say,
I'm sorry I didn't meet you guys
the other day for lunch.
I feel bad that I flaked on you.
Now I'm thinking, I'm like,
it's better this than something else.
So, that's why I came today,
I was like, I miss hanging out
with everybody.
You live a very tiny life on earth
and enjoy yourself
-and do what makes you happy.
-Totally true.
[Kris] And how much fun did we have?
[Scott] Listen, we have
a nice little time for ourselves.
-A nice little time.
-I love you.
I love you.
[upbeat music]
I hate this ottoman with a passion.
-Like…
-[Kim] It's pretty gross.
[Kourtney] I honestly cannot stand it.
[Kourtney] Hi!
Hello.
[humming]
[laughter]
[phone ringing]
[Kim] Hey, Michelle.
[Michelle] Hey, how are you?
-I'm good, how are you?
-[Michelle] I'm good.
I've had no anxiety on the road.
-[Michelle] That's awesome.
-You know what's funny?
Now that I think about it,
I really haven't had anxiety
since I saw you.
-Like no bull [bleep].
-[Michelle] That's amazing.
-I cured you.
-Yeah, I think you did.
[Michelle] There is no cure for anxiety.
And the thing is sometimes
when people talk about this stuff
and kind of get educated
about where the thoughts are coming from
there's a calming quality in that.
[Kim] Yeah, totally.
I have, like, a little bit more
of, like, a handle.
Like, I just, it's not
freaking me out as much.
[Michelle] That's good.
And, uh, how's Kendall doing?
[Kim] She's the same.
And she's supposed to fly out
for work in a couple of days.
Like, that's
when she gets her anxiety, so…
[Michelle] Right. Right,
right, right. on the plane.
[Michelle] You can also just do simple,
like, breathing exercises.
So, you know,
do meditation or mindfulness.
Yeah, maybe.
[Kim] I got such a good control
over my anxiety,
I want that for Kendall
and I want her to really work on it
'cause Kendall's been staying in LA
and living in this anxiety fear
about traveling,
and that's not really realistic
for her career.
I don't think
this has to get the best of her.
[upbeat music]
[Kendall] I hate bodysuits
more than anything.
-[Kim] Hmm?
-I said I hate bodysuits
more than anything. I'm too long for them.
Wait, do you like what I did
to my phone, seriously?
-[Kendall] Yeah. Yeah.
-Isn't it cute?
'Cause I wanted, like, a KIMOJI case
but, like, a LuMee case so I put stickers.
So what's so crazy is that
I literally haven't had anxiety.
-That's crazy.
-[Kim] Haven't even thought about it.
-[Kendall] Mm-hm.
-But I also think that…
everybody handles things
in different ways.
So I think maybe it's really good
if we just like, try meditating.
You know, I'll kind of,
like, let you do your thing
since I've tried meditating,
it's not my thing.
I think actually talking to the girl
was more my thing.
[Kim] As a way to try to help Kendall,
I set up a meditation for her and I
just to have this, like, little session.
[Kim] Some people live by it.
And because, you know,
there is no cure for anxiety.
You have to get control of your feelings.
Unless you want to change your job
and do something totally different,
which you don't. So I feel like
you just have to, like…
get ahold of it, you know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-[Kim] I'll bring you out there.
You know, you can just see if you like it.
[Kendall] Okay.
I'm into it.
[Kim] So let's go.
[Kendall] I do feel like Kim is right,
'cause I do love my career.
And I love being able to travel
the world, and I feel blessed.
This is the lifestyle I want to live,
so meditation's something
that I'm willing to try
just to kind of cope with it.
How serene is this?
Oh, wow, are you trying to hold my hand?
[chuckles]
-Yeah.
-[Heather] Hello.
-[Kim] How are you?
-Hi, good, I'm Heather.
-Hi, I'm Kim.
-[Heather] Kim, nice to meet you.
-Hi. I'm Kendall. Let us…
-[woman] Nice to meet you.
-[Heather] … have a seat.
-[Kim] Ooh, what's this?
So what we're gonna do is
we're gonna start
with just learning to watch
the mind a little bit.
[Heather] Now getting into a posture.
Whatever's comfortable for you.
So the thinking mind
tells us what to do all day.
So for this moment in time,
what we're doing is
we're dropping into our wisdom mind.
Dropping that question,
"What do you need?" Asking the heart.
Developing another voice
rather than that inner thinker,
we can have
that compassionate voice saying,
"I'm here to give you comfort."
"I'm here to listen to you."
"I'm here, you're safe."
We can create that inner soother
to help care for our heart,
our body and our mind.
We just slowly
begin to strengthen this muscle,
allowing ourselves to give ourselves care.
And when we're ready,
gently opening the eyes.
Well, you had a lot of stillness.
-Really?
-[Heather] Yes, that was great.
-Is that a good thing?
-Yes, that's a really good thing.
-There was a lot of stillness.
-I feel like I zoned out.
-That's a good thing, right?
-[Kendall] Yeah.
-No, I loved it.
-Good.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
[Kendall] It's pretty amazing because…
this is definitely making me, like,
relax a little bit and find some peace.
And knowing that…
having anxiety isn't something
that you can just fix
and it'll go away,
meditation's definitely
something that could help me.
It's something that I can obviously take
everywhere with me.
Whenever I feel like I need it.
[Heather] So we can do those practices
when we're not anxious
and still bring in that compassioned voice
even when things are really stressful.
-Well, thank you.
-[Heather] You're welcome.
Thank you.
[upbeat music]
[Kendall] What are these juices?
[Kim] Take whatever.
[chuckles]
[groans, gags]
You know what's weird is
I usually don't like meditating,
-but I kind of liked it.
-Yeah.
I feel like I should tell Mom.
Oh, my god, call Mom and be like,
"We have to cancel. I can't do it."
I already said that to her.
It's gonna be like,
-"Did you cancel it?"
-[line ringing]
[Kris on phone] Hey, Kendall.
Hi, did you cancel everything?
[Kris] Cancel everything?
-Yeah, like…
-[Kris] Are you kidding me?
No, I didn't cancel anything, Kendall.
I mean, these people
are gonna lose their minds.
Everybody's booked
and they're counting on you.
Mom, chill, chill.
[Kris] Why would I chill?
-It's not funny.
-Because I think I'll be okay.
I just did a meditation class
and I feel like it might actually help.
-I really liked it.
-[Kris] That's really cool.
Do you think that you know how to do that
if you tried it again
on your own, Kendall?
Yeah.
[Kris] Well, I'm proud of you
for doing that.
-That's awesome.
-[Kendall] Thanks.
-Love you.
-[Kris] All right. I love you, too.
I really don't think I would've done it
if you hadn't have made me
do it, so thank you.
Sometimes it's good to be forced
to do things.
[Kim] On the next episode…
I think it's crazy
what's going on in the world
and I'm passionate
about stricter gun laws.
If you get involved
with that type of stuff,
you're gonna get a lot of hate.
[Kris] Where's the interview person?
[Kris] We are doing a legacy video
with my mom, Mary Jo,
and I'm nervous.
What's your biggest fear?
I try not to fear.
[Kris chokes up]
I don't wanna say it.
Why did you ask me that?
I can't believe I'm crying.