[upbeat music playing]
[Kendall] This is a huge bowl of fruit.
[Kourtney] Yeah, does it ever get eaten
or just get thrown away
every week and restocked?
[Kendall] That's really bad.
There are people in Africa
that are starving.
Did one of you guys
wait for the [bleep] answer?
-Can I have a peach?
-No, you can't.
I don't have enough.
First of all, I hope you guys
know I have a fruit bowl
every single morning
and I make myself smoothies.
And do you know
how many trees I've planted
so I can have a lot of those fruits?
You have mango and peach trees outside?
Shut the [bleep] up
about my [bleep] fruit bowl.
Go back to your gluten-free house
and let me live with,
like, a world of Oreos,
and gluten, and flour, and wheat
and whatever the [bleep] I want.
Okay.
[theme music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Kourtney] Since I've been
drinking those floral drops--
[Khloé] Oh, is your heart
getting more open?
No, I literally cry at, like--
I cried at an Adam Levine song
today in the car.
No. You're not a crier.
Something's wrong with you.
-I'm crying now.
-[chuckles]
[Khloé] So, Chyna,
like, we should do something
really special for her.
Make her feel, like,
welcomed to the family
and, like, that we
are celebrating the baby,
not just at the shower she already has.
Chyna is throwing a baby shower
and it really sucks
because the date that the baby shower is
me and my whole family
are gonna be out of the country.
[Khloé] We still really want
to throw her something special
so that Rob knows
that we're all supportive
and on board with their relationship.
Let's call her and say,
"Hey, is there anything
that you've been dying to do
since you've been pregnant?"
-Okay. I will call her.
-[Khloé] Okay.
[line ringing]
[Chyna] Hi, Kourt.
-[Kourtney] Hi.
-[Khloé] Hi, Chyna Balls.
[Chyna] Oh, hi.
[Kourtney] So, I just found out
that all of us
are not gonna be in town
the weekend of your shower.
-[Chyna] Okay.
-So, we want to do something…
[Chyna] For the baby shower?
Well, like, I mean,
not even as a baby shower,
like, just something, like,
-special that we could all do.
-Like a pampering day for you.
Like when I was pregnant,
they took me--
We want to…
we want to spoil you
and Kourtney's so bad
at this conversation.
-Shut up.
-[Khloé] You shut up.
-[Kourtney] Khloé.
-Stop hitting yourself.
We want to spoil you,
and lavish you
and make you just whatever you want to do.
If you've been craving to do something,
but if you want to do anything
we want to treat you.
[Chyna] Ooh.
[Kourtney] We'll all brainstorm
and think of something,
just, like, something with all of us.
[Chyna] Yeah, something small
and, like, intimate.
I'm down.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
[Kourtney] Yeah. Okay, bye.
Listen, you don't tell someone…
[imitates Kourtney]
…we're not all gonna be here
for your baby shower.
Like, act a little more,
like, apologetic and sincere.
[in high-pitched voice]
We're all not gonna be here
for your baby shower.
-That's what you should do.
-[laughs]
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] You got to sign this,
it's for DASH.
Mm. I am a secretary.
[Khloé] What am I?
[Kim] You're the president?
[gasps]
[Kim] Think Kourtney
is just an authorized signer.
[Kim chuckles]
[Khloé] I have so much
that I need to do workwise.
Mom is so [bleep] annoying.
[Kim] Why?
Like, they wanted to do this
whole fitness thing with me.
What I want to do is, like,
my backpack that, like,
I'm always wearing and paparazzi,
everyone's like,
"What's in your backpack?"
It would be, like,
the fitness survival kit.
But, like,
I haven't been able to, like,
reach Mom or, like, get
any direct answers out of her.
[slow tense music playing]
Like, I'm super annoyed.
[Kim] My mom has always been our manager.
She is a good manager,
but she's just been, like,
dropping the ball a lot lately.
We all feel a little bit
neglected sometimes.
She goes through phases
of who she's, like, really diving into.
-Just timeless.
-And it should be Khloé's,
like, emergency fitness kit.
I know what it's like when, you know,
you want something executed
and you can't figure it out.
And I feel bad for Khloé,
so I totally want to help her.
[Khloé] It's just really important to me.
[Kim] She should talk to my KIMOJI people
'cause we're doing, like,
all stuff like lighters,
ashtrays, slides, like,
can't be that different.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] I don't really believe in a brand,
but I hate that…
once, but it's also…
Your mom, I think,
was just in an accident.
-[Khloé gasps]
-[Alexa] She's at the 76 by Calabasas.
-[Kylie] Let's go. We'll drive together.
-[woman] Yeah.
I just can't believe my mom
was in a car accident.
[Alexa] They're on their way.
They're on their way.
[Khloé] I don't know how bad it is.
I don't know if she's okay.
I know nothing.
[sirens wailing]
It happened so fast.
[Kris] You don't have time
to think about anything.
You just brace yourself for impact.
[sirens wailing]
Within minutes,
my kids sprang to my side,
which comforted me so much
because in an instant,
your life can change.
[soft music playing]
Totaled my car.
It was just so scary.
Thank God you're all right.
No, you guys,
-did you see the pictures?
-No, I'm okay.
-[Khloé] It looks so bad.
-[Kris] I'm going along
the road and I'm driving.
The light's green, not going fast.
[Kylie] He thought he could
make it or something?
[Kris] He thought he could make it.
And then right behind him,
the other dude
-decides to do the same thing.
-[Kim] Was it a paparazzi?
And I'm just sitting there
going, "Holy [bleep]."
-Kylie and I went to see her.
-So, I just hung on
for dear life and closed my eyes.
[Kris] Totaled. That car is done.
-It's just a car.
-[Kim] We're at her house now.
We'll buy you a new one.
We can't buy a new mommy. Oh.
I love you so much.
Thank you for coming.
I don't know what I would've done
if you guys all didn't come.
Kanye, thank you
-for coming, too.
-Kylie was crying.
-All right. I love you.
-[Kim] I would've cried, too.
[Khloé] I know, well, I was crying, too.
Scared me.
I'm just still… like this.
You know? It rattles you.
[Kanye] The world's crazy.
[Khloé] It's so scary
to see my mom like that.
She is completely shooken-up.
And when we got the call,
we were like,
"She got into an accident, okay."
Like, we didn't…
still didn't think it was big.
Then we drove up the street
and we found her.
Both of our hearts dropped.
Like, Kylie started crying.
Like, what if that was
the last time we saw Mom?
-Like, that's not okay.
-[Kim] I know.
-God forbid.
-[Scott] Yeah.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Hey. What's going on?
I'm so exhausted.
-Everything hurts.
-[Kim] I feel you.
And I have so much to do…
-[Kim] Do you want help with something?
-…and I'm just tired.
[Kris] Well, to be honest,
I'm working on this
Australia date for Kylie.
-[Kim] Yeah.
-But…
I don't know, it's just a lot.
It's a lot of details.
You'd probably lose focus in five minutes.
Why don't you just chill?
I'll help you.
[Kris] Really?
I would say, okay,
she needs security, glam,
she should find one person
to do hair and makeup,
and have them pay for hotel,
flights, and a fee.
But it's take care of your own travel,
so I would need you to get on the phone
-with the travel agent.
-[Kim] Let me get her on the phone.
I mean, I've joked a lot that I could be
my sister's manager
better than my mom could be.
I think I do give a lot of good,
creative input.
And I know they, like, listen.
So I feel like
I could totally handle this.
-[Kylie] Kim.
-[Kim] Hey.
So, Mom's not feeling good
so I'm just helping her
with your Australia trip.
[Kylie] Are you at Mom's house?
[Kim] Yeah.
Um, there's, like,
really good shopping,
I can tell you, like,
all that kind of stuff.
But, to save some money,
would you ever use,
like, someone from Australia
to do both hair and makeup?
[Kylie] No.
Why, do you want to have Ariel
at that time or something?
No, not at all. I was just
helping you save money.
'Cause the travel's included.
[Kylie] I don't know.
Okay, think about it
and maybe let's talk in a little bit
and figure out if you even want to go.
-[Kylie] All right.
-Bye.
[Kim] All right, we got this.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Khloé] Oh! Wow!
-[Rob] Oh, that's not--
That's definitely not Kourtney. [chuckles]
Wow. I see you.
-What is going…
-[Scott] Oh, my goodness.
What gave you the confidence
to wear that today?
[Kim] To wear what?
Stand up.
[Scott] Isn't that lingerie?
-You guys are insane.
-[Khloé] You want some of my Big Stick?
I prefer to suck on my own Big Stick.
[Scott] Bet you do, you little sucker.
Yeah, just give it a lick,
just give it a lick, Bobby.
Just one lick. Oh, yeah.
-[Scott] Oh, just one lick, Rob!
-[Khloé] Just one lick.
[Scott] Don't be weird.
[Khloé] Yeah, lick it once!
[Scott] Oh, it feels so good,
but it hurts. Oh, God, yes!
-Give it to me!
-[Rob laughs]
[Scott] Hey, don't hurt him. Oh, God.
[Rob] It's pretty good, though.
I don't remember it tasting like that.
'Cause you never had them
stuffed in your mouth
-by your sister.
-[Khloé laughs]
[Rob] Oh, man.
You seem good. You seem
like you're in good spirits.
Yeah, I'm completely fine.
Okay. I'm just making sure,
you go like this.
[Rob] I do go like that.
[Khloé] How are you and Chyna?
[Rob] We don't live together.
[slow tense music playing]
[Khloé] You're not together?
I'm not super comfortable at her house,
and she's not super comfortable at mine.
So after the baby, you guys
are gonna move in together?
I don't know.
[Khloé] I thought Rob and Chyna
were getting better,
and I'm so disappointed that
they're spending time apart.
A baby doesn't fix any situation.
So I think Rob and Chyna
have a lot of things to work on.
Hopefully, with a baby involved,
maybe that would motivate Rob
to try a little harder,
and to do things a little differently.
Wait, are you and Chyna still engaged?
[Kim] Wait, are you
and Chyna still engaged?
[Rob] I mean, I don't expect
to get no ring back
if we weren't. I'm not tripping.
Rob and Chyna's relationship
is the craziest up-and-down situation.
[Kim] It's like a lot all at once.
I'm just hoping that they just,
you know, can figure it out
before the baby comes.
Have you guys built your crib
and everything yet?
[Rob] No.
[Khloé] Have you read any baby books?
No.
Do you know how to take care of a baby?
-No.
-[laughter]
[Rob] But, um, I'm a first-time dad,
so I'm sure I'm not gonna be perfect.
-[Khloé] Nobody is.
-[Rob] Yeah.
[Khloé] Rob, just do it again.
-Don't do that to me.
-[laughter]
-[Scott] It's not right.
-[Khloé] Just say something.
[laughter]
[Rob] Hey!
[laughter continues]
Oh…
[Khloé] You want to go look
at the guest house?
[Rob] Yeah.
-You guys not coming or…
-[Scott] Uh-uh.
[Khloé] Scott doesn't care.
[Scott] I was just there.
[Kim] What do you think
about them not living together?
I mean, I'm not
the best example, you know?
-[Kim] Yeah.
-I've been in similar situations
with Kourtney before
and after we've had kids,
-do you know what I'm saying?
-[Kim] Yeah.
And it's never easy, I mean,
Kourtney and I make it work,
but we're pretty unique.
Hopefully it works out for them,
but I do think,
if they're gonna make it work,
they need to, like, join forces.
-Totally.
-[Scott] I just hope
that they just, like,
get on the same page,
-and, like, push together.
-True.
[Scott] I mean, I would if I was him.
Maybe, you know,
he'll take the baby on as his,
like, his first priority
and that'll be his thing that,
like, really, like,
gives him satisfaction in life.
-Yeah.
-Little babies are tough.
-[Kim] Mm-hmm.
-Then it becomes, like,
the best job in the world,
taking care of a kid.
Now it's like, I look at Mason,
and he's just like,
nothing even gets by the kid,
he's just, like, so funny and so quick.
-He's so funny.
-Speaking of Marty,
-I'm going over to get him now.
-[Kim] You are?
I'm gonna go see what he's doing.
-I'll see you later.
-'Kay.
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] Hi, Coca-Cola.
-[Kim groans]
-I like your jack.
Thank you. I was thinking
it's too big for me,
so you could probably have it, but…
So anyway, I just set up
your meeting with Whalerock,
and I just want
to make sure that, you know,
I have everything that you're thinking of,
'cause I want them to try to,
like, start sourcing out
people that could actually
make this stuff.
I think Whalerock could be great.
[upbeat music playing]
My mom is still in bed recovering.
So I'm gonna be managing
all the girls this week.
I know this fitness backpack's
really important to Khloé,
so I've set up a meeting for her
to meet with a team
that I think can really execute this
and get it going, and she can
sell it on her own website.
I've been trying to do this
for literally a year,
like, since before my book came out,
like, that's what I wanted.
I appreciate you,
like, actually, like,
putting it into effect.
Totally.
Kim definitely has built her own empire
and knows what she's doing.
And so why not have her be
the little Kris Jenner for a minute?
You're gonna be in the meeting, right?
'Cause you know everything,
you've done this before,
I feel like you, like, have a vision.
All right.
I will be there.
[upbeat music playing]
[Rob] You know I'm about
to have a baby, Mase?
-[grunts]
-[Mason] Yeah.
What do you think we'd get Rob ready
for, like, having a little baby,
like when you were a little baby?
-[Mason] I don't know.
-[Scott] I did Lamaze,
I did, like, how to, like,
have the baby
and, like, I don't
know what I really did--
[Rob] Lamaze is, though, if you're…
if you're doing it vaginally, right?
Or som-- Or does that
have nothing to do with…
-Wait, what's Lamaze?
-[Scott] I think it's just,
like, breezing--
breathing exercises and whatnot.
[Rob] Yeah, I mean,
I'm open to whatever.
I'm sure I'll have plenty of questions.
I'm definitely not perfect,
so I don't want to give advice to Rob.
That's why I'm suggesting that he goes
and takes some classes
on how to be a new dad,
and I just want him to be well-equipped.
[Rob] You remember that one time
where you were like,
"Hey, Bob,
can you, uh, pee on my toys?"
-[Mason] No.
-[laughs]
I think you definitely need
to take a class on parenting.
I know I'm gonna need help, so…
I don't think this urinating
is what you do to raise a child.
[laughs]
[Scott] It's important for Rob to have
a nice, close relationship with his baby,
so I think he needs to try to
learn how to take care of her.
Especially when he's going to be
raising this child
half the time himself.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Kylie] Hey.
-[Kim] Hey!
-How are you?
-Cutie.
[Kylie] You look super cute.
[Kim] Thank you. So?
I'm working with this artist
to do, like, art all over my body.
As long as, like, you have
some cool poses and stuff.
[Kim] In between doing things
for Khloé, Kylie, and myself,
I've had to run around all day.
So I stop by Kylie's Complex shoot.
I want to help her look like,
as cool as possible
and just help her
with anything that she needs.
Remember, I was like,
"You've got to do a Complex shoot."
Is it like, sexy?
-Yeah, it is.
-[Kim] Yes.
It's like, editorial, though.
Oh, but I need you to do,
like, raunchy.
[Kylie] That's what I thought
this shoot was.
Like, ass out.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
I would have called them.
[Kylie] I haven't started.
-Oh, you haven't?
-No.
[Kim] I want to see the mood boards.
-I'm gonna go look.
-All right.
[Kim] I'll be right back.
What is she wearing today?
[Monica] More with the latex vibe,
-but there's like…
-[Kim] Oh, cool.
[Monica] See in all those photos,
it kind of pops a little more,
-like the red…
-[Kim] Yeah.
It just depends
what she feels comfortable wearing.
[Kim] Oh, good. I love all this.
My favorite girl!
[Monica] Hey-ya.
[Khloé] How are you? I miss you.
Oh, the real MVP is here.
Hi. You look beautiful.
[Kylie] So do you.
You haven't seen my face yet.
[Kim] I asked Khloé to meet me
because we really need
to go over some details
for her KHLO-FIT meeting.
Multitasking is key
to being a good manager.
Honestly, I feel like I could handle this.
[whoops]
-[Khloé] Oh, my goodness.
-[Kim] Look at you!
[Khloé] You look beautiful.
You just look so hot,
I can't handle it.
[Kylie] Thanks.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Everything's going so good
at Kylie's shoot.
She looks amazing. And honestly,
I think I'm doing a pretty good job
at being her manager.
Hey, what did they say?
[Kim] But there's just so much
going on, it's like, nonstop.
So, juggling it all is… it's a lot.
[Kim] Bye.
[upbeat music playing]
You have a white spot up here, I think.
I've had this white spot
for like, 400 years
and I don't know what it is.
[Kourtney] That's an alien mark.
Okay, good. Anyway,
so Rob came over the other day
and he was in, literally,
the best mood ever.
He was so fun,
so funny, like the old Rob.
-To your house?
-[Khloé] Mm-hmm.
But, he did say…
which is, like, a little weird.
He did say him and Chyna,
they're definitely separated,
they live in their own places.
So, they're not together?
Oh, whenever I say,
"So, are you guys still engaged?"
He's like, "Whatever."
Like, he's not like,
tripping off the title.
They're so high and low.
I just now feel like,
I still want to do
something for Chyna, but--
Why don't we do something for him?
[Khloé] That's what I was thinking.
Maybe we could throw Rob a shower.
[gasps] What?
[Khloé] We're gonna throw Rob a shower?
We could always throw Rob
and Chyna something.
I'm sure that it's overwhelming for Rob,
but no matter what is going on,
we just want to do something fun
and positive and just, show Rob
how much we're supporting him.
[line ringing]
-[Rob] Yo.
-Hey, Rob.
[Khloé] Rob, dawg.
Kourt's with me.
[Kourtney] We were thinking that we should
throw you and Chyna,
like, a little celebration
to celebrate becoming a dad.
[Rob] Well, that would be really good.
Just tell me when you all want
to do this great party
and I will be there.
And I'm very appreciative.
[Kourtney] Okay.
[Rob] Okay, love you.
[Khloé] Love you. Okay.
-[Rob] Bye, Kourt.
-Bye, love you.
So, we'll be partying it up.
-Can't wait!
-[chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
[line dialing]
[phone chimes]
[line ringing]
-[Kourtney] Hello?
-[Kim] Hey,
I just wanted to get a breakdown
of what your schedule is
over the next few weeks.
[Kourtney] Yeah,
we need to figure out mine
and Khloé's workout line.
[Kim] Workout line, okay.
[Kourtney] The animation thing,
I just want to see deal points.
I'll call Todd and relay that to him.
[line ringing]
Hey, Ky, it's Kim.
I want to go over
your travel for Australia,
so call me when you have time.
[line ringing]
-[Kim] Hey.
-[Khloé] Hey. Coming up, I have
a Women's Health shoot,
a GQ shoot,
I'm co-hosting The Ellen show.
Wait, you said, um, Ellen--
You, oh, GQ shoot.
[Khloé] I'm co-hosting with Ellen.
I have like,
three different book signings.
I have the launch
of my denim on October 18.
I have to do Jimmy Kimmel at some point.
SoulCycle charity event.
I have to meet
with a charity called Step Up.
I am, like, super overwhelmed.
There's a lot going on.
You know,
juggling all of my sisters.
I think managing five girls is definitely
a lot harder than I thought it would be.
[Khloé] I need to make sure
that the charity
and everything
is done for my book signing.
So, if you could help me
with that stuff, that's awesome.
[upbeat music playing]
-[Scott] Hello.
-[Leslye] Hi, there. I'm Leslye.
-[Scott] Hey.
-Nice to meet you.
-I got three of my own kids.
-So, you're here to teach me.
Not at all. I'm just making sure
my brother Rob learns.
[Scott] So, I set up a class
for a woman to come to Rob's house.
Basically, just,
you know, a one-on-one
that gets you prepared
to have your first child.
-How are you? Rob.
-Hi.
[Rob] So what are we learning today?
Well, we're gonna learn
a little bit about the girl.
How to bathe,
and diaper, and dress.
-[Rob] Okay.
-See, you're not even holding
-the kid right already.
-Nah, I know how.
-I'm up in this bitch.
-[Rob laughs]
-Are you gonna cut the cord?
-Probably, yeah.
-[Scott] I did.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-[Leslye] You did?
-[Scott] It's fun, yeah.
And they'll hand you a scissor
and you'll cut it here.
Then the nurse will cut it lower down.
-Okay.
-They don't want dads
to feel guilty if the baby has an outie.
-[Rob] Got you.
-So, that's why you--
[Scott] Right, they want a Bentley.
-Right.
-[laughs] Good one.
So you want to go from the center, out.
Is that okay, little girl?
Let me get the other eye.
-Oh, no.
-[Leslye] Now you use--
-Ooh, and then, oh.
-[Scott] Idiot.
[Leslye] You use a clean corner.
[Rob] There you go. Got you.
Poor guy just gave his kid pink eye.
[Leslye] Now we're gonna get underneath--
[Scott] Aw. How nice.
[Leslye] Now, we're gonna put a onesie on.
-Roll it up like a donut.
-Ooh.
[Rob] You better put
your [bleep] hand in there.
-[Rob laughs]
-[Leslye] Good job.
[Scott] Rob looks like
he knows his way around a baby.
But I'm not gonna lie,
a plastic doll
is a lot easier than something real.
I think this is definitely
a good stepping stone,
but he definitely has a ton more to learn.
-[Scott] Oh!
-[Leslye] Ooh…
That's called a concussion
in my book, ladies and gentlemen.
Well, I wouldn't do it that hard.
-[Leslye chuckles]
-[Rob] Learned a lot.
-[Leslye] Yeah?
-[Rob] Yeah, thank you.
-[Rob smooches]
-Aw…
-And thank you.
-May I?
[upbeat music playing]
[Khloé] Hello!
-[Jen] Hi.
-[Khloé] Hi.
-Sorry about today.
-[Jen] All good.
Today's just been… crazy busy.
-Jeff couldn't be here.
-Yeah, Jeff couldn't be here,
-just with the time change.
-It's okay.
[Khloé] Well, Kim is supposed to be here,
but I have no idea where she is.
Okay. Um, I filled Jared in
on our conversation,
so basically, we just want
to hone in on everything from you.
To, like products, like what
you want to accomplish.
Have you decided
how you want to, like, brand it?
[Khloé] Um…
Hmm…
[Jen] Do you want to brand it KHLO-FIT ?
I want to brand it KHLO-FIT.
-[Jen] Okay.
-[Khloé] Um…
[Khloé] I'm a little frustrated
because I'm being asked a ton of questions
and I just wish I had someone
on my team to just make sure
that I'm making the right decision.
Kimberly arranged it for me,
and she also told me
she was gonna be here.
But she's nowhere to be found. [chuckles]
Did you like some of these,
or do you want to…
-I want to…
-[Jen] We can do a second pass
-at them, too…
-…look more.
-[Jen] Okay.
-[Khloé] Um…
Can you guys excuse me for one minute?
Totally.
[line ringing]
[Kim] Hey.
[Khloé] Hey. Are you not coming
to my meeting?
[Kim] What meeting?
Kim, the merch meeting that you set up.
[Kim] I'm, um… I'm rushing
to a meeting with Kylie
for this Australian appearance
we're working on.
Okay.
I'm really irritated.
I just feel like it's--
Like, this keeps
happening to me, so I don't know
what the [bleep] it is about managing us.
But it's not okay.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Hi. What are you doing?
How was your meeting?
I mean, it was good, I just wish
you were here, though.
I know. But I was busy
doing the LuMee stuff.
And then I was busy with Kylie's thing.
I just, like, I can't be
at two places at once, like--
Yeah, but don't [bleep] double book!
I thought I was supposed to be
a priority for you.
You made this whole spiel to me
how you're gonna be a better manager,
and let me show you how this is done.
And you're the same [bleep] person.
Did Kris Jenner
even set up the meeting? No.
[Khloé] Yeah, but you didn't
follow through.
For you to tell me,
"Hey, go and have a meeting
with my people," cool,
but you said
you were gonna be in here,
you forgot, you did Kylie.
And I don't really know
why you're taking over for Mom
when you're acting just like Mom.
Mom forgets about me all the time.
She's never at my meetings.
So, why am I trading one
forgetful manager for another?
-Because in--
-[Kim] I'll call them.
So, I'm sorry.
Like, I'll definitely,
you know, be here next time.
But I'll call them now,
and I'll get, like,
a report sheet on how the meeting went,
and what products they think
that they can really do.
So, have no fear.
[light music playing]
I feel really, really bad
for Khloé,
and I don't want her to feel
like there's no one there to support her.
[Kim] Like, I'm trying to do my best,
but I should've been there.
And, I mean, if anything,
it just really makes me
empathize with my mom,
and just how much she has on her plate,
and how she can't be everywhere at once.
And I totally get it.
The moral of this story is,
I think Mom just needs a team,
'cause obviously it's, like,
hard for one person
to be able to do this.
We've always said that.
Especially when she is like…
Like how Kendall and Kylie have Liz.
-[Kim] Totally.
-[Khloé] Liz is such an OG.
I'm gonna steal Liz
from Kendall and Kylie.
Seriously. Maybe that's,
like, our ambush move.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
-[Scott] Hello.
-[Lisa] Hi. How are you?
-[Scott] Hi.
-[Lisa] Hi, I'm Lisa.
-[Scott] Hey. I'm Scott.
-[Lisa] Nice to meet you.
-[Scott] This is my friend, Rob.
-[Rob] Hey.
-Rob, nice to meet you.
-[Rob] How are you?
I hear you're taking over today.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Rob needs to get in shape,
'cause he's about to be a new dad.
-That's what I heard. Good luck.
-[Rob] Yeah.
Thank you.
[baby crying]
[Scott] I wish I could say
that only sometimes parenting was chaotic,
but it's pretty much
at all times, 24 hours a day.
It's just difficult all around.
So, I figure, like, bring Rob
to a friend's daycare center,
and see if he can really be hands-on
when the kid is not plastic.
-All right. Rob, get in there.
-[laughs]
[Scott] Just start grabbing some kids up.
So, what are we thinking, guys?
-Some games?
-[baby cries]
-Oh, oh! Pick him up.
-See?
Here, come on. You want to play?
Where you going?
You can't go on the carpet
with your shoes on.
You got to take your shoes off.
[Scott] We got a runner!
-[baby cries]
-[Rob] Uh-oh.
-Here.
-[crying continues]
This kid hasn't moved in two days.
[Scott] You all right, buddy.
What's shaking?
What's-- Ooh!
You look like Popeye.
[babies crying]
Everyone, just start crying.
[sighs]
[crying continues]
[Rob] Scott, are you gonna do anything?
[Scott] This is for you
to start to understand
the responsibilities of children.
I already know. I've been
in this game for years.
[Rob] All right,
I'mma go look for him, then.
Oh, no! Oh!
[Scott] That's not bad.
That's a normal day.
[Rob] Here, I'll clean 'em.
No crying.
-[Scott] Oh, God.
-[Rob] You don't see me crying.
[Scott] You're about to see me cry.
Get ready, Rob,
this is gonna be every day
for the rest of your life.
-[Rob] Wanna go outside?
-[baby crying]
-[Rob] Here you go. No? [chuckles]
-[Scott] Aw.
She didn't want to go down?
Looks like somebody loves Bobby.
I feel like, I tried to make this,
like, a little bit of a lesson,
or an experience,
but I realize that…
you're a good-hearted person,
and you're gonna be a good-hearted dad.
-[Rob] Yeah.
-That, you can't teach.
You're gonna be unbelievable
with your daughter.
You know, there's definitely
a couple of things
that Rob still needs to learn.
But that's the keyword.
He can learn them.
But at the end of the day,
he definitely has the heart of a parent,
and I think he's gonna be
an unbelievable one.
[Scott] Oh, my goodness.
Very impressed
with your gymnastics skills.
-I got to tell you.
-It's your turn.
What do you want me
to try to do? A split?
-Mm-hmm.
-How do you do that?
Just slide in.
[grunts]
[screams]
-[Rob] Oh, my God.
-Is that good?
[screams] Oh!
[exhales deeply]
That's what I'm talking about.
[Scott] Good effort. Good effort.
[upbeat music playing]
There's some more monkeys.
We could do a monkey theme.
[Kris] Do you like this one?
-[Scott] It's kind of cool.
-[Kris] Okay. You hold this.
And you hold this.
And let me just think about it.
Oh, look.
This is so cute. We could do--
Where's the monkey?
-[Scott] I put them in storage.
-Here.
-I'll put that--
-That goes with it.
I'll go start a storage lot.
[Kris] Okay. I'm so excited.
After taking a minute,
after my accident,
my body feels good,
my neck feels better,
which makes me happy,
because now I can focus
on the gifts for Rob's shower.
-[Scott] You're just taking everything--
-[gasps]
I like that one better.
See that one over there
with just the daisies?
-Right. That's what I'm saying.
-We need that one.
I'm having another grandchild,
and it's such a blessing.
[Kris] Look at these.
Oh! They're just wonderful.
-They look big, no?
-[Kris] For six to 18 months.
Yeah, but they put a diaper under it.
-Ah. Well, the kid's…
-Goes on top.
…probably gonna have a big butt, anyway.
Okay. Get that. I love this.
We need the matching blanket.
-[Kris] We want the hat.
-Take the hat.
Oh! Do we have a changing table?
[Kris] We'll take one of those.
That's what-- We are gonna do
something practical here.
Practical would've been
if we left, like, 25 minutes ago.
Never had so much fun in my life.
[Kris] I'm so excited about this party.
I can't think of any more
important reason to celebrate.
Do you have a breast pump?
-Uh, I…
-Yeah.
But we need a huge one,
'cause she's got huge knockers.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] I think I was
in a 2Pac video, you guys.
Kim, you were not in a 2Pac video.
-Swear to God.
-[Kourtney] Yes.
-2Pac!
-[Khloé] Kourtney…
2Pac is never your style.
-Never.
-I like 2Pac.
I've got to find this,
because I swear,
me, Kim, and Bijou were in a 2Pac video.
-[Kim] No one knows…
-[Khloé] Can you find it?
-You got to find it.
-[phone chimes]
[chiming continues]
[Kim] Rob and Chyna are fighting again.
[Khloé] What's the fighting about?
-[Kim] I don't know, I mean--
-[Khloé] Like, intense?
[Kim] She texts some crazy things.
He texts her crazy things all night long.
He just doesn't want to go to the shower.
[dramatic music playing]
We have the shower planned
for tomorrow for Rob and Chyna.
But now they get into this big fight,
and we don't know what's going on.
He said that he doesn't want
to celebrate a shower
because this pregnancy
has been really bad for him
and really awful for him.
You guys, our brother's
coming to the shower.
That's crazy.
So what do we do?
[Khloé] I don't know.
I feel like we should try to…
get him to come for Mom.
If it's for nobody else,
it should be for her.
She does so much for him.
We just really want to do this for Rob.
Especially my mom.
She's so excited to give him presents,
and just, like,
really, like, celebrate him,
so I think she's definitely
not gonna take it well
if he doesn't show up.
I hate that, like, I just have to be
the middleman between these two.
[line ringing]
-[Chyna] Hey.
-Hey.
[Kim] So, Chyna, Rob is now saying
he doesn't want to come to the shower,
and I just don't know what to do.
[Chyna] Oh, [bleep]. Okay.
[Kim] We, you know,
want to shower you,
but we also want him to be
a part of it. And for him--
[Chyna] Yes, him involved,
no, for sure.
Uh, listen, I'm for that.
You should just have it with Rob,
I totally understand.
I love that Chyna is so understanding
and has this great idea
that we'll just make the shower for Rob.
[Kim] But I just want my brother
to figure out how to be a partner.
The drama has got to stop.
[Chyna] Just let me know
how Rob is feeling.
Okay.
[Chyna] Thanks for calling me,
though. Bye.
-[Kim] Okay, bye.
-Bye.
[upbeat music playing]
I was gonna wear that dress today.
And the choker!
[Khloé] Kourtney, you look so cute.
It's Buford.
What an amazing shower.
[Kris] The shower looks great.
With guy stuff, and things
that a dad would need.
[Kylie] Wait, wait, keep going,
keep going, keep going.
[Kris] I want to really celebrate Rob
and make it really special for him,
and show him how excited we are.
By the way,
why didn't I get a baby shower
the three times I had kids?
I don't know, it's a more…
unusual relationship.
You want to see something
more unusual than us?
[Kris laughs]
-[Kim] Hey.
-[Rob] I'm not coming to the shower
if Chyna's not coming.
What were you guys even thinking?
I don't even wanna
talk about this anymore.
[Kim] I mean, this is crazy.
All we're trying to do
is to keep my brother happy.
[Scott] Wait, so where's Bob?
Isn't this his shower?
[Kim] He can't even show up
to his own shower?
Like, we've put so much time
and energy into this.
I don't know,
it makes no sense to me.
[Kim] You guys,
I have an announcement!
Oh, God.
[Kim] Well, since no one's here to enjoy…
[Khloé] What's happening?
[Kim] I just got off the phone
with Rob, he's not coming.
[Kris] What a little butt face.
-What's happening?
-Rob and Chyna got into a fight,
so we thought we were doing
the best thing to not have drama.
So we made it a guy's baby shower
and invited Rob's guy friends.
And Chyna was so cool with that.
She's like, "Look,
I'm having my other shower."
"It's all good,
like, don't worry about it."
And then Rob now flipped out on us,
like this was supposed to be about her.
[Kim] Now no one's coming.
[Kendall] I can't deal with the dram.
[Kris] Oh, brother.
[Kim] I mean, this is crazy.
Rob is accusing us
of not being supportive of him and Chyna,
and all we're doing
is trying to be supportive.
And we're trying to just do
whatever he wants.
We thought he wanted a shower with her,
then we thought he didn't want
the shower with her,
so we tried to do it for him,
and then he gets mad and doesn't show up.
I can't take this [bleep].
Like, I can't tiptoe anymore.
Like, I've had it.
[Kris] I'm just sad that Rob's not here.
[Khloé] [bleep] Rob. Ruins everything.
[upbeat music playing]
[phone ringing]
-[Kris] Hey, Rob.
-[Rob] Hey, Mom.
What's up, honey?
[Rob] I know it's been a few days
since the shower, but I heard
why Chyna wasn't there.
I am so sorry that I messed
everything up for the shower,
but if you could just go to the backyard,
I got a little surprise for you.
[Kris] I think it's safe to say
that our attempt at throwing Rob and Chyna
a baby shower did not go quite as planned.
-Oh, Rob!
-[Sheila] Oh!
[Kris] This is the cutest surprise.
He sent me balloons.
And they're amazing.
Amazing.
-[Kris] Just really sweet.
-[Rob] I'm sorry about the baby shower.
Hopefully, we can get
the whole family together soon
and I'll make up for it.
[Kim] Oh, thank you, Rob. I love you.
[Rob] All right, I love you.
-He's a wonderful…
-[Joyce] Gorgeous.
-…wonderful guy.
-[Joyce] So thoughtful.
Aw. That's really cool.
Really, really cool.
I just have the best kids.
[upbeat music playing]
[Kim] Whoa.
Are you guys all gonna spin me?
I'm gonna be too dizzy.
Rob and Chyna
aren't fighting at the moment,
so we all rush over to Kourtney's
just to let them know we love them,
we support their crazy asses,
and open up their gifts real quick…
before they start fighting again.
-[Kris] Hey.
-Oh, hey.
-Look who's here.
-[Scott] Welcome to the…
Hey, guys.
[Kris] Oh, presents.
[Khloé] Oh, hello.
Okay, so I want to just
start off this little soiree
by having Rob and Chyna
open this gift first
because this is very special.
Paul Crane told us
that he was probably gonna be a girl.
So I had something made
to bring Rob home from the hospital.
These better not be some thigh-high boots.
I wanted you to open this gift
because this is what Rob looked like…
when he came home from the hospital.
[Rob] Oh, in a pink, uh, pink thing?
-[Kris] In his baby bunting.
-[all] Aw…
Which of course I saved
for 30-- almost 30 years.
-[Rob] Is this the same one?
-That's so cute.
-[Kris] Same one.
-[Chyna] You kept that?
-[Kim] That's cute.
-You know?
-[Chyna] That is so sweet.
-[Kris] Isn't it cute?
So Rob, why didn't you show up
to the baby shower?
Um, pretty much it was a misunderstanding,
and I thought you guys
were trying to be shady,
and, like, only surprise me
and not include her.
So, I took it offensively,
and, obviously, didn't show up.
So instead of talking to your family,
you just decided to, like…
I want it to be about
both of us. That was just my…
It should be about…
it should be about the women
that's birthing the baby
just as much as it should--
It's both of us.
I just took it the wrong way.
-My bad.
-[Kris] But the good news
is you're a sensitive dude,
and we love you.
And it's all good,
and I love you guys.
-And thank you for this.
-This is amazing. Thank you.
[Rob] Of course,
I feel terrible that the shower
that they planned for… for me got ruined.
Ooh! This is really nice.
Sometimes when Chyna and I
aren't doing so well,
I let it get the best of me,
and I need to work on that.
That's cute.
[Rob] I'm super excited
to be having this baby.
It's something that I've always wanted.
I just picked out
some of my favorite books.
[Rob] Thank you, Kourt.
Rob has wanted to be a dad
for as long as I can remember.
Baby Robert?
[Kris] It's every mother's dream
to see her child be happy.
This is Robert's first Christmas.
[Kris] So, for Rob…
this is such a great step
in the right direction.
And I'm so proud of that boy.
Oh, Rob, it's a daddy bag.
Look, they got a princess hat.
Despite all of the craziness,
and all the drama,
there's, like,
so much to be thankful for.
New beginnings, new baby.
It'll be so much fun.
I can't wait.
Oh, this is so sweet.
[Rob] This is all very, very nice.
-[Kris] Do you like it?
-Thank you so much.
[Kris] You're welcome.
We all love you so much,
and we're so happy
that this is all happening,
and we can't wait till she's born.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mom, you want me to open this?
[Kris] Yeah, there are gifts in there.
Look, babe.
[Kim] A little Hermès robe.
[Rob] Ooh, little Hermès robe.
[Kris] Open it. Look at this.
[Rob] Two white Range Rovers, pretty good.
Oh, my God.
[Kris] It's cashmere, which--
It's La Perla.
Isn't that great?
And then that goes with it.
Wait, no one got the baby a Birkin bag?
[laughs]
[camera shutter clicking]
[Chyna] Coming up on the
"Rob and Chyna Baby Special."
The baby's finally here.
-Here, Ma, feel right here.
-[Shalana exclaims]
I'm gonna simulate a contraction for you.
[moaning loudly]
[bleep]. I need to learn that
-just to learn that.
-[laughs]
-[King squeals]
-[Chyna laughs]
[Chyna] It's King's birthday coming up,
and I just want it to be,
like, super special,
'cause this is his last year
-of being an only child.
-[children cheering]
So, what are you gonna do now?
Moving? Staying?
I'm gonna have to go back to her house.
With a pregnant woman,
you're gonna have to suck this one up.
Paige, I know you don't want to leave me.
-[Paige] That's what you came here to say?
-[Chyna] Are you gonna miss me?
[Scott] Congrats on the baby shower.
Hey, hey!
I thought this was, like, a chill thing.
I didn't know it was, like, the Oscars.
Did you ever think about a water birth?
I think she's gonna do a C-section.
-What?
-But she's down to do that.
-She's down to go natural?
-[Rob] Yeah.
Who's gonna be in the room
while you have this baby?
My mom, Kris, Rob.
Oh, Kris is gonna be in the room?
[Rob] Chyna's mom just got into town.
What was that whole thing
that your mom said
that she said bad things about her?
Her mom's just, like, a loose cannon.
Sometimes it's like you intimidate people.
I go off when it's deserved.
And you not acting accordingly,
I'mma handle you.
I'm trying to find my mom
so she can see you.
-Oh, God, here we go.
-[Shalana] Excuse me.
-Are you scared?
-Yeah.
[indistinct chattering]
[crying] I'm freaking out.
[Kris] This is Dad.
[baby crying]