My enemy is near.
Give me the strength.
Guide my hand to kill him
and return alive to kill those who remain.
May all evil omens, the dire cry of birds,
a malign conjunction of stars,
all evil dreams and angry words...
Master?
A samurai is honorable.
You are no samurai.
May they all be drained of power.
The ninth level.
Fowler.
Ninety-five, 96, 97, 98, 99.
Thick milk, long soured,
over old curds.
The best dairy on the Irish isle,
shared with you on our own.
I was raised on this.
Milk?
From a cow?
I shipped in two beeves special
to feed my honored guest.
Hm.
A good... sourness.
I never tire
of your people's aversion to impoliteness.
A taboo against offense,
even as you plan the death of thousands.
Surely... not so many need to die.
Anyone who stands in the way.
Anyone not on their knees when it's over.
Your guns will be ready?
They are all ready.
Already ready. Ready for all.
All we need are loyal men
ready to fire them.
You ask Master Chiba
to wager his excellent position
as advisor to the shogun.
The risks are great.
Thousands of men
guard the shogun's castle.
Ten thousand.
Twenty. It doesn't matter.
They guard it with knives.
No one makes
a better blade than your people.
No one invents
better ways to kill people than mine.
A gun will never
be as beautiful as a sword.
But with a gun,
you can take any sword you want.
The shogun and his entire family
will be dead come spring.
And Master Chiba
will be the right hand
of our appointed man...
That was tasteless of me.
Our men are trained and eager to serve.
Each one hates the shogun
with all the blood in his heart.
Oh, I don't hate the shogun.
I just want his chair.
It's him.
He's come.
I told you he'd come.
I want to watch.
Why set traps
only to mash the rat yourself?
Sit, we have business.
I want to watch.
But you know what's next. My flowers.
It won't be enough.
Fine.
Send your giant.
You will
get yourself killed.
You are a monster.
No one can know you're hiding.
I thought you had to be something special.
Go ahead.
Just jump.
It felt... dark.
Master?
Ringo?
Mizu!
Mizu?
Taigen.
That's...
That's my scarf.
Taigen.
Are you real?
I think so.
Can you walk?
Might be slow.
This is up.
Down is that way.
- Out is...
- We're not leaving.
We're going to the ninth level.
I have a man to kill.
I hate you.
Tea party.
I'll help.
No one gets to kill you, but...
Put me back in the dungeon.
♪ For whom the bell tolls ♪
I am not afraid.
My whole life has been a battle.
An apprentice
would never leave his master's side.
I'll avenge us, Mama.
I swear it.
Hate... you.
He's nowhere. He disappeared!
I told you.
I said this samurai could not be stopped,
but you wouldn't listen.
Just a man. Let him come.
Perhaps we should
excuse ourselves from their danger.
What danger?
An attack on the shogun's emissary
is an attack on the shogun himself.
No one would dare
attack them with us here.
Yes.
That's true.
Abijah Fowler.
Where is he?
You see?
No one murders so well as the British.
It's our number one export.
Look at you.
No one's ever made it up
half this far before.
How did you like our monkeys?
Oh, you found your friend.
He was stupidly loyal.
And he wouldn't tell us a thing about you.
Not even to save his fingernails.
You came all this way... for me?
Because of what I just may be to you?
May be.
I thought I accounted
for all my bastards over the years.
They line the tunnel you came in.
All those half-breeds, like you.
I'll kill you.
All four of you.
I see.
Who was it?
I heard something happened to old Violet.
Was that you?
For Violet.
Are you still alive?
Why?
I know what I'm supposed to do.
Be a samurai, like you.
Okay.
I'll teach you.