Someone murdered
the Guardians of the Globe
last night.
I'm Allen, by the way.
The Coalition of Planets
will want to hear about you.
I couldn't move.
My heart was racing.
That's fear.
I don't have
anyone to talk to,
so I keep it all inside.
What's this?
Something that helped me.
Yeah!
Ooh, crap.
You brought me to Paris?
Is that a casino?
Make sure the voice
in your ear isn't
the only one you listen to.
You're way too good for me!
You goddamn geriatric hypocrite.
- Come on!
- You and I were never a thing.
The Immortal and I are.
I call me the Shapesmith.
You're not
your father, Mark.
That's why I'm going back.
I guess this is it.
Time to push my baby bird
out of the nest.
It's a good thing
I can already fly.
You're
gonna be okay, right?
You know I can be home in like
five minutes if you need me.
I'll be fine.
Anger is a part of it.
Part of the grieving.
Yeah, I... I know.
I promised myself
I wouldn't cry.
Oh, this past year's
just been so...
Tough?
Yeah.
But college is a fresh start.
And I want you to enjoy
every second of it.
This is your chance
to figure out who you are.
And I don't mean Invincible.
I mean Mark Grayson.
My only son.
My... my baby boy.
- My...
- Okay, okay.
- I love you, Mom.
- Mmm.
And don't do drugs.
Would they even work on me?
You do not need to find out.
I'll come home
for dinner on Sunday.
Um...
one second, please.
Shh, okay.
Just let me take this call.
Okay.
Hi. Sorry.
Hi. Um...
I got your card
from my friend Olga.
- My name is Debbie G...
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah-yeah, no. Uh, sorry,
no last names, Debbie.
But Olga told me about you.
I've been expecting your call.
Séance Dog? Really?
- What are we, 12?
- Hmm.
Does that look crooked to you?
Help me out here, Mark.
You already have a girlfriend
and you're a superhero.
I, on the other hand, am single
and have no superpowers
and, thus, actually
have to attempt game.
This isn't helping.
Maybe it'll just make you
look better by comparison.
♪ ♪
Huh. Excellent point.
Okay. See this?
It's a sock?
And when it's on the door
handle like so,
it means go eat a taco
or fly to Spain
or do whatever you have to do,
but don't come in
until the sock is gone.
And I will do the same
for you. Got it?
Hi, um, there's
some stuff out here.
Does it belong to you guys?
- Oh! Toys.
- Uh, they're collectibles.
Sorry, buddy.
I don't know
what I was thinking.
Who has sex
on the first day of college?
I don't know, Mark.
Lots of people, probably.
- Us, for example?
- Us?
My roommate doesn't arrive
until tomorrow, so...
we have the
whole place to ourselves.
Uh, o-okay, I mean, yeah.
Like... like, right now?
I mean, we could.
O-Okay. Um... yeah.
I bought these.
Okay. Good.
Good to have those. Mmm.
♪ I wasn't in the mood for...
Wait.
You don't have, like,
super sperm
or something, do you?
Uh, it's not...
I mean, it seems normal.
Not that I would...
I-I think it's fine.
♪ I could do this ♪
♪ It was kind of like
a summer love...
And you wouldn't accidentally
crush me or something?
Like, if you get excited?
I've seen what you can do.
No. I would never...
That's not, like,
a thing I would do.
Maybe we'll try with me on top,
just to be safe.
Sure.
♪ I can't control this...
Turn off the lights first?
- How'd you do that?
- Superpowers, baby.
♪ I need a medic ♪
- Don't call me "baby."
- Got it.
♪ Can you stay still
while I'm like this...
And so,
dear audience,
perhaps it's time to give
Amber and Mark some privacy
and turn our attention
to the stars
and a story that began
generations ago in...
We begin on the planet Unopa.
A peaceful and thriving world,
the Unopans had achieved
harmony with nature
and technology...
...until everything changed
in the blink of an eye.
Like a plague of
unequaled potency,
a dark force invaded Unopa.
It swept across the planet,
conquering it
in a matter of days.
The Unopans that died never knew
who their conquerors were.
The ones that lived
quickly learned the name...
Viltrumite.
However,
the Unopan spirit was unbroken.
Biding their time for decades,
they waited for
a moment of weakness
and rebelled.
Unfortunately, they still
underestimated their oppressors.
But all was not lost.
Ever resourceful, some
Unopans were able to escape,
abandoning their home
for the stars
and the promise of a new life.
Within a generation,
they started breeding camps
on various Unopan outposts
to rebuild their population,
the rumors of which caught
some very powerful
galactic attention.
Impressed with
the Unopan survival
and escape from
a Viltrumite invasion,
Thaedus, the leader of
the Coalition of Planets,
invited them
to the planet Talescria
to join their ranks.
You have
our deepest sympathies,
Marvin of Unopa.
The Viltrumite campaign has
become the scourge of the galaxy
and we stand united against it.
We are currently devising
a weapon to stop them.
If you wish to help,
we would be happy
to join your coalition.
Marvin explained
to Thaedus
that the breeding camps
were also
a genetic enhancement program
designed to breed a soldier
that could defeat
a Viltrumite in combat.
The results were...
not promising.
Until... Allen.
He was
the first and only success.
From the day he was born,
Allen was trained to be
the greatest fighter
the universe had ever known.
Even before adulthood,
an opponent could not be found
who didn't fall to his might.
Soon, it was time for Allen to
embark on his first mission.
But while stronger than
most of the universe,
Allen still couldn't match
even a single Viltrumite
in combat.
The program was considered
a failure
and ended.
Instead, Allen was made
a planetary evaluation officer
and sent to discover
any being able to defeat him
in hope of finding
an ally strong enough
to withstand a Viltrumite.
And while it may be true
that Allen was supposed to be
keeping tabs on the planet
Urath and accidentally
went to Earth instead,
his mistake led him
to Mark Grayson,
a half-human, half-Viltrumite
sympathetic to
the coalition cause.
Because sometimes,
to change the entire universe,
you have to be...
♪ Trouble's on
when you travel light ♪
♪ Dropped call
in the dead of night...
Home sweet home.
♪ Will you answer me? ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Make amends
on another strike...
This time
Allen bears a rare
and valuable gift
for the coalition.
Hope.
Data log.
Hello to you, too.
Here you go.
Hmm.
You found the right planet
this time.
Yes, I found the right planet.
Because it was the wrong planet
you already found before.
- Sure, but that's not really...
- Most of our agents don't make
so many astronavigational
mistakes.
Listen, sparky.
Is it still a mistake if
it ends up saving the universe?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
You're late.
General Telia.
My apologies.
I got here as soon as I could.
The Viltrumites hit Aikreon
while you were gone.
What? But they just
joined the council...
It's terrified the sector.
Other planets we were talking to
cut all communications.
We need more allies.
And they're making it
very difficult.
Then good thing I found us one.
What news, Allen of Unopa?
Did you warn the Earth champion
that a Viltrumite lives
among his people?
Yeah, I did.
But it turns out
he's a Viltrumite, too.
His name is Mark
and he's only half-Viltrumite.
Unbelievable.
I know, I know.
It sounds bad.
But he is not like them.
He didn't even know
what a Viltrumite was
until recently.
How is that possible?
No one told him, I guess.
When he got his powers,
all he wanted to do was
help other humans.
Then his father decided it was
time to conquer the planet,
so they, they got
in a fight about it.
Viltrumite against Viltrumite?
That has not happened
since the great purge.
And get this.
After they fought, his dad left.
Like, left the planet.
Disappeared completely.
We could never trust
one of them.
Mark isn't like
other Viltrumites.
He just wants to
protect his world.
And conquer others in its name.
No, stop.
That is not his deal.
He's a good guy,
not a conqueror.
So far.
Have you guys been
listening at all?
For years we've been
searching for a hole
in the Viltrumites' armor.
This could be it.
Thaedus, you can't trust
this report.
Allen is right.
Viltrumites never abandon
their missions.
Yet one has.
Viltrumites
do not battle each other,
but a son defies his father.
These are weaknesses.
The first we've found
and ones we must
learn to exploit.
Perhaps Viltrum's grip
on the galaxy is not
as steady as we imagine.
You have done well, Allen,
and given us much to discuss.
We will call on you again soon.
Thank you, great Thaedus.
I'm honored to serve.
They have no idea
what this means.
If there are other
Viltrumite kids out there,
maybe we can turn them
against their parents, too.
Also, why are they
breeding with other races?
I thought Viltrumites believed
in racial purity.
See? That's a good question.
Why didn't they ask
stuff like that
instead of shouting at me?
Allen, before you depart,
a word?
Of course, wise Thaedus.
I find it convenient
and somewhat alarming
that Aikreon was hit so soon
after joining the coalition.
It's as if the Viltrumites
had knowledge
from inside the council.
You want me to discover
if someone's betrayed us.
Ah, Allen, you continue
to prove yourself
the coalition's most
valuable asset.
Thank you, sir.
If there's a mole,
I'll find them.
Hey, Vorg.
Hey, little buddy.
Did you miss me?
Yes, you did.
You did miss your daddy,
didn't you?
Shh.
Huh?
Did you miss me?
Oh, I missed you.
- Yeah? How much?
- The most.
Or like ten times that amount.
Maybe more even.
Oh, let's see if that's true.
Oh, goodness.
Tentacles.
I, uh...
Perhaps now would be
a good time to return to Earth
and rejoin Amber Bennett
and Mark Grayson
as they begin their studies
at the prestigious
Upstate University.
Oh, I see, uh...
No. Let's not do that, then.
Well, um...
Aha, aha.
Here we find
the Unopan feline.
Perhaps unsurprisingly,
he has one large eye
in the center of his head.
But that doesn't
stop him from having
all manner of
household adventures.
Oh, man,
I have been dying for this.
I don't know
how you eat kanzlok.
It's disgusting.
He doesn't think so.
Mmm... Mm?
No matter how far I travel,
Talescria's still
the most beautiful planet
I've ever seen.
There's hundreds of planets
that look exactly like it.
Sure. But only one has you.
Wow.
Hey, what did Thaedus
want to talk about
after the council meeting?
Um...
Look, I'm not really
supposed to, uh...
Okay, okay, fine.
Thaedus thinks there's a mole.
And I am supposed to...
Allen!
Oh, fuck.
Unopan,
answer our questions
and we will consider
sparing your life.
That is not your style.
Isn't it kill first,
ask questions... never?
You will tell us everything
about your encounter with
the Viltrumite of Earth.
I mean, not technically
a question if...
Are you certain
he sired an heir?
he abandoned his post?
Who told you that?
I mean it.
I'd really like to know
because...
Where's the father now?
The father?
Which one was he again?
You biclops all kind of
look the same to me.
♪ ♪
Great Thaedus.
How is he?
Uh... alive. For now.
It may not seem like it,
but that is cause
for celebration.
They once again underestimate
the Unopan will to survive.
I know you and Allen are
special to one another.
Thank you, sir.
To come here,
attack Allen at home,
the Viltrumites must know
we've discovered something.
Something that scares them.
And we will exploit it.
You should get some rest.
Go.
I will watch over him.
Forgive me, Allen.
Come on.
- Two more.
- Come on.
Two more.
Are we gonna talk about this,
or is it just gonna be
awkward forever?
Uh... the second one?
God, why do you have to be
so immature?
I'm immature? Uh,
you cheated on me
with the Immortal.
That's what you think happened?
Seriously?
And even if that was true,
you were cheating on Eve
with me first.
Okay, but that worked out
in your favor.
You are unbelievable.
And you're gross.
The Immortal's like
2,000 years old, you know.
Not that I have to justify
anything to you ever,
but if you add up
the amount of time
my duplicates and I have lived,
we are probably the same age.
Oh, okay, okay.
So I'm too young for you now?
I-I-Is that it?
No, Rex.
You're just an asshole.
Well, how is that news?
Look, come on, Kate, talk to me.
What is this about?
You really want to know, Rex?
Yeah, I kinda do.
Fine.
The Immortal's
the only person I've ever met
who's died
as many times as I have.
Maybe you don't understand that,
but it means something.
He gets it.
And... Rex doesn't.
I get that you
shouldn't be eavesdropping.
So please fuck
the fuck off already.
It's not your gym, dickbag.
What? Are you gonna knock
my teeth out again?
- Don't be a jerk, Rex.
- Too late.
Uh, at least I'm not a cheater.
- But you literally are!
- But that was before!
I'm not now.
Oh, hello, chums.
I'd like to run while remaining
in a stationary location.
Is that cool beans?
Where are you from?
For real.
Go ahead, Shapesmith.
I'll just be over there.
In a stationary location.
Well, this has been
about as much fun
as eating a light bulb.
Hey, Mozart, what's all this?
Uh... it's Strauss, actually.
Is that a brain?
Is that your brain?
Uh... yes.
You're gonna make me ask,
aren't you?
I was less than satisfied
with my performance
against the Giant.
Oh, yeah.
You totally shit the bed
on that one.
It sucks actually
feeling fear, doesn't it?
It was...
unacceptable.
Sorry.
Sensitivity's never been
my strong suit.
No, you're right.
I-I don't need you
to sugarcoat it.
Which is why I've decided
to resolve the problem.
I set up
this visual feedback system
so I could practice controlling
my fear response
via meditation
and active thought.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
People feel fear for a reason.
And it's usually a good reason.
Fear is an extraneous emotion
that serves no real purpose
for someone like me.
I strongly disagree, but...
I guess
you'll find out the hard way.
Have fun next time you fall
off a cliff or something.
Amanda?
Fear hasn't just made me useless
in battle.
It-It's prevented me
from doing something else
I've wanted to do
for quite some time.
Will you go to a movie with me?
A... movie?
Oh.
Sure.
Sure, Rudy.
I'll-I'll go to a movie
with you.
It feels like vertigo.
They talk about
the physical symptoms of grief--
depression, lethargy, all that.
Uh, but...
when the thought of her
takes me by surprise
in the middle of the day,
it's like I'm falling.
I try to grab on to something
but there's nothing to grab.
It's terrifying
and exhausting, and I just...
I still miss her so much.
That's all I got.
Thanks, Theo.
Okay, let's take a few,
everybody.
Carol?
Hi! You must be Debbie.
I'm so sorry
about the other day.
My three-month-old has
the worst colic right now.
Ugh, I remember.
My son,
he was such a fussy baby.
How old is he now?
Eighteen.
Practically a man.
He is.
So, um, ground rules.
We're not that different
from other support groups
except we're even more strict
when it comes to identity.
First names only.
You aren't required to share
till you're ready,
but that's why we're
all sacrificing a Tuesday night,
so might as well
make the most of it.
Bathroom's down the hall.
Coffee tastes like battery acid.
Any questions?
I think you covered it.
Great. Have a seat.
All right, everybody, who's up?
Hi. I'm Lucinda.
Hi, Lucinda.
I didn't say much
at my first meeting either.
Took me almost a month
to talk to anybody.
Now they can't shut me up.
I see.
Sorry.
I can leave you alone.
N-No, it's fine. I j...
Uh, I dropped my son off
at college today.
Empty house?
Yeah.
It's okay. I totally get it.
We all do.
Hey, don't take this
the wrong way,
but there's a bar
down the street
some of us like to go to
after group.
Oh.
Uh, I just figured,
since it seems like neither
of us wants to go home.
But no pressure, of course.
Sure.
I could use a drink.
It's, uh, it's kind of a dive.
The best ones are.
Never?
Of course I've watched films,
but, no,
I've never attended one.
I had more important things
to do.
And I, uh...
wouldn't have fit before.
Someday you'll have to tell me
all about your childhood.
Oh, we're already seeing
a horror movie tonight.
Hey. You wanted to test
your fear response again.
Uh, two tickets
for Midnight Slaughter.
That's rated "R."
I see.
And?
You need your parents to buy you
R-rated tickets.
That's ridiculous.
How does a parent's presence
change a film's suitability
for the underage?
It changes it
in that I don't get fired
- for selling you a ticket.
- Hey.
It's fine. They're my kids.
They can see the movie.
What?
You want to do a DNA test now?
- How...
- This might be your
first movie, but it's not mine.
You'd be surprised what people
will do for ten bucks.
Wait, if this is
your first movie,
what other normal stuff
haven't you done?
This is supposed
to be appetizing?
Says the guy who used
to eat food through his butt.
That's not how...
It entered through my...
Mmm.
Is it appetizing now?
I know these aren't good for me,
but...
Oh, shut up.
A good burger and fries
is one of the greatest pleasures
in life.
Yes. Mmm. I'm discovering that.
Oh! Oh! I'm sorry!
Let me get you some more.
Uh, waiter?
Waiter, uh, more fries, please.
Rudy, there's no waiters
in Burger Mart.
Did you move
after your partner
passed away?
I moved the furniture.
Couldn't afford to relocate.
You?
I stayed for my son, but... now?
I don't know.
Maybe it's time for a change.
Change is good.
Yeah.
Problem is, where would I go?
Somewhere new.
So much of it
still feels connected to him.
When we wanted Indian food,
we'd go to India.
We'd fly to Tokyo and back
on a Wednesday night.
Oh.
One Christmas Eve,
we even made a snowman
at the North Pole.
My son cried when he didn't see
Santa's workshop,
so we told him we'd gone
to the South Pole by mistake.
Sounds like you two had
a pretty amazing life together.
We did.
You can still be angry.
That's okay. God knows I am.
Thanks.
It's good to talk
with someone who understands.
I wish
I could tell you it gets easier,
- but Alana's been gone
nearly a year...
- Uh...
...and I still reach across
the bed for her every morning.
Alana?
- You mean...
- Yeah.
She was the Green Ghost.
Guess I just broke
rule number one of SOS.
Not that it matters now,
since she got murdered
by that alien psychopath.
I-I didn't know
she had a partner.
We used to fight about that.
She wanted to protect me.
I need to use the restroom.
Are you okay?
No, I'll-I'll be right back.
Oh, my God.
You had sex with Amber.
Whoa, what?
- William.
- How was it?
- I want all the details.
- Gross.
No. No way. No.
We're roommates now. This is
what roommates talk about.
Okay, well, what about you?
How was Mr. Is This Your Stuff?
What are you talking about?
That hot guy from earlier.
I came back, and you had
the sock on the door.
Oh.
Ugh, I wish.
I must have forgotten to take it
off after my demonstration.
Wait, y-you thought
h-he and I...
Uh, yeah.
Hmm.
Super flattered.
But I'm kind of still screwed-up
about what happened to Rick.
I always imagined we'd be here
at Upstate together.
Cecil said he's doing better.
He should be released
in a month or so.
I know.
Sorry, I wasn't trying
to make you feel bad.
No, it's, it's okay.
Hey, I bet that's somebody ready
for round two.
Coming, Ambers.
It's not Amber.
We made plans
for tomorrow night.
I bet you did.
Mark Grayson?
It's for you.
Mark Grayson.
I need your help.
Who are you?
Why, it is I, Séance Dog.
Fight fire with fire,
fight evil with magic.
That's me.
Huh?
Mark.
I come with an important...
Séance Dog isn't real.
He's a comic book character.
In your dimension, yes.
But there exist myriad
other worlds
where dogs and magic are
as real as the air you breathe.
We have dogs.
Dogs are real.
Well, then you're halfway
to understanding.
Open your mind and let me help
you reach the other side.
Hey, well, whatever you're
doing, don't, I'm warning you.
Mark Grayson, I come because...
Wait! Please!
You don't understand.
Last chance.
Who are you,
and what do you want?
I'm sorry, my disguise
was meant to disarm you.
I thought if I appeared
as something you love...
- Disarm me for what?
- Please.
I'm not a threat.
The journey to your world
has taken me most of my life.
May I rise?
If you answer my questions.
My name is Nuolzot.
I am from the planet Thraxa.
My people sent me
to plead for your help.
Thraxa?
It's a couple galaxies away,
uh, give or take.
I mean, not very far.
You go... It doesn't matter.
How do you know who I am?
Rumors of the one
they call Invincible
have spread like wildfire.
Your speed, your strength.
You are the only one
who can save our people
from the meteor showers
destroying our world.
Okay, listen, um...
Nuolzot.
Nuol... zot.
I just got to college, man.
I haven't even had
my first day of classes yet.
Are you kidding me,
Mark?
Nuolzot came all the way here
from...
to beg for your help,
and you're too busy?
How many bug people
are in danger?
All of them.
But, like, a number.
Oh. Forty-two billion.
Don't worry about your classes.
I'll cover for you somehow.
Why do you care so much?
Because last time you didn't
want to help someone,
we both regretted it.
We believe in you,
Mark Grayson.
No,
you can't just go
to some random planet
with some random alien.
Are you insane?
The Guardians can keep an eye
on things while I'm gone.
I won't be more than
a few weeks. A month tops.
Depending on asteroid traffic.
Oh, it shouldn't be
that bad.
It shouldn't be that bad.
You work for me
here on Earth.
Look, a-a lot of people
died because of me, Cecil.
This is a chance to save lives.
Billions of them.
And this is an order: do not go.
I need to listen to myself
before I listen to you.
Your father felt the same way.
Well, I'll check in
when I get back.
Goddamn it, Mark.
Fucking kid.
You're a good human,
Mark Grayson.
Hey, when I'm in this outfit,
I'm Invincible.
So far.
No, I'm saying, like, you have
to call me Invincible.
It's like a secret identity.
Oh, right, of course.
Invincible.
We need to make
a quick stop first.
Hey, you. How's it going?
Hey. Come to your window.
And?
Look up.
Mark?
Uh, I have to go away
for a few weeks.
To space again.
Like, right now?
A lot of people are gonna die
if I don't.
- I'm sorry, but I...
- No, stop, stop.
Don't apologize.
Never apologize
for saving lives.
This is the deal,
and I'm good with it. Go.
Thanks.
Can you tell my mom, please?
Yeah, of course.
Be careful.
Always.
Amber, I, uh...
Yeah?
I love you.
Are you comfortable,
Mark Gray...
Uh, sorry. Invincible?
Yeah. Thanks.
Hey, how long until
we get to Thraxa?
Approximately six
of your Earth days.
Space sucks.
Debbie. Are you okay?
Di-Did I say something wrong?
I'm sorry. Tonight...
Tonight's been a little much.
I get it. I-It's a lot.
I haven't talked to anyone
about any of this,
except my son,
and that probably makes me
a bad parent on top
of everything else.
Hey,
it takes time to heal.
I can't heal because
my husband's not dead.
He's just gone.
He's gone because...
because he murdered Alana
and the other Guardians
and almost killed my son, too.
Your husband.
Your husband's Omni-Man?
I thought he was Nolan Grayson,
but that wasn't true.
The last 20 years of my life
have been a lie.
I wish he was dead.
I wish I could grieve
and move on, but I ca...
I-I can't.
I wish he was dead, too.
But not for your sake.
You shouldn't come back
to the group.
It wouldn't be a safe space
with you there.
I didn't know.
I didn't know who he was.
You should have.
Invincible?
Invincible.
- Invincible.
- Huh!
We're here.
Uh... hi?
Oh, don't mind them.
Come.
The monarch wants
to meet you at once.
Wait, what exactly about
this planet needs saving?
Where are the meteors?
Meteors?
What meteors?
The ones that are
killing billions?
Oh, yeah, those meteors.
You know, must be
a touch of dementia.
We age much quicker
than you humans, you know.
Uh, don't worry,
the monarch will explain all.
Your Majesty.
May I present Invincible
of Earth.
Oh.
Hello, son.
Huh?
It's been a while.
Dad?