Hey.
Honey, how did it go?
Well, the company
actually folded
while I was in the interview.
Oh.
But...
(Chuckles)
You stole all their sugar.
Yeah. That's not all.
Mm-hmm.
And look, salt and pepper...
Ooh, hoo.
We got creamer, and... wait for it.
Mm-hmm.
Wait for it.
Uh-huh.
Ketchup.
Ooh, hoo!
Well, it'll all come in handy
'cause you got your last
unemployment check today.
Oh, yeah. I can't believe
it's already been a year.
I can't either.
But don't worry about it.
As you can see, our lifestyle
doesn't have to suffer.
(Laughs)
Oh, hey, your insurance from
Pontiac is about to run out,
so I made an appointment for you
to get a physical tomorrow.
No, sweetheart, I told you...
Oh, no, hey.
Lee, as a woman,
I'm gonna have to ask you
to stop comparing
a prostate exam
to the pinball scene
in "The Accused."
No, it's not okay.
Hey, dad.
Hey.
My phone's not working.
Oh. Huh.
Well, let me take a look.
Oh, yeah.
Just as I suspected.
I cancelled your service.
What?
I'm sorry, Kat.
Would a packet of soy sauce
make you feel better?
Look, it's just until
I find a job. Okay?
But what am I gonna do
in the meantime?
Sweetie, we have a landline.
A landline? Don't those
give you brain cancer?
You know what?
I'm just gonna have to find
myself a rich, older boyfriend.
You and me both.
Check it out.
We're in the paper.
Really?
Yeah.
"St. Louis unemployment
hits record high."
Mm. Ah, they couldn't have
done it without us.
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'm gonna figure something out,
all right.
You know the deal.
If I'm working, you're working.
Right back at ya, bro.
Mm-hmm.
What's up, guys?
Hey, Brian.
Hey, B.
Did you get your last check?
Yep. Hard to believe.
A year ago,
we were sittin' pretty.
St. Louis Pontiac's
top salesman, head mechanic,
and nearly accident-free
courtesy shuttle driver.
(Chuckles)
Now look at us.
How did this happen?
Well, it's a recession.
It's not a recession.
It's a mancession.
Look, women are taking over
the workforce.
Soon, they'll start
getting rid of men.
They'll just keep a few of us
around as sex slaves.
That part doesn't sound so bad.
Not the kind of sex you like,
Angel.
Just kissing
and cuddling and...
Listening.
Well, I'll tell you what. I'm
not going down without a fight.
I did hear they're hiring
down at, uh, Astro Taco.
No! That place is a dump.
I mean, we still have our pride.
(Laughs) For now.
When the women take over,
they'll make pride illegal.
That and eating on the toilet.
Ah, thanks, doc.
That prostate exam wasn't
as bad as I expected.
Beers really took the edge off.
I love your bracelet.
It was a little present
to myself.
I could wait around
for a guy to buy it for me,
but none of them have
any money.
Oh. So the drug business
is good, uh?
Bazonkers. I have got more work
than I can handle.
In fact, if you know anyone,
we are looking to hire.
Uh, really?
'Cause I'm a salesman
and I-I happen to be
between jobs.
Oh, we're kind of just
looking for girls.
Really? Why?
Well, we've had some guys,
but the doctors seem to want
to nail them less.
Okay, see ya next time.
(Chuckles)
Um, Mr. Standish?
Yeah?
How would you like
to pay for your physical?
What do you mean? I showed you
my insurance card on the way in.
But your coverage lapsed
last week.
What?!
The total is $900.
Oh, my God.
How the hell
am I gonna get $900?
Oh, I'm sorry, Connie.
(Telephone ringing)
Lee Standish?
Yes?
We're ready for you.
Oh, well, wish me luck.
Thanks for the tampon.
(Chuckles)
♪♪♪
(Man) ♪ hmm ♪
Hi. I'm Vanessa Warner.
I run the midwest drug sales
division here at Coreco.
Oh. Lee Standish.
Um...
(Chuckles)
So I got a chance
to look at your resume.
And I have to say,
I'm intrigued.
Mm.
You sold Pontiacs?
Oh, yes, yes.
Believe it or not,
that it my actual resume.
What was it like working there?
There couldn't have been
many women.
No, I was the only one.
Mm. That must've been hard.
Oh, it was!
The guys were always sassing me
or patting my Fanny
or...
Ogling my... my teats.
Well, you are a very...
Beautiful woman.
Oh.
And you played...
Football in college?
Oh!
Is that still on there?
Yes. I-I played
lingerie football.
(Chuckles) But anyway,
what I really wanna talk about
are some of
the amazing pharmaceuticals
that Coreco makes.
For instance, your new
arthritis drug Polluxor?
The results it's been getting
in nonpartisan clinical trials
are just stunning.
And the fact that it has
all the advantages
of low dose corticosteroids
without any of the side effects
of the Cox-2 selective nsaids?
(Chuckles)
I mean, get out of town!
You're impressive.
Mm.
Most of the girls
who interview here
think clinical trials
are the things Lindsay Lohan
keeps having to go to.
I'm not your ordinary girl.
No, you're not.
Honey.
Hi.
I got a job!
Are... are... are you serious?
Doing what?
Uh, working as a salesman
at drug company.
You know, talking
in my regular voice,
my genitals just hanging free.
Oh, honey! Yay!
(Laughs)
Oh! I don't wanna say
that I'd given up hope,
but, yeah, I kinda had.
Yeah, well, me, too.
Yeah.
My brave face
was getting so tired.
But we did it.
We did it.
We made it through.
Mwah!
(Laughs)
Come on, I'm taking you out.
Let's celebrate.
Okay. Let me just
go get changed.
No, what you have on is fine.
We're just going to the bar.
The bar?
Yeah, yeah.
I called Angel and Brian.
We're gonna m... ah, Angel and Brian.
You know what? I suddenly
do not feel like going out.
Okay. (Kisses)
I'll just wake you up
for sex later. Yeah?
Okay, wait. You seem mad.
What...
What is it?
Why don't you give it
some thought?
And just see
what you come up with. Okay?
Oh, sorry, ladies!
A man got a job.
(Chuckles)
Guess you'll have to wait
a little while longer
for your sex slaves.
(Laughs)
So... when can we come by
the office
so you can take us out
to lunch?
Mm. Mm.
Um...
Well, you know, I, um...
I don't get a lunch break.
Well, then how about getting us
some job interviews?
Uh... come on, Brian.
The man just got hired.
Now he's supposed to
put his ass on the line for you?
I'm sorry.
It's just getting a little
awkward living with my ex-wife.
The new husband?
Not a big fan.
(Clears throat)
Thanks for getting him
off my back.
No problem. But we still
have our deal, right?
If you're working, I'm working.
Well, um...
I'm not sure you'd be up
for everything...
This job requires.
But I'm Puerto Rican.
I'd be great at selling drugs.
Ah.
That's not what I mean.
Then what do you mean?
Just that, um...
I don't think
you'd totally fit in.
Oh, I get it. It's because
I'm a mechanic, right?
No. I'm not good enough to
work in your fancy office?
No, that's not what I meant, Angel.
I... no, no.
It's good.
I'm glad to know
what you really think of me.
Come on, man.
Enjoy your stupid celebration.
Ahem.
Uh, pardon me.
Mm-hmm?
Oh!
Hi, I'm... I'm Lee.
I just finished my orientation.
I wasn't sure where my desk is.
Welcome! I'm Kelly.
Oh, hi.
This is your desk right here.
And... wait.
Have we met before?
Oh, I don't think so.
I've never been
to that doctor's office.
You must be
the giant car saleswoman.
Vanessa told me about you.
Yes, hi. I'm... I'm...
Lee Standish. Yes, I know.
I'm Grace Hudson.
I've been
the regional sales leader
for the last couple of years.
But from what Vanessa tells me,
it looks like I might have
some competition.
Oh, I don't know about that.
Yeah, I don't know about that
either.
Cute bag.
Oh, thank you!
Come on, grace.
Don't be such a bitch.
What? I-I said I liked it.
We know what you meant.
We do?
Oh! You must be
the new girl!
I'm Kristin.
I used to be the new girl,
but not anymore!
Please tell me you're not
already in a book club.
(Mouths word)
So what's your story?
Are you married?
Wait, wait.
I'm really good at this.
Um, so no wedding ring,
but I do see a tan line
on your ring finger.
Mm.
So...
Divorced.
Did he leave you
for someone smaller?
Wow, you guys just
dive right in, don't you?
You're right.
We're so rude to pry.
Was it messy?
Any traumatized kids at home?
Well, I suppose
there's no harm in telling you
I-I do have
a 14-year-old daughter.
Oh, my God!
I'm a single mom, too.
Ethan is 8.
He's always the only one
at "bring your kid to work" day,
but now your daughter
will be there, too!
Oh, she can't.
She's, um...
She's in a bubble.
(Cell phone rings)
Oh, that's me.
(Ring)
Ooh, I should take this.
It's my, uh, my...
Waxer. (Chuckles)
(Ring)
(Normal voice) Hello?
Hey, Lee,
I don't like the way
we left things.
We need to have a conversation.
Sweetheart,
now's not a good time, okay?
Me and the guys at work...
Hey, sweetie, we're gonna get
some lunch. Wanna join us?
Who's that woman?
(Feminine voice)
I'll be right there.
And who's that woman?
(Normal voice) It's no one.
I've gotta go.
(Beep)
(Groans)
Oh, come on Lee.
Have a seat.
Okay. Let me get my...
I am just so...
Hungry.
Oh. Mm.
All right. So...
There we go.
Bon appetit. (Chuckles)
Mmm!
Uh, excuse me?
Welcome to Astro Taco.
Arriba, arriba.
Can I help you?
Uh, yes.
Um, uh, one...
One steak burrito, please.
One steak.
(Beeping)
(Cash register whirs)
$5.75.
Okay.
(Whirring)
Ole, ole. Have a nice day.
Oh, you, too.
(Normal voice)
Ah, screw it.
(Feminine voice)
Uh, pardon me?
I have a bone to pick with you.
You gave me change for a $10,
and I gave you a $300.
Lady, you're crazy.
Get out of here.
Okay. But just one more thing
I have to say.
(Normal voice) It's me.
Lee.
Lee?
Yeah.
This is what I had to do
to get a job.
Okay, my eyes are up here.
That's how I got the job,
and I wanna help you
get one, too.
How did you even do this?
You really wanna know?
(The Black Eyed Peas' "My Humps"
playing)
♪ What you gonna do
with all that junk? ♪
♪ all that junk
inside your trunk? ♪
♪ I'm-a get, get, get,
get you drunk ♪
♪ get you love drunk
off my hump ♪
♪ my hump, my hump ♪
♪ my hump, my hump, my hump ♪
♪ my lovely little lumps ♪
♪ check it out ♪
♪ my hump,
my hump, my hump, my hump ♪
♪ my hump, my hump, my hump ♪
♪ my lovely lady lumps ♪
In the back and in the front ♪
♪ my lovin' got you ♪
♪ she got me spendin' ♪
♪ spendin' all your money
on me ♪
♪ and spendin' time on me ♪
Excuse me.
(Gasps) Oh, my God!
Help me.
♪ Spendin' all your money
on me ♪
Please.
So... what do you say?
I don't know, man.
You have to understand,
this kind of thing
doesn't really fly
in my culture.
Oh! Oh, 'cause, you know,
my culture
just freakin' loves it.
Look, man, you're
my best friend, you know?
I cannot stand
seeing you like this.
I'd be proud
to work with you again,
the fancy office
and everything.
Hey, Angel,
bathroom needs cleaning.
I just cleaned it
ten minutes ago.
(Laughs)
Welcome to Astro Taco.
(Destiny's Child's
"Bootylicious" playing)
♪ I don't think you're ready
for this jelly ♪
For this jelly ♪
♪ I don't think you're ready
for this ♪
Hey, Shakira,
tone down the booty shake
a little, will ya?
This is what my body does, bro.
♪ I don't think you're ready
for this ♪
♪ and my body's
too bootylicious... ♪
(Feminine voice) Hi.
I'm here for my interview.
Hi. I'm Vanessa.
Likewise.
I mean, Angel Ortiz.
It's nice to meet you.
I love your scarf.
Oh, thank you.
And your ass looks tight
in those pants.
Hey!
How you doing?
Oh, pretty good.
Little itchy.
I hope grace isn't being
too rough on you.
She gave me a hard time
when I first started
working here, too,
and now
we're such good friends.
We even have nicknames
for each other.
Like, I call her "hottie"
or princess,"
and she calls me
"sausage fingers."
Anyway, I got you something.
Oh! Wow!
Thank you. (Gasps)
Thank you so much!
(Chuckles)
But can I ask you something?
What... what's so bad
about my pocketbook?
Besides the fact that
you call it a pocketbook?
Look, uh, don't take this
the wrong way,
but it seems like you haven't
been shopping in this century.
Oh.
Really?
Look, I-I know
what it's like
having to work and take care
of a kid all by yourself.
Not that it was any easier
when I was married.
My husband was no help.
He was always just hanging out
at the bar with his friends.
Was yours like that?
Well, maybe a little.
But, you know, he would
invite me along to the bar.
Oh, ooh! What a prince!
(Chuckles)
Anyway, the bag is
just a reminder
that you're a woman.
And you have needs.
You can't neglect yourself.
Well, maybe you're right.
Maybe I have been
neglecting... myself
well, stop it!
Oh!
Oh! Oh! Oh.
And inside the bag
is the next selection
for book club.
It's about a girl
who comes of age
during a spelling bee
in Rwanda.
Oh.
Spoiler alert... she dies.
Lee! Lee!
Oh. Um, pardon me
for just one moment.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you. (Chuckles)
(Normal voice) How'd it go?
(Normal voice) I blew it.
Why didn't you tell me
she was so hot?
My ace bandage was holding on
for dear life.
You... you want me to talk to her?
I'll talk...
No, no, no. She already left
for a meeting.
And I don't want you risking
your job for me.
I'm sure Astro Taco
will take me back.
Oh, man.
Jessica,
will you call Dr. Lerner
and tell him I'm gonna be late?
My car won't start.
(Keys clatter)
(Mouthing words)
(Feminine voice) I know
a little bit about cars.
♪♪♪
(Women) To Angel!
To Angel.
To me!
So you fixed Vanessa's car?
Mm-hmm, and once I got it
running, she was like,
"anyone who would
get under a car in a skirt
is worth taking a chance on."
How did you know how
to do that?
Oh, it was easy.
I just had to tune the solenoid
so the drive gear meshed
with the flywheel.
(Singsongy) Anywho...
What is Vanessa like as a boss?
Is she just all about the job
or does she have a husband?
No, no husband.
Really?
Yeah, and personally, I think
she might be a lesbian.
Nice.
(Sighs deeply)
(Cell phone rings)
Oh, that's me.
(Ring)
Oh, well, I really should
be getting home.
You know, single mom and all.
What?
Shh.
Hello? Have I gotten drunk
and slept with a random guy yet?
No one is going home
until we dance.
(Women giggle)
(Florida's "low" playing)
♪ Apple bottom jeans, jeans ♪
♪ boots with the fur,
with the fur ♪
♪ the whole club
was looking at her ♪
♪ she hit the floor,
she hit the floor ♪
♪ next thing you know ♪
♪ shawty got low, low, low,
low, low, low, low, low ♪
♪ them baggy sweatpants ♪
♪ and the reeboks with
the straps, with the straps ♪
♪ she turned around and gave
that big booty a smack ♪
♪ she hit the floor,
she hit the floor ♪
♪ next thing you know ♪
♪ shawty got low, low, low,
low, low, low, low, low ♪
Go, Lee! Go, Lee!
Go, Lee! Go, Lee! Go, Lee!
I'm going! I'm going!
(Beep)
I can't believe your father
is ignoring my calls.
He better not even think about
waking me up tonight
for sex... ophone lessons.
(Cell phone rings)
See, mom?
I'm sure that's dad now.
That's not my phone.
(Ring)
(Beep)
Hello?
(Imitates surfer) Hey, Kat,
it's me, a high school dude.
I was wondering
if you wanna, like,
interact on
a social networking site.
And who is this?
(Normal voice)
You are welcome.
Oh, my gosh. Thank you!
Mwah.
I don't care
how much mom hates you.
I think you're awesome.
(Chuckles)
Okay, before you say anything,
I got you something as well.
This is gorgeous.
How the hell
did you pick it out?
(Chuckles)
Look, I-I think that
I lost sight of the fact
that I'm not the only one
this past year's been tough on.
Okay?
And I am sorry
if I've been neglecting you.
Look at that.
You figured it out.
I did.
Tonight, I'm taking you out.
Mm?
Not to the bar.
(Chuckles) Yeah,
and Angel and Brian?
Will be
at least two tables away.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I almost forgot.
Look inside the bag.
There's more.
Ooh!
"A rainbow over Rwanda"?
Spoiler alert... she dies.
Just go strike up
a conversation with her.
Okay. I can do this.
Yeah.
(Indistinct conversations)
Hi. I'm Angel.
Sarah. I was hoping
you'd come over.
Really?
(Chuckles)
Well, in the case,
can I just cut to the chase?
Absolutely.
You have
no visible panty lines.
How do you make that happen?
I'm not wearing any underwear.
Yeah, that's not gonna work
for me.
... sync by Rafael upd ...
www.Addic7ed.Com/