- I know I seem mental, but I'm fine.
- OK.
- How's everything at the cafe?
- You really don't have to.
I got the Finland promotion.
- That's amazing!
- Thank you.
- I'm turning it down.
- What?
One of my pieces has gone missing.
You must have bent over backwards
to get something like that.
Who's the artist?
I stole that sculpture
from a certain somebody's studio.
Mum died three years ago.
She had a double mastectomy,
but never really recovered.
Don't let other people get in
the way of what you really want.
My husband isn't other people, OK?
My husband is my life!
Your husband tried to kiss me
on your birthday.
Did he?
Have you seen my sister?!
I mean, we're all being very
grown-up about this, but...
Let me know if you feel
any discomfort.
No, it's lovely, thank you.
Your father informed me
of your family history.
Yeah, evil boobs everywhere.
Arm up, please.
Stop it!
I'm sorry, I'm just ticklish.
Examined your sister this morning.
Did you? Does she...
Is she all right? Did she seem all right?
- Yes. Why?
Just... can't get hold of her.
She seemed very busy.
Sure.
Dad books us boob appointments
once a year,
to make sure our tits don't turn
on us like Mum's did.
It's a bit of a hassle
but, at the end of the day,
it's nice to be touched.
Bet you look forward
to seeing Claire.
A lot more to touch,
if you know what I mean.
I'm sorry. It's just...
there are worse jobs.
Look...
I check for cancerous lumps
in mammary glands.
Now, any pleasure I derive from that
is entirely dependent upon whether
or not I am about to save your life.
Of course, Doctor.
You can put your clothes back on.
Hey!
She's here.
- I've been waiting out here for nearly 10 minutes.
Yeah, you left me on
a fucking Silent Hill.
Yes, well, I had to.
Did you get back OK?
God, this is so stressful.
Mum's memorial lunch.
I should have worn my other coat.
Visiting Dad is hell for Claire.
I see it more as a sport.
It's so inappropriate
that she should be here.
- Have you spoken to Martin?
- No, it's fine. Everything's fine.
- Everything's totally fine.
- It sounds like it's fine.
Can you please just give me
some space?
You're standing so close to me!
- Ready?
- No.
Don't tell Dad about Finland.
And don't provoke her.
Let's just get out of this alive, OK?
Girls.
Got to hand it to her. Hi.
You shouldn't have.
They're actually for Dad.
Are they freesias?
Yeah, they were sort of
a favourite of...
Gosh, how special.
How lovely.
Aren't they stunning?
Aw, let's just leave them...
...there.
Lovely.
Come in.
Who's Dad sawing in half?
- Just the tree.
- Sorry?
The tree in the back garden.
Why are you taking the tree down?
Felicity tried to use it
to get out.
She's very expensive.
This is nice.
Thank you.
This is beautiful!
I hope you don't mind my being here,
but my Pilates fell through, so...
- Of course.
- No, it's lovely.
It's a sad day.
A sad, sad day.
I'll get the champagne.
This is my favourite bit.
I wonder who's going to...
That's a lovely cushion.
Thanks. It's an original.
Gosh.
I love your hat.
It's a hair scarf.
Looks like a hat.
Well, it's a hair scarf.
OK.
- Is Martin coming?
- No.
He's away.
I'm very excited to meet
your new chap.
Is he...
No, he's a different one.
You do turn over fast!
Dad will come in with some weird
canapes in a second.
Girls!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hello... yeah.
Sorry about all that noise.
You got a drink?
Sorry.
I forgot your glass.
You're both looking
very healthy, very...
very good and healthy and...
Did you talk to Dr Samuels
about your...?
Yes.
And they're happy, getting along...
...all right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah. Great.
Good. Excellent.
You are my...
...daughters.
- Yep.
- Yes.
Yeah, we are.
Sit down.
I think I should say a few words
about your mother.
Ignore me.
Ignore me, ignore me.
This day is not an easy one.
Cheers.
To Mum.
To Margaret.
Dearest Margaret.
Just the most generous woman.
- Yeah, well, she certainly was...
- Yeah, she was great.
It was...
It was the voice she used...
for the pigeons.
She always made
them sound so rude, you know?
But very, very funny.
She used to take the girls
around the park and point at the...
The squirrel voices were the best.
Run...!
- Run! Fucking run!
- Run-run-run-run-run!
Run-run-run-run!
Yes, yes, my ex had a similar thing -
voices and fun.
Really, really funny man.
Really funny.
Can I help you with the food?
Yes, yes, I should...
And take that off.
So, are you going to Finland?
You're going to have
to talk to me eventually.
Plaits.
Either she's got her period
or some serious shit's gone down.
She always does something slightly
different around her period.
She gets really bad PMT.
Mum used to call it
her monthly confidence crisis.
But it's PMT.
The only way she can get through it
is to reinvent herself
in some small way.
What?
I'm doing a wee on this cushion.
What?!
I sort of wish you were.
What are you doing?
Just put it back
where you got it from, OK?
- No!
- Just do it.
I don't want it in my house.
I'm doing you a massive favour.
She could really go to town
on you for this.
Come on, what's she going to do?
Draw me?
- Go.
- No.
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK...
Jesus!
Why are we sneaking?
- We're not allowed upstairs.
- Of course we are.
God...
I keep forgetting
that she's actually talented.
I know, it's infuriating.
Go on, then.
Where's her head?
She's got your boobs -
she doesn't need one.
OK...
OK. Hey...
Is everything OK?
With Martin?
You've invited someone today?
Yeah. Yeah, he's horrifically hot -
you're going to puke
when you see him.
Are you on your period?
- Why would you ask that?
- The plaits.
- No reason.
- Say it. - The plaits.
Hey...
Do you think she's ever
painted Dad naked?
I think you should take your nose
out of other people's marriages.
Sneaking a preview, are we?
Sorry, I spilled my champagne and...
I got distracted on my way
to the bathroom.
Me too.
It's really beautiful work.
Thank you.
Let me show you to the loo.
That's all right.
I grew up in this house.
It's all changed now, though.
Your father's in the kitchen.
Great.
I'll go and torment him.
He hates being alone
in a room with me.
Watch this.
Hi, Dad.
I just need some...
- Just need...
- What do you need? - I need some...
salt.
There it is.
Here it is, yeah.
So...
...how are you, darling?
Have you got enough...
clothes?
I can never have enough clothes.
And how is the cafe?
Well, the lease is up
in a couple of days, and...
I don't think I can
really afford to...
I think I'm just going to
have to... accept that it's...
I'm sorry about that, darling.
But, of course, we're just a little bit
tight on the purse strings, too.
No,
I wasn't asking you for any...
We've just been keeping it quiet.
We haven't been able to...
to buy anything or do anything,
and...
What's that?
That? That's just a...
tiny little house we're...
we're buying in...
...in France.
Lovely.
Yeah. I...
I just wanted to talk to you...
...about this exhibition.
What exhibition?
- No!
- Jesus, Dad! Again?
No, it doesn't...
Pick it up, pick it up!
Help me pick these up.
Please, please!
She mustn't see it.
- She mustn't find out.
- OK, OK...
Five second rule.
No, I have never bought
into that rule.
It's disgusting.
What are you doing?
Just a little family tradition.
What odd fun.
What are the rules?
Thank God.
That'll be your man.
I mean, I didn't want
to show off, but...
Gosh...
You really are...
So, how did you two meet?
Fucked me up the arse.
I used to manage a bar, and I...
just found her crying,
in the toilet one night.
How about you two?
How did you two meet?
Through our mother, actually.
How's work, Claire?
Fine.
Nothing new.
She used to be our godmother.
Still am.
But then their parents split up...
Mum died.
And we just became
even closer friends.
Actually, you know - and I can say
this because I'm an artist -
but you really are very
good-looking.
Thank you.
Very.
I mean, almost...
...too good-looking.
Well, if you'll excuse me, I'm going
to go and do that old human thing.
How's the exhibition going?
Yes, yes...
I wanted to talk to you about that.
Talking about me?
- Very favourably.
- All good things, I swear.
And again...
- Have you found a venue?
- What exhibition?
Thank you so much for asking.
We have, actually...
There are some elements of the work
that I, you know,
I wanted to talk to you about.
It's a "sexhibition."
But, don't panic, it's nothing scary.
It's simply a journey through
my physical and sexual life,
climaxing in a few pieces
inspired by and moulded on
your father.
And there are photos.
I've taken a photo of my naked body
every year for the past 30 years.
Why?
Well, I think it's important for
women of all ages to see how
my body has changed over the years.
I think they have to have
a healthy perspective
on my body.
- Don't they?
- Absolutely.
I mean, I don't need to tell you,
but your father is
a deeply sexual man.
No, you don't.
Just did.
- Knew it.
- I'm just very lucky.
I will be touched
until the day I die.
And so will you, Claire.
I mean, it's really
all that humans want -
is to be loved...
...and to be touched.
Tell Dad about your promotion,
Claire.
There's nothing to tell.
What promotion?
Finland.
- Odd place.
- Any news?
No.
She got it.
Fuck's sake!
Congratulations, Claire.
- Thank you.
- Clever girl!
Can we not?
This is so exciting...
She's turning it down.
- Why?
Why, why not? Why, Claire?
Claire, are you pregnant?
Why aren't you getting on a plane
to your gold rich future?
- This is everything you've worked for...
- Why...?
Because you CAN'T just fuck off
on aeroplanes, and leave your weird
stepson and broken sister
to fend for themselves, OK?
Excuse me.
She's your sister,
it's your job to annoy her...
No, no, I'm just
so annoyed with myself!
I wish I could just...
meet myself and just...
have a go at myself!
Do your worst.
Come on, bitch!
You don't take yourself seriously.
Pussy.
You need to reach out to your family.
You need to stop provoking
your sister - just grow up.
You do not take yourself seriously
as a businesswoman,
you need to pay your fucking bills,
you need to be
nicer to Hillary
and you need to get a new hat!
Is that better?
Yeah, it's better.
OK...
Off you go.
The art work in this house is...
stunning.
Who is it?
If I tell you, will you promise
to come to my sexhibition?
It's not your work...
Will you come?
It would be an honour.
How's your little restaurant?
It's a cafe.
Don't do it a disservice.
I'm not. It's a cafe.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Your father tells me you're struggling.
- Well...
I think we all are.
Well, yes.
But, I mean,
now there's only one of you...
God, I can't imagine
what you've been through.
I'm sorry, have I missed something?
Well... her dear little friend died,
and left her to run the cafe
on her own.
Jesus.
God, that is truly awful.
How did she die?
- She killed herself.
- It was an accident.
Well...
Maybe it's time to let
the little restaurant go.
Give it up.
Sell it - have a little holiday.
We did this.
And, whatever happens,
we never let it go, OK?
Excuse me.
Have you seen Felicity?
No, sorry.
Gosh, all sorts of things go missing
in this house, don't they?
- Big house.
- Yes, lovely house.
The sculpture turned up.
- Did it?
- Yes.
Must have just toppled off the side.
Well, if you rid a woman
of her head and limbs,
you can't expect her
to do anything other than...
roll around.
What?
Your father and I often say,
when you've had a few drinks,
you're so like your mother.
Look at these.
So, the party's moved to the hallway.
Always a good sign.
Does anyone mind if I leave?
I've got a dicky tummy.
So swift...
Thanks.
I'm not going to kiss you
because I'm probably very ill.
You too. Come on.
Goodbye then, my...
...my daughters.
Goodbye.
What a lovely occasion.
Yeah. See you at the sexhibition.
No, there's absolutely no need to...
- Yes, lovely.
- No, no - I'll definitely be there.
I will definitely be there.
Hold up!
You trying to keep me overnight?
Very good-looking.
I might never see you again,
but you're very good-looking.
Yes, yes... very good-looking.
Thanks, I owe you.
No, I owe you.
It's been really nice to spend
the day with a normal family.
I actually feel quite emotional.
Will you stay with me tonight?
Sure.
I'm going to go warm up the bike.
- Lovely to meet you, Claire.
- You too.
What's his...?
Fucked me up the arse.
Yep. It's...
I totally see that now.
I'm sorry I was...
Listen to me.
I'm going to leave Martin.
I'm going to give you
the money for the cafe,
and I'm going to go
to fucking Finland.
OK.
And...
That is the coolest thing
you've ever done.
I know.
Thanks, Claire.
Shall we...?
We can try.
- I'll see you at the sexhibition.
- Yeah.