(GREEF KARGA LAUGHS)
GREEF KARGA: They all hate you, Mando.
Because you're a legend!
THE MANDALORIAN: How many had fobs?
GREEF KARGA: All of them.
Any idea what they gonna do with it?
GREEF KARGA: I didn't ask. It's against the Guild Code.
THE MANDALORIAN: Sorgan.
No star port, no industrial centers,
no population density.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm leaving him here.
Traveling with me,
that's no life for a kid.
(GUNSHOT)
CARA: They know he's here.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yes.
Then they'll keep coming.
(LASERS FIRING)
(FIRING CONTINUES)
MAN: Hand over the child, Mando.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
I might let you live.
(THE CHILD WHIMPERS)
(ALARM BLARING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Hold on.
Come on.
MAN: I can bring you in warm or I can bring you in cold.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's my line.
(SCREAMING)
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(ALARM BEEPING)
(SWITCHES CLICKING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Losing fuel.
(ENGINE POWERS DOWN)
(THE CHILD GIGGLES)
(ENGINE SPUTTERS)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(ENGINE POWERS UP)
(CONSOLE BEEPS)
(BUTTONS BEEPING)
(RADIO STATIC)
OPERATOR: (ON RADIO) This is Mos Eisley Tower.
We are tracking you.
Head for bay three-five, over.
THE MANDALORIAN: Copy that.
Locked in for three-five.
(DOOR BEEPING)
(CHATTERING)
(PIT DROIDS SCREAM)
PELI MOTTO: Hey!
Hey!
You damage one of my
droids, you'll pay for it.
THE MANDALORIAN: Just keep them away from my ship.
Yeah? You think that's
a good idea, do ya?
Let's look at your ship.
(BANGS ON SHIP)
Oof! Look at that.
Ugh, you got a lot of carbon
scorin' building up top.
Yeah.
If I didn't know better, I'd
think you were in a shootout.
Special tool for that one.
(SIGHS) I am gonna have to rotate that.
You got a fuel leak.
Look at that, this is a mess.
How did you even land?
That's gonna set you back.
THE MANDALORIAN: I've got 500 Imperial Credits.
That's all you got? Well,
what do you guys think?
(CHATTERING)
That should at least cover the hangar.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'll get you your money.
Hmm. I've heard that before.
THE MANDALORIAN: Just remember...
Yeah, no droids. I heard ya.
You don't have to say it twice.
Jeez.
Womp rat.
- I'm in.
- (PIT DROID CHATTERS)
And I am gonna raise you
three bolts and a motivator.
- (THE CHILD SHRIEKS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
(PIT DROID IMITATES SHRIEK)
(SHRIEKING CONTINUES)
Shh. Quick, grab my blaster rifle.
I'd stay in that ship if I were you.
What?
(THE CHILD COOS)
Now, now.
Let Peli take a good look at you.
All right, there you go.
(SIGHS)
Did that bounty hunter leave you
all alone in that big nasty ship?
- (PIT DROID CHATTERS)
- (CHUCKLES)
How do I know what it
is? Give me a second.
All right. Now, would
you like some food?
Are you hungry?
- Okay. Fetch us something to eat. Quick!
- (PIT DROID CHATTERS)
I don't know... Something
with bones in it.
Okay. (SHUSHES)
(COOING)
PELI MOTTO: Now, here's the plan.
I am going to look after you
until The Mandalorian gets back,
and then I'm gonna charge
him extra for watching you.
You see how that works?
Yeah, bright eyes?
We're a team. Mmm-hmm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(CHITTERING)
(WHIRRING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Hey, droid, I'm a hunter.
I'm lookin' for some work.
Unfortunately, the Bounty Guild
no longer operates from Tatooine.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm not
looking for Guild work.
I am afraid that does not
improve your situation,
at least by my calculation.
Think again, tin can.
If you're looking for work,
have a seat, my friend.
Name's Toro, Toro Calican.
Come on, relax.
Picked up this Bounty Puck
before I left the Mid Rim.
Fennec Shand, an Assassin.
Heard she's been on the run
ever since the New Republic put
all her employers in lockdown.
THE MANDALORIAN: I know the name.
I followed this tracking fob here.
Now the positional data suggests
she's headed out beyond the Dune Sea.
Should be an easy job.
THE MANDALORIAN: Well, good luck with that.
Wait, wait, wait, hey. I
thought you needed work?
THE MANDALORIAN: How long with the Guild?
Long enough.
THE MANDALORIAN: Clearly not.
Fennec Shand is an elite mercenary.
She made her name killing for
all the top crime syndicates,
including the Hutts.
If you go after her, you
won't make it past sunrise.
This is my first job.
You can keep the money, all of it.
I just need this job
to get into the Guild.
(SCOFFS) I can't do it alone.
THE MANDALORIAN: Meet me at Hangar three-five in half an hour.
Bring two speeder bikes and
give me the tracking fob.
Don't worry, got it all memorized.
THE MANDALORIAN: Half an hour.
Looks like you're stuck
with me now, partner.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Hey!
- (GASPS) I'm awake! I'm awake!
Oh. (SHUSHES)
- THE MANDALORIAN: Where is he?
- PELI MOTTO: Quiet!
Oh. (SHUSHES) It's okay. You woke it up.
Do you have any idea how long
it took me to get it to sleep?
THE MANDALORIAN: Give him to me.
PELI MOTTO: Not so fast!
You can't just leave a
child all alone like that.
You know, you have an awful lot
to learn about raisin' a young one.
(COOS)
Anyway, I started the
repair on the fuel leak.
There you go. I had a couple
setbacks I want to talk to you about.
You know, I didn't use
any droids, as requested,
so it took me a lot
longer than I expected.
But I figured you were good for the money
since you have an extra mouth to feed.
THE MANDALORIAN: Thank you.
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh, I guess I was right.
You got a job, didn't you?
You know, it's costing me a lot of money
to keep these droids even powered up.
Hey, Mando, what do you
think? Not too shabby, huh?
(CLICKS)
What'd you expect? This
ain't Corellia. Ma'am.
(THE CHILD CHUCKLES)
(ENGINES START)
(THE CHILD BABBLES)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(SPEEDER BIKES POWER DOWN)
- What's going on?
- THE MANDALORIAN: Look. Up ahead.
(BANTHAS GROANING)
TORO CALICAN: Tusken Raiders.
I heard the locals
talking about this filth.
THE MANDALORIAN: Tuskens think they're the locals.
- (TORO CALICAN SCOFFS)
- Everyone else is just trespassing.
Whatever they call themselves,
they best keep their distance.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah? Why don't you tell them yourself?
(TUSKENS YELLING)
Relax.
- What are you doing?
- THE MANDALORIAN: Negotiating.
What's going on?
THE MANDALORIAN: We need passage across their land.
- Let me see the binocs.
- Why?
(STAMMERS) Hey! What?
- Those were brand new.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah? They were.
(ENGINE REVVING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Get down.
What? Oh.
(DEWBACK GRUNTING)
THE MANDALORIAN: All right, tell me what you see.
TORO CALICAN: Dewback.
Looks like the rider is still attached.
Is that her? Is that the target?
THE MANDALORIAN: I don't know.
I'll go. You cover me.
Stay down.
(DEWBACK BELLOWS)
Whoa, whoa.
TORO CALICAN: Well, is it her? Is she dead?
THE MANDALORIAN: It's another bounty hunter.
Hey, I hope you don't plan on
keeping all that stuff for yourself.
- Can I at least have that blaster?
- (TRACKING FOB BEEPING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Get down!
- (GRUNTS)
- (TORO CALICAN EXCLAIMS)
Mando!
(GRUNTS)
What happened?
(PANTING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Sniper bolt.
Only an MK-modified rifle
could make that shot.
Are you all right?
THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah. Hit me in the beskar,
and at that range beskar held up.
Wait, I don't wear any beskar.
THE MANDALORIAN: Nope.
Well, so what do we do?
THE MANDALORIAN: You see where that shot came from?
Yeah, it came from that ridge.
THE MANDALORIAN: Okay, we're gonna wait until dark.
Well, what if she escapes?
THE MANDALORIAN: She's got the high ground.
She'll wait for us to
make the first move.
I'm gonna rest. You take
the first watch. Stay low!
All right, suns are
down. Time to ride, Mando.
Come on, wake up.
Look at you, asleep on the job, old man.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
THE MANDALORIAN: You done?
Yeah. I was just, you know,
waking you up. Come on.
THE MANDALORIAN: Get on your bike.
Ride as fast as you
can towards those rocks.
That's your plan? (SCOFFS) She'll
snipe us right off the bikes.
THE MANDALORIAN: It's a flash charge.
We alternate shots,
it'll blind any scope temporarily.
Combine that with our
speed and we got a chance.
A chance?
THE MANDALORIAN: Hey, you wanted this. Get ready.
(ENGINES REVVING)
(GRUNTS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Now!
(STRAINS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
TORO CALICAN: Not so fast, Fennec.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(LASERS FIRING IN DISTANCE)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(BONE CRACKS)
(SCREAMING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Nice distraction.
(TORO CALICAN GROANS)
TORO CALICAN: Ow.
Yeah, good work, partner.
THE MANDALORIAN: Cuff yourself.
Why don't you go find your blaster?
A Mandalorian.
It's been a long time since
I've seen one of your kind.
Ever been to Nevarro?
I hear things didn't go so well there,
but it looks like you got off easy.
You don't have to worry
about gettin' to Nevarro,
or anywhere else, once we turn you in.
You know, I really should thank you.
You're my ticket into the Guild.
You're welcome.
FENNEC SHAND: Uh-oh. Looks like one of us has to walk.
THE MANDALORIAN: Or we could drag you.
All right, so what is the plan?
THE MANDALORIAN: I need you to go find that dewback we saw.
And leave you here with
my bounty and my ride?
Yeah, I don't think so, Mando.
(LENS WHIRRING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Okay, I'll do it.
Watch her, and don't let
her get near the bike.
She's no good to us dead.
(TORO CALICAN SIGHS)
(FENNEC SHAND SIGHS)
Oh, it's been a while.
Oh, look, the suns are coming up.
Quiet.
Look, there's still time to
make my rendezvous in Mos Espa.
Take me to it and I can pay
you double the price on my head.
I don't care about the money.
FENNEC SHAND: Oh, so the Mandalorian keeps all the money for himself.
- TORO CALICAN: Only because I let him.
- (SCOFFS)
FENNEC SHAND: Doesn't seem that way.
I mean, it seems like
he's calling all the shots.
Shows what you know.
I hired Mando, this is my job.
Bringin' you in will make me a full
member of the Bounty Hunters Guild.
You already have something the
Guild values far more than me.
You just don't see it.
- What?
- The Mandalorian.
His armor alone's worth
more than my bounty.
I already told you, I
don't care about the money.
Then think what it would
do for your reputation.
A Mandalorian shot up
the Guild on Nevarro,
took some high value
target and went rogue.
That Mandalorian?
Like I said, you don't see many.
You bring the Guild that traitor,
and they'll welcome you with open arms.
Your name will be legendary.
(SIGHS)
How can we be sure he's the one?
Word is, he still has
the target with him.
Some say it's a child.
Look, if you're afraid to take him on,
fear not. I can help you with that.
Take some advice, kid.
You wanna be a bounty hunter?
Make the best deal for
yourself and survive.
(EXHALES)
(GRUNTS)
TORO CALICAN: That's good advice,
but if I took those binders
off of you I'd be a dead man.
And if the Mandalorian's worth
more than you are, well...
Who wouldn't want to be a legend?
Thanks for the tip.
(DEWBACK SNORTING)
(SIGHS)
(OBJECT CLATTERING)
(PIT DROIDS CHATTERING)
TORO CALICAN: Took you long enough, Mando.
Looks like I'm calling the
shots now. Huh, partner?
Drop your blaster and raise 'em.
- Cuff him.
- Ugh.
You're a Guild traitor, Mando.
And I'm willing to bet that
this here is the target
you helped escape.
(WHISPERING) You're
smarter than you look.
TORO CALICAN: Fennec was right.
Bringing you in won't just
make me a member of the Guild,
it'll make me legendary.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
- THE MANDALORIAN: Stay back.
- PELI MOTTO: Gotta get it.
Where is it?
(THE CHILD BABBLES)
There you are. (EXCLAIMS)
Are you hiding from us? Huh?
- Look at you.
- (THE CHILD COOS)
That's all right. I know.
That was really loud for
your big old ears, wasn't it?
- It's okay. Shh.
- (THE CHILD BABBLES)
(BABBLES)
PELI MOTTO: Be careful with him.
So, I take it you didn't get paid?
(SIGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN: That cover me?
Yeah. Yes, this is gonna cover you.
All right, Pit Droids!
Let's drag this outta here!
(PIT DROIDS CHATTERING)
I don't know, drag
it to Beggar's Canyon.
(PIT DROIDS CHATTERING)
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44