There is one job.
Underworld?
Face to face.
- (DROID SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
- (BEEPS)
Bounty hunting is a
complicated profession.
Proof of termination
is also acceptable for a lower fee.
THE MANDALORIAN: My ship has
been destroyed. I'm trapped here.
(WIND WHISTLING)
- (COOING)
- (THE MANDALORIAN SIGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN: These are my
parts. They stole them from me.
UGNAUGHT: You can trade.
THE MANDALORIAN: (IN ENGLISH)
The egg? What egg?
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(MUDHORN ROARING)
(CONSOLE BEEPING)
- (CLICKS SWITCH)
- (WHIRRING)
(COOING)
(DEVICE BEEPS)
- (CLICKS SWITCH)
- (TRILLING)
Mando. I've received your
transmission. Wonderful news.
Upon your return, deliver the
quarry directly to the client.
(CHUCKLES) I have no idea if he wants
to eat it or hang it on his wall,
but he's very antsy.
Safe passage! You know where to find me.
THE MANDALORIAN: It's not a toy.
(COOING)
(CONTINUES COOING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(COOS)
(CONTINUES COOING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKING JAWA)
(COOING)
(DROID SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(BEEPS)
(DOOR UNLOCKING)
(COOING)
(WHINES)
THE MANDALORIAN: Easy with that.
STORMTROOPER 1: You take it easy.
Yes!
(THE CHILD COOING)
Yes, yes, yes!
Yes.
(THE CHILD WHIMPERING)
- Very healthy. Yes.
- (DEVICE BEEPS)
Your reputation was not unwarranted.
THE MANDALORIAN: How many
fobs did you give out?
This asset was of
extreme importance to me.
I had to ensure its delivery.
But to the winner...
Go the spoils.
(BEEPS, HISSES)
Such a large bounty for
such a small package.
(THE CHILD WHINING)
(CRYING)
THE MANDALORIAN: What are your plans for it?
How uncharacteristic of
one of your reputation.
You have taken both
commission and payment.
(DOOR OPENS)
Is it not the Code of the Guild
that these events are now forgotten?
That Beskar is enough
to make a handsome
replacement for your armor.
Unfortunately, finding a
Mandalorian in these trying times
is more difficult
than finding the steel.
(HISSES)
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BEEPS)
(HISSES)
ARMORER: This amount
can be shaped many ways.
THE MANDALORIAN: My armor has lost it's integrity.
I may need to begin again.
ARMORER: Indeed. I can
form a full cuirass.
This would be in order for your station.
THE MANDALORIAN: That would be a great honor.
ARMORER: I must warn you.
It will draw many eyes.
(HEAVY INFANTRY GRUNTS)
(SCOFFS) These were cast
in an Imperial smelter.
These are the spoils of the Great Purge.
The reason that we live
hidden like sand rats.
ARMORER: Our secrecy is our survival.
Our survival is our strength.
HEAVY INFANTRY: Our strength
was once in our numbers.
Now we live in the shadows and only
come above ground one at a time.
Our world was shattered by the Empire,
with whom this coward shares tables.
(HEAVY INFANTRY GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(HEAVY INFANTRY GROANS)
(BOTH CONTINUE GRUNTING)
ARMORER: The Empire is no longer.
And the Beskar has returned.
When one chooses to walk
the Way of the Mandalore,
you are both hunter and prey.
How can one be a coward if
one chooses this way of life?
Have you ever removed your helmet?
THE MANDALORIAN: No.
ARMORER: Has it ever
been removed by others?
THE MANDALORIAN: Never.
ARMORER: This is the Way.
MANDALORIAN GROUP: This is the Way.
HEAVY INFANTRY: This is the Way.
ARMORER: What caused this damage?
THE MANDALORIAN: A Mudhorn.
ARMORER: Then you have earned
the Mudhorn as your signet.
I shall craft it.
THE MANDALORIAN: I can't
accept. It wasn't a noble kill.
I was helped by an enemy.
ARMORER: Why would an
enemy help you in battle?
THE MANDALORIAN: It did
not know it was my enemy.
ARMORER: Since you forgo a signet,
I shall use the excess
to forge whistling birds.
THE MANDALORIAN: Whistling
birds will do well.
Reserve some for the foundlings.
ARMORER: As it should always be.
The foundlings are the future.
This is the Way.
MANDALORIAN GROUP: This is the Way.
THE MANDALORIAN: This is the Way.
(SIZZLING)
ARMORER: Whistling birds are a powerful
defense against multiple enemies.
Use them sparingly, for they are rare.
(WHIRS, POWERS ON)
(BEEPS)
- (WHIRS, THUDS)
- (GURGLING)
(EXPLOSIONS)
(CLANKS)
(CLANKING CONTINUES)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SIZZLING)
(CLANKING CONTINUES)
(LOUD THUD)
(PEOPLE CONTINUE SCREAMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
GREEF KARGA: Look, I told you.
I'm not interested in your excuses!
(SPEAKING HUTTESE)
(IN ENGLISH) You had your shot,
dust breather, but you failed.
No pucks for you. Now get outta here.
(BOUNTY HUNTER GRUMBLES)
GREEF KARGA: Ah! Mando! (LAUGHS)
They all hate you, Mando.
Because you're a legend!
THE MANDALORIAN: How many of them had tracking fobs?
(SCOFFS) All of them. All of them!
But not one of them closed the deal.
Only you, Mando. Only you.
(SCOFFS)
GREEF KARGA: And with it,
the richest reward this
parsec has ever seen.
Please sit, my friend.
(CHUCKLES)
They're all weighing the Beskar
in their minds, but not me.
No. I, for one, I
celebrate your success.
Because it is my success as well.
Hell! Even I am rich. (CHUCKLES)
Now, how can I show my gratitude
to my most valuable partner?
THE MANDALORIAN: I want my next job.
Next job?
Take some time off. Enjoy yourself.
I'll take you to the
Twi'lek healing baths.
THE MANDALORIAN: I want my next job.
Sure. Fine.
You hunters like to keep busy, right?
Well, these are all far away.
The further, the better.
Well, take your pick. You've earned it.
Ah. That's the best one of the lot.
A nobleman's son skipped bail.
(CHUCKLES) Looks like you're
headed to the ocean dunes of Karnac.
THE MANDALORIAN: Any idea what they're gonna do with it?
With what?
THE MANDALORIAN: The kid.
I didn't ask. It's
against the Guild Code.
THE MANDALORIAN: They work for the Empire.
What are they doing here?
The Empire is gone, Mando.
All that are left are
mercenaries and warlords.
But if it bothers you,
just go back to the Core and
report them to the New Republic.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's a joke.
Mando, enjoy your rewards.
Buy a camtono of spice.
By the time you come out of hyperdrive,
you will have forgotten all about it.
(ENGINE POWERING ON)
(ENGINE POWERING DOWN)
(DEVICE WHINING, STATIC)
THE CLIENT: (OVER COMMS) I don't care.
I order you to extract the necessary
material and be done with it.
- (STATIC)
- (INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
DR. PERSHING: He has explicitly
ordered us to bring it back alive.
THE CLIENT: Finish your business quickly,
as I no longer can guarantee your safety.
STORMTROOPER 1: Check the perimeter.
(RAPID BEEPING)
(EXPLOSION)
(ALARM BLARING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(STORMTROOPERS GROAN)
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(STORMTROOPER GROANS)
(STORMTROOPER GRUNTS, GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(STORMTROOPER GROANS)
No, no, no, no, please.
Please. No. No, no.
(DR. PERSHING GASPS)
DR. PERSHING: No, please.
Please don't hurt
him. It's just a child.
Please. No. No! Please. No. No, no.
THE MANDALORIAN: What did you do to it? What did you do it?
I protected him. I protected him.
If it wasn't for me, he
would already be dead!
Please! Please. Please.
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
STORMTROOPER 1: Look, there!
STORMTROOPER 2: Split up. We'll flush him out.
STORMTROOPER 1: Copy.
Give it up. There's nowhere to... (GROANS)
(STORMTROOPER GROANS)
STORMTROOPER: Hey! (GROANS)
(STORMTROOPER SCREAMING)
(THE CHILD COOS)
STORMTROOPER 1: Freeze!
STORMTROOPER 2: Don't move.
STORMTROOPER 1: Hands up.
STORMTROOPER 3: Drop the blaster.
THE MANDALORIAN: Wait. What I'm holding is very valuable.
Here.
(THE CHILD WHIMPERS)
STORMTROOPER 1: Now turn and face me.
STORMTROOPER 2: Stand up!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(THE CHILD COOS)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (TRACKING FOBS BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Welcome back, Mando!
Now put the package down.
THE MANDALORIAN: Step aside. I'm going to my ship.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You put the bounty down and
perhaps I'll let you pass.
THE MANDALORIAN: The kid's coming with me.
If you truly care about the kid,
then you'll put it on the speeder
and we'll discuss terms.
THE MANDALORIAN: How do I know I can trust you?
(SCOFFS) Because I'm your only hope.
(COOS)
(GROANS)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
- THE MANDALORIAN: Drive.
- (DROID BEEPING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Drive!
(BOUNTY HUNTER GROANS)
(DROID POWERS DOWN)
(GROANS)
(ALL CLAMORING)
That's one impressive weapon!
THE MANDALORIAN: Here's what I'll do.
I'm gonna walk to my ship with the kid
and you're gonna let it happen.
No. How about this?
We take the kid,
and if you try to stop us,
we kill you and we strip
your body for parts.
(GROANS)
GREEF KARGA: Don't hit the target!
(BOUNTY HUNTERS GROANING)
(COOS)
(FIRING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING)
HEAVY INFANTRY: Get out of here! We'll hold them off!
THE MANDALORIAN: You're going to have to relocate the covert.
HEAVY INFANTRY: This is the Way.
THE MANDALORIAN: This is the Way.
(FIRING CONTINUES)
GREEF KARGA: Hold it, Mando.
I didn't want it to come to this.
But then you broke the Code.
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(GROANING, INHALES SHARPLY)
THE MANDALORIAN: I gotta get one of those.
(THE CHILD COOS)
(GIGGLES)
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44