THE MANDALORIAN: The kid's coming with me.
(GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTS)
(LASERS FIRING)
Who's he tracking?
THE MANDALORIAN: The kid.
CARA: Then they’ll keep coming.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yes.
(ENGINE HISSING)
RAN: Mando.
Is that you under that bucket?
THE MANDALORIAN: Ran.
RAN: I didn't really know if I'd
ever see you in these parts again.
Good to see you.
You know, to be honest,
I was a little surprised
when you reached out to me.
You know, 'cause I... I hear things.
Like, maybe things between you
and the Guild aren't workin' out.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'll be fine.
Okay. Well, you know the policy.
No questions.
And you, you're welcome
back here anytime.
THE MANDALORIAN: So, what's the job?
Yeah, one of our associates ran afoul of
some competitors and got himself caught.
So, I'm puttin' together
a crew to spring him.
It's a five person job. I got four.
All I need is the ride,
and you brought it.
THE MANDALORIAN: The ship wasn't part of the deal.
Well, the Crest is the only
reason I let you back in here.
What's the look?
Is that gratitude?
(LAUGHS)
Uh-huh. I think it is.
(RAN CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Hey, Mayfeld.
MAYFELD: Yeah?
RAN: This is Mando, the
guy I was tellin' you about.
We used to do jobs way back when.
This is the guy?
Yeah, we were all young, tryin'
to make a name for ourselves.
(LAUGHS) Yeah, but runnin'
with a Mandalorian, that was...
That brought us some reputation.
Oh, yeah? What did he get out of it?
(LAUGHS) I asked him that one time.
You remember what you said, Mando?
Target practice. (LAUGHING)
Target practice.
We did some crazy stuff, didn't we?
THE MANDALORIAN: That was a long time ago.
Well...
Well, I don't go out
anymore. You understand?
So, uh, Mayfeld, he's
gonna run point on this job.
If he says it, it's
like it's comin' from me.
You good with that?
THE MANDALORIAN: You tell me.
(RAN LAUGHS)
You haven't changed one bit.
Yeah, well, things have
changed around here.
RAN: Yeah, well, Mayfeld, he's...
He's one of the best
triggermen I've ever seen.
Former Imperial sharpshooter.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's not saying much.
I wasn't a stormtrooper, wiseass.
Don't take long, does it? (LAUGHING)
MAYFELD: Razor Crest? I can't
believe that thing can fly.
Looks like a Canto Bight slot machine.
All right. The good-lookin' fellow
there with the horns, that's Burg.
This may surprise you,
but he's our muscle.
(GRUNTS)
So, this is a Mandalorian.
- I thought they'd be bigger.
- (CHUCKLES)
Droid's name is Zero.
THE MANDALORIAN: I thought
you said you had four.
XI'AN: He does.
Hello, Mando.
THE MANDALORIAN: Xi'an.
Tell me why I shouldn't cut
you down where you stand?
THE MANDALORIAN: Nice to see you, too.
(ALL LAUGH)
(SIGHS) I missed you.
This is shiny.
(CLICKS TONGUE) You wear it well.
Do we need to leave
the room or something?
Well, Xi'an's been a little
heartbroken since Mando left our group.
Aw. You gonna be okay, sweetheart?
Oh, I'm all business now.
Learned from the best.
All right, lovebirds.
Break it up till you get on the ship.
Right now we don't have much time.
(BURG GRUNTS)
Tiny. (LAUGHING)
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
ZERO: Fuel.
Navigation. Hyperdrive.
Landing gear.
Comms.
GREEF KARGA: Mando...
I received... (DISTORTED)
I received wonderful news.
Upon your... Upon your... Deliver
the quarry. Deliver the...
ZERO: Hmm.
So, the package is being moved
on a fortified transport ship.
Now, we got a limited window
to board, find our friend,
get him out of there
before they make their jump.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's a New Republic prison ship.
Your man wasn't taken by a
rival syndicate. He was arrested.
- So what?
- (GRUNTS)
A job is a job.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's a max security transport
and I'm not looking for that kinda heat.
Well, neither are we.
So just don't mess up.
The good news for you is
the ship is manned by droids.
Still hate the machines, Mando?
ZERO: Despite recent modifications,
the ship is still quite a mess.
The power lines are leaking,
the navigation is intermittent,
and the hyperdrive is only
operating at 67.3% efficiency.
We have much better ships.
Why are we using this one?
'Cause the Razor Crest is off the old
Imperial and the New Republic grid.
It's a ghost.
Yeah, and we need a ship that can get
close enough to jam New Republic code.
So, when we drop out of hyperspace here,
if we immediately bank
into this kinda attitude,
we should be right in their blind spot,
which will give us just enough time
for your ship to scramble our signal.
THE MANDALORIAN: It's not possible. Even for the Crest.
That's why he's flyin'.
(MAYFELD LAUGHING)
Mando, I know you're
a pretty good pilot,
but we need you on the
trigger. Not on the wheel.
ZERO: Don't worry, Mandalorian.
My response time is quicker than
organics. And I'm smarter, too.
All right. I... Yeah. That's good.
Forgive the programming. He's
a little rough around the edges.
But he is the best.
THE MANDALORIAN: How can you trust it?
(CLICKS TONGUE) You know me,
Mando. I don't trust anybody.
Just like the good old days, Mando. Huh?
(SHIP ENGINE HISSING)
(XI'AN SIGHS)
Will you sit down?
- (GRUNTS)
- (SNARLS)
(LAUGHING)
ZERO: Calculations complete.
Jumping to hyperspace now.
Feel free to join the others.
I will handle it from here.
(KEYS BEEPING)
(BURG LAUGHING)
(BURG GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
(BURG GROWLING)
MAYFELD: Hey, hey, hey.
Okay. Okay. Okay, I get it.
I'm a little particular
about my personal space, too.
So, let's just do this job.
We get in, we get out, and you
don't have to see our faces anymore.
Someone tell me why we
even need a Mandalorian.
Well, apparently they're the
greatest warriors in the galaxy.
So they say.
Then why are they all dead?
(BOTH LAUGH)
Well, you flew with him, Xi'an.
Is he as good as they say?
Ask him about the job on Alzoc III.
- THE MANDALORIAN: I did what I had to.
- (XI'AN CHUCKLES)
Oh, but you liked it.
See, I know who you really are.
- He never takes off the helmet?
- (CHUCKLES)
This is the Way.
- (XI'AN CHUCKLES)
- MAYFELD: Huh.
I wonder what you look like under there.
Maybe he's a Gungan.
Is that why yousa don't
wanna show your face?
(ALL GUFFAW)
- You ever seen his face?
- (XI'AN GASPS SOFTLY)
A lady never tells.
Aw. Come on, Mando. We all
gotta trust each other here.
You gotta show us somethin'.
Come on. Just lift the helmet up.
Come on.
Let's all see your eyes.
BURG: I'll do it.
(GRUNTING)
(THE CHILD COOS)
Whoa! What is that?
(MAYFELD CHUCKLES)
You get lonely up here, buddy? Huh?
(COOS)
Wait a minute. Did
you two make that? Huh?
What is it, like a pet or somethin'?
THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah.
Something like that.
Didn't take you for the type.
Maybe that code of
yours has made you soft.
MAYFELD: Me, I was
never really into pets.
Yeah, I didn't have the
temperament. Patience, you know?
I mean, I tried, but never worked out.
But I'm thinkin'
maybe I'll try again
with this little fella.
Huh?
- (THE CHILD COOS)
- (XI'AN CHUCKLES)
(MAYFELD CHUCKLES)
ZERO: Dropping out of hyperspace now.
Commencing final approach, now.
Cloaking signal, now.
(BURG GRUNTS)
- (XI'AN GRUNTS)
- ZERO: Engaging coupling now.
- ZERO: Coupling confirmed. We are down.
- (SNARLS)
ZERO: And relax.
- Commence extraction now.
- (THE CHILD COOING)
Useless droid didn't even
give us a proper countdown.
Z, are you sure they can't see us?
ZERO: The Razor Crest is
scrambling our signature
and I am inside the prison system.
It's impressive that this
gunship had survived the Empire
without being impounded.
All right, we got a job
to do. Mando, you're up.
(XI'AN GIGGLES)
(RAPID BEEPING)
(BEEPING)
- It's me?
- Always you.
Zero.
- (GRUNTS)
- Get us to the control room.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
ZERO: Sub level three.
Disabling onboard surveillance.
MAYFELD: All right, we're on the clock.
When we engage those droids,
they're gonna be all over us.
THE MANDALORIAN: I know the drill.
ZERO: Bio trackers activated.
I've got eyes.
All right, let's go.
THE MANDALORIAN: I don't like this.
You always were paranoid.
Is that true, Mando?
Were you always paranoid?
(ALIEN PRISONER GRUNTING)
(SNARLS)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
ZERO: Approaching control room.
Make a left at the next juncture.
(DROID CHATTERING)
What? It's just a little mousey.
- Come here, little mousey.
- MAYFELD: Burg.
- Mousey, come here. Come here.
No! Burg, what are you doin'?
What?
SECURITY DROID: Intruder
alert. Open fire.
We're too exposed here.
If they get a signal out,
it's not gonna matter.
Mando, let's go! You're
supposed to be somethin' special.
I knew it. I knew it!
(XI'AN GROWLS)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
(THE MANDALORIAN GROANS)
(PRISONERS CLAMORING)
(BURG SCOFFS)
Make sure you clean up your mess.
(BURG GRUNTS)
ZERO: It seems your
presence has been detected.
Redirecting security alert
away from your position.
Z, open the door!
ZERO: But I'm detecting
an organic signature.
MAYFELD: Yeah, okay. All right. Just open the door!
Stop!
(STUTTERS) Just stop right there.
(BREATHING HEAVILY) You put
down the blasters right now.
Nice shoes.
DAVAN: Put down your blasters.
Matches his belt.
(LAUGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN: There were only
supposed to be droids on this ship.
MAYFELD: Hang on, hang
on. Let's see here. Uh...
Cell two-two-one.
All right, now for our
well-dressed friend.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey,
hey. Easy. Easy, egghead.
Put that down. Put that down. Come on.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Easy.
- Put it down now!
THE MANDALORIAN: Easy. Nobody has
to get hurt here. Just calm down.
What is that thing?
THE MANDALORIAN: It's a tracking beacon.
He presses that thing, we're all done.
A New Republic attack team
will hone in on that signal
and blow us all to hell.
Put it down!
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
You didn't think we needed to
know that tiny little detail?
I didn't think we'd get to this point.
Yet here we are.
Are you questioning my
managerial style, Xi'an?
(CHUCKLES) No, sir.
THE MANDALORIAN: Hey. Listen to me.
Hey, hey, hey. Listen to me, okay?
Look.
- Hey. Put it down.
- Are you crazy?
THE MANDALORIAN: Put it down.
What's your name?
(STAMMERING)
- It's Davan.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Davan.
We're not here for you.
We're here for a prisoner.
If you let us go about our job,
you can walk away with your life.
No, he won't.
Hey.
You realize what you're
gonna bring down on us?
You think I care about that?
THE MANDALORIAN: We're not killing anybody.
Get that blaster out of my face, Mando.
THE MANDALORIAN: I can't do that.
Get that blaster out of my face, Mando!
(BURG GROWLS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Don't.
Would you both just shut up?
Crazy Twi.
I had it under control.
Yeah. Looked like it. (CHUCKLES)
(RAPID BEEPING)
Was that thing blinking before?
Was it?
- ZERO: Zero to Mayfeld. Zero to Mayfeld.
- What?
ZERO: I've detected a New
Republic distress signal
homing in on your location.
You have approximately 20 minutes.
We only need five.
MAYFELD: Let's go, let's
go. Move, move, move!
(ROARS)
(GRUNTING)
(BURG GROWLS)
- (BEEPS)
- Z, open it up.
ZERO: You have 15 minutes remaining.
MAYFELD: Open it up!
THE MANDALORIAN: Qin.
Funny, the man who left
me behind is now my savior.
- Mando.
- (BURG GROWLS)
- Brother!
- Sister. (CHUCKLES)
Attack's on the way. He's
already dead meat. Let's go!
Come on, it's better this way.
You deserve this!
MAYFELD: Let's go!
GREEF KARGA: (DISTORTED) Mando. Mando?
I've received your transmission.
Upon your return, deliver the
quarry directly to the client.
- I have no idea...
- ZERO: Interesting.
MAYFELD: Zero, we got Qin.
ZERO: I found some
information on The Mandalorian.
From the Bounty Hunters Guild.
Yeah, do whatever. Just
get us off this ship.
ZERO: You have 10 minutes remaining.
(GRUNTING)
(THE MANDALORIAN PANTING)
(CONSOLE BEEPING)
- ZERO: Zero to Mayfeld. Zero to Mayfeld.
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Yeah?
- ZERO: You have a potential problem.
He has escaped.
(SCREAMING)
- I told you we should've ended him.
- I know!
- This is your fault!
- MAYFELD: I know!
- BURG: Go! Go, go, go!
- MAYFELD: Come on!
- XI'AN: No!
- BURG: No!
- No!
- Burg! Burg!
(GROWLS)
ZERO: Zero to Mayfeld.
Mayfeld, do you copy?
It seems comms are no longer
functioning, therefore
you cannot hear me.
- You are on your own.
- (THE CHILD COOS)
ZERO: Curious.
(BOTH GROWLING)
It's all right. You and
the Devaronian, split up.
Find Mando and kill him.
Then find a way back to the ship!
Zero! We need a path.
Zero!
- (GRUNTS)
- (YELLS)
Do you have a name?
Mayfeld.
(CHUCKLES) Well, Mr. Mayfeld,
you're gonna get me
the hell off this ship.
Hey, wait. What about your sister?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What about her?
Nice family.
(ALARM BLARING)
(RAPID BEEPING)
(LAUGHS)
Mando always did hate droids. (LAUGHS)
- Z?
- (RADIO STATIC)
- MAYFELD: Z?
- (STATIC CONTINUES)
Hey, hey.
Whatever Ran promised, I'll
see to it you get triple share.
Just get him.
You better be good for it.
(QIN CHUCKLES)
(SING-SONG) Mando.
(GRUNTING)
(COMMS FEEDBACK WHINING, CLATTERS)
(GASPS)
Where are you, little mouse?
(GROANING)
(GROWLS)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
(BURG GRUNTING)
(THE MANDALORIAN GROANS)
(BURG GROWLING)
(THE MANDALORIAN GROANING)
(BURG AND THE MANDALORIAN
CONTINUE GRUNTING)
Let's see your face, Mandalorian.
(BURG LAUGHING)
(GROWLING)
(LAUGHING)
(YELLS)
Zero, where is he?
(FEEDBACK WHINING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (GROANS)
- (YELLS)
(XI'AN GASPS)
(DOOR HISSING)
- (DROID BEEPING)
- (MAYFELD EXCLAIMS)
What the...
No!
(DOOR HISSING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
THE MANDALORIAN: Qin.
You killed the others.
THE MANDALORIAN: They got what they deserved.
(SNARLS SOFTLY)
You kill me, you don't get your money.
Whatever Ran promised, I'll
make sure you get it, and more.
Come on, Mando. (SCOFFS)
Be reasonable.
Huh?
You were hired to do a job, right?
So do it.
Isn't that your code?
Aren't you a man of honor?
(QIN LAUGHING)
(BEEPS)
(COOS SOFTLY)
(GUN FIRES)
- (THE CHILD COOING)
- (BODY THUDS)
(COOS)
(SIGNAL WHINING)
(QIN LAUGHING)
Where are the others?
THE MANDALORIAN: No questions
asked. That's the policy, right?
Yeah. That is the policy.
THE MANDALORIAN: I did the job.
Yeah, you did.
THE MANDALORIAN: Just like the good old days.
Yeah, just like the good old days.
(DOOR HISSING)
Kill him.
(LAUGHING)
(QIN LAUGHING)
(DEVICE BEEPING)
What's this?
That bastard.
(BOTH GASPING)
I got a clear signal
on the tracking beacon.
Copy that.
Are those X-wings?
Yep. That's definitely
a tracking beacon.
Looks like they're launching a gunship.
Copy. Goin' in.
(THE MANDALORIAN SIGHS)
I told you that was a bad idea.
(COOS)
(SNARLS)
- Sync and corrections by VitoSilans - www.addic7ed.com -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44