THE CLIENT: Such a large bounty
- for such a small package.
- (CRYING)
THE MANDALORIAN: My armor
has lost its integrity.
I may need to begin again.
ARMORER: I must warn you.
It will draw many eyes.
GREEF KARGA: They all hate you, Mando.
Now, how can I show my gratitude
to my most valuable partner?
THE MANDALORIAN: What
are they doing with it?
GREEF KARGA: I didn't ask.
It's against the Guild Code.
(EXPLOSION)
THE MANDALORIAN: Step
aside. I'm going to my ship.
You put the bounty down and
perhaps I'll let you pass.
THE MANDALORIAN: How many
of them had tracking fobs?
All of them. All of them!
WINTA: (SING-SONGY)
I'm gonna get you. (GIGGLING)
(GIGGLES)
(INAUDIBLE)
- (CREATURE CHITTERING)
- Oh.
(WINTA GRUNTING)
(LOUD THUDDING)
(DISTANT EXPLOSION)
- Go, go, go!
- They're back!
- WOMAN 1: Go!
- MAN 1: Run for cover.
- WOMAN 2: Get inside!
- WINTA: Mama!
Mama!
- MAN 3: Go!
- (FIRING CONTINUES)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- Mama!
- Winta!
WINTA: Mama!
(WHIMPERS)
(KLATOOINIANS YELLING)
Come on.
- (WINTA WHIMPERS)
- (SHUSHING)
(GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(ROARS)
(OMERA GASPS, PANTING)
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
(THE CHILD COOING)
(BEEPS)
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
THE MANDALORIAN: Stop touching things.
(COOS)
(RATTLING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Let's see. Sorgan.
Looks like there's no star
port, no industrial centers,
no population density.
Real backwater skug hole.
Which means it's perfect for us.
You ready to lay low and stretch
your legs for a couple of months,
you little womp rat?
Nobody's gonna find us here.
(ENGINE HISSING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Listen.
I'm gonna go out there
and I'm gonna look around.
It shouldn't take too long.
Now, don't touch anything.
I'll find us some lodging,
then I'll come back for you.
You stay right here.
You stay. Don't move.
- You understand?
- (GRUNTS)
Great.
(DOOR HISSES, WHIRRING)
(COOS)
(SIGHS)
Oh, what the hell? Come on.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (YELPS)
(GIGGLING)
Welcome, travelers. Can I
interest you in anything?
THE MANDALORIAN: Bone
broth, for the little one.
Oh, well, you're in luck. I
just took down a grinjer,
so there's plenty.
Can I interest you in a
porringer of broth as well?
- THE MANDALORIAN: Just the one.
- WOMAN: Very well.
THE MANDALORIAN: That one over
there. When did she arrive?
I've seen her here for
the last week or so.
- What's her business here?
- WOMAN: Business?
Oh, well, there's not much business
in Sorgan, so I can't say. (CHUCKLING)
She doesn't strike me as a log
runner. Well, thank you, sir.
I will get that broth to
you as soon as possible,
and I will throw in a flagon of
spotchka just for good measure.
I will be right back with that.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Keep an eye on the kid.
- (COIN CLINKS)
Yes, sir.
(BEEPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(THE MANDALORIAN GROANING SOFTLY)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (THE MANDALORIAN CHOKES)
(BOTH PANTING)
(SLURPING)
(CHITTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: You want some soup?
CARA: Saw most of my action
mopping up after Endor.
Mostly Ex-Imperial Warlords.
They wanted it fast and quiet.
They'd send us in on the drop ships.
No support, just us.
Then when the Imps were
gone, the politics started.
We were peacekeepers, protecting
delegates, suppressing riots.
Not what I signed up for.
THE MANDALORIAN: How'd you end up here?
Let's just call it an early retirement.
Look, I knew you were Guild.
I figured you had a fob on me.
That's why I came at you so hard.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah,
that's what I figured.
Well, this has been a real treat,
but unless you wanna go another round,
one of us is gonna have to
move on, and I was here first.
THE MANDALORIAN: Well, looks
like this planet's taken.
(INSECTS BUZZING)
(RAZOR CREST WHIRRING)
Excuse me.
CABEN: Excuse me, sir.
THE MANDALORIAN: There
something I can help you with?
Uh, yeah.
Raiders.
We have money.
THE MANDALORIAN: So, you
think I'm some kinda mercenary?
You are a Mandalorian, right?
Or at least wearing Mandalorian armor.
That is Mandalorian armor, right?
- THE MANDALORIAN: It is.
- See? I told him.
Sir, I've read a lot about
your people... (STAMMERS) Tribe.
- If half of what I read is true...
- We have money.
- THE MANDALORIAN: How much?
- Everything we have, sir.
- Our whole harvest was stolen.
- Krill. We're krill farmers.
CABEN: We brew spotchka.
Our whole village chipped in.
THE MANDALORIAN: It's not enough.
Are you sure? You don't
even know what the job is.
THE MANDALORIAN: I know
it's not enough. Good luck.
This is everything we have.
We'll give you more
after the next harvest.
(DOOR HISSING)
Come on. Let's head back.
Took us the whole day to get here.
Now we have to ride
back with no protection
to the middle of nowhere.
THE MANDALORIAN: Where do you live?
On a farm. Weren't you listening?
We're farmers.
THE MANDALORIAN:
In the middle of nowhere?
Yes.
THE MANDALORIAN: You have lodging?
Yeah. Absolutely.
THE MANDALORIAN: Good. Come up and help.
(CLATTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm
gonna need one more thing.
Give me those credits.
Ready for round two?
CARA: So, we're basically
running off a band
of Raiders for lunch money?
THE MANDALORIAN: They're quartering
us in the middle of nowhere.
Last I checked, that's
a pretty square deal
for somebody in your position.
Worst case scenario,
you tune up your blaster.
Best case, we're a deterrent.
I can't imagine there's
anything living in these trees
that an ex-shock
trooper couldn't handle.
(COOING)
KID 1: Everyone, they're here!
(KIDS GIGGLING)
KID 2: Come on.
THE MANDALORIAN: Well, looks
like they're happy to see us.
- Looks like.
- (THE CHILD LAUGHING)
- Hi.
- KID: He's so cute.
- (BABBLES)
- KID: Aw!
(KIDS AND THE CHILD CONTINUE GIGGLING)
Please come in.
I hope this is comfortable for you.
Sorry that all we have is the barn.
THE MANDALORIAN: This will do fine.
I stacked some blankets over here.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Thank you. That's very kind.
(WINTA GASPS)
This is my daughter, Winta.
We don't get a lot of
visitors around here.
She's not used to strangers.
This nice man is going to help
protect us from the bad ones.
Thank you.
Come on, Winta. Let's
give our guests some room.
OMERA: Knock, knock.
THE MANDALORIAN: Come in.
(COOING)
Can I feed him?
THE MANDALORIAN: Sure.
Are you hungry?
(GIGGLING)
Can I play with him?
THE MANDALORIAN: (SIGHS) Sure.
(THE CHILD COOING)
WINTA: (GIGGLES) Come on.
(BABBLING)
- THE MANDALORIAN: I don't think...
- They'll be fine.
- I don't...
I brought you some food.
I noticed you didn't eat out there.
I'll leave it here for when I go.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's
very thoughtful of you.
Do you mind if ask you something?
THE MANDALORIAN: Go ahead.
How long has it been since
you've taken that off?
THE MANDALORIAN: Yesterday.
I mean, in front of someone else.
THE MANDALORIAN: I wasn't
much older than they are.
(KIDS GIGGLING)
You haven't shown your face
to anyone since you were a kid?
THE MANDALORIAN: No. I was
happy that they took me in.
My parents were killed and the
Mandalorians took care of me.
I'm sorry.
THE MANDALORIAN: This is the Way.
Let us know if there's
anything you need.
THE MANDALORIAN: Thank you.
(KIDS CONTINUE GIGGLING)
(BEEPS)
THE MANDALORIAN: About 15 or 20
of them came through here on foot.
And something big sheared
off those branches.
AT-ST.
THE MANDALORIAN: Imperial
walker. What's it doing here?
I don't know.
But this is more than I signed up for.
THE MANDALORIAN: Bad news.
You can't live here anymore.
- What?
- Why?
Nice bedside manner.
THE MANDALORIAN: You
think you can do better?
Can't do much worse.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
I know this is not the
news you wanted to hear,
but there are no other options.
- You took the job.
- Yeah.
That was before we
knew about the AT-ST.
What is that?
The armored walker
with two enormous guns
that you knew about and didn't tell us.
- WOMAN 1: Help us.
- WOMAN 2: Please.
- MAN 1: You're supposed to help us.
- WOMAN 3: But we hired you.
- WOMAN 4: Please.
- We have nowhere to go.
CARA: Sure you do. This is a big planet.
I mean, I've seen a lot smaller.
My grandparents seeded these ponds.
- It took generations.
- WOMAN: Yeah.
I understand. I do. But
there are only two of us.
No, there's not.
There's at least 20 here.
- CABEN: Yeah.
- CARA: I mean fighters. Be realistic.
- CABEN: We can learn.
- STOKE: We can.
- CABEN: Give us a chance.
- STOKE: Please.
I've seen that thing take out
entire companies of soldiers
in a matter of minutes.
(ALL MURMURING)
We're not leaving.
You cannot fight that thing.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Unless we show them how.
MAN 1: Show us.
MAN 2: Yeah, we can do this.
THE MANDALORIAN: You
got two problems here.
You got the bandits,
and you got the mech.
We'll handle the AT-ST,
but you gotta protect us when
they come out of the woods.
And I don't have to tell
you how dangerous they are.
Cara Dune here was a veteran.
She was a drop soldier
for the Rebellion,
and she's gonna lay out a plan
for you, so listen carefully.
Now, there's nothing on this planet
that can damage the legs on this thing,
so we're gonna build a trap.
We're gonna need to dig
real deep, right here,
so that when it steps in, it drops.
The two of us will hit
their camp. Provoke them.
That'll bring the fight out of
the woods and down here to us.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm gonna
need you to cut down trees
and build barricades along these edges.
I need it high enough so
that they can't get over,
and strong enough so that
it can't break through.
Okay. Who knows how to shoot?
CARA: Ready, one. Move your leg out.
Get ready.
One.
- Get into it. One.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Fire.
- CARA: One.
- (ALL GRUNTING)
Two.
Three.
Four.
Reset.
Louder.
- One.
- (ALL CONTINUE GRUNTING)
Two.
THE MANDALORIAN: The sun is about
to set, and we'll be leaving soon.
When we return, we're coming in hot.
We'll be ready.
(KLATOOINIANS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(KLATOOINIAN 1 SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
- (KLATOOINIAN GRUNTS)
- (CARA GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LIQUID BUBBLING)
(BEEPING)
(BUBBLING)
(WHISTLES)
(KLATOOINIANS GRUNTING)
(CARA GRUNTING)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(KLATOOINIAN YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES BEEPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS, GRUNTS)
- (BEEPING RAPIDLY)
- (CARA GRUNTING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Come on. I'll cover you.
(THE MANDALORIAN EXCLAIMS)
(BOTH GROAN)
(BOTH PANTING)
CARA: I hope the plan worked.
THE MANDALORIAN: Go. Go!
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
It's okay.
This is it. Once that thing steps
into the pond, it's goin' down.
(TREES CREAKING IN DISTANCE)
(THUDDING)
Weapons ready.
(THUDDING GROWS LOUDER)
THE MANDALORIAN: Just a few more steps.
It stopped.
THE MANDALORIAN: Get down. Get down.
Caben. Stay there.
CARA: Hold your positions.
(KLATOOINIANS YELLING)
Open fire.
THE MANDALORIAN: We gotta get
that thing to step forward.
(PANTING) I'm thinking.
MAN: Stay back, stay back!
(ALL SCREAMING)
New plan.
THE MANDALORIAN: What
do you have in mind?
Give me the pulse rifle.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'll cover you.
Come on, you got this.
CARA: Come to Mama.
This is it. It's now or never.
- Go.
- (YELLING)
(ALL YELLING)
Caben, Stoke, get out there.
(YELLING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Take the
bait, you hunk of junk.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(THE MANDALORIAN PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHING IN RELIEF)
(ALL CHEERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Was that the plan?
(BOTH PANTING)
Somethin' like that. (LAUGHING)
- (BABBLES)
- (CHITTERING)
ALL: Ew!
(LAUGHTER)
CARA: Thank you.
Can I set you something in the house?
THE MANDALORIAN:
Uh, thank you. Maybe later.
He's very happy here.
THE MANDALORIAN: He is.
Fits right in.
So, what happens if
you take that thing off?
They come after you and kill you?
THE MANDALORIAN: No. You just
can't ever put it back on again.
That's it?
So you can slip off the helmet,
and settle down with that
beautiful young widow,
and raise your kid sitting
here, sipping spotchka?
THE MANDALORIAN: You know, we raised
some hell here a few weeks back.
It's too much action for
a backwater town like this.
Word travels fast.
We might wanna cycle
the charts and move on.
Would not wanna be the
one who's gotta tell him.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm leaving him here.
Traveling with me,
that's no life for a kid.
I did my job, he's safe.
Better chance at a life.
KID 1: Come on. Come on.
It's gonna break his little heart.
THE MANDALORIAN: He'll
get over it. We all do.
(TRACKING FOB BEEPING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Excuse
me. Can I have a word?
Of course.
THE MANDALORIAN: It's very nice here.
Yes.
THE MANDALORIAN: I think it's
clear he's... He's happy here.
What about you?
THE MANDALORIAN: Me?
Are you happy here?
We want you to stay.
The community's grateful.
You can pack all this away
in case there's ever trouble.
You and your boy could have a good life.
He could be a child for a while.
Wouldn't that be nice?
THE MANDALORIAN: It would.
(RAPID BEEPING)
THE MANDALORIAN: I don't belong here.
But he does.
I understand.
I will look after him as one of my own.
(RAPID BEEPING CONTINUES)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (KIDS SCREAMING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Go get the kids.
(BODY THUDS)
(BEEPING)
Who's he tracking?
THE MANDALORIAN: The kid.
They know he's here.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yes.
Then they'll keep coming.
(CRACKLING)
Are you sure you don't want an escort?
THE MANDALORIAN: I appreciate the offer,
but we're gonna bypass the town
and head right to the Razor Crest.
Well then, until our paths cross.
THE MANDALORIAN: Until our paths cross.
- WINTA: I'm gonna miss you so much.
- (COOS)
(CRYING)
Thank you.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --