- What's your highest bounty?
- There is one job.
- Underworld?
- Deep pocket.
Greef Karga said you were the best
in the parsec.
I have a camtono of Beskar waiting for you
upon delivery of the asset.
You are Mandalorian!
I will help you.
Many have passed through.
They seek the same one.
IG Unit! Stand down.
You are a Guild member?
I have a suggestion.
We split the reward.
This is acceptable.
The tracking fob is still active.
There is a life form present.
I thought you were dead.
This is what was causing all the fuss?
I think it's a child.
It is better to deliver it alive then.
My ship
has been destroyed. I'm trapped here.
Stripped. Not destroyed.
The Jawas steal. They don't destroy.
Stolen or destroyed,
makes no difference to me.
They're protected
by their crawling fortress.
There's no way to recover the parts.
You can trade.
With Jawas?
Are you out of your mind?
I will take you to them.
I have spoken.
Hey! Spit that out.
They really don't like you
for some reason.
Well, I did disintegrate a few of them.
You need to drop your rifle.
I'm a Mandalorian.
Weapons are part of my religion.
Then you are not getting your parts back.
Fine.
And the blaster.
Good day.
They will trade all the parts
for the beskar.
I'm not gonna trade anything.
These are my parts.
They stole them from me.
- You understand this?
- No!
Whoa. Easy, easy.
Get away from it!
The egg? What egg?
Mando!
I have it.
I've got the egg.
I'm surprised you waited.
I'm surprised you took so long.
Is it still sleeping?
Yes.
Was it injured?
I don't think so.
Not physically.
Explain it to me again.
I still don't understand what happened.
Neither do I.
There's no way we're gonna get this to
work without a full maintenance facility.
This is gonna take days to fix.
If you care to help, it might go faster.
There is much work to do.
I can't thank you enough.
Please allow me to give you
a portion of the reward.
I cannot accept.
You are my guest
and I am therefore in your service.
I could use a crew member of your ability,
and I can pay handsomely.
I am honored,
but I have worked a lifetime
to finally be free of servitude.
I understand.
Then all I can offer is my thanks.
And I offer mine.
Thank you for bringing peace to my valley.
And good luck with The Child.
May it survive and bring you
a handsome reward.
I have spoken.