You were hired to do a job. So do it.
Isn't that your code?
Aren't you a man of honor?
IG Unit! Stand down.
You are a Guild member?
I have a suggestion.
We split the reward.
I could use a crew
member of your ability.
I am honored, but I have worked a
lifetime to finally
be free of servitude.
Then all I can offer is my thanks.
And I offer mine.
Thank you for bringing
peace to my valley.
I saw most of my action
cleaning up after Endor.
Mostly Ex-Imperial warlords.
Such a large bounty for
such a small package.
What they're gonna do with it?
I didn't ask.
It's against the Guild Code.
My friend, if you are
receiving this transmission,
that means you are alive.
You might be surprised to
hear this, but I am alive too.
I guess we can call it even.
A lot has happened since
we last saw each other.
The man who hired you is still here,
and his ranks of ex-Imperial
guards have grown.
They have imposed
despotic rule over my city,
which has impeded the
livelihood of the Guild.
We consider him an enemy,
but we cannot get close
enough to take him out.
If you would consider
one last commission,
I will very much make
it worth your while.
You have been successful so far
in staving off their hunters,
but they will not stop
until they have their prize.
So, here is my proposition.
Return to Nevarro.
Bring the child as bait.
I will arrange an exchange,
and provide loyal Guild
members as protection.
Once we get near the client,
you kill him, and we
both get what we want.
If you succeed, you keep the child
and I will have your name
cleared with the Guild,
for a man of honor should not
be forced to live in exile.
I await your arrival with optimism.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Pay up, mudscuffers!
Come on. That's mine, thank you.
All right, thank you.
Looking for some work?
It seems like a
straightforward operation.
They're providing the plan
and firepower. I'm the snare.
- With the kid?
- That's why I'm coming to you.
I don't know. I've
been advised to lay low.
If anybody runs my chain code,
I'll rot in a cell
for he rest of my life.
I thought you were a veteran.
Come back soon.
I've been a lot of things since.
Most of them carry a life sentence.
If I so much as book passage on a ship
registered to the New Republic, I'm...
I have a ship. I can
bring you there and back
with a handsome reward.
You can live free of worry.
I'm already free of worry,
and I'm not in the mood
to play soldier anymore.
Especially fighting some local warlord.
He's not a local warlord.
He's Imperial.
I'm in.
Does your contact need to vet me?
Doesn't know you're coming.
Really? That could be a problem.
It won't.
But if it is, that's his problem.
He all right up there alone?
Yeah.
Pick one.
You trust the contact?
Not particularly.
He and I had a run-in last time I
was there on some Guild business.
So then why are we going?
I don't have a choice.
You saw what happened on Sorgan.
They'll keep sending hunters.
The kid will never be
safe until the Imp is dead.
And you're okay with
bringing him back there?
Not really. That's why I'm bringing you.
We need someone to watch that thing.
Yeah.
You got anyone you can trust?
Whoa! Easy. Whoa!
It hasn't grown much.
I think it might be a Strand-Cast.
I don't think it was engineered.
I've worked in the gene farms.
This one looks evolved. Too ugly.
This one, on the other hand,
looks like she was farmed
in the Cytocaves of Nora.
This is Cara Dune. She
was a shock trooper.
You were a Dropper?
Did you serve?
On the other side, I'm afraid.
But I'm proud to say that
I paid out my clan's debt,
and now I serve no one but myself.
Would anyone care for some tea?
Please lower your blasters.
He will not harm you.
That thing is programmed
to kill the baby.
Not anymore.
It was left behind in the
wake of your destruction.
I found it laying where it fell.
Devoid of all life.
I recovered the flotsam
and staked it as my own
in accordance with the
Charter of the New Republic.
Little remained of its neural harness.
Reconstruction was quite difficult...
...but not impossible.
It had to learn everything from scratch.
This is something that cannot be
taught with the twist of a spanner.
It requires patience and repetition.
I spent day after day
reinforcing its development
with patience and affirmation.
It developed a personality
as its experiences grew.
Is it still a hunter?
No. But it will protect.
Tea?
I've run into some problems.
I figured as much. Why
else would you return?
I wanna hire your services.
I'm retired from service.
I can pay you handsomely, Ugnaught.
I have a name. It is Kuiil.
I need someone to protect
the little one, Kuiil.
I'm not suited for such work.
I can reprogram IG-11
for nursing and protocol.
No.
I don't want that
droid anywhere near him.
Why're you so distrustful of droids?
It tried to kill him.
It was programmed to do so.
Droids are not good or bad.
They are neutral reflections
of those who imprint them.
I've seen otherwise.
Do you trust me?
From what I can tell, yes.
Then you will trust my work.
IG-11 will join me.
And we do it not for payment,
but to protect the child
from Imperial slavery.
None will be free until the
old ways are gone forever.
Okay.
And the blurrgs will join me as well.
The blurrgs?
I have spoken.
I got you, Mando.
Care to double the bet?
No! No, no! Stop!
We're friends, we're
friends. Cara is my friend!
That is not okay!
Hmm. Very curious.
Curious? It almost killed me!
The story you told me of the
mudhorn now makes more sense.
- What is it?
- What it is, I don't know.
But what it does, this...
This I've heard rumors of.
What? When you worked for the Empire?
When I was sold to the Empire,
in indentured servitude.
Yet somehow, you walk free.
I bought my freedom through
the skill of my hands
and the labor of three
of your human lifetimes.
Do not cast doubt upon that of
what I am nor whom I shall serve.
Tell you what. I could really use
your craftwork right now.
Can you pad this container
so the child can sleep better?
I shall fabricate a better one.
Then perhaps this Dropper can
see how one can win their freedom
with the skill of one's hands.
So, we're going to Nevarro?
- Have you ever been?
- No.
We lost a lot of our forces there.
The city's dug in pretty deep.
No cover when you drop in.
It stayed in Empire control
'till the end of the war.
The warlord we're taking
out was an Imperial officer.
- What station?
- Hard to tell.
No insignia anymore.
I took out the safehouse
when I snatched the kid.
More Imps have reinforced since.
There's something more going on.
Maybe. We'll find out more when we land.
I have prepared second meal.
Would you care to be
served here or below?
I'm not hungry.
Under no circumstances does
that thing leave the ship.
You got a real thing
for droids, don't you?
I got a real thing for that droid.
The Ugnaught said he rewired it.
That droid was designed to kill things.
I don't care how much
wiring he replaced.
It goes against its nature.
Well, it shouldn't be a long job anyway.
We take out the head Imp,
the rest will run like rats.
Sorry for the remote rendezvous, Mando,
but things have gotten complicated
since you were last here.
It appears that
introductions are in order.
It seems we've both
provided a security detail.
I recommend the shock
trooper guards the ship.
These lava fields are lousy with Jawas.
She's coming with me.
But the town is now run by ex-Empire.
If a Rebel Dropper is with us,
they'll all get their hackles up.
She's coming.
Fine.
At least cover your tattoo.
No need to flaunt it.
Now, where is the little one?
So, this little bogwing is
what all the fuss was about.
What a precious little creature.
I can see why you didn't want to harm
a hair on its wrinkled little head.
Well, I'm glad this matter will
be put to rest once and for all.
The sun drops fast on Nevarro.
We can walk for a spell,
camp out at the riverbank,
then make our way into
town at first light.
I guess the little bugger's a carnivore.
Never seen anything like it.
They were ready to pay a
king's ransom for that thing.
Must be for some kind
of highfalutin menagerie.
Let's go over the plan again.
We both enter the common house.
We show the client the bait.
We join him at the
table. And you kill him.
Tell me about his reinforcements.
They're all ex-Empire.
As soon as they lose their
paycheck, poof, they'll all scatter.
- And what if they don't?
- They will.
That's not good enough.
If, for argument's sake,
a few of them don't realize
that I'm their best path
to alternative employment
and they elect to react impulsively,
then these three fine Guild Hunters,
along with that
battle-hardened shock trooper,
will cut down anyone who bucks.
How many will there be?
No more than four.
He travels with, at most, a Fire Team.
Trust me.
Nothing can go wrong.
No! Let go of her!
Drop her now!
Drop her!
He's hurt badly.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm fine. Ow!
Hold still.
They got you good.
How bad?
Bad.
The poison's spreading fast.
So this... This is how it happens.
Don't be so dramatic.
I need another medpac!
Got any other medpacs?
Anyone?
I'm guessing that's a "no".
It's still spreading.
This isn't working.
Get this thing outta here.
Wait.
He's trying to eat me.
You think they're
having second thoughts?
Could be.
I need your eyes.
I'm watching.
I guess this is it.
There's something you should know.
The plan was to kill
you and take the kid.
But after what happened last night,
I couldn't go through with it.
Go on. You can gun me down here and now
and it wouldn't violate the Code.
But if you do, this
child will never be safe.
We'll take our chances.
The Imperial client is obsessed
with obtaining this asset.
You tried to run, but
where did it get you?
This is ridiculous.
Perhaps you should let him speak.
Listen, we both need the
client to be eliminated.
Let me take the child to
him and then you two...
- No.
- Let's just kill him and get outta here.
He's right.
What are you doing?
As long as the Imp lives, he'll
send hunters after the child.
It's a trap.
- Bring me.
- Bring you?
Tell him you captured me.
Get me close to him and I'll kill him.
That's a good idea.
Give me your blaster.
This is insane.
- It's the only way.
- Well, I'm coming with you.
No, no, no. That would
make them suspicious.
I don't care. I'm coming.
Tell them she caught me.
Fine. Then she can bring the child.
No. The kid goes back in the ship.
But without the child,
none of this works!
I have a plan. Kuiil, ride
back to the Razor Crest
with the child and seal yourself in.
When you're inside, engage
ground security protocols.
Nothing on this planet
will breach those doors.
Here's a comlink.
I will keep the child safe.
Don't forget to cover your stripes.
Let's go.
Chain code?
I have a gift for the boss.
I'll give you 20 credits for the helmet.
Ha-ha! Not a chance.
That's going on my wall.
On your wall?
Go with it.
Go ahead.
You said four.
There are more than four troopers.
Four guarding the client.
Many more here in town.
Things got really heated once
Mando crashed the safehouse.
Slip him his blaster.
Not yet.
Here we are.
You see? Four.
Look what I brought you. As promised.
What exquisite craftmanship.
It is amazing how
beautiful beskar can be
when forged by its ancestral artisans.
Can I offer you a libation to celebrate
the closing of our shared narrative?
I would be obliged.
Please sit.
It is a shame that
your people suffered so.
Just as in this situation,
it was all avoidable.
Why did Mandalore resist our expansion?
The Empire improves
every system it touches.
Judge by any metric.
Safety, prosperity,
trade, opportunity, peace.
Compare Imperial rule
to what is happening now.
Look outside.
Is the world more peaceful
since the revolution?
I see nothing but death and chaos.
I would like to see the baby.
Uh...
It is asleep.
We all will be quiet.
Open the pram.
Don't think me to be rude.
I must take this call.
Give me the blaster.
You get one shot.
This is bad. You said four.
Well, there are more.
What can I tell you?
Yes, Moff Gideon?
Have they brought the child?
Yes, they have.
Currently, it is sleeping.
You may wanna check again.
Four stormtroopers?
This is bad.
Kuiil? Are you back to the ship yet?
Are you there? Do you copy?
Yes!
- Are you back to the ship yet?
- Not yet.
Get back to the ship and
bail. Get the kid out of here.
We're pinned down!
You have something I want.
Who's this guy?
You may think you have some idea
of what you are in possession of,
but you do not.
Kuiil, are you back to the
ship yet? They're onto us!
Kuiil, come in!
In a few moments, it will be mine.
Kuiil! Do you copy?
Kuiil!
It means more to me
than you will ever know.
Kuiil! Are you there?
Come in, Kuiil.
Kuiil, come in.
Kuiil? Are you there?
Do you copy?
Kuiil?
Kuiil!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --