Tonight, I get scared half to death
on our track,
We host our own art exhibition and the world
champion is in our reasonably priced car,
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Thank you, everybody!
Thank you, Hello! Hello and welcome,
Welcome, everybody,
Now, a few years ago, we got very
excited by this, the Noble M400,
But then the man behind the company
that made it upped sticks and left
and then they stopped making it and then the
whole operation just disappeared from the radar,
Now though... it's back,
This is what it's come up with,
Designed and built by some blokes I've never
heard of on an industrial estate in Leicester,
it's called the M600,
Underneath
the rather featureless body,
the chassis is made not from
carbon fibre, but stainless steel,
The V8 that powers it
is lifted from this,
Yep, It uses the same engine,
albeit with a couple of turbo
chargers that Volvo use in the XC90,
So, built in Leicestershire from
bits of the Industrial Revolution
and powered by the engine
from a Volvo school bus,
And the cost? &#163;200,000,
That does seem like a lot for a car
that has no satellite navigation,
no climate control, no airbag,
It doesn't even have
anti-lock brakes,
The men from Leicestershire
say ABS is just another example
of the nanny state sticking its
nose in, and that's very admirable,
But you can't help suspecting
the real reason it doesn't have ABS
is because when you're operating out
of a industrial unit in Leicestershire,
you can't really afford them,
There's another problem as well,
What kind of person looks at
the established range of supercars
and thinks,
I don't like any of them?
However, it turns out that there is
a reason why you might choose a Noble,
rather than a Porsche, or a Ferrari
or a Lamborghini,
or an Aston Martin,
or a McLaren Mercedes,
You see, in terms of sheer speed,
the Noble can blow all of that lot
into the middle of last week,
Let me show you
what I'm on about here,
I'm currently doing 40 mph
in second gear, Ready? Foot down,
And there's 60,
40-60 in one second, One!
In fourth gear,
100 to 120 in two seconds,
100 to 130 in three seconds,
It does 150 to 170 so quick that your
eyeballs bounce off the back of your skull...
like squash balls!
Break it, break it! Oh, my God!
You have to push, There's very
little servo assistance there,
If you push too hard, you'll lock
them up because there's no ABS,
God, it's quick!
That's mind-blowingly fast,
That is properly,
head-alteringly quick,
Flat out,
it'll do 225 miles an hour,
Mainly because the engine,
despite the Volvo connection,
develops 650 horsepower,
The whole car only weighs 1,250kg,
And the news
keeps on getting better,
This down here
is exactly the same switch
that a pilot uses in a Tornado
fighter-bomber to fire the missiles,
It was specifically designed so it couldn't
be used by accident and that is a good thing,
Because in here, what it does
is turn the traction control off,
Argh! I wish I'd kept it on!
I really wish I'd kept it on!
The margin for error
in most supercars is actually quite
wide, but in this, it really isn't,
Stop,
It's a constant nightmare,
1% too much speed going into a
corner, you get understeer like that,
1% too much throttle to
correct it, you've got oversteer,
1% wrong with the steering,
you're going to spin,
Remember, there are no electronic
driver aids to help you out,
There's no medevac chopper,
You get it wrong,
you're on your own!
There is a fantastic
sweet spot in this thing,
But even when you find it, you're
often too terrified to enjoy the moment,
To really enjoy it
and to find it regularly...
...you have to be a much
better driver than I am,
I'm not really doing this justice,
Driving it fast, then,
you need to be good,
But weirdly, to drive it at all,
you don't,
Happily, if you wind the engine down
to 550 horsepower or 450,
which you can do using
this switch here,
it becomes a different animal,
It becomes completely docile,
Calm, No harder to drive
than... a Nissan Micra,
And like the old Noble, it's
quiet and extremely comfortable,
It really does ride beautifully,
Summing this car up, then, is hard,
because let's be honest,
there are several very good reasons
why you shouldn't buy one,
But there is one
very good reason why you should...
Losers!
APPLAUSE
So it's that fast? That edgy?
That edgy?
Honestly, it's the nearest I've ever come
to collecting a camera car on a shoot,
I think that was the first time I've ever
seen you properly scared on our track,
Oh, I was, No, I really was,
It's not so bad when it's dry, but when it's
wet you have to have the reactions of a housefly,
So not a fat, balding middle-aged man,
then?
Not that, which is why we're now going
to hand it over to our tame racing driver,
Some say that you shouldn't
go round to his house
for your Christmas lunch, unless you
enjoy the great taste of seagull,
And that the reason
he always wears a helmet
is because a man once smashed him in the
face with a model of Salisbury Cathedral,
All we know is
he's called the Stig!
And he's off! We've had rain for the past
few weeks now and we've got a dusting of snow,
Still hoping for good things,
since Stig is one of the few things
that can really get to the
bottom of a Noble, He loves them!
That is nice through there,
Beautiful on the way out,
# In the bleak midwinter... #
Appropriate music for this weather,
Performing in the style of
a Kray brother's funeral there,
A bit of twitchiness on the way in, but tasty
on the way out of Chicago, now Hammerhead,
He came in very fast, understeering
as I discovered earlier,
but Stiggy knows how to drive
through and find that sweet spot,
# Oh, God
Oh, my king... #
Right, time now to unleash the
twin-turbo kick in the kidneys,
He does seem to be sawing
at the wheel a lot in there,
It is a brute, this car,
but the Stig isn't fazed,
That would be literally impossible,
Two corners left,
He's still working hard, but the
car itself looks really composed,
Coming up to Gambon,
slices through there
and across the line!
APPLAUSE
OK, Here it is! Here it is,
It goes, mmm...
Hang on,
you've just gone above a 599,
Yes, And above a Scuderia,
That's that fast Lambo, <span
tts:color=yellow0 And above the Enzo,
That's an Enzo up there!
Past the Veyron,
Past the Zonda convertible...
Whoa! <span tts:color=yellow0
To there!
So it's expensive, but it works?
Excellent, Right,
Now we will do the news
and we begin with the this -
it's a new Aston Martin,
It's called the Rapide,
You can think of it as a DB9
with two extra doors,
That means there's room back here
for two extra fully-grown adults
to enjoy the 470 horsepower,
V12 motoring experience,
And they can enjoy exquisite details, such as
these magnetically located grab handles, look,
It won't flap around
when you're driving along,
All this is yours for &#163;140,000,
Now,
that is quite a bit more expensive
than Porsche's four-door,
the Panamera,
but there are two very good reasons
why you should choose the Aston Martin,
Firstly, and unlike the Porsche,
it does look rather magnificent,
Secondly, most importantly,
this is quintessentially British,
Despite the fact
that it's made in Austria,
Which I think is in Germany,
OK, Now, as you can see,
we are surrounded here
by a mountain of motoring-related
Christmas present ideas,
<span tts:color=yellow0 I say present ideas,
actually it's landfill, Oh, yes,
We haven't got time to get through all
of it, but I want to start with this,
Perfume, as we know,
is a very popular Christmas gift,
Big names, Givenchy, Chanel,
Now look... The RAC,
Yes, the RAC has launched this,
They're calling it Eau De Voiture,
Ooh, sounds promising!
What you do is
you spray it into your car
and it makes it smell
like a minicab,
It's quite strong! <span tts:color=yellow0
Have some of that,
<span
tts:color=yellow0 Because it smells... Oh, shit!
My eyes!
You cretin! <span tts:color=yellow0
I'm blind!
The thing is, what it does,
and I've really got a lot of it now,
is it's one of those smells that makes
you think it's covering up other smells,
Like Femme Fresh,
LAUGHTER
Because it's a very strong smell in it's own right,
but it suggests that there are other things masking,
You get notes, don't you? You get
notes, undercurrents, Suggestions of...
I can smell the fruity stuff,
but also a bit of stale wee,
Sick?
I can get a really beery burp,
All the things
you'd expect in a minicab,
I have another gift suggestion here
for Christmas,
Are you fed up with people bumping
into you in a crowd situation?
<span tts:color=yellow0 Yes, I am!
Well, I have the solution here
with these small, ear-mounted
human indicators, I kid you not,
What happens is, I'm walking along,
say in a shopping centre,
Here I am in a shopping centre
and you'll be the crowd?
There's a danger of jostling here,
because I'm going to that shop on my right,
You can indicate!
So now you know and you can take evasive action,
Yes, Actually,
I fancy the record shop over there,
Everybody knows what's happening, I think it's a very
good gift,
So how much are they? Do we know?
Oh, I don't know, Some money,
Land Rover are taking
a very pragmatic approach
to the Christmas gift idea
and they have produced this,
It's the Land Rover distress
whistle and it will cost you &#163;1,50,
I just want to paint the scene
for you, You're in the wilderness
in your Land Rover and you drive into
an impassable gully, You become stuck,
It starts to fill up with water,
You're out of food,
you're almost out of fuel,
You cannot get a signal
on your mobile phone
and you're bleeding heavily from a
severe abdominal wound, But it's OK!
HE BLOWS WHISTLE
If I was there with you in that
situation and you produced that whistle,
I would beat you to death, <span
tts:color=cyan0 That's nice,
Well, yes, <span tts:color=yellow0
Look at this superb shirt,
It's got everything
you need, really,
It has a web address here,
It's stitched into the collar
and then on the back,
<span tts:color=yellow0 look at that
- Mercedes-Benz, That's classy,
Oh, yeah, Really, honestly, it's hard to
think of any way that this could be improved,
That says, I have a washing machine and
everything else I own is already in it,
But, James, you like a flowery
shirt, so why wouldn't you like that?
Well, why would you want
a web address?
Jeremy? Jeremy?
OK, this is a bad thing,
That's a bad thing,
It's got out of hand,
It's all right, No, it's gone out,
Relax,
That's actually quite...
Jeremy has
set fire to the Christmas presents!
I have actually set fire to
the Land Rover teddy bear, No,
You know
the smoking rules in Britain?
<span tts:color=yellow0
My eyes! Sorry about that!
Anyway, look - I think...
It's still on fire! <span tts:color=yellow0
It's not,
It's smouldering, that's all,
Look at this!
It's a fork on one end and
a 10mm ring spanner on the other,
And the best thing is, there's
another spanner in the middle!
No, but this means
you can go seamlessly
from mending your motorcycle to
eating a pie without even pausing,
<span tts:color=yellow0
Look at this, Wow!
You say wow,
This is some packaging,
You know the sort of packaging? You're
going to sever your fingers getting in there,
When you get in there,
you've got this metal thing,
Then you get underneath your car,
use what fingers you have left
from opening the packaging
to attach it to your exhaust pipe,
And then it makes a noise
which fools other road users
into thinking
that your car is turbo-charged,
Is it like that wastegate
noise when you lift off?
Brilliant,
We could attach you -
it would be easier,
It's not really going to fool anybody bolted
onto my Panda, whatever sort of noise it makes,
Chaps, you know how difficult
it is to choose the right calendar,
<span tts:color=yellow0 Obviously you choose it now and
you've got to live with it, It's a big commitment,
For 12 months,
you have to live with it,
So I'm a bit stumped on what I'm going to
use next year, because there's this one,
This is Her Majesty's
Prisons of England,
Different picture every month,
<span tts:color=yellow0 But then I found this one
- Birmingham's Outer Circle Municipal Bus Route, Oh, nice!
But then I found, I think, the
solution to my calendar problems,
The Unofficial...
Oh, yes!
CHEERING
Who did that? It's awful!
You can have it, James,
I've got loads,
Why are you
drunk in all the pictures?
It looks like all the pictures were
taken coming out of award ceremonies,
so, yes, I probably was drunk, <span tts:color=yellow0
Do you know what I really love about that calendar?
Because it's unofficial, you all go and
buy one, he receives not one single penny,
I know, I know!
Thank you for publicising it,
It's very kind of you,
We'd like to recommend this
calendar, Everybody go and buy it,
Get rid of that thing!
Let's do
the rest of the show like that,
Why does everything get
broken in our Christmas thing?
As we know, the Lottery Fund
has spent millions of pounds
turning old warehouses in places like Liverpool
and the West Midlands into art galleries,
And we also know that they have
all been an unmitigated failure,
We think the reason for this is because
they haven't got any cars in them,
Art experts will tell you that cars
aren't art, We think they can be,
Back in the 1970s, BMW started
making things like this over here,
It's a three-litre CSL, but the bodywork has
been painted by American artist Alexander Calder,
Then in the '90s,
there was a three-series race car,
The body's been painted by artist
Sandro Chia, Then over here,
an 850 CSI - that's been painted
by British artist David Hockney,
Provincial galleries would never
accept this sort of thing these days,
and that, we reckon,
is exactly why they're failing,
So we decided to take over the
Mima Gallery in Middlesbrough,
And using nothing
but motoring-based art,
we would attempt to get 30,000 visitors
through the door up North in a single week,
And that's as many as Tate
Britain gets in a week in London,
This is the North,
which is where northerners live,
And this is the art gallery
we've taken over,
We'd simply clear out the paintings
northern people plainly don't want to see,
and fill it with motoring
exhibits that hopefully they do,
To decide what these exhibits would be, we
went to our secret motoring art base in Surrey,
<span tts:color=yellow0
What on earth is that? It's a car,
The artist claims that he makes
these by painting them
and then driving a remote control
over them, I mean, I like it,
I like it, <span tts:color=cyan0
It's got a joie de vivre to it,
Yes, put it in! Oh!
It's Damon Hill in the wet,
<span tts:color=yellow0
Superb, That goes in,
What he should have done
is just given us that bit,
That would now look like one of Monet's visions of
his lily pond, but it would be about Formula One,
It does have a Monet
quality to it, no question,
I'm sorry, gentlemen, this
is the worst painting I've ever seen
<span tts:color=yellow0 in my entire
life and it's not coming, Or is it?
Maybe this is a commentary
on the superhuman,
almost alien nature of
a Formula One driver at this level,
Because clearly this isn't human,
That much is immediately apparent,
What it's done is suck the life out
of this corpse in the overalls her,
All of that is gone,
drained out by this creature,
This is coming with us,
This is properly amazing stuff,
And so is that, I think in
Middlesbrough this will go well,
Why-aye, a tab! They're refuelling
his car and he's having a tab,
That is, without doubt,
the centrepiece of our exhibition,
It's exquisite work, <span tts:color=cyan0
That is not going in,
<span tts:color=yellow0
Hammond... It cannot go in!
We went round
the room ticking the yeses,
Look at the way they've captured
his moustache so beautifully here,
Not just that moustache, but
the other two moustaches as well,
So this is a collage
out of press comments about him,
I see,
Excellent, Definitely going in,
Oh, gentlemen!
Gentlemen! I bet you any money
that in the North,
people will be stunned by this,
It's a V8 Shark,
<span tts:color=cyan0 If it provokes a response, that's going,
In addition to the pre-prepared art,
we've been making some ourselves,
James, for example,
is keen to make a sculpture,
I've decided to de-construct the car,
literally, as you can see, and artistically,
Then rather than try and rebuild it as
a sculpture that speaks about the car,
I'm going to do it as a sculpture that speaks
about my emotions, my feelings, when I drive a car,
Inspired to some extent by Picasso...
What you need to bear in mind
is if you can get an artist,
somebody with frizzy hair and sticky-out
teeth, to say it's art, then it's art,
While James set to work
on his big metal face,
Richard went off to create a modern day
interpretation of Constable's Hay Wain,
Right...
Unlike Richard, I'm not very good at
drawing, because I didn't go to art school,
So my painting will be done by this,
The 2005 Red Bull F1 car, Yep,
Its three-litre V10
will be my brush,
All we need now
is a tame racing driver,
Some say he has a massive chin,
and that's true, he does,
Because he's David Coulthard,
So are you ready for this?
I think so, I'm still trying
to get my head round the concept,
Well, the idea is very simple,
We are going to put
paintballs into the air box,
They will then shoot out of
the exhaust, and into the canvas
that I'll be holding behind the car,
so we'll sort of splatter the canvas
using this car as our brush,
Sounds beautiful, <span tts:color=yellow0 It's
triggered to start firing them at 5,000 RPM,
So you need to go to 5,000,
Can you do that?
I can probably manage that, <span tts:color=yellow0 So if you
want to hop in, mate, I'll go and stand behind the vehicle,
Actually I might just put
some protection on my head,
I've done some weird things
in my life, but this is up there,
All right then, David, Ready!
Argh! Oh, God! Oh!
My gloves!
I'm not giving him mouth-to-mouth,
that's for sure,
Things were going badly for me, but
they were worse for Sir Henry May,
Every day, over 10,000 people go to the
National Gallery to see the Hay Wain,
More will come and see this, because it's
got more of a social statement about it,
Also, because I'd substituted
the Hay Wain for a Zonda,
It's poetry in paint,
One's now protected and using
a stronger aluminium canvas,
Coulthard and I were in business,
A plane of light
just bouncing off here,
Work it in, work it in...
With the paintball painting finished,
I was now busy on another creation,
What I'm doing is spraying the car with a special
paint that shows up best in ultra-violet light,
Sorry, sorry! So when I've finished, Mr Coulthard
is going to take it for a spin round the track,
It will streak, showing me
where the air flow has gone,
Sorry, sorry again, Sorry, mate,
With the car dripping wet,
David set off,
But unfortunately some of the paint
had gone on his visor,
Oh, dear!
After wiping his helmet, he set
off again to create some 200mph art,
You sprayed my helmet,
You shot one of my testicles,
Oh, I see, that helmet,
That was, I admit, a mistake,
but you should
see what has been achieved,
When we put this
under ultra-violet light...
Can we edit the spin out? <span tts:color=yellow0
Yes, we can edit that out!
You promise?
Projects completed,
we reconvened at the secret base,
where our exhibits
were to be assessed by Rupert Maas,
an art dealer
from the Antiques Roadshow,
It was a lot better than this,
<span tts:color=yellow0 The problem was, it didn't
dry, It's sort of still happening, isn't it?
It's performance art, because
it has streaked in a living way,
Yes...
It fell off the easel,
I mean, it really is nature and the
automotive world absolutely crashing together,
It's very good, Very good,
Quite, quite, I have to say, I think it is
probably more compost than art, but thank you,
Annoyingly, Rupert seemed to quite
interested in James May's big face,
It's called
Acceleration Face Number One,
I mean, I was inspired
to some extent by Der Blaue Reiter
and some of the works of that era, <span
tts:color=lime0 And African masks, Exactly,
The African mask has had an influence on it, It's very
angular, it's quite simplistic, it's quite primitive,
<span tts:color=yellow0
Has it been on fire? No,
What does the expert think? <span tts:color=lime0 Well, let's have
a look at it in the round, I quite like the welding, Oh!
We can repair this, James,
<span tts:color=yellow0
That's better! You see?
The Mona Lisa of the scrapheap,
The rest of the visit
wasn't any better,
<span tts:color=yellow0 Is there anything
here that catches your eye? No,
<span tts:color=yellow0
Does that one work? No,
Is this no good? No,
Does it work on any level for you?
<span tts:color=lime0
No, Does it have artistic merit?
No, So all of this is terrible?
Frankly, yes, <span tts:color=yellow0 Thank you
very much for coming along, Thank you,
I value your opinion, I won't
necessarily pay any attention to it,
In fact, none of us will, But thank you very much for
coming, Rupert,
Feeling a bit disheartened, we decided
to try and create our own BMW art car,
We need to agree on
a light source and a viewpoint,
Our genius plan was to paint the
inside of the car on the outside,
with James taking the bonnet,
me the side, and Jeremy the boot,
Can you tell what it is yet?
Jeremy, though,
didn't quite get the idea,
Right, red for the blood,
Er, mate...
What?
It's supposed to be
what's INSIDE the car,
How do you know there isn't
a horse's head in the boot?
For our final creation, we had to cut a car in
half, which meant using a dangerous plasma cutter,
That meant
we had to take precautions,
<span tts:color=yellow0 I could help,
You can't do this with a hammer,
That's exactly why
you're taped to a chair,
This is like a scene
out of Reservoir Dogs,
Don't give us ideas,
Guys, where did you find that car?
It was just outside with
all the rest of them for this,
It says here,
RJO4 RWZ, it's a rental car,
APPLAUSE
We'll see how that pans out
later on,
but now it's time to put a
star in our reasonably priced car,
Now, my guest tonight won the 2009
Formula One World Drivers' Championship,
He won the 2009 World Constructors'
Championship for Brawn,
And when he was pipped to the BBC's
Sports Personality of the Year award
last weekend, by Ryan Giggs,
he won the 2009 trophy
for the best forced smile,
Let's see
if he's still gritting his teeth,
Ladies and gentlemen, Jenson Button!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Thank you,
He's here,
Hello to you, Well done,
<span tts:color=yellow0 Jenson Button,
Formula One World Champion, Wooh!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Have a seat, Have a seat,
OK, that's the congratulations
over now the commiserations,
Because this
time last week...
Did anybody see
Sports Personality Of The Year?
<span tts:color=lime0
Yes, Yes,
I mean, let's be honest, Ryan Giggs,
he's 73,
And he can still kick a football,
I think you do need an
award for this, actually,
We have actually got a clip of the
moment, If you want to look away,
Everyone else can see this,
here we go, This is the moment,
Well, that is a shock,
That's a big shock,
Yeah,
That is a... That is a rictus grin,
that is,
I could be an actor with that, no?
No, you couldn't,
You couldn't because what I loved
was when he said
I haven't got a speech ready I
thought, no, but the man behind you has,
So anyway, I just want to know because I'm
sure loads of people will be interested,
It was actually this time last year,
there you were gearing up for a new season,
You had got Ross Brawn on board
who's obviously a genius designer
and then the call comes through from Honda that
they're pulling out of the sport, How did that feel?
It was difficult, I had just got back from, I
was in Lanzarote doing some fitness training,
I was all ready for the new season,
I arrived at Gatwick and I got a
message from my manager saying,
it's over,
Honda are pulling out of the sport,
It was a really difficult thing
to take in, Because you know, will
were going to be racing in 2009, We were going to
have a competitive car, possibility of winning races,
There was a lot of work
that went into that car and
it would have been an absolute
tragedy if it wasn't on the grid,
So all I could do was stay focused and
try to help the team as much as I could,
And that's what we did, we got through a
difficult winter and we produced a car...
<span tts:color=yellow0 And this was when Ross was able to buy what
remained of the Honda team,
Now, you came here last time having not won a
race in Formula One and you had done about 14011,
And you said you'd cheerfully
give up the jets, the lifestyle, the Monte Carlo for that first win,
But the thing is you damn nearly did give up
all that lifestyle to go to Brawn, didn't you?
I mean how big a sort of cut
was it in terms of everything?
There were 700 odd people working at the
factory and they had to scale down the team
so obviously there were some redundancies,
which was tough, even for the people that stayed,
But we all gave as much as we could
and we tried to help as much as we can,
I suppose it would be impossible to
say, no, I want n million dollars
a year when people are
being made redundant,
Because you went to 20% of
your salary or something,
Can't remember the figure
at the moment,
But don't feel sorry for me,
LAUGHTER
But that first test that you did
in what would become the Brawn car,
were you surprised how fast it was?
I knew we had built a good
car because all the numbers
said so in the wind tunnel but until you
actually drive it, yeah, you don't know 100%,
But we bolted in the Mercedes Benz engine in the
back because obviously it wasn't made for that engine,
We had to sort of trim the chassis down and
make sure the gearbox fitted, just about fitted,
With some spaces and what have you,
And went out and tested it at Barcelona and after
five laps I really felt comfortable in the car,
And I came and I said, Guys, you know,
this is all right, This is a good baseline,
Even though it was a last minute
botch job to get the Mercedes engine,
Yes, yep, this fills pretty nice,
My engineer came up to me and said,
<span tts:color=lime0 Jenson, you are seven tenths quicker
than anyone, They had been testing for three months,
Seven-tenths, <span tts:color=lime0 Seven tenths, Which
is a lot, That's three years in Formula One,
It's massive, <span tts:color=yellow0 Oh yeah,
And then every race people were putting on
big packages and for us to try and
keep the advantage was impossible,
So, yeah, it's been a
very tricky season,
Leading the championship from
start to finish sounds easy,
But it's not,
It's really, really hard,
Cos I have to say,
I mean Brazil, I don't know
if anybody was watching Brazil
which was the penultimate race,
You had to come fourth and
then you were definitely
World Champion irrespective
of what anyone else did,
Let's just have a look at these clips of
you in that race needing to come fourth,
So that's big John, isn't it?
<span tts:color=yellow0
Grosjean? Grosjean, Yeah,
'Can he do it?'
'Another stunning piece of driving under pressure from
Button,'
Look at that
again, that's round the outside,
'Wonderful move by
Button squeezed in there,'
We're almost doing 200 miles an hour there you can't really see
it from the camera but it's
Jesus that's so close,
'Jenson Button through,'
'I have to say,
he's been impressive,'
So this is now whatever
his name is, the Red Bull,
That was last of the late
breakers, wasn't it? Take that,
APPLAUSE
Great drive, <span tts:color=lime0 Thank you,
That was the drive of a champion that was,
You know when it kicks out...
When I'm driving a car and it
kicks out like that, I poo myself,
This might sound really silly and
think I'm a bit of a know it all, but
<span tts:color=lime0 I did actually do that on
purpose a little bit, What, kick the tail out?
Because I had to make sure that I could get to turn
two first and one of the only way of doing it is
a little bit of oversteer makes the guy a
little nervous that you're getting close,
And that is what happened, And the
great thing is he backed out of it,
Sorry, I just need to... This is very peculiar,
So you have the World Championship riding on
your having to finish the race,
obviously to get the World Championship,
And you kick the arse of the car
out, ON PURPOSE,
to unnerve whoever he is,
Well, it's giving him less room he's
got no room to turn on the inside,
Yes but what if you had
cocked it up,
You know for me to win the world championship before the
last race was a must,
I really wanted to get it done
before so I had to take the risk,
Now, obviously we are
looking forward to you versus Lewis,
Are you going to
be able to beat him?
That's the aim, I
wouldn't be doing it if not,
That's going to be, I tell you it's
going to be a fascinating battle,
This is a massive buzz for me,
It's so exciting,
I've been in F1 for ten years and
having the chance to race
alongside Lewis at McLaren, it's
something I'm really excited about,
Can we just talk
about your road cars?
Have you not got a Veyron? <span tts:color=lime0
Yes, I have, Can I just ask what's the fastest you've driven it?
Um, 70 times... Less 10%... 77,
LAUGHTER
<span
tts:color=yellow0 Do you believe him? Has it?
I sneaked in one day and unlocked the bars and drove round your
circuit,
Was it any good here?
It was all right, except for you had... I can't say
what I was going to say, Because I want to sell it,
LAUGHTER
So anyway, obviously you came here
into our Liana,
I tell you what,
I had to change my driving style here,
I think it was the snow, possibly,
You say that, you're such a fusspot,
No, seriously, listen to this, You've
got to listen to me, I'm a guest,
LAUGHTER
Go on because it would just
be a racing driver excuse,
No, it isn't an excuse
but I jumped in
and I sat there revving the engine with
the heater on thinking, I'm so nervous,
This thing is an amazing bit of
kit,
I've learnt so much coming here I'm really
going to take it into the 2010 season,
Who would like to see Jenson's lap?
<span tts:color=cyan0
Yeah!
There you go, It's
obviously the old Liana,
And there it is,
We haven't seen that for ages,
<span tts:color=lime0
Look how wet it is, It's damp,
Think like this is for the
World Championship, come on JB,
It's more important than the
Formula One world championship,
Look at it, it's greasy,
In F1 if it's wet the tyres work,
if it's greasy you just slide,
<span tts:color=yellow0 You're holding on nicely through there,
It is interesting, that first turn,
Yes, I'm
impressed, no power understeer,
<span tts:color=yellow0 First turn you took the
wide line in, A little bit wild, JB, Come on!
At least I'm not singing,
You're not singing, And Lewis has a different line
in that first corner and he's adamant about it,
<span tts:color=yellow0 So there you
go, you see, now that's tidy,
I tell you what, I'm more scared
driving this than I'm a Formula One car,
I was, This bit here is scary,
<span tts:color=yellow0 It is, If you go on the red wires, that's
quite slippery, I think they should put this on the F1 calendar,
This place rocks,
Oh, That was nice and close
to the tyres made the move,
Second to last corner
here let's have a look,
Yes, that's good,
<span tts:color=yellow0 Got the back out a bit,
Come-on, got the back out again,
There we are,
Across the line,
I thought that looked
quite good, that,
So,
APPLAUSE
So, Here we go, Jenson... Button,
<span tts:color=lime0 See that, I didn't
even lean forward, You will,
No, really, Where do you reckon?
It felt good,
Very slippery but I could slide
the car through the corners,
It was fun, I don't think
I'm quicker than I was before,
Because it was dry, how would I be?
Well, Lewis was here in exactly the
same car in exactly the same conditions,
<span tts:color=yellow0 They rarely were exactly
the same, I'm a better driver than I was then,
You did it, he's a 1,44,7,
you did it in 1...
40...
4...
9...
<span
tts:color=yellow0 You just missed out,
But give him a huge one,
Wait a minute, I'll
give you the wet,
Look at that,
Do you know what it was? It was that
showboating in the last two corners,
It was fun, though,
That little thing is so fun,
It is, You should try the
more powerful Chevrolet Lacetti,
Well, they wouldn't let
me have a go in that one,
No, because that's the Formula One
car,
Anyway ladies and gentlemen, I give
our World Champion, Jenson Button,
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
And actually your face will be
back in a minute because what we're going
to do now is pick up our art gallery film,
James and I arrived by aeroplane
fresh from the south,
Where do Geordies actually come from?
Geordies are from the Northeast,
Maybe they're all Geordies, Then
there's others, Foggies, aren't there?
There's the Foggies and the
Muggies and the monkey hangers,
<span tts:color=cyan0 I don't know what they
are, Are they all types of Geordie?
<span tts:color=cyan0 Well I think so,
Or are they, maybe they're different,
They all say why-aye so
they must all be Geordies,
As our BMW art car was so valuable, I
decided to drive it to the exhibition myself,
What I have here is a 3,5
litre straight six painting,
It's art that moves you,
quite literally, moves you,
At the Middlesbrough Institute Of
Modern Art, Captain Sense of Direction
had decided to make an audio guide to that
would steer visitors around the exhibits,
If you turn through almost 180 degrees to your left
or even to your right in fact because it of course
makes no difference whatsoever and walk
straight ahead towards the wall and rotating to
your right and not quite through 180
degrees but probably about 155,
I, meanwhile was on the road, touring the local radio
stations in a bid to drum up some support for our show,
This is fantastic,
I've got a van,
I've got a list of phone
numbers and I've got a mission,
I'm a PR agent,
And then walking through the white
door we arrive at the upstairs gallery,
Actually, that's not right, You need to come out
and turn left or right if you haven't gone through
the white door through the
glass door, which you push,
You are then in
the upstairs gallery,
The first stop on my publicity tour
was Radio Tees,
Who cares about the weather
because it's the weekend,
Who cares when Top Gear is in town,
And Richard flipping Hammond is with
us,
Here comes the publicity,
Welcome to Teesside, You of course used to work
here many many years ago, why are you here?'
Well, it's great to be here,
I did used to work here, apparently,
I worked in a lot of radio
stations for not very long,
What are you doing!
'So yes I worked here... '
<span tts:color=yellow0 Talk about the exhibition,
And I have fond memories of working here,
Nobody's interested in your
bloody memories,
Because I started in radio York
in 1989,
Oh for crying out loud!
For the rest of the interview Hammond
brilliantly publicised... himself,
I've just started something up called
Blast Lab, a kids' science show,
Oh, for God's sake,
This is ridiculous,
To make matters worse
in the gallery May was busy
ignoring our instructions to
make the audio guide interesting,
As it was codenamed during development,
rejecting the complicated hydragas suspension
of its forebear, the Allegro,
in favour of a straightforward
steel-sprung chassis with a rear axle derived
from a design already used to great effect,
Hello?
Yeah, I'm doing it,
I've just,
Yes, I know it's got to be done by
it 3,30, But I can't do it because
people keep ringing me up and
asking me if I've done it yet,
As I bore down on Middlesbrough, Hammond's
publicity tour was going from bad to worse,
Yes, I did, I started in 1989
at Radio York,
'Yeah, absolutely, I think Total Wipeout
has been a tremendous success... '
I'm going to have a heart attack!
There's one where people
have to climb a platform and
in front of them are four massive red
inflatable balls and they have to...
Total Wipeout is just
idiots falling over,
Talk about our art exhibition!
The good people of Hartlepool,
Hammond is in town with his
PR machine,
At Mima, the other idiot was
in the gallery of motor-racing,
A subject about
which he knows nothing,
Some pictures of racing
cars going around corners...
Hopefully, these cardboard boxes
won't be here by the time you arrive,
There's a man on fire,
There's a car going along, erm...
And then I had a problem,
I was coming round the corner
doing about 27mph
and a cow was there,
And I just had nowhere
to go because of this...
I'd say there was a school bus... well it was
a bus full of children, handicapped children,
and I saw some ginger
ones on so I just...
I thought, well I'm going to have
to miss that, so I'll put it
in the ditch rather than injure
the children,
That story didn't wash,
Take a deep breath, Sir, Lips around
the tube, constant stream of breath,
Keep going, keep going, keep going,
thank you,
The good news was, I scored zero,
The bad news came when the car
was towed out of the ditch,
That's not too...
It is quite bad, Oh, God,
And my attempts to mask the damage
with T-Cut just made everything worse,
ENGINE REVS
This was an important
exhibit for us, this car,
I'm casting around in my head for someone to
blame but it's just me, it keeps coming back at me,
So, when we met up, I decided
to do the honourable thing,
And go on the attack,
Did you hear what he did on the...?
<span tts:color=cyan0 Yes, I did hear what you did on
the radio, I've been working my backside off,
You have been and done one interview and
you talked about Blast Lab, Total Wipeout...
He didn't ask the right questions, <span
tts:color=yellow0 I told you,
I know more about PR than you,
I was on top of it,
Listen, none of this detracts
from the fact, and I can read it in
your face, that you've been an idiot
and you have ruined the whole event,
By the way, Thanks for asking,
<span tts:color=yellow0
I'm fine, We don't care,
Evidently, No, it has not...
As the exhibition was due to open the following
morning, we agreed to stop bickering and get to work,
James went off to rouse the troops,
And Richard
relaunched his PR campaign,
My work is complete,
One mobile billboard,
But better still,
just to really give the message,
what I've done is actually put one of the exhibits
from the gallery, on the move, lit and everything,
so that people can see it, I'll leave
the door open as I am driving around,
THAT is PR, <span tts:color=lime0 I'm good,
I was with Stephen Wiltshire, the artist famous
for creating detailed drawings from memory,
So which bit of New York do you think
you're going to put behind the car?
I'm going to
put the Brooklyn Bridge,
Brooklyn Bridge, OK,
Out on the streets, the PR machine
had adopted a more personal approach,
People of Middlesbrough,
Tomorrow morning is your opportunity to soak
up some art, Madame, in the black tracksuit,
Sir, in the white tracksuit
top, you could visit Mima,
You, young man, in the grey
black tracksuit trousers,
You sir, in the blue tracksuit top,
Tomorrow morning, nine o'clock at
Mima,
Art is for the masses,
art is for you sir,
In the black tracksuit trousers and you
young man in the blue tracksuit trousers,
There is a festival of art
available for you,
Back at the gallery it was all go,
Each of us had chosen what he
thought was the
best-looking car of all time,
And Jeremy and I were
busy installing them,
Richard had gone for his
own, Series 1 Land Rover,
Jeremy for a Ferrari 275 GTS,
No, it is absolutely terrific,
I bet if you turn the radio on it'll just be
the beginning of The Italian Job, That music,
And I'd gone for a
Lamborghini Countach,
How long have you talked about the
Lamborghini Countach for on the audio tape?
Please tell me it's no
more than two seconds,
A few minutes,
It's a very important car,
So, this idea that...
seriously James...
Yes, but you're only thinking in
terms of numbers of people coming
<span tts:color=cyan0 through, which I know is an honourable
ambition...
Yes, but they have to come to a
gallery and experience some art,
OK, what's this James? This is how I want
to see the people of Middlesbrough, OK,
On your left, there's a Lamborghini Countach,
that's a Ferrari 275 GTS and there's a Land-Rover,
In here,
we've actually got some art,
That's the speed
I want them to be doing,
If they saunter, if they're standing there,
saying, Oh, look at the wire wheels and the seats...
The log jam,
There was, however, a more immediate
problem, Oh, hang on a minute,
<span tts:color=yellow0
Hang on, Is it too wide?
Well, yeah, We cannot not have it,
<span tts:color=yellow0 Can't it just be there?
Eventually, the Countach was
bought in on a special giant thing,
And with that done,
we went to check on Stephen,
So that's four hours, And it's gone from a blank
piece of paper to that James, in four hours,
<span tts:color=cyan0 That's extremely good,
How many times have you been to this place,
Twice, in the Brooklyn Heights,
So you remember the detail on this bridge, just from
standing here two times?
That car is astonishing,
<span tts:color=yellow0 I know, You're pedantic on these things,
That is really accurate,
Darkness fell but still
Hammond's PR onslaught rumbled on,
We've stuffed the Mima
gallery full of things
that people want to go and see,
Obviously, it's automotive themed...
And long into the night, James and I were
arguing about where the art car should go,
So what, you want to position it to draw
people's attention to the bit you crashed?
<span tts:color=yellow0
Well, yes, No, I disagree,
OK, it needs to be...
Leave it like that, Please
go, get on with your next job,
I'm very happy, Leave it there,
Show day, And amazingly, our
exhibition was looking rather good,
We had installed many thought-provoking
pieces including, Stig World,
A video installation where visitors get a
glimpse of what goes on inside his helmet,
We also had our ground-breaking
masterpiece called, What's Europcar
Going To Say About This?,
and obviously Our BMW art car,
We knew that all of this would bring in the
multitudes and prove that motoring is the way forward
for the nation's art galleries, so we went on
to the roof for our first glimpse of the queues,
We'll be able to look at
the crowd from over here,
Are you ready, steady...
It's not that big, is it?
It was a disaster,
And the news from the outlying
car-parks was even worse,
It was like a scene from Omega Man,
It's now 10 to 10, As you can see,
we've been open for 15 minutes,
And there is just...
There, officially now,
the people looking after
the exhibits, outnumbering the
number of people looking at it,
My carefully-prepared personal
lectures were a complete waste of time,
For me, the artist has managed
to avoid any kind of branding,
It's just simply pure...
To hit our targets we needed 800 visitors
an hour but it just wasn't happening,
I am just doing a
rough head count here,
<span tts:color=yellow0
That's about... It's not a lot,
Around 75 people, tops,
By midday the numbers had picked up a bit but
instead of following the prescribed route through
the gallery, everyone was all over the
place thanks to James' useless audio guide,
'And then walking through the white
door, we arrive at the upstairs gallery,'
'Actually, that's not quite right,'
'Into the next room,
The door of which should be open,'
HIGH-PITCHED ALARM BLARES
'Bloody Nora,'
'Yeah, but I can't do it because people keep
ringing me up and asking me if I've done it yet,'
'I can't even turn it off,'
Worse still, Hammond had forgotten
to do his homework on the exhibits,
That's a Ferrari 275 GTS,
As you can see, the lines are...
It's lovely,
<span tts:color=lime0 Nice colour,
Yes, it is a lovely colour, yes, it is,
We called an emergency meeting,
OK, right, what are we
doing, what are we doing?
Don't skid away, let's just relax,
Please... <span tts:color=yellow0 What is going to
work about it? This is a catastrophe, James,
<span tts:color=cyan0 It's not a catastrophe...
Plainly, Hammond's
PR had been rubbish,
So, to bring in the crowds
we needed to find one,
And we did,
FOOTBALL FANS CHANT
At half-time, we would
make a hearts and minds
appeal for the Middlesbrough fans
to come to our show after the match,
Sadly, though, we put Captain
Geordie in charge of our outfits,
BOOING AND WHISTLING
Is this not...?
Give us a minute,
CHEERING
People of the Northeast,
We apologise for
that terrible mistake,
We are here to ask... Please, we have
an art exhibition at the Mima Gallery,
we need your support,
we have Ferraris, Lamborghinis,
we have Richard
Hammond's Land Rover,
Er, anything else?
No, Oh, there's one thing,
Nottingham, You can't come,
The away fans responded with
good grace,
# You fat bastard, you fat bastard
you fat bastard... #
You fat bastard!
Amazingly, though, our plan worked,
In you come,
If you start shuffling
through that way,
Soon the place was packed, which meant
I could finally unveil our centrepiece,
Without a doubt, the highlight,
the highlight of the show so far,
How much do you have to
hate somebody
to sit down with a piece of
cloth and then do that to him?
Among the crowd was a learned art scholar who
could see James' sculpture for what it was,
<span
tts:color=lime0 Yeah, Nothing to see, Nothing to see,
The crowds, though, meant we had a
new problem with a James' audio guide,
Not only was it still getting everybody lost but
as I'd feared it was also extremely long-winded,
'And latterly, to
5,2 litres, an expansion'
'that was accompanied by the
fitment of a new cylinder head... '
PHONE RINGS <span
tts:color=cyan0 'Hello,'
This meant the visitors weren't
moving through the gallery fast enough,
Have you been listening to the audio guide?
How is it?
Pretty boring,
With bottlenecks springing up everywhere
there was no way we'd get the numbers through,
So I was forced to shorten
my personal lectures a bit,
Right, everybody, there's only one
interesting thing in here
and it's that painting there of the
Bentley, Good, you've seen it, off we go,
There we are, that's
a BMW, we've done it,
In here's a Formula One car
with some paint on it, lovely,
Right, out, Out,
Out, you, you, off you go,
<span tts:color=yellow0 James, however, simply didn't
get the idea of this at all, Does he know?
Does a cat know it's a cat?
Does a dog know when its old,
What does he actually know?
What are you doing
with them up there?
Well, I'll tell you
exactly what's happening,
Everybody's getting into a room where
James May is talking and they're stuck,
This called for drastic measures,
So
in machine terms he's extremely bright but he's inanimate,
Does he have any feelings? Can we transfer
our own feelings on to the crash-test dummy?
Sorry,
Rodin's Thinker, He's sort of naked,
The point of
art is, you have to interact with it, You don't just look at it,
What's that stink?
Sorry about that, it's
unfortunate, but...
OK, if you'd like to move to the exits
now, tremendous, thank you for leaving here,
Sorry about the smell, I've
no idea how that happened,
Soon the crowds were moving along at a fair old
pace, which meant there wasn't much more we could do,
<span tts:color=yellow0 We've got the best
exhibits that we could have got, Yep,
We've done the best
PR that we can do,
Oh yeah,
It's now time for us to bail out
and let the numbers roll in,
With that, Back to the studio,
I finally got to say that,
APPLAUSE
OK,
I have the figures here, remember...
Remember, we had to beat 30,000,
Yes, so... <span tts:color=yellow0 And
what we actually managed was 50,000,
Yes, yes,
No, no, 15,
15,000,
Oh,
so, a half of what we needed then,
Yeah, we were halfway there,
But, this is still an all-time
record for the Mima Gallery,
Yes, That is brilliant, <span tts:color=yellow0
We did it,
We sort of did it, We did something,
Cars are the future of art,
They are and that is a bombshell
and that means we can end,
Now, we're back on December 27th with an elongated
special in which we drive across South America,
That is quite something,
But until then,
Have a very, very happy Christmas,
Take care, Good night,
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd