Tonight,
the stupidest car in the world.
A Vauxhall you might actually like.
And who has won what in
the Top Gear awards ceremony?
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Hello everybody!
Welcome, and a happy new year.
Happy new year to everybody.
Now, like many of you here, I suffer from
insomnia. I've tried everything over the years.
I've tried eating lettuce, counting
sheep, I even resorted last night
to James May's new talking book. LAUGHTER
That didn't work either.
Now, Richard Hammond seems to have
accidentally uncovered
what might be a cure.
This is a Lexus.
It's called the RX 450h,
and it's everything you'd expect
from what Alan Partridge called
the Japanese Mercedes.
It's quiet, it's well-made, it's got a
lentil matic hybrid engine, all very clever.
All things you'd expect from a car company
that has won many awards over the years.
Neatest panel gap consistency in
the executive saloon sector award.
And the coveted, that's a nice paint
finish award. Three years running.
I think you're getting the picture.
All Lexuses are beautifully made
and impeccably engineered to achieve
unmatched levels of dullness.
So when they announced recently,
"We've made a sports car,"
oh, how we laughed in the office!
Right up until the moment we saw it.
Yeah... Egg on face.
Foot in mouth. Humble pie,
for breakfast, lunch and dinner.
It's called the LFA.
Despite being a Lexus, it
doesn't have many Lexussy features.
There's no eat your greens
hybrid hiding under the bonnet.
There's no golf clubs hiding in
the boot. It's even got a spoiler.
It's the real deal.
And if you're still not convinced
that this thing is a supercar,
then let me give you
some nerdy-licious numbers.
552 horse power.
Same as the Gallardo.
0 to 60, 3.7 seconds.
Same as a Ferrari 599.
Top speed, 202 mph. That's
faster than an Aston Martin DBS.
OK, I think what I need to do here
is just find out how that works.
Stop.
Sport.
Ooh, yeah!
That I like.
ENGINE REVS
And go!
Woah... that's... explosive!
It's immediate.
There's no waiting for a second.
It is just stop, wham, going!
150.
170.
That's really quite a fast car.
Now, this being a Lexus, you might
expected to be not just a supercar,
but a supercar full of
immense attention to detail.
You'd be right.
4.8 litre V10, and yet somehow the
Lexus boffins have managed to make it
only the size of a V8, and as light
as a V6.
But that's not the most
amazing thing about it.
No, the most amazing
thing is the way it revs.
The engine is so lively,
they've had to fit this computer
game style virtual rev counter.
Because a normal analogue rev counter
can't keep pace
with how quickly
this thing gains and loses revs.
And then there's the beautifully
nerdy flappy paddle gear change.
The paddle to change up is lighter to
use than the paddle to change down.
Just so you know you're
going in the right direction.
HE LAUGHS
Amazing stuff from a company that
has never built a supercar before.
Which is why they took their
sweet time over this one.
Nine years in fact.
At first, the body
was made of aluminium.
Then, after years of work,
it was deemed too heavy,
so it was scrapped and they began
all over again, using carbon fibre.
Lightness was an obsession.
The steering wheel, for example,
is also made of carbon fibre.
The pedals are milled from a single
piece of aluminium.
And even the complex Lexus
stereo has been a on the Atkins.
Geekiness is everywhere here.
These mirrors are specially
shaped so they
funnel air
into these air intakes.
The designers were so obsessed with
good handling,
that even the water bottle for the
windscreen washers
is buried somewhere deep down there,
next to the petrol tank, to try and
keep as much of the weight as low as
possible and inside the wheelbase.
Just like an F1 car.
Don't be fooled by this gap.
That's not shoddy build quality,
that's a specially designed intake.
So, it's definitely a Lexus, and it
definitely looks like a supercar.
The question is,
does it feel like one?
It's lively...
TYRES SCREECH
The brakes are ferocious. After caning it
around this track, no sign of getting tired.
There's an initial lead from the
front end. It's quite a soft feeling.
The thing just wallows in,
and you can give it a boot-full with
the rear end.
In!
HE LAUGHS
TYRES SCREECH
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
Get it wrong and it takes absolutely
no prisoners. It just spits you out.
Get it right though, and you'll be
laughing.
Oh, yes! There you go!
HE LAUGHS
There we are. What a turn-up
from the librarian of the car world.
Which brings me to the
obvious question...
Would one buy one?
That all depends how much it costs.
L50,000, oh, yes!
L100,000, yeah. L150,000? Well, it's
expensive, but it'll be exclusive.
As it happens, the LFA
doesn't cost L150,000. No.
The LFA costs L340,000.
That's 130,000 more
than a Ferrari 599.
For a car
that's no faster than a 599.
And you know what?
Even at that price,
Lexus won't make
any money on each one they sell.
What this car is,
is an engineer's wet dream.
It's a brilliant creation,
and praise the Lord it exists.
But price wise,
it's on a different planet.
And there's another slight issue.
At the end of the day, and here
it is, the actual end of the day,
yes, I'm in the Lexus. Oh, God.
I can never get away from that.
"Will the owner of a
L340,000 LEXUS move it?"
That's me. Sorry.
It just doesn't...
It's a Lexus. It just is.
APPLAUSE
I'm baffled. I'm more baffled than
I've ever been.
Hammond, does this car,
does it do 1158 mph?
Yes. Really? No. So, it isn't sixtimes faster than a Nissan GTR?
No. But it costs six times more?
Yeah, it does. Why? Well, it's made
of exotic materials.
It needs to be!
It needs to be made out of myrrh!
Is this windscreen wipermade out of saffron? No.
But there's a lot of carbon fibre.
Hammond, my bog seat at homeis made out of carbon fibre.
It didn't cost 340,000 quid.
Honestly, I just don't
understand this car.
Hopefully, our tame racing driver
will be able to make sense of it.
Some say
that he has to take his shoes off
with an Allen key.
And that his new year's resolution
is to eat fewer mice.
All we know is,
he's called The Stig.
And he's off!
It's wet out there, yet again.
Thank you, Copenhagen!
Let's see how the confusing and
expensive Lexus copes in these conditions.
Here he comes...
Look at that, through the first
corner. Rocking up a bit there.
A little bit of
over steer on the way out.
CHAS AND DAVE SONG PLAYS
Stig, still enjoying a cockney
knees-up,
which is strange because
his knees are on his face.
There's Chicago, a
little bit more over steer.
How is it going to cope
on a moist hammerhead?
Will that
clever weight distribution help?
Running a bit wide, a bit slithery.
You can hear he's having to use the throttle
very gingerly as he gets out of there.
Right, now he can
really mash his paw down.
This thing sounds like
an old F1 car.
Let's hope it's not using know-how from
the Toyota team, or it'll be rubbish.
Two corners left, spearing
into the second to last one.
Just a flash of corrective lock.
Gambon, that's clean.
And across the line.
Do you have the time? I do.
It did it in 1:22.8,
which puts it there.
But critically, I've got to write
on there that it's wet, very wet.
That's the fastest wet lapwe've ever had. By a long way.
That next one is Lambo Gallardo.
The Gallardo, there. Look at that!
Three seconds a lap faster
for three times the price!
It's a bargain!
At the beginning of every year,
the BBC gives us a big lump of money
and tells us to go away
and make 14 programmes.
What we do is we divide that
lump of money by 14,
and that gives us
the budget for every show.
It's simple!
Unfortunately, and I don't
know how this happened, we've
made a complete Horlicks of it.
Which meant that when we got
to make this show, we had,
and I'm not joking, I'm not making
this up, almost no money at all.
No. And you didn't actually thehelp with your Lexus film? Why?
It had a space ship in it. It wasn't actually there
when I filmed it. Was it?
So, it was added? Yeah. And that's
cheaper than just using
a real space ship.
I don't think it is.
That stuff costs a bloody fortune.
We know that now the bill has come
in. I'm sorry, I got carried away.
Listen, stop bickering you two.
We now have to do the news and that's impossible,
because it's not the week you think it is.
It's actually December, December 9th.
It really is. We had the studiobooked for today,
and we've had to use it even
though we know you're in 2010.
This fly flying around here has
actually died by the time you watch this.
The real problem is obviously, between now and when
you're watching this, anything could have happened.
Somebody could have invented a car
that I don't know, runs on jelly.
We might have declared
war with France...
HE LAUGHS
Instead of the news, what we're
going to do, we're going to take
a look ahead to some cars
that are coming out
this year. This year. This year. Yes!
Lots of them, in fact. There's the new Jaguar
XJ, we're very much looking forward to that.
The Aston Martin 177,
the million-pound Aston.
But the one that really caught my
eye is this, it's the Honda CR-V,
and I think you'll agree it
looks absolutely fantastic.
However, I then read the bumpf.
It has a 1.5 litre engine, and a
boot full of lithium ion batteries.
That's not a bloody hybrid, is it?
Yes. You see what they've done here,
this is organic tofu,
dressed up as
a juicy steak. But don't be fooled.
Don't be fooled, people. James?
A car I'm really looking forward
to is the new Saab 95, here it is.
Unless of course Saab wentbust in the last two weeks... Which is a real possibility!
Seriously, James, really...
Do this two ways, we will edit it. Yeah. Cover yourself.
A car I'm really looking forward to
is the new Saab 95. There it is.
A car I was looking forward to was
the new Saab 95.
LAUGHTER
That's what it was going to look
like. They said... They say...
What? They said. Oh, yes. They say,
or said, that it's
based on a jet fighter,
or was, but it isn't wasn't.
LAUGHTER
It's actually based on a Vauxhall.
You can or could get three engines,
maybe you could get three engines.
The best of which
was or is a 2.8 litre V6.
That will start at about L25,000.
It looks great.
James, why haven't you got a Saab?Because they've gone bust.
But if they haven't, then it is a very good
question because I do actually quite like a Saab.
They are a little bit alternative
and tend to be driven by quite
interesting people. That's
why he got hasn't got one then!
HE LAUGHS
Here's a car I'm looking forward to.
911 Turbo Cabriolet.
What?! Hammond, sorry!
It's twin turbos, seven speed double
clutch gearbox, flappy paddles.
I want one.
How old are you?
39. And 361 days.
Technically, yeah.
You know what that means, don't you?
The mid-life crisis is arriving.
Soon you'll be growing your hair,
whitening your teeth...
Have you bought a
Harley-Davidson recently?
Yes. Have you? All right, it's
happening! I agree!
I quite like the look of this.
This is the Citroen DS3.
That's going to be about L12,000.
It's sort of the size of a Mini.
Can I tell you the biggest problem
with this car?
When we buy cars - and we all do
this whether we like it or not -
we tend to think most of all about
what it will be worth
when we come to sell it, which is
perfectly reasonable.
The reason why we don't buy orange
and lime green cars is you think,
I won't be able to sell it in a
couple of years,
I'll get the grey one. I think
that's what will happen with this
because you will look at it and go,
I really like this, but what if
nobody else does and I won't be able
to sell it.
Or what if it's as out of date as
Roger Moore's safari suit
when he was James Bond? That's a
shame because right now it looks great.
It looks fantastic. I think that's one of the
best-looking cars that will be coming out next year.
No, you got it... No, this year.
This BLEEP year! Right, stop!Oh, God!
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
Oh, God!
Let's move, on because this is another car I'm really looking forward to. It's this
- 911 GT3RS.
Are you only
looking forward to 911s?
I am having a mid-life crisis, it's
my right. I think that's a great car.
Lighter, faster. I think it wouldhave been OK when you were in your30s, Hammond.
I think it's bright and fun and people
will look at it and think I'm young in it.
It's just a Beetle. It was designed
by Hitler and it's a Beetle.
Yes, it was.
It wasn't.
Was.
Who says it was?
Was it designed by Hitler?Yes.
You remember, you were here.
At least I'm looking forward
to something this year.
You're just saying everything
is going to be terrible.
Not everything.
One car has caught my eye.
Ferrari 458.
This is the replacement for the 430.
Hmmm. What do you mean - hmmm?
I already think the Ferrari F430 is
the best car in the world.
It makes my little fizzy...
My rude thing...
I guarantee this is going to
be a lot better than a 430.
If that's true it could explode.
Does anybody else suddenly feel sick?
Yes. I don't want to see your
fizzy rude penis blowing up...
No, no, arrrgh! Let's just move on!
I don't want to know!
The fact of the matter is this. This has got a lot
more tech than a 430. It's a lot lighter than a 430.
I think the 430 has
about 480 horsepower.
This has 562.
The thing I love about it most of
all is that it's the first Ferrari
since 1975 that actually looks
properly pretty. I'm just
completely bowled over by it.
Actually, we probably won't be
allowed to drive Ferraris because
a couple of weeks ago,
before Christmas...
Nice one. A big meetingin Copenhagen and many,many things were resolved there.
One of them - I'm pretty certain - will be
that we have to get out of our cars more often.
And that brings us
on to something we have over here.
In this plastic suitcase
is a folding the allegedly assisted
bicycle. It's called the Gocycle.
I think you'll find
it's called the Go Cycle.
Not the Gocycle, you idiot. That
says Gocycle.
Never mind. It costs L1200
and, as you can see, it is...
Oh.
I thought it was a folding bicycle. It's
a bloody bag full of bicycle components.
Have I got to build it? Would you
like me to give you a hand with it?
That's the most terrifying thing
Jeremy Clarkson can say to anyone.
I wonder if maybe you
two should go away.
Good idea, because this is not
the only post Copenhagen solution.
Hammond, what have you got here?I have this.
What it is is a skateboard for people
who can't be bothered to skateboard.
I'll get it all started up because
it is electrically powered.
This device controls your speed.
Why don't you give that
to me and I'll control it.
No, that's the most terrifying
thing you can possibly say.
Are you really going to ride that?Yes, I am.
Apparently this has a curve system.
Though how something can have
regenerative braking
when I can't see how the brakes
work I don't know - but it works!
This is much better.
It was designed by a man who wanted something
that would combine his love of cross-country skiing
and his love of cycling, and
then converted to run on batteries,
by someone who didn't
like either of those things.
It is quite pricey, L1,600, around about the
same as in 19995 Series BMW, but it is quite fast.
Top speed is 15mph.
Yeah, mine is faster.
I promise you this is quicker.
Race. Race?! Come on.
Anyone want to see a race? Yeah!
Back to here, lap of the studio.
3, 2, 1- go. I've got
wheelspin, a lot of wheelspin.
Come on, you stupid thing!I'm a 40-year-old man
taking up skateboarding.
I've got grip, I've got grip!
I've hit the wall!
James, are you still working on that
thing? Yes. Want to go on this?
No. It's great once you'vegot the hang of it. No.
Suit yourself.
I'm a bit bored with this.
I'm going to go and introduced
Jeremy's film on the BMW X6.
Normally he would go and drive it in a
sewer or blow it up or something like that.
Unfortunately, Richard Hammond
spent most of what we have left
on his stupid... ARGH!
Sorry.
Unfortunately, Richard Hammond, who
has just broken our Christmas tree,
spent most of what we had left
on his stupid Lexus film.
Our instructions to Jeremy were very
specific. Keep it cheap and simple.
Right. One simple film coming up.
The X6 is BMW's attempt
to make a car which looks,
and goes, like a coupe,
but has a tall driving position
and a bit of off-road ability.
They call it
a Sports Activity Vehicle.
It's available with a choice of two
petrol engines, both of which
will attract the new L950
showroom tax...
And two diesels which won't.
In the cabin,
there is space for four.
But those in the back will be awfully
cramped due to the sloping roof line.
Inside it's all typical BMW,
except for this rather clever split
opening glove box lid.
It works well here.
But what if
you're the wrong way up?
To find out I went to Sydney,
which is in Australia.
Obviously everything here is upside-down and yet
it still works beautifully. That is impressive.
So...
How does the X6 drive?
In many ways, it's quite annoying.
You can't see out of the back very
well and it's got the iDrive system
which can only be operated
if you are 14.
No.
I don't know what any of that means.
Satellite navigation. You are coming up to a
complicated junction, trying to see which way it is.
You think it's a bit chilly, I'll just ease
the temperature up and the screen has gone!
I don't know which way to
go because...
Why are you telling me that?!
Then there's the gear lever.
It's on back-to-front cos if you
want to change down you push it away.
If you want to change up
you pull it towards you.
There's no point resorting to the paddles on
the steering wheel as unlike in a normal car,
where one change is down and one change
is up, in this they both do the same thing.
And what was the boss of BMW doing when
all the clowns in the laptop department
were coming up with this rubbish?
I can only assume she was
in a motel with a Swiss spy.
That would be preposterous!
Still, for a big, tall
car it's not bad in bends.
Unfortunately, to make it not bad,
they have had to put quite a lot
of beef and granite
in the suspension.
In Britain that makes it
really quite uncomfortable.
But what about countries
where the roads are smooth?
To find out, I went to Spain.
No, it's uncomfortable here as well.
The fact is this - it would be more
comfortable if it weren't so tall.
There's a similar problem
with the performance.
Yes, the twin-turbo three litre
diesel that I've got in this
particular model will get me from 0
- 60 in seven seconds, and that's not bad.
But how much faster and how much
more economical would it have been
if the body wasn't so enormous?
You'd imagine that the advantages
of that big, high riding body would
become clear in the countryside.
But there's no low-range gearbox,
there's no ride-high control and
there's no locking differentials.
It doesn't take long for those
omissions to have an effect.
You see,
that really says a lot, doesn't it?
The only way round this
is to get out and complete
your journey on foot.
That's the handbrake on and in park.
Help!
I'm still going down the hill.
Maybe it can handle snow
a bit better.
To find out I went to the
highest ski resort in the Alps.
No.
It can't.
So it's too focused on being a
road car to be any good off-road.
And it's too focused
on being tall and heavy
to be any good on the road either.
And that, I'm afraid,
is far from the end of the story.
You see, the X6 was conceived at a time when we
all thought the banks knew what they were doing.
But it went on sale moments after
we discovered they didn't.
And, I'm sorry, but in a recession a
car like this just looks ridiculous.
To explain what I'm on about
I went in search of a metaphor.
And, inevitably,
that led me to Hong Kong.
You see that skyscraper,
the one Batman jumped off?
It's not particularly beautiful,
it's not particularly useful.
It was built by a world for a world
that doesn't really exist any more.
Remind you of anything?
To sum up, the Range Rover
is a much better all-rounder.
Which is why we use them
as camera tracking cars.
The X6 is too cramped, too complicated
and, with prices starting at L42,000,
too expensive as well!
Then you're going to need at least L1,500 a
year to run it, not including depreciation.
And I think I'd rather spend that
sort of money on a Caribbean holiday.
To find out, I went to Barbados.
I think a bit more research.
No. This is definitely better -
definitely.
APPLAUSE
Thank you very much.
I pride myself on my thoroughness.
What? Excuse me.
What?You are an apocalyptic dingleberry.
Why? You went to the Alps. Yes.
You went to Spain. Yes.
You went to Australia to see
if the glove box works. Yes.
You went to Barbados. Yes. You went to...
Hong Kong. That was just for astupid metaphor. Yes, I did do that.
You're a bigger idiot
than Richard Hammond.
You know what it means? What? What
it meant was there was virtually
no money left for my film,
which you can see later.
I promise I didn't do
it deliberately. Really?!
It's now time to put a star
in our reasonably priced car.
Now, because of the budget issues this
week, we did have a bit of a problem.
Tom Cruise, for example,
was going to charge us L150.
Bonio out of U2 wanted
175 quid to come over here.
So, would you please welcome
a former tramp? Seasick Steve.
APPLAUSE
Sorry about this. How are you? Have a seat.
We have an accident every year and there it is.
I should explain to those of you who
are thinking and the tramp is who?
This guy is a musical sensation. I mean Brit
nominee, when was it, last year? Glastonbury.
My wife queued up for five daysto come and see that show you did. I'm sorry.
You have become this
amazing sensation.
The instruments you play aren't
exactly conventional instruments.
I mean, your guitar, for example.
I don't play the guitar but I know
they have six strings. Yours doesn't.
I've got some that have got one string but that's
just a plank of wood with a string nailed on it.
That's called a diddlybo.
I've got this other guitar that's got three strings
that I got from a friend of mine in Mississippi.
He found it at a junk store.
I brought it home and my wife looked at that
guitar and goes, "That's going to make you famous. "
And it has! Because, one day, a little known
broadcasting organisation called the BBC
called up and said, "Could you
come on the Jools Holland Show?"
I didn't even know
what Jools Holland was.
Just so that people can understand
the noise that Steve can make out of
this three-string guitar,
just have a listen to this.
# The dog house
Dog house
# Sing the dog house
# Sing the dog house... #
I had to just do that so you could just hear
that this... Where does that voice come from?
Obviously your mouth.
Drinking? Drinking.
So your first hit album, I should
say, it was called
I Started Out With Nothing And
I've Still Got Most Of It Left.
Yes. Which I think is the best
album title literally of all time.
The new one's called...?A Man From Another Time.
Again, pretty apt. We're going to
get on to this name - Seasick Steve.
Forgive me for asking. You must have
been asked a million times but why?
I just get sick on boats.
Like real sick. I don't go out
on the boats too much.
I went on a ferry boat from Norway to
Denmark and threw up all night long.
The next morning, someone thought
it was funny. You're Seasick Steve!
And that stuck? Yeah, sort of.
You may be Seasick Steve but you can't be Carsick
Steve because what you probably don't realise,
we haven't got to this bit,
we've got a serious car man here.
How many cars have you ownedover the years? I try to count. I know it's in the hundreds.
In America, cars are real cheap.
You can buy a late '30s,
early '40s car for 50 bucks.
So I'd buy it for 50 and drive it
for two or three weeks until it died
and leave it on the end of the road
and then go and get another one.
They were all over.
What was the favourite
from this list of hundreds?
My favourite truly is a car I have
right now which I've had for a while.
It's a '51 Chevy station wagon.
It's just a complete beat-up car butit runs good. Where is that now?
It's actually over here. I've got
it over here now. You keep it in theUK? Yeah, I've got it over here.
I've got that and a tractor. You've
got to do a bit of farming then?
I don't care about the farming
part but I like ploughing.
So, presumably, I was listening
to a comedian on the radio the other
day talking about the importance
and reliability of getting to gigs.
Yeah. You don't use the Chevy.
Because presumably it's, "I'm sorry,
"Seasick Steve can't appear tonight
because his Chevy's broken down. "
I've got one of those big Mercedes
vans, like a big white one.
It's got like a wood burning
stove and fishing gear.
It's got like a log cabin inside.
It's real nice.
There's all these lines of those big tour
buses and then my old beat-up van in the middle.
Seasick Steve's arrived.
They saw me coming a long way away.
So, you've not called
the eco-bug then? What's that?
It was a thing in Copenhagen.
You've got to have a Toyota Prius
now - a hybrid. No, thanks.
My boy told me I could drive
my '51 Chevy the rest of my life,
and all the life I've had before,
and not make as much pollution as
one of them new cars costs to make.
I'll stick with the '51 Chevy,
thank you. Yes, good man.
That's the ticket.
One of the things I noticed,
looking back through the list of the hundreds of cars
you've owned, there's MGs, S-type Jag, E-type Jag.
You do like British cars. Yeah.
Why? I like the way...
Not all of them but I like the way they smell inside them old ones
- the leather and everything.
What is a Morris Minor doing in
there? That is Britain's Beetle.
I was up in Liverpool playing
up there a few years back.
I met this guy who had, I think a '55 split window. An early one.
He asked me if I wanted to buy it. I said, yeah. Punch him, punch him!
My friend, he has Morris Minors.
He thought it would be real funny to
make me a guitar out of Morris Minors.
Seriously?These are two Morris Minor hubcaps.
That's the best use I've ever seen for anything
on a Morris Minor. Go on, play it! Let's hear it.
So, now you can have something goodto say about a Morris Minor. Yeah.
Maybe not.
Are you going to give us a tune?
No, I'm not going to give you a
tune, I'm going to make a noise.
Morris Minor.
I'm startled. A Morris Minor noise.
That's the best use
of a Morris Minor ever.
So, OK, the car man.
You came down here and drove possibly the
most modern car you've ever driven then.
My biggest problem is the shifter'son the wrong side. Correct side.
I kept rolling the window down.
But it is. I have to say that Lacetti
is getting a bit knackered now.
I didn't help at all. I apologise. No, we're thinking of gettinga new car for the next series.
You would be the last person
ever to go on the board.
I'm probably be the last
person on the board, too.
Like a double whammy!Who'd like to see Seasick's lap?
Yes!
Let's have a look how it went.
I'm embarrassed now.
Now, I'm trying to remember
all the things Stig told me.
I can hardly remember...
What day is it actually?
I've no idea. That is a beard in a car and that it
is tidy line cutting the corner.
That's OK. A bit damp.
A lot of under steer there.
You can make a lot of noise but you ain't
going very fast when you make the noise.
That's true.
We've got more understeer here. Yes.
Quite a lot through there.
That's slowing you down a bit.
The radio came on.
I don't want to hear no radio.
I'm busy racing, dude.
Dipping nicely into Hammerhead.
This looks like a good line. Yes,
looking very tidy on the way in.
And on the way out?
Very nice.
This is embarrassing. No, it isn't. This gear change was.
That's the worst.
This is the most fun I've probably ever had in my
whole life and that's probably kind of pathetic.
Let's have a look through here. Let's
see if you've got to any gentleman's...
This car...
is amazing.
Fast - that is quick.
Coming into the
second to last corner.
Don't go on the grass, it's too wet.
You're on the grass a bit there.
Go, go, go! And around Gander.
A little bit slow on that one.
Across the line, everybody.
Very well done!
Very well done. Oh, boy!
You care, don't you?
I really care. I know I let down theside but you got to give it a shot. You gave it a shot.
I tried to get points for being a
little older but they didn't go for it.
I'd love to cheat here and give you a fast
time but unfortunately it was a slow one.
I know that. It wasn't a slow one.
What it was was, ready?
One minute and, bearing
in mind it was moist, 51.8.
Which means you go there.
You're faster than Tom Jones. That's enough. I'll take that.
That's good enough for me.
And he was in the dry.
You're faster than Helen Mirren...
Don't rub it in no more.
That's kind of it. Steve,
this has been an absolute joy.
A 100% pleasure for me. 100%.
Ladies and gentlemen, Seasick Steve. Thank you very much.
Thank you so much. Great music.
Right. It is now time
for me to present my film.
And, for reasons that I am sure
by now are abundantly clear,
it's about a medium-sized
Vauxhall and a nice old lady.
Right, here we go.
A lengthy yet hopefully interesting
and value-for-money film
about a Vauxhall.
If you're a proper car bore, you will
know that anything wearing the VXR badge,
I have one here
on the steering wheel,
is part of Vauxhall's
Turbo Nutter ASBO range.
And so it turns out.
The engine, for example,
is a turbo-charged 2.8 litre V6.
Which produces
a meaty 321 horse power.
That's a few horse power short of
our old track favourite, the VXR8,
but, nevertheless, this executive-style
car is good for 60 in under 6 seconds.
If it didn't have
the hand of nannying,
an electronic speed limiter,
it would do 170 miles an hour.
It does shift, this thing.
And the performance modifications
don't stop with the engine.
321 horse power is asking
a lot of front-wheel drive.
This version has four-wheel drive
to keep everything nice and calm
and civilised and under control.
It also has a very clever
front suspension,
very similar to the one
used on the Focus RS,
which, as we know, is very good.
Also, the suspension has been lowered by 10mm
and you can choose from different driver settings.
At the moment I'm in normal mode,
which is the one I like,
but if I press this button, "sport"
- now the suspension is firmed up a little bit.
Can I feel that? Yes.
But lots of cars
have a sport button.
The insignia, however, has
another one that goes up to 11.
This one which is marked "VXR".
Press that and the
suspension gets even harder.
The throttle response is sharpened up a bit but,
most importantly, the instruments become red!
I mean, that's just fantastic.
It's a fire-breathing monster
with a spine of iron.
And the prize for all
this VXR-ishness?
Just over L30,000,
which, in Top Gear maths,
where we tend to round things up a bit,
makes it actually pretty good value.
Because the equivalent Audi S4
would be nearly L5,000 more.
And that's all you really
need to know about it.
But, obviously,
I have to keep going.
So I will, by explaining that the
insignia VXR is surprisingly restrained,
both to look at and to sit in.
It is, therefore,
the first de-chavved VXR.
The first fast Vauxhall that would know
which way round a baseball cap goes.
This is actually a very
civilised car. It's very quiet.
The ride is very good and yet, without the
VXR button on, it still goes like stink.
It's also very spacious and it has a big boot
- and much more equipment than a pricier Audi.
And now I really have
run out of things to say.
But rather than go
back to the studio,
I'm going to introduce you to
someone I've always wanted to meet.
A lady called Margaret Calvert.
And here she is. Hello, Margaret.
Hello, James.
You may never have heard
of Margaret but, believe me,
if you are a motorist in Britain, she's one
of the most important people in your life.
If it hadn't been for Margaret
and her mates,
I would now be going the wrong way or
possibly even having a terrible crash.
You see, Margaret, along with
her colleague Jock Kinneir,
is responsible for creating something special
that we take for granted every single day.
The road signs of Britain.
I think you've perhaps made me
more important than I really am.
Oh, I doubt it.
Margaret's work began in the 1950s,
when car ownership was booming
and the Government, alarmed at the clogged-up
roads, decided to build the first motorways.
However, existing road signs were totally
inadequate for the new, high-speed highways.
No one designed motorway signs before
because we hadn't had a motorway. Yes.
And the whole job of making that
system of signs clear to the car,
which was still a new thing for
most people... The driver, yes.
And at speeds that were still new...
That all fell to a man and his
former student from an art college.
They gave you the whole job. Absolutely.
We were both on a crash-course
learning curve
to come to grips with
designing road signs.
It wasn't a fashion thing.
We were designing for permanence.
We were designing for something that
wouldn't look dated in 5 or 10 years' time.
Margaret explained how
the colour system of our road signs
was carefully designed to make words
and numbers as clear as possible
at the high speeds motorway-borne
cars could then achieve.
And she and Jock horrified
the signposting establishment
by using upper
and lowercase letters,
instead of the accepted
block capitals.
And that's to do
with word recognition.
You read a shape, whereas if it's all
in capitals, it takes you longer to read.
So you don't have to read it in upper and lower.
You see the shape and you know what it says.
Exactly that. So your brain
fills in, you know, the middle bits.
Most people wouldn't realise how involved this is.
They'd think it's just lettering you stick on a sign.
Absolutely, yes. And it still works.
It's basically the same system.
Margaret's work didn't stop
at motorway signs
because she and Jock then went on to design just about
every other road sign you see in the Highway Code.
So you designed
a new type-face... Yes.
.. Which became known
as Transport. Yes.
And then you had to design the actual
pictures for your warning signs. Yes.
That's you, isn't it? That was
actually a very difficult one to do.
The important thing was to
make it look like an action.
That it would really alert you to the possibility
of two children walking across the road,
so hopefully you would try to
save lives by getting that right.
The previous sign had
a grammar-school boy
with a satchel
and the girl behind him.
And they weren't holding hands
or anything like that.
And I just thought that this
is a little bit more caring
and so I switched it round.
I based that, actually, on me.
I based it on
what I wore as a child.
So is that actually you?It is, actually, yes.
At this point, I was starting
to run out of intelligent questions.
What do you make of the car? Because
I can't quite make my mind up but...
They always have faces,
don't they? Yes.
And I think some kind of look very
shark-like, some look very aggressive.
It looks like a car that's
been designed by a committee.
And then I ran out of
intelligent things to say.
But would you agree with me that it
would look a bit sexier in glasses?
That's a very interesting...
I think you're quite unusual.
Back on the road, we inevitably came
across one of her most commonly-used signs.
The story I read about you
was that you did that sign
and then the joke emerged it was a man struggling
with an umbrella and that joke's been around for years.
And that annoyed you and you wished
you'd done it slightly differently?
Well, I would have put a shoulder
on it, just. And I'd... Huh?
Oh, what, you want me to draw it on?
Yes. No. Come on.
I'm not doing it. I'll do it.
But I want you to direct me. OK.
Right, think of drawing a spade.
As if you're drawing a spade, yeah?
What do you think?
Well, I think from here,
it's sort of, it's wrong.
Not only did she not like my drawing, she
didn't find my gear changes very good either.
That was a bit of a... Yes, sorry,
that wasn't very good, was it?
No, that wasn't a good gear. Let's try that again.
Yeah, do that. I was trying
to be clever. Oh, right.
Skipping the cogs, so we're
doubling down into second.
Oh, right, yes. Even then, it
was a little bit juddery. Now...
Yeah, a bit... Is that better?A bit better. Could be smoother.
Sorry.
I decided to speed up,
and that didn't work either.
Oh my gosh!
Margaret didn't like
this sort of driving.
And as we headed for home, plainly,
she decided to get her own back.
Big road sign. It is nice to thinkthat your legacy is spread all overthe country. Well, it is a legacy.
I suppose. And that's why I end up
sitting next to people like you.
Talking about road signs.
Did you put my seat heater onfor a joke? No, I didn't. Is it on?
Well done, mate. Good work.
Well done.
I have to say, when Margaret came on, it got
better, OK? The thing is though, I have a question.
She really designed all of the road signs of
Britain? Well, her and, what was it, four others?
Four or five people in total, yes.
Because I was thinking, if they decided
to change all the road signs now,
how many people would
this government employ?
A million. It would.
They'd want 5,000 people just to decide what
the little girl on the school sign looked like.
Oh yes, should she
have a burka, a turban?
And then that man in the "men at
work" sign is clearly a man... Yes!
And that's not right.
No. They'd rectify that.
In the modern "men at work" sign there wouldn't
be a man, just be a pile of unused gravel.
Just a queue of cars
stopped for no reason.
It's OK, we've filled the time now.
OK. Er, so, let's move on
to the Top Gear award ceremony!
Oh, yes. This is the biggie. Oh, yes!
It's a big day. It is a biggie. A big day in the calendar.
A big day for us all.
What are you doing? What... What? Just that.
It's an award ceremony, I'm wearing
a gold lame jacket. It's appropriate.
It's quite sudden, isn't it?
Erm, anyway.
First award is Injury of the Year.
And the nominations are - Richard in
our Headhammer Thrust i-Eagle, Geoff.
We're going to crash.
Ow, my chest!
Jeremy making paint-ball art.
Ready!
Ah!
And James on a gangplank in Bolivia.
It's like literally beingwith Livingstone... Yeah.
And...
Mm-mm! It was a good one.
A good moment there, mate.
Well done.
Both of us did cough blood.
I have the winner here. Injury of
the Year award and the winner is...
It's actually none of those.
Now, I should say
before I announce this,
that when we film a car on Top Gear, there is always
a light, OK, in the top corner of the windscreen.
Now, we've been doing this show for
years, so it would be impossible to forget
that that light is there and that it's very
sharp, unless, of course, you were a colossal anus.
East Midlands airport. You might have to...
What? The camera.
What have you done?
Ow! BLEEP It really hurts. Agh!
Well done, chaps.
Gosh. It's an honour.
It is an honour.
Thank you. Thank you.
Now, as always, we present an award
to the person who's driven around our track
fastest of all in the course of the year.
The fastest man around the Top Gear track, the
fastest celebrity in the reasonably-priced car,
from AC/DC, it's Brian Johnson!
Sadly, Brian is in Florida
at the moment
and none of us could be bothered to
go over there and give him his award.
But we did find a film crew who very
kindly volunteered to do it for us.
Thanks very much for this wonderful
honour and for this fabulous trophy.
You must have spent
a fortune on this!
My name's Brian, not "Brain".
And that's an ice hockey player
on top of there, look. Never mind.
This'll do me for now.
So have a great time at Christmas
and I'll see you soon, guys.
Thanks, everybody. Bye-bye.
Brain Johnson! Well, I'm sorry.
That's the worst thing we've everdone. It was cheap. It was cheap.
And now it's time to get serious, because
it's time for our Car of the Year award, OK.
This, of course, is an
extremely coveted award.
Manufacturers all over the world
will be watching with bated breath.
OK, the nominations
are the new Volkswagen Polo.
It's already won the slightly less
coveted European Car of the Year award.
And the Kia Ceed, for its pleasing equipment levels
and ground-breaking seven-year comprehensive warranty.
And the Suzuki Alto, for its willing engine
and its attractive price tag of just L7,495.
And the winner for being much,
much better than all of those,
is the Lamborghini Gallardo Balboni!
Yes. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. What a winner.
That's as it should be.
We were impressed with
its stripe, it's V10 engine,
its rear-wheel drive,
the savagery of its exhaust,
and its stripe.
No, seriously,
we think the Polo is tremendous, OK?
Beautifully made and so on.
And that's OK if you're an
accountant, but we're not.
What we look for in a car is, and I'm
loathed to use the word, it's an X factor.
Something you can't really
put your finger on.
And that's what we look for.
Yes. And the Lamborghini has something you can put your finger on
- a stripe.
We're moving on. There's a lot of people
tune in for this moment every year.
Which is clever because
we've never done it before.
It's the Forklift Truck Driver
of the Year award.
The nominations are...
This chap.
Here he is, look. You're all right, back up, you're
all right. Oh, no. Wait a minute, hang on. Ooh!
But the winner without a question
or shadow of doubt is this chap.
Yep, back up, careful, careful...
Ooh, bit quick.
No, ooh, that's not gone well.
Wow! I mean...
Unbelievable... Credit where it's due. A fine effort.
Well, it's appropriate we should now
move on to the Golden Cock award.
This of course, is awarded... Here it
is, Richard demonstrating for you now.
It's awarded to the member
of the Top Gear team who has,
in the course of making
the programme over the year,
been a complete clattering buttock.
Now, there were several cases behind the
scenes this year that we had to consider.
There was the time when James May, whilst
following the Range Rover camera car,
somehow managed to lose
sight of it for a moment
and then start following an
entirely different Range Rover.
And he failed to notice for an hour
that it didn't have a camera crew in it and
was in fact nothing to do with Top Gear at all.
Just to give you an idea of the
degree of James's idiocy there,
here's a picture of a normal
Range Rover. There it is, look.
And now here's a picture of
one of our filming Range Rovers.
There is a giveaway there.
But in the end, there really
could only be one winner.
You may remember the steam train
race we had earlier on in the year.
Well, four minutes before the train was due to leave,
that's four minutes before the race was due to begin,
we were presented with a Jaguar XK with
the keys in the ignition, engine running...
and the doors locked.
So, the Golden Cock has to go to that man who was
trusted to deliver that priceless car on that crucial day,
and left it with us
in that condition.
And that man was...
The Stig!
Yes. Where is he?
He's here.
Stig, the Golden Cock. Yes.
Oh, it's great.
He's touched. He's touched,
I can tell. I should point out,
Stig, that is a rolling award.
We have to have it back now to
give it to next year's winner.
So if I can have that... Ah!
No, you have to give it back so
it sits in our trophy cupboard.
Stig, give me the Golden Cock. Just... Stig,
give me the Gol... Give me the Gol... I need...
Stig, I need the, give me the Gol...
No, not that. Stig, give me the
Golden Cock. Stig, give me the Cock.
We've lost both Cocks.
Have you got his Cock?
Some of it. Yes. It's amazing.
You're joking, is thatall we have left of the Golden...
Oh, mate, it's weird.
He fights like a choirboy
but you can hear his jaws just snapping shut
in his helmet all the time. It's terrifying.
I've got some of it back anyway.
Well, well done, Hammond.
Anyway, that was the Golden Cock.
What I'm doing is I'm blathering. Yeah. You are.
How short can you make anhour-long programme? I don't know.
OK, seriously, honestly, because
James's film was so short,
we do actually have time
for one more award. Yes, we do.
And since this is 2010, we can give
an award to the car of the decade.
Now we are taking this quite seriously.
There are a lot of worthy contenders.
And we considered everything from the
Rolls-Royce Phantom to the new Mini.
Another car that makes our list of those
being considered, Pagani for the Zonda.
Yeah, we also considered,
did we not, the Range Rover TDV8,
simply for being all the car
you could ever possibly need.
And then the light bulb went on,
because we realised there could
actually only be one car
of what the Daily Mail will
undoubtedly call "the noughties".
It was a car that just
rewrote the rule book, really.
An amazing piece of engineering.
A genuine Concorde moment.
So, ladies and gentlemen,
the Top Gear car of the decade
is the Bugatti Veyron.
APPLAUSE
Keep going, keep going.
Yes. More applause. More than that.
Yeah! What about that?
Ha ha!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
We're there! We've made it to the
end of the hour. We've done it.
Thank you so much for watching.
We'll see you again later in
the year. Have a happy new year.
Take care, everyone. Good night.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd
E-mail : subtitling@bbc.co.uk
Ripped by KArkhon for Addic7ed.com