George Sr. had come
to a political fund-raiser
to get support
for a wall project...
To separate
the U.S. and Mexico.
...that some
considered insensitive...
- Which was my idea!
- Was your idea.
- ...even though he himself...
- Oh. Tender.
was feeling more sensitive
by the day.
Curious feeling.
But he tried to muster
the old self-confidence
for his face time
with Herbert Love.
And I-I just think
there will be a lot of support
flowing in this relationship,
and your base...
You got a point
behind all those teeth of yours?
If you support the wall,
I'll give you
a piece of the action.
- Action? Action Jackson?
- Yeah.
- Yes, sir.
- What do I look like, Carl Weathers to you?
- Oh, no, no.
- Not at all.
- No.
- This, of course, is Herbert Love.
My name is Herbert Love,
and I want you
to say "high-low"
to my low-high plan.
A candidate
whose campaign slogan
was embraced by everyone
from the very wealthy...
And who doesn't want
a high income?
...to their bankers
and tax attorneys.
High-low, high-low,
it's off to work I go--for you.
My name is Herbert Love,
and I most definitely
approve this message.
Do I look like someone
who eats at CW Swappigans?
See, I stand for three things:
one, getting
Barack Hussein Obama
Wama Comma Mama on a Llama
out of office...
It's a crazy-town name.
Two, low taxes
for high income earners.
That's my low-high plan.
- I know it.
- And three,
getting a little something
in my slushie fund
so that I'm nice and loose
and can help make
numbers one and two happen.
I don't want to be the one to
say it, but I happen to be fond
of redheads and greenbacks.
- George Sr. had neither.
- Oh, I-I...
- How would you like both?
- Get it for me tonight,
and I'll make your wall thing
the third point
of my three-point plan.
All I got right now is:
"You want to reach
"your hand into my pocket
to pay for your birth control?
I get to put my hand
in your pocket to put it in."
But when unveiled it
in Garden Grove,
I had to duck a
woman's pump and a mini pizza.
Oops.
Coming up with money, however,
would be difficult
for George Sr.,
who hadn't been acting
like his old self--
something his twin brother
Oscar had done
- You know, the wall.
- much more successfully
earlier that day,
when, in retribution...
Have you baked your brain
in that pizza oven?
...to a brother
who lied to him...
So he only did buy that land
for personal gain.
Well... Oscar.
- Oscar.
- ...Oscar chose to lie
- with George's wife.
- Call me Father B.
And, although too explicit
for an American audience,
the lovemaking was intense
and beautiful
but for one small
misunderstanding
that occurred
during the afterglow.
No. I-I mean...
it's good to be out of that
sweaty old hot box
at the compound.
No, this was am...
this was amazing.
And Oscar finally got
more information
- Speaking of that...
- about his brother's plans.
...we may need to have
a president ready to go
if something should happen
to Lucille 2
while we're building the wall.
So we are building a wall.
Right where Oscar
thought he would be spending
the rest of his life.
Turn him around three times
and put him in Fullerton,
- he won't know the difference.
- Fullerton.
You know, I think we should
send our son down there.
Give him some training,
show that he has a job,
let him sweat a little.
Buster? No, no.
I won't... I won't hear of it.
It could kill him.
I meant Gob.
Oh. Oh, fine.
Yeah, send him down.
I love that.
Now the story of a family
whose future
was abruptly canceled
and the one father
who had no choice
but to keep himself together.
It's George Sr.'s...
Unaware that he was being
cuckolded by his brother,
George Sr. was struggling
to find money
to bribe Herbert Love.
Didn't someone die
in one of these things?
Oh, no, not in one of ours.
Although his pitch had lost
some of its luster.
And, you know, I mean, it's
better than dying in the snow.
I mean, not...
not-not that you'll die,
but if you had to choose,
uh, I mean...
- Brr, you know?
- Hmm.
Well, I'll think about it.
Would you like a mini-quiche?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I thought you were a successful
Republican strategist.
- I'm so sorry.
- Why, 'cause I'm black?
Oh, no...
It was over.
But at least
he could go home...
Cindy's going to love these.
Excuse me, Red,
you're not the only one
- who likes coconut shrimp.
- ...with some coconut shrimp.
Well, I should have
known you'd be here,
supporting this right-wing,
dangerous crackpot.
Lindsay, I forgot--
you dyed your hair.
What are you doing here?
I'm supporting Love, as well.
We're both doing that.
Oh, honey, I-I've wanted
to contact you
every single day since last May.
I haven't seen you
since January.
Yeah, the first four months,
I was in denial. How are you?
Are... are you good?
Do you have any money?
Not really.
- Oh.
- Oh, except for
a $50, 000 check
your wife sent to my daughter
for plastic surgery.
What kind of a woman does that?
I thought there
was no money left.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, that's awful.
I mean, she's just precious
the way she is.
Does Maisie even know
about this?
No, thank God.
And her name is Maeby.
You don't think Maisie's cuter?
You know what I want to do?
I want to take this,
and I want to deposit it
in a trust fund
that she can't open
until she's 21.
- I guess I can't use it anyway.
- Are you kidding me?
You are the most beautiful
little girl I know.
And if you have any more work,
your cartilage
is going to collapse.
Let me see if I can...
- There you go.
- And that's when
George Sr. finally tipped
a black man.
- Got the check.
- ...okay?
Ooh! Hey, you got the check.
Third party.
Oh, man.
- I am going to put this on my wall.
- Oh...
George Sr.
left the hotelhoping he'd
accomplished something.
And on the news the next day...
We have got...
to build a wall
between us and Mexico.
...he found out he had.
- Yes!
- And aside from hating
the wrinkles he saw
in the rearview mirror
around his eyes and brow,
George Sr. was happy.
♪ All you need is smiles ♪
♪ Lots and lots
of smiley smiles ♪
♪ All you need is... ♪
What the (bleep)
is he smiling about?
Hello!
Oh, we're just doing a survey
for the U.S. government, ma'am.
Oh, no, I-I'm a man.
I was just wearing,
uh, this blouse
because I was, uh, driving
and I hate my arms.
What's the tape for?
Laying out border coordinates
for when they put up the wall.
Shh! You're not supposed
to tell them what it's for.
Well, he already
mentioned the tape,
and he looks American.
- Yeah, but he's in Mexico.
- Wait.
Guys, no, no, Mexico starts
- back there, by the gully.
- Whoever told you that's
probably chomping on the maca,
if you know what I mean.
So, what you're saying
to me is that
on this side of the tape,
I'm in Mexico,
but when I come over here...
Whoa. We're going to need
to see a passport, sir.
Pasaporte.
George Sr.
liked to make men
who disappoint him suffer.
But things change.
You really hurt
my feelings, guys.
- No hugging... ma'am.
- I'm sorry.
George Sr.
had just discovered
that the millions of dollars
of American property
he owned was worthless.
How did you not notice?
You saw all the papers.
And in Mexico.
You can't expect me to read
every page of that deal.
Besides, that one
was particularly difficult
because it was all in Spanish.
It says very clearly,
on my business card,
"Se habla español."
"I do not speak Spanish."
And it was your brother Oscar
who told me it
was on the border.
How did he not know?
Unfortunately,
Oscar missed the signs.
You think it's okay
to burn these?
Well, this is America.
If they don't want us
to burn signs,
they shouldn't write them
in Spanish.
- Everybody!
- ♪ Sign, sign, everywhere a sign... ♪
Only Heartfire knew the truth.
But the singing was so loud,
no one could hear her thoughts.
I bribed Love
to push for the building
of the wall,
and I don't have the land
to build it on!
Shh, shh, shh.
Call Herbert Love, all right?
Tell him you would
greatly appreciate it
if he'd rescind his support
for the wall.
And make him a flip-flopper?
I can't do that.
Actually, he'd tried,
but couldn't afford it.
It's a 40 for the flip
and a 40 for the flop,
and since it's going to cause
a flap, I'd say another 40.
So it's a flat 40-40-40
flip-flop and a flap fee.
Well, then find someone
who has influence with him.
Hold on.
A client is, uh, coming,
and I don't know where Oscar is.
He's disappeared.
And there is something up
with him
because he is scary now.
He has changed.
Hey, you've changed,
you big (bleep).
You're acting
like a little girl lately.
And not in the good way.
Pull yourself together.
Act like a man.
You're right, you're right.
- Okay, love you.
- Love you, too. Bye.
Cash, no receipt.
- Hot day, Father.
- Hot day, Father B.
- Hot day.
- Hot day, Father.
Hello, Father.
Don't call me that!
What are you doing here?
- You and Mom talked about it.
- We did...?
Oscar.
In fact, it was Oscar
who spoke to Lucille
about hiring Gob, but not
before an ominous warning.
But, you know,
he has magical abilities.
He can handle a lot more
than we give him credit for.
I know... What?!
I would have been here sooner,
but I had to go down
to San Diego
and loop my way back up
because they put up
that border ribbon.
- Which is totally new,
- Shh!
and I wasn't expecting it;
it's fine.
Anyway, Father,
you've got to get me a job
so I can be prepared...
to be president.
All right, you got to keep this
"father" stuff to yourself.
I can't have these people think
that I raised a limo driver.
I'm not a limo driver.
I'm a gentleman honey farmer.
The only thing I've got
back there are my bees.
- Beans?
- No, bees!
- Bees?
- Bees!
Bees! Oh, bees!
The boxes fell over
on the way here
when I had to swerve
to avoid an ostrich.
You got to do something
about this--these people
paid a lot of money.
Do something!
No, they won't listen to me.
- They've all got CCD.
- CCD?
Colony collapse disorder.
The guy sold me
just really sick bees.
Don't worry.
Dad, they're going to hive.
They always hive.
Usually by seeking out
a structure
that most resembles a hive.
Bees! Wonderful bees!
It's okay.
It's okay. Gob, get in there
- and get them out!
- Okay, I'm on it.
But then George Sr.
got some more bad news.
Hello, brother.
Thought I'd find you
in a blouse and a beekeeper hat.
What are you doing here?
No, no, no, no, no.
We cannot be seen
next to each other.
I'm Dr. Norman!
Well, if you don't want
to be seen, then you
go in the sweat lodge.
You owe me.
Is that a fact?
Listen, you told me
the property was on the border.
It is 50 feet south
of the border, Oscar.
Well, excuse me, but they hadn't
put up the tape yet.
So I was going off Buster's map.
Oh, God, it was Buster's map.
Buster had indeed made the map,
as a cartography student,
because the class where you get
to see naked people,
and draw them, was full.
And you lied to me.
You told me you bought
this property to live on.
No, you bought this property
to put up a wall.
I told one lie,
but I-I was going to share
the money with you.
- Two lies.
- And why do I think
that you charge more than
five dollars for lemonade?
Three small lies.
Now, will you do me a favor,
just get in the tent.
Gob's getting rid of the bees,
and we'll push the matinee
till 3:00.
No, I'm sick and tired
of being in that hut
pretending to be you.
Maybe I should go out there
and pretend to be you.
So, good-bye, George.
This is the last
you'll see of me.
Just gonna use the can
for one second.
There's two Dr. Normans!
George Sr. headed up
north to see his wife
before his brother could,
but he soon found out
he was too late by a day.
Oh, I know what you're coming up
- to do to me.
- Right.
What?
Yesterday, you were amazing.
Georgie, I can't stop
thinking about it.
You haven't been
like that in years.
Oh, right.
- You mean, slow-witted?
- I hope you're ready
for more of the same today.
Uh...  Oh, God.
George Sr. had a few problems:
his brother was
sleeping with his wife,
the property he was going to
sell to the government...
to build the U.S. wall on
was in Mexico...
All right...
all right...
...and his sweat lodge colony
had just collapsed.
Okay.
So he had to deal with
first things first.
If my identical twin brother
can get it up, then shouldn't I?
Have you had any sexual feeling
at all lately?
No!
You know, the Hopi Indians
believe that this spot here,
- Okay.
- when manipulated,
- can create sexual feeling.
- That's my penis.
Well, you don't have to tell me.
Nothing?
No, just a little curiosity
as to why you're checking
your second hand.
Oh, this isn't my office.
You know, I-I don't get it.
I've been popping the pills,
and, I mean, I mean, nothing.
- Are you under any pressure?
- Oh, no.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
I mean, there's some
violating federal law stuff
that'd put me in prison
for the rest of my life,
but I've made love with
treason charges over me before.
But no, it's something else.
It's not just the sex.
I feel...
I feel wrong.
Somehow.
And I'm becoming weak.
Sorry, had the old
thinking cap on.
Let's go to the lists.
And Dr. Norman
proceeded to run through
a checklist of alternative
medicine questions.
Okay, did you drink some water
that might have
a homeopathic memory
of some molecule?
Do you keep track
of the molecules you ingest?
Well, with homeopathy,
it's the molecules
you don't ingest.
But I'm the one
who can get hard,
so let's focus on you.
He then went on to explore
some supernatural
or high-concept
premise possibilities.
Any earthquakes
in a Chinese restaurant
- while you were trying to prove
something to your mother? - No.
Any wishes you may have
phrased badly,
or while a child
was blowing out a candle?
No.
Have you come across
any ancient games, let's say,
glowing games, uh, either
board based or carnival based,
that you may have played against
the wishes of your best friend?
- No.
- Curses, hexes, spells,
shaman, medicine men?
Wait.
The strong will become the weak.
The weak will become the strong.
I did hallucinate one ancient
foreboding warrior harbinger
while I chewed maca root
about a year ago.
Could that be something?
No, it's not the maca.
Your body wants the maca.
It's not the maca.
But finally,
out of desperation,
he turned to Western medicine.
Okay, tell you what,
let's get some film on you.
I'd like you to get
on an MRI machine
and try to ride it to climax.
I'm gonna send you over
to Orange County Imaging--
they do a ton of that.
Okay, do I get magazines?
Yeah, I'll write you
a script for that.
They got a place right around
the corner that plays ball.
Thank you.
Oh, (bleep). Run.
What? Oh.
And soon, after getting
his prescription filled...
Uh... hola...
I have a, um--magazines?
...he was on his way
to debase himself
in an MRI machine
when he ran into a son
with whom he'd lost touch.
Dad, what are you doing here?
I wanted to speak to you...
in person.
Then you're here to apologize;
that right?
- Sure.
- Although, he covered pretty well.
And-and of course to see you
at Orange County Im-a-gine.
I went to you
for a simple signature,
and you told me to go to hell.
Actually, it was
the newly potent Oscar,
who, like one of
Gob's sick bees,
was pollinating one barren
flower after another,
who told Michael to go to hell.
- Go to hell.
- Huh?
Which is how George Sr.
not only was left with
Senor Senoritas,
and that's when he got a lead
on his wall problem.
Do you know a guy
named Herbert Love?
I know a lot of people, sure.
And soon, he surprised Michael
by giving him his rights
for the movie project.
I didn't know it was about
lying to a girl.
- Give me the release.
- You'd do this for me?
- Of course I will.
- And then, didn't surprise him.
If you'll do something for me.
I knew it.
Michael, you got to get
this Love guy against the wall
between the U.S. and Mexico.
That's not right.
You're really opposed
to this wall, huh?
When did you
become pro-immigrant?
I have changed, Michael.
I cry
at the drop of a hat,
and I hate the way I look.
I actually had one cute hat,
and it...
it blew off
at the CVS parking lot.
And this whole car
full of black kids ran over it,
for no reason.
And they saw it!
They saw it!
Michael...
Anyway, I live down there now.
And I care for these people
who just want
to come into this country
and ply their wares
and let us freely fill the bay
with their culture.
Hey, don't get me started
on the Cinco, Dad.
I haven't been to one
in 20 years.
There's gonna be blowback there;
it's just gonna happen.
You can't swim in that bay
for a month after
without getting
nacho cheese sauce in your hair.
It's coming.
Can you help me, then,
with Love?
At his speech, at Cinco?
Can you do that for your dad?
What he didn't tell Michael was
that the family would go broke
if they had to build the wall.
Of course I will.
Maybe, if he had,
Michael wouldn't have
overplayed his hand
as a big-shot producer
who knew lots of people.
But a deal was soon struck...
- Thanks, Pop.
- All right.
...and Michael,
signed contract in hand,
went to show off
at the Ealing Club,
while George Sr.,
magazine in hand,
went to (bleep) off
in an MRI machine.
George Sr. finally
went to visit a wife
who was under the impression
that he was back for more.
The wrong land?
It's under control;
I'm trying to get Love
to come out against the wall.
We can't afford to build it
if we're not
selling the land
back to the government.
It'll ruin us.
It'll ruin us
if we don't build it.
George, you've gone puny again.
Where's the man who took
ahold of me yesterday
and bent me over this couch?
Okay, okay,
let's not sully its memory.
Look, we make sure Herbert Love
comes out against the wall,
right after we get
enough of it up
to trigger
the government payment.
And speaking of
getting enough of it up,
what's going on down here?
You need a little more Marilyn
like I did yesterday?
♪ Happy birthday,
Mr. President... ♪
I-I don't want to be
Mr. President.
Huh. Especially with
all this going down.
Oh, and speaking of president,
what's happening with Gob?
You gave him a job?
Yes, but then I-I fired him.
He caused my colony to collapse.
Oh, my God, George,
get him another job.
You must have some favors
you can call in somewhere.
And then you can have some of
my favors, Mr. President.
As much as I'd like to stay
and lay some more pipe with you,
I better get moving
on this thing.
And so, the next day,
George Sr. once again
called upon his son.
Michael B. Project.
Yeah, you got to give Gob a job.
Something in
the, uh, building company
or, uh, hey, I think
he'd get a big kick
out of the movie business.
N-N-No, Dad, hey.
He knows nothing
about producing.
Look, I don't care
if it's producing a movie
that's never gonna be made
or selling houses
that no one's gonna buy,
I just want my son
to have a job
where his incompetence
won't be out of place.
Anyway, he's on his way
to Sudden Valley now.
No, he isn't.
No, no, come on, Dad...
- No, no, now?
- What, what?
He's gonna make it
less valuable?
Which I told you
was gonna happen, by the way.
Oh, here it is.
Here it is.
Yeah, there it is!
Knew it was coming.
And even though George
had imposed on Michael,
it was Gob...
What the hell?
...who felt
he had a cross to bear.
What the hell?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, I got the right of--
- Hey, hey, hey...
- N-No, don't. It's mine.
- Okay, coming through here.
- Mine... Hah!
No... no, no!
My right of... way!
- There! Mine!
- Okay.
Hey...
Gob!
Michael!
And the two brothers
reunited...
Hey, Gob.
Michael.
...happy to see each other.
Gob?
At first.
Michael.
So, hear you need help moving
these memorials to the death
of the housing market.
Actually that was a memorial
- to the death of Pete the mailman.
- I knew that.
I brought one, too--
size of the man's heart.
I just got to figure out
how to get it out of the car.
If I could remember
how I got it in.
That's not
from your Christian magic act?
Christian magic act?
If I were Muslim, would you say
"Muslim magic act"?
No, but it is hard to imagine
any Muslim handcuffing himself
to a glittery cross
and living to tell about it.
Yeah, well, the Christians
aren't so (bleep)-hot
about it either.
Hmm, well...
Michael could see
that his brother was unhappy
and that his life had not
worked out
the way he had hoped.
Things are incredible for me,
I'm having an incredible year.
I am a movie producer now,
producing a movie,
so they've got me
in this enormous office.
I told 'em
I don't want to be driving
to Beverly Hills
every single day,
so they put me in an enormous
office just over here.
Rental.
My personal life is off
the charts. I've met someone.
Can't really give you any
information--kind of famousy.
- Well, good for you. I also met someone.
- Have you?
Also famousy.
Can't give you any information.
In fact, Michael didn't even
find out who she was
until one night, earlier.
Oh, my God. I'm dating Ron
Howard's girlfriend.
Although he did have
some of the details wrong.
She's an actress.
You know her.
She was Ron's
illegitimate daughter,
a fact unbeknownst to many.
Well, we kind of like to keep
that quiet.
A woman who, like Bryce Dallas
and Paige Carlyle,
was named after
where she was conceived.
And she actually had worked
for some A-list directors.
She did a Terrence Malick...
Are we the same?
She got the lead
in a Woody Allen film...
But I felt like I was in
The Iceman Cometh,
but, you know,
in my case, he faketh.
...and was once even directed
by her own father.
Action!
Next time, don't pocket it,
pay for it.
Shoplifting: not cool.
- ...in a public service announcement.
- And cut!
Which, like all of
Ron's work...
You know, I think we got it.
...was inspired
by a photograph.
Rebel was indeed a rebel.
But Michael didn't possess
that information.
I can give you some information
about your airless office
you're gonna be spending
most mornings in.
You know, what I could go for
is some guac.
Well, you don't live there
anymore, Gob.
This heat just makes,
makes me want guac.
Now, now, I know
I've got these things,
uh, very, you know,
meticulously maintained.
There's...
There are some vultures.
I think they might
still smell Pete.
Yeah, if it wasn't for the movie
thing, I would do it myself.
They practically sell
themselves; you just got
- to bring the people in.
- I'm ready to move in today.
No, well, people other than you,
- bring those people in.
- I'm starving.
Starving? No, you're not
gonna find anything here.
They've been abandoned for...
Lindsay.
No, no, this--maybe Tobias.
It was John Beard.
Shall we?
Well, the value of these homes
isn't gonna go down
if we don't sell one today.
Let me see
if I can find a, uh...
Do you have a bottle opener?
Great idea.
And after a few more drinks and
a little more depreciation...
- That was surprising.
- ...Michael admitted he had
a rival for his girlfriend.
You don't have to worry
about Ron Howard.
I mean, he's not
competition for you.
- Really?
- Yeah, I mean, the guy's
like 100 years old.
What's he gonna do,
poke you in the eyes?
Oh, you're confused.
Ron Howard directed Apollo 13.
You're thinking of Moe Howard,
the angry stooge who's been dead
for a quarter century.
Well, that's good 'cause the
whole time I'm thinking, like,
"unless she likes
a guy who's funny."
- Sure.
- Because that guy is funny.
- 'Cause the whole time you're like...
- You know...
- "Is he gonna poke me in the eyes?"
- Gob,
I don't think that th-the
movie--it might not even happen
because I don't think
that I can ask my son.
What happened between him and me
was very disappointing.
You don't need to tell me
about disappointment and sons.
Let's not forget Steve Holt.
That's the story
of our relationship.
Right, well, I was talking about
a son disappointing a father.
Yeah, that does make it
different.
Look, Michael,
he doesn't respect you,
so you have
to make him respect you.
Show him that you're a big shot,
that you don't need to
live in your son's dorm.
No, I just live
in my parents' penthouse now.
Well, then, take him to the
Ealing Club; it's all showbiz.
I used to hang out there
all the time.
It's just actresses
and stuff like that.
I don't know
if I could pick up the phone
and call him and ask him.
- You know what, Michael?
- Hmm?
I'll call him for you.
Really, you'd do that for me?
It's the least I could do.
You've given me
a new sense of purpose.
Did you actually have
an old one?
'Cause it always seemed
like you were just looking
for the easy way out.
Yeah, that was it.
Hi, I'm George Bluth
of the Bluth Company, and, uh...
George Sr.,
meanwhile, was also finding
an easy way out
of the wall problem.
...we've built this wall.
We have miles and,
and miles of wall.
Will you confirm that, soldier?
It's ab-about protecting
our border,
which is why, uh,
we have a member
of our armed forces
with us today.
Say hello.
It's, uh, triple-reinforced,
steel-reinforced,
and I don't really
know how to, how to say
that, uh, what it does is,
it protects, um...
It's Mexican-proof.
So-- can't say-- it...
Well, gosh darn it,
it is Mexican-proof.
Sit up.
- Uh...
- Daddy, my tummy's turning.
All right.
- Uh, it's, uh, triple-reinforced.
- I got...
Daddy, I got to get out,
- I got to get out.
- Uh, we're gonna be...
Oh, for God's sakes, get out.
I need to get out,
I need to get out.
- Oh, for...
- I need to get out, I need to get out.
We're not gonna... we'll edit
this part out and, uh...
Anyhow...
But George Sr.
hadn't built miles of wall.
He just found a roundabout way
to make it seem that way,
and one week later at Cinco,
George arrived,
hoping to hear Herbert Love...
No, thanks. I've already crushed
one with my car.
...sway public opinion
against the wall
so the Bluth Company
wouldn't be on the hook
- to build it for real.
- Pop, hey, hi.
- Michael, what happened?
- Yeah.
Oh, the--it's a terrible week,
but I'm gonna fix things
once and for all right now.
- Is this about Love?
- No, it's about money,
but I-I'm--I will pay her back,
uh, one way or the other.
Who?
Lucille 2--I'm gonna get her
- against the wall.
- No, no, no, no, no,
she cannot know about this wall.
Fine, I'll get her up against
the top of the staircar.
I don't care,
it's gonna happen, though.
I am talking about Herbert Love.
- Is he going to oppose the
building of the wall? - Oh, yes.
I took care of that.
He is going to announce that
in his speech tonight.
That is great news.
Listen, I-I-I have to go.
I have to see if I can pass
this testosterone test.
I do, too.
And, listen, not a word to...
How dare you?
Lucille 2.
Did you think
I wouldn't find out?
I was going to cut you in.
I was trying to protect you
so they wouldn't link you to it,
but it turns out that we can't
afford to build it anyway.
- Build what?
- The wall in Mexico, the, the high wall.
- What were, what were you talking about?
- I was talking
about you giving money
to Herbert Love in his campaign
- against me.
- Oh, no, no,
that was to get Love
to support the wall.
Oh, I tell you, I've been
all over the place on this one.
I can't be running a company
that's building a wall
I campaigned against!
Listen to me,
it's taken care of.
I just ran into Michael.
He's got Love against the wall.
It's done, it's gonna be in
the speech tonight, it's over.
It better be,
or I'll talk about it
in my speech tonight.
Now, I've got a staircar
to wave from.
And I can't be seen with you.
'Cause I'm fat.
It's because I am fat.
You think I'm a fat person.
You are such a drama queen.
George Sr. was worried.
These fat arms.
I don't understand this.
And so, it was in
a state of agitation
that George Sr. arrived
for his doctor's appointment.
Excuse me, Dr. Norman?
- You're mistaken.
- Dr. Norman,
it's me, George Bluth.
Oh, George, yes,
thank you for meeting me here.
I like to do a little
housecleaning on the fourth.
Old quinceañera candles.
I was wondering if you could
tell me my test results.
Oh, yes, yes, uh, well,
your testosterone numbers
are off the charts.
Below the charts,
under the charts.
I don't know how to say that.
You have almost
no testosterone at all.
I don't know the exact numbers,
but it's somewhere
in the baby range.
On the plus side,
your estrogen levels are that
of a very healthy woman
in the throes of her menses.
May I see my results?
Ah, I wish you'd asked me
about five minutes ago.
I think I dumped it
with a pot pipe
and a bottle
of cheetah sedative.
Also, the people
at Orange County Imaging
said that you were masturbating
in an MRI tube?
- Oh, no.
- But, Doctor,
you, you told me to.
I did no such thing.
Oh, no.
No, no, you can't do that.
That sounds like something
I would say
when I had my thinking cap on.
You, sir, are a very funny lady.
That's what they always say
to the unattractive one.
It was finally time
for Herbert Love
to make his speech, when the
party was suddenly ransacked.
Of course, it was Cinco,
so it took a while
for anyone to notice.
It appeared
the Hispanic community had had
enough of Cinco de Cuatro.
- Oh, God, the blowback.
- Put up this wall!
But the blowback created
a greater blowback
as the crowd that had gathered
to hear Herbert Love speak
was whipped into a frenzy.
Put up this wall!
And that's when George knew
he was in real trouble.
Put up this wall!
Fortunately,
he was able to find a disguise.
Oh, God.
- Unfortunately...
- This feels right.
Lindsay surprises Michael
after a long absence
from his life.
Lindsay.
It's been a long time.
I know.
Oh, this is
a little embarrassing.
But I have been meaning
to get down there,
- so let's just...
- You're right,
I mean, it's not like we're
even technically related.
- That's true.
- Okay, well, then, I'll start with a smear.
And George Sr. gets
more comfortable in hiding.
Yes?
Uh, Detective Smee,
Orange County Police.
I need to speak with you.
Lucille Austero went missing
last night.
- You mind if we ask you a few questions?
- Oh...!
I-I don't allow men
in my apartment
without my husband present.