(playful music)
(ding)
(pop)
DR. CHIMPSKY:
Ten, nine, eight -
Ah, Rocket Monkeys!
* They're Rocket Monkeys,
Monkeys in space *
* They try to be heroes,
but they're easy to replace *
* They're not the brightest,
they're not the best *
* They're not the coolest,
they also have bad breath *
* Rocket Monkeys,
Rocket Monkeys *
Oo oo ooh *
* Give them a mission,
they'll do their best *
* The best is relative,
don't you forget *
* Rocket Monkeys!
[Snoring]
Good morning
Rocket Monkeys,
today you have a very
important miss-
Hellooo!
Hello!?
[Making a racket]
[Snoring]
Yay-OK!
Cock a doodle doo!
[Cock a doodle doo variations]
Oy!
[Sigh] I have cocked
my last doodle-doo.
Why don't I just
tell you the mission?
Good thinking.
Yeah. Meet me
in the cargo bay.
May I present...
King Killya.
Move it, Chumpsky!
This is my story.
Behold!
These are the riches from
the Kingdom of Killya!
GASI is transporting
them to my new home,
where they will be
a surprise gift
for my girlfriend,
Bunbuns.
You have
a girlfriend?
Ow!
I mean,
of course you do!
Anything happens
to Bunbun's gifts,
this is what will
happen to you...
I'm a visual aide!
[Crushing, ripping]
[Robot shouting in pain]
Oh my bolts!
I got it.
Don't worry,
I will get help from
my crazy monkeys.
[Laughing]
Better yet,
what I'll do is
I'll keep the monkeys out
of this mission altogether.
Yeah.
Probably for the best.
[Snoring]
[Kitty alarm meows]
[Excited scream]
It's red
undies month!
One whole month of
fuzzy red comfort!
Argyle?
Nooo.
Green? Nope.
Puce?
Not today.
Brownie? Don't worry,
you'll get your turn...
once I wash you.
Beige?
Nope.
Plaid? Nope...
Where'd they go?
Gus!
What's up,
Broski?
Are you wearing my lucky
red banana undies?
I resent these wild,
unfounded accusations
that I'm wearing your
lucky red banana undies.
I've got tons
of my own.
[Breath crumbles undies]
[Nervous giggle]
[Shriek]
You monster!
I told you never to touch my
red banana undies - ever!
No. Don't touch.
Don't do it.
No touchy.
Stop it. Get it away.
Don't do it...
You know, bro,
there's a little word
called 'sharing'.
Look it up!
Oh yeah? Well, there's
a little word called
"Give me back my
banana undies!"
That's more
than one word
and it's not little,
it's several words!
Well it's still
in the dictionary
if you look them
up individually!
Boys, boys!
What's this all about?
Mom? What are
you doing here?
One of you must have
pocket dialed me.
Hey!
That's my phone!
Give it back!
Mom! Wally
won't share!
Me?! Gus is
Mr. Never-Shares!
Boys!
Don't you remember
"The Sharing Song?"
Hit it!
* You better
listen to mama. *
* Mama says share.
* Mama says care.
* Mama says
sharing is caring. *
* You wanna stay in
mama's good book? *
* You better pass the share
and show you care! *
* You better
listen to mama. *
* Sharing is caring!
* That's what
mama says! *
* That's what mama says!
[***]
You better
listen to Mama!
Mom's right.
We need to share.
Well, I'm way more
sharey than you!
Well, I'm the Share-Master
General! Just saying.
I'm Senior Sharino from
the planet Mucho Share-o.
Well, I'm the
King of Shares
who lives in
Share-wood forest.
I'm share-re-re-re...
the Sharifker of Sharogians...
shares...
Well, Sharey Christmas,
'cause I'm Santa Share-aus!
Wait! Where'd Gus go?
I wasn't finished!
Let's see here.
We've got -
Okay, that's three pairs
of solid gold pantyhose.
Check.
One life-size velvet donkey.
Che-wow,
a velvet donkey, huh?
Who knows what that's for?
But still,
I'll check that one off...
A half dozen ruby-incrusted
Dynasty Eggs -
And wait -
How did this get in here?
[Pulling efforts]
[Scream]
[Slo-mo]
Oh my bolts!
Oooh!
Ah!
Oh! Ah!
Oh!
[Relieved sigh]
You better not be breaking
Bunbun's stuff!
Or else...
It's a living.
[Crushing sounds]
[Robot screaming in pain]
Yes, yes,
threat acknowledged.
Oh, Inky!
Have some
delicious bananas!
I sooo want to
share them with you.
Wally! Those are from
my private collection!
Ooh, sounds like someone
doesn't like to share.
J'accuse!
Au contraire,
mon frere!
I love to share.
Here, Inky, let me share
this uniform with you.
Let me share this
monkey tail with you!
Let me share these!
And I'll share
whatever these are!
Why not sample this?
How about a
slice of that?
How about some
of these?
Free Stuff!
Gus' memories
stored in a jar!
Have all of
Wally's comics.
Gus's secret diary
written in lasagna!
Wally's dumb banana
art collection!
Here, how about
Gus' spine?
Graft it to your own spine,
have two spines!
How about Wally's
fingernails...
that you can
grow Wally from?
Okay then, all treasure
present and accounted for!
Now for a couple of
added precautions...
There!
Everything is safe.
Which is to say,
far away from monkeys.
MONKEYS:
Yay-OK!
We ran out of
stuff to share.
Yeah. Got any ideas?
So sorry,
monkeys.
I, uh,
I wish I could help,
but really my
bolts are tied.
GUS: Here,
have this lock!
WALLY:
Have these boards!
Have whatever this is!
Have these chains!
Aw, nothing left
to share...
MONKEYS:
Sharing is caring!
Sorry, but these
don't belong to you...
[Yay-OK shouts in pain]
MONKEYS:
Sharesies!
That is not your possession!
GUS:
Here you go!
Hey! Give that back!
I tell you!
WALLY:
And one for you!
YAY-OK: I am just going to take
what does not belong to you...
Could I please just get
back the possessions
that technically
do not belong to you -
[Roar]
Oh dear...
Sorry?
[Growl]
[Yay-OK screams]
[Belch]
Everything is gone!
The mission is a
complete failure!
King Killya is
going to crush me.
I'm finished.
Done. Over.
Kaput.
Turn out the lights
the party's over!
Relax, bro bot.
WALLY: Here,
have an omelet.
I don't really eat food,
but if I'm going
to be crushed,
I may as well try it...
[Chewing]
Huh. I tell you,
this actually isn't half bad.
What is in it?
The usual -
bananas, onions,
a half-dozen ruby-incrusted
antique eggs...
[Spit take]
Monkeys! I tried to keep you
out of this mission,
but if we don't
return all of the treasure
in perfect condition,
King Killya will
robo-crunch me!
Flatten...
flatten me.
[Hyperventilating]
Nothing...
[hyperventilating]
left of Yay-OK...
Sounds like someone's got a
case of the grumpy-wumpies.
I know what you need.
Hugs!
Yes, hugging is nice.
Here's an issue -
kind of important -
SOMEONE SHOULD BE
DRIVING THE SHIP!
Ah...
Note to self -
Always wear a seat belt.
KING KILLYA:
About time you arrived!
I want my precious
property NOW!
Funny thing about property,
Mr. Killya.
I mean who really
owns anything anyway?
Who are we
anyways?
Why are we
even here?
Gimme... stuff...
NOW!
[Yay-OK squirts oil]
[Embarrassed giggle]
Oh, Mr. King
Killya...
Ta-da!
Excellent!
But how is that possible?
Looks like I
won't have to
[chewing noises]
you after all.
Bun Bun is going
to be so happy!
What trickery is this?!
My treasure...
gone!
I have nothing!
Well not
nothing-nothing...
Sharing is caring!
Sharing?
I'll show you sharing!
One for you.
And one
for you!
And another!
And one for you!
[Killya pummels others]
BERNICE:
That's enough, Pookie!
You've had your fun,
now drop my boys!
Mom?!
But Bunbuns!
They gave away all my
kingdom's priceless treasures.
It was all for you!
It's just stuff.
Besides,
I've got my boys...
and I've got my Pookie!
And I've got
this jukebox.
What else do I need?
[***]
* You better
listen to mama! *
* Mama says share!
* Mama says care!
* Mama says
sharing is caring! *
[***]
Pookie! You're
not singing!
Mama says sharing
is caring...
WALLY:
* Gamgam's on her way!
* Gamgam's on
her way! *
* Gamgam's on her way!
It's a hip-hop-happy day! *
* Oh...
* Gamgam's on her way!
Gamgam's on her way...*
Take it!
[Unenthusiastic]
* And she'll be here today.
Where's the excitement?
This is Gamgam
we're talking about!
[Doorbell]
BERNICE:
Hi boys!
So nice of you to take care of
your grandmother while I'm...
busy...
planting my excuse tree...
Oh, look at the time.
Gotta run!
I'm free!
[Thunder]
[Scream]
[Excited gasp]
Yay, Gamgams!
[Unenthusiastic]
Yay, Gamgams...
Your mother couldn't
wait to get rid of me.
You, fix me some tea.
Metal one,
take my trunk.
And don't you be swiping
any of my unmentionables.
Hey! How come I'm not
hearing my song?
* Twinkle, twinkle,
little star, *
* how I wonder
what you are... *
[Delighted squeal]
You look adorable!
Now come give your
Gamgam some sugar.
You're so squishy, Gamgam!
[Sniff] And you smell
like burnt logs!
Such a sweet boy...
Who are you?!
It's me, Gus.
Right...
The other one.
Welcome,
Grandmother Monkey!
It is always
a pleasure
to be screamed at
and treated poorly.
Care for a slice of
nuts-and-bolts cake?
Garbage! My toaster
can do better!
[Muttering] I'd like to put
you in a toaster, Gamgam.
What did
you say?!
Nothing.
That's what I thought.
Gary! Show me
to my room.
My dogs
are killing me.
[Strained]
Here's your room, Gamgam...
It's too far from the
little grandma's room!
I've got a bladder
the size of a raisin.
What about that
one over there?
GUS: That's
Yay-OK's room.
Get a move on!
[Relieved sigh]
What's this
doo-hickey do?
[Vomiting]
Oh dear, there's
only one banana...
Oooh, half for my precious
little Wally...
[Baby-talk]
Wally wuvs his Gamgam!
And the other half...
for me!
[Pulling efforts]
[Scream]
[Shudder]
Quit your bellyaching, Gary!
Why can't you be more
like your brother?
Your bunions
are the best, GG!
Oh, that feels so good!
"Gary, clean my ears."
"Gary, my tea's
too cold."
"Gary, starch
my support hose."
I can't take
this anymore!
We've got to get
Gamgam off this ship.
Oh, sure,
she's cruel.
Harsh? Mean-spirited?
Smells funny?
Horrible to look at,
all of those things!
I do not like her.
But giving your
gamgam the boot
is a bit, uh, drastic,
don't you think?
What do you think -
Stacked heel or steel toe?
Gus, you are
all worked up.
Let's get some shut-eye,
and tomorrow is a new day.
* Everything is fine
in the world today... *
[Terrified scream]
[Gamgam in ecstasy]
[Terrified screaming]
I am in!
Whatever it takes,
we are getting that
Gamagam off this ship!
[Snoring]
Oh, how adorable!
Oh, that's a
fabulous figurine...
And another one!
That is perfect for
my collection...
Eyeballs on that
little fella...
* Ding dong,
grandma's gone! *
* Gone, gone, gone,
gone gone-y gone. *
* Say goodbye to Gamgam!
See ya Gamgam!
My evil attack robot
is almost complete!
Bwahahaha!
But I can't help but think
something is missing...
Ooh!
By the phlegmballs
of Falconer!
Don't you know
how to drive?
Don't you talk to me
like that, young man.
Why would you put
this robot here?
Squids these days -
No respect!
So cranky!
So powerful!
Why, this gives me an idea...
Where's the toilet?
I need to do a doodoo.
The cranky granny is
now under my control!
You call that
a stun-beam?
[Sigh]
Hey bro, been having
fun with Gamgam?
Best time ever!
Isn't that right, Yay-OK?
Yes... Uh,
very good times.
It was the best of
times some would say...
the memories...
the, uh, things that
you'll never ...
they'll never leave
you, really...
[Nervous giggle]
[Yawn]
What's that, Gamgam?
Oh, you want to play
with Wally now?
* I love Gamgam -
You're so draggy,
Gamgam!
At last, I have
harnessed the power
of granny strength!
Seriously?
A granny-powered robot?
Work with me here.
I'm improvising.
Finally, I'll be able
to exact revenge
on the Council to
Stop Super Villains,
conveniently located
at GASI headquarters!
Unleash the old lady bot!
[Maniacal laughter]
[Creaky, decrepit
robot moving]
[Sigh]
[Gus playing
video game]
WALLY: Gus!
Your game's too noisy!
Gamgam likes quiet time -
you know that!
I don't hear
her complaining.
Yay-OK, do you?
I uh, actually,
my hearing...
You know, my hearing,
it is not so good...
She doesn't mind,
do ya, Gamgam?
[Screaming]
Gamgam!
She's just...
uh... tired. Yeah.
That's what happens when
old ladies get tired.
Their heads fall off.
[Nervous laugh]
Hey sweetpeas!
Just checking in.
Are you having fun
with the boys, Gamgam?
[Granny voice]
So much fun, uhm...
Gus's mum.
They're taking
good care of me...
Oh yes, and I have
no pains...
We love time
with gamgam!
Wow! She must be
really tired.
Soon you will be at
GASI Headquarters,
where I will unleash
my ultimate revenge!
[Horns honking]
[Angry shouting]
Say when,
Gamgam...
When!
Enough with
the pouring!
Rocket Monkeys,
GASI headquarters
is being attacked by -
Wally, why are
you pouring tea
for what is clearly a
headless granny doll dummy?
[Gasp] How dare you talk
about Gamgam that way?!
Yeah, that's clearly
our grandmother...
[As Gamgam]
I love my Gussypoo!
And my
Yay-OK poo!
I can't take it anymore!
My guilt sensors
are off the charts!
It was us!
We sent away your
precious Gamgam!
How dare you!
[Wally pummels Yay-OK]
Hello!
Still talking here!
GASI Headquarters is
under attack by Nefarious
and his crazed
mega-Granny bot!
It's our first-ever Code Grey!
I'm pretty excited
about that.
[Screams]
Release the
stale cookies!
[Shout]
Take this!
[Evil laugh]
Gamgam!
How could you, Gus?
And you too, Yay-OK!
Handing Gamgam
over to Nefarious!
You know she's just a
sweet old lady, deep down.
Seriously?
Deep, deep...
deeeep down.
That's where she's nice.
Half for my precious
little Wally...
and the other half...
for me.
Here, you can have the peel.
You're right, Wal.
I never saw it
before now.
She always gave me the
tastiest part of the banana -
the peel.
We have to get
Gamgam back...
and I know just
how to do it!
You can't
laser-blast Gamgam!
It's a risk I'm
willing to take...
and let's be honest,
she has it coming.
Gus!
Fine, we'll get Gamgam back
the Rocket Monkey way!
[Pit farts]
[Actual farts]
Those monkeys are
making potty sounds!
How very rude!
Arm the hard candy
cannons with peppermint -
the flavor nobody likes!
Bwahaha!
[Shriek]
[Retching]
[Evil laugh]
GUS:
Hey, Gamgam!
You know those sweaters
you gave us for Christmas?
Uuugly!
Never even
wore it!
Oh my galoshes!
Ignore the monkeys!
Deploy the Gamgama-phone!
* [Loud, old-timey music]
Horrible...
granny music...
Ears...
burning!
That's the cat's pajamas!
Hee-hee!
Looks like we've only
got one hope left.
Way ahead of you, bro...
Oh, right.
* Twinkle, twinkle,
little star, *
* how I wonder
what you are... *
GAMGAM:
Oh, they're adorable!
By the tenderloin
of Turner,
turn up the [bleeped swearing]
crankiness!
You watch that tongue
of yours, young squid,
or I'll rip it
right out of ya
and I'll slap ya
with it!
Are you
kidding me?!
This is [extensive,
bleeped swearing] ridiculous!
[Groans in pain]
I needed a doctor...
I warned ya, Sonny!
Here's a little something
for your potty mouth!
[As Gamgam]
Ooh, Gussy poo!
You were such a brave
little monkey today!
Thanks, Gamgam.
I sound nothing
like that!
YAY-OK:
Bolts!
[Pained] * Twinkle twinkle
little star... *
YAY-OK:
* They're Rocket Monkeys,
* They're monkeys in space,
* They try to be heroes,
but they're easy to replace, *
* They're not the brightest,
and they're not the best. *
* OK, they're not the coolest,
and they have stinky breath. *
* Oh, you Rocket Monkeys,
oh, you Rocket Monkeys, *
* Rocket Monkeys,
Oo oo ooh... *
* Give them a mission,
and they'll do their best. *
* Their best is relative,
don't you forget. *
DR. CHIMPSKY:
Ten, nine, eight...
Ah, Rocket Monkeys!
* They're Rocket Monkeys,
Monkeys in space *
* They try to be heroes,
but they're easy to replace *
* They're not the brightest,
they're not the best *
* They're not the coolest,
they also have bad breath *
* Rocket Monkeys,
Rocket Monkeys *
Oo oo ooh *
* Give them a mission,
they'll do their best *
* Their best is relative,
don't you forget *
* Rocket Monkeys!
YAY-OK:
Go Monkeys!
GUS: * Weedily weedilly
weedilly wee! *
* Gonna spend
our pay *
* all day today
* 'til it's gone,
gone, gone, *
* 'til it's
gone away! *
[Deedilly-wop scatting]
Gonna spend our pay!
[Crash]
Welcome to Barnabus
Briggs' Emporium,
purveyor of fine goods and
slightly discounted oddities!
What can I interest
you in today,
my hairy,
indiscriminate consumers?
A ham helmet?
Cheese lamp?
Five alarm goat?
[Bleat]
What's this?
You have a keen eye,
my simian friend.
That is a genuine er...
Um...
Space rock!
I can let you
have it for say...
Ten sniggets!
[Sniff]
[Slurp]
Ten sniggets!?
For this smelly old rock?
Ha!
Who'd buy something so
completely worthless?
Oof!
I'll take it!
Excellent choice.
Sold!
Product comes with a
one second warranty.
Warranty is expired.
No returns.
All sales final.
No responsibility for any
injuries caused by merchandise.
Sucka!
I can't believe you
bought that junk!
Feast your eyes on this!
Well, at least it's
under warranty.
Warranty is expired.
Fubb!
Hey, this rock rocks!
This will never
get irritating!
Fubb! Fubb!
Ever!
[Blowing on rock]
[Giggle]
Why did I even
bother buying this?
It blew up in my face!
[Scream]
Fubb!
[Wally blowing into
rock while snoring]
Wally?
Wally! WALLY!
[Yawn]
What is it, bro?
Say Wal, can I see that
supercool rock of yours?
Positutely!
All you have to do is ask.
Thanks...
[Shouting and
smashing rock]
Whew!
Much better.
There you go, Wal.
Well... good-night.
Thanks, Gus!
[Deep inhale]
* [Playing actual
musical notes] *
[Scream]
Whoa!
You're right!
This is much better.
You're the best.
Best!
You're the besty-best
best best...
* [Playing rock
like a horn] *
[Girlish screaming,
gushing, and cheering]
So talented and dreamy!
Rocket Monkey Wally,
you have such talent.
Way more talent than...
you know... him.
Hello!
I'm right here!
I didn't say
anything.
I just pointed...
talent...
less-talent...
I get it!
And I say to that, HA!
Stand back, and let a real
musical talent do his thing.
* [Armpit fart melody]
I'm inspired, Gus -
Inspired to tell you
to clean the toilets.
[Laughing]
Wally, keep
playing, man.
This is my jam!
My toast with
marmal-jam!
Yeah!
Jimmy jim jam,
yummy yummy ham ham!
And maybe I'm gonna
have me some lamb! Bah!
No fair! I'm the one
who saw the rock first!
It should'a been mine!
Why does Wally get
all the breaks?!
I guess it's because I was
born with a surplus of talent
and you were born with
a surplus of jealous!
And fungus!
I'm not in
the way, am I?
Listen, I'll give you twenty
sniggets for that rock!
Not for sale!
But I'm your bro!
I never ask you
for anything.
[Sniffle] Remember when
I chewed your food
and spat it in your mouth
because you were too tired
to chew it yourself?
Remember the time I
took a poo-poo for you
because your poo-poo
was too gross
and you didn't
wanna see it?
I'm just playin'
with you, bro.
Me rocka es tu rocka,
know what I'm sayin'?
That's German for
"sure thing", probably.
Thanks...
SUCKA!!
And now for some sweet
Gustav J. Monkey music.
[Big inhale]
[Failing to produce notes]
Huh.
My lips must be a little dry.
[Slurping, lip smacking,
and gargling]
[Frustrated puffing]
Why won't you play for me?!
Why?!
[Panting]
MYSTERIOUS VOICE:
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Cool down, daddio!
[Sustained/screamed]
It's a talking rock!!
[More screaming]
You can talk?!
Bingo, yarddog.
Mr. Cheapwad
doesn't think
my riffs are worth
the sniggets!
Excuse me, I am not
a Mr. Cheapwad!
Says you!
Maybe you need a
little reminder.
Feast your peepers on this
jumpin' flash jack-back...
Oh, that's nice!
Oh yeah!
Uh...
your point?
Sorry, monkeyman,
it's all one big
flashback for me.
[Scatting] Let me slip
you the straight skinny!
You're a cheap-skate!
Tight on the purse strings!
Your bro gets it,
so he gets the love.
Wait a sec -
You're the one
making the music...
Which means Wally's
a no-talent bum!
I don't think you're
digging my point.
Aren't I? I'm the best!
I'm the best!
* I miss my rocky...
Ow!
You're back!
[Baby-talk]
Hello my little rocky!
I missed you so much!
"Natural talent!"
Ha!
It was the rock making
the music, not you!
Go on! Tell him!
Say something!
Okay, just play!
Show us what you got!
[Fly buzzing]
Come on, rock,
rock it out, rock!
Why won't you play?!
Wait a second...
Maybe because it is,
uh, just a rock.
But it spoke to me!
It gave me the straight skinny,
whatever that means.
Oh, Gussy-Gus!
Poor, sad, deluded,
less-talented bro!
If you can't blow,
you'll never know!
[Laugh] Know what I'm sayin'?
* [Plays rock]
But you're not
really playing that!
Don't you see?
It's the rock!
He's making a fool
out of all of you!
[Scream]
Stupid rock... stupid Wally...
stupid Yay-OK.
Stupid ship... stupid space...
Stupid galaxy!
Stupid universe!
I have to find a way to prove
that rock is a lying
son of a boulder.
But how?
[Scatting]
Feelin' the power!
Rockin' the shower!
Scrub-a-dub-dub!
Rock, you are so busted!
Yay-OK! Quick!
To the showers.
Your cover's blown, rock!
Oh, I see, Gus...
Wally is even more talented
in his naked state.
What a natural -
Oof!
[Scream]
Hi, Gus!
No one can resist the sweet
temptress that is karaoke!
* [Jazzy tune]
* They're rocket monkeys,
monkeys in space! *
* They try to be heroes,
but they're easy to replace! *
Wally!
Yay-OK!
Yay-OK?
We're playing
monkey stew!
I'm the potato!
Whatever.
Just check this out!
Wow.
Nothing.
Submarine!
Hurray!
* [Rock singing]
[Gasp] Wally!
Yay-Ok! Rock!
Singing!
Singing rock!
A rock.
Very interesting.
Ah, who am I kidding?
Boring. Very boring.
I tell ya, sleepy.
[Stammering]
But... he... it...
Wow, Gus,
you really are tense.
What you need is some
sweet rock music.
* [Playing rock]
[Swooning sigh]
Ah, Wally...
Hey Wal, can I just see
that rock for a sec?
I see no reason
why not!
Great!
[Crazed laughter]
I'm the potato!
So, you won't play
for Gus, huh?
So Gus hasn't got
any talent, huh?!
So I'm a big ol'
cheapyskate, huh?!
I'll show you, you...
rock!
Whoa, bro!
Easy on the finish, man!
Sing your way outta
this one, buddy!
Not cool, man!
[Laughter]
Rock-a-bye-bye, baby!
Hope you like the
sound of MY music.
It's in the key of
[makes explosion sound].
Hey Gus, have you
seen my rock?
Let me see...
Is that it over there?
[Snicker]
Bro!
Why would you
do that?!
Because you sit there
and play that rock,
and it isn't really
you that's playing it.
And now it likes you
more than it likes me?!
And why would it
call me a cheapskate?
[Crying, bawling]
For shame,
Rocket Monkey Gus.
For shame!
To have a brother as
talented as Wally -
and for you to be
so untalented -
that is a gift!
That should
be treasured!
Darwin's nuggets!
Now I feel like
a pile of poop.
Fine.
I'll get your Rock back!
[Shushing]
[Slurping]
[Scatting]
[Bomb ticking]
Okay, Rock, Gus is here
to reluctantly save you.
Guilt's a bummer,
monkey man.
[Ding]
Oh yeah...
that.
[Scream]
[Crash]
Sorry, Wal.
This is all I could save.
Cool! Now there's
a piece for everyone!
Here!
* [Both playing
rock horns] *
Meh.
I'll take it.
[Braying noise]
YAY-OK:
Come on. Oh!
I'm bumping into everything.
I cannot manoeuvre myself.
[grunting]
Darn it, Rocket Monkeys...
your business and toys
and junks are everywhere!
Agh! Oy!
[sigh]
At least I still have
my own little sanctuary.
Hope you don't mind.
We're just temporarily
storing our stuff
in your room forever.
No Rocket Monkeys!
Your hoarding
is out of control!
This isn't hoarding!
It's extreme stuff-saving.
[whistle blows]
Stuff-saving?
That is what you call
this...this disaster?
Ah, everything is a mess!
I cannot even think
myself straight!
Okay, Yay-Ok,
just take a moment.
Just calm yourself.
[meditation sounds]
I know!
Why don't we have a yard sale?
I don't think so.
You don't know what
a good idea is.
You're a robot.
You don't have thoughts.
[cross-talk]
You don't know what things
are with your brain, Weirdo.
Think of the sniggets
you could make.
[crickets chirping]
Which you could use to purchase
even more useless stuff.
BOTH:
Yard sale!
Monkey yard sale!
Even though we're not
actually selling a yard!
And it's not really a sale,
because everything
is over-priced!
Excellent sales pitch.
Way to bring in the crowds.
Wow, generating
the excitement...
Okay, let's check out
the monkey merchandise.
One coat hanger,
a bag of toenail clippings,
eeh,
six pizza crusts,
and a stick with some type
of like a string tied to it.
This is what you're
selling, huh?
75 sniggets for an
empty pudding cup?
I mean, what kind of crazy
person would pay that?
I'll give you 85 sniggets
for the pudding cup.
Nice try, bucko.
Not for sale!
Oh! Wow!
This is going really
well, gentlemens.
Why don't I bring out more stuff
that you will never sell.
Oh goody!
More pudding cups,
I hope!
We're not just going
to give our stuff away!
Hey!
Ooo!
Retro pudding cup?
I'll give you
100 sniggets for it.
I'll give you 120.
I'll give you 150!
I'll give you 170!
I'll give you 190!
Okay, hear my out;
I'm gonna give
you less sniggets,
so we're going down
to ten sniggets,
but I'm giving you
all my blood.
I'll give you four
of my eyebrows
and a 7-foot long horse!
[neighs]
[indistinct cross-talk]
I hate to interrupt your
ridiculous haggling, but...
Where do you want me
to put these?
[gasp]
That voice!
Is it possible?
* FROM THE SCRAP YARDS
OF THE HEAVENS *
* THERE WAS BORN A LEGEND!
* PART BOT, ALL THUNDER
* TH-TH-TH-TH-THUNDERBOT!
Where do you want
me to put these?
[sigh]
* TH-TH-TH-TH-THUNDERBOT!
Hello!
Where do you want me
to put these?
Thunderbot!
Oh!
How much for the robot?
How dare you?
Friends don't sell friends.
What if I gave you this?
[whistle]
[angels singing]
[gibberish]
So we have a deal?
[squealing]
Monkeys,
you know I am GASI property.
I cannot be sold for profit--
[scream]
[sinister laugh]
Yay-Ok would be proud
because we sold something.
YAY-OK:
Not proud!
Someone help Yay-Ok!
[cackles]
After years of searching,
my creepy obsession
has finally paid off.
The one, the only Thunderbot.
And uh, what makes you think
I am this so-called Thunderbot?
Please, you're Thunderbot.
I got all your collectibles.
I got your action figure,
your plushie,
your trading cards,
your jock strap,
your bubble bath, your lipstick
and your deodorant!
I got your toothbrush,
I got your sponge...
Fine.
Okay.
So I was Thunderbot.
But I am not part of your
creepy nerd collection!
Hey!
I bought you fairsies and
squarsies from those monkeys,
and that means one thing...
Press conference!
Press
conference?
Where did that come from?
Did I miss something?
What is?
Who? What?
Thunderbot!
Oh. Over here!
Me! ME! Please!
Thunderbot!
Quick question over here!
Quick question!
Fine, okay.
I'll play along.
Hey! You...
over there?
The one who is not a nerd.
Gamester X from The Daily X!
How many episodes of "The
Adventures of Thunderbot"
did you make?
Too many.
In episode 65, when you
battled Sarcasmatron
for the Sword of Isosceles,
did you guys really
fall in love?
Just friends.
What happened to
your robo-horse, Zozo?
Rehab.
In the last episode
of Thunderbot
you were strapped
to a doomsday rocket
on a collision course with
the Blaze-omedra star.
Then the show just ended.
ANNOUNCER: Attention,
fans of Thunderbot.
This show has been canceled
due to its high
level of POOPINESS.
So what happened?
I'll tell you what happened,
the producers stiffed me
on the royalties.
Thanks for nothing, Ira!
Huh?
Oh, you mean
with the character?
Nothing.
It's only TV!
It is not real.
Not real?
NOT REAL!
I'm about to show you
just how real it is!
Monkeys!
Did you hear something?
Yeah, I did.
As the writer/
director/producer/
of the official
Thunderbot finale,
I want this done right,
people!
Give me screaming
for your life
and then a miraculous escape
from certain, fiery death.
[maniacal laughter]
MOTHER:
Myron!
Inside voice!
You're cruisin'
for a timeout, young man!
[sigh]
Sorry, Mom!
(quietly)
I'm not sorry!
I couldn't even
be less sorry right now...
Listen.
How 'bout I just
sign a glossy 8 by 10
and we'll call it
a day, huh?
Quiet on the set!
You will never succeed!
My monkeys will rescue me!
Now that was
a successful yard sale!
Absopooply, we didn't
even sell anything.
Except for that old timey robot.
What was his name again?
Why do I have to
remember everything?
Isn't Yay-Ok supposed
to clean up after us?
[crickets chirping]
Hey, that's his name!
We sold Yay-Ok!
We should get him to clean up.
Good idea, bro.
[screaming]
More tension,
Thunderbot!
[doorbell]
Where's my latte?
MOTHER:
Get the door, Myron!
I don't have
my face on yet!
(shouts)
I got it, Ma!
What do I have,
a sign on my back
that says
'breathe down this'?
Whoa!
Take back your bananas.
We want our robot.
Hey, Wal,
look!
[gasp]
It's Thunderbot's
thunder punch fists!
Take that!
[indistinct cross-talk]
No!
That's original packaging!
But we love Thunderbot!
TOY:
Ira, I want my residuals!
We used to watch it
all the time.
* FROM THE SCRAP YARDS
OF THE HEAVENS *
* THERE WAS BORN A LEGEND!
Where do you want me
to put these!
So where's Yay-Ok?
[sigh]
Open your eyes, monkey.
Yay-Ok is Thunderbot!
Hilarious.
Yay-Ok and Thunderbot
don't look anything alike!
[scream]
I forgot how
dangerous acting was.
Huh.
Whadya know?
Yay-Ok is Thunderbot!
And you think you know someone!
You are watching the official
Gamester X production
of the Thunderbot finale
which I wrote,
produced, catered,
and am currently directing.
I remember the series
being less screamy.
I blame the writing, producing,
directing and catering!
And the acting!
Criticism accepted!
Help, Monkeys!
Help!
You see, that's what's wrong
with this direction.
No super hero would say,
"Help, monkeys, help!"
Yeah, who asks monkeys
for help?
(chuckles)
We're useless.
MOTHER:
Myron!
Do your furry little friends
want some numnums?
(shouts)
Ma!
No one wants numnums!
I could go for some numnums.
Am I the only one here
that could go for numnums?
I'm in for numnums.
(shouts)
Cut!
[sigh]
Take five!
You gotta be kidding me
with this stuff.
No touchy!
You heard what he said,
no touchy!
[monkey shrieks]
[screaming]
Ugh!
Track left....
Your other left!
Okay turn the camera
upside down...
...and Dutch it!
Okay no sound.
No sound on this one.
No lights.
Okay give me a nod.
Give me a nod. Push in.
...and pull out...
Let's do a couple takes
without the cameras on.
Could you uh,
kill that light there
and then put the shadow
under his face?
Let's switch
personalities.
Just switch 'em
real quick.
but an anti-bounce
over his neck?
Can we get the boom
in the shot?
Can we get
the boom in the shot?
Can we get the boom out
of the shot, please?
Boom out!
Boom in!
Okay, just bring it in a bit...
Boom out!
I just wanna see
the tip of it...
Boom out!
Just a little bit
of boom in the shot.
Okay, but put
a furry thing on it.
Okay.
Numnums are here.
Where do you want me
to put these?
...put these...
[gasps]
Wally, did you hear
that delivery?
Now, that's acting!
Oh, I've got monkeybumps.
You should be
in the movies.
Well, I do fancy myself
the super hero-type.
I already
have the costume.
TH-TH-TH-THUNDERBOT!
You convinced me.
That part needs
a new hero... Me!
(shouts)
Cut!
Oh, my bolts!
That was close!
Sorry, kid, this just
isn't working out.
You're looking
a little rusty...
The whole screamy thing
is pretty played out...
and just everything
you're bring to it is...
[gag sound]
I don't like it!
Alright.
Tie me in tight!
[excited giggles]
This has to look real!
Happy to oblige.
All right!
ACTION!
[maniacal laugh]
I knew you'd rescue me.
Thank you, gentlemens.
For what?
You were terrible.
Your baby screams
were ruining the finale.
HEY MA!
LOOK AT ME!
I'M A STAR!
[loud explosion]
Guess we now know
how Thunderbot ends.
Stinko.
I've seen more emotional
depth in a teaspoon.
Yeah, and really.
I get it.
You fly into the star,
you die.
But what about the mother?
They don't even deal
with that part.
[organ music]
Cut!
You call that a tribute?
Come on, what,
do I gotta do everything here?
Okay, move the lights in.
Lets get a nice close-up.
Whaddya mean
we're out of time!
Might as well cast
my mom in this thing
for all the good you
guys are doing me... Ow!