- All right, William, you sit
over there in that seat.
- Hey, Bill.
- How you doing?
- Oh, hanging out.
God, getting ready for
the Arkansas football season.
-In 2015, as part of
a "Nathan for You" DVD release,
Comedy Central asked me
to record
an audio commentary track
for some of
my favorite episodes.
In one segment, I helped
a struggling souvenir shop
and in the process
met a professional Bill Gates
impersonator named Bill Heath.
- When we started
our computers...
back in the '80s,
it was huge--
in the business,
they were huge machines.
-I found him to be
a really interesting person,
so when it came time
to record the commentary
for his episode,
I invited him to join us
and share his favorite memories
from making the show.
- Yeah, the owner
of the shop,
I came in--
I was explaining to him
about how the computers
were founded
when we founded them
and so forth.
-But during
the recording
Bill's attention
seemed scattered.
He not only took a seven-minute
call from his phone company...
Right, people were posting
about the event on Twitter.
- Yes, I want to
lower the rate.
How long
will it be?
- William, who is--
who is on the phone?
- AT&amp;T.
Yeah, what's your number?
I'm gonna call you back
on this promotion.
-but he also
went into detail
about a long-lost love
from his past,
a woman named
Frances Gaddy.
- I should have married her,
everybody interfered.
- Who interfered?
- Oh, my mother, you know,
a lot of friends.
They--they--you know, mothers,
a lot of mothers
have picked out the girl
they want you to marry.
Well, it doesn't work
that way.
- Is that a regret
of yours?
- It's one of 'em, yeah,
I look back.
I should have
married her.
[sighs]
I don't know
where she is now.
I've been trying
to find her.
-I didn't think much of it
at the time,
but as the months
went on,
Bill began to show up
at the office unannounced
to deliver gifts...
- Oh, it's
a serving set.
- Yeah.
-grab a quick snack,
or just to hang out,
and the name Frances Gaddy
kept coming up.
Thoughts of this failed romance
from over 50 years ago
seemed to completely
consume him.
Frances?
I don't know.
Can I use the
bathroom quickly,
and then we'll talk
when I come out?
- Sure.
- Okay.
And in getting to know him,
I began to understand why.
At the age of 78,
Bill lived alone
and had never married.
His closest bond was with
his alma mater's football team,
the Arkansas Razorbacks.
- Each year
I give $3,000 total
for the Arkansas Razorbacks
athletic programs.
Whoo, pigs!
Sooey!
Razorbacks!
Number one.
-His lifestyle was modest
and very organized.
- This is a stack of
loan offers.
RISE preapproved
for $2,600.
Here's the same
RISE for $5,000.
$1,000 prequalified,
in your account $2,500.
-With such meticulous record
keeping in his daily life,
it was surprising that he had
no information about Frances
other than her name.
Have you looked for her?
I mean--
- I tried once
or twice, yeah.
-An exhaustive Internet search
turned up nothing.
If she had married someone,
it was likely she'd have
a different last name.
And that meant with over
600,000 women named Frances
currently living
in the U.S.,
the task of finding
the one Bill was looking for
would take an incredible amount
of time and effort.
But the challenge of solving
a near-impossible mystery
intrigued me.
Plus, there was something about
an old man
so filled with regret that was
hard for me to ignore,
and I realized
if I didn't help him do this,
no one would.
[somber music]
♪
It was becoming clear
that finding this woman
would take a lot more effort
than a Google search.
But before devoting
my time to this,
I wanted to see what
Bill's motivations were.
- Oh, I need to confess
a lot of things to her
about what--
between the time we--
the lapse of time
and fill in the gaps,
her gaps
and my gaps,
to put the puzzle
together.
- I mean, a best-case scenario,
what do you hope will happen?
- Well, I hope
I can find her.
- And then what?
What happens when you find her?
- Well, I'll go
from there.
- Well, what does
that mean?
- Well, if she's
married,
you have to accept it
that way.
- But if she's not?
- If she's not, well,
maybe we could get married...
[laughs]
finally.
- You still love her?
- Yeah, I do.
-I was moved by how
romantic of a tale this was.
- Love it hard to come by,
you know.
-The possibility of
reuniting Bill
with his long-lost love
was so cool.
So I told him
I had some good news.
I want to use the resources
of my show
to help you
find Frances.
- Well, that's--
I think that's a true friend
that would do that.
-But Bill hadn't seen
or spoken to Frances
in over 50 years,
leaving us with
very little to go on.
- You know, she married
on the rebound,
unhappy marriage,
she got a divorce,
and I think she got another
divorce, I don't know.
- So wait,
who did she marry?
- Charles something.
I don't remember his last name.
- She married
a Charles.
- Yes.
- But she could be
married again?
- She could be.
- You just don't know.
- I don't know.
-The only thing
he did know for sure
was her name
before she was married
and what she looked like
in 1961.
- Brown hair,
brown eyes.
-With no photos and just
a sketch of Frances
that Bill did
from memory...
So this is the woman
we're looking for?
♪
- Yes.
-it quickly
became clear
this was going to be
an uphill battle.
But Bill did recall one thing
that could be helpful.
- Last time I saw her was in
Little Rock in Arkansas.
I was working at
Moses Melody Shop,
the music record store.
-I felt that if I could get
Bill back to the city
where they first dated, it
might jog some of his memories.
So I booked us a flight
to Little Rock, Arkansas,
to begin our search
for Frances.
[mid-tempo music]
It had been some time
since Bill had been back
in his home state,
and he seemed enthusiastic
to return.
Are you excited, Bill?
- Yeah.
It's hometown, man.
I grew up here.
-And as I had hoped,
it wasn't long
before old memories began
to come back.
- God, mother used to
pick me up right there,
that station.
There was a plant
right there.
Dr. Pepper Company
right there, man.
Now, that's the old
West Side Junior High.
My uncle taught there.
-With Bill's past
fresh in his mind,
we headed downtown
to Moses Melody Shop,
the last place
Bill had seen Frances
over 50 years ago.
- It used to be right there,
the second building.
I don't think
it's there anymore.
Everything has
changed.
-Things had changed.
Moses Melodies was now
a wig store,
but once inside,
memories of that final
encounter with Frances
began to resurface.
- Well, there was
a counter, like, here.
I was right here,
and she came in that way.
I was behind
the counter here.
- Okay.
- She brought
her tape recorder.
That's the last
time I saw her.
-As he continued,
I began to understand
what a loss this was
for him.
- She cried, said,
"I'll love you to my grave."
I never will
forget that.
- That's what
she said to you?
- Mm-hmm, that's
what she told me.
- So why'd you never
see her again?
- She said, "You want your
career." I headed to Hollywood.
She said,
"You want your career."
Those are the breaks.
[chuckles]
-I was starting
to realize
why I was so drawn to
Bill's story.
As someone who also left
a lot behind
to pursue a career
in Hollywood,
I couldn't help but feel
an odd kinship with him.
But the fact
remained that
we still had nothing concrete
to go off of
besides a first name
and Bill's sketch.
- Yeah.
- White?
- White.
- She's white.
It was as if we were trying to
find a missing person.
This is a woman.
And it was hard to know
what would lead us to her
or where to even begin.
On the way back
to our hotel,
Bill wanted to take me by
his old high school.
- Central High, the integration,
nine black students.
They had to get
the federal troops in here
to enter them.
We always got along
with the blacks,
no problem.
It's too bad that
it had to come to this,
but it happened.
-It was neat to learn
a bit of the history
of Bill's high school,
but then something came up
that could be useful.
Did Frances go to
your high school?
- Um...
No, she went to
Dumas High School, I believe.
Dumas, Arkansas.
- Dumas.
It turned out that Dumas
was a town
just under two hours
from Little Rock,
and if I could get in touch
with their high school,
they'd most likely have
student records
or even an old yearbook that
could give us a clue.
But the school was closed
for the day
so we'd have to call
in the morning
In the meantime,
we checked into our hotel
in downtown Little Rock,
and after getting unpacked
and grabbing some dinner,
we decided to
call it a night.
[cell phone chimes off]
This is kind of
a fun trip, huh?
- Yeah.
- Just the boys.
- Mm-hmm.
- Can I ask you
something?
- Yes.
- What's your favorite memory
of Frances?
- Probably when we were
on the bed there together.
- When you were
on the bed together?
- Yeah.
- What did you do
on the bed?
- Well, I was trying to
have sex with her.
- Oh, cool.
All right,
should we go to bed?
- I guess so.
- All right,
good night, Bill.
- Good night.
- You gonna get
under the covers?
- Oh, I'm okay
right now. Thank you.
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪
-The next morning
while Bill was getting ready,
I decided to follow up
on our Dumas High School lead
when I hit
a bit of a snag.
I'm not a parent.
-Well, on our campus,
to be--
to even be here
as a visitor
you're supposed to be
a parent or a guardian.
-The school told me they
wouldn't release
any of their
student records
and their strict
visitor policy
prevented us from
even coming by
and looking at
an old yearbook.
I guess
a 78-year-old man
trying to track down
a former student
that he's in love with
does raise a few red flags.
But after doing a bit of
research on the city of Dumas,
something occurred to me
that could possibly be
our way in.
Dumas' main claim to fame
was that
they were the shooting location
for the 2012
Matthew McConaughey movie
"Mud."
It was clearly a point of pride
for everyone in Dumas.
So if we could pretend that
we were in town
to shoot a sequel
to "Mud,"
called "Mud 2: Never Clean,"
I was confident the city
would grant us access
to any location
in Dumas,
including their
high school
with its archive
of yearbooks.
But to pull this off,
we'd need some credibility,
so I contacted an actor named
Richard Ledbetter
who could be seen faintly
in the background
of a scene in
the original "Mud"
to come in and audition for
what he believed
was a starring role
in "Mud 2."
So firstly, we loved
your work in "Mud" one.
- Thank you.
- I'm assuming you remember
Bill Goldstein
from the original shoot.
- I don't know that we met.
I don't think--
Your face is--both of your faces
are very familiar.
- Oh, yeah. Well, we were
around all the time,
so I'm sure you--
you saw us here and there.
- It's a fantastic movie.
Great job.
- Thank you.
-For his audition,
I'd written some lines
for a scene from "Mud 2" that
Bill would read with him.
- [clears throat]
What's going on here?
This place is
absolutely a mess.
- I know.
- We have to clean
this high school library up.
It's covered
in Mud again.
- And I thought things
were dirty last time,
but this time
it's filthy.
- It's absolutely
ridiculous,
all this mud.
- Great.
That was--
- He got into the lines
very well.
The way he read it lightly
and then he went into
a stronger phase
of the wording.
- Okay.
Let him know.
You can tell him.
- You've got the part.
- Fantastic.
Thank you.
-With an actor
from the original movie
now part of our team,
we contacted Dumas High
to say we were in town
scouting locations
for the "Mud" sequel.
And as I expected, they gladly
opened their doors to us.
He was in the scene
with the motorcycle
driving beside
the train tracks.
- Okay.
- You could see him
in the background
with the shiny hair.
With the school staff
starstruck,
they gave us
the VIP treatment,
taking us on a tour
of their entire campus
to show off what
the high school had to offer.
But what they didn't know
was that our real purpose
was to find
their old yearbooks.
This is a great
location.
Where do you keep
the yearbooks?
We told them "Mud 2" was
a 1950s period film
and that their yearbooks would
be a helpful visual reference
for re-creating
the era.
- Hey, there's '57.
-Frances was at Dumas High
in the late '50s.
So when we found a '57,
I knew we had what we needed.
Would it be possible
for our props department
to look at
one of these?
- I don't know
why not.
-And with that,
Bill and I had pulled off
a genuine heist.
So once we got to
a secure location,
it was time to check out
what we had.
- There she is.
[somber music]
That's her.
- That's her?
- Yes, that is her.
♪
Golly.
She--
[laughs]
That's her.
It's her.
♪
That's her.
-The yearbook would be
an amazing resource.
Not only did it have the names
of her classmates
that we could try
to track down,
but we also now had
a photo of her,
and that meant there might be
a way to figure out
what Frances
looked like today.
So I contacted a professional
age-progression specialist
who I had worked with in
the past named, Cornelius Ladd,
flew him out to Arkansas,
and booked him a hotel room
adjacent to ours
where he set up everything
he needed to get to work.
- This is, um...
two of the same
printer.
- Right, right.
You always want to have
a backup when you travel.
- Oh, okay.
That's great.
Good to have a...
backup.
- Right.
Right.
-But after giving him
the photo,
Cornelius pointed out that
this job would require
a more advanced technique.
- The last one,
we only age progressed
those children ten years.
- Right.
- But now, you're talking about
50 years,
and the main thing about
age progression is the gravity.
What makes people age
is gravity.
If there were no gravity--
for instance,
if we all lived
in outer space,
as we will one day,
your face would have--
would never change.
You'd always look like
how you look right now.
- Okay.
- There would be no gravity
pulling on your face.
With this picture
I'm working with,
or this face or this person,
I'm working with gravity.
- Right, okay.
- As a side note, though,
you might find this interesting.
Scientists are predicting that
in the next 30 years
we'll be able to walk into
a doctor's office,
get a treatment that's
affordable to everybody,
and you'll be able to live to be
600 years on average.
-I gave Cornelius
a Jumpdrive
with a scanned copy of
Frances' yearbook photo on it
and then left him
to his work.
[upbeat music]
And a few hours later,
he called me back in
with his completed rendition
of what Frances
would look like today.
So this is her...
- I aged it--
- 75?
- 76, yeah.
75, 76 years old.
And even at--
even at 76,
she still looks--she's
still an attractive person.
- Right, yeah.
- I think.
- How--how accurate
would you say this is
of what Frances
looks like today?
- I would say
it's a 95% chance
she looks
just like that.
- 95%?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
I didn't know if
I'd ever fully understand
the science
of age progression,
but it was
the best clue we had
as to what a 76-year-old
Frances might look like.
So I brought Bill
the updated photo
to see what he thought.
- Oh, my gosh.
- That's what we got.
I don't know if
it's 100% accurate,
but there's not that many
age progressionists around
so, you know, we have to take
what we can get, I guess.
- Who did this?
- Cornelius Ladd.
If there was a chance Frances
still lived in the area,
I felt it was worthwhile
to do a poster campaign
while we chased down
other leads.
So we put up
hundreds of fliers
throughout Little Rock
and Dumas
in the hope
someone would recognize her
and give us a call.
The next morning, Bill decided
to relocate from the hotel
to his niece Shelly's house
who lived on the outskirts
of Little Rock.
She invited him
to stay with her
and I was curious to meet
a family member of Bill's
as I thought it might help me
gain insight
into his past,
and more importantly, Frances.
- Hi.
- Hello!
- Hey there.
- How are you?
- Fine.
Good to see you.
- Good to see you.
Oh.
Y'all come on in.
Drake's married and moved to
northwest Arkansas.
Natalie and--
- Who?
- Drake.
- Oh, yeah.
- And Dakota, as you know,
and Dylan are still in school.
So we're--
we're good.
Chris and I are finally
empty nesters.
- Finally got
freedom, huh?
- Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
So no,
but we're doing good so.
- Well, that color
in the dining room,
you didn't have that
when I was here, did you?
- I did have that
when you were here, yeah.
- That's nice.
- Thank you.
-After some catching up
with Shelly,
Bill headed upstairs to his
grand-nephew Dakota's bedroom
to unpack
and get settled.
Meanwhile, Shelly brought me
into the kitchen
to show me some
old family albums.
That's Bill?
- That's Bill.
Isn't he cute?
- Look at that haircut.
- [laughs]
Look at that hat.
So this is
Easter 1939,
and that's Bill.
- What a cutie.
- I know.
That's a picture
of him in, I think--
- This is Bill?
- Uh-huh,
in his younger years.
- No.
- Yeah.
Look at that hair.
- Oh, my God.
- Mm-hmm.
-I was stunned to see that Bill
was once incredibly handsome,
and for the first time,
his Hollywood aspirations
started to make sense.
So I was hopeful Shelly would
be able to shine more light
on this man who left
the love of his life
for a shot at fame.
- Bill's dad died
when he was five years old,
and his dad,
I think,
was in his 50s
when he died,
so he was fairly young.
- Huh.
- And he really struggled
emotionally
trying to
deal with that.
And I think there's just
different points of his life
that he just kind of felt,
you know,
that maybe he's been entitled
to certain things
and life doesn't always
work out that way.
I think that's harder for him
to move past.
- Bill's memories about Frances
are very foggy...
- Mm-hmm.
- and vague...
- and there's a lot of
half information.
And so I was hoping maybe you
might know stuff or--
Has he mentioned her
to you?
- Briefly, but yeah,
briefly, he has.
Evidently, I think
he dated her
and my grandmother
didn't want him to marry her.
Is that what
he's told you?
- He said something
like that, yeah.
I get a sense he really regrets
not marrying her.
- Yes.
- He says he should have
married her.
- Yes.
And Bill keeps
in touch with--
I mean, you know, he has his
little, literally, black book
and he keeps in touch with
a lot of people:
relatives, friends.
He's very, very good
about that.
So the fact that
he lost touch with her
is kind of interesting
to me.
-It was curious that Shelly,
who knew Bill so well,
thought it was odd he hadn't
kept in touch with Frances.
And as we kept talking,
the conversation got
even more interesting.
How long has Bill
been doing
Bill Gates
impersonations?
- Um...
I guess since
he's been on the show.
- I mean--what?
- I guess since
he's done him for you guys.
To our knowledge,
he's never done any before.
- Before
"Nathan for You"?
- I don't think he's done
any impersonations.
Did he say he has?
- He told me he did it
professionally
when I first met him.
- Oh, I don't know.
To my knowledge, he hasn't,
be he--
here again,
he could have done something
and I wouldn't
know about it.
- Huh.
Bill was even more of an enigma
than I had expected.
It was hard to tell
what was true about him,
and it crossed my mind that
his relationship with Frances
might not be all
that he made it out to be.
If I was gonna continue
dedicating my time
to helping this man,
I needed to know that
he was being honest with me.
What's your favorite nut?
- Peanuts.
- I love peanuts.
- Yeah, I like it.
- Can I ask you
something?
- Go ahead.
- How long have you been
a Bill Gates impersonator for?
[upbeat music]
- Oh, four years, I think,
wasn't it?
Why do you ask that?
- When I first
met you...
- Yeah.
- you told me
you impersonated Bill Gates
for a living.
- Well...
did I say
for a living?
- You do this
for a living, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
Yeah.
- Well, that must have been
a misunderstanding.
- By you or by me?
- Well, you know,
between two people
it could be
a misunderstanding.
- So was it a misunderstanding
or did you lie to me?
- [laughs]
I never lied to you.
- You said you were
a professional Bill Gates.
- I don't know where
you got that.
- It's in the show.
♪
You told me
on camera.
♪
Are you exaggerating anything
about this relationship
with Frances that
I should know about?
- No.
No exaggeration.
Everything I've told you
is the truth.
- You've told me
everything?
- Well, everything
that I can remember,
but if I think of anything else,
I'll let you know.
♪
- You weren't like a stalker
or anything, right?
- No.
[laughs]
- Okay.
- No.
You think I was--
look like a stalker?
[dramatic music]
-It wasn't the most
reassuring conversation.
Bill had an odd way of
communicating
that was hard to decipher.
- Here I go
digging in again.
♪
-And as I left that day,
I found it hard to know
what to really believe
about this relationship
from so long ago.
♪
- Her--her name
is Frances?
Do you know her name before
she got married by any chance?
Okay.
The next day I got a call
from someone
who had seen one of
our Frances posters
and thought it might be
his great-grandmother.
Do you know what year
she was born?
She's old, right?
He didn't know many details
about her past,
but before putting us
in touch with her,
he asked to meet us
during his lunch break.
Okay, thanks so much.
All right.
So I hurried over to
Shelly's house
to update Bill
on the news.
So a guy
named Jake called
because he saw
the Frances posters.
His great-grandma's name
is Frances.
She has a different
last name,
but he doesn't know
what her name was.
- He thinks
that's her?
- He doesn't know.
[dramatic music]
♪
[dog barking]
Jake?
- Yes, sir.
- Hey.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hi,
how are you?
Nathan.
- Nice to meet you.
- Bill.
- You don't remember
her maiden name?
- No. I'm--I'm
her great-grandson so,
and she's been
married--
well, she was actually
married a couple of times.
- Who, she was?
- Yes.
- Remember, I told you that
she was married twice.
- Right. How--she was
married twice?
- More than once for sure.
- Okay.
- She's out in Roland.
- Well, could I
meet her now?
- Possibly, yeah.
-After showing Jake that we
were good for the reward money,
he was willing
to help us out.
So he gave us his
great-grandma's address
and we headed
across town
to see if this was
the Frances
that Bill had been
searching for.
I think we're close.
[dramatic music]
You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[birds chirping]
[knock on door]
- Hello.
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- You're Frances?
- I'm Frances.
I'm Frances Watson.
- What was your maiden name?
Was it Gaddy?
- No, my maiden name
was Aplin.
- Oh, okay.
I was looking for
a Francis Gaddy.
- No.
Come--come in,
I'm sorry.
I'm not--I'm not meaning to
make you stand out here
on the street corner.
- Hi, I'm Nathan.
- Hi, Nathan.
- Hi.
- I'm Frances.
- Hi, nice to
meet you.
Is this--
is this the--
- No.
- So this woman
doesn't ring a bell?
Okay.
- Could I use
your restroom?
- Just a moment and let me see
if there's anybody in it
because there's more than
one person in this house so.
- Okay.
- You can't wait?
- Well, when
the bladder's full,
you feel better
when you empty it
even though
you could wait.
- I'll--I'll wait
outside, Bill.
- God bless you.
- Thank you.
I appreciate all your help.
♪
- Hey, you all good?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- It wasn't her,
though.
♪
- How was
her bathroom?
- Mm, it was
all right, you know,
but it could have
been cleaner.
-After doing some research
in the phone book,
I discovered that
there was no one
with the first name Frances
that still lived in Dumas.
I was hopeful that
one of her old classmates
might still have
a connection to her
but I was struggling to find
any that were still alive
who would respond
to my emails.
While we were in town,
Bill attended his 60-year
high school reunion
at Little Rock Central High.
- Oh, hello!
-Dozens of his old classmates
who still lived in the area
came out to catch up,
share stories,
and take photos.
Seeing all of Bill's
old friends reconnect
gave me an idea
that maybe something like this
would be a way
to get Frances' classmates
to come to us.
In the yearbook we had,
Frances was a sophomore.
So I designed an invite for
a Dumas High School
class of 1959
57-year reunion,
printed out
thousands of copies,
and then met up with a group
of local boys with bikes
to distribute them in the hopes
that anyone from the yearbook
who was still in town
would come to the event.
All right, so which one
of you guys is the leader?
- He's the boss.
- You're the leader?
- Yeah.
- I'm gonna talk to you then.
- All right.
- I'm gonna need
these fliers distributed
to every home
in Dumas, okay?
- All right.
- Now, I don't want you guys,
you know, throwing them in
the trash and saying you did it.
I really need them
to go to every home, okay?
- All right.
You got it.
- Got it?
- Got it.
- Okay. You guys seem like
good boys, so I can trust you.
All right.
- Sounds good.
- Great.
- Yes, sir.
-So with the invites
being delivered,
I rented a church social hall
and began preparations.
We decided it would be best
if Bill attended
posing as
a fellow student
so he could blend in
and ask about Frances
without arousing
suspicion.
Are you cool to go
undercover again?
- Yeah.
-So I picked someone
in the yearbook
who Bill somewhere
resembled...
You kinda
look like him.
and then we spent the afternoon
practicing his portrayal
using the information
we had.
- Hi, I'm Alex Sanford.
You might remember me
from the chess club,
the glee club.
And we all were
in high school together,
and I just
want to say
happy Dumas
class reunion.
-Bill was pretty convincing
as Alex,
but I also needed him to
memorize facts
about other members
of the class
that he might
encounter.
Tommy Peacock.
- Uh...
glee club, track.
- No, basketball,
band, and track.
- Basketball, band,
and track.
- Got it?
- Mm-hmm.
-He was still
a little shaky,
but it would have to do,
because before long,
the night of the reunion
was upon us.
We had successfully transformed
the church social hall
I had rented into a ballroom
fit for Cinderella herself,
and Bill looked like the
spitting image of Alex Sanford
in the thick-rimmed,
nonprescription glasses
we had purchased from
Sam's Club.
So while we waited for
guests to arrive,
Bill hid outside while
I changed into the outfit
of the school mascot,
the Dumas Bobcat,
so I could covertly
come to Bill's aid
if he ever needed help.
[big band music]
♪
We only got a few RSVPs,
but I was hopeful
one of these people
would have kept in touch
with Frances over the years
and perhaps even know
her whereabouts.
So once the room had filled
and the guests were mingling,
it was time for Bill
to make his entrance.
[playing "When the Saints
Go Marching In"]
♪
- Alex Sanford, Doris,
it's been a while.
I'm a neurosurgeon.
-Before asking anyone
about Frances,
I had Bill make
some small talk
to make sure
he was blending in.
- Well, I can't believe I'm
sitting here with Tommy Peacock,
basketball, band,
and track.
- [laughs]
I was a better
tenor sax player
than I was at basketball
or track runner.
- Are you still
running track?
- No, sir.
- No.
-But I knew that Bill would
still have to do more
to be fully embraced
by the group.
- Grade school,
wasn't it?
-From my research,
I learned that Dumas
had an unofficial town anthem
called "I'm a Ding Dong Daddy
from Dumas."
So before the event,
I rehearsed it with Bill
knowing it would be
a surefire way
of proving
he was a local.
And with the song lyrics hidden
on teleprompter
behind the Arkansas flag,
I signaled Bill
to hit the stage
to cement
his insider status.
[jazz music]
♪
- ♪ Yeah, I'm a ding dong daddy
from Dumas ♪
♪ And you ought to
see me do my stuff ♪
♪ I'm a fella
from Horner's Corner ♪
♪ Can you [stammers]
♪ I'm a paper cuttin' cutie
got a gal named Katy ♪
♪ She's a little heavy lady
and I call her baby ♪
♪ I'm a ding dong daddy
from Dumas ♪
♪ And you ought to see me
do my stuff ♪
♪ Yes a ding dong daddy
from Dumas ♪
♪ And you ought to see me
do my stuff ♪
-The performance
was a hit,
and it seemed like even
the most skeptical in the group
couldn't deny they were
looking at a local.
♪
So with Bill in
their good graces,
it was time for him to start
asking about Frances.
[cheers and applause]
- Thank you.
- Whoo!
- Alex Sanford.
Nice to see you again.
Have you ever heard anything
from Frances Gaddy?
No.
Whatever happened to
Frances Gaddy?
You ever
hear from her?
-But no one Bill talked to had
seen or heard from her
since high school.
Some thought she had moved
out of state years ago
but no one was sure.
- Where is she now?
You haven't heard
anything, period.
-If Frances had left
the state,
this search would become
exponentially more difficult,
and by the end
of the night,
I was having
serious doubts
that we would ever find
this woman.
These are from 1960?
- Yes.
- All of these are
from Frances?
- Frances.
-While going through
some storage
at his older sister Betsy's
house over the weekend,
Bill has discovered
dozens of letters
that Frances has written him
between 1960 and '61.
[somber piano music]
♪
- "Dear Bill, just a note to say
I'm thinking about you
"as usual tonight.
"I'm all alone tonight
and I wish you were here,
"but your picture is
sitting on my other pillow.
"Each time that I look up
and see your picture,
"it reminds me of how much
that I love you.
"It seems like a thousand years
since I've talked to you.
"I wish that it was possible
for us to see each other
"but it isn't.
"I think about you a lot.
"Some day we will be able
to have each other
"and we will appreciate
the value
"of a pure and true love
"that we both have worked
and waited so long for.
"My love is pure and clean
for you, darling,
and only for you."
- That's a strong
statement.
♪
- She was in love
with you, Bill.
♪
It was the first real evidence
of their relationship
I had seen,
but as I kept reading,
I realized there was
a lot more going on here
than Bill had led me
to believe.
"Dearest Bill,
"I'm sorry I haven't written to
you sooner this week.
"I'm warning you,
"I won't listen to this
much longer.
"I am disgusted with you
"of all this talk and gossip
"about you and Gloria.
- You and who?
- Gloria?
- Was her name
mentioned there?
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah.
- Who's Gloria?
- That was a woman.
- Were you
cheating on her?
- I think we went out
a few times.
-These letters chronicled
the breakdown of a relationship
that was far more complex
than the storybook version
Bill had given me.
and it did
make me wonder
if there was anything else
he was hiding.
"I know I'm not beautiful
and I'm not an actress."
- Oh, she was beautiful,
come on.
- "There are many things
I do not know about you.
Bill, I can't believe that
you're playing with my love."
- Yeah.
Well...
- Why does she say
she doesn't know you?
"There are many things
I do not know about you."
What does that mean?
- I don't know.
I--
Maybe she couldn't
figure out me.
- Can you
figure out you?
- [chuckles]
Myself?
Sometimes I wonder.
[dramatic music]
- And you find yourself
in a different place...
a place where you were
when you were 20 years old...
when you were attending
the First Baptist Church
in Little Rock, Arkansas.
And take a look down
at your feet...
and notice what
you're wearing.
-I had booked Bill
some sessions
with a local hypnotherapist
in the hopes it could dig up
some memories
that would help me
understand this man.
But after
several sessions,
all he seemed to recall
were old statistics
about the Arkansas Razorbacks.
- It was a bad call.
We should have won the game.
Should have
won the game,
and...
it was 15-14 was
the final score.
- Wow.
-Meanwhile, I'd been going
through the letters
Frances had sent Bill
nearly 60 years ago
trying to piece together
the details
of what I was beginning
to understand
had been a very complex
relationship.
Frances was head over heels
for Bill,
and I was struck by how much
she believed in him,
his career,
and their future together.
-Each day makes me
love you more
It's hard to explain.
In a way
it is unexplainable.
We can work together for the
kind of future that we want.
I realize that it will be
a long, hard struggle
to reach your goal
as an actor and singer,
but someday you will reach it
with God's help.
You will make it.
-But as hopeful
as she was,
there were some passages
that gave me pause.
-One that I'll have
for the man that I marry
will be purity.
If you don't want a girl
like that, I'm sorry.
I knew that you wanted to know
just how far that I would go.
Well, you know now.
Let us drop that subject now.
-In these letters,
Bill almost seemed like
a different person
than the man I knew.
-I don't believe
you can love anyone
if you don't respect them.
-And I couldn't help
but wonder
if he acted differently
around women.
If there was a potential of
reuniting these two,
I wanted to make sure that Bill
would act appropriately.
There's this guy, Bill,
that was--
he's, like, searching for
this long-lost love.
-Okay.
-So I found
someone online
who was willing to
go on a date with Bill
so I could observe his behavior
in a romantic setting.
Just so you know, he's--
he's very old.
Like, extremely old.
-[laughs]
I have a lot of clients
that are widowed
or a lot
that are widowed,
divorced, newly divorced.
[laughs]
-Her name was Maci,
and even though I didn't know
much about the escort business,
she was cool with my request to
have the date with Bill
be only talking
with no touching.
-Yeah,
mm-hmm.
-So I made a booking through
her website
at her flirtation rate
of $350 an hour
and then met up with Bill
to see if I could get him to
agree to a date with Maci.
I thought it might be nice for
you to have
some companionship,
you know,
someone to
hang out with.
So I decided to book you
a session
with an escort.
- [laughs]
Really?
Escort service?
- Yeah, she's
a professional escort.
- No,
I'm sorry.
- You don't
want that?
- I hate to use
that term,
you gotta know
what you're sticking it in.
- Jesus, Bill.
- That's right.
- Even after I told Bill it
wasn't supposed to be sexual,
he declined, saying it went
against his values.
- Sodom and Gomorrah sin.
- A sin?
- Yes.
-It was too bad Bill didn't
want to do it
but since we had already
paid her,
I felt it might be worth
interviewing Maci
to see if she had any insights
into the mind-set
of old, single men.
So later that day,
she agreed to meet up with me
for an on-camera chat.
- I've never
done this, so...
- You've never
been on camera.
- Like--no.
- Oh, really?
- [laughs]
Never.
- Is it weird for you?
- It is
a little weird, yeah.
- Okay.
Are you okay with it?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- Okay.
- It's just different.
-It took a little time
for Maci to get comfortable
with the cameras,
but she soon volunteered
to tell me about
what she does.
- A lot of IT people,
a lot of, like,
corporate America finance.
- That's who you see
the most.
- Attorneys, doctors.
- Oh, wow.
What about judges?
- I've met a judge,
I have.
- Really?
- I've met a preacher.
I've met--
[laughs]
I've actually met
two preachers.
- Met, meaning,
like, they--
- Yeah.
-I was surprised to learn that
the escort business
was a lot more normal
and accepted
than I initially thought.
- Like, I meet
some really great people
and they'll want to
keep in touch.
Like, they'll send emails and be
like, "Hey, how are you doing?"
- Really?
- "Hope everything's okay."
Yeah.
If I feel like
I'm gonna connect with you,
I know I'm gonna have
a good time,
and you're probably gonna have
a good time, too.
-Maci's perspective was
fascinating,
but she also wanted to know
more about me.
I make a show called
"Nathan for You" on--
- Okay.
- and it's one Comedy Central.
It's--
- Is it funny?
Is it like
a funny thing?
- I mean,
I hope sometimes.
- [laughs]
- I don't know.
Do you think
I'm funny?
- I don't know.
You seem kind of
serious right now.
- Do you want to see
some of the show?
I have--
- Yeah.
- I have it in my computer
in my backpack.
- Yeah, I'll watch it.
- You want to?
- Yeah.
- Okay,
I'll go get it.
- Okay.
- All right, wait here.
-My name is
Nathan Fielder,
and I graduated from one of
Canada's top business schools
with really good grades.
Now, I'm using
my knowledge
to help struggling
small business owners...
- Was that actually
your grades?
-competitive world.
Maci seemed to enjoy
my show.
- You're a little funny.
- Okay.
- Kind of mean but...
- Mean?
- but you're a little funny.
Yeah.
- What do you mean?
- You lied to
every last one of them.
- I mean,
it's business.
- You're like mean funny.
[laughs]
- It's business,
right?
- You're right, yeah.
-But eventually
she had to get going,
so we said
our good-byes.
Bye, Maci.
- Bye.
[upbeat music]
-Without any
promising leads to pursue,
I found myself stuck
in a strange city
with a lot of free time
on my hands.
I spent most of my nights
staying in
and watching TV
or going out to a nearby bar
to chat up the locals.
What does?
Oh, your watchband
wears out?
Yeah, that--
that's not good.
But overall, I found the social
interactions to be lacking,
and I realized the only
interesting conversation
I'd had in a long time
was with Maci.
So I decided to
call her up
and see if she wanted
to hang out again.
-Hello.
- Hi, Maci?
-Hey.
- I had
a really good time
talking to you in the park
and stuff.
I was wondering if you would
want to hang out again
or...
-Well, it's $350
for the hour.
You just let me know
when you want to book.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- Good.
How are you?
- Good to see you.
- This is for you.
- We don't do that
in public, but it's okay.
- Oh, okay, really?
- [laughs]
Yes.
- Okay, when do I--
I didn't know.
I just wanted
to make sure.
- It's a gift card
or a gift bag.
- Oh, what
do you mean?
- So it doesn't look
funny in public.
- What am I
supposed to do?
- [laughs]
- Oh, you say--
- When you're
in public--
- You give
a gift card.
- Like a card,
like a greeting card.
- Oh, okay. Okay,
okay, I know for next time.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
I'm so--yeah.
It was a little odd to be
paying someone
for their company,
but Maci had a way
of making it feel normal.
- I watched some more
of your stuff.
- Really?
- I did.
- What'd you think?
- Okay, so...
[laughs]
I watched the...
Ghost Realtor.
- Oh, yeah.
- That one was
really funny.
- Thank you, Maci.
That's really nice
of you to say.
I had a really fun evening
with Maci,
and after the hour was up, I
knew I wanted to see her again.
So over the next week,
I set up a couple more dates.
Happy birthday.
- [laughs]
Thank you.
- I did it right,
right?
- You did. You're learning.
- Okay.
This is the type of place
you'd propose to someone.
- Oh, you're not gonna
propose, are you?
- No, I'm not.
- Okay, good.
[laughs]
- I'm just saying, it's the
type, you know what I mean.
- It is kind of
the type of place.
- Yeah.
You have a nice laugh.
- I actually hate
my laugh.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- I think you have
a nice laugh.
- It's awkward,
I don't know.
- No, you have
a nice laugh.
- Well, thank you.
- You're welcome.
[sighs]
- Bye, Maci.
- Bye.
- Okay,
see you soon.
- See ya.
-We had been in Arkansas
for several weeks now
and I was starting to
lose sight
of what I was
even doing here.
I felt unfocused, just filming
things for no reason
in the hope something
interesting might happen.
We had accumulated
hundreds of hours of footage
but I couldn't tell
if this search for Frances
would amount to anything.
- Can you switch to
Fox News?
-A part of me wondered if Bill
was just a bored old man
looking for an adventure
to keep himself busy
and if I was just
a bored younger man
who also wanted
an adventure
because he was tired of doing
the same show
for four seasons.
[somber music]
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
[laughs]
- Okay.
Apparently they shot
"Gone with the Wind" here.
- I've never
seen it.
-And the more
we kept shooting things,
the harder it was to tell
where the show ended
and life began.
- Just do it again.
Okay, do it again.
[laughs]
- No, only twice.
- You want me
to hold your hand?
- Do you want to
hold my hand?
- Kind of, yeah.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Your hands
are cold.
- I know.
- Does that make you
uncomfortable?
- No.
- Okay.
- I like it.
- Good.
-Near the end of
one of our hangouts,
Maci asked if I wanted
our next date
to be
a little more private.
- You just
let me know.
- Let you know what?
- That that's what
you want to do.
- So I just--
just let you know...
- Yeah.
- what I want
and then--
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[upbeat music]
♪
- [breathes deeply]
Hello.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hey. Good.
How are you?
- Good.
Nice to see you.
- Good to see you.
Come on in.
[upbeat dance music]
-♪ Down, dig down, dig
diggy diggy down down diggy ♪
♪ Down, dig down, dig diggy
diggy down, diggy diggy ♪
-♪ Down, dig down, dig
diggy diggy down down diggy ♪
♪ Down, dig down, dig diggy
down down down down down ♪
-♪ Down, dig down, dig
diggy diggy down down diggy ♪
♪ Down, dig down, dig diggy
diggy down, diggy diggy ♪
-♪ Down, dig down, dig
diggy diggy down down diggy ♪
♪ Down, dig down, dig diggy
diggy down ♪
-♪ Down, dig down, dig
diggy diggy down down diggy ♪
♪ Down, dig down, dig diggy
diggy down, diggy diggy ♪
-♪ Down, dig down, dig
diggy diggy down down diggy ♪
♪ Down, diggy diggy
- [laughs]
- [exhales sharply]
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
- [laughs]
Okay. Good.
- I like you.
- I like you, too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
Cool.
[somber music]
We had been contacting
local cemeteries
to see if they had anyone with
the last name Gaddy
buried there.
At first, we weren't getting
much traction,
but then a promising lead
emerged.
We discovered that there was
a Gaddy family grave plot
on the outskirts
of Dumas.
- Here it is.
-It wasn't Frances,
but after Bill took
a closer look,
the name seemed to
ring a bell.
- Well, now that I'm
looking at the names
and the dates here,
it's a possibility
it could be her parents.
I vaguely remember
her father's name.
- What was it?
- Well, I thought
it was Robert.
I don't know about
Crews.
-If Bill was
remembering correctly,
and this was
Frances' father's gravestone,
there's a chance his obituary
would contain information
about any
surviving children.
So the next day we headed to
the Little Rock Public Library
to look at
their newspaper archives
from 1982.
That's it?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- See, that goes under there,
under the glass,
and then under here.
[indistinct]
- Like that?
- Yeah.
[somber music]
♪
Oh, wait,
here it is.
Robert Crews Gaddy
age 63,
of Texarkana, Texas,
formerly of Little Rock.
Survivors are
two daughters,
Frances Munroe
of North Musk--
Muskegon, Michigan.
-With this information,
we were able to track down
the Facebook page
of a Fran Munroe who
lived in Bellaire, Michigan.
- My God.
[laughs]
You think that's her?
- Oh, my God, Bill.
- Oh!
[laughs]
- Look,
Dumas Senior High.
- Yeah. That's gotta
be her right now.
[laughs]
- Class of 1959.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's her.
- 100%.
- I would say 100%.
-I had to admit
that even at 76,
she was stunning
and surprisingly similar to
Cornelius' age progression.
- I can't believe they
got this up.
[laughs]
- Look at you.
You look like
a schoolboy again.
- [laughs]
Golly.
Whoo!
-But then we found something
that put a damper
on Bill's excitement.
That's her husband.
- Shoot.
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
Let's see
what he looks like, though.
-We had always known
this was a possibility,
but it seemed to bring out
a side of Bill
that I had
never seen before.
- She could have done better
than that.
He's not Mr. Good Looking,
I don't think.
- Well, that's not
very nice to say.
- I'm sorry,
but I didn't mean it that way.
He looks like
he's overweight.
-Bill became fixated on
Frances' husband.
- He's an attorney.
BA in English, football,
track captain,
glee club.
Gee.
[laughs]
I should have
married her.
Should have
-And he started to
get ideas in his head.
- Well, we
go to Michigan.
- What?
- We go there.
Meet her in person.
Rehash what
should have been.
- But she's married now.
- She could get a divorce
and marry me.
♪
- Okay.
[exhales sharply]
[laughter]
Oh, all right.
♪
- She loved me
to her grave.
She said it,
and that old saying,
it's never too late.
-I didn't really know
what to make
of what Bill
was telling me.
He seemed undeterred by the
fact that Frances had a husband
and just kept repeating
the promise she had made to him
nearly 60 years ago.
- That's pretty strong words,
I'll love you to my grave.
Well, she said she would love me
to her grave.
Isn't that
pretty strong love?
Remember, she said
she'd love me to her grave.
-And for the first time
since agreeing to help Bill,
I didn't know
what to do.
-Bill was dead set
on going to Michigan
to profess his love
to Frances.
I knew he felt strongly
about her,
but I hadn't considered
the possibility
that Bill would try to get her
to divorce her husband.
Do you think there's a chance
she'd do that?
- There's a chance.
It's the roll
of the dice.
7 come 11.
-My gut was telling me that
this was a bad idea
and that Bill's chances of
succeeding were slim.
But who knows?
Frances' love for Bill
in those letters
seemed so deep.
Maybe after
all these years
she felt the same regret
he did.
Regardless, if Bill really
wanted to surprise Frances
at her front door,
I felt obligated
to make sure
he was putting
his best foot forward.
So I found a professional
actress online
who closely resembled
Frances' look and age
to be Bill's
rehearsal partner.
I then arranged with
a local theater company
who is currently staging
a production
of "Young Frankenstein"
to let us use their venue
as a practice space
during one of
their days off,
and using some furniture
we found backstage,
we created a makeshift set
to play as Frances' home.
Bye the time June, our actress,
arrived from Los Angeles,
she had studied up on
Frances' letters,
which I had given her
so she'd have a better sense
of the woman
she'd be portraying.
- He disappointed her and--
and hurt her.
-And before long, it was time
for her to meet the man
she had read
so much about.
- Oh, hi, Bill.
- June is the actress that
will be playing Frances.
- Pleasure meeting you.
- Pleasure.
- What do you think?
Is the look pretty accurate?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
- Not bad.
- [laughs]
- Okay.
- Of course, it's not--
- You've got nice teeth.
- Thank you.
- It's so long since
you've seen her, right?
- Ooh, look at her teeth.
Look at 'em.
You've got 'em all.
They're yours.
- Yes, they're mine.
- Nothing fake.
- They're mine.
They're all mine.
-Right away, I began to see
the side of Bill
that Frances had alluded to
in her letters
and I knew we had a lot of work
ahead of us.
For our initial
run-through,
I asked Bill to show me
what he was thinking of doing
when he arrived
at Frances' home,
and then we would adjust
from there if necessary.
All right, so, Bill, you're
arriving at Frances' door.
This is the first time
you've seen her in 50 years.
Okay, ready?
And action.
[knock on door]
- Frances, God, I can't
believe it's you!
- Bill, oh, my God!
It's been so long.
Is it really you?
- Man.
- Oh.
Oh, my goodness.
- I can't believe
it's you.
[cries]
All these years.
- I know, I know,
I know. Sit.
- We should have married.
Why didn't you marry me?
- So, Bill, tell me
all about yourself.
Now, easy on.
It's been 47 years now.
I'm a married woman,
so just take it easy.
Just take it slow.
I just want--
Now--
- Okay, pause.
Bill, can I ask you why you
rubbed her leg like that?
- Where?
Her leg?
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
It's just--
- June, as Frances, how do you
think she would feel
if he touched her?
- Uncomfortable.
-The first run-through
was troubling.
Bill's initial attempts
to win over Frances
came across
as either creepy...
- Is your husband
a jealous man?
-or desperate.
- But I'm asking you again
to marry me, please.
-He just couldn't engage
with Frances
like a normal
human being.
- Surprise!
-And bringing in
our "Mud 2" actor
to play her husband only seemed
to make things worse.
- I'm here to marry...
- My wife.
- your wife.
Do you understand...
- But she's my wife.
- English?
-He was just unable
to see the situation
from Frances'
perspective.
And worst of all,
our Frances stand-in
was not convinced.
- You should be
a little bit more...
understanding,
'cause if you push that
on her too fast--
- Yeah, that could be bad.
- You know what I mean?
You know, be more like
a gentleman.
-So to help Bill better
understand
what Frances
might be feeling,
we decided to do
a role-reversal exercise
using a wig I picked up
from a store down the block.
- You don't know how
I've cried myself to sleep
thinking of you.
Losing sleep
for hours.
- I'm sorry, Frances.
- Well, it's like when
a person kills somebody,
they're sorry, but that doesn't
bring 'em back to life.
-After embodying Frances
for nearly an hour,
it seemed to give Bill
some new perspective.
- Never heard from you,
write you letters,
call you on the phone,
ignore the calls.
All you wanted
was the career,
the career
in Hollywood.
You were just doing it
for yourself.
Self-centered.
-And once he switched back
to himself again,
a softer side of Bill
seemed to emerge.
- I cheated on you.
I kept you misleading
that we were gonna marry.
I didn't answer
your letters.
I've been living
with regret
how I've--
it was really hard.
I know you have
a happy family,
a nice home,
and happily married,
but I would be lying
if I said I didn't have
feelings for you,
because I do.
I just want you
to know, Frances,
that I really
love you so much.
-By then end
of rehearsal,
I felt like Bill had made
huge strides.
[dramatic music]
[applause]
And even June
was feeling optimistic
about his chances
of winning over Frances.
- I think there's
a possibility,
and of course, there's
a stronger possibility
if she's not in
a happy marriage.
But of course, you know,
one doesn't know that
until the actual
time comes.
-It was hard to know exactly
how things would play out
on the day,
but we'd soon find out
because it was time
to go to Michigan.
- Love you.
- Bye, Shelly.
Love you.
- Okay.
Well, good luck.
Let me know
how it goes.
- Thank you.
I know.
- [laughs]
Oh.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- [sniffs]
- You gonna be
okay?
- It's gonna
be okay.
- It is.
It's gonna be okay.
So you never know.
You never know
what you'll find up there.
- That's right.
- So [indistinct].
- [sniffs]
♪
-We headed to the airport
and boarded our flight
for the 950-mile trip north
to Traverse City, Michigan.
By the time we arrived,
it was getting late,
so we decided to head to
the hotel and call it a night
with a plan to go to
Frances' house
first thing in the morning.
-And that's why
I'm introducing
comprehensive
immigration reform
within the first 100 days
with a path to citizenship.
-Thank you, Secretary Clinton.
I wanted to follow up--
- Look at the--
- Yeah?
- [chuckles]
He's--he's the man
for the presidency,
I'm telling you.
I've told you that before.
Donald H. Trump,
I believe is his middle initial,
isn't it?
- I think it's J.
- Huh?
- Why are you
telling me this?
- Well, I'm trying to
convince you
that Trump is the man.
You seem to think
he's not gonna win.
- Well, he's losing
in the polls.
- You can't go by
the polls.
- What can you
go by?
-I'd like to hear from--I'd
like to hear from Secretary--
- Election day.
-I voted for border security
and there are--
[dramatic music]
-The next morning
as Bill got ready,
I copied down Frances' address
and phone number
from the online
Whitepages.
♪
Bill didn't say a word to me
that entire morning.
I could tell there was
a lot on his mind.
♪
It's funny how the more
comfortable you get
with someone,
the less you feel the need
to fill the silence with talk.
♪
What are you
thinking?
- Well, I'm just
thinking.
♪
- Bill?
- Mm-hmm.
- What are you
thinking about?
- Oh, I'm just--
♪
-Frances' address
took us to a small,
wooded neighborhood
off of Lake Michigan.
- [exhales sharply]
-The plan was for Bill
to go to the door
by himself at first
while we hung back
so she wouldn't be startled
by the cameras.
This is it.
It's right down there.
- Oh. Okay.
[chuckles]
It's right
down there.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
Oh, Lord.
God have mercy.
[laughs]
- [laughs]
But when it came time
to get out,
Bill didn't want to go down
without us.
- Well, I thought wouldn't
you want it that way
with the cameras?
- Well, it seems like
a personal moment for you.
- Oh, bring
the cameras.
I like all the PR.
[laughs]
You heard it,
the PR.
- What do you mean?
- Public relations,
PR.
-And it concerned me
that Bill didn't realize
how showing up at her front
door with a camera crew
might freak her out.
What do you think
it'll be like for her?
- I--she wouldn't
mind it.
- The cameras?
- Right.
-If he really wanted to
go down there with the crew,
I suggested that
he call her first.
- We could.
You have her number?
-So I moved our car
out of sight around the corner
and dialed Frances' number
into Bill's phone
so he could
make the call.
You ready?
- Ready.
[telephone rings]
-Hello?
- Hello, Frances?
-Yes.
- How are you?
-Fine.
Who's calling?
- Well, I want you
to guess.
-Oh, I can't.
[laughs]
I don't know.
- Well, you think hard.
Doesn't my voice
sound familiar to you?
-No.
- No?
- It's been a long time,
Frances.
-Yeah, you've got me
wondering now.
Who is this?
Hello?
- Yeah, I'm here.
-Okay.
- Uh...
- Tell her.
- You don't know who I am?
Think hard.
I don't sound familiar
to you?
-No.
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this Jim Beckley?
- Who?
-Beckley?
- No.
-No?
Oh.
- Tell her
who you are.
- Yeah.
All right, I'm gonna
tell you who I am.
-Okay.
- Bill Heath.
Hello?
-Hello.
- Bill Heath.
-Bill Heath?
- H-E-A-T-H.
-Okay.
Hi, Bill, how are you?
- You remember me now,
don't you?
-Yes, I do.
Of course I do.
Well, what are you
up to?
- Oh, trying to do right.
-[laughs]
Okay, is that hard?
- So--but I, you know,
I've been thinking about you
a lot of the times
and I said finally,
you know, I'm just
gonna call you
and--
-Okay.
- So--
-So what's going on
in your life?
- I'm out in LA now,
still working as
an actor out there.
-Well, good for you.
Good for you.
- So--
-That's what you
always wanted to do.
- Right.
-Do you have
any children?
- No, I--
I should have
married you maybe.
You know--
you know how it is.
-[laughs]
Well, I have
nine grandchildren.
- Really?
-Yes.
- So--
-No, I'm a--I'm a grandmother
with nine grandchildren,
and we have
twin granddaughters
that are almost
three years old.
-As the call went on,
15 minutes in,
Bill still hadn't mentioned
to Frances
that he was
right outside of her house.
- What do you remember most
about my mother?
-What do I remember most
about your mother?
She didn't like me.
- Oh! What?
-She didn't.
- Why do you say that?
-Well, it's true.
- What makes you
say that?
-Why would she say it?
I don't know,
but she--she didn't.
- Well, are you happy?
-Am I happy?
Yes, I'm happy.
Why?
- You're on your second
marriage, right?
-Mm-hmm.
- Good grief.
Doesn't seem possible.
How many years has it been?
-Well, let's see.
Dave and I have been married
for almost 47--
oh, we have been married
47 years.
- Mm.
Well, the years go by.
-Yeah, they do go by.
- The snap of a finger,
they go by.
-[laughs]
- Have you thought about me much
through the years?
-Of course.
- Do you ever want to pick up
the phone and call me?
-Of course.
- But you never did.
Was it hard?
Hello?
-Hello.
- Was it hard
to do that?
Can you hear me,
Frances?
-Yes, I can--
Yes, I can hear you.
- Well--
well, I just--
you've been on my mind
so much,
and I just had to
call you...
-Well, thank you.
- you know, just to hear
your voice.
My life is--
it's cheered me up so.
-Well, good for you.
Are you all right?
- Am I all right?
-Mm-hmm.
Your health-wise?
- Yes.
Knock on the wood.
-[laughs]
Well, listen,
you take care of yourself.
It's nice
to hear from you
and...
may God bless you.
- And what was that again?
-I said,
and may God bless you.
- Oh, thank you.
The same to you.
-Thank you, Bill.
- Bye-bye.
God bless.
-Good-bye.
- All right.
How do you feel?
- How do I feel?
- [laughs] You know,
about the conversation.
- How do you feel?
- You seemed more
nervous than I--
I wasn't nervous, was I?
I didn't seem nervous.
- Do you still want to
go inside?
- No, I don't think so.
I talked to her,
that's enough.
I couldn't marry her.
It wouldn't work now.
- Do you feel like
she's over you?
[somber music]
- Well, she sounded like it,
like it was just memories or--
♪
She didn't even recognize
my voice.
♪
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- You want to
go home?
- Yeah.
♪
-When we got back to
the hotel that night,
there was a bee
on the loose...
- Oop!
-and Bill seemed determined
to get it.
♪
- [sighs]
He won't give up.
[bleep]!
Excuse me.
♪
[toilet flushes]
All right,
down the toilet.
- Good work.
-After spending so much time
in Arkansas,
I found myself digging my way
out of all the other work
that had piled up
in Los Angeles.
I was working late hours
and finding it hard to
adjust back to my routine.
Bill wasn't really
on my mind much anymore.
I think a part of me
wanted to believe
that he would find
a happy ending,
and when that
didn't happen,
it was
a bit of a bummer.
Then one day
out of the blue,
Bill asked to come by the
office to give me something.
- I got something
for you.
- Really?
This is for me?
- Yes.
- What is it?
Wow.
Thank you, Bill.
Is this
a serving tray?
- Yeah, you can put
pasta on there,
salads, anything.
- Wow.
- I know the salesman
and we picked it out.
We thought that
that would be
appropriate for you.
- This is really sweet of you
to give this to me.
- Of course.
That's a small token for what--
what you've done.
I appreciate everything.
-The tray was really nice,
but I discovered
that Bill wasn't just here
to say thanks.
- What are your thoughts on that
actress that came from LA
to Arkansas?
- June?
I thought she was good.
- Well, just--
[laughs]
- What do you mean?
What did you think of her?
- Well, you know.
She'd be a good contact
for me.
- Why are you smiling, Bill?
- [laughs]
I don't--
- Do you have a crush
on her, Bill?
- I didn't say
a crush on--
- Do you have a crush
on June?
- I worked with her one time.
[laughs]
- Why are you laughing?
Look at you, Bill.
You're blushing.
Oh, my God.
- I don't know what
her phone number is so.
- You want to call her
right now?
- Yeah.
[telephone rings]
[ring]
-Hello.
- June?
-Yes.
- How are you?
-I'm good.
How are you?
- Do you know who
you're speaking with?
-Is this Bill?
- [laughs]
Yeah, that's--
this is Bill.
-It's easy to look at
someone else's life
as a cautionary tale.
After all, no one wants to be
old and filled with regret.
- Good grief.
- Oh, my goodness.
Oh, how sharp
you look.
- Well, you look--
- Oh.
- Boy, you know, I'm gonna
compliment your teeth again.
They're gorgeous.
- [laughs]
- Let's toast
to your teeth.
- All right.
My mother always told me,
she said,
"You get to that dentist
every six months, June."
I said,
"All right, Mom."
-But if you look closer
and see that
that life is filled with
moments of sincere joy,
however fleeting,
it's hard to say if it was
really a bad life after all.
Anyways, I wanted to
let you know
that I booked my ticket
yesterday.
I'm really excited
to see you.
Yours, Nathan.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Hey.
Good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- You want to hop--
- Can we sit up here?
- Sure, yeah.
It's good
to see you again.
- [laughs]
It's good to see you again.
It's an interesting
little place.
- On the map
it was blue,
so I thought it would be
a nice river, but--
- Yeah, I thought we were
gonna drive trucks.
- Yeah.
[laughter]
- You good with that?
- Mm-hmm.
- You and your
super cold hands.
- Thanks for
warming them up.
- No problem.
[giggles]
It's kind of weird having
cameras around, right?
- We can turn them off
if you want.
- [laughs]
Could we?
- Do you want to?
- [laughs]
I feel like that--does
that defeat the purpose maybe?
- Of what?
- I don't know.
- What's the purpose?
- You're filming
something.
It's kind of
the purpose, right?
[The Kinnardlys'
"Be Happy For Me"]
♪
- We do have this drone.
It would be cool to get
a drone shot maybe.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
♪
-♪ Don't be sad be glad
♪ Be happy for me
♪ I'll be home come sundown
♪ In the land where I'm free
♪ Though you think
you're alone ♪
♪ By your side I will be
♪ Don't be sad
♪ Be happy for me
♪
♪ And the mountains are high
♪ In the land where I'm free
♪ And they reach for the sky
♪ Like my dreams
♪ And the sound that I love
♪ Is the song of the sea
♪ Don't be sad
♪ Be happy
♪ Happy for me
♪