CAPTAIN MARLEAU
THE MYSTERIES OF FAITH
-Hello, my child.
-Hello, Sister.
How can I help?
I've come to stay a bit in
your guest house.
Did you call ahead?
No.
You know, we have strict rules here.
We ask a lot of our guests.
Yes, I know.
And you give a lot, too.
Of course.
I have a duty to remind you
that this is a place of silence.
I promise, my lips are sealed.
We ask our guests
to join our community in prayer
and for some attendance at services.
I've had a long journey, Sister.
I...
I'll inform our Mother Superior.
That's Mother Louise, right?
-Do you know her?
-No, not yet.
But we have a friend in common.
Tell her that Carlos Iniesta sent me.
I do not think
I have ever heard of that man,
young lady.
Maybe you erased him
from your memory.
Carlos Iniesta
hasn't forgotten you.
He hasn't forgotten who you are
or what you did.
-What do you want?
-I need to disappear for a while.
As you'll understand,
this isn't the appropriate place.
No, you haven't understood.
Carlos insists.
I won't be blackmailed, young lady.
This is the house of God.
You'd better believe me,
Mother Louise,
I won't leave.
Or should I speak
to your community?
I could tell them why you came here.
Come in.
Oh, excuse me, Mother.
I didn't know you were busy.
Sister Maryse,
be so kind as to take this lady
to Sister Françoise,
so she can be shown to a room.
Very good, Mother.
By the way, my name is Manuela.
Welcome.
What?
What do you want?
Nothing, Mother.
I am Alpha and Omega,
the beginning and the ending.
Blessed are they
that do His commandments...
Eat, Mother,
you've hardly touched your food.
...and may enter through the gates,
into the city.
For without are dogs
and sorcerers...
Continue your reading, Sister Maryse.
And finish lunch in silence, Sisters.
Sister Maryse needs to be
with our Mother all the time.
Sometimes it almost seems
that she's in love.
I won't let her take up that position
without doing something.
After all,
I've been here longer than she has.
If I can put a spoke
in her wheel, then I will.
I, Jesus,
have sent my angel to testify to you
these things in the churches.
Don't let her down.
She's so fragile.
Being a liberated cop
isn't that easy.
Hello.
-Can I have a coffee, please?
-Of course.
Is the Ostwald police station
far from here?
No, it's half an hour, maximum.
I wonder if she's got anything on,
under that skirt.
She's probably like the Scots,
with their kilts.
-They let it all hang out.
-I'm going to ask her.
Stop.
-That's not a good idea, buddy.
-What?
Who asked you, Davy Crockett?
I'm a gendarme.
So, what do I do
with your drunken mugs?
Do I breathalyze you
or just take you in?
-We didn't mean any disrespect.
-No, of course not.
And are girls in miniskirts
asking to be raped?
What?
Go and clean the tables, one by one,
with your tongue, if necessary.
And then apologize.
Get to it!
Shift your fat ass!
Marguerite Croton
taught me in grade 7.
She said you should never give up
on a numbskull.
POLICE
Get out and show us some ID.
OK, take it easy,
-it's still early.
-This isn't a campsite, you know.
Don't shout, I'm not dead.
What's crawled up his ass?
Get out, right now.
You're at a police station!
Open this door!
What a ballbreaker.
Ow!
My door!
I'm sorry about the mix-up, Captain.
That's OK, I'm used to dealing
with my colleagues' prejudice.
Come in.
Ah, here he is!
A nice cup of coffee
and some pastries.
That's how you wake people up.
Brigadier Brière
will take you to the barracks
-and show you your apartment.
-No need.
Sorry?
I'd rather go native.
Isn't there a local B&B or something?
-But...
-They won't care about my ways.
They even encourage them.
Don't worry, Commandant.
Brière, show the captain
somewhere to stay in town
and take her over.
I'm a big girl, now.
I can pee on my own.
We were expecting you tomorrow,
but would you like
to visit the brigade now?
Despite your olfactory respect,
I think I might need a shower first,
Commandant.
Come in.
Commandant,
something's going on downtown.
A young girl jumped from
her window in front of her neighbor.
-Brière, you go, with Garcia.
-Garcia's not here, Commandant.
The crazy biker was out on the N83.
What crazy biker is that?
He's spent the last two weeks
breaking the speed records.
He gets his kicks
by outrunning our patrols.
It sounds
like a lot of fun around here.
I'll go with Brière.
Right, Brière?
-Commandant.
-Captain.
Move on, please.
This is not a circus.
She was young. Poor thing.
-Hello.
Did you see anything?
I was coming home.
I put my bag down to get my keys,
I heard a shout, I turned around
and she just came falling down.
-You heard a shout?
-Yes.
Yes, a loud shout.
That's why I turned around.
She fell down, in front of me.
Did you see anyone else?
No, no-one.
Thanks. We'll be in touch.
There's a funny smell in here.
What a dump!
The Stork Hotel!
That name is like a sign.
The flight of the storks.
Like that girl...
OK, forget it.
Anyone home?
Unbelievable!
Here he is.
Sorry, no.
OK, I can give you the number
for my therapist. Her name's Olga.
I wanted to see the room
the dead woman was in.
She was up on the top floor.
OK, take me up.
Who are you?
The cavalry.
Up you go, darling.
-Isn't there an elevator?
-It's broken down.
-You go up first.
-I can't, I have a heart condition.
My heart's racing.
Ah, right.
Wait here.
What's the room number?
-It's the Tulips.
-She was in the Tulips?
-Yes, she was.
-Now she's pushing up the daisies.
Brière!
The Tulips are on the top floor.
I'm coming, Captain.
What did they want?
I don't know. It was the girl.
You picked a good day to drop by.
I didn't drop by.
Yes, I know, I meant...
You get my point.
You can go out.
I need to be alone, to think.
About what?
I don't think
there's much to think about here.
That's what makes us different,
Brière.
The kid jumped out of the window.
It's sad, OK, but...
But...
the door.
That door was open when I got here.
And?
If you're going to kill yourself,
you shut the door.
It's basic stuff.
OK, let's change tactics.
Seal things off
and find out who she was.
And get an autopsy done, quick,
on the kid,
as you wish.
What time do you call this?
-We came as fast as we could.
-Right.
France is good.
Mother, please,
sorry, but we need
to discuss the accounts.
-The accounts, Sister Beatrice?
-Yes, it's important.
-Isn't it time for vespers?
-Yes, but...
-The accounts can wait, Sister.
We will conclude tonight
by worshipping the Virgin Mary.
Let's not be late.
So, to recap, her name was Manuela,
she had a strong Spanish accent
and paid for two nights, in cash.
-Yes.
But you didn't check her name
by asking for ID,
because you didn't want
to get taxed on her stay.
I can assure you...
We don't jail people for that,
unfortunately.
So, you said
you still have two people staying.
And what were you doing
when she jumped?
I was at the local bar, because...
-My wife left me five years ago.
-Yes.
-I'm surprised.
-I have to pass the time.
So your wife left you
and you run your palace on your own?
More or less,
but I have a young cleaning lady
who does a few hours a week,
to help me out a bit.
-A cleaning lady, right.
And what do you call
the room opposite the Tulips?
-The Sunflowers.
That's less bad
than the Chrysanthemums.
Isn't that funny? It doesn't matter.
I'll take the Sunflowers,
because I like Van Gogh.
I'll get the key.
-I'll only be staying 2-3 nights.
-OK.
Nice curtains.
My wife chose them.
She had good taste, you know.
So, the Sunflowers.
-Sunflowers.
-It's a nice room.
That's kind.
The elevator's broken.
My God, this is ugly.
This is so depressing.
What's going on with this guy?
A tourist.
What's he doing?
Hello.
-Are you looking for something?
-Yes, I'm looking for meaning.
Captain Marleau.
I've got a couple
of mystic-legal questions to ask.
Please, follow me.
It's funny,
you don't look like a country priest.
You don't look
like a typical police officer.
The job's about more than a uniform.
You've got a nice place here.
Very classy.
Oh!
Do you sleep here?
Yes.
I arrived in the parish
six weeks ago,
but I haven't really settled in yet.
You don't like work accommodation
either.
My predecessor was an old man.
I'm giving him time to move out.
What were you doing
at the hotel earlier?
Getting washed.
The house of God is magnificent,
but there's no bathroom.
The manager
kindly lets me use his facilities.
The manger's nice.
And why don't you sleep there?
I prefer it here.
These walls have a history.
I can speak to them.
To the walls?
The Inquisition burned people
for less than that.
And did you ever talk
to the young girl that died?
No.
You never met her.
I didn't know she was there.
Ah.
Then why did you stop, earlier on,
at the spot where she crashed?
To pray for her.
It won't help her much now.
The good Lord
doesn't care about appearances.
Who knows, maybe He'll be
even happier to see her.
Tell that to a stiff
and it'll hit you with its coffin.
Believing in our consumer society
is more absurd than believing in God.
Amen! That's the first time
I've agreed with a priest.
You'll end up converting me.
And what's your take on suicide?
-It's condemned, traditionally.
-Why?
Human life belongs to God.
Suicide is a rupture
in that relationship.
So, if you're unhappy,
you just have to put up with it.
It's like a permanent job
that you can't walk out on.
OK.
Do you know this man?
St. Benedict, without a doubt.
By the way,
when your sinner took the leap,
where were you?
With my predecessor, Grégoire.
St. Benedict was a priest
who founded his monastery
at Monte Cassino, in 530.
Ah.
The precepts and rules
that he pronounced
are still followed to this day.
Like what, for example?
The Récollets Abbey
maintains the tradition
of taking in guests and the poor.
The Sisters receive them,
with respect
and humanity.
Ah! Humanity! Jaurès!
-Thanks for your cooperation.
-You're welcome, my child.
Ah!
Sorry to keep going on,
but are you absolutely sure
Vincent didn't stop by
the day before yesterday.
You know,
old age and its trials
are carrying me off, for sure,
but my memory isn't failing me yet.
I didn't mean to upset you.
Entschuldigung.
I'm just finishing with my move.
I haven't left here for three days.
OK.
They don't dust much here.
So then...
Small wad, big alibi.
I don't understand, Mother.
I've been over it three times.
Money doesn't just disappear,
Sister Beatrice.
I've checked everything,
I assure you.
It's almost 3,000 euros down.
Mother Louise is right.
Money doesn't disappear.
You must've made a mistake.
And pull yourself together,
Sister Beatrice.
I'm sorry, Mother,
but I'm absolutely sure.
Give me the accounts
and the key to the safe, Sister.
I'll start over, Mother,
if you don't mind.
I'll do it.
Let me, please.
Sister Maryse, take our Sister back.
Very good, Mother.
You can rely on me, Mother,
you don't need to worry.
I'll do it.
Leave me alone.
I need to be alone.
Do you understand?
No one here would steal.
-I didn't say that.
-You implied it.
I know it's who you suspect.
Jean - because you don't like him.
INSTITUTE OF FORENSICS
-Hello, Captain Marleau.
-Hello.
I'm looking for Dr. Gravos.
She's on the left.
Thanks.
On the left. Gravos.
On the left, Gravos.
Dr. Gravos?
She was around 25.
She's Caucasian
and I'd say she may've been
from southern Europe.
Spain, I think.
What makes you say that?
Long brown hair,
tanned skin,
well defined nose and features.
It's a bit simplistic,
but she's a typical
Andalusian beauty.
Ah, right.
I'm from the north.
How could you tell that?
You've got a slight accent.
You're a comic.
No, I mean physically.
Surely...
your beautiful grey-green eyes.
-They're beautiful.
-Thanks.
Nicely creased.
Those are the characteristics
of people that smile a lot.
And people from the north
smile a lot.
That's a bit of a cliché.
We smile a lot,
we're alcoholic, we're inbred
and terrorists all have beards.
It's a bit of a dodgy methodology.
-Let's get back to our Spaniard.
-Yes.
There's no doubt that she
and the child she was carrying
both died from the fall.
What child?
Was she pregnant?
Yes, she was.
Three and a half months.
Oh my God.
Quite.
There's something else.
Look.
You see, on her arm,
there's very recent bruising.
Whoever grabbed hold of her arm
did it hard enough to hurt her.
So, he might have helped her
on her way down?
That's something God only knows.
Give me his address, if you have it.
I'll bring him in.
The genetic and toxicological tests
will be ready in two days.
OK.
Great.
Ah, there are photos, too.
Nice.
-A cigarette?
-No, I'm more into grass, to relax.
-Ah, right.
-Yes.
If the test results come in early,
you can contact me
at The Stork Hotel.
Are you staying there?
You're not superstitious.
No, it brings bad luck.
If the murderer returns to the site,
I'll be there.
-See you soon.
-Bye.
It's funny,
because in Alsace,
the stork is a sign of good luck.
It's associated with births.
Your storks must've been on a break,
when she fell,
with that baby in her belly.
-It's sad.
-Yes, it's sad.
By the way, how tall was she?
-About five foot four.
-Really?
That's good. See you soon.
Goodbye.
Hello.
I'd like my key, please.
I'm in Sunflowers.
-Huh?
-Sunflowers.
Have you been working here long?
Two years. I do mornings.
Ah. And how's the boss?
He's lazy.
Since his wife left,
he's been in the local café, mostly.
-Ah, right.
-Yes.
He wife left.
And does he try it on with you?
Are you kidding?
He's got bad breath
and he's bone idle,
but other than that, he's OK.
-How tall are you?
-Sorry?
How tall are you?
Five foot four. Why?
Move back a bit.
Let's see your shoes.
Not bad.
-Pretty nice, eh?
-Yes.
Come with me.
Come on, follow me.
-What for?
-You'll see, it'll be fun.
Come on.
Act like you wanted
to jump out of the window.
-Jump out of the window?
-Yes, imagine you want to jump.
Put your back into it.
-It won't work. But if I....
-Hey!
You'd be dead, instantly.
You'd go splat.
Like a watermelon.
-Like?
-A watermelon.
Hello.
Ah, there you are.
They said I'd find you here.
Bad reputations spread fast
in small towns.
You're not doing anyone any harm.
Doing my thing?
Brassens, pinball, leather jacket -
Being a priest is your only fault.
I knew you'd say that.
Shove over and let me have a go.
Let the artist work.
You know, in Douai, they call me
the Bar Owners' Terror.
-Tell me about your life, padre.
-My life?
-Like what?
-Everything. About everything.
Everything.
Captain, the Church is a mystery
that sometimes elicits no answer.
I'm happy to serve and obey.
Disobedience, padre, disobedience.
That's the only religion,
as St. Howard Zinn said.
Hot damn! I got three plays.
You're not bad.
-Hello, Sister.
-Hello, Father.
-Sorry, the cloisters are off limits.
-Sister.
-I didn't recognize you, Father.
-That's OK.
I was praying.
How can I help?
I'm Captain Marleau.
I want to talk to your boss.
Or your Mother.
I mean, to the Superior.
Don't worry.
Captain Marleau is unusual,
but a very reasonable woman.
-My Mother...
-If you don't mind,
take me to the chapel.
I'd like to pray there.
-Prepare the Mass.
-Very good, Father.
I believe you asked to see me.
I'm sorry.
I was communing with your goldfish.
Don't apologize.
I'm very happy,
if you've found serenity here.
Captain Marleau.
I have cold hands.
How can I help, Captain?
I won't keep you long.
Could I just ask a few questions?
Can we walk and talk?
Let's go.
Ah, hang on.
I want to show you something.
Where did I put it?
-Do you recognize him?
-Yes, that's St. Benedict.
We sell these in the local bookshops.
-Do you make them here?
-Yes.
We make all sorts of artisanal items,
to help meet the costs
of our nunnery.
You're not a bit Spanish,
by any chance?
After almost 30 years here,
my accent still gives me away.
Hey! ¡Yo también!
-¿Sí?
-Northerner.
Vengo del norte de la Francia.
Big accent.
You know what I mean.
It's funny.
It's funny too,
the bookmark that I showed you
belonged to a Spanish woman, too.
-It belonged?
-It belonged.
She's dead.
She fell. Fourth floor. Whack. Kaput.
Santa Maria...
Madre de Dios.
¿Por qué?
¿Por que?
Are you OK?
Are you sure?
Thank you.
Is this the girl we're talking about?
Yes, that's her.
We took her in,
in our guest house.
How long did she stay?
I don't really know.
-Maybe a week or two.
-Two weeks?
Yes.
What happened?
I don't know.
But it wasn't an accident.
Did she...
Did she what? Commit suicide?
Is that the word you're looking for?
That's what I'd like to know.
What was a girl like that
doing in a convent?
Eh?
People come to our nunnery
to be in silence,
to open up to an encounter with God.
If she wanted an encounter with God,
she got it.
Did you know her?
I think she was called Ma...
-Manuela.
-But Manuela what?
Our guests don't have to show ID,
Captain.
A nunnery
isn't tourist accommodation.
I understand, but...
I'm from Roubaix.
If I meet another northerner,
I'll say hi, local style,
and he'll answer me back.
We're from the same place.
Right?
The people that stay here
are called to prayer.
As I told you, Captain,
this is a place of meditation,
not of talk.
I didn't think
it was a swingers' club.
And didn't you ever try
a few words of Spanish on her,
just for fun?
Our lives here are devoted
to the search for union with God.
The only language that I speak here
is the Lord's.
And does the Lord
speak Spanish or French?
We pray in French,
but I often speak to him in Spanish.
OK,
who did the kid speak to last,
just before she left here?
I suppose it was Jean.
He takes our guests into town,
if they don't have transportation.
Jean.
Who's Jean?
He's the gardener and odd-job man.
Jean links us to the outside world.
So where can I find this link
to the outside world?
He'll be caring for the trees,
in the orchard.
Excuse me, Captain,
but this news has upset me.
I'd like to organize
a Mass for the child.
Thanks.
All right, Johnny Boy?
Sorry?
-Have we met?
-No, not yet.
I'm Captain Marleau.
Captain of what?
Is there a boat behind me? No.
What does that say?
So, what do you think?
What do you want from me?
Come down, I'll tell you.
-Get down, Johnny Boy.
-OK, take it easy.
There we go.
You look funny.
Yes, she was pretty,
but not very talkative.
Where did you take her,
four days ago?
She said she wanted to go
to Amsterdam this week,
so I dropped her at the Stork Hotel,
to wait.
Amsterdam?
Yes, Amsterdam.
Did she stay long here?
I don't know. Just under a month.
Are you sure?
Yes.
All the others are veiled,
so she wasn't hard to spot,
around here.
To spot?
Where were you in the morning,
two days ago?
In town at the garden center.
The garden center?
Yes, I'm not sure if you're aware,
but gardeners go
to garden centers.
That's how it works.
And cops go to the cop center.
It can't be easy
for a straight guy like you
to be surrounded by all these women.
Right, but I don't live here.
I live in town.
Still, with all those dresses,
swirling around you.
The dance of the veils.
Doesn't that get you going?
Didn't you ever get the urge
to try it on with the Spanish girl?
This is getting annoying.
I'm a girl from Barcelona.
Olé! Really? Never?
Aren't you getting tired of these
dumb questions? I have to work.
You don't seem that upset
about her death.
What do you want me to say?
Do you want me to cry for you?
It's sad. There it is.
I've got to work,
out in the garden.
-Yes.
-I'm busy.
Your garden. Divine nature. Right?
That's much more important
than a kid's death.
Damn religion!
Unbelievable!
Shall we go?
You're everywhere, Sister Françoise.
She's truly ubiquitous.
Captain.
So, Captain, did your visit put you
on the right track?
All roads lead to man.
-Or to Rome.
-Yes.
And you weren't tempted
to take the veil?
The veil?
A veil for your crisis of faith.
You'd like that, Mr. Priest.
I'd like nothing more.
That would require some people -
look at me -
to find the path of truth.
What do you mean?
I looked into it.
You weren't with Abbot Gregory
on the day that girl jumped.
-Huh?
-Huh. So, what about that?
I was with an old lover, Captain.
A lover.
Well well.
You've risen in my estimation.
Where can I meet this lover?
I need to speak to her, too.
I doubt she could help.
I'll still need to.
If you want us to be friends.
Or I'll have to invite you both
to the station.
There's no need.
-We'll come to see you.
-OK. Is she nice?
-She's jet black.
-Interesting.
Here we go.
-Hi, you bunch of deadbeats.
-Captain.
So?
It's all good.
Vigier is with an R.
-Ah, sorry.
-Yes.
-There.
-So, how long? How long?
Two minutes, if he's in the database.
This reminds me
of my first microwave.
-So...
-Those are some ugly mugs.
Look. That's him!
Jean Vigier,
born March 27, 1960, in Strasbourg.
It seems we know him.
He's a known sex offender.
Look.
He was arrested for attempted rape,
in 1985.
Speak of the devil,
as my auntie Nicole used to say.
I knew it!
He did five years in prison
and hasn't had contact
with the police since.
Then let's bring him in.
We'll have a little informal chat.
Is Brière listening?
Who's going to pick up the gardener,
tomorrow morning? Brière is.
-OK.
-Cancel your game of squash.
See you.
She's incredible.
Guten Abend!
Is anyone here?
This place is so slack.
Sunflowers.
They should have called it
the Old Poppy.
Too much.
The sinews of war.
The Lord's word.
What's this?
Isa... Isabel...
Judo...
Isabella Jura... Jurado
Mother, it's Sister Maryse.
I need to talk to you.
I need you to enlighten me.
Let me in, please.
You know how much
your word means to me.
Mea culpa, mea culpa.
Mea culpa.
Danke schön.
You reek of grass.
Hello, soldier.
OK?
Hi.
You can leave us.
OK, Captain.
When I think of Éléonore, my God...
Brassens takes me back.
I hate it.
So?
How's Johnny Boy, today?
Well...
Sorry, but what exactly
am I doing here?
You tell me.
Can't you think of any reason?
No. I've got no damn idea.
No damn idea?
It's funny hearing that word
in your mouth.
If you've got no damn idea,
why did you try to run
when they picked you up?
I'm allergic to cops.
Is that a good enough answer?
A fundamentalist Catholic anarchist.
Oh my God! I'm so scared.
You know, sir,
when someone runs away,
for no reason,
it means he's done something wrong.
-If you say so.
-No.
No, what I say, is that given
your rather inglorious past,
I thought
we could deepen our acquaintance -
no pun intended.
Here we go again.
I'd like to get things straight,
if that's OK.
I'm sorry, but I had nothing to do
with this girl's death.
I messed up when I was young
and I paid a heavy price for it.
Since then, I've cleaned up.
God and God alone is my guide now.
God guides your step...
But when God
was leading that girl into thin air,
at the time she jumped,
you were in a garden center.
-Yes, that's right.
-Exactly.
Which one?
Oh please.
We're going round in circles.
Mother?
Don't you feel well?
-What?
-Don't you feel well?
I'm sorry, Mother, but...
I think you've hurt yourself.
There's blood
on the back of your dress.
That's nothing.
It's just a scratch.
-Shall I take a look?
-No.
Really, it's nothing.
What's going on, Mother?
I'm not up to it.
-I can't do it.
-Calm down.
Please, Mother.
I'm not worth of my task.
I'm not worthy of Our Lord's gaze.
Of course you are.
You're an outstanding
Mother Superior.
For all of us.
For me.
No.
The Lord knows who I am.
And soon He'll call me back.
I'm here, Mother.
I'm here.
I'm watching over you.
Whatever mistakes you've made,
I'll always be here.
You know how much I love you.
I don't want your love.
I can't go on.
You can't understand.
No one can.
I'm worried about Mother Louise.
Guard me, should the foe assail me.
Call me when my life shall fail me.
His alibi is solid.
Three employees at the garden center
say they saw him there.
Ah.
What about the kid's identity?
Still nothing?
That's such a pain.
Could you look in your magic machine?
Search for Isabel Jurado or Jugado.
Something like that.
Look.
You see the images in this column?
Basically,
that's the young girl's DNA.
Ah, I see.
And this is the DNA....
from the baby she was carrying.
OK.
That clearly shows
they each had totally different DNA.
What? I don't get it.
She was a surrogate mother.
-She was...
-Carrying a child for another couple.
She made no genetic contribution,
herself.
Ah, I see! So is that legal in Spain?
No more than it is in France.
And in Holland?
No, not in Holland either.
-Really?
-Their legislation is like ours,
except for abortion.
Abortion?
Yes, it's the only country in Europe
where it's legal up to 24 weeks
after the last menstrual cycle.
Are you leaving already?
Yes, I am. What are you up to?
I see you're over
your emotional difficulties.
-They come and go.
-That's right.
You can climb the stairs now.
And how are you?
I wanted to say, last time.
You were both here
when that kid jumped, weren't you?
You weren't in the bistro. I asked.
It's true, we were both here,
but we didn't see or hear anything.
No way.
Are you happy?
Yes.
I'll leave the key with you.
-Thanks.
-Keep up the good work.
That's that.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
I recognized you as I overtook.
Take a look at you.
That's a bit S&M, isn't it?
This is my old lover, Captain.
My alibi, if you'd rather.
I see.
That's a fine machine.
The cops are all after you, you know?
-We all have our weaknesses.
-This one could cost you.
-A load of points, then your license.
-Do you think so?
-Yes.
-How's your investigation?
My investigation? It's going nowhere.
I'm going to meditate on it
and shift down a gear.
-Will you find your haven of peace?
-Have a guess.
OK, I'm off.
Bye, Captain.
Yeah - drive carefully.
I don't cancel people's fines.
Thanks.
Hello.
What can I do for you?
You...
who have come to spend
a few hours or days in the shadows
of our abbey,
know that you are now our guest.
We adopt you.
Did you call earlier?
Yes. Wasn't that good?
It was a tribute to Barbara.
Wait here
while I tell the Mother Superior.
OK.
Captain, I won't deny
I was surprised by your sudden desire
to stay among us.
Really?
Why is that?
Because meditation and solitude
require silence.
-What are you in search of?
-The truth.
What truth?
A nunnery is a good place
to search
for the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth.
Why did you lie to me?
I beg your pardon?
You said Manuela stayed here
for two weeks.
That's not true.
She stayed for a month.
Lying is a sin, Mother.
We spend our days in prayer.
The days merge into one
and we can lose our sense of time.
To that extent?
If you want to question me,
wouldn't it be easier
at the station, Captain.
It certainly would.
I could have done.
But then I thought
I would go straight to the nunnery.
It's ideal for confessions.
Isn't it?
You're welcome among us.
Gracias.
Sister Françoise will show you
your room and help you to settle in.
I would be very grateful
if you would conform to our rules.
Good night, Captain.
You should stop bleeding.
I'm sorry.
It'd be pleasing
if you could show me the signs.
Buenas noches, Madre
You naughty girl!
It's not good to eavesdrop.
I'll tell St. Benedict.
I wasn't.
I was only kidding.
I don't have his number.
Meals are served in the refectory.
Breakfast is at 8am,
lunch is at 12pm
and dinner is at 6pm.
OK.
You will also need to help
with our daily tasks:
serving, cleaning and washing.
What a bit of luck.
I'm the ironing queen.
So, here's your room.
The sheets are in the little closet.
Great.
It would be preferable
if you also attended our services.
I won't need asking twice, I swear.
Ouala!
Thanks.
What?
I know it's nasty.
Open your mouth, close your eyes.
What's this?
Excuse me, kiddo.
Easy.
Lord, Lord...
Wash me of my iniquity.
Cleanse me of my sin,
for I have transgressed
and my sin is still before me.
I have sinned, I have sinned.
I've sinned against You,
against You alone.
You will be just when You speak
when You judge me.
When You judge me.
So, what's in here?
Jurado, Isabel.
Thanks, darling.
Isabel Jurado.
Oh, you little liar.
It's not good to lie like that.
Here we go.
There.
And there.
Thanks, kiddo.
-Good evening, Sister.
-May Jesus light your path.
Since I met you,
you've lit my path.
Let them be as chaff before the wind.
Let their way be dark and slippery
and the angel persecute him.
-See you tomorrow, Brother.
-Yes, Sister.
There you go, Sister.
Mother Louise spent a lot of time
with her.
Of course, she brought her
into our community.
And they spoke
the language of Cervantes.
What was Manuela like?
When she arrived
she seemed greatly troubled,
but her time here seemed to help.
Our Mother took care of her.
She was transformed.
By the end,
she was coming to our services.
I'd be grateful
if you respected our rules, Captain.
Our daily work
should be done in silence.
And our Sisters
should set an example.
The Marshal isn't that easy going.
She's always currying favor
with our Mother,
with her irreproachable behavior.
Isn't jealousy
one of the seven deadly sins?
I think she's over here.
OK, Brière?
Hello, Captain.
I didn't know you liked gardening.
In vino veritas.
Here.
-We identified her this morning.
-Oh?
Manuela's full name
was Manuela Iniesta Lopez.
She's niece to Carlos Iniesta,
a nasty Spanish crook,
who was involved in some shady stuff.
Manuela Lopez.
I knew a Lopez.
Manuela was booked in Spain,
for prostitution and drugs.
A junkie whore - how original.
-But not a very Catholic trajectory.
-Not really.
-Oh, one other thing, Captain.
-What?
Last week, the Guardia Civil
found Carlos's body, in a pond,
just outside Madrid.
I've always said,
swimming is a dangerous sport.
Don't try it at home.
And it's harder with your hands
tied behind your back.
You're funny, Brière.
Now get going.
-Will you keep me posted?
-If I can. I've got yoga at 10am.
A little drink is nice...
Am I interrupting?
We were hoping you'd make yourself
a little less obtrusive, Captain.
Not everyone can just disappear,
like Isabel Jurado.
Or how do the Spanish pronounce it?
"Jurado". That's the jota, right?
Yes.
Leave us, please.
-But, Mother...
-Leave us, Sister Maryse.
The Captain and I
have things to talk about.
Very good, Mother.
Where shall we talk?
I don't care.
I just want the truth.
But this will be more like
a confession for you, so...
I'd never met Manuela,
before she arrived here.
But she brought an old shadow
back to my memory.
A man? Carlos Iniesta?
Did she have to hide because of him?
Was it about the surrogate baby?
She stole it, you know.
She stole the baby she was carrying.
She stole it?
How do you mean?
A couple gave her a lot of money
to carry their baby.
But Carlos said it wasn't enough.
So he wanted to get her away,
so he could extort money from them.
Is that it?
Yes.
Carlos put her in touch with them.
They were unsavory types.
The girl was scared.
-This is yours, isn't it?
-Yes.
Did you give it to her
or did she just take it?
I gave it to her.
You know, during her last days here,
she was in a state of total panic.
She couldn't reach Carlos.
She wanted to run away.
To Amsterdam?
She wanted a way to end to it all,
to get her freedom back.
A way? What way?
Abortion.
I tried to talk her out of it,
to make her see
the path of love and reason,
but...
You couldn't stop yourself.
You slipped her the money.
And my Bible.
What else could I do,
but pray for her,
pray that she'd keep that child?
But...
Why did you agree to it?
Why did you agree to hide her
in the nunnery?
I thought of it as atonement.
I was atoning for a mistake I made,
30 years ago.
I was far from thinking
that my life belonged to God.
I was beautiful, I think,
carefree and unaware.
That was when
I started to spend time with Carlos.
He was already a thug,
but I was very...
He was beautiful.
He's dead.
You killed him.
I'm going to report you.
No...
Carlos threatened to report me,
for murder,
so I jumped on a train, for France.
As soon as I arrived,
I went into a church
And I've never left, since.
Lord!
Can you ever forgive me?
We know You, because we know Jesus
and the Father and Son are one.
We know through faith,
which is a true marker.
Later, we shall know You
through a vision.
Let yourself be filled
by the Holy Spirit.
-Hello Séverine.
-Hello.
It's chucking it down.
Isn't he here?
-Have you seen the priest?
-Not today.
Ah, OK.
See you later.
Bye.
Thanks be to You,
who ordered the light to shine
amid the darkness
and to light up our hearts,
and give us the understanding
that leads us to know
the face of Jesus Christ,
the true light.
Better still, eternal life
is to know you,
the only true God
and the one that you sent,
Jesus Christ.
We know You, because...
My mind is made up, Sisters.
I just spoke to our bishop,
on the telephone.
He's expecting me this evening,
in Strasbourg.
Mother,
I'm sure that whatever your sin,
Our Lord will watch over you.
I humbly ask for forgiveness.
From all of you.
My sisters,
I humbly ask your forgiveness.
-Forgive me.
-But how can you leave us?
How can you leave us?
I'm not abandoning you, I promise.
But the lies that have long
accompanied me in my Christian life
are finally to be revealed.
It's my duty now
to assume them,
within our Holy Church
and before its representatives.
My Sisters,
my Sisters,
I entrust you to the wisdom
of Sister Célestine.
Do you think the couple killed Carlos
and then tracked Manuela down?
Carlos, yes, but not Manuela.
They wouldn't kill a girl
that was carrying their child.
The world can be distasteful.
We must retain hope.
That sounds a bit daft.
Do you think?
By the way,
are nuns entitled
to have visitors in their cells?
Other than other nuns, no.
Really?
And can they leave the convent?
Not without the consent
of the bishop and abbess.
It's a bit like jail.
The food's a lot better.
-Have you had a revelation?
-Can't you see?
-Is your ride parked nearby?
-It's just there.
It's as if I could hear a voice,
telling me:
"That's our link with the exterior."
Or it's tinnitus.
Give me a ride. Quick!
There you go.
It's just as I said. I was right.
I thought we'd find you here.
It's pretty obvious.
And you were here, at the time.
I know, I checked.
But that doesn't really matter.
That's good,
because I've got nothing to say.
But I can tell you something.
You weren't alone on that day.
You were with one of the nuns.
You were her taxi.
You left the nunnery early with her
and dropped her off,
then you came to do your shopping
and dropped her off in the evening,
back at the nunnery.
True or false?
Listen to me,
they can't leave the nunnery
and I swore an oath.
Stop trying to fool me.
-I saw you that night...
-What?
Yes, you were coming out
of one of the nun's cells.
Who was it?
Hey? Who are you so close to?
Talk, Jean.
Only the truth is good to tell.
Sister Maryse. It's Sister Maryse.
But it's not what you think.
She's reconciling me to faith.
With faith?
That's some faith.
And did Maryse
ask you to drop her off in town?
Yes.
What did I say?
How could you do this?
How could you renounce your vows?
Don't make this harder
than it already is.
How can you abandon me?
That Spanish girl has bewitched you.
She's torn you from me.
How could you tell her to abort?
What are you saying?
I never said any such thing. Never!
-Abortion is a crime.
-Calm down, Sister Maryse.
I beg you.
You're betraying what we are.
-No.
-How could you
give her the money from our work?
I...
Our Lord's money, for such a sin.
And you expect me
to stand by and do nothing?
Only God is love.
I beg you to open this door.
For the love of God, open this door.
I won't let you abandon me.
I beg you to open this door.
Only God is love.
Open this door, for the love of God!
It's awful, Father.
She won't open the door.
She was shouting. It's awful.
We can't hear a sound.
I'm scared something bad happened.
-Take your flock to the chapel.
-Come with me, please, Sisters.
Captain Marleau and our sisters
need us to pray.
And pray hard.
Maryse! Can you hear me?
It's Marleau.
Maryse? I'm going to come in, OK?
That way, we can talk.
If you're not just plaster,
it's time to help.
Stay where you are.
Don't come any closer, do you hear?
Don't come any closer.
Maryse, let the Mother Superior
come with me.
If Mother Louise goes,
I'll kill myself.
Things can't end like this, Maryse,
you know that.
Look at your Christ.
Hasn't he suffered enough?
He suffered for people like you.
You pushed that girl,
didn't you?
If she'd listened,
it wouldn't have happened.
She didn't want to hear God's will.
She was going to abort the baby.
I know, Maryse, I know.
I told her that our money
couldn't be used
for such a sin.
She should heed the Lord's voice.
But she mocked the love
that binds me to Mother Louise.
Please, Sister Maryse.
So I lifted her up,
with a divine strength
guiding my arm.
I pushed her.
She didn't have time to shout.
My God, what have I done?
What have I done?
Lord, have mercy.
Have mercy.
OK, just take it easy.
We're not cowboys.
She'll come quietly.
It's not heavy duty.
It'll be OK. Don't worry.
Let me come with her, please.
OK, go ahead.
Let's go.
Sisters, let us pray for their souls.
Deliver me, Lord, from eternal death
on the fearful day of reckoning,
when You come
to test the world with fire.
I am in fear and trembling
of the approaching judgment
and the anger to come.
May I?
God be with you.
Thank you.
Don't cry.
SAVERNE RAILWAY STATION
So, you're leaving the nunnery?
Yes,
I've failed in my mission.
An abbess should protect her sisters.
I didn't see she was suffering
and losing her mind.
Yes, maybe.
But it's the big day now.
You need to face up to the truth.
-The land of fairies is over now.
-Yes.
You're strong.
You can do it. You'll see.
Thanks, Captain.
It's thanks to you
that I can appear as I truly am
before the Lord.
Now I need to honor my appointment
with the archbishop.
I have to tell him the truth.
Ah, on that subject,
I have something for you.
It's a police report.
-But...
-From the Guardia Civil.
-Are you arresting me?
-No, I'm not arresting you.
In 1985, you pushed a man.
He died, but not because of you.
Sorry?
Some hikers found his body,
two or three days later.
His skull had been beaten in,
with a stone.
I suppose it was Carlos.
-What?
-What will I do?
Captain, arrest me, please.
I've nowhere to go. He'll find me.
I don't want to end up like Manuela.
I've got good news.
Carlos is dead.
-Dead?
-Yes.
He drowned, with his hands
tied behind his back.
May he rest in peace.
Good be praised, Captain.
-I have to go.
-Go, or you'll miss your train.
Isabel, how do you say "good luck"
in Spanish?
-"Buena suerte", Captain.
-Buena suerte.
It's not a holy relic!
Thanks, this changes everything!
¡Hasta la victoria siempre!
Ciao!
Problems, Captain?
-Ah, you're here.
-Yes.
This thing here won't work.
It's so annoying.
Machines are like the soul.
They can be capricious.
-Shall I give you a ride?
-Yes, but I wanted to ask something.
What does having faith change?
Nothing and everything.
If that's all, you can shut your gob,
as my grandmother said.
Faith won't stop you limping,
but someone that loves you
will be at the end of the road.
Shall we play some pinball, instead?
Let's go.
Let's go! See you later, hot wheels.
Jesus is coming back.
Jesus is coming back to your people.
From upon your cross on high,
show us the way,
You, that know it so well.
Jesus says bear left!