Take me to seventh heaven.
OK.
You have to control your fall
and trajectory.
And see where everyone is.
You're not alone.
If while you're falling,
you go under your partner like this,
he'll fall on you.
It would be dumb to die so young.
-Carlos, you're holding us up!
-I'm coming!
-Have what you need?
-Yes. You'll look great.
CAPTAIN MARLEAU
125, 126, 127, 128,
129, 130, 131, 132...
Bidding on the clouds?
138, 139, 140.
Yes! I knew it!
What? Have we declared war?
Do you see that?
That silhouette, that arch...
Beautiful.
Yeah, that's a plane.
It's much more than that.
Are you kidding?
It's an angel from heaven.
I bet it would take 140 seconds
to circle the valley.
I always win my bets.
Lucky you.
I hate lucky people.
They're a personal affront.
It's not luck.
It's intelligence.
Exactly. That's even worse,
as Britney would say.
-OK. Goodbye, madam.
-Goodbye, madam.
UP IN THE AIR
I'll go first.
OK. Grab on.
Take me to seventh heaven.
There's only one.
Where's the other one?
There's one on the ground.
Alexandrine.
Dammit!
Yes, the Captain's here now.
Gentlemen.
Thank you.
Well?
It looks like she died from fractures
and internal bleeding
due to the speed of the fall,
which, at 4,000 meters
going against buoyant support,
was no faster than 195km/h.
Stop. I'm scared of heights.
I'm going to throw up.
Alexandrine Raguenès, member
of the Grandes Ailes parachute club.
23 years old, single.
Poor little thing.
Get the Captain, please.
Captain, the parachute specialist
wants to talk to you.
A parachutist?
I hope he's not here to torture us.
What do you say?
I'll say tampering, Captain.
Neither the main
nor emergency parachute opened,
and there's no hand deploy.
The grips were stuck
and the release mechanism failed.
Jeannette, go get a translator.
Of what?
An earth-to-sky translator. Go on.
She's actually going!
Jeannette, why are you leaving?
Come back.
Bijart will translate for us.
A hand deploy
is a small extraction parachute.
The parachutist takes it out
and releases it. It flies off,
pulling the strap
to pull on the chute and open it.
And bam! It didn't open.
-How awful!
-Yes, how awful!
It was a professional job.
The strap was cut.
They must have cut
the emergency parachute too,
which didn't open.
Tampering equals premeditation,
which equals murder.
Call the prosecutor, Jeannette.
Our team won't win the championship
this year.
What do you want?
To go and pretend?
Observe a minute of silence
like nothing happened?
We have 3 months...
We're not going. And stop drinking.
You're killing yourself.
Tell your husband to let it go.
This is not the time. Not today.
I'm sorry, old man. I love you.
That's why I'm a pain.
OK, OK.
And you're right.
All we can do is drink.
Elvira, another round for everyone.
Thanks.
To young Alexandrine.
Hello, ladies and gentlemen.
The national police would like
to offer its sincere condolences.
Oh! You don't waste any time.
Drinking straight up!
Be careful.
My colleagues are waiting outside
with breathalyzers.
They're so tricky.
So what are you betting on?
Accident or sabotage?
I never play around with death.
Me neither.
And besides, I'd be cheating,
because I just learned Alexandrine's
parachute was tampered with.
Folks,
Captain Marleau
and the corrections staff
will now circulate
to take your statements
and fingerprints
and scrape the inside of your cheeks
using a small cotton swab
found under your seats.
Thank you for choosing
Marleau Airlines.
Gentlemen, they're all yours.
You'll see. It's fun.
It tickles.
Odds are 100 to 1 one of you
is the murderer. Want to bet?
Are you obsessed?
You'd be surprised to know
I never bet on death or crime.
Too bad. It would save me time.
You've got it all wrong, Captain.
Everyone here loved Alexandrine.
Exactly. Love is a gypsy child.
It follows no laws.
And that makes for a good crime.
And if you like crime...
Watch out for me!
Hey, hey, hey!
Where to, Churchill?
My name is Clémence Dos Santos.
Nice to meet you.
Did you know the victim?
My husband Carlos is an instructor.
He jumped with her.
Is that why you were looking
up into the air?
-You saw me?
-Yes.
I didn't recognize you.
It was just this morning!
I'm sorry. I'm terrible with faces.
So you wouldn't recognize
the victim's face either?
No. Carlos was upset
after the accident,
but I didn't know her.
I never met her.
Well, get a good look at my face,
because I think
you'll be seeing it again soon.
She's strange, that one.
Run a background check on her:
Clémence Dos Santos.
She doesn't remember seeing me
this morning. How irritating.
Really? That's strange.
Is this Alexandrine in this photo?
She did a summer course
two years ago. She caught the bug.
She gave 100%.
I was training her for her license
so she could join
our formation skydiving team.
What's formation skydiving?
Not like defamation skydiving?
No. It's a sort of team sport.
But the slightest mistake
will cost you.
Does infidelity count?
That has nothing to do with it!
She was my student.
What exactly happened up there?
Nothing unusual.
It was our first jump of the day.
We did several tricks. It's on film.
You can watch the video.
Then we each went
in our own direction,
so we wouldn't hit each other.
I opened my parachute and...
I didn't see Alexandrine's.
She was gone.
Good morning!
Hush! Hush, Barbare.
Lie down, Barbare.
-Hello.
-Hello. Elvira Chastagne.
I'm in charge of traffic control
on the base.
And this is Barbare.
Marleau, national police.
Nice to meet you.
Someone's calling you.
Elvira, what do I do with the client?
Today won't work.
They closed the runway,
and I don't know
when they'll open it again.
Tomorrow or... a little later.
Thanks. Talk to you later.
You're making a real mess here.
It's awful.
Oh, it's awful!
Who could do that?
That's exactly what I wanted
to ask you.
Maybe the cat's among the pigeons.
A cat that knows about parachutes!
I pitched my tent at the end
of the runway. Is that a problem?
No, not at all.
If you need me,
I live in that little house,
with the flowerpots.
I'm there 24 hours a day.
The Labor Law is awful.
OK, well, thank you.
See you later.
Bye, Babar. Your dog doesn't look
like an elephant.
Thanks. You're a dear.
Ah! Do you recognize me now?
Yes. I'm not crazy.
You didn't yesterday.
I don't know what you mean,
but I remember you.
And you're not with your husband?
Who?
Your husband, Carlos Dos Santos.
He's my ex-husband.
Oh, I didn't think so.
I'd never go back to a jerk
who sleeps around.
I'm not a masochist.
So you think it's possible
he slept with Alexandrine?
I don't know who she is
but I'll bet 10 to 1 he did.
And I always win my bets.
Goodbye, Captain.
I bet... Sorry.
Jeannette!
See how he folds?
Do you do that at home?
-Uh... no!
-Me neither!
Sir?
When they finish folding them,
where do they go?
In there.
Who has a key?
We all have a key.
All the team members.
And who checks the parachutes?
Who checked Alexandrine's,
for example?
She did when folding it.
Before jumping, Carlos,
her instructor. They checked
each other's and jumped together.
Carlos. What a coincidence.
Carlos is a good guy.
He wouldn't hurt a fly.
He encouraged her.
He swore she'd jump
in the championship this year.
And then...
She didn't fall by herself.
The silence here is crazy!
You'd think you were in a cathedral.
Tell me, Mister...
What's your name?
Thibault Le Preux.
You were first on the scene.
Yes. She died in my arms.
I was a soldier for 20 years
but never saw a battlefield.
It's the first time I stared death
in the eyes.
What did she say?
She called for Carlos.
Oh, wow! It's an architect's house!
It's the Boulay forest.
I can see it's not a housing project!
Gentlemen.
-Hello.
-Hello!
This is beautiful!
As beautiful inside as outside!
Look at this view!
Thanks. It's my job.
I'm a landscape architect.
Oh, you designed those trees?
It's crazy. They look real.
Amazing!
Parachute jumps must pay well.
No. I pay for them.
Can't I earn more than my husband?
If I was a landscape architect,
I'd make more than my husband too.
But I don't have one.
Like you. You're divorced.
-From whom?
-Mr. Carlos.
Who told you that?
You did, earlier.
It doesn't matter.
Where is he?
He's not home yet.
He's in total shock.
Imagine a student dying in your arms.
But you bet me 10 to 1
she was his mistress.
That wasn't me, Captain.
It was my twin sister, Clara.
Your sister?
OK. So when you smoke smelly cigars
and make bets, it's your sister?
That's her.
And she was married to your husband?
She is his ex-wife, yes.
OK.
So you're your own sister-in-law,
in a way?
I'm lost.
Would you like some tea?
Was your husband a fighter pilot?
For 20 years.
With Thibault Le Preux,
who you must have met.
He was his mechanic.
They're inseparable.
Like Tanguy and Laverdure.
I loved watching them on TV.
So do you love diving,
flying and parachuting?
Is it your drug?
I fund the club but I hate planes.
You make no money from it?
My parents had plans
they always put off.
They wanted to go to Borneo and see
the sun rise over the North Cape.
They died in a plane crash
when I was 15.
Oh, my God!
I hated heights ever since
and live life to the fullest.
I understand.
So was it Carlos who told you
about the girl's death?
Yes, right away.
He said he'd never fly again.
I went to the club.
I said he couldn't give up,
that I loved him alive!
"Let's love each other alive,
not wait for death to abide."
That's St. François Valéry.
Write it.
Go on. Write it.
So what did your husband say?
Nothing. That was it.
Speak...
of the devil.
And he appears.
Carlos, could we speak alone
for a minute?
I have a question.
I have nothing to hide,
especially not from my wife.
Really?
Are you sure?
Because right before
Alexandrine died,
she said a name: Carlos.
Then she died, like in Batman.
Who said that?
God. We were chatting online earlier
but got cut off.
Your signal is weak here.
I still have this headache.
Never get old, Ismaël.
Why'd you say we were quitting?
I didn't say that,
just that I won't be there next week.
Are you kidding?
I'm screwed.
You're doing the job.
Look around. Cops are everywhere.
It's dangerous.
It has to calm down.
We must be invisible.
I'm not playing around.
I need my money. Now!
OK, OK. I'll work something out.
I'm your friend, Ismaël.
Don't forget that.
Let's go, sir.
I'm sorry, Mr. Raguenes,
but I need to know
who your daughter was.
I didn't know her that well.
I didn't even know
she was a parachutist.
I'm a farmer.
I never have time.
And her mother?
I was widowed 15 years ago.
I raised my daughter
as best as I could.
What kind of girl was Alexandrine?
She didn't need anyone.
When she was 11,
she wanted to go to boarding school.
She loved to work!
When was the last time
you talked to her?
At Christmas.
The neighbors told us
the seals were broken.
I let the technician in,
but maybe I shouldn't have.
I should've closed the scene
until you came back from the morgue.
But since you didn't answer
your phone, I...
Stop!
Can you stop with the guilt?
You're like an old Jesuit!
Yes, Captain.
Stop that too. I'm sick of it.
Did you find any samples, anything?
The technician took samples.
Clumps of hair
stuck in the shower drain.
Apparently hair can talk.
What language?
Say Portuguese
and I'll hit you.
Talking hair!
Can you imagine the morning breath?
Did you find any fingerprints?
No. Whoever came in here
wiped off all the fingerprints.
Did the cleaning fairy
steal anything?
I couldn't say.
But we have the computer,
because the guys who came to seal it
took it to the lab.
Now that's good news!
Always start with good news.
Otherwise how will we live?
Yes, Captain!
You nut.
What are you doing in the dark?
Come to bed.
Be honest.
Did you and she...?
Alexandrine?
She liked me a lot.
I was like her father or something.
Why didn't I ever meet her?
She would've bored you.
You're lying, Carlos.
I find it very pedestrian.
Clémence! There was never anything
between me and Alexandrine.
I swear!
I was about to close.
See? Even Barbare doesn't like me.
Give me something to drink.
The usual?
The usual, yes.
-There you go.
-Thanks.
I'll pour myself one.
Sing me my song.
Your song? Oh!
I want someone to choose me,
to love me,
before I get old,
to have a brave boy,
a friend, do this one thing:
just want me.
Cheers.
Hi, Mom.
I had a great day today.
I'm happy.
Even though I still miss you.
After all these years.
Of course I love him.
He's strong. He's funny.
Who is he?
He's gentle.
Tell Auntie Marleau.
But he's not free.
But I love him the way he is.
His name is Carlos.
Carlos!
Wait. What's the time code...
05:50:12.
I'll die if he leaves
You don't know how right you are,
sweetie.
Don't move!
Oh! What's his name?
Take it easy, Scooby Doo.
His name is Carlos.
I'll die if he leaves me.
OK. We'd been sleeping together
for a year.
You lied to me.
That's not good.
And yesterday you cleaned
her apartment.
I know you did.
Don't deny it.
The lab confirmed it.
It was our secret,
and I'd like it to stay that way.
A secret she wanted
to tell your wife.
Just before she died.
And when you have a rich wife
like yours,
that's a motive.
I didn't kill her.
OK. Then who did? A friend?
I don't know... Your wife?
No. Not her.
Not over that.
We have an open relationship.
You shocked?
Not at all.
I'm so unshocked
that I'll go tell your wife.
No, you can't.
I don't mind!
You can't hurt her.
Or what?
Are you going to be like Pinochet,
take me up in your plane
and throw me overboard?
That's one idea.
Fascist.
ohh, It's hot.
I heard you set up camp
at the end of the runway.
That's not very wise.
It's safe. An Alpine Shepherd
was watching me all night.
Is it true you spoke to Alexandrine
just before she died?
Yes.
You think I'm an idiot?
I know I look like one, but come on.
I spoke to the coroner.
He says she died
before she hit the ground.
So you couldn't have.
I swear I heard her call for Carlos!
I'm not crazy.
No. Well, yes.
He told me after she fell.
He was crying.
It's strange, because usually
we tell each other everything,
but he never told me.
Do you know De Seyne and Vladimir?
De Seyne was a pilot
and Vladimir was his mechanic.
De Seyne refused to jump
from a burning plane
because Vladimir was onboard
but had no parachute.
They tried to land twice
before they crashed.
They were buried together.
You see, madam,
Carlos and I are the same way.
Lovely. You're like the Montaigne
and Boétie of flying.
May I?
Go ahead.
Thank you. That's kind of you.
Then it's strange he didn't tell you
he'd been seeing Alexandrine
for a year.
Maybe he didn't want to hurt me.
Before marrying Clémence 2 years ago,
Carlos was married to Clara.
Then one day,
he left her, divorced her,
and married the other one.
I like Clémence, but I have to say
that Clara was different.
She's like us.
She loves planes.
Of course, the two sisters
got in a fight,
and I had to choose a side.
Choose a side, my friend.
You chose Carlos's side,
like Alexandrine.
Maybe that wasn't such a good idea.
Bye!
Hello.
Come in, quick.
I'm making a fire.
My boiler
broke and of course,
the heating guy never showed up.
The house is drafty.
Make yourself useful.
If you're interested,
I'm on an investigation
into Alexandrine Raguenes,
or her murder, anyway.
Of course I am.
Especially if my sister's involved.
Really?
That should feel better now.
Oh, it's hot!
Oh, do you kayak?
That's a giant oar.
It's a propeller.
Really?
This is my office, where I work.
I usually draw the curtains.
I like the dark.
It helps me concentrate. I write.
What are you writing? A novel?
I'm a historian,
studying the cathartic function
of torture in Ancient Rome.
The cross, the fire, the wheel.
Crosses of fire were gory.
And throwing a young girl
off a cliff was torture too.
Yes. They threw people
off the Tarpeian Rock,
but that was during the Republic.
I'm an Empire expert.
A Lady Napoleon?
Not exactly.
What was Lady Napoleon doing
on Thursday night?
I was here in this chair,
working until dawn.
OK.
Would you like some tea, Captain?
No, I'm joking.
What would you like?
Vodka, cognac, bourbon?
Doesn't matter. I drink local.
Hops, grapes, whatever you like.
You have a beautiful home.
Too bad we can't smoke.
Oh, no. That's right.
You smoke cigars.
So, can anyone testify
you were here that night?
I live alone.
You're a woman of good taste.
I didn't have a choice.
When your husband leaves you
for your twin,
you feel a bit bitter about men.
I understand.
So when you found out your ex-husband
was cheating on your sister,
did you go, "Yeah!" or, "Ohh..."?
Why do you care?
I care because, just for example,
if in a fit of anger,
you took revenge on Alexandrine.
Then my investigation would be over.
Nap, recess, gym.
But if I were the murderer,
I wouldn't kill her
but that jerk Carlos.
I didn't do anything.
Neither did I.
Is he that much of a jerk?
One day, he asked for a divorce.
That same day, I found out
he'd had a mistress for months:
my sister.
-How's that?
-It doesn't earn him much empathy.
I tried everything. I wanted
to get revenge, to make him pay.
I won a huge alimony settlement.
Guess what? My sister paid it.
I last saw them in court.
She said, "Now we don't owe you."
For what?
You know, I find hate and anger
exhausting.
I prefer a mustard bath.
But you don't seem exhausted.
With your little arms,
you can defend yourself
against anyone who gets in your way.
You have no idea.
In Caligula's day,
the torture for guys like him
was damnatio ad bestias.
What?
Torn apart alive
by ferocious animals.
How awful! Poor animals.
-Hello.
Well?
This is good,
but what if we move the pergola
toward the pond?
What do you think?
I'll be right back.
Clara?
The police just came over
to ask me about Carlos.
He killed his mistress.
What are you saying?
Nothing. I just wanted you to know
that he'll suck you dry
and then abandon you.
And you'll die alone.
Where is Carlos?
He's not answering his phone.
I don't know.
Did you know? How long
have you been covering for him?
I'm sorry.
He's my friend.
I know you don't like me much.
Why do you say that?
That's not true.
Don't bother.
I don't like you either.
This one?
No, maybe that one, on the left.
Oh, yes. Hang on.
I've almost got it.
No, no.
This one?
What the hell is going on here?
You scared me, Captain!
I hope so.
What are you two doing in here?
You authorized Mr. Dos Santos
to get Alexandrine's parachute.
Me? I didn't authorize anything.
Especially not a key witness
to walk around the evidence room.
Are you crazy?
I thought it was OK.
And Mr. Dos Santos
swore you said it was OK.
Go find a whistle.
You're back on traffic duty.
I don't want to see you. Go!
Come on...
I know she's not too bright,
but what's your excuse?
I need to see what the murderer did.
The tampering would be his signature.
The parachute isn't here.
It's on the judge's desk.
You want to play CSI?
Go play with him.
What time is it? 15:27.
I'm placing you in custody.
What's wrong with you?
You're a real piece of work.
You enter the victim's apartment,
you try to steal evidence
from under my nose,
which is rather big,
and you marry twin sisters
and cheat on them both.
In short, you lie to everyone.
It's a bit much.
You saw Clara.
She's completely insane.
Well, I understand.
I have a friend.
On his wedding day, his wife cheated
on him with his best friend.
He went insane.
So I imagine being cheated on
by your own twin sister
must really be something.
I picked the wrong sister.
Then I spent years with the one
who stinks of death.
But one day I decided it had to stop,
because life is too short.
So I grab it, eat it, devour it.
You're not Prince Charming.
You're the ogre.
But then who is the big bad wolf?
It's not me.
I would never do anything
that could risk
putting me in a 7m2 hole
and keep me from flying.
Never.
Then who did?
Clara.
I admit I considered it,
but I need a motive.
-Hate.
-Yes. That's not bad.
And an hour ago, she threatened
to throw you to the bestias.
I don't know what they are,
but they don't sound vegetarian.
We have to replace these five steps
with a disabled ramp.
OK.
Yoohoo!
Who's that?
Hello! Police.
What's the problem?
Can't you see we're working?
You think we're here to play Colombo?
Hang on. I left my cigarettes
on the desk. May I?
Cigarettes? Aren't you ashamed
to smoke at your age?
Let me see.
Fumar mata.
OK, go kill yourself outside.
Vià.
-Hello, madam.
-Captain.
I have a little search warrant
signed by the judge,
and I wanted to inform you
that your husband is in custody.
That's it.
I'm freaking out.
There are at least 20 of them.
Yes, really aggressive.
It's about the parachutist, clearly.
It's some serious action.
Hang on. I'll send a photo.
No photos allowed.
Captain.
Don't touch that.
It's personal.
Madam, don't get upset.
If it's not relevant,
we'll put it back. That's it.
They're letters from my mom.
How are they relevant?
What exactly are you looking for?
Anything: scissors,
pruning shears, tweezers...
Anything that can cut.
I'm not much fun.
Oh, look! Come see this, Captain.
That's a Beretta 9mm.
Do much sport shooting?
It's Carlos's service weapon.
I suppose you have the permit for it?
I suppose I could find it
somewhere in this mess.
Is there ammunition too?
No. There never was.
He never shot it.
Here's a valid permit.
Geez. You're upset.
When your head's in your shoulders,
it means you're upset.
You look like your sister.
Same green eyes.
Did Clara send you here?
When did you find out
about Alexandrine and Mr. Carlos?
Recently.
When you found out,
how angry were you?
Angry enough to kill her.
I'm joking.
There's a time and place.
National police, OK?
-Will you return my Beretta?
-I have to.
She wasn't killed by a gun
but a parachute.
And your permit is good.
I'm disappointed.
And Carlos?
No, I'm hanging on to him.
You can't have it both ways, madam.
OK, guys. Let's go.
Say bye to the lady.
-Goodbye, Madam.
You're very lucky
I don't like punishing people.
Thank you, Captain.
Let's play a game.
You take my phone.
I bet you
that in less than one minute,
the prosecutor will call me.
I bet you a beer.
Know why? Because we're not all equal
in the eyes of the law!
Some say we are,
but some are more equal than others.
Watch closely.
Well?
I win a beer!
-Pass it to me.
-I'll pick up.
Hello? Prosecutor, my God!
What a pleasant surprise.
How... Yes, of course.
We'll leave her alone.
The chief of staff? No!
OK. Very well then.
No problem. Thank you.
Goodbye, Prosecutor.
Goodbye.
You can hang up.
See? I told you.
So what do we do, Captain?
Stop questioning Clémence Dos Santos?
Why would we do a thing like that?
You just told the prosecutor
we'd leave her alone.
Listen, grasshopper.
Sometimes people think
they want one thing
but they really want the opposite.
Got it?
Can I have a drink?
Not your boring old tea either.
I heard your husband is in custody,
so I came over.
I spent many dinners
alone waiting too.
He always came home
with his pretty face full of lies.
Did you kill that girl?
Did you?
I wouldn't do it that way.
I don't know parachutes.
But you...
I'm not afraid of jumping,
or killing, I don't think.
But I had no reason to kill her.
On the contrary.
I'm glad he made you suffer too.
And I hope it really hurts.
Even though what I went through
is different from what you will.
Because competing
with a simple mistress
and your twin sister
is not the same thing.
I apologized 1,000 times, Clara.
I loved him then and I do now.
So did I.
I wouldn't kill her.
But I could kill him,
if I get the chance.
Don't take him from me.
What are the odds I will?
3 to 1? 15 to 1?
I don't play those games.
They're not funny.
Well, I do.
You had to pay a big price for him,
but now he's destroying you.
It wouldn't be hard
to get rid of him.
I could do it.
Get out.
Mr. Dos Santos, you're free to go.
This way, please.
You look thrilled.
What's all this?
I want you to go.
I want you out of my life.
I'm beat, my back hurts...
I don't care.
I don't want to hear it. Get out.
Was it Clara?
She came here, didn't she?
I knew it.
Don't let her do this to us.
Your sister is crazy.
I love you, Clémence.
You're all I have.
I didn't kill that girl,
or sleep with her.
She was in love.
She said all kinds of things,
made things up.
When I was 14,
I had a boyfriend, Julien.
One day I went out with someone else,
and I told him.
He got sick and left school.
I never saw him again.
My dad yelled at me and told me
admitting it
hurts someone for no reason.
I'm not 14 anymore, Carlos,
and I want to know the truth.
Don't protect me.
Come here.
Come here, I said.
You weren't followed?
You still interested?
Yes. You think I enjoy not flying,
This has made a mess of things.
You're lucky I'm nice.
He's gone. Gone!
I'm sure you had dozens
of mistresses, Dad.
How do I know?
Intuition. But you never left Mom.
You busy?
I knew you'd be here today.
Leave us alone, Clara.
Stay away from your sister.
You're hurting her.
Leave us alone!
You're one to talk.
Who cheated on her? Took her money?
Lied to her all day long?
Me?
Don't touch me!
Hey! Calm down, Addams Family.
This isn't Dracula, but it bites.
Careful.
You don't have to exaggerate,
Ms. Innocent.
You'll pay in court.
Sorry, but I have to re-arrest you,
Mr. Carlos.
OK, but I want to show you
something first.
What?
Alexandrine's body
was released to her family.
The funeral is on Tuesday.
I'm going.
I'll go with you.
What about you?
I'll go too.
Good.
I'm going too.
What's Carlos doing?
Carlos is doing what he can.
Look. He's taking off.
It's small. It's tiny.
Aaaah! Did we take off?
We're going to fall!
We're going to crash!
I knew it!
Stop it!
I'm scared! I fell
off a stepladder when I was little.
I'm scared of heights!
You know, you should never let go
of childhood phobias
of things like spiders and heights.
That's what you say!
It's letting go of your childhood.
This is what I wanted to show you.
I shared it with Alexandrine.
And that's stronger than anything.
Really?
Well, I know a guy named Bacarus.
He got too close to the sun
and melted.
Flying is one of mankind's
greatest dreams.
What's that path?
Where does it go?
Nice and easy.
I actually liked it.
You didn't put on your blinker.
My colleagues are on the runway.
They'll arrest you.
This way out.
Your place is too small
for legs like mine.
Next time we'll jump.
The guy who gets me to jump
from a plane
hasn't been born yet.
Oh, shoot.
Maybe you can help me after all.
I got the forensics report
on Alexandrine's parachute.
In short, it says the saboteur,
or the murderer,
cut the straps on both parachutes,
the main one and emergency one.
What do you think?
You can't stop that.
You can't? Wouldn't you have noticed?
When you were folding it
or before you jumped?
When we check a parachute,
we look for mistakes,
not malicious intent.
Well, happy trails.
The investigation isn't over,
but it's stalled!
It's a complicated job.
I love crime thrillers.
You're lucky.
Can I take you to dinner?
You can tell me all about it.
No, that won't be possible,
my friend,
because you're a suspect,
to put it simply,
and we're investigators,
so no dice.
Apples and oranges don't mix.
OK.
When you're done,
I'll take you to dinner.
I promise.
You're in love, Sergeant.
Not at all, Captain.
We were just talking.
She's in love!
Be careful. We're like prostitutes.
You can't
fall in love.
Of course! I'm not an idiot.
Rebelling?
Good! It's about time.
Come on.
Let's go play drug dogs.
Hang on, Jeannette.
Oh, this is rustic.
I like it.
Look, Captain.
There are tracks.
That's what I saw from the plane.
As my friend Jean-Louis says,
where there's one, there's more.
Look. They keep going.
It's like a path.
But how can a car get through here?
Just like a cow.
It pushes the gate.
What is this road?
Look at your GPS.
Hang on.
There are potholes.
This road is D191, to Erosse.
Eros, pass me the sponge.
Then to Orléans and La Rochelle?
Yes.
It looks like an abandoned
hunting cabin.
There' are no animals
when there are houses like this.
Let's see what's inside.
Oh! Your Canadian cabin
doesn't look so abandoned.
The lock is brand-new.
Shall we go in the old-fashioned way?
One, two and... three!
There's nothing. It's clean.
It's too clean, in fact.
That means someone swept.
Do you have your chemistry kit,
Marie Curie?
Yes, Captain.
Then before it gets dark,
take these little fingerprints
off the lock. OK?
OK.
You're too good.
I didn't know about that path.
I never go to the end
of the property. No one does.
I'd be surprised...
It's mowed! Right?
If it's mowed, it's maintained.
We have a farmer who mows for us,
and there's Ismaël too.
Ismaël doesn't have much money,
so we pay him to work
eight hours a week.
That's nice.
So Ismaël manages the fence.
Yes. Why?
You're no cop.
I can tell by your mischievous look.
Call the lab and ask them
to compare Ismaël's fingerprints
to the ones on the lock, OK?
-OK.
-Thanks!
Tilt!
Thank you.
It's impressive how fast
a Babarman dog can eat!
I timed him.
It takes him 9 seconds.
Fumar mata...
Were you in Spain?
No, Ismaël gets them
and sells them to me.
Ismaël again.
That's a terrible idea.
Dealing in cigarettes kills.
I called the lab, Captain.
The fingerprints match Ismaël's.
There you go.
And what would he keep in his cabin,
other than vodka and cigarettes?
And it all goes through your runway.
That's also what airfields are for.
That's impossible.
I see everything, know everything.
I make the flight plans
and...
Nothing gets by you.
Nothing gets by me.
Then you're an accomplice.
And so is your dog.
So handcuffs, police, prison,
dog pound.
No, I'm kidding.
So where can we find
the cigarette king?
It stinks.
There are two of them.
-Who's that?
-I don't know.
National Police.
-Olaf Longstrump?
-Yes.
That's a dumb name.
Captain Marleau. Step aside.
Is that the new Tarkovski?
I saw it. He dies at the end.
Smells like weed in here.
I'm looking for a Mr. Ismaël Diallo.
Do you know him?
He doesn't live here.
When I got a girlfriend
I asked him to leave.
Know where he's living now?
No, no idea.
I told you everything.
Can we watch the movie now?
You know what?
You're lying, Pinocchio.
I'll be back later.
What did she say?
The lady said she's coming back.
Arrivederci.
Jeannette, are you coming?
Goodbye.
Well?
We should tell Ismaël
the cops are after him.
Why bother?
He got himself into trouble.
He could have blood on his hands.
I'm not getting involved.
Are we coming back?
No, but I'll sic the drug squad
on them.
Tonight we'll set up a patrol
at the airfield
in case he comes back.
Then we'll catch his ass!
Hello? Yes.
What?
Gentlemen.
What does it look like?
He was shot in the middle
of the chest.
I'd say he died
between 23:00 and 2:00 a.m.
Any signs of a fight?
Looks like it.
He must have fought.
Look at this mess: here, here...
Fought or argued.
Maybe he was defending himself.
Maybe he found out
about Ismaël's smuggling.
And so did Alexandrine.
Either way, no more flying for him.
Where is the widow?
In her office.
Thank you.
Madam.
I didn't hear anything.
I sleep with earplugs.
You weren't worried he wasn't in bed?
We were sleeping apart.
Around 4:00 a.m.,
I walked by the guest room.
The door was open.
He wasn't inside.
I saw a light in the living room.
I went in...
And you found him.
4:00 a.m. is pretty early.
I was getting water.
Water...
And did you find the murder weapon?
Where is the Beretta?
I don't understand.
It was there.
Still no ammunition?
There was a bullet hole.
I don't know.
You don't know, you don't know.
Get any visitors last night?
Someone must have known
where the gun was kept.
No, no one.
What caliber bullet
do you think killed him?
I'd bet it was a 9mm.
Beretta 9mm?
I have to remove it.
Of course.
How stupid of me. Bye.
Jeannette, are you coming?
Someone's asking for you.
-Who?
-Raphaël.
What'd he find?
What is it?
and found the pistol.
The fingerprints were wiped clean.
I also found an open box
of ammunition and this strap.
It's the same as the one
on Alexandrine's parachute.
Do you think his wife
killed them both out of jealousy?
You look disappointed.
I'll make the call.
Are you coming?
Quit flirting!
So who tampered
with the parachute for you?
A friend? Someone you paid?
Of course I was hurt when I found out
Carlos was sleeping with that girl.
But I'd never kill her.
I don't know about parachutes!
You don't. But your sister does.
Isn't she a longtime fan of flying?
She was your accomplice.
I don't see Clara anymore.
She hates me for taking Carlos.
That's understandable.
You can't know.
Well, I'm not Noam Chomsky,
but sometimes I get flashes
of intelligence, so explain it.
We may look physically identical,
but we're profoundly different.
Our whole lives,
people tried to compare us.
In a game of spot the difference,
Clara won every time.
More funny, more brilliant,
more spiritual, more everything...
I understand,
because if I'd had a twin sister,
she would've had it rough too,
poor thing.
I was more serious, more studious,
certainly not very fun.
Even my parents never hid
that they preferred my sister.
So when Carlos told me
he'd always preferred me to her,
I was shocked, and I couldn't resist.
Did you know your sister
and your husband fought yesterday?
I had to separate them.
She almost bit me.
He didn't tell me.
As usual.
I'm very annoyed, Mrs. Clémence,
because I have a lot
of compelling evidence against you.
A little too much, for my taste.
So I'll ask the question
one last time:
did your sister know
where you hid this gun?
I haven't seen Clara in two years.
She had no idea where that gun was.
What are you doing here?
How'd you get out?
Through the wall?
It's witchcraft...
No, genetics.
I want to see Captain Marleau.
End of the hall.
Thank you.
Where is she?
Calm down, keep your distance,
take a chair and sit down.
Where's my sister?
Yesterday you couldn't care less
about her.
What do you know?
I'm very curious,
so explain it to me.
I'm listening.
When we are together,
nothing can stop us.
When life separates us,
everything falls apart.
How sad. Poor little rich girl.
And in the meantime, in Syria...
OK, OK.
What were you doing last night
around midnight?
I was playing poker at Réjane's.
I won a ton of money.
They'll remember.
OK. We'll check.
And as for your sister,
the judge will decide.
For the Romans,
Justice was the daughter of Jupiter.
She wore a blindfold
as a sign of impartiality.
Captain, are you sure
you're being impartial?
I don't know,
but I bet 10 to 1 you'll tell me.
I think you find my sister
profoundly unsympathetic.
She is beautiful, rich, cultured,
and a bit too reserved
for your taste.
That often makes people misjudge her.
But she didn't kill Carlos.
Did you?
I would love to, but I didn't.
I would never have taken the man
my sister loves.
A sister's love is delicious.
Especially with pastry.
Are you another sister?
Which wall will you go through?
I'll go through the door
after seven hours in custody.
That will be fine.
My bag, please.
I knew you couldn't help
going through the wall.
Captain, why are you doing that?
That's your report.
Yep. Clara was cleared.
At the time of the crime she was
playing cards with the prefect's son,
a certain Jérôme Léglise.
And she beat him in poker.
And her sister?
Her sister was released too.
It's no big deal.
We'll keep an eye on her
and see where it leads.
Do you think they could have
switched places?
That's a version I would've loved,
but just know that not everyone
has your imagination, my dear.
Let's say that were the case.
Clémence would be a real idiot
if she left the gun and the straps
in the car.
Would you like tea or coffee?
Hot chocolate.
OK.
The gun under the spare tire, maybe.
But what would the straps
be doing there?
Why not get rid of them?
Like she would bring them home
and wait for us to find them.
That's nonsense.
You're right.
It makes no sense.
I agree.
I'm looking for Ismaël Diallo.
Where is he?
Ismaël? Why?
Because.
I saw him go into the hangar earlier.
The hangar over there?
OK. Come on. We'll walk.
This isn't right.
You're shorting me.
It's an advance.
I can't give you any more.
You'll have to, or I'll kill you!
You're dead. You hear me?
You're done, my friend. Look.
Ismaël?
Yoohoo, Ismaël!
Where is that idiot?
Hey, Captain!
The idiot's not dead.
Ismaël?
Dammit! Catch him!
So we have: one phone,
a pack of cigarettes
marked "Fumar mata."
Tu hablas español
or should I translate?
These will kill you.
And a little stack of cash.
How much is there?
At least 500 euros.
For a guy with no money,
you're loaded.
I hope we find Le Preux,
otherwise you'll have to pay
for the both of you.
And there are already two bodies...
How much is two plus two?
-30 years?
-Yes. You'll get life in prison.
I didn't kill anyone.
Not Alexandrine, not Carlos.
I just set up a business to get by.
Every other Thursday,
Le Preux flies a private plane
to his sister's in the Pyrenees,
with a rich guy who plays bridge
and comes back at night.
During the day, Le Preux loads
the merchandise from Spain.
The border's on the property.
How are you?
The guy suspects nothing.
All he cares about is cards.
At night, I unload the merchandise,
store it and sell it.
Oh! What's this little key?
I bet it opens the cabin
at the end of the path.
That's right.
I took the goods out.
We thought we'd get caught.
I have a daughter, you know.
A little angel.
If I don't pay support,
I can't see her.
She's all I have.
I made mistakes.
I'm in debt.
I need money.
I need to see my daughter.
But I didn't kill anyone.
Don't cry, Jeannette.
How do you recognize
the different parachutes?
Aren't they all the same?
They have our colors,
for the championship.
They're numbered, here.
Ah, OK. But could Alexandrine
have confused her parachute
with Carlos's?
No. He would've realized it.
Carlos saw everything.
Ah, he saw everything.
So he saw the cigarette smuggling.
So Le Preux wanted to kill him.
So he came here at night.
But it was dark.
He didn't turn the lights on
because the dog would eat him,
so he groped around
and got the wrong parachute.
He would never have hurt Carlos.
They were like brothers.
Yes, but in the Bible,
plenty of brothers kill each other.
-Captain?
-What is it, Jeannette?
Ismaël told me Le Preux was going
to where they hid the merchandise.
OK. Let's go.
I'm sure he's in here.
Ah! Le Preux.
Dammit. It's locked.
Problem? There are always solutions.
There we go.
-Is that legal?
-No.
You look over there.
Oh, a big plane!
Find anything?
Nothing?
Wow! A big propeller!
It looks like what they use
on gondolas, those big oars.
The last one I saw was in Venice.
No, the last time I saw one
was at Cambelle Manor.
Like Campbell's Soup.
Come see this, Captain.
Here. It will go faster with this.
You don't smoke?
-No.
-OK then!
Let's seize it all.
What is all this?
Does he smuggle medicine too?
I know someone who can tell me
what this is.
It's Marleau! Can you help me?
Marleau! You know how much
I love helping you!
If I say Betaxol
and Duretine 500,
what would you say?
You're dealing with someone
with a very bad heart.
What does your patient do
for a living?
He repairs Soviet planes
or something.
He flies planes and parachutes.
I'd be surprised!
Taking all those drugs, the rascal!
He's not allowed to fly!
No doubt about it.
Marleau, I have a friend,
Dr. Perrotin.
He's a civil aviation doctor.
Give him a call.
He's a good guy.
I kiss your hand!
Bye, Marleau.
The police?
Ah, Dr. Salaun sent you.
Dr. Perottin?
Yes, I'll find him right away.
Here he is.
Doctor, it's the national police.
Unfit... for good?
Thank you.
My goodness!
Well?
Le Preux is done with planes.
He's not allowed to fly.
You know who told
the health authorities? Carlos.
He got revenge?
That's a pretty good motive.
What? Don't you like it?
I prefer the sister-switching.
Sister-switching?
You naughty little thing.
I thought you were more S&M.
What are you doing here?
What do you want?
Hello?
Why the gun, Thibault?
Clémence!
You don't have to shout.
It's just us.
Don't be afraid, Clara.
Carlos is dead.
He paid for his mistakes.
He begged me before he died...
He asked me...
No, he asked us...
Answer the phone.
I can't pick up. I'm driving!
Thank you.
Hello?
Captain Marleau?
My sister is in danger.
Yes. From Thibault Le Preux?
Yes.
I know.
OK, OK. We'll send you a car.
Yes. Hang up.
Turn on the siren, sweetie.
Don't look at me like that.
Did you kill the girl?
She died, yes.
But I didn't mean to.
I drank and made a mistake.
Carlos should have died.
So after you made a mistake,
you fixed it? How persistent of you!
He read the coroner's report
and realized it was me.
Why'd you want to kill him?
Because I have a heart problem.
And Carlos knew.
He didn't want to cover for me
and wanted to keep me from flying.
You understand!
It's more than cruel!
It's inhuman!
Thibault, you're sick.
I've known a long time.
I covered for you, but...
I can't anymore. I'm done.
I can't take that risk.
If I can't fly,
I may as well kill myself.
Stop. Don't say that.
Isidore will take over for you.
I'm sorry, old man.
It's nothing against you.
It's just too dangerous.
Then there was you.
What about me?
I love you, Clara.
I've always loved you.
And you chose Carlos.
So what now?
Let's go away together.
I'll take you far away,
far from here,
far from your sister,
far from all this mess.
I love you, you know.
I love you.
It feels so good
to be able to tell you that.
Kiss me, darling. Kiss...
Captain. It's the only room
in the house with a light on.
All the others are dark.
They must be there.
OK. Let's go see.
What are you doing?
Coming with you!
Are you crazy? It's too dangerous.
You stay here. She's insane!
And what do I do?
Stay by the window.
Stay with your friends, OK?
Don't worry. It will be fine.
What are you doing here?
Go back to Jeannette.
She's insane, that one.
Are you ready?
Yes. Ready.
Don't move!
Back up. Let us go.
-Let her go.
-Clara!
Get out of here, Clémence!
Get out of here!
Don't move.
Go, Clémence! Get out of here.
Back off, Clémence!
Don't move. Come on, guys!
Get out of here.
Carlos will be among the clouds,
like he wanted.
I think, anyway.
We never talked about death
or immobility.
We thought we were invincible.
He did, anyway.
He thought being in the sky
made him immortal.
Go on, cry.
It's good for you.
I would've liked a twin sister.
A pretty little thing, like me.
But too much beauty in one family
wouldn't be elegant.
Subtitling: Hiventy