CAPTAIN MARLEAU
ILLUSION
Alex!
Alex, that's enough now!
It's not funny!
Have you seen Alex?
No, sorry.
Alex! Alex!
Alex!
Alex...
Alex, you scared me!
Come on.
Come, Alex.
LEO
Fine... Fine, but
could you move it
towards me a little...
and a bit more in front?
Sorry to ask you that now, but...
-Mrs. Garin?
-Yes?
Are the garlands okay?
Yes, very nice. Put some over there,
that'll look nice.
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Brilliant, Cédric! Really!
You had me fooled
right the way through.
I never saw it coming.
I never guessed the culprit.
Very good.
I'm delighted, but you...
Why can't you be less formal with me?
I'd rather be formal
if unpleasant things are to be said.
You've got unpleasant things to say?
No. But you do.
What don't you like
about my manuscript?
Nothing, nothing at all. Well...
two or three tiny blunders.
The cop breaking down near
where the murder happens,
I find that a bit...
a bit silly, a bit unsubtle...
What's up with you, honey?
Shit! Fuck! I don't believe this!
Bloody thing! Dammit!
Fuck, there's no signal either!
No way!
Hello?
Well, you won't get stolen.
Look at that!
At least it's not raining.
It's pretty here!
Hello! Anyone there?
Hey, my darling,
did you have fun with Elsa?
Okay, time for your maths lesson.
But, Dad, there's no school today.
It's Wednesday.
Other kids don't get to have
a teacher like Cédric to themselves!
And look at the playground you have!
Right? Off you go.
Go on, off you go!
Or you won't be ready for the party!
Shall we do this, Champ?
I need to talk to you.
Not here, there are too many people.
I thought I could trust you.
Why do you say that?
You're here as an au pair. I pay you
well, you get bed and board.
This is your home.
But we said "no visits". Remember?
Where do you two meet?
In your bedroom?
In Marc's studio.
When he's out recording his stuff.
You really disappoint me, Elsa.
I'm sorry.
You know I'm fond of you,
so sort it out by tonight. Okay?
Another mid-life crisis?
Leave me alone.
It's not your problem.
Well, it is a bit, isn't it?
-Do you have a sister?
-No.
Then I have no use for you.
Bunch of idiots!
Fucking idiots...
I'm sick of this!
Stop!
Police, good evening.
Nice to see that some people
still care about others at this time.
Right, I'm getting in the back.
Hi, doggies. Okay, off we go!
Right, Auntie Marleau's getting out.
There we go.
Right, goodbye, girls! Bye!
CAFÉ
THE WHITE CROSS
-Good evening.
-Evening.
I'm sorry, I smell of mutts.
What a nice place! My God!
Not many folk about. It's quiet.
Yup, the rats have abandoned ship.
Gilles Garin's giving a party,
so they're all there.
Garin? Who is Gilles Garin?
Never heard of Gilles Garin?
The famous crime novelist?
The "Master of Thrills"?
Crime novels are rubbish,
I prefer romance.
It's more realistic.
I've got all the "Mills and Boons".
Could I get a small beer?
Just a tiny wee snifter.
Ta.
How come you're not at the do?
Don't you like pen-pushers?
Yes, but not all of them.
Are you eating?
And sleeping.
Do you have any rooms?
Yes.
Are the local mechanics
at his Majesty's bash as well?
I'll make you some food.
That's kind of you!
Stop, that's enough now.
What's wrong, Sir,
this is a party, isn't it?
My dear friends!
How lovely it is to see you all here
with us:
Alex, my son, the love of my life,
Judith, my wife,
the other love of my life,
and my publisher.
So please don't tell her
my next book isn't finished yet.
I'm counting on you.
Otherwise, I'll be in trouble.
As you know,
I don't go in for long speeches,
I prefer the pen.
I'll be brief,
since I haven't prepared a speech.
Today is a... special day for me.
For all of us.
And I thought
today's date would be perfect
for launching a...
special project too.
You see, I think that each one of us,
each one of you,
can become a writer.
I think
that everyone has something to say,
an imagination, a story to tell.
So, I have created a foundation:
The...
Alex...
and Leo Foundation.
Each year,
this foundation will propose
a short story competition.
On whatever subject you like.
Love, revenge, murder, bereavement...
It is up to you. You decide.
And the winner...
The...
What's with Garin?
Leo died four years ago.
The winner will receive 3,000 euros
and have the privilege
of being helped...
by "the Master of Thrills"
to finish his or her story,
which my company shall publish.
But I think you all know about that.
Party time!
What's that? Fireworks? I love 'em!
The pen-pusher's do?
For sure. That kind of power play
has to be him!
You're not very receptive to
the charms of literature, my friend.
Let's say I prefer charm
to be a bit more discreet.
I'm the opposite.
I like trashy stuff,
kitschy, ugly stuff.
Like your lamp over there.
What's wrong with my lamp?
It's nice, I like it.
It was my mother's.
Sorry.
Strange
that Elsa didn't come to the party.
Shall we see if she's okay?
No, we can't disturb her
at this hour. It's far too late.
I'm sure she's fine. Don't worry.
Shit! Unbelievable!
Hello? What?
No, no, I'm out jogging.
Yeah. So she's dead, so what?
I'll be there later. Yup, bye.
They're getting on my tits.
Lieutenant Tahar.
Garin.
She was part of the family.
I have some questions to ask you.
No need to go easy on me,
Lieutenant.
I don't know much anyway.
When was the last time
you saw the victim?
She felt poorly last night,
she went to bed at 7 p.m.
She wasn't at breakfast,
so I went to see her...
I'll call the police chief in Lille,
he's a friend.
He'll spare no expense.
Out here, us gendarmes are competent.
I've called Forensics.
They're sending someone over.
I'm on the force: Captain Marleau.
This is you?
Yes, before the operation.
I used to be called Bernard.
Ta!
What's with you?
Where is it?
Who are you?
Undertakers' customer care agent.
-Which way?
-First floor.
-First floor?
-Yeah.
I'd say she died last night
between 9 p.m. and 11 p.m.
Hello, ladies and gents!
Captain Marleau.
So what's happened?
Lieutenant Tahar.
I've just rung the unit.
How did you get here so quickly?
I can run the 400 m
in under 5 minutes 30.
So, preliminary findings?
Rigor mortis,
what d'you reckon, mate?
Garin, Gilles Garin.
I am...
Well, I was this girl's employer.
She looked after my son.
Ah, so you're our famous writer?
You hosted that bash last night
for the village?
With the bangers, concerts, etc,
nasty smokescreen
for a murder, right?
What do you mean?
You think I staged a smokescreen?
No...
But please undershtand, dear shir,
I never imply anything.
Even under torture.
Down with irony!
I was simply saying reality
is sometimes fucked up.
For example, a writer might be
after inspiration for his next book.
And it turns out rotten
for a kid like her.
I might ring my friend in Lille...
Better to be safe than sorry.
No, definitely not.
Lille is out with this jurisdiction.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
Do what you like,
but stay off my crime scene.
You'll dirty it.
I did actually take precautions.
When I found the body,
I stayed in the doorway.
I know the procedure.
Ah, you're a meticulous man.
I love that!
Great. Well, since we have
the circumstances,
could we talk about the...
protagonists in this story?
That's what you call them, right?
For example,
might someone hold something
against this girl?
I don't know. No.
Elsa had no past.
She was my best friend's daughter.
Before he died,
I promised I'd look after her.
We're her only relatives.
So she didn't even have
an old sugar daddy somewhere?
-No.
-No?
No. No one. Only us.
If I can help you...
Ah, that's so kind of you. Thank you.
You could help by leaving the room.
It's nothing personal...
but when I have a star like you
in front of me...
I lose my cool... I don't know...
I won't be able to work.
Okay, as you wish.
Well, I remain
at your disposal, of course.
I'm going to blush.
Thank you, Boss.
Wasn't he going a bit over the top?
"The poor kitten is dead."
Acting like Robert Hirsch,
Isabelle Adjani, right?
Right then, it's up to us three.
It's hot, isn't it?
So, the victim's called Elsa Floriot
and she was 22.
Yeah... Elsa Floriot, 22 years old.
Look at these!
Do they suit me?
Well, I... I...
Yeah, okay...
Here, this is nuts, see it?
The underwear is very...
But the outerwear...
is rather... right?
Yes, definitely. Yes.
I wonder who she allowed
to look beneath the appearances?
She was a little devil, right?
I like her!
It'll be okay, my darling.
Let me give you a hug.
I want Dad!
What's wrong?
He's crying, I wanted to comfort him,
he pushed me away.
He'll only see you.
It'll pass. It'll pass...
You've said that for four years
and it hasn't.
I can't take the rejection.
What have I done?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
Just that you're Leo's mother.
That's true...
I feel like I lost him when his...
when his brother died.
It wasn't my fault.
I can't do anything
if he's always upset with me.
He's not upset with you.
Quite the opposite.
He can't bear your pain. Understand?
I've overcome it.
I overcame it for him!
Yes, but he doesn't know that.
I'll talk to him, I promise.
Thank you.
Apparently, a detective's here?
Two of them, two gendarmes.
The first looks like
a virtuous, former soldier.
And the second...
I have no words to describe her.
Bang!
Was I good?
The scream was a bit...
Well, the rest was okay.
"A bit"? Look at this!
This is clearly
not a house for pretty flowers.
Captain? Bullet came from a 9 mm.
Let's see.
Hollow-point bullet,
maximum velocity,
to do maximum damage.
That's why the bullet went through.
This is military ammo.
Wow, you know your stuff!
I did ten years in the Paras
before joining the gendarmerie.
I knew a Para once:
Corporal Babazoule.
Would you get this ammunition
at a local gunsmith?
Definitely not.
You need to move your queen.
Otherwise, I'll take you again.
Yoohoo! Hello!
So, are you Alex, then?
Is that Davy Crockett's hat?
No, it's not,
it's a cat that I stuffed.
Listen, I'm not sure
this is the right moment.
Okay. If you're a good boy,
I'll stuff one just for you.
But you must tell me about Elsa.
What? Doesn't he like cats?
You can't talk to him like that!
Alex is shocked by her death.
Plus, four years ago yesterday,
his twin brother drowned in the lake.
How nasty!
Shit, I didn't know, I'm sorry.
Alex has never got over it.
And now Elsa...
I understand. And who are you?
I'm Alex's tutor.
"Shooter", right?
Very funny. I know it's not common,
but that's how it is.
I teach him and I write.
You're a novelist?
That's interesting.
I need an expert's advice.
Don't you think
it's an incredible coincidence
that the babysitter is killed
on the anniversary
of the brother's death?
Life is more incredible than novels.
What beautiful words...
Deeper than a gorge.
Cédric!
The Child Divine has spoken.
Cédric! Come back!
Go play in the woods, oboes play,
set bagpipes sounding!
No one ever listens to me anyway...
Yoohoo!
Wow! It's pretty in here!
Looks like Indiana Jones' office.
You water
those old plants every day, right?
Yes.
Do you polish
all that stuff up there too?
No, only Sir
is allowed to touch them.
Only Sir, right?
Where does Sir practice?
On the grounds?
He doesn't shoot!
You must be our Miss Marple?
And you must be an artist, right?
Everyone is, here.
Marc Durieux.
I wear several hats:
I'm the master's brother-in-law,
a resident,
and experimental musician.
And what do you "experimentalize"?
Tap your foot at a steady beat.
Go on, go on.
Fascinating, I love it!
Hey, how come Gilles
has an arsenal like that
if he never uses it?
Because any worthy crime novelist
has to have a gun collection.
He also has a car,
but he doesn't drive,
a computer,
but he writes by hand.
He paid for the school repairs
but his son doesn't attend.
Why?
Isn't it good enough for him?
And when he writes novels, does he
kill folk or is this an exception?
In my experience,
he's more mouth than action.
Okay. I wanted to show you something.
Ever seen these before?
They're not my size, sorry.
Let me see.
No, not your color either!
Elsa's color though.
Did Elsa Floriot
have a boyfriend or girlfriend?
She always looked after Alex.
She hardly ever left the property,
she had to be on hand:
Gilles' orders.
I understand, it's so hard
to get good Filipino staff,
available 24 hours a day,
and undocumented workers at that too.
Tell me, your master crime writer,
I think he likes
all his courtiers around him, right?
Maybe we inspire him?
Do you ever knock?
There's no point.
I always end up getting in anyway.
Ah, a clock like Granny Zazane has!
Is there a cuckoo in it?
Not in that model.
How stupid.
I like it when things are hidden.
It reminds me of my childhood.
You have three clocks!
Yes, I do.
Is this the Football World Cup?
It's not really from the same era.
My offer of help still stands.
Yeah?
Yes, I'm not a total novice,
I've done internships at the DRPJ
in Paris, Scotland Yard...
Wow! You speak English then?
-Not really.
-Me neither.
I trained later in life,
in my family.
My aunt killed my uncle:
incest
in an ostensibly respectable family.
Well, anyway, going back to Elsa:
I have a theory.
Are you interested?
Go ahead! No need to be shy.
It is pretty simple.
The murder occurred while everyone
was outside at the party.
A thief made the most of that,
but ran into Elsa.
He panicked, shot her...
And the gunshot couldn't be heard
over the fireworks.
That's pretty poor, really!
You can do better.
Plus, that's impossible.
-Do you know why?
-No.
Come along, I'll show you.
I saw that!
You've started smoking again, right?
No, I've just quit.
Yeah, yeah. Come and see this.
It's much classier
using a Smith & Wesson Model 10
than a SIG Sauer to kill someone!
I dunno, I've never tried.
So why do you have so many guns?
All these weapons were held
by people who once used them.
I like to imagine their characters,
lives, reasons for killing.
It helps me create my characters.
And could I see...
Your Swiss Army Luger?
Or is that too private?
Who said I had one?
A bullet hole.
Excuse me?
The bullet that killed Elsa.
It came from a military weapon
made between 1904 and 1947, it seems.
I'd happily bet
that it used to be on your display...
Looks like you've just won your bet.
You were right.
But I can't see a burglar
taking the Luger
without knowing the manor.
Yes, he would have to know
where the keysie-weezie was.
So it must be
someone from the household.
This collection is no secret.
Given all the people
that were at the party,
God knows
who could've got in here.
Your little do
happened at just the right time.
For the murderer, I mean.
Wait! Wait, no, I've an idea.
France 3 and Cédric
filmed us all night long.
The video may reveal something.
Yeah, that's a great idea!
If someone from the village did it,
that means a lot of suspects.
Three hundred and ninety exactly.
390! The catering
must have been expensive!
Out of those 390 people,
might one of the men or women
have worn this type of thing?
-No?
-I don't know. No.
Too bad, I'll give them to Tahar.
Another annoying thing is
that we haven't found Elsa's mobile.
That's normal. She didn't have one.
Really?
Youngsters need phones
like shareholders need redundancies.
Yes, but I banned her
from having one here.
I don't want my son
touching ultra-connected devices.
The waves are bad for the brain.
Not as bad as a bullet though.
Do you have children?
What for?
Well then, I can do
without your expertise on the matter.
I don't care:
I'm for everyone being sterilized.
Know what I'd like you to do?
Get all the fingerprints:
from the gun display, drawer, key.
Then, seal off the gun room, okay?
Also, get the video of the party.
Ask France 3, they'll send it to you.
And ask thingummy's family at
the enchanted manor for their video.
I'd like to see it.
And the murder weapon?
Six feet under.
-What?
-In the grounds or in the lake.
Shall I get divers?
No, do that, get my car fixed,
and find me another.
And not a police car: I'm discreet.
The key of your car, please.
Come on.
Thanks, poppet.
Looks like you're popular.
Yes, did you hear
what the captain said?
Seal off the gun room. Okay?
-See you tomorrow, Fanny!
-Bye, Albert.
...raped and beaten up.
The cook's friend told me.
She was probably
tortured with a knife.
Who could've done it?
Well, if there's a sadist
at large in the village,
I'm not letting my kids go out!
Who said it was a sadist?
Yes, and maybe the girl
wasn't as clean as all that.
Sometimes, you reap what you sow.
It'll make a good story
for Garin's contest.
God knows. It could just be
a publicity stunt for his next book.
It's happened before.
That's enough! Will you all shut up?
You know nothing,
so shut your mouths!
Show some respect.
The kid's dead.
My niece works
at the Gendarmerie switchboard:
seems like they've sent us
a champion detective.
Hello, ladies and gents.
Gendarmerie.
It'd be quite good here. Fanny?
Could I get a small table
to use as a desk?
-Of course.
-Thank you.
Some champion!
We are the champions...
Jogging makes me hungry!
Fanny, could you put this on my tab?
Yes.
There you are!
When you cleaned my room,
my book fell on the floor
and it was open on its spine!
Is that a problem?
Yes, it is!
That is Gilles Garin's first novel,
with the original cover!
He was 28 when it came out!
He still lived
in Rue des Archives, Paris!
That book is priceless.
Do you see the problem now?
Let's discuss it in my room, okay?
I'm also part of his fan club.
In Bousbecque.
I'm the only member.
You're not the cleaner?
No, not really. Well, yes, sometimes
I'm sent in to pick up the rubbish.
Police. Step into my office.
Smells bad in here, right?
Were you at Garin's party last night?
That must've been fun
for a fan like you.
I wasn't invited.
Really? That's strange.
You know someone was murdered?
No, not him. He is full of beans.
Unlike his babysitter.
Did you know Elsa Floriot?
Elsa? Yes... Well, no!
Why? Do you suspect me?
Should I?
I'm more interested
in Garin and his gang.
Garin? Don't be ridiculous!
Ridiculous! You're completely mad!
The cops will delve into our lives.
In detail.
You're aware of that, aren't you?
Yes, I write crime novels.
If you slept with Elsa,
I want to hear it from you, now!
Not from that nutter
in the Russian hat!
Judith, Elsa was Pierre's daughter.
Stop saying that!
Pierre's been dead for six years!
He won't find out!
Did you sleep with Elsa?
You're mad! You're mad!
Stop being so jealous! Stop it!
It's hurting us.
I'm not hiding anything!
Really? So what are those papers
you're burning?
Poor manuscripts.
I don't want the cops reading them.
Or anyone. Not even you.
I'm ashamed of them. Get it?
Listen,
I made a mistake, I admit that.
But since Leo died,
I haven't strayed.
If I find out you're lying,
I'll leave you,
that'll be it!
You'll never see me again.
I'm sorry.
All these deaths!
I can't take it any more!
Who did that? Shit!
I thought you'd stopped drinking?
That was the deal, right?
You should try.
Might do you good.
Marc, stop! Don't start that again.
No, leave it.
We're all on edge. Elsa's death
has been painful for everyone.
Especially for Alex.
And it's not over:
what with that nutter they've sent.
She's not like
any cop I've ever seen!
Beware of appearances.
She looks and talks like an idiot,
but she's anything but.
How far have you got
with your alternative music concerto?
Because I've already reserved
the auditorium.
Please respect the deadline for once.
Don't pressure him.
He needs peace to be creative.
You're lucky. I don't know
if you deserve this guardian angel.
Forgive him:
what with Leo and Elsa both dead,
he's a bit lost.
No, he's right, and you know it.
I'm a failure.
Be quiet.
Stop listening to yourself and work.
I believe in you.
And I love you.
And stop drinking.
What a gorgeous smell!
I'd like one in my room
because it smells of dogs.
Can I take that one?
Yes, okay.
That's kind of you.
Come on, chubby cheeks! Ta!
BÉNÉDICTE HARTMAN'S BODY
FOUND IN THE MEYER BREWERY
So, what books
have you had published?
2006, 2008, 2009, 2010,
2011, 2012. Is that all?
You've written nothing since 2012?
You're paid to do fuck all!
What bollocks!
Who's this?
Tahar? Yes, Tahar?
Do you mind? Calling a girl
at this hour! Know what that means?
I'm only joking! You don't have
a sense of humor at night, do you?
Yeah? I don't care what car.
As long as it works.
No, not an automatic!
That's an oik's car!
That's all there is?
Oh well, too bad.
Yeah, good night, ducky.
Fuck. It's hard being a cop.
What else?
"Jenny Eyes and Gilles Garin:
romance on the Basque coast."
She's young enough
to be his granddaughter.
"... ecstatic in the arms of Jenny,
25 years his junior."
What bollocks!
THE WHITE CROSS HOTEL
Party time!
-Hello.
Hello there!
She seems a bit strange,
the girl who just went out.
No. Just a bit shy, I think.
She's quite nice.
She's usually out all day long.
A hiker.
Tell me... I was wondering...
How did Elsa die, exactly?
Folk here are saying
all kinds of stuff.
Yeah, well, they're idiots.
Let them talk.
Your jam's delicious. I love it.
We all know Garin did it!
Asshole! He wanted
to restore the droit du seigneur
and the girl didn't agree.
Just shut up, Carl.
When I delivered wood to Garin,
I saw him eyeing her up.
Like the wolf in Red Hot Riding Hood.
Good morning, Nasty FM!
So,
you appear to have a nose
for sniffing out predators.
That interests me.
How does it work? When it goes red,
there's one in the area, right?
Mr. Carl?
May I see your I.D., please?
I've done nothing wrong!
Your I.D., I said!
No need for a breathalyzer, methinks!
However, we'll do a wee DNA test:
you never know.
I've done nothing!
I swear. Ask anyone, I'm innocent.
Never say, "I swear".
Never. It makes you look suspicious,
straightaway!
Unless you have proof
for what you say.
I'm listening, dear boy.
Did Mr. Garin kill the girl?
I wasn't being serious.
Just a bit of fun, right?
Hilarious. LOL!
Do you know what happened in WWII
because of gossip
and slander like that?
Know where they sent people?
To Compiègne, not far from here.
Or Drancy, if you were Jewish.
So, if you have no proof...
Maybe you are right,
Mr. Garin may be guilty...
but if you have no proof,
you shut your gob.
And stick it back
in your morning pastis! Got it?
-May I?
-Yes, you may.
No kidding! Tell me, do you know
where they've left my car?
Yes, she said, "just out there."
Great.
Can I leave my laptop with you?
I'll get it later. Thanks, honey.
Tweet, tweet! Modern!
Ta!
Captain Marleau, I was expecting you.
A list of all the house staff.
I was told
you've seen the party videos?
Thoroughly!
Yes, no kidding, you didn't leave
the party for a minute!
Neither did your mates.
Great alibi, well done.
I'm delighted.
I'm not. It annoys me.
I'm basic, I like things simple,
with an ideal suspect,
a weapon, a clear, precise alibi.
This is unclear! Annoying!
Cheer up, I have a serious lead.
Well, I think I have.
What is it?
Two years ago,
Judith was attacked by an erotomaniac
who'd been targeting me.
She got out of a psychiatric hospital
three weeks ago.
Of course,
she's subject to a restraining order,
but you never know with those people.
But why would she kill
your babysitter?
I don't know.
Maybe she decided
to lay into all the women around me?
Yeah...
Here, look. That's her.
A police friend sent me it.
Stay where you are.
And tell your wife and kid
not to leave the place, okay?
What's going on?
Tahar, send two men
to the manor right away.
Quick!
Send two men to the hotel
in case the crazy woman goes back.
She'll have a pop at Judith next!
Wait, I'll call you back.
Come down, Master Crow.
I was just checking they were okay.
No, that's my job!
Your job is to stay
at least 300 m away from the Garins.
That's okay, I'm 400 m away.
What?
Did you measure that from inside?
No. Come down
or I'll call the cavalry.
Blimey!
Yeah, Tahar.
Yeah, it's okay, I've got her.
Yeah, we're going.
Get your butt over here. Come on!
"Huh"? No, not you!
She went "huh"!
-Ladies!
-Hello.
Fanny, can I have my laptop?
Yes.
-And two beers too.
-Yes.
No, tea. A tea, please.
Okay.
Enjoy your meal!
I'll show you something insane!
Our favorite writer's party.
Ah, silly me, you were there,
of course, weren't you?
You're so photogenic!
And a bit of a liar too, right?
I couldn't resist it.
I lied because of the injunction.
But I did no harm.
I just wanted to be near Gilles,
to see him, hear him.
I was less than 10 meters from him!
It was amazing!
Amazing!
And how many meters
were you from Elsa Floriot?
I didn't touch her, I swear.
She wasn't even at the party.
But didn't you attack Judith Garin
three years ago?
No. She attacked me.
She couldn't bear
what Gilles and I had.
What was that exactly?
Thank you.
Do you know Blanche St Léger?
The heroine in Gilles' novels?
That's me.
You'd better change the tea.
It's affecting you.
Blanche is a librarian like me.
My age, looks like me.
I am his muse.
Every time he writes,
I'm in his fingers.
I'm in his life for eternity.
Why would I lay into
some passing girl?
Yes, why?
So, you didn't enter the manor?
Er...
How come your fingerprints
are on the Luger display case?
I just wanted to see the katana
from The Samurai's Honor!
I'd never hurt Gilles or his family!
I love him! I love him!
Just get her out of here! Blimey!
She's nuts.
How could she have known
where the display case key was?
She spent her time spying on him.
Yes, okay, thank you.
My love to Eve and the kids.
Yes, thanks, thanks.
She's in custody.
My mate from the prosecution office
confirmed it.
They'll place her
under investigation for murder.
She should never have left
the psychiatric hospital.
At least it's over.
He's right. Let's turn the page.
Let's try to go forward, for Alex.
Is this a bad time?
How sweet, the family
gathered together like this!
We've been told about
Corinne Vidal's arrest.
She says she's innocent.
She had motive, opportunity,
and access to the weapon.
But did Col. Mustard
kill Ms. Scarlett in the study
with the candlestick?
We don't know.
Mr. Garin,
I want to show you something.
She's a nasty piece of work!
Come and see.
She should be in custody!
No, Tahar's watching her. Right,
Tahar? Come and see this.
Here are two plants:
plant A and plant B.
We found plant A
the day after the crime
in the bedroom. Okay?
It was in this state.
A bit wilted, basically.
The odd thing is,
Joséphine watered it the day before.
I don't know.
I don't have green fingers.
Me neither, but I have eyes, see?
So I put plant B here.
I put it here, in the same spot.
I left it
for the same period of time.
And it looks beautiful.
Strange, right?
Maybe, I don't know. Ask my gardener.
No need. Give me your hand.
Give it to me! I won't eat it!
Let's place
the little paw gently on this.
Is it hot or cold?
-It's cold.
-Yes.
But on the day after the crime,
it was warm.
That means it was on all night. So?
Does that ring a bell?
That's Ice Crime!
-Yup.
-That's in Ice Crime!
Remember?
The killer turns the heating up
to delay rigor mortis and confuse
the estimation of the time of death.
I get it now! Page 395.
Oh, Mr. Garin!
Get her out of here.
Okay, off you go.
No, no.
Yes, yes. Off you go.
Sorry,
how could I ever imagine
that the killer
would be inspired by my own novels?
He must have read all your books,
that's for sure.
Like Corinne.
But you have a computerized boiler.
And Tahar
read the data from your boiler.
We've re-estimated
the time of death:
it was
between 5 p.m. and 8 p.m., in fact.
-Before the party?
-Yes.
There was
a soundcheck for the quartet.
That may be
why nobody heard anything.
Maybe, yes.
What bothers me is that
Corinne was at the hotel then.
There are witnesses. Annoying, right?
So, I was thinking, maybe...
I don't know.
What were you doing at that time?
I'm a suspect?
Yes.
So what could my motive have been?
Elsa looked after my son.
Why would I kill her?
I don't know.
After all,
you are the great master of suspense,
the great seducer.
You are handsome.
And Elsa was cute too.
-Cute?
-Cute, yes.
A bit like your old girlfriend,
that young actress.
She was the same age as Elsa, right?
Yes, well, you know,
that's all in the past, Captain.
A long time ago.
Do you think
I'm stupid enough to kill
using my own novel as inspiration?
No.
I don't think you're stupid at all.
A bit wily, maybe. Yes!
Wily enough to put us off the scent.
I'm sure of that.
You deserve to be
in one of my books, you know.
Thank you.
But unfortunately for you,
I have an alibi.
Shit.
I was with Cédric,
working on his manuscript.
Cédric, the other writer.
Yes, well, he will be. Talented too.
In fact, I suspect
he even sought this job
so he could achieve his aim.
Not very nice.
Cédric...
If he's expecting help from you,
he'll have to wait,
because you're a bit short
on inspiration, aren't you?
How long since you last wrote a book?
Four years, isn't it?
If I didn't hold you
in such high esteem, Captain,
I could get upset.
Yeah, but people like me,
I don't know why.
It must be my... glamourous side.
It must be that.
What? I'm not that ugly, am I?
Well? They're not going to
release that woman, are they?
I fear they are.
When will it end?
I've had enough of this!
I'm scared.
I worked on my manuscript
until 7:45 p.m. with Gilles.
After, we all went
and got ready for the party.
You don't believe me?
Two suspects
using each other for an alibi
happens all too often.
I'm a suspect now, am I?
Yes! Exciting, right?
I had no reason to kill Elsa.
I didn't have problems with her.
Who did then?
That's not what I meant.
Marc... Durieux. He was chasing her.
Sometimes... rather insistently.
One day, I had to intervene.
You've only just remembered that now?
You should take a screening test
for early-onset Alzheimer's.
They do great ones now.
Well played.
Tell me: your tortured artist...
When he's not making frenzied,
Christian Vander-style sounds,
what's he like with the ladies?
My brother-in-law?
Of course.
In Paris, he racked up the notches.
He liked people to know.
What about here?
It's different here.
This is a village,
the prettiest women are all married.
It's harder and riskier.
There are young women.
They're still available.
You mean Elsa?
That's not a bad view? Even
from behind, it must inspire you.
Not as much as that.
Yes, I can see.
You should write a bit.
Maybe.
Do you really believe he could...?
I don't believe anything.
I'm not even baptized.
I let
my feculent imagination run wild
and then I do my wee reports
on my wee machine!
"Feculent imagination"...
At 6 p.m., I was at the town hall
with the council.
I was playing
the phone music on hold
that they ordered from me.
Oh yeah?
Your sound stuff?
Well, at least
it'll keep the callers at bay.
I don't make music to sell it.
It is research.
Researchers don't make much money.
Fortunately, you have Garin.
Is that why you're helping
your Sugar Daddy's mates?
Gilles is right when he says
you're not as stupid as you look.
He said that? I'm flattered.
Thank him for me.
Anyway, after you played them
your weird opera,
you came back here?
No, I went
and had a drink at Fanny's.
I got there at about 6:30 p.m.
Was it Cédric who told you
I was hanging around Elsa?
Why "Cédric"?
He must be scared.
That little shit
was hitting on her, not me.
I can understand.
She was a pretty girl and...
And what?
Elsa was no saint.
She dressed like a nun
because of Garin,
but there's no mistaking
the looks she gave.
Yeah?
And that didn't tickle your chops?
No! I prefer them
more vampish and tortured.
But Cédric is young.
And despite his good looks,
he's more of an academic,
not very experienced.
I reckon he's more into Grindr.
But Garin never noticed?
Even if he did,
Elsa took good care of Alex.
Is this the stuff you record?
I see there's one from 3 days ago,
recorded between 5 and 8 p.m.
Weren't you at the town hall
and café then?
I leave mics on
on the grounds sometimes.
Your pals must be happy
that you tap their conversations.
I'm keeping this.
Yes, he did come in at 6:30 p.m.
Going for Gold was on.
We never miss it.
The whole bar plays.
When did he go?
I don't know, just after the...
Ah yes! Just after
the local news at 7:50 p.m.
I remember they announced
the Compiègne
Philharmonic's concerts.
He screamed, "That's shit!"
On this list, there's a Julien Brun:
a relative?
He's my son.
Really? He's Garin's gardener too?
No, not exactly.
No, he's a council gardener.
But when Garin
needs his rose bushes pruned,
he's sent by the mayor,
if you know what I mean.
Okay. So your local taxes are used
to prune Garin's roses?
I call that abuse of social assets.
Disgusting!
What Garin wants, Garin gets.
At the manor and anywhere else.
You hate him, right?
He thinks he's the village lord.
His mother was much nicer.
You knew her?
She worked in the hotel
when my parents ran it.
She was a teen mum,
she lived here with her son.
Garin and I are five years apart
but we got on well.
Then his mother married the baron
and he became the little lord.
And that broke your heart,
really pissed you off.
You were in love with him,
weren't you?
You read too many romance novels.
I love them: your mind drifts off
into wonderful... How can I put it?
Anyway, who cares.
So, who was your son's father?
Not Garin.
Is that your Julien in the photo?
Cute, right?
Does he have a boyfriend, girlfriend?
No, I'd know about it.
Don't bank on it!
At his age, you never tell all.
Especially not to Mum.
I'm off to the kitchen.
Okay.
The prosecutor just phoned me.
You're off the hook,
given that you helped us out.
-Thank you!
-No problem.
You're great. You're so great!
Okay! That's enough!
Or I'll lock you up again!
And watch out, okay?
Leave Garin in peace now.
No. No,
I can't leave him unprotected.
Why not?
His wife is toxic.
She takes advantage of his kindness.
She's the murderer.
Yeah.
Only because you can't stand her?
No,
because she's pathologically jealous.
And she's his publisher:
she knows his work by heart.
She killed Elsa
and made Gilles look guilty
in order to separate us.
But Blanche
won't be pushed around.
Yes, well, amen to that.
By the way,
did Elsa have a bloke or not?
Could this be him?
The gardener? No.
Well, I never saw him with her.
Really? Well, thanks.
Instead of spying on people,
you should write stories
and sign up for that competition:
that's your thing.
That's not fair play.
Blanche St Léger doesn't write,
she acts.
Yes, true, I forgot.
And I feel
she's going to return. I feel it.
Yeah, yeah, good, good, bye.
You're hurting yourself
standing here.
Remember when we took them
for that boat ride?
You told them that you were a pirate
before you wrote books.
Then they both wanted
an eye patch and a wooden leg.
Alex drew a picture
of us four earlier.
He, his brother and you are so tall
that your heads touch the clouds.
And I'm tiny, perching on a flower.
It's not personal.
Work on your topspin,
catch it on the bounce.
He's really talented, you know.
He's your brother,
that's enough for me.
Catch it!
You can't even get that one!
What does she want now?
Can't she leave us be?
Don't worry.
How are you lovebirds?
Out for a walk?
How about a girlie chat?
Don't worry,
I'm ugly, but I don't bite.
It'll be fine, you'll see.
He's good, right?
Like the Williams' dad.
Is that a Nagra?
You don't like tennis, do you?
Do you prefer football?
Don't you talk?
He's hard work, that kid.
We do what we can.
I'm not judging you.
My job is observing, listening.
Like Corinne Vidal, for instance.
That woman? She talks nonsense.
Really?
She's psychotic.
Yes, I was jealous years ago,
but it's over now.
And Gilles' behaviour
is beyond reproach.
Are you sure?
It may seem naive to you, but yes.
I can feel it.
He's changed a lot since...
Since Alex's brother
had his accident?
Life can be shit sometimes, right?
Gilles lives for his family now.
That's what matters most to him.
So I had no reason to kill Elsa.
I want to believe you,
but you need an alibi,
a really good one.
I was with the caterers all afternoon
getting the party ready.
Check with the firm, Belon.
Started smoking again?
Yes, after eight years.
Silly, I know.
I'm the wrong person to lecture you.
So she's got it into her head
that it was one of us.
Yes.
She's like a dog
that won't let go of its bone.
Hey, honey?
Did you see Elsa
before the fireworks?
Yes. Till he had
his maths lesson with Cédric.
Ah, yes.
Come on, Joséphine.
He finished at 5:30 p.m.,
if my memory serves me right.
But did you see Elsa
after your lesson?
No, he was playing alone in his room.
Your mum's annoying, right?
"I'm big now, Mommy,
I can talk for myself!"
Did you see her or not?
Well, I heard her.
I was in the garden and I heard her
shouting in Uncle Marc's studio.
What was she saying?
I dunno.
But she had her angry voice on.
Who do you think
Elsa was arguing with?
You don't know? A man, woman?
You are starting
to really annoy me, Captain!
Leave my son alone!
He's not even nine
and he's already suffered!
So, paws off!
You're impulsive, aren't you?
Careful, you may hurt someone.
I'll give you my shrink's number:
Olga's great.
She only costs 50 euros.
Tahar?
Come on...
That's it, the writer's seething.
Like a slow-cooked leg of lamb.
You turn on the gas,
there's a heat shock,
then you lower the heat
and it simmers for seven hours.
Do you like lamb?
-Yes, definitely.
-Yeah!
I have the ballistics report.
What does it say? Let's see.
Here.
So,
da dee da dee da... 5.93!
Fuck!
Velocity... Analysis...
Da dee da... Point of impact...
Well, well! Incredible, right?
I am sorry, Captain.
It was hard
for Alex to lose his brother.
He had barely recovered.
And then this.
I'm worried he'll go down again.
I understand.
You know,
under my ushanka, I have a heart too.
Is that
why you don't send him to school?
He's still too fragile.
It would do him good
to see other folk, other kids too.
Maybe, I don't know.
I'm doing my best, going with my gut.
But, what with Elsa's death...
Once again, sorry.
No harm done. Shall we go?
By the way,
do you like slow-cooked leg of lamb?
Certainly.
Slow-cooked leg of lamb?
According to ballistics, the shot
came from hip level.
From the spot I'm on.
The culprit enters the room,
Elsa wakes up.
He's surprised
and shoots instinctively.
And he gets naked
and dances the Carmagnole.
Fuck! She must've put it somewhere!
And what would that be?
Her mobile phone!
A 22-year-old girl must have a phone,
even if her dad, her boss,
or the Holy Spirit doesn't agree!
This is insane!
We looked for her
but she's not with any provider.
And prepaid cards?
Prepaid phone cards exist.
I'm sure they have them here!
Where the fuck did she put it?
Not in here.
You left this in the lounge.
The bank phoned.
Your manager was charming.
He even offered condolences for Elsa.
He was upset when he realized
I didn't know about the money
you paid her every month.
Rather large sums for an au pair.
I can explain.
Don't bother.
My brother was right.
You haven't changed.
Except that you pay them now.
You're pathetic.
Mr. Garin, the mad lady
with the sheepskin rug on her head
is searching Alex's room.
Douai, this is Douai. The train
will stop for 2 minutes. Toot, toot!
That's one tortured kid.
Get out! You shouldn't be in here!
Calm down, Sir.
And lower your voice. Or we can do
your interview somewhere else:
at the station.
Really?
I just spoke to the prosecutor.
You're off the case
if you're not done by tomorrow night!
Ooh! I'm scared...
Look what I've just found?
Whose little phone is this?
I don't know.
Well, it is agreed,
I accept thy challenge.
By tomorrow night, I shall have found
the murderer, my dear cousin.
I love acting. Wasn't I good?
Certainly.
She was cute,right?
Did she have a bloke?
Isn't that the gardener?
Yes. Maybe their liaison
made the writer jealous?
For sure.
I love you, Judith.
I love you, okay?
Why do you feel threatened
every time I see a woman?
Because you love trophies.
Stop it!
No. Even I'm one.
You show me off.
You love me
more than the others
but I'm still a fucking trophy!
No, stop it, would you?
I want to be your wife, Gilles,
your mistress,
and I want to be
your son's mother again.
You need to have verified
everyone's alibis by tomorrow night!
The town hall people,
the guys employed by that clown,
the caterer, and the temps too:
get me all that info
before tomorrow night.
Otherwise, I'm in deep shit.
Wow! That's magic!
Yeah.
You should look at this afterwards.
What is it?
Julien's record.
Julien would never do that!
He's not violent.
That's not what it says here:
"assault on a public road,
assault and battery."
It was a fight at a dance.
That happens, doesn't it?
1 month in hospital! He gave the guy
a whooping. That's a long time!
What's he like?
Is he a jealous type?
It wasn't serious with Elsa:
he would've mentioned her.
Plus, Elsa wasn't hit, she was shot!
Ladies and gents, we're closing.
Go on, out!
Come on, faster than that!
Or I'll lock you all up!
What do you think this is?
Right, if you want me to help
your son, I need information.
Where was Julien?
I swear I don't know where he is.
I haven't seen him
since the afternoon of the party!
That's why you think
maybe he killed her, right?
Tahar?
Yes, can I get
Julien Brun's GPS coordinates?
His phone GPS, his geolocation...
Incredible!
In The Dead Island Mystery,
I catch the killer
by geolocating his phone!
What are you doing here?
It's rude to eavesdrop!
Only joking! I like rude folk.
What's up?
I've selected passages
from my best investigations
to help you in yours.
Stay there.
Here.
It's... You will look after them,
won't you?
They're the apple of my eye.
My whole life's in here.
-I helped a cop in Death is No Fix.
-Oh yeah?
We're a good team, aren't we?
Great. Right, good night.
Are you okay, my darling?
A bit sad? Do you miss her?
Everyone misses her.
Time to sleep now. You need to sleep.
Right, into bed now.
Love you.
Right, that's it. He's asleep.
Poor little lamb.
He needed his mummy and daddy.
Yes.
Marleau is right when she says
we're keeping Alex in a tomb.
There's not enough laughter
in this house.
Talking of Marleau,
the Julien situation was unexpected.
It won't hold for long.
He hasn't a killer's profile.
I'm not so sure.
He was seeing her,
he is nowhere to be found,
and he can be violent.
It could work very well.
Fanny Brun is at the gate, Sir.
She says it's important.
Help me, I beg you.
It can't be him! Not my Julien!
Calm down. I'll call
the prosecutor's office tomorrow.
It's too late tonight.
You will help me? Promise.
I swear. Remember?
"Cross my heart and hope to die..."
"Stick a needle in my eye."
That's it. Now, go home.
Off you go.
She's worried sick.
It's okay. I'm already jealous
of the women you will meet,
I won't worry about your exes.
The money for Elsa
was for her to resume her studies
when Alex
no longer needed her.
To compensate her
for all her time lost here.
But I should've told you.
I believe you.
I want us to get through this
and be happy again.
Fuck, he's crazy.
What rubbish! There are even
door sounds. What nonsense.
Ah, maybe not.
What is it now? Who is it?
Well?
What?
The books! Did you quiver?
Laugh? Cry? Tremble?
That's Gilles Garin for you.
Unique.
Dedication, a universe, a mystery.
You said it:
he's a mystery all right.
Which do you like best?
Look, I've got a crime to solve.
Ah, funny, that's not my favorite.
But there's a great twist
on page 263.
Yeah, okay, okay.
We'll discuss it when I've read it.
Right, goodbye.
Here. This is the best.
I nearly forgot.
-Okay?
-Ah yes, this one. Thanks, bye!
-Good night!
-Yeah, okay.
Me, read such shite?
Aren't the Jacksons on this?
Shut the fuck up!
What are you doing? Come to bed.
I won't sleep.
I have a good way to relax you.
It's a lost cause tonight.
Really? You think so?
Wanna bet?
Yeah. Really?
Ah, that's good news!
Great, thanks! Bye!
Good news, Fanny.
At the time of the murder,
your son was getting drunk
in a bar in Joigny.
He ended up in the drunk tank.
How's that for an alibi?
I knew it.
Do you know where he is now?
No. And it's pissing me off
because I need to ask your alky son
a couple of questions, right?
-What storyline are you after?
-What?
What storyline are you after?
One where he pulls the strings
to silence Blanche.
You mean me?
Yeah, right.
Sort of like
all the suspects have motives,
but they have rotten alibis.
See what I mean?
To cloud the issue, like looking
for a grain of sand on a beach.
Or a needle in a haystack?
Exactly.
Cold-blooded Murder.
Really?
You haven't read it?
Not yet.
The culprit does the same,
but I work it out on p. 276.
Ta.
Okay, we take it up a gear.
That's it now!
I want Garin and Co.'s phone records,
bills, bank statements,
and a list of their hobbies!
Classy!
You're my desert prince.
Careful of my little legs.
There's nothing going on between us.
Of course.
Hey, Garin, this really isn't cool!
If you only give me till tonight,
how can I read all your books?
Nobody's forcing you
to do such an awful chore.
The murderer is.
He's been copying
those two books of yours.
What're they called?
Cold-blooded Murder
and.. not Ice Age...
I've seen that film.
Anyway, something to do with ice.
It's not very sporting!
So, you still think I'm guilty?
And I'm using my novels?
Well, what else could it be?
Ah...
Maybe you're protecting someone.
That, too, is one of the ploys I use
in several of my books.
Would you like a list?
Watch it, Garin,
I have a good right cross.
And I dodge well.
Yeah...
However,
when Blanche St Léger
makes allegations in my novels,
she has proof.
Yeah...
Be careful, Garin.
This is not a novel.
Julien!
Tell me about your crush on Elsa.
I adore love stories!
She told me to meet her at 4:30 p.m.
No way! You can't do this to me!
I love you!
He's pressuring me.
He'll kick me out if we carry on.
Hand in your notice then!
Who gives a shit about Garin's son?
You're dumping me for your job?
No way.
Are you shagging him?
It's not my fault... I swear...
I love him.
Are you mad?
You're young, beautiful.
He'll leave you, he's married!
Not for long.
She said she'd tell Judith
and she would leave Garin.
What happened after that?
I realized it was over,
went off in my car,
found a bar, started drinking. Things
degenerated, owner called the cops.
Okay. But why did you
go off the radar afterwards?
When I heard about Elsa,
I got scared.
I thought,
if someone had heard our row...
I was the ideal culprit.
He rang me earlier
to reassure me
and I said he could come back.
I like Juju and his silly stories,
but that won't get us anywhere.
Frankly,
there aren't enough suspects,
or rather, there are too many,
and not enough culprits.
Do you see what I mean?
I think that Garin
is working backwards. It is a trap.
Wait,
Garin could've silenced the girl,
thinking she would tell his wife.
Or it could've been jealous Judith
because Elsa had told her all?
Yeah. Or it was Judith's brother!
If she leaves her husband,
Durieux can kiss goodbye
to chateau life, his studio,
and his "contemp...tible music"
concerts.
There's Cédric too.
He's in the running:
he loved Elsa.
Yeah...
What the hell are you doing?
Take a look at this!
-What?
-You should look.
It'll interest you.
The bitches!
They really took the piss out of me!
Look! Cédric and Durieux!
Look!
Right, relax and concentrate.
Go on, Alex. Nice, big movements!
Push me! Push me!
Before the beetles get me!
I loved this when I was a kid.
Yeah?
Did you call me here to push you,
or do you have something to say?
The one doesn't exclude the other.
I wanted to check something.
So, Cédric and Durieux
were both hitting on Elsa, right?
I told you, I don't know.
Okay, but is that possible or not?
Marc is a womanizer,
Cédric is the same age as Elsa, so...
Yes... It's credible...
Credible? You blow me away, frankly!
Yup. Either you're very stupid,
which I don't believe for a minute,
or you're really clever,
a total master.
Passing two gay men off as straight
so they become murder suspects?
I take my ushanka off to you!
You overestimate me.
And you're humble too. Great!
So, in light of this,
who are our suspects now?
You or your wife, or both of you?
Did your wife know
you were sleeping with Elsa?
I wasn't involved with Elsa.
That's not what Juju said.
He even said
that she left him to go with you.
Okay, not now,
not in front of my son. Please.
My office, five minutes.
Six! Watch out, the clock's ticking.
Back a bit!
Don't move.
Is he improving?
He's got a good touch.
And he enjoys it.
Look after him, okay?
-Nice weather too!
-Yeah.
Right, watch the ball. Perfect!
Good!
Move towards the ball, step back.
I love oak.
It's beautiful, it smells good,
like coffins.
It's frank, it's direct,
it's not like those stupid reeds.
It doesn't bend.
In short, oak doesn't lie.
You win, Captain.
We'll... We'll cut our losses.
Elsa was going to
tell Judith everything.
It was impossible to reason with her.
So you killed her?
That's strange:
with the imagination you have,
how come you chose
such a stupid way to do it?
You don't get it.
Judith would have left with Alex.
I couldn't have handled that.
I have already lost one...
one son.
I couldn't bear to lose a second.
Okay. But why have you made
everything so confusing?
Because I underestimated you.
I'm sorry.
It's easier to kill with a pen,
right?
That said, making it look
like everyone was guilty:
brilliant!
You totally got me there!
I take no credit.
Everyone depends on me here.
Even your wife?
Your wife seems to love you.
No, she was the only one
who didn't know.
How honorable you are:
classy, to the very end.
I might start a new series in prison.
With a character like you in it.
Someone sexy then. That's kind!
Could we...
Could we avoid using handcuffs?
In front of my son?
Sure.
You're not coming with us.
Go and join your kid.
You're not arresting me?
No. You've cried wolf so often,
I don't believe you.
But I confessed.
No, you didn't confess,
you strung me along!
But the final act
has only just begun, my dear.
I've always dreamt of saying that.
How stupid.
Don't sulk,
you're still under judicial scrutiny!
In case you decide to go to Panama
with your little family.
Will you drive?
Certainly.
What kind of car is this?
You sure about this?
Yes, this car prefers you to me!
I don't mean the car.
Garin? Yeah, yeah. It's not Garin.
He's protecting someone.
Nice try, but it's not him.
He had a motive.
What about Julien's testimony?
Know what I do with testimony?
I chuck it out in Babazoule Street!
Know the song?
Last night... in Babazoule Street...
-You know it?
-Yes.
We found...
A strangled girl on the ground!
Three, four!
The police... full of mischief...
Put up posters...
Yeah, that's it!
Which told us that...
Three, four!
I'm thirsty! I've heard so many lies,
I can no longer swallow!
Can I have a beer, please?
Here, this came in for you.
What is it?
Phone tracking details.
Julien's phone's GPS.
A bit late now.
Thanks.
Ah, maybe not!
Look. Back in a minute.
Can I have Julien's room key, please?
Excuse me?
Julien's room key?
Thank you.
Just like rolling a joint:
you never forget.
Yes!
Now then...
Nothing underneath, honey?
What's this? What is this?
Bingo!
I've searched Julien's room. Nothing.
Yeah? Well, I got lucky! Look.
Yeah? How much?
20,000 euros, I'd say.
Not bad for an innocent guy?
Yup. Are you ever wrong?
No, I'm always right, especially
when it comes to guys. Girls too.
Juju!
I've got
your phone's GPS coordinates here.
Funny: it says
you went to Garin's place
just before going to your mom's.
Were you missing your roses?
Look. Did the roses phone you?
Must've been hard for them:
leaving the ground,
finding a phone,
keying in your number
with their thorns,
then having a 43-second conversation!
To me, it looks more like
a summons from Garin, right?
Why would Garin want to see me?
I don't know...
To tell you about your scene
in Act II?
You know, the love scene
where you break up
and your chin trembles.
You nearly had me sobbing:
you were good.
It was true.
I loved her, I wanted us to go away.
Yeah, half-true. Cut the crap.
Yes, Elsa did dump you. But why?
She was scared of losing her job.
And that must've hurt your pride.
Yes or no?
Why would I have lied to you?
"Why would I have lied to you"?
You should do auditions, you know.
You're good!
But I don't know many temps
who earn a fee of 20,000 euros.
You searched my car!
You can't do that!
What do you mean?
In emergencies, I search what I like!
Okay?
I won the money at poker.
Yeah, sure you did.
Don't worry.
I'll tell Garin you're not a snitch.
Hey! Give me my money back!
This is evidence.
And I play poker too:
I've got a game with Jojo.
Bye.
What are you doing?
No, you can't arrest Garin!
It wasn't him!
It can't be him! No! No!
Shove off! Shove off!
She's totally nuts!
Garin? Judith, where is your husband?
Quick!
I don't know, in his office?
What's wrong?
Stay there. Don't move.
Fuck...
What's this?
"I cheated on my wife...
I killed Elsa...
I hope my son forgives me."
Fuck, I suspected this. Idiot!
Why?
If he kills himself,
he can't recant his confessions!
Where is he?
What does this mean?
It means
he's trying to save your son.
Your son killed Elsa, didn't he?
Wake up! Stop play-acting!
Gilles has gone to kill himself.
Where?
I don't know! I swear!
Leo? Where did Leo drown?
In the lake.
Fuck! Check round the house.
No!
No! Gilles! No, don't do it!
Please! You have no right!
Garin! Garin!
Think of Blanche!
If you kill yourself, she'll die...
And me too!
I'm warning you!
If you do it, I'll jump in the water!
And Blanche can't swim!
Silly idiot! You'll screw it all up!
Clear off! You're heavy too!
-Bugger off up your ladder!
-Captain, we must do something!
Clear off!
Help him!
Garin! Garin, wait till I get there.
Don't move!
Fuck, look at me!
This isn't Captain Marleau,
it's Captain Nemo! I'm coming, Garin!
You never let go, do you?
No. They call me
the Carpathian pubic louse.
So, tell me. What's the story?
When he went into Elsa's room
with the Luger,
he didn't mean to kill her?
Accident, right?
What are you doing in my room, Alex?
What are you doing with that?
Why are you playing with that?
The priest told me
when I died, I would see Leo.
Do you think that's true?
It's not loaded?
What have you done, my darling?
What have you done?
Come, come.
Since Leo died,
Alex has been a shadow of himself.
It was an accident.
Alex is only nine years old.
He won't be charged.
I'm a public figure.
His name will be all over the papers,
in all the media, on the radio, TV,
social media, everywhere.
For his whole life,
he'll be the kid that killed.
He'll never get over it...
Of course he will!
I should've checked the Luger
for bullets.
It's my fault, all my fault.
As was Leo's death.
Daddy! Daddy!
No, double for the rights!
He's not going to get stingy?
No, absolutely not!
No, I will not give in.
-Daddy!
-No, be quiet!
I'm on the pho--
Leo!
No, Garin, don't be stupid. Wait.
If you shoot yourself,
who'll look after your kid?
Judith.
I couldn't have coped without her.
When Leo died,
she single-handedly cared for us.
Do you think she could handle that
a second time? No.
Alex will need his father.
He'll need you
when the truth comes out.
It'll still come out
if you shoot yourself.
And how will he cope?
Can you imagine
how guilty he'll feel?
"Where's your dad?"
"He killed himself because of me."
How can you live with that?
I'm tired.
Go on, shoot. What can I say?
Go on, let him cope by himself!
What will his mother say to him? Huh?
When you're dead?
How will she stop him
from killing himself?
He'll want to copy you,
he'll kill himself.
Do you want him to drown himself?
Blow his own head off?
End up in a loony bin?
Become a drug addict?
Because that will happen.
One way or another.
You know it will.
You're a better psychologist than me.
Don't be an idiot, Garin,
give me that. It's over now.
Hello!
I've come to say goodbye.
I saw the prosecutor.
Elsa's death
will be treated as an accident.
And since you have authorization
for the guns, you won't be charged.
Right, I'll leave you two alone.
Thank you.
No charges? Even
for obstructing the investigation?
Don't push it, mind you!
But you won't go to prison,
I don't think.
You'll have a good lawyer.
You'll make them cry
in the courtroom.
I have something for you.
To thank you.
Signed first editions.
Ice Crime and Cold-blooded Murder.
You always get
the last word in!
Yes. You don't have to read them.
Really? I might read them then!
Inchallah!
Thanks to you, I'll get Alex
out of his ivory tower.
I'd call it a "prison".
Anyway, you're the poet.
I've decided
to put him in the village school.
Ah, social diversity?
It'll do him no harm.
I may not look it, but I am strong.
You can count on me, Alex.
I'll always be here to protect you.
Mommy...
You know... I have
loads of ideas for a new novel.
By the way, what's your first name?
My first name? Captain.
Well then,
thank you... "Captain".
Idiot!
Bye, lovebirds!
Come in!
Your car is washed, repaired,
and waiting down below.
Not a moment too soon, right?
Well, it's an old car.
It's not easy to find the parts.
The old ones are always the best.
I have something to show you!
What?
It's Gilles' next manuscript.
You haven't been back to the manor?
You're really nuts, right?
Just for five minutes.
I left right away.
Look, he's created a new character.
A woman. Captain Lomart.
Lomart?
Lomart. Does it ring a bell?
Any first name?
Victor.
-Victor?
-Victor.
Not bad.
United we stand! Right, bye!
What? My bag stinks?
Yes, a right stench!
Your nose is too close to your mouth.
Fanny!
Yes?
I wanted to say goodbye. Kiss?
Yes.
There we go.
You're always welcome here.
I'll be back
for the next murder, promise.
-Goodbye!
-Bye.
You washed it?
Yes! It was dirty!
It looks awful.
Come on, shake a leg!
There you go.
See ya, sweetie!
-Safe journey.
-Kisses!
Subtitling: Hiventy