Go on, move it, you!
CAPTAIN MARLEAU
Héloïse!
No, I'm Cécile.
Sorry...
Nightmare...
My god. Oh, my god.
-You want a coffee?
-No.
I've got to go,
I've got an important delivery.
It's 5 a.m.
Well, yes.
That's right, I'm late.
-Cool, see you in three months.
-Cécile...
You and I...
It's my fault.
-I shouldn't have.
-Don't say anything.
It's better that way.
I get it.
You got a cigarette?
Need a light?
I'll smoke it later.
Show me your hand.
Oh, my poor man...
I see misfortune.
Misfortune is upon you.
-There's someone roaming.
-What?
-Nearby you.
-Who?
Who? The devil.
-Understand? It's the devil.
-Alright, leave me be.
-You need to go.
-I'm not superstitious.
-You aren't superstitious?
-No!
CAPTAIN MARLEAU
PHILIPPE MUIR
A MOVIE DIRECTED
BY JOSÉE DAYAN
SAMUEL
MANAGEMENT OFFICE
Hey, it's Samuel. I'm not here,
but you already know that.
Only leave a message
if it's good news.
Samuel, it's me, it's dad.
Call me back please,
it's urgent.
Blanche?
Philippe, what are you doing here?
I'm looking for Samuel, is he here?
Have you seen him?
He was at the warehouse
yesterday, why? What's going on?
Manuella is dead.
-What?
-Yes.
I found her in the office.
She was murdered.
Oh, no...
-What's that got to do with Samuel?
-I'm looking for him.
Where is he?
-I have no idea!
-I need to talk to him.
Philippe...
There were all these papers
strewn around her corpse.
See? Deliveries that had been
carried out.
-Hours, everything.
-So what?
It was Manuella's job
to check all that.
You should've left it as it was.
I panicked, I didn't take it all.
We'll handle everything step by step.
You find Samuel,
and I'll call the police.
-Are you sure?
-Of course.
Why wouldn't I call them?
We have nothing to hide.
-Except if...
-If what?
Philippe...
You can't suspect your son
of having killed her?
No. Honestly, Blanche...
We're so distant,
him and I, that...
You completely lost your mind.
Samuel didn't kill anyone, okay?
And I'm calling the police.
Okay. You're the one who's right.
We'll do like we said.
You know where to find him?
I tried to call him,
but it went straight to voicemail.
Don't worry, Philippe.
Everything will be fine.
-Everything will be fine, Philippe.
-Yes.
POLICE
I'm a woman, I'm not disabled!
Ladies & gents...
Captain Marleau, homicide.
-Blanche Muir.
-No handshake.
You'll stink of Vaseline.
Know why?
Oiled this morning.
Vaseline is great,
it's handy.
But it stinks.
Shall we?
-Hey Gravos, how you doing?
-Hello.
-So, is this yours?
-No, I handle hours and stocks.
The company belongs
to my brother, Philippe.
-What is all this?
-She's totally nuts.
-What's this?
-I don't know.
She was our accountant.
Manuella Morales.
And who found the body?
My brother, this morning.
Where's your brother?
I'm going to need his statement.
He had to go on an urgent delivery.
He asked me to tell you.
That so?
And you here, miss?
Did you not see anything?
-No, I saw nothing.
-Oh.
Listen. You're going to tell
your brother over the phone.
You're going to tell him, from me:
"As long as we haven't found
the guy who did this,
urgent deliveries are over."
-Alright?
-Yes, of course.
Well yeah, duh.
Any news from Samuel?
Philippe, call me back
when you get this.
It's urgent, Captain Marleau
wants a statement from you.
What's this thingy?
-This yours?
-No. Everybody gets coffee here.
Well yeah, but...
Hey!
Will you take this to the lab,
please?
Because you never know,
you know?
You never know what could...
Can you call your brother back?
Be a little insistant.
You can just press redial.
It's faster that way, you know?
-He's still on voicemail.
-Oh, yeah?
He's in Spain, he doesn't get service
there. He'll be back around 6 p. m.
Did his voicemail tell you that?
That's crazy.
New technologies,
nano-technologies, all that...
When I call up my brother,
he answers.
If he doesn't answer, I call back.
But people...
saying I'm dead, I'm ill...
COURTROOM
Will you give me file 23?
Well, get the file to me, okay?
I need to talk to you.
JUDGE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE APPLICATION OF SENTENCES
Your company accountant was killed.
I better understand
why you came, now.
Don't worry, I'll tell the cops:
"He can't have killed his associate,
"he was making love to me
and dumping me."
I'm sorry, I've got no excuse.
I'm an asshole, that's all.
I'm not resentful,
I'll say we were together.
You're wrong, Cécile.
I didn't come for me.
I don't care
about what the cops might say.
I came about the kid.
I don't know where he is.
What, Samuel?
-What's he got to do with all this?
-Nothing, I hope.
You don't know where he is,
do you?
Let's sum it up:
You dump me at 5 a.m., and at 8 a.m.,
you come and beg me to find your son.
What makes you think
I'm dumb enough to help you?
You're right, I'm sorry, I...
I'm overwhelmed.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Come back, Philippe.
You're in luck, you found
the queen of dumbs.
Who is this guy, now?
Where does he think he is?
You show up just now?
Who are you, anyway?
Léopold Salaun, coroner.
Wait!
Not a word,
I'll read your mind.
"This coroner asshole has no business
on my crime scene."
Well yes, because cold meat,
I prefer to see it
while it's still warm!
If you see what I mean.
In its natural habitat.
Then, hop!
Off we go to the morgue,
chop it up, weigh it,
and wrap it up.
Guys, just because I'm talking to
a woman doesn't mean you can dawdle!
I like to titillate those big
Q-tips, too.
They do look like giant Q-tips.
I'm Captain Marleau, homicide,
I was transferred to Perpignan.
Charmed.
She was killed last night,
between five or six in the morning.
I'll tell you exactly
when I've opened her up.
-Three hits. The bullets were...
-It's nine millimeter, yeah.
With a silencer. The tip
was touching on the first shot.
So that means she knew
her murderer, then.
Because I would never let
someone come so close.
She defended her life dearly,
she fought to the end.
I got some DNA on her fingernails.
There, see, she took a hit.
-A big slap.
-Oh, yeah.
-That's funny.
-Really?
-You think so?
-Yes, because...
Let's say you're the killer...
You don't look like one,
even if you look a bit like Landru...
You want to kill this chick
because you don't like her,
and you're in luck, because you have
a silent, solid gun at home,
that's available in several colors...
You going to slap this chick around
before you kill her? No.
What would you do?
I don't know.
I don't deal with feelings.
I just deal with the meat.
Maybe his girl
knows where he is.
You didn't know
he had a one?
Since his mother's death,
him and I have...
-Has it been going on for long?
-6 months.
They met here,
she was leaving my office.
And you know him,
he asked her out for a drink.
-And she said yes.
-She's a junkie, too?
She got a one-year suspended sentence
for dealing ecstasy.
Hang on, I must have
her contact info somewhere.
Salomé Delvigne.
No address, just where she works:
in a bar in Cauliaux, Villa rouge.
-I don't know how to thank you.
-I'm doing it for Samuel.
I'll go find him, thanks.
It's a night bar.
It doesn't open until 22:00.
See you there at 22:00.
I'm going with you.
After all, taking care of your son
is my job.
Thank you.
Watch her head.
Tell me when, Laurence.
There we go.
As fast as possible, mmh?
You, I want to see you
to interrogate you very soon.
You, not right away.
If I got this right,
your job is handling deliveries,
checking all that comes and goes.
And lately, you've noticed nothing
strange?
Any issues?
No, the company is doing pretty well.
In this economy, we can't complain.
Got it. Muir...
Muir Philippe, Blanche, Samuel...
Really a family business, how nice.
Yeah, but not only.
There's also Pierrot,
he's a heavy truck driver.
Jennifer Lavaux, the secretary,
and there was Manuella.
Ah, yeah, right.
ADMINISTRATIVE SERVICES
I remember the day Philippe
introduced me to her.
It was last year.
She showed up in her pink jacket,
she looked all around her,
and she softly said:
"Hire me as your accountant,
I'll double your revenue in a year."
"Hire me..."
Well, she did it.
She instigated budgetary restrictions
my brother wouldn't imagine.
She started inspecting the drivers,
their margins,
their mileage.
She lowered salaries
and increased bonuses.
She ruined the competition.
And our profits margin tripled.
Well...
That's a lovely eulogy, really,
it was very moving.
She seems like a lovely character.
But I'd like to find Samuel, myself.
Where is that guy?
He's on his way back from a delivery,
he's just been told.
That's unfortunate. Meanwhile,
do you mind going to get mister...
-Lacoudre, is that it?
-Pierrot?
-Sure, I'll call him right away.
-I will talk to him.
You're too kind, madam.
Oh, Mrs. Muir!
No, wait, you're Miss Muir, right?
You're not the missus,
you're the sister, is that it?
-It's miss, yes.
-Miss Muir, got it.
-You'll be sticking around, right?
-Where do you want me to go?
I don't want to be told again
that a member of the Muir family
-has vanished into nature.
-Relax.
You're too kind.
Pierrot?
-Alright, go on.
-I'm going.
-Come in, sir.
-Nice to meet you.
-Jennifer, you're next.
-Yes.
Otherwise people leave
and I get in trouble.
What's the atmosphere like here?
Prior to this morning, I mean.
-Well-spirited, I imagine.
-Really?
Even after
Mrs. Morales arrived?
Because that chick seemed like
she had some oomph to her, no?
Yes, maybe it was better before.
She wanted to control everything.
If you were a minute
behind schedule, you'd catch hell.
-The truckers didn't like that much?
-No.
And so, last night,
what happened in particular?
-Nothing in particular.
-No? Yes, come on, think about it.
I don't know, a fight,
or maybe...
A dude who was
behaving weirdly?
Or a trucker who was mad because
Mrs. Morales was
micro-managing his affairs?
It was the same as usual.
-What's this?
-Excuse me, I need a file.
And Blanche Muir,
what's she to you?
-A colleague.
-Sure, she is!
I need to make a photocopy.
I'm not a courtship ritual specialist
but I'm not blind, either.
-There's nothing.
-But you would like...
To smother her in little kisses, no?
That has nothing to do
with Manuella's death.
It does and I'll tell you why, sir.
If you love her, then you might not
tell me everything about Blanche.
-But she didn't do anything.
-Sure, but her brother, her nephew?
I'll only speak in the presence
of a lawyer. I know my rights.
You have rights when you're
in custody. Are you? No.
Although, be patient,
it could happen. I'm off.
Miss Muir!
If you see your bro,
if you ever get a hold of him,
tell him I'm expecting him.
At Mrs. Morales' house.
Captain Marleau.
Philippe Muir.
She lived here all alone?
No kids, no fella, no girl?
Can you smell that?
It stinks.
This pad reeks of loneliness.
It reeks of TV dinners
being eaten all alone.
It reeks of sadness.
It reeks of tears we hold back.
The sighs that no one hears.
But... Are you sure
she was single?
Because if she was, who was
she getting all dolled up for?
She was pretty.
Your sister told me
you're a widower.
You never thought
of getting married again?
It's funny, because...
you smell like her.
The same scent.
Loneliness smells strong.
It doesn't just go away in the wash.
So I was wondering if...
Well, you know, if...
Do you never finish
your sentences?
Were you and Manuella lovers,
Mr. Muir?
No.
Say, we're looking for
Salomé Delvigne.
Over there, maybe.
I hate kids your age.
They do stupid shit all the time,
they have fun and don't give a fuck.
We, the old,
we can't do anything else.
Nothing else than wait
and be scared for them.
You know why?
Because we're so fucking stupid
that we can't manage to love you.
Fuck off!
My kid's name is Samuel.
And his girlfriend's name is Salomé.
And she works here,
she's a waitress here.
So if one of you knows
where I can find her,
I'll be over there, by the bar.
And I'll be waiting all night.
And I will be scared for him.
'Cause I'm a real dumbass.
Come in.
You're making me do overtime.
Here you go.
All the video footage
from the past week.
That's very kind.
You can go now,
I'll figure it out.
-By the way...
-Yes?
You didn't like Manuella
at all, did you?
-Oh, yes.
-Yes? No...
You're kidding.
Good night.
Alright, goodbye.
That's right...
So...
The Oscar for the best
company film
goes to...
Muir Transport. Conversations
with people ignoring one another.
I bet I'm going to be bored.
-Here, it's empty.
-You sure you want another?
I need courage to tell you
an unpleasant thing.
I'll take one too, then.
Can we get two more, please?
Without too much soda water.
No wait, no soda water at all.
Just alcohol.
Thank you.
So?
Do you often sleep with women
and then run off?
No. It's happened to me before,
but not often.
It's my first time sleeping
with a guy who dumps me upon waking.
Am I that bad?
You're an incredible woman.
Admirable.
Very pretty.
And brilliant.
You are fucking with me.
I spent the day
waiting for your call.
It's been three months since we met
for Samuel's...
-You want to talk to me?
-It's about Salomé.
She was supposed to come tonight.
She didn't and she's unreachable.
-Since when?
-Last night.
All right.
Oh, shit.
Héloïse!
-Where are you coming from?
-Grenoble. An urgent delivery.
In Grenoble?
I didn't mark anything down.
What's going on with you, Pierrot?
-What are you doing here so early?
-I wanted to see you.
Pretending to run into me?
-Why don't you just come see me?
-You never have time.
Always taking care
of your nephew or brother.
I know you don't like him.
But he's a great guy, I promise.
If you knew him better...
I saved that guy's ass
from the cops.
The morning of the crime,
he was there.
I saw him.
And I shut it.
Thank you, Pierrot.
When all of this is over, we can
get to know each other a little,
you and I, okay?
We'll go out for a nice meal,
just the two of us.
Hello!
You're still here?
Yes, I'm still here
for a good while.
I must have been a rabbit
in another life.
Anytime I'm anywhere,
I've got to dig my little hole.
Give me a hand, now,
help me get back up.
It's a good thing you're here, 'cause
I'd like to show you something.
On the footage, here,
there's a guy,
and I don't know who he is.
Is he a part of the company or not?
Take a look.
That's Samuel, my nephew.
Oh, sorry.
Because this guy's in real trouble.
I'm telling you.
Oh that's right, Samuel Muir!
How silly I am.
Just look at this would you.
See what he says?
No?
-I don't know how to read lips.
-Me neither, but look.
He grabs her by the shoulders,
then he says something.
"I'm going to kill you."
And then, a few hours later,
boom! She's dead.
Yes, look. I don't want to act like
some two-bit Columbo,
but that smells like a clue.
And do you have footage
of the murder?
Well, the thing is that...
The video files after 5:12 were
all erased. What a coincidence.
Clever beast.
I'm sorry for you, captain.
Samuel was over at my place
the night before last, for dinner.
Since he had a drink,
I didn't want him on his motorcycle.
He's got his room there anyway.
I live at our parents'.
When Philippe left, someone had to
stay to take care of those old walls.
-Alright, will you buy me a coffee?
-Yes, down at the end of the hall.
I slept bad.
You know what?
It's a good thing
you're close to him.
That way, you can call him
so I can find him
and talk to him real quick.
I'm not patient.
Go ahead, right behind you.
I'm not patient,
I think I must be bipolar.
Because even with like an ATM,
when it says "Please Wait" on it,
it pisses me off!
I want to hit it.
-You want a big or a small one?
-A big one.
With 3 sugars.
Hey, it's Samuel. I'm not here,
but you already know that.
Only leave a message
if it's good news.
Samuel, look, it's dad.
I've been looking for you
for two days. Call me back.
-Can I help you?
-I'm exhausted. Can I have a coffee?
Help yourself, it's over there,
I just made it.
You look in a right state, today.
You too.
That's nice of you.
It's because I raged all night
with some young kids.
Who were of age, mind you.
And what's your excuse?
Because, as a hardened bachelor,
-what do you do at night?
-If you only knew.
I'd rather not.
I brought along
your son Samuel's file.
It's quite the long-read.
Unlawful acts,
blows and injuries,
and crack consumption, too.
It's not that big of a deal.
We aren't asking that much
of him either.
His teenage years were hard.
Come on, that's a load of crap.
Honestly?
I had some shitty
teenage years, too.
I lived in a housing project,
and my mom was an alcoholic.
I tore legs off grasshoppers.
But it didn't turn me
into a serial killer.
No, but...
His mother died
in a truck accident,
in Spain.
He was 10 years old.
I raised him as well as I could.
It apparently wasn't good enough.
Luckily, my sister was there.
I think that without her,
I wouldn't have known what to do.
I was depressed, staying in.
You know what depression is?
You don't want to see anyone,
you want to sleep all day.
It lasted for a long time.
It takes time.
Your place is nice.
-She's pretty, no?
-Yeah.
When she left us,
I really hit rock bottom.
Samuel spun out of control.
I didn't notice.
He stopped working hard at school.
He started smoking weed.
After that, it was cocaine,
and the heroin,
and then crack, then klonopin,
then alcohol, then...
All that stuff.
And then there were
the downward spirals,
the nervous breakdowns.
Hell, in short.
I emerged from rock bottom,
and I took him with me to the garage.
Because I wanted to help him get
out of it. He'd decided he wanted to.
He was seeing a shrink.
And he was on meds.
He figured it out.
That kid really put me
through the wringer.
And I've never seen anyone
as unlucky as him.
Every time there was a hard blow,
boom, it was him it hit.
I can tell you that deep down,
he really is a good kid.
Well, a good kid...
That's one way to look at it.
He did threaten to kill a broad,
Manuella Morales.
And a few hours later...
-She was dead.
-No, I just don't believe that.
I just refuse to believe that.
I refuse to believe
he'd do such a thing.
You know, I met a guy
who's done some crack once.
He was completely stoned.
He was fighting with a machete.
Against some cornstalks, he thought
they were Afghani soldiers.
-Nothing surprises me anymore.
-Yes...
Samuel can't do such a thing.
He couldn't have done
such a thing.
With the way his mother
brought him up, there's no way.
Yet weirdly, I do get the impression
that you think your son is guilty.
Am I wrong?
Your sister told me
you'd be here today.
Sorry to bother you,
but it's important.
I know where Samuel's girlfriend
can be found.
It's not that I don't like you.
It's that I'm bad luck.
It's like a curse.
I know it's ridiculous.
I don't believe it myself.
But it's true.
All the women I've loved
wind up dying.
And if they only slept with you once,
does it count?
I'm already fucked,
so I might as well enjoy it.
I had my first girlfriend at 18.
We were very serious.
I had that girl under my skin.
It was a first for me.
It was true love.
Six months later,
a car smashed her scooter
to smithereens.
She died on the spot.
Then, there was Héloïse.
I met her in Spain.
Love at first sight.
We got married,
and we had Samuel.
Then we came back here.
I started working for myself.
But Héloïse was homesick, so,
I told myself we could figure it out.
We could keep the business going
with my sister here,
and that I would go over there.
After all, it wouldn't change much.
We got ready for a weekend trip
to go find a house there,
so we could go live there.
We were supposed to go together
but I couldn't go with her.
An order came in at the last minute.
I had to go to Lille
to do a delivery.
She fell asleep behind the wheel,
and she died.
Good God.
After that, there was Manuella.
I knew that things
could happen.
But...
I was scared.
And then one day I gave in.
I kissed her.
You know where she is now.
And then there's you.
There's us.
As soon as I saw you, I loved you.
I loved you. I don't want anything
whatsoever to happen to you.
I'm scared.
Are you serious?
You really think you're bad luck?
Where do we find
Samuel's girlfriend, then?
CORONER
LÉOPOLD SALAUN
What, it's me!
You've got some nerve,
bothering me while I'm working.
I've killed for less.
I know, it would have been the same
for me. I'm sorry.
No but, I'm happy to see you.
Although I imagine you're here
for her, not just for my enjoyment.
-Oh, doctor.
-Call me Léopold.
Oh no, I couldn't.
I'm sorry, captain,
but meaning no offense,
I've seen better,
as far as corpses go.
I've seen some that tell
amazing stories.
Stories of passionate love,
terrible revenge stories,
couple's secrets...
I'll stop you there, I'm sorry,
but I'm going to need your help,
because on the Q-tip end,
it's a mess.
All they've found are fingerprints
from company employees.
Nothing suspicious.
I'll need you, if possible.
Your wishes are my command.
Manuella Morales died
around 6 a.m.
According to her bolus,
she'd had dinner 10 hours prior.
It was Sushi night.
With raw tuna, avocado, mango,
shrimp, raw salmon...
Salmon? With what's
in the oceans, that's gross.
Yes, crab, kiwi, lobster...
-Makes you hungry?
-Seven euros a pop.
Seven euros? Seems like someone
thought she was the bee's knees.
Kiwi-crab maki
are one of
chef Yannick Ménard specialties.
They only sell them
at Rashōmon.
-Where?
-Rashōmon!
Like the Kurosawa film. I could
take you there one of these nights.
Anyway, other than than, I've got
the DNA from under her fingernails.
So, who's DNA is it?
Hey there!
I'm not bothering you, am I?
I've got an assessment to finish,
Manuella's files. But I can help you.
No.
I'll figure it out, just keep
working as you see fit.
I'll look around by myself,
like a big girl.
This is wild.
Have you noticed? Your nephew
eats up more diesel
than the other truckers do.
A third more.
Does he go far?
I don't know.
Well, it's easy, look. The journeys
are written down right here.
Last week, for instance,
he went to Spain.
From Collioure to Cadaquès
to get 7 tons of primer,
like his dad the night before.
Except that the dad used up
17 euros worth,
whereas he used up
28 euros worth.
You know how to count, no?
It means he went twice as far.
No? So where'd he go?
-You don't know?
-No.
I'll show you how.
You take a pair of compasses...
This is 28 euros worth of distance.
You take a map, and look.
It means that he went all the way...
-Barcelona.
-So what, what does that prove?
Well, I don't know, miss, it shows
that an enterprising kid like that
can use the company's trucks
to go see other customers and provide
them with different merchandise,
especially a kid
who is a notorious crack consumer!
Samuel has kicked the habit.
You know that very well.
This is fiction.
Maybe for now, but I bet
that if we go into his truck,
it will become a reality.
What does this have to do
with Manuella's death?
It's simple, Manuella went
ferreting about all over the place.
Look, she's highlighted things, here.
She found the same issues as I did.
Which proves that curiosity
can kill the cat.
Samuel can't have killed Manuella.
-There's no way!
-There's no way?
Well then why did you get him
a totally bogus alibi?
He's been gone for two days,
since Morales' death!
Family love is nice, it's lovely.
But it has its limits!
Oh yes, I forgot to mention.
We found your nephew's DNA.
Wanna know where?
-Beneath the victim's fingernails.
-You're bluffing.
Here it is.
They both work here,
I think.
What the fuck
can they be doing here?
To be, or not to...
be.
That is the question.
Whether 'tis nobler in the mind
to suffer the slings
and arrows
of outrageous fortune,
or to take arms against a sea of
troubles and by opposing end them.
To die.
To sleep.
To sleep?
Perchance to dream.
Excuse me.
We're looking for a young woman
named Salomé.
You're interrupting Hamlet, sir.
You're interrupting Shakespeare.
Do you respect actors?
I may be bothering you,
but it's very important.
It's a matter of life or death.
-First one on the left.
-Thank you.
From the top.
Did you know he danced?
His mother was a dance teacher.
I knew she brought him along, but...
But I didn't know that... No.
You still have
a lot to learn about him.
-Is that his girlfriend?
-That's me.
-I didn't expect to see him here.
-And yet this is our home.
Where is he?
I desperately need to speak to him.
-I'm not a snitch.
-I need to see him.
-The cops want to talk to him.
-What do they want?
There was a murder.
He's the main suspect.
-It wasn't him.
-I know, that's not the issue.
I bet you he won't talk to them.
Do you love him?
I might.
Then try and convince him to come.
Nobody can. You're
his father, you should know that.
Well then, just tell him
that I need to see him.
And also tell him
that I'm proud of him.
Good evening.
-Good evening, madam.
-Evening, Jennifer.
This is his truck, no?
Let's see...
There we are.
Now we know why he was driving
further than the others.
Because of this.
-Is that soil?
-Soil...
Did your mother teach you nothing?
Soil, this?
No, this is pot, hash,
a drug that is soft...
but illegal.
So, your nephew,
was using the truck to traffic drugs
between Spain and France.
Morales must've caught on right away,
what with her cost-cutting obsession.
Well, what would you have done?
-I don't know.
-I think I would have fired him.
-Fired my nephew?
-Yes, booted his ass right out.
Maybe that's playing it too safe.
I would have blackmailed him.
The kid mustn't have liked that.
Which makes sense, I get it.
Shall we smoke ourselves a doobie?
I'm just kidding!
-When the gendarmerie...
-What a nutcase.
Pirouette, peanut...
There was once a little man
Pirouette, peanut
Who had a very curious house
And it was a cardboard house
Pirouette, peanut
It was a cardboard house...
Are you nuts, you scared me!
I wanted to be the first.
-The first to what?
-Why, to wish you a happy birthday.
Well, you won, you're the first.
Here.
Pierrot, you shouldn't have.
I'm a bit ashamed, I don't even
know your birthday.
Doesn't matter, it's not
about me. Open it.
Heavens, you're mad, Pierrot!
-This is far too much!
-Do you like it?
Well, of course.
-I really picked it out for you.
-Thank you.
Dad's car!
You got it back?
I had it repaired for you.
You'll have to pass
the technical controls.
Honestly.
Did you think I would
forget your birthday?
No.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, sweetie.
To us.
-And to Samuel.
-To us.
We're going to figure this out.
We always did.
Look at that lake.
It's its birthday, too.
It's been twenty-seven years.
Twenty-seven years that our hiding
places have been covered in water.
Do you remember? That little village?
Once in a while, the steeple
comes poking back out. It's strange.
Do you remember that?
Of course.
You don't forget anything.
You tuck it away in the secret
drawers of memory.
-What happened to you there?
-Oh, this? It's nothing.
Must've grazed myself getting
out of the pick-up.
And do you remember this?
Oh yes, I remember that.
You said that if you blew on it,
it would heal.
That's right.
-Blanche.
-Hello Samuel, how are you honey?
-You wanted to see me?
-Manuella was killed.
The cops want to get
your statement.
They think you did it.
Security footage shows you slapping
her. Why did you do that?
-Give him a second to take it in!
-None of your business.
-It was between her and me.
-Yes, but she was killed afterwards.
-I didn't do anything.
-We know that, honey.
Well, tell that to the cops, then.
You think I'd do such a thing?
No, he doesn't think that!
I can see it in his eyes.
You're thinking your fucking son
fucked up again! You never trust me.
I told you I quit!
Sure, you say you kicked the habit,
but then sneak hash into your dad's
trucks. Of course he's mad!
Hey!
No funny business.
We're going to go to
the police station, calmly, and chat.
You ratted me out, you bastard!
-I'll never trust you again!
-We'll let him know. Come on.
So?
It's true,
Manuella and I had a fight.
How come?
Was she mad because you were
using up her diesel
-for your dumbass trafficking?
-What trafficking?
Hey! Stop!
We started off bad, but don't you try
and treat me like I'm a dumbass.
For heaven's sake.
What's this?
I was young too, once.
Ugly, but young. So I know what
that good shit looks like.
You think that's funny?
What is that?
It's not compost
to grow lettuce in.
Chill, it was my stash.
For your own stash, you don't need
to go all the way to Barcelona.
The party square
is two kilometers away.
You can get whatever you want there.
So?
You're not the sharpest
tool in the shed, huh?
Honestly.
I don't know, when you've got
a rotten record like yours,
you keep your mouth shut.
You watch your step. No?
Let me spell it out for you.
You know your darling aunt, Blanche,
she wants to save
your dumb ass.
You dig?
Except her alibi
is a total piece of shit.
Know why?
Because you, in fact,
you were carrying hash,
your boss caught you,
and you slapped her
and you killed her, simple as that!
Sit back down.
Where do you think this is?
I'm not your mom.
So chill out, and then tell me
what's going on. I'm listening.
I've transported cannabis
three times.
I wanted to get my girlfriend
a real present.
And Manuella caught me.
Well that was no reason
to slap her.
-That's not why I slapped her!
-Then why did you?
I don't know... When I told her it
was for a girl, she went hysterical.
She told me I was like my father.
A seducer, a pervert.
So, I don't know, I flipped out.
Your father, a seducer?
-I thought he'd been alone ten years.
-You don't get it, do you?
Manuella was into my father.
And he discarded her
like a used tissue.
Philippe?
I decided to come,
you seemed distraught.
Yes, Samuel is in custody,
I need a lawyer.
Call Dorisse from me.
She's the best.
I don't know how to thank you.
-You don't know what you want, huh?
-Yes, I do. This is to protect you.
That's too easy.
You're the one you're protecting.
You're bad luck, so you'd
rather do nothing?
Who do you think you're fooling
except you?
You just can't love anyone
other than yourself, that's al!
Wait.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you crying?
Did Philippe Muir hit you?
-No, it's not that.
-What then?
Psychological violence?
Did he mistreat you?
Don't go getting any ideas.
He just doesn't want me.
Nothing to lock him up over.
He's a funny guy,
that one is, isn't he?
-He feels guilt for his wife's death.
-Guilt? How so?
Not guilty for real.
He's convinced all the women he loves
wind up dying because of him.
But that's typical.
I've met plenty of killers,
of predators.
Through work, obviously.
It's strange, but every time,
they regret doing it. Really, though.
This is not like that.
-Philippe Muir isn't a...
-He isn't what?
How long have you known him for?
We met three months ago, when
I began Samuel's judicial follow-up.
And we saw each other again
3 days ago.
So you're old childhood friends.
You know him very well, basically.
What're you implying?
Nothing at all.
If you're accusing him of murdering
Manuella Morales, forget about it.
We spent that night together.
He even left at 5 a.m.
Well sure, but...
Here's the thing, Manuella Morales
was killed at 6 a.m.
Cuts you short, no?
-Your dad is here.
-You ready?
-What? They let me go?
-Someone testified on your behalf.
Salomé!
She said you were together
on the murder night.
-You're free.
-Thanks for telling me.
-Is it my dad who...
-Yes, he came to get me,
told me you needed me.
Where'd he find you?
He's already been to the studio, he's
even seen one of your performances.
-You having me followed?
-No!
-Chill, I invited him.
-You never mentioned the dancing.
What would you have done
if I told you I wanted to dance?
You only ever wanted one thing:
for me to become a trucker
and take over the business.
I did that for you.
-So you wouldn't fall prey to crack.
-But I hate trucks!
I even hate cars.
Engines, tires.
Brake pads, highway miles,
that stuff makes me hurl.
Look, Samuel,
I don't have much to teach you.
So if you want to dance,
and if you're happy...
That's fine with me.
Thanks for coming to get me.
Thank you.
Thanks, dad.
Hey, Carpentier!
What the hell is this?
You let Samuel Muir go?
His girlfriend claims they were in
Marseille when it happened.
At a rave.
They arrived around midnight.
-And do we have proof?
-The bouncers remember him well.
Samuel was so drunk
they kicked him out at 8 a.m.
-It's nice, being young.
-You think?
Between killing a guy
and having to hear 8 hours of techno,
not sure I'd choose techno.
Even if I swallowed some E.
Well, the alibi was confirmed
by their friends and the bouncers.
Yes? Okay.
Captain!
Blanche Muir has been
in a car accident.
They haven't found
her body yet.
Fuck.
That was all we needed.
...a road accident.
Thank you. You alright, partner?
-Hello.
-It's this way.
-Where's the body?
-We just found it.
She jumped out before the crash.
-She's in there.
-In there?
-Is she going to be okay?
-Yeah, with a few cuts.
Crazy reflexes.
-Can I talk to her?
-Not yet, she's totally in shock.
Cars sure are dangerous.
Especially with Philippe Muir.
Hello.
-Have you begun swabbing?
-Yes.
I don't usually do autopsies on car.
It's only because it's you.
I know, but I thought there was
a stiff in the car.
What's up with this info you gave me?
Dumbasses.
Honestly, I'm sorry.
I'm wasting your time.
If you like, I can cut into
the engine and wheels.
-Can't be too different from a body.
-You'd really do that for me?
-Come check it out.
-You're too kind.
Help me, doc.
Thank you.
Here, you see?
-That's ugly, that is.
-Real ugly.
You think you could do a quick
swab for fingerprints?
-That would be a huge help.
-I'll do what I can.
But you were right to get me to come.
The woman driving this car
really should have died.
Well, that's what the guy who
cut the break line right there
wanted to make happen.
Alright, I'll let you get back to it.
Thank you.
-So, how are you doing?
-Great.
Just a couple scratches.
No kidding, I was very lucky.
It all depends on
your point of view.
Well, the car definitely
wasn't as lucky.
It's too bad,
it was our father's car.
Philippe had just gotten it back
and given it to me for my birthday.
And tell me, your brother's
first wife, Héloïse.
How did she die, exactly?
-A car accident.
-That so.
How strange, just like you.
Am I losing it
or is there a pattern?
She fell asleep behind the wheel.
I'm sure someone
could have drugged her.
-Someone did cut your break line.
-That was just wear and tear.
-It was an old car.
-Wear and tear, sure.
Look, captain...
My brother loves me.
We're everything to each other.
He would never have wanted
to kill me, never.
Well, that's just it.
I suspect him of killing
all of the women he loves.
You see, there was his first wife,
Héloïse: yeek.
His accountant Manuella, yeek two.
And you, a near-yeek.
If I'm right,
we'll have to arrest him.
Because otherwise
his new girlfriend's in trouble.
What? You didn't know?
He's having a liaison.
Philippe Muir.
You'll need to follow me.
-Philippe.
-Yes.
She says you have
a new girlfriend.
She's lying, isn't she?
No...
I forgot to tell you.
It's Cécile Castelnau.
Want me to do anything?
Yes, if ever I don't come back,
would you mind letting her know?
Thank you.
Let's go.
Tell me, Mr. Muir, do you murder
all the ladies who love you?
Because right now, it's 17:23.
You'll be in custody.
For the murder of Manuella Morales.
Let's recap.
You spent the night at
Cécile Castelnau's place, right?
And then, you, and I quote:
"Wandered around the streets
for an hour."
Of course, given the time,
nobody saw you?
Yes.
Yes, there was, uh...
There was a trailer
with an old woman nearby.
And she took my hand
and told me that I...
was going to have a bad day.
She had no idea.
A bad day?
That's a bit rich,
because a bad day...
You did have a nice little roll
in the hay with Cécile,
just before.
A nice one nighter, hey?
Without the domestic life bullshit.
Ain't that groovy?
That's the dream, no?
You don't get it at all.
Really?
All I wanted to do was to go back
and hold Cécile.
And to sleep until the next day.
I don't get why you didn't, then.
And I feel like it's not bad
with her, is it?
You're pretty popular, no?
No?
-You not going to answer, Mr. Muir ?
-You couldn't understand.
Whenever I love a woman,
she dies.
That's it.
I know it seems ridiculous,
but that's the way it is.
No, it's not ridiculous.
Up until then,
we pretty much agree.
The women
who hang out around you
have a higher-than-average
death rate.
A premature death rate. Violent, too.
You know what we're going to do?
We're going to start over.
And you're going to explain
how you kill all of them.
Go ahead, I'm listening.
Alright, so you've
identified the fingerprints?
Thanks, old pal.
It's a present I promised
to someone dear to me.
What's wrong? Have you never
wanted to please a woman?
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Oh, hello.
Alright, my dear friend.
I know who sabotaged the car.
Really? Well, you better watch out.
I'm close to asking you to marry me.
Just an inch.
-Still no news from Blanche?
-No, she hasn't arrived, yet.
What's she up to?
Mr. Lacoudre,
did I forget to tell you?
-You're under arrest.
-What?
Yes, follow me.
Blanche is in the hospital.
You didn't kill her,
which really pisses you off!
You wanted her to die
when you cut her brake wires.
I wanted to wreck her car,
not to hurt her.
Stop it.
I saw you having a fight with her
one morning.
You resented her
because she wasn't in love with you.
No, it's her birthday.
I got her a necklace,
I spent over two hours
picking it out in the shop.
And she put it down on a table
and forgot about it.
-That's no reason to kill someone.
-Put yourself in my shoes.
I give her some jewelry, and then
that asshole shows up with a car.
He's her whole life,
her brother!
-And you can't stand her brother.
-No. Philippe this, Philippe that.
Yeah, I get that.
All this "Philippe" stuff
gets old after a while.
So is that why?
You took your revenge because he's
popular with the ladies?
-You get what I'm saying?
-No, I don't.
Sure, so you killed all the girls
who were hovering around him.
-His wife...
-Hang on, no.
I wrecked the car,
I'll give you that.
But I didn't know his wife.
I've been here for 4 years.
-That bullshit true?
-Yes.
Fuck. Stay there, don't move.
Carpentier!
Mr. Muir, come with me.
Hurry up, quick!
-Where are we going right now?
-You'll see, hurry your ass up.
I'm not superstitious.
It's bad luck, knock on wood.
This whole curse story of yours...
I've been trying to find
a rational explanation for it.
-I don't get it.
-You say all the women you love die.
Except that you don't die,
there's always someone by your side.
Someone protecting you,
someone who loves you.
And who even loves you more
than all the women
and all the guys
you'll love in your life.
You know who I mean?
For instance, with Héloïse.
When you were supposed
to find a house,
you cancelled your trip.
Why?
Because someone sent you to the other
side of France on a delivery.
You aren't cursed
like some old king, sir.
It's your sister.
She's totally nuts.
I mean real fucking nuts.
Stop following me.
Go on, scram.
Wait for me here,
I'm going up there alone.
I said wait, that's an order.
Can't you read?
-Put your hands in the air!
-Move, and I'll shoot!
Put your weapon down.
-Put your weapon down.
-Yeah, okay.
There.
Stay calm, okay?
Everything's fine.
Let her go, Blanche.
She didn't do anything.
Philippe, you're here.
Yes.
Come on now, Blanche.
Give me that gun.
You're going to hurt yourself.
Come on.
-Come here.
-Your brother's right.
Come on, give me that.
I promise I'll let you both
talk in peace.
Let her go,
she has nothing to do with this.
Do you really love this woman,
Philippe?
No, Blanche.
I only love you.
Come on.
Give me that gun.
Then we can talk.
Just you and me, okay?
Do as he says. It's your only
hope of getting out of this.
Look...
You're bleeding.
Give me your weapon.
I'll blow on your hurt spot,
want me to?
No, don't move, you!
Philippe!
No!
Come on, Blanche.
Come on.
I could never stand the idea
of seeing him with other women.
First, there was Julia.
He was spending more and more
time with her.
On Sundays, he barely even
came home for lunch.
One night, I was coming back
from a party, I was drunk.
And then, in front of me,
in my car's headlights,
I saw her on the road.
I sped up.
I hadn't planned it at all.
That's just how it happened.
There you go.
Then, there was Héloïse.
I really liked her.
Things could've gone on
as they were, but she had
to want to move back to Spain,
to bring both Philippe
and Samuel with her.
That's when you sent
Philippe to Lille?
Yes, that's right.
And I told Héloïse
I'd accompany her for a bit.
I left her in Madrid, after dropping
a sleeping pill in her glass.
And then...
Life began its course once more.
We were all together,
Philippe, Samuel, and I.
Just like a real family,
that's all I can call it.
And then...
He had to do it again.
Alright...
Come on in.
You can take her.
Couldn't he have just
controlled himself?
You see what kinds of situations
he gets us into!
This fucking idiot!
Fucking idiot!
Hey there!
Welcome to paradise.
Captain Marleau and her crew
wish you an enjoyable stay.
I wanted to bring you some flowers.
But it seemed somber, so I brought
this. Do they not have glasses, here?
Well, we'll drink it out the bottle.
You know much about wine?
This one's supposed to be good.
From Aniane.
Cheers!
I prefer beer, myself.
You want some?
No, thank you.
You see, Mr. Muir?
Your curse story was a bunch
of bullshit. There's no such thing.
So now, if you want to be in love,
there aren't too many risks.
But cover up!
Ouch!
You're making a mistake,
this stuff's good.
Cécile.
It's here, is it?
And here we are.
-Rassomon?
-Rashômon.
The restaurant
where they make the delicious sushis
that we found
in the stomach of Manuella Morales!
That's so nice!
Yes, bravo!
That's great!
I'd believe in god and shit.
Honestly, it's awesome.
So?
Afterwards, well, if you want,
I've got a bit of Chartreuse
at home.
It's delightful.
It's like baby Jesus
in velvet underpants.
I don't like underwear. It's itchy.
But I'm game.
There's just one thing, though.
I only put out on the first date.
That's perfect, works for me.
Let's eat first.
Subtitling: Hiventy