Mirror, mirror,
who is the ugliest
in the police force?
Huh?
Captain Marleau!
CAPTAIN MARLEAU
Don't worry about it!
Make yourself at home!
Ah...
Are you the Satyr of these woods?
I'm the owner.
Some people have no manners!
The public track is over there,
and this is private property.
I love hazelnut-smelling
prohibited tracks.
It's the law.
Is the stupidest law is the best one?
I'm in luck then.
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
We're off on the right foot!
Not there!
Yes!
Idiot!
You'll see!
THE NIGHT OF THE RED MOON
POLICE
So?
Sorry, it just finished.
The next episode is at 2:00 a.m.
No way! Can't they do reruns?
I hate that!
The red moon is the most beautiful
because it was in the most beautiful
skies that this immortal appeared.
I'm thirsty for blood, mortal.
I'll eat you, Little Red Riding Hood!
Shut up!
It's serious, Léonard.
This isn't a joke.
You can wait in the car, Manon.
-You promised!
-And you promised to shut up!
Go and wait over there.
-What's the worst that can happen?
-Yeah?
Apparently Chalard hired a guard.
Maybe it's just a rumor,
but we don't know.
Come on, Julien. Let's do a selfie.
-A souvenir.
-Come on.
Ready...
Cheese!
I'll come back with you.
Then we separate, as we said. OK?
Does he think he's God's sidekick.
Don't say that, poor mortal.
He is God.
Amen.
NO TO THE GOLF COURSE
Yeah, that's great.
Little rascals!
I'll make you scatter, you sparrows.
-Run!
-Léonard!
Léonard!
Julien!
You know, dear,
-I wanted to tell you a secret.
-What secret, Mom?
Alexis isn't who you think.
He's your...
Your what? Your brother?
Your murderer?
Your dad? Damn!
Where's the circuit breaker?
Damn it!
Alain Peras, Entzheim mayor,
we've lost electricity.
Please send a team quickly.
Shine it higher.
What did they say?
Answering machine.
Third time this year.
I'll have to keep the landline
all day.
You can just not pick up.
After all, you came for nothing.
I can't leave people in the dark.
You mean you can't leave people
in the dark before elections?
Are you afraid
they'll vote for Chalard?
You never know with these people.
Hammer, please.
It's not starting.
It just needs a feminine touch.
And Jeanne said:
"Let there be light!"
And there was light.
And sly and cruel,
she let him leave in the dark
and the rain.
He, who hoped to snore by her side
till the morning.
Because she thought that hell
could always wait.
Have you thought about it?
Listen, Alain...
I love you, you love me,
we love each other.
We don't want to lose what we have.
And what if it's important to me?
Why? Huh? Can you explain?
Why now?
We've been together three years.
-What will it change?
-Maybe you don't care, but
getting married means something
to me.
Yes, you're right.
I don't care about marriage. Come on.
Manon? Manon,
what are you doing there?
What's wrong?
We wanted... we wanted to put up
a banner to protest the golf course
-and he's dead.
-Who's dead?
-Chalard?
-No.
Léonard.
Jeanne, Léonard died in my arms.
And someone else,
but I don't know who.
But he's dead, too.
Hi, Jeanne...
Think of me from time to time.
Don't worry, it's OK.
It's OK.
-Captain. How are you?
-Hi, Brière.
It's cold today.
Hi, Captain.
-Comrades.
-Thank you.
So, where's Oscar?
-With the body.
-Ah...
-Can you get me a coffee?
-Sure.
Oscar! Hi! It's nice to see you!
Give me a kiss!
It's a pleasure, Captain.
You're still uptight.
You won't forgive me.
-So?
-There it is.
Poor thing...
It should be illegal to die so young.
What happened?
He fell.
A fall of about 5.5 meters.
He fell on his head
causing compression
of the spinal cord,
which would have caused quadriplegia.
But that's not the cause of death.
He died from a heart attack
after muscle paralysis.
His posture was tense.
Time of death: 2:08 a.m.
-08? That's very precise...
-His watch.
It stopped on impact.
Do we have his papers?
No, he didn't have them.
But the mayor is there.
He should know who it is.
A kid killed at the top of a tree
at 2:00 a.m., disguised as Zorro.
They say we should guide the youth.
It disgusts me.
We're off again...
I saw him a few times
at the Milles Sources cafe.
They're a bit loud,
but they don't hurt anyone.
Excuse me.
When there's a blackout,
I suddenly become God.
Yes, Geneviève?
Get me another one. That's horrible.
Thanks, bye.
All this to sort out...
There's a dead girl.
But I'm not the mayor.
The mayor needs to sort out
the big dramas and the small ones.
-Do you still need me?
-No.
Yes! Because yesterday,
I met the owner of the dump,
and it was like love at first sight.
I want to see him again. Who is it?
Michel Chalard.
A businessman from Entzheim.
He worked in Bordeaux
and he inherited this land.
He's doing something big.
A golf course, entertainment.
That's good
for your electoral campaign.
First: jobs,
second: jobs,
and third: jobs!
It's good for him.
He's running against me.
Captain!
There's a new body.
This isn't possible.
What is it about here?
1943 Mauser cartridge,
shot recently.
Ah, there you are.
There's no bullet wound.
How did he die?
There are dead people
everywhere here.
Well, what do we have?
At first glance,
the only wound is a blow
to the left side of the face.
Violent but the only one.
You're telling me that
he was struck and died unconscious?
Some bad luck.
His color is black
and his number is zero.
Given the wound, I'd say
the butt of a Mauser 43.
-From where the shell comes.
-The shell...
So, what's his name?
Robert Perdriel, security guard.
He lived alone with his cat.
I know the type.
What was he guarding here
apart from trees and nettles?
This morning, when I arrived,
I saw tire tracks.
Like a quick getaway.
-I think there were at least three.
-Why do you say that?
Footsteps near the tree.
And I found this.
A bit of black synthetic tissue,
burned by an iron.
-A piece of Zorro's cape.
-Yeah?
Sometimes, I just want to kiss you.
I don't know what stops me.
Your breath, maybe.
With your permission, I'm off
to my corpses.
Captain! Captain, look what I found.
What is it?
Do you smoke joints?
-I found it near the body.
-Which one? There's plenty.
The second one.
-The big one?
-Yeah.
Good work.
-What did you find?
-Something from Zorro.
To the left, there's Entzheim
about ten kilometers away.
On the right is Ms. Dewaere's
animal park,
the mayor's girlfriend.
Is she the type to climb trees
in a Zorro mask?
In some senses, yes, but... no.
-Do you get it?
-No.
I prefer my jokes to be direct.
Look, Captain.
What are you doing?
You're like a dog.
We're lucky.
Barbie bunny!
The things we find in this forest!
Here.
Go and get my car, we'll meet
at Ms. Dewaere's, OK?
-No, I'd prefer to come with you...
-No.
Fusion couples are like fusion jazz,
I hate it.
A bunny killed a hunter...
It was a bunny who
had a rifle.
WOLF VALLEY
Ms. Dewaere's car left at about 3:00
and the dog barked at around 3:30.
I don't know why.
Did you hear a shot?
Yes, maybe. I think I did.
As it was during the blackout,
I thought nothing of it.
Someone fired?
Yeah, it came
from Michel Chalard's wood.
A shot from a 1943 rifle.
-A Mauser.
-A Mauser 43?
That's from the war.
Who has these guns?
-I thought you'd tell me.
-No, sorry,
but I would've noticed
a rifle like that.
-OK, thanks.
-No problem.
Ah, Mr. Gabriel,
I want to show you something,
if I can find it in this mess...
A scarf from a Renaud concert.
Do you know who owns this?
No, I don't.
It's not mine.
OK.
It's nice here.
I like Alsace. I come back often.
It's really nice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
is there only one entry to the park?
Yes, the main entry.
After, people drive around
like they want.
-I'll let my boss know.
-OK.
-She doesn't like authority.
-She's not the only one.
Yeah. Dangerous liaisons...
They maintain passion, as...
Malkovich or Werther said...
Get up. The police are here.
Hurry up, you're explaining
to them. Get up.
Jeanne, don't make me do it.
The judge can't put me away.
He'll jump on it.
You can't make me.
I've tried hard, Jeanne.
Six years in the clink, Jeanne.
I can't. I'd prefer to die.
You're so annoying.
And I'm an idiot.
Come on.
I'll get you when they've left.
Wait, Jeanne. I can't find my phone.
It must be in the room. I'll find it.
Don't move.
It's hot here.
Les Bidochons, I love it.
-Make yourself at home.
-Thank you.
-Is that your son?
-No, not at all.
It's Mr. Louis, the old guard.
Funny you thought he was my son,
we were the same age.
He died more than 15 years ago.
He has no wrinkles.
-Me, on the other hand...
-Yeah.
I took over his lodge and changed
the decor.
I have simple tastes. I'm an old guy.
-Ah... excuse me.
-It's OK.
Hello?
Yeah.
OK, I'll tell him.
-OK
-Poor thing.
Goodbye.
She said you can go to see her.
She seems gruff, but she's nice.
Yeah. I see.
Do you want to live a boring life?
With no fun?
Do you know what adrenaline is?
Risk?
Putting your life on the line?
In ten minutes, max, you have a rush.
Like a fix, but better.
What's wrong? Are you afraid?
Yes, I'm afraid.
I like it.
I'm coming.
Your coffee's horrible!
Horrible coffee, horrible coffee.
Could I have another cup? No?
You're the type to say no.
Do you need something from me?
Yeah, I wanted to know
if you've seen a witness
because apparently
there's one hiding here.
A witness?
Not a Jehovah's witness.
A murder witness. Double murder.
Who was killed?
Did it happen here?
Look! He's coming! How are you honey?
Do you have pigs? I like pigs.
It's not a farm here.
So, around 2:00 this morning,
did you hear a shot?
You weren't asleep?
-During the blackout?
-You had a blackout?
-Yes.
-That's men. When they drink.
No, during the blackout.
No, I just turned on the generator.
No, I would've heard a shot.
Sound travels far here.
I want to show you something...
I don't know where I found it...
There's a bit...
I often travel so I put everything
in my pockets.
There it is.
Are you familiar with this?
It's the weapon?
It could be, it's that ugly.
Whoever has this phone, my God,
if they're more than nine,
I'd put them in prison
-for bad taste.
-Good news. It's not mine.
You can leave me.
-You're good-natured, you know?
-Yes, I know.
Do you know anyone around here
who collects old guns?
I'm talking things
from the Second World War,
Mausers. Are you into that?
No, it's not my thing.
If I may, weapons are worse taste
than pink phones.
Not wrong.
I have candy, too.
You want one?
No, thanks.
Oh, shit.
-That's all we needed.
-Who's that?
-Michel Chalard.
-Ah, the owner.
Marleau?
Captain Marleau. Seeing as
we don't have the same salary,
can you at least speak correctly?
How are you?
Alsace is small. For lovers like us.
You know each other?
Not really, we just met.
But it'll last.
We haven't really met each other.
Michel Chalard,
I'm the owner of the property
where the drama was.
Aspiring mayor, too.
Sofa promotion?
I had a guard for surveillance.
That's who they killed.
Why do you say "they"?
How do you know there were several?
What do you know?
Did you see them?
There's a band of them.
They tagged my property walls,
defamed me on the internet.
I complained, but nothing happened.
-Do you know their name?
-No.
They're all anonymous.
A big Z as a signature.
And I'm the bad one.
Even though I'm trying
to bring life back to my home.
-He's good, Zorro.
-The Zorros,
maybe they're afraid
of new Robin Hoods?
Bad Robin Hoods
who apparently bring work
from Samsonite and Goodyear.
I think these kids
were walking on the hazelnut track,
got to your clearing,
and what did they see?
A non-declared construction site.
That's not Republican.
Is that the secret you wanted kept?
Yes, it's true, the authorizations
were slow.
I knew I'd have them,
so, I planned for it.
Like all the big men,
Angela Davis, Marie Curie, etc.
I don't know, this clearing's
always attracted psychos.
They came to do their things.
Now, kids come to smoke joints,
so, I got a guard,
Robert Perdriel, a brave man.
Did he smoke or carry joints?
Was he armed? No, I don't think so.
No...
I wanted to show you.
Do you know this phone?
Ah, speaking of phones... excuse me.
Yes... yes, you're going to hurt me?
It will be incredible.
Yes.
You don't seem to be friends
with Chalard.
It has nothing to do
with your investigation.
Well, you know...
Territorial lords can cross paths.
Just like your property
is penetrable.
Because it seems your guard
heard the dog barking last night.
So, I'm going to check amongst
the bears if there's an intruder.
If something happens to you,
it could come down on me.
I can defend myself.
-I don't need anyone.
-Ah, no?
Unless you have a search warrant?
Yes, I always have one on me.
Little bear!
Hello!
No, I think I left it at home.
Come back when you've found it.
OK. What time is it?
Hello! Auntie Marteau is here.
-9:58
-58?
Show me. They're precise,
these pocket watches.
My grandma had one.
We must have put it on the...
well, we don't care.
How much is the entry fee?
Five euros. It's on the sign.
Ah, really? I'm not sure if I have
that much on me. It's a lot.
Do you do discounts
for public servants,
part-time workers, etc.?
Because it might be hard.
Hey! What wouldn't we do
to come and see the beautiful bear?
Come on, come on.
OK, I'm off.
See you soon!
Hey! Mr. Chalard!
There are bears. We're off to see
the wolves. Are you coming?
OK, why not?
"Wooo" says the wolf!
So, if I understood,
it seems like you have a problem
with Ms. Dewaere?
The golf course? Yes,
it's not going well.
It's hardcore country mentality.
And Jeanne Dewaere
isn't very accommodating.
I noticed. What does she have to do
with the golf course?
Look at this house.
Ideal for a panoramic restaurant.
We could make the terrace bigger
and seat 80 people.
Yeah! I have an idea:
upstairs rooms for the golfers,
they can do 18 holes
and then after...
-You see what I mean?
-Ah, yes.
But, where does Jeanne put her tent?
Amongst the wolves?
I'll make her a loft room
in the attic.
She lives alone, you know?
-Think of the lost space.
-I am!
-She said no?
-Exactly.
-She's the type to say no.
-I respect her.
-But she has a character...
-Yes, how could we say it?
She's difficult.
Poor people don't know
what's good for them.
Luckily, there are people like you
to do the thinking.
-Captain!
-What?
Sorry, Mr. Chalard, I must go.
Don't hesitate to get in touch.
I feel guilty for the guard.
Guilty? How guilty?
You killed him?
I'm joking, Mr. Chalard!
-So?
-The butt is at the lab,
the cartridge, too.
For the piece of material,
forensics was right--
it's from Zorro's cape.
Otherwise, the guard,
Robert Perdriel, lived alone.
He didn't want
a weapon. He said that if he had one,
he wouldn't use it.
-Not wrong.
-That's it.
And the cartridge, for the moment,
has nothing to do with our case,
but maybe...
-well, we don't know.
-I don't understand what you said.
I'm going for a run, to clear
my head, because you...
I wasn't clear there...
Yeah, yeah, keep going!
You can do it!
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, hello!
Look, I'm a redhead, too.
Look. I'm a ginger.
Give me a kiss.
You don't want to give me a kiss?
OK, I'm off, then.
Hello, Michel! It's nice to see you.
-How are you, Gabriel?
-Good.
A bit shaken, like everyone.
-It must be hard for you.
-You can say that again.
It's bad timing, with the elections.
Yeah. It's not a good memory.
What was the old guard's name?
Arthur Lerois.
He died in the same place.
Except that it was
a real murder.
He would have been 45.
It's strange to grow old.
While the dead, they stay
forever young.
Do you know anything?
As I always say, the best-informed
man in Entzheim is Gabriel.
You know me. I don't like confusion.
But I don't know if I should say
that I found a strange mess
in the boss's trash.
That's interesting.
And that's not counting
the dog barking at 3:30 a.m.
Here.
I found this.
Hello, little dogs.
Brière.
No, she's not far. Yes.
Ah, yes, OK. Great.
Thanks a lot. OK, I'll go right away.
It isn't like the boss
to have a pink telephone.
And you saw that it's not possible
to intrude into the park.
Virgile reacts immediately.
-Even from afar.
-Yeah?
Well, apparently he was barking.
Virgile? No, definitely not.
-I would have heard him.
-Ah, OK.
How do you like Ms. Dewaere ?
A bit? A lot? Like crazy?
I owe her everything.
Do you know many
women who hire ex-inmates
with no questions?
Not really. It's not typical.
That rhymes with trustworthy.
Trustworthy to the point of lying
to cops, for example.
Are there many ex-inmates ready
to do that?
To cover her?
Yeah, she helps anyone she can.
I'll say something:
when she took over the animal park,
Arthur Lerois, the guard,
he'd done six months for bodily harm.
Everyone advised her to fire him.
Interesting.
Captain.
We identified the victim.
It's Léonard Vincenne.
A student on vacation
with his friend Julien Redon.
The address is St.-George-les-Mines.
OK. And the cartridge?
It's from a Mauser 43.
It was shot recently and look, here.
A license for a Mauser.
Jean-Marie Chalard.
Isn't that the father of...
-of Michel?
-Yeah.
-Where's my parka?
-Back there.
Let's go and get it.
Did you hear that?
The Mauser was Chalard's.
So, he killed the guard.
I'm not surprised.
There's something about him.
No, you're not right.
Me and Chalard grew up together.
He wouldn't touch a fly.
You're naive, Gabriel.
You always see the good.
There's my parka.
-Why did you forget it there?
-Sorry...
Calm down. Look at it.
There's candy inside.
OK, let's go.
Go in front if it's dangerous.
There are wolves!
Our last selfie with Léonard.
Good reason to get rid of it.
You don't realize.
A firearm, a murder.
That's not what you told me.
Ah, yes, the rifle shot.
-I'd forgotten.
-How did you forget?
Look at me. Answer me honestly.
Do you know something
about the guard's death?
Jeanne, I didn't even know
he was there!
And Julien, he disappeared?
I don't know. I have no news.
Hold on.
The police can't come to you.
They can't prove anything.
Now, you're going back to work.
Like normal.
No, I can't, Jeanne!
Of course you can!
You're hard on me.
Yeah, I'm hard.
That's why I take risks
to save your skin!
Little idiot!
No, Jeanne, wait.
Sorry.
I didn't want to say that. I'm sorry.
That's Julien Redon's house.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, pretty sure.
What's going on?
It's a police squad.
Where do they think they are?
Goddamn special forces.
The crazier we get,
the more we laugh,
-but not sure we have the same humor.
-No, that's true.
Comrades. So, what's going on?
Julien Redon has been
on the watchlist a while.
The Interior Ministry saw
his texts online. Calls for uprising.
So, we're taking over
the investigation.
Procurer's orders.
It's come from the top.
Well, if it's from the top...
Is that Julien Redon ?
Yes.
He confessed to the murder.
He said it was accidental.
He says that he and Léonard
wanted to mock Michel Chalard.
They wanted to attach
a banner to the trees.
"To mock"? You police talk funny.
Did Redon say there were three?
No, there were just two.
Him and Vincenne.
Sorry, Captain, we have work to do.
Ah, yes, and we don't?
This is ridiculous.
If they're terrorists,
I'm the Dalai Lama.
We're not going
to leave them, Captain?
Let's keep going. We're on a roll.
You just have to give them that.
It'll give them something to do.
Are you joking? I found that.
No, I won't.
We're not giving them that.
Ah... concealment of proof...
Do you want to enlist
in the Red Brigade?
Anarchist!
No, I'm joking. Look, did you see?
When you left my parka,
someone stole the phone.
Nothing inside, no sim card.
You're joking!
I don't think I'm made
for this job. Dad was right.
Your dad's a fool.
Thanks to you, we're close.
If we find who stole the sim card,
we know who wants
to cover up the case.
You understand? Here.
What are you doing?
Finally alone.
I thought you'd appreciate
my discretion.
Let me tell you,
you're in trouble, Jeanne.
Impeding a terrorist
investigation case
is bad.
What?
-Your protégée is at risk.
-Who?
Manon. The little delinquent.
It's maybe not my place,
but you have a bad taste for thugs.
Like Jean-Claude, the drug addict.
-Ex.
-Ah, ex-drug addict.
Or Arthur, the ex-guard.
A real riffraff, that guy.
Six months for bodily harm.
Arthur was the most adorable
person I met.
He was attacked.
But the police didn't listen.
In any case, this attraction
to criminals...
Have you thought of psychoanalysis?
What do you want?
Still the same thing.
Our agreement for the golf course.
Get out of here.
I know you're doing it to win votes.
I have proof that Manon was involved,
and that you've hidden the suspect
of a double terrorist act.
I'm nice. I've said nothing...
until now.
Look. My new project.
It's a win-win situation.
Congratulations.
I'm convinced now not to sign.
It's not a proposition,
it's blackmail.
Ah... I understand.
You think I'm bluffing.
-Hello?
-Captain Marleau?
It's Michel Chalard. I just realized
I have a document
that could help you.
-Send it to Brière.
-No, I want to give it to you.
-Where can we meet?
-My place, at 3:00 p.m.
Perfect.
You have until 3:00 p.m to sign.
The judge has let us continue.
You really want to look
for the sim card?
It's worth a shot.
Because, you see, Jeanne Dewaere
was in a perfect position
to search through my parka.
I don't like people going through
my things without asking.
-So, what do we do?
-What do we do...
Let's look through her file...
her judicial file.
Because going through a cop's things
is the work of a pro.
An innocent person wouldn't do that.
It's clear, Jeanne Dewaere sent
the little Zorros there.
Do you understand me?
I was afraid you'd be closed.
I would like some prickly flowers.
Flowers like whips.
-Are you seeing him?
-Yes.
I don't know how you do it.
With his boorish charm,
he's so sexy!
ENTZHEIM TOWN HALL
So?
I'm gonna break that Chalard's jaw
and then denounce him.
-And Manon?
-And you?
Do you realize what you did?
I helped a girl in need.
And you stole from a cop.
Do you know the consequences?
For a girl who is exploiting you.
Like for all of them who abuse you.
You've never said that before.
You think that?
I think that Manon
should tell the police.
It wouldn't hurt her
to tell the truth.
-And you stay out of it.
-It's a big risk.
She needs to take responsibility.
It was her own fault.
Her life will be finished!
We're all confused at 20!
She's an adult.
She must be responsible.
Responsible?
Do you realize what you're saying?
Complicity to murder,
that's ten years.
And you don't just lose freedom.
It's your dignity too!
Your joy for life.
You always speak about that.
And then there's the boredom.
Boredom which gnaws away at you.
That's what prison means.
Can you imagine her inside?
No. I can't.
And you?
Thanks to you, I know what to do.
Patrick, it's Alain.
I need some confidential info
on someone I know.
Jeanne Dewaere.
NO TO THE GOLF COURSE
Yeah.
Are you sure it's not
another Jeanne Dewaere?
Are you sure?
Goddamnit!
Mr. Chalard!
It's me, it's Véronique.
Mr. Chalard?
I can't believe it.
Léonard was really nice.
Always a nice thing to say, helpful,
all of them, Julien, Raoul, Frédéric.
And the little florist. Manon.
They love having a laugh, a drink.
They did well in their village
with the shop.
-There's things happening.
-Yeah.
Dangerous terrorists, what a joke.
It creates links. Shops are good.
Do you know Jeanne Dewaere?
Reserved, discrete, but nice.
She looks after troubled kids.
She finds them work, a place to stay.
Ah, I know the story.
Ms. I-know-how-to-do-things-best.
OK, I'll prepare you a nice lunch.
It will rejuvenate you.
-Thank you!
-Captain!
Oh, yeah?
You were right.
I know, I'm always right.
It's my job.
Jeanne Dewaere, formerly Ferrari,
married Marco Ferrari
20 years ago, a real scoundrel.
She was busted robbing a post office.
One cop died, Marco, too.
Sentenced to 12 years,
released after eight.
Look.
Trial...
Ah, yes, Dewaere,
that's why we missed it.
"Robbery reaches its end."
Well done! Let me buy you lunch.
He's completely crazy.
You know where your gloves were?
In the greenhouse!
Even a few seeds
can stuff everything up!
What do I tell the lab?
Due to someone who can't read,
we kill the wolves?
Do you realize?
You again.
You're beautiful angry.
But less than in photos.
Let's go.
After you, dear friend.
Sir.
What are you hoping for?
A signed confession?
"I, Jeanne Dewaere,
am guilty of a murder."
That would do nicely.
You're such a cop.
You don't want people to live.
Only an ex-con would say clichés
like that.
All the cops I've met want one thing:
us to mess up again.
Well, not untrue.
But as Super Didier said:
"Crooks are like cops--
some are good."
And I believe what I see.
Yet, you're here.
You know my file,
so, you judge me as guilty.
Whoa, your case
isn't the case of the century.
Calm down.
So, tell me, calmly, nicely,
that you stole a sim card,
and we'll make a deal.
-A stolen sim card?
-Yeah.
A sim card.
Do you have proof?
Not on me, but I'll find it.
When you find it,
come back to see me. OK?
You really are a pig!
I adore girls like you,
but you need to stop screwing around.
Let me remind you
that we have two deaths.
Including a kid.
The second has been arrested
and the third is on the run.
So, help me.
They're disadvantaged,
not terrorists. They'll do time!
If you want to help them,
you have to speak.
You need to speak now.
Do you understand?
Sorry, I have a call.
-What Brière?
-Captain
Enunciate, I don't understand.
He's dead.
OK, I'm coming.
What is that?
No to the golf course!
Down with exploitation
in the U.A.E.!
Comrades.
Captain, come quick.
-Hi, losers.
-Hello, Captain.
Well, well, well.
Chalard doesn't get bored.
A pool.
He brought that back
from the Caymans.
What's that?
What is it?
-Where's the cadaver?
-Upstairs.
Is that from the art show?
Looks like Matthew Barney.
Go on, he won't eat you.
Come on!
Well...
Nice eclipse.
Hello, honey.
What's that?
Manon, artisanal florist.
Chalard...
What's this?
Mushrooms.
Wow.
Wait for me.
-Captain.
-I'm here.
Stop doing that. It annoys me.
You look like you were
the teacher's pet.
The world doesn't belong
to those with veto power,
-but to those who disobey.
-That's libertarian,
-for a cop.
-A lady cop.
Got to break rules. What is it?
The murder witness is here.
Why didn't you say?
Oh, my God!
Is he really dead?
Very observant. Who are you?
His lady.
What does that mean in local lingo?
-I kept his house in order.
-That doesn't mean anything.
-Did you find him like that?
-Yes.
I tried to call, but nothing.
Nothing.
That's because he was dead.
He was never away from his phone.
The killer must have it.
The killer?
Who spoke of a murder?
It's funny you speak like that.
His success caused jealousy.
And the garters and fishnets,
was that routine
or just for big occasions?
It never happened.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have stayed.
I have something of interest.
What?
We're in a full red moon.
You want my stylist's number?
The red moon is the night
of the big reveal.
The truth exposed.
Exactly. The red moon is at Easter.
Three bodies in 24 hours.
You talk about the truth.
Captain?
What is it?
Look what I found
on the social networks.
The pink bunny phone.
It's Manon Bechet's phone,
the florist.
Doesn't it seem like a coincidence?
Absolutely. So, first link:
the flowers.
Because the flowers were bought
in Manon's shop.
You know what?
She's part of the cards club.
I loved playing cards
when I was young.
I'll leave you then.
Goodbye, ma'am.
-I'm going to clean up .
-No, this is a crime scene.
Don't touch anything.
Yes, Captain?
Oscar, it's Marleau.
What did you find?
At first glance, it looked like
an erotic game gone bad
or suicide with a macabre scene,
but given the skin's texture,
it looks more like poisoning.
Really?
Maybe cyanide,
but if there's atropine action,
it's probably digitalis.
And so?
The signs are contradictory.
Yes, and so?
I need to ask another colleague.
Wait, I know someone.
Ah, yes. It's the Snowden of poisons.
The Ricky Gervais
of intestinal lamella.
-Great.
-I'll call him.
Pool...
Pool, pool,
who is the most beautiful cop?
Not me.
CRIMINAL RECORD MANON BECHET.
Are you Manon Bechet ?
National Police,
Captain Marleau.
Bechet... aren't you from Australia?
From Sydney? No?
I've got a frog catcher.
Just wait five minutes.
It's ringing.
No.
I read your file.
You stole bottles of alcohol.
We've all done that. It's no biggie.
But I did notice one thing.
You sold drugs to someone
from the police drug brigade.
And the court gave you
mitigating circumstances
for your stupidity?
Did you come to mock me?
We're not well paid.
We need to laugh.
Otherwise, I also saw
Ms. Dewaere is your reference.
Does she know
about your pink bunny phone?
Speaking of pink,
did someone come
to buy some roses this morning?
Who?
Red roses?
23, I counted them.
Émilie Guingamp, the hairdresser.
-Chalard's mistress?
-Mistress?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
All I can say is that Émilie
is a nice girl.
Nice isn't a job.
Brière, it's Marleau.
Can you search
for a nice hairdresser,
Émilie Guingamp?
Like the train station.
In exchange, I'll bring you
a nice florist.
Yeah.
We'll put her in custody.
Carpentier!
Can you put the girl in custody,
please?
-Do you have the T.V. programs?
-No, Captain.
-What are you doing?
-I was waiting for you.
Come and look. The newspaper
published a photo of Chalard.
I got you a copy.
Where did they get that,
the scavengers?
I don't know. I called,
but there was no response.
Look at this.
I went through Chalard's accounts.
Look what I found.
I don't understand. What is it?
Michel Chalard bet
on high-risk loans.
Yeah...
Look, he also bet on the conditions
of a partnership,
particularly on Ms. Dewaere's
animal park.
He was desperate for money.
Strange to kill a desperate man.
-Usually, it's the opposite.
-True.
He was also the owner
of Manon Bechet's florist.
He wanted to turn it into
a golf shop.
He even took her to court
to expel her.
I don't think Manon Bechet
liked Monsieur Chalard,
in my opinion.
Good work, my boy.
Go and get yourself a reward.
-Mr. Gabriel?
-Yes, I'm here.
Look what I found out the front.
Do you know much about mushrooms?
Me? Well, without boasting,
I'm the king of mushrooms.
Mushrooms are easy.
There are only two categories:
basidiomycetes and ascomycetes.
Did you give any to Michel Chalard,
by chance?
Yes, yesterday. Why?
Do you know how many?
Of course, there are some here.
Go for it. They're yesterday's.
Smell that.
Ah, gross.
I don't like mushrooms.
I prefer music.
I'm going to put something together
for fans of "moderato cantabile."
I'm have a pass
to Barbès National Orchestra,
but it's not working.
And I'm never wrong.
Why do you ask?
Because Michel Chalard
didn't die by hanging.
Oh?
Are you sure?
On my mother's life...
who is dead.
Hello!
Guess why I'm here.
-No idea.
-At least guess.
You have to play to win.
-Come on!
-I don't want to guess.
Oh, come on!
I'm not in a joking mood today. OK?
You're no fun.
Look at this.
I know your methods.
You want me to react? It won't work.
Well, no reaction is a reaction.
My methods aren't so stupid,
you know.
Do you want my real opinion?
I didn't like him.
I won't pretend to be sad.
-Not even a little tear?
-No.
He didn't even deserve hate.
You think my sadness...
What you said was beautiful. Poetic.
Can I help you to feed them?
No? I'll wait, then.
We'll talk after.
Your little protégée is in custody.
Did you know about Chalard?
He was going to throw Manon
out of her shop.
-He was a bastard.
-There we go.
Finally, a swear word.
You keep animal fur.
Manon is a brave girl.
I helped her get on her feet.
But she's still fragile.
Chalard would have finished her.
So, to save her,
you're prepared to steal sim cards?
That's more than dedication.
That's devotion.
It would have sent her over the edge.
I wanted to help.
How much?
To the point of killing Chalard?
Because...
you'll say it's a coincidence,
but just before dying, he told me:
"I have some revelations
about Ms. Dewaere."
Funny, no?
If you think I'm guilty,
just lock me up.
-Do you have a lawyer?
-Yes.
But he's not much fun.
I'll say nothing.
Like most of them.
Sorry, I have a call. Who's calling?
Yeah?
OK?
OK, cool.
See you soon.
Sorry, I have to go,
because your protégée
is less stubborn than you.
She's decided to speak. Great, right?
I swear, Manon isn't involved
in his death.
I swear.
We'll see... Inshallah.
I have a plus in my job:
I come across as so stupid
that people feel sorry for me,
they end up accusing each other.
Cool, right? Well, see you soon.
You know you're lucky
to be in custody with me?
One: I have no man,
two: I have no woman or children
and I don't have gastro.
So, I have all the time in the world.
I'm listening.
Why were you at Chalard's
the other night?
We wanted to protest his golf course.
We went with a banner.
Dressed as Zorro.
-We thought it was funny.
-Yeah.
Except someone was waiting
when you arrived.
There was a shot.
Yes, I know, from the guard,
with Chalard's Mauser,
which he'd lent him. OK, then?
Then, I ran off.
I went to Jeanne and she helped me.
And that's all.
That's all I know.
I hope for your case
that Chalard's mistress
didn't see you at his house.
-Why?
-Why? Because, one:
around his body was a bouquet
from your florist.
OK?
Two: you have a motive,
because your friend's dead.
And three: you have
a criminal record, my girl.
So, either you killed him,
or you have a very good alibi.
See what I'm saying?
Well?
-Is Chalard's mistress there?
-No.
I don't know why, at this time.
Her car's there.
We might find something.
Ah, yeah.
You're right! You're not so stupid.
Thanks.
Powerful car.
Let's have a look, then...
If I call Chalard, what will happen?
Voila...
There we go.
Is that Chalard's phone?
Yeah. It's like a frog Kama Sutra.
-Is it her?
-Yeah.
A crime of passion, then?
What's wrong? You seem upset.
A bit, yeah.
Murderers are like that.
Crimes are often completely stupid,
stupid phones...
I'll say this: murderers are often
are stupider than you think.
Hello!
Ms. Guingamp!
-My God, it's ugly.
-Yeah.
-Shall we go up?
Ms. Guingamp?
Remorse? Suicide?
No, she's asleep.
Go and make her a coffee.
Stop looking!
Make a strong coffee,
black with salt, so she vomits.
What's this? What a joke.
Not very practical.
Oh... earrings.
Chalard didn't want those on.
Ali Baba's cave.
Strange hairbrush.
Ah! Bunny ears.
Come on, honey.
Up you get!
Ms. Boulier, it's nice to see you.
Thanks for coming. Here.
See you soon?
Hello, ladies. How are you?
Everything going well?
Have a good day.
Thanks.
Hello.
What's this?
Can I count on you?
-Thanks, Mr. Mayor.
-Thanks, goodbye.
Goodbye.
Why aren't you picking up?
I followed you yesterday.
Hello, ma'am.
How are you? Have a good day.
I saw you go to his house.
-Do you think I killed him?
-You tell me.
-Hello, Mr. Mayor.
-Hello, ma'am.
-I'm awaiting your answer.
-Come to my office.
Goodbye.
You hated him for the golf course.
You go to his house, soon after
he's dead.
What should I think?
Do you think I killed him?
You never answer my questions.
Because you don't want to know.
-You don't like women with no past.
-You're wrong.
I searched your past
and wasn't disappointed.
Jeanne Ferrari. 12 years.
Eight.
An ex-inmate.
You don't hesitate
to throw away anyone with history.
If you want to turn me in,
don't worry, they already know.
Why didn't you say?
To avoid a reaction.
It looks like you don't know me.
Same for me.
I don't recognize you.
Your father and I crossed you off.
You're no longer our girl.
Who's this man in a suit
shaking people's hands?
Distributing flyers
to win the election?
I don't know him.
Come on, come on!
It was fun.
He read that strangling
helps the orgasm.
So, he wanted to try.
Sex makes you lose your head,
you know?
Well, you've lost your head
to the point of forgetting
Chalard's telephone.
We filmed each other.
I didn't want the sex-tape
to be seen.
I know some use that to get famous,
but I don't need that.
-The hairdressing's going well.
-I can see that.
So, he died before your eyes.
Yes.
I did the knot,
tightened it a bit,
then, he started coughing
and feeling unwell. So, I undid it.
But it got worse and worse. I tried
to undo the rope,
but it was strangling him.
I swear that's the truth.
I'd never hurt him.
But I was so scared...
I left straight away
and I took two pills.
I told myself to sleep on it.
I was going to come and see you.
I swear...
I was so scared.
I understand.
There's something not right
there, in your video,
which is short but trashy.
The casting is really good,
but the story's dated,
it's basic. Regarding the timing,
you need a new script, look...
He has no bottoms.
-Bottoms?
-Yeah,
that you put on the bottom
or the top, depending who you are.
Look, in this newspaper.
Far from suggesting
the media lies to us...
Look here, he's wearing bottoms
and lipstick.
While in the film, he isn't.
How is that?
Ask Jeanne Dewaere.
Why? Is she a funeral director?
She killed him.
When I arrived, Michel was so happy,
he said he had her.
That she had no choice but to accept.
-Calm down, ma'am!
-You're kidding!
I demand to see Captain Marleau.
I have a confession.
OK, guys, I'll take care of this.
How can I help you?
I can't let an innocent person
be accused.
I killed Michel Chalard.
The love of my life.
OK, I'm not a shrink. Sit down.
This will save you 50 euros.
I'm listening. What is it?
I'd had enough
of his debauched ways.
So, I poisoned his tea.
A dose strong enough for him to fall
asleep in her arms, rather than...
-Well, you understand.
-No.
I didn't want him to die.
I couldn't have known
it was dangerous.
Lord...
OK, Brière, you can let
Manon Bechet go.
-And the police squad?
-We don't care.
They won't care about a banner.
We don't put our noses
in their business.
And I like Zorro.
So, go and do the deed
my little munchkin.
As for you...
Into custody.
Rest and relaxation.
For a long time.
I was maybe the only one,
but I loved Michel Chalard.
How can I tell him now?
Poison. My god, what a joke.
I would have given him more
for what he did.
It brings us back
to Ms. Dewaere, then.
What are you doing?
Get out of here!
Ah... sorry.
Hello, Léopold?
Yeah, it's me. Yeah.
OK, I'm on my way.
Yes, I'm alone.
See you soon?
Do you understand what I felt?
Put yourself in my place.
I was with someone with a past
I had no idea about.
Let me digest it a little.
So?
This election is important.
I'll be frank:
in school, people called me
"the mayor," and I liked it.
I thought you were in custody.
I was.
With the funny policewoman.
I'm not sure if she's an idiot
or a real bitch.
Maybe she's really nice.
She's the first of her kind.
Well, she believed me.
I'm so relieved,
you wouldn't believe it.
She was strange but cool
at the same time.
Yeah, she's really strange. I agree.
-Do you want a coffee?
-Yes, please.
Jeanne, I want to warn you:
for Chalard's murder,
you're the prime suspect.
I'm afraid, Jeanne.
For you, this time.
Oscar! Here's Léopold.
Léopold, this is Oscar.
Alias: Nonos.
He doesn't seem like much now,
but as soon as he gets cold meat,
he comes to life.
And this is Léopold.
Alias: Popol,
the God of guts,
the Eric Clapton of intestines,
great lover of toxicology,
-among other things...
-Thank you, my friend.
My friends' friends are my friends.
And if they're in forensics,
obviously,
that's even better.
Léopold,
I'm sorry to make you work
secretly like this.
Not at all!
It reminds me of my student years,
when we stole hands from cadavers
to slide them in girls' pockets.
We filled intestines with water
and put them above the kitchen door.
It got my mom every time.
Intestines are always good.
What is this bucket of guts?
That's Chalard. Léopold! Here he is!
It reminds me of a famous
tripe recipe,
Well prepared tripe
is a sure way to heaven.
It's rare. Very rare, this.
And like everything rare,
it demands time
and infinite delicacy.
So, we'll take our time.
I'll leave you, then, boys,
with intestinal joys.
I have to work.
Come back quick, we'll miss you.
-The two of us.
-The three of us.
-Captain?
-I'm here.
-I have the lab results.
-Ah, great.
They worked hard.
I put pressure on them.
Bravo, my dear. Well done.
So, Chalard's photo was taken
with a Leica from 1956
with double viewfinders.
It's an incredible camera.
It'll catch a drop of dew.
OK.
We know it was developed at home.
That's good.
-And you?
-I'm working, if you can't see.
Because the murderer
is not here at the moment.
But the murderer always comes back
to the crime scene.
That's why I'm waiting.
Did you see? This book's good.
He wasn't lying, the guard.
His mushrooms were indeed edible.
Are you staying?
I told you, I'm waiting.
And I don't like threesomes,
so you can leave.
-Goodbye, Captain.
-Bye, honey.
So, inocybes...
What's that?
So, did someone lose her earring?
I came to see Chalard yesterday.
For good reason.
I heard about Manon's eviction.
I came to plead.
And?
And when I arrived, he was dead.
Chalard?
What time was it?
-2:15.
-Ah, yes.
The famous pocket watch.
It's a good watch.
On another note,
do you know someone
with a photo lab at home?
Someone who does portraits
a bit... fancy.
Why?
It's not for me. I prefer videos.
No, there's a local photographer
who immortalized Chalard
with a Leica.
So, I'd like to see him
to discuss antiques.
Do you know anyone?
I don't know. Not me, anyway.
OK. You can go, then.
Is it a trap?
You're completely paranoid!
I'll keep the earring,
you can go home.
Do you want to sleep with me?
I snore.
Do you mind?
Goodnight.
They're beautiful, right?
I need to speak to you.
Why?
The cop mentioned a Leica that
was used to take a photo of the body.
I didn't say, but I know who has one.
Why?
For Arthur.
What?
When he was killed
in an apparent hunting accident,
we were together, him and me,
in the clearing,
on Chalard's land.
Go and do your business elsewhere!
Arthur...
Arthur!
The police opened an investigation,
but no one found the killer.
The case was filed away.
Why say nothing?
It was my revenge.
I never saw his face.
I never saw who fired.
But I swore, one day I'd know.
Why now?
All I knew was that he was killed
by a Mauser 43.
When the police spoke, I understood.
Don't move!
-What's going on?
-You're involved, too.
You're the key piece.
You still don't know
who killed Chalard?
This piece that will
let you heal morbillivirus?
Your Calabar bean.
You know who killed Chalard? You.
No one will believe it.
-Oh, yes!
-I don't have a motive.
You wanted to heal...
-You wanted revenge
-Let me go!
for your protégés Léonard and Manon!
Everyone knows your penchant
for delinquents.
And you've lost this one.
You know I've always tried
to help you.
If you'd spoken about Arthur earlier,
I would have done what I could.
You accepted the police's version.
No questions asked.
Arthur trusted you,
and you left him hanging.
Like all the others.
Let me go!
We're here, dear.
Did you see the newspaper?
They put a nice suit on Chalard.
"Shocking pants
for a fashionable man."
Well, there's the epitaph...
1987. Léopold Salaun.
The forensic scientist
from the Angoulême murders.
Am I right?
-Wait, no way.
-You've had some night. Tell us.
So, first point:
Michel Chalard
died between 12:30 and 1:00 p.m.
-Are you sure?
-100%
More precisely, I bet 12:50
and Oscar...
12:42, 12:43, maximum.
Second point: the weapon
-was an African bean.
-No?
-Physostigma.
-Yeah?
A plant used for exorcism rituals.
It has incredible
medicinal capacities,
but, as always,
it has a double effect.
It can heal or... kill.
Lethal dose: 0.2 milligrams.
Do you realize?
By grinding it, it's very easy
to hide in food
or to inject in a mushroom.
Ah...
And who has a plantation?
Plantations for medical research?
And who has an off-limit greenhouse?
Well, my dear?
The key is in the ignition.
Nothing strange.
-We didn't find Ms. Dewaere's truck.
-Damn.
I'll call Brière.
Thanks.
Yeah, it's me.
Can you send out a search
for Ms. Dewaere?
And give her truck's license plate.
Thanks.
-Hello.
-Are you OK?
-Yes.
You're wrong if you suspect her.
She's a good person.
She saved my life.
Did she say something?
No, I didn't see her.
I heard her car start,
but at 5:00 a.m., I'm in bed.
Captain!
I'm here!
I found the weapon.
Looks like mussels.
No, I don't think so.
Ah, OK.
Was she working on bean medication?
Is that how Michel died?
Can I have a look around, sir?
-Of course.
-After you.
-Yes.
-OK.
I have something for you. Come here.
I've always been loyal to her.
I'd give her my life.
I trust you.
You're not going to arrest me.
No, I'm not the type.
What did I do with it?
There it is.
Michel wanted me to testify.
About what?
That I found these in her bins.
Just before they were emptied.
Will that get me into trouble?
I don't know.
Michel is a good guy.
We grew up together.
It's a real shame.
Oh, Gaby...
you know what my mom said?
She said: "the best liars are those
who know how to shut up."
Hi, guys. It's not warm, eh?
I'm off to the dump.
It's only open today.
-No, you can't leave.
-Really?
It's OK. We've searched it.
-Go on.
-Thanks, guys.
-Goodbye.
-You coming?
-How are you?
-Good.
Do you believe Jeanne
could have killed him?
No.
You don't think so or you know so?
Did she speak about her past?
-Yeah.
-Ah, yeah?
Did she speak about prison, her ex,
the robberies, all of it?
Jeanne never lied to me.
-I knew it all along.
-Be careful.
Because a false testimony can
not only send a President tumbling,
but a mayor, too.
-So, are you sure?
-Yes.
You know the day he was killed,
Jeanne was at his house?
She left an earring.
I know.
I followed her.
-What time was it?
-Just past 2:00 p.m.
-But I really thought Jeanne...
-It's OK, you've cleared her.
Chalard was already dead at 2:00 p.m.
If she killed him,
I don't know why
she would have come back.
Unless she's sly.
-No.
Why are you here?
I wanted to know something:
your guard... what's his name...
Gabriel,
does he have a Leica?
-You know, to take photos.
-Yes.
There we go.
Thank you, Mr. Alain.
Good luck!
Don't move.
Don't move!
Where are you taking me?
What is it?
He said he was off to the dump.
And, as the truck had been checked...
He's not there. We don't know
where he is.
OK. What else?
We found Ms. Dewaere's car hidden
in the wood,
with her purse, her bank card,
her driving license.
It doesn't seem
like she left voluntarily.
Go and check the guard's lodge.
Then, meet me there.
What does he want?
Why did you come back?
We'll find her. Don't worry.
Stop following me. It annoys me.
You're very clingy.
-Captain! Captain!
-What is it?
-Come and see.
-What?
Didn't you understand?
This is where she must have been.
What's that?
Your girlfriend said she'd
never collaborate with cops.
She left us this.
But she didn't say the destination.
-Captain!
-Yeah?
-Here's the Leica.
-Yeah.
I found it here.
Look, it's a real photo lab.
OK, I don't understand.
OK, let's go back to the start.
So, Gabriel, the guard,
he distorted Chalard's body
with pants, red lipstick,
all sorts of things.
He takes a photo.
He sends it to the newspaper.
Do you know your electorates?
-Why would he do that?
-I don't know.
It's even stranger to distort him
knowing Chalard was traditional.
He wanted women to wear dresses,
men to be men.
He was very homophobic.
And Gabriel and Arthur,
did they know each other?
They were always together
before he died.
-How did he die?
-Hunting accident.
-Where?
-On Chalard's property.
In the clearing.
That seems suspicious.
Let's go. Quickly!
Hurry up!
-Where are we going?
-Keep going!
Stop! You're hurting me.
Let me go!
I admit to killing Michel Chalard,
who was going to denounce me.
Unable to live with my act,
I decided to kill myself
in the same way I killed him.
Stay there.
I admit to killing Michel Chalard
who was going to denounce me
Unable to live with my act,
I decided to kill myself
in the same way I killed him.
My only regret
is that no one will know
what he did to Arthur.
You're right, Gabriel.
Everyone should know.
Don't kill me.
Don't move!
OK, Captain?
Thanks, Brière.
Let me go!
Let me go, pigs!
Are you writing memoirs?
No, I'm writing
Captain Marleau's lessons.
-You idiot.
-Can you sign it for me?
Do you want a selfie, too?
And don't forget,
first lesson: disobedience.
It's compulsory.
I'm touched, Captain.
Well, what did you think?
I do have a heart.
I need to say something.
Listen well, I won't repeat it.
One: I love you totally,
past, present and future.
Two: I have a childhood friend
who's a great lawyer.
Your defense'll be strong.
Three: I love being mayor,
but I love you more.
Jeanne,
I have the honor of not asking you.
Let's not get married.
But I want to.
The tripe is served.
Thank you.
Tripe! Tripe!
She's promising, the little girl.
Yes, I'm proud of my new recruit.
Shame that Ms. Dewaere has her.
Well, as you know,
I need a new guard for the park.
Manon applied.
She was very convincing
in the interview.
Surprised?
I hope you'll keep up
your activities.
And stop putting banners in trees.
Do graffiti.
It's quicker and safer.
As a souvenir
of an unforgettable autopsy,
as precise as you, dear friend and
delicious like you, my dear.
To the red moon,
to all the gingers
and the Zorros of the world.
And to the law.
Subtitling: Hiventy