BETWEEN WINDS AND TIDES
Alex.
Can you take some pictures?
I think there are
strangulation marks.
OK? Thanks.
Gwen is dead.
- What?
- Yeah.
The police have summoned me
for 6pm.
- Why?
- I don't know.
They'll want to know
about her internship.
She left with Salmon last night.
You saw her too.
I can't get it out of my mind.
You don't think he could have...
A 17-year-old girl...
Nobody would do that.
And yet somebody did.
Not him.
Then why did they leave together?
I don't know!
What do you know about him?
Where's he from?
Where does all his money come from?
He earned it.
You're under his spell.
You're useless when he's around.
I'll go and talk to him!
Do you think he'll tell you
if he killed Gwen?
Tarek!
What's up? Wait.
- What's the matter?
- Yann's sister Gwen is dead.
Was it an accident?
No. My dad's just told me
she was murdered.
It'll be all right.
Look at me. It'll be OK.
You come in on Sundays?
In the hope of running into you.
You're as attractive as ever.
One day, my grandma said to me:
"You're as beautiful as sin."
That would suit you.
Is that a compliment?
Who knows?
You'll have to ask my grandma.
You certainly seemed
to charm Gwen.
Not really. I drove her home,
but I didn't even get a kiss.
"Goodbye, see you on Monday."
Youngsters nowadays...
- You didn't go back to your place?
- No.
That's a good thing,
because they've just found her body.
No. That can't be true.
- What happened?
- She was killed.
Let me be frank.
I don't want to do the cops' job,
but Gwen gave Josephine
the bill of sale to sign.
So?
They argued.
Josephine was furious with Gwen.
I've never liked Josephine.
She's got a crazy side to her.
And you think she killed Christian?
He sold us a plot,
and he was killed shortly after.
Gwen and Josephine argued,
and then Gwen is killed...
That woman is evil, Nadia.
She leaves death in her wake.
You may be right.
You didn't stay with Gwen?
I swear on what I hold dearest:
my mother.
Anyway, I've always preferred
mature women.
It's like with seasons,
I prefer summer to spring.
Go away.
Go away. I want to be alone.
Let me sit in a corner.
I promise I won't talk.
Someone will have to talk to Yann
when he comes back.
Ferdinand can give you something
to help you sleep.
I don't want to sleep.
I want to think about Gwen.
And...
go to the boathouse.
Tell Richard we're closing shop.
Can I go and see Cecile?
She doesn't want to see anyone.
Not even you?
There must be people
who are closer to her than I am.
I doubt it.
Calm down.
Take this, it will do you good.
All I did was go to town for an hour!
Jo... please.
No. Stop it! No!
Hello.
It was open, so I let myself in.
I've brought you something.
This.
That's your scarf.
Don't you want to know
where I found it?
I found it on the rocks,
on Gwen Prigent's body.
Where were you this morning?
She was here, with me.
- Really?
- We've been together all morning.
Right...
That's strange,
because someone saw you
driving in town this morning.
And I touched your engine.
It's still warm.
So I think you're lying.
You're both lying.
No?
It's 11.05am. You are in police
custody in connection with the murder
of Gwen Prigent.
Please follow me.
Cecile Prigent.
We've asked to see you
but you'll have to come back later.
Thank you.
Come in.
It's cold in here.
Cup of tea?
One like you have,
with malt whisky.
There... Lots of whisky.
We don't need any tea.
There you are.
Take it!
Cheers.
I'll fetch Mr Quemener.
Mr Quemener,
can you come in here, please?
Hello.
Come in, please.
You already know each other,
don't you?
- Yes.
- Of course.
So then, Mr Quemener,
Mrs de Kersaint-Gilly signed
a sales agreement with your company.
Yesterday afternoon.
And your niece Gwen
recorded the signature.
That's correct.
- Were you angry with her?
- Why would I be? I wanted to sell.
You told me that you wanted
to die on your land.
- Have you changed your mind?
- Yes.
The bailiffs changed my mind.
"The bailiffs"... Right.
Mr Quemener, however, says
that you had a very violent argument
with Gwen.
Is that true?
It's none of your business.
None of my business?
When there are two bodies,
everything is my business.
Why did you tell Gwen
that she was indebted to you?
It's just a phrase!
That's great. Thanks, ma'am.
Mr Quemener, I'll see you out.
Let's go.
I'll be back in a tick.
I'll do the washing-up.
Come on then, Mr Quemener.
Keep an eye on Kersaint-Gilly.
Wait, Mr Quemener!
Stay there, I'll be right back.
Alex.
I need you to compare the DNA
on this glass
with the DNA found on the victim.
That'll take 10 days.
No. I need it tomorrow.
Otherwise I'll shoot you
with a gun without a serial number.
I'm not the human-resources
manager.
Why would I have to manage
human resources?
I'm fed up with it.
Mr Quemener,
why did you hire your niece?
She'd always wanted
to be an architect.
She dreamt of working with us.
That's very nice of you.
But it's not innocent,
seeing that you wanted to buy
your sister's boathouse.
So what?
Ill-intentioned people might say:
"He hired the daughter
"to influence the mother."
See?
- I don't see, no.
- Neither do I.
I'm still searching.
I do research, like Pasteur.
- Goodbye, Mr Quemener.
- Goodbye.
Why is she in police custody?
Why Gwen? What had she done?
I don't know.
But my grandma's being held
for questioning.
It's OK, stay.
It makes no sense.
What are you doing?
They're my grandma's things!
Not any more.
Come on, gentlemen, let's go.
- Are you sure?
- 99% sure.
99%? Is that your answer?
It's tepid!
You can't be loved by everyone.
I chose to be loved by some
and hated by others.
- Sure or not?
- Sure.
Good. I like you.
You're welcome!
Are you coping?
Could my grandma
have killed her husband and Gwen?
It's crazy!
I can't believe it.
My grandpa, maybe,
but not Gwen.
She mentioned her
at every opportunity, comparing us.
I was always less brilliant,
less blond, less everything.
Gwen was her dream granddaughter.
Her hair always looked nice,
she was always so clever...
Listen...
Yesterday, I went to the office.
I heard Nadia Quemener
and Vincent Salmon
talking about Gwen.
She asked him if he'd left with her.
"Left"?
As in gone home together?
Maybe. He denied it
but she didn't seem to believe him.
And then they...
- Well...
- Spit it out!
They made love.
You really don't want to eat?
It's good, it's cheese.
Right.
Shall we stop messing around now?
I'll recap.
First of all, your husband
was found on your land,
murdered with a hunting rifle.
That's unfortunate for you
because you don't have an alibi
but you do have a very good motive.
Your husband was ruining you.
Shall I go on?
Gwen Prigent is then found murdered.
It so happens
that you were overheard
having a violent argument with her.
And your scarf was found
on her body.
That's not great.
You say you have an alibi,
that you were with your doctor,
Dr Lebovitz.
Unfortunately, I have a witness
who says you weren't.
You were seen driving
in your car at that time.
That's not great either.
I didn't tell you...
I called your bank.
Apparently you opened
an account for Gwen.
How come? That's odd.
You've been putting money in it
for 16 years.
That's a long time.
Especially when you're broke.
No?
So why have you hidden
the fact you're Gwen's grandma?
Does Cecile know that Gwen
isn't her daughter?
She won't like it when you tell her.
That's some family secret!
Still not hungry?
Don't you want to finish
your sandwich?
- It'll help, you'll see.
- If you say so.
That's just how you were
at the clinic.
You thought I couldn't heal you.
And yet I got
your smile back, didn't I?
- That was a thousand years ago.
- No! 17 years ago.
Right. You should sleep now.
I'll take my leave.
- Is my mum OK?
- Yes. She should sleep.
I hate this waiting.
Let the cops do their job.
Do you remember,
when Gwen was born,
Cecile was having
a nervous breakdown...
Yes, I remember.
You were the opposite.
You were incredibly happy.
That was the happiest time
in my life.
And the most horrible.
Within a year,
I'd lived my life on fast-forward.
I met Solene, she got pregnant,
and she died...
After that, all I wanted
was to get away,
to stay out at sea.
"The eternal widower",
as Cecile called you.
That sounds like a criticism.
No, you were perfect.
You went to see her,
brought flowers...
but did you ever wonder
why she had a breakdown?
Just after you met Solene.
We need to know what happened.
They've arrested Josephine.
What does that mean?
Did she do it?
Maybe not.
Dammit...
How long are we going to
just sit and wait?
- Don't you want to do something?
- I want to see Gwen, and hug her.
Have you got a solution?
I thought you might be hungry.
I should get back.
Etienne will be wondering where I am.
Tell him you were
at an inauguration.
Don't worry about me,
I know how to lie.
Any news about the investigation?
Are you worried?
No, but I find Josephine scary.
So scornful and self-assured.
You should know.
Your family has suffered
because of them.
Why are you bringing up my family?
How do you know?
You told me.
That my mother worked for them?
I never did.
Etienne must have told me, then.
Are you sure you've not
enquired about me?
Power is making you paranoid.
Maybe.
My mother worked
for that woman for 10 years.
- You lived on their estate?
- Yes.
I lived in the house in the clearing
where Ingrid lives now.
Renan was a little prince
and I was the caretakers' daughter.
I'll never forgive her.
- Did they treat you badly?
- Not even.
They never shouted at me.
They even gave me dolls
for Christmas, with neat blond hair.
They were condescending,
the way masters are
with their servants.
Poor you...
I don't want to be pitied,
I want to be respected.
Hello?
Wait a second.
Yes, it's working.
Josephine de Kersaint-Gilly
is in police custody.
OK.
Where were you?
I've been waiting for 3 hours!
I was at the prefecture.
The commission
has approved the blueprint.
- We're going to have our marina.
- Wonderful.
Is that it?
I thought you were going to
leap for joy!
I was so impatient to tell you!
I am delighted, really.
We've got to call Salmon.
I can't reach him.
Have you seen him?
No. Why would I have?
What's up, Nadia?
Still nothing to say?
I've got better things to do.
I'm wasting my time.
You can go home.
Scram!
Just like that?
Yeah, just like that.
I forgot to tell you...
Prepare an overnight bag.
If ever you're remanded in custody,
you'll be needing mittens,
thermals,
jumpers - not cashmere.
Things get pinched in jail,
and it's cold.
I've not had heating at home
for a long time.
The temperature may be the same,
but the atmosphere isn't!
There's the bars on the windows
and the smell...
Since you've got some free time,
sort out your family secrets.
It won't do you any harm.
Goodbye, Mrs Kersaint-Gilly.
"De Kersaint-Gilly"...
Tarek!
They've released you?
They're not very friendly.
They're waiting for me
to be charged with both murders.
I've been to my house.
It looks odd without furniture.
The bailiffs took everything.
Sorry, I couldn't stop them.
I can live without furniture.
Right...
Would you like some tea?
Sure.
Thanks.
I've not killed anybody.
I believe you.
I've not known you very long,
but I know you couldn't do
such a thing.
I feel like giving you a hug.
- What's holding me back?
- Nothing, really.
The bailiffs I saw when I was younger
didn't give me any hugs.
Neither did my mother.
I'm not sure what that was,
but I feel I'm interrupting.
I'm teaching the signs of affection.
You sure pick your moments!
I'm afraid I have
to talk to you, Renan.
And you're not going
to like this moment.
Lebovitz lives here.
Dr Lebovitz
General Practitioner
Anybody home?
This isn't a state-run hospital!
Yes?
- Hello.
I'd like to see Dr Lebovitz.
I'm sorry,
he's out seeing patients.
I'm Captain Marleau.
I'd like to see the clinic archives.
Without the doctor's permission,
I don't think I can...
- This his desk?
- Yes.
That's funny...
That's nice.
Wood fires are great.
I use gas for heating...
It's expensive!
I'd like to see the archives for '97,
Cecile Prigent's delivery.
Not Pringent. "I", Prigent.
"I", for "intelligence."
I told you, I can't.
Yes, you can. Just get up
and fetch them. Come on!
- You're responsible.
- Yes, I'm responsible.
There they are!
You see? You could.
Thank you, miss.
Could I have a coffee, too?
"Cecile Prigent"...
Hello, doctor! How are you?
What are you doing here?
Those are confidential files!
Oh well, too bad.
- Let's talk pregnancies.
- Are you pregnant?
No. Why?
Oh, no! I mean an old pregnancy
that happened 17 years ago.
The thing that's troubling me
is that Gwen Prigent
and Ingrid de Kersaint-Gilly
are both 17.
I don't get it.
Born the same day
in the same clinic.
That can happen.
Sure.
Swapped babies are rare, though.
Though my mum used to say:
"They must have
swapped you at birth."
What was I saying?
Oh, yes!
Did you know that
Josephine de Kersaint-Gilly
and the Prigent girl were related?
- I don't understand.
- Yes, you do.
I'm not going to teach you about DNA!
I've compared the two:
100% compatible.
There's no point lying, doctor.
I know the story.
I'd just like to hear your version.
Leave.
Very well.
Cecile and Solene gave birth
the same day in my clinic.
Renan's wife was clinically dead.
When I managed to deliver
her child,
the baby girl was also half dead.
Doctor Lebovitz!
Cecile was giving birth
in the room next door.
Or rather, didn't want to give birth.
She'd spent 3 months in my clinic
for depression.
Was it the same
when her son was born?
No, it was just for that child.
She didn't want to give birth to it.
I'll take her.
Put the other one in an incubator.
I don't think I understand.
Ferdinand told me
that Solene wouldn't live,
nor would your daughter,
or so he thought.
I panicked.
I thought a child
would give you a reason to live...
So we took the babies
and we swapped them.
You mean Gwen was my daughter?
But... we thought
she wouldn't live.
- And?
- And, and...
Nothing. Time went by.
Cecile recovered
from her breakdown,
she raised her daughter
with her big brother,
she loved her,
adored her, protected her.
That was her way to make up for
those difficult early days and...
And Gwen became
this wonderful young girl...
so pretty, so smart.
That's why you loved her.
Because she was
your real granddaughter.
And you raised Ingrid,
Cecile's daughter. That's it.
Why keep it quiet?
We couldn't turn back the clock.
That's just the way it is!
It seemed unfair to give Cecile
the only child that was alive
when she screamed
that she didn't want it.
And to tell you that your wife
and daughter had died...
That's it.
- You are a monster.
- No.
No.
We thought we could
balance out fate.
People who think they're God
are scary.
Sounds a bit schizo, doesn't it?
What a lot of X-rays!
They're lung X-rays.
So I see.
But there's more. Look.
And a femur.
What's this?
A foot. It's a nice one.
And a head...
So what? I don't know
what you're getting at.
Josephine's body...
You know it by heart.
I'm her family doctor.
Not only her doctor.
You've written little notes.
Lovely style.
It reads like Chateaubriand,
in a medical way.
And I quote:
"Josephine came to consult me today.
"Slight fever, sensitive chest."
"She looks paler than usual."
"I fear she may have
an ear infection."
"Josephine is wilting."
That's not very elegant.
"I'd like to send her to Italy."
Nicer than La Bourboule!
"Her foot is sore.
"I'd so like to..." What's that?
"...protect her"?
That's so cute.
Honestly, bravo.
I like that.
But it doesn't read
like someone's medical file.
So what does it read like?
I don't know.
A lesson in the anatomy of love?
You can't do this.
Why did Ferdinand go along with it?
He's always admired my mother.
If she asked him
to jump into a fire, he'd do it.
He was always there
to heal our bumps,
my mum's migraines,
to keep an eye on her cholesterol,
her blood pressure,
even her alcohol consumption.
You mean he's in love with her?
Yes. Maybe that's what
being in love is all about.
That's why Josephine
wanted to separate them.
Brother and sister...
Are you OK?
We need to talk, honey.
Is there any news?
Yes.
What are we waiting for?
"Patience and the fullness of time
do more than force or fury";
as my old colleague "Rat Face"
used to say.
Ah... There she is.
Hello. Come in.
Please take a seat.
So, Mrs de Kersaint-Gilly,
did you consult
Dr Ferdinand Lebovitz
- that's a nice name -
on 7 February, at 10pm?
I'm in bed by 10pm.
Really? I go to bed early, too.
I watch series.
I say that because you have marks
around your neck,
and Dr Lebovitz...
I'm not inventing this,
he wrote it down.
He says you had
"strangulation marks
"at the jugulars."
Here, right?
How could you have known
without seeing her?
I found out later.
I drew conclusions.
Very smart!
Good conclusion.
And did you find out
on the eve of her husband's death?
- So that means Gwen was...
- My daughter.
- And you are...
- Yes. You know as much as us now.
All I can add is that...
every month, I drew a line
on the castle wall.
That wall saw you grow
one centimetre at a time.
As did I.
You are my daughter and I don't care
what DNA says.
I love you, Dad.
You didn't ask for this, poor Ingrid,
but we can't pretend we don't know.
So what do we do?
I'm convinced that being a parent
isn't a given.
You have to earn it.
We'll create something,
a new family.
I'm sure we'll find a way.
I know it will be easy.
I've loved you
for a long time already.
Mrs de Kersaint-Gilly
is going to be charged with
the murder of her husband.
Considering the evidence,
I think she'll get at least 15 years.
Is that what you want?
You've always helped her.
If you want to do something,
now's the time.
Don't tell me you don't care
she'll go to prison!
You've always cared for her.
Do you know
what she'll go through?
So?
It's true, Josephine.
I killed Christian.
I couldn't stand his hitting you.
- You saw us?
- Yes.
But how? It was dark.
I always follow you.
I watch you.
I hide in the bushes.
I try to hold my breath.
I know all your habits:
your morning walk, your evening one.
Only that night,
nothing was as usual.
You were with Christian
and you were having an argument.
Because it's late and very dark.
There's a full moon.
I'll walk you home.
Oh, wait. Christian...
The bank called.
There's 8,000 euros missing.
- Bankers are jerks.
- Who can count.
Where did the money go?
- That's none of your business.
- Yes it is! You're ruining us!
And you stink of alcohol.
Goddamn it!
- No...
- Let her go!
Let her go!
Stupid bitch!
Are you OK?
I couldn't bear to see him
harm this woman.
Josephine!
Josephine, are you there?
Open the door, for God's sake!
Come on, Jo!
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was angry.
I can explain.
Josephine?
Is someone there?
Come on...
Can I say goodbye to him?
- I don't know what to say.
- Don't say anything.
Someone taught me
how to do that.
You've left them alone in there?
If they wanted to run off together,
they'd have done it long ago.
What? Do you never watch
TV series?
You don't read romantic novels?
- No.
- There's a surprise!
When I saw you,
I thought: "He doesn't."
You're the kind who plays
table tennis, right?
Not bad, eh?
I could watch it 1,000 times!
- Do you want a drink?
- No thanks.
It's beautiful!
So the cops bought the story
of the old bag doing it?
I think so.
She was in police custody.
They released her after 48 hours
pending her indictment.
Things are looking up.
Yes, but I can't sleep at night.
She was 17.
That's no age to die.
This is no time for weakness.
Don't be stupid.
The boss likes you.
He can't keep guys
who feel melancholic.
They don't make good employees.
I'm not a robot.
I know. What a shame!
You have to make do.
He can't criticize me.
I made no mistakes with Gwen.
I like seeing you like this.
With your usual... fieriness.
Here.
That should pay for everything.
And finance
the death of Cecile Prigent.
Cecile, get up.
- We've got a problem.
- What?
The commission has approved
the marina.
They're laying down cement.
There's another problem.
Richard has left.
He's left?
He's found a job elsewhere.
He's 58!
Who's given him work?
Your brother.
Bastard!
We have to fight.
We need you.
For the marina,
for Yann, for my father.
- And for me, too.
- Yes, you're right.
We can't let them
get away with it.
That's the spirit!
They're all avoiding me.
I can understand why.
I've messed up their lives.
What you did was awful.
That's sweet. And honest!
And my poor Ferdinand is in jail.
He feels the cold.
He likes to be surrounded
by his little things.
Oh no, not her!
I see the bailiffs
weren't very conciliatory.
No.
They'd take the plaster
I put in the cracks if they could.
But Tarek brought me
a teapot and a stove.
And Renan?
He's on his boat.
He doesn't want to see me.
I've brought you your money back.
Well, Gwen's.
Keep it, it's yours.
- I don't want it.
- I don't know what to say to you.
I loved my son...
When I heard Solene had died,
I thought he might kill himself.
A child would force him
to stay alive.
- And you didn't stop shouting...
- That I was a bad mum?
I know.
Forgive me.
That's not why I'm here.
I'm asking you to change your mind
about selling up.
That's not possible.
I've signed all the deeds.
Buy it back
with the money you'd given Gwen.
Fight with us against the marina.
We need everyone on board.
Even me?
It's too late to undo
what you've done.
Concentrate on what can be saved:
Ingrid, Yann, Renan,
and me.
We've done it. It's incredible.
Do you like it?
Thanks.
- It's amazing.
- Yes, it's beautiful.
Magical!
We've done it.
Are you pleased, Vincent?
I have always been a supporter
of daring architecture
and modern designs.
Today I am proud to inaugurate
the first stage in our marina,
the Sunshine Lighthouse!
Bravo!
This lighthouse will represent
our town's progression
towards a world that looks ahead
and faces the future!
Bravo!
Dear friends, can I ask you
to raise your glasses?
- Will you have a drink?
- Please.
To you.
Cheers.
No, miss.
I need to speak to my aunt,
Nadia Quemener.
- Let her go.
- Sorry.
- It's about Gwen.
- What do you want?
She spent her last evening
at your husband's agency.
Who did she leave with?
I can't help you.
If you know something,
please tell me.
I really can't help you.
Ingrid,
I can't do anything to help you.
Goodbye.
I found this in Salmon's home.
Now go, we're being watched.
Are you going fishing again?
It's difficult for everybody, Yann.
For me too.
You can't keep avoiding me.
What are we going to do now?
We kissed
and fondled each other.
I dreamt of going to sea with you.
Now we'll trim the Christmas tree
together, and call Cecile mum?
I don't know!
At least we can try.
Try what?
I don't know.
I need you here, Yann.
Before she died,
Gwen spent the evening
at Quemener's agency.
- Whose is this?
- She left it at Salmon's.
- Who gave it to you?
- Nadia.
What does it mean?
Salmon was the last person
to see her alive.
- You're avoiding me.
- Me? Absolutely not.
You're lying and avoiding me.
Yes. I find you scary.
You can't have it both ways.
Things come at a price.
Like the death of a 17-year-old?
What do you mean?
Gwen spent her last night
at your place.
What does that prove?
I found one of the earrings
she had on that night under your bed.
I know I shouldn't be
telling you this.
It's serious.
I'm going to see Marleau.
No. You can't do that.
How are you going to stop me?
Are you going to kill me too?
- Give me the earring.
- I don't have it.
- Where is it?
- I'll die before I tell you!
In case something happened to me,
I left an account with my lawyer.
If I get into trouble,
you're my accomplice.
What are you doing?
I've filled her up.
You off again?
I've hired someone.
We'll set off tomorrow morning.
- Will you be OK?
- Yeah.
Cecile...
- I'm proud of you.
- Renan...
meet my future skipper,
Stephane Petitjean.
- Hello.
- Watch over her.
- I will!
I'm sorry, my son should be here.
Ah, youngsters...
He probably stayed over
at a girlfriend's.
He phoned to tell me
he wouldn't be coming home
but he didn't say where he'd be.
I know the feeling.
It's hard to let our kids
fly the nest.
My eldest is the same,
and yet he's of age.
So is Yann.
- Is your son called Yann?
- Yes.
That's funny.
Mine's called Yannick.
- A real hothead.
- Like my son.
Ah, kids!
They drive us up the wall!
That's just the way it is.
Don't worry,
we'll cope fine without him.
OK. I'm sure you're right.
I'll call him when we get back.
Let's go.
Neither lord nor master
nor kibble
Well, don't mind us!
So, did you see him?
Answer me!
I went to Salmon's
and I was hit on the head.
- I wanted to talk to him.
- So?
I got a blow to the head!
I can't remember anything!
And I missed the trawler.
Who cares?
I'm fed up of your shit.
If you want to do this on the quiet,
count me out.
I'm going to the cops.
You coming?
Yeah! Just a minute.
Come in.
Come in. I don't bite
and I'm not hungry.
What's up?
I'm listening.
- I was knocked out.
- He woke up in a ditch.
After Gwen died,
I saw Nadia Quemener and Salmon
making love.
Nadia gave me this.
It belonged to Gwen.
That's familiar.
I found the other one
on her body.
Right, guys...
Sit down, take a deep breath,
and tell me everything
from the start.
Come on, wake up!
Coffee?
- Yes please, Cecile.
- OK.
Stay tuned
for the special weather report.
Strong gale to storm-force warnings
in the South-West,
force 9 to 10,
with gusts reaching 70 to 80...
Sugar?
For Christ's sake!
Why didn't you come and tell me this
before now?
Let's go. Come on!
Hurry up!
Ah, kids...
Nobody.
Right. Salmon isn't home.
This is what we'll do:
I'll search the premises
with my colleagues.
You stay here and hide.
If he comes, sound the horn.
Don't move,
and no smoking in my car!
What are you doing?
I'm coming.
Excuse me.
Do you know Cecile Prigent?
Yes. She's out at sea.
Shit. I'm late,
but it's not my fault.
I got a call.
They said my kid was ill,
so I dashed to his house.
- And?
- He was fast asleep.
I think somebody
played a trick on me,
or didn't want me to take the job.
What job?
Skipper on the trawler.
- The skipper left with her.
- I doubt it!
Here's the paperwork.
- You're Stephane Petitjean?
- Yes.
I don't believe it!
Cecile!
Oh, no! Shit!
Nothing in here.
That's strange.
Watch this.
I knew it!
The Dunkirk Carnival!
It's full of disguises.
He looks like Jacques Dutronc.
He never seems to age.
He's an oddball.
When do you think he was born?
This says 1962.
These are false papers.
What do you think?
He looks 30.
It could be Faust.
It's not false, it's true.
Faust, who sold his soul
to the devil in exchange for
youth, money and beauty.
Never heard of him?
I have.
I'm a cop but I'm not ignorant.
Do your job,
instead of parading your culture
like a prize poodle.
It stinks of money here.
I can smell it.
- I'll come.
- Are you her husband?
No... Well, yes.
I'm coming too.
1, 2, 3.
Goodness! Look at that.
Have you ever seen any?
There's loads of them.
That's good for us.
You know why?
It means Salmon will come back.
Unless he's run off.
No. You need loads of dough
to do a runner. Loads!
He needs his money right now.
That worked out well.
Great!
Found anything?
Not yet.
- There's something there.
- Show me.
I looked up there.
We'll just wait for him.
Hello, ma'am.
What happened?
They've found Gwen's prints
at Salmon's place, and blood.
Shit... Where is he?
I can't reach him.
He's run off, of course!
With all his secrets!
- He's not left anything?
- Only a body.
No, I mean... I don't know.
A message for me?
Are you deaf?
He killed Gwen!
And you want a goodbye note?
Honestly...
I'll call him.
- Straight to voicemail.
- Obviously!
You think he wants
to end up in jail?
I was sure he loved me.
Pick up...
I'm looking for
Mr Renan de Kersaint-Gilly.
Yes, he's next door.
I've come to wait with you.
I'm sorry for everything I've done.
- But I did it for you.
- I know.
- What are you doing?
- Clearing off.
You can't go like that, Vincent.
You can't leave me.
What'll become of me?
- Stop!
- Get off me!
Get him!
Go on, lock him up!
Off you go!
Good work, guys!
I'm sure he loves me.
I know it.
Mr President,
Etienne Quemener here.
My agency is closing down.
Yes, I'm filing for bankruptcy.
No, we won't be able to
carry out the work.
We'll be able to breathe
the sea air.
Yes, breathe!
We're suffocating here!
Suffocating!
FOR SALE
I wanted to tell you
something about him.
He wasn't always an old fool.
Sometimes, but not always.
We even had some good times.
We met on a boat.
I'd been sick as a dog.
He pretended not to notice,
and you were born 2 years later.
He was so happy to have a son.
He played with you a lot.
Do you remember?
- No.
- Oh, he did.
One day, he'd made you a toy,
a little car.
But he wasn't good with his hands.
Boy, did I laugh!
It just looked like... an old crate.
So I told you that it was a magic box
that you shouldn't open because
a magical creature lived inside.
It would die if I opened the box,
and I had to feed it secrets.
They would make him grow.
- I remember.
- Yes...
I'd invented that for you to feel
less lonely, as a little boy here.
And for him, too,
to salvage his gift.
And that box...
you kept it
all through your childhood.
I always pictured that animal
as a little blue fish.
If I didn't speak to it,
it would become transparent,
about to disappear,
so I'd whisper a few secrets to it.
And it turned blue again.
That's funny.
In my mind, it was a unicorn.
You know, this estate...
When I first saw it,
I thought I would...
die here.
That this was where I would die.
Well...
I got that right.
Don't worry, I'll look after him.
Come back soon.
I've got a good reason to.
- Ready?
- Hell yes!
I may be the heir,
but this money is worthless
if I don't have love!
You have power and money.
Is that not enough?
I have to confess a terrible secret.
What, John?
Steven's been unfaithful for years.
That's not possible.
He loves and respects me.
Look at this ring.
No! Listen to me, Cynthia.
I'm busy.
He stole Christopher's identity
and emptied his bank accounts.
You're kidding!
As you know,
I have always striven
to protect the sea and the fishermen,
to protect them,
come hell or high water.
Ferdinand!
Ferdinand.
What are you doing here?
There's no room in jail
while I'm on remand.
The prisons are full.
My trial won't take place
for a couple of years.
In the meantime...
You've got time for a drink.
Yes.
- They released you?
- Yes.
Unbelievable!
- Extraordinary!
- Yes.
I heard that Salmon and the man
who attacked Cecile were dead.
Yes, they were both shot.
Salmon when he was taken to prison,
the other one in his hospital bed.
Two rifle shots.
Witnesses say they saw a woman.
They've not found her.
- Their boss?
- No, no.
Apparently, Salmon received
transfers from offshore accounts.
They've traced
a Mr Philippe de Ville.
The police investigated,
they even searched his home,
but they didn't find any DNA.
He was the devil.
- Etienne must have taken it hard.
- It was very strange.
He wandered the streets
saying that Salmon loved him.
Then he left town
and no one knows where he is.
But I got my clearing back.
Before vanishing, he returned it.
You've left it outside?
- It looks good there.
- Yes.
And it's more comfortable.
We can sit here now
and see the trees in blossom.
- And the lighthouse...
- It's mine now.
It's grown on me.
Cecile has got me involved
in a marina project
to modernize the harbour.
Anyway... We've launched
a major referendum.
She's in charge of all that.
The days are getting longer.
You can tell spring is near.
How long do you have?
- 2 years.
- 2 years? That's marvellous!
It'll make each season
even more amazing.
Like an end-of-the-world feeling.
Thank you.
No.
Let me thank you.
Subtitles: Eclair Group