CAPTAIN MARLEAU
THALASSO FOG
Come on, come on!
Go on, climb up there! Go on!
Who gave me
this band of weaklings?
Good to see you, Captain.
Don't get excited,
just passing through.
Go on! Go on! And boom,
you're dead, you climbed too high!
Not how to win!
Have you warmed up?
-Yes, of course.
-Yes.
One, two, three!
He is cute.
-Captain.
-Comrade.
-Hello.
Your dancers are pretty.
Attack me.
Mime weapon attack
and come at me like
you want to stab me with a knife.
Simple. All in the dodge. Up.
Get up. Try again.
Go on. Attack me!
-You okay?
-Yes, thank you.
Can I take his place?
Captain Marleau...
We will do the exercise backwards.
It's me attacking you
and you try to dodge me.
Ready?
Careful. Arthritis.
My favorite blow: the balls.
I love Patrick Dewaere.
It was good, but it was--
They're too careful, right?
They're not letting go, are they?
Stop. You're too far away
from one another.
You should feel the right distance.
Be aware of the other's body.
If not, it won't work, okay?
You understand that?
Okay, we'll start again.
Restart, from the start of the lifts,
let's go!
Five, six, seven, eight, and...
Wait, wait! Don't forget,
they're crazy in love.
So every time you can,
make eye contact.
Right in the eyes.
We are telling a love story,
everyone.
Garance is right.
Forget yourselves!
A good dancer is a dancer
whose technique disappears...
And Vladimir says so! Okay?
Pardon me.
It's you? Yes, no, tonight of course.
Garance? Are you okay?
Yes, in the garden. Agreed?
Garance, you okay?
Yes. Shall we go over it again?
Yes, let's go.
Kids, restart! Let's go!
Eye contact, let's go.
Five, six, seven, eight, and...
-How are you?
-Very good, Sir.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-Evening, Ida.
-Hello, Mr. Thibaut.
Is Luc in his office?
Exactly. Want me
to tell him you're here?
Yes, please.
Has my wife arrived yet?
She's at the restaurant.
Good. Are you more beautiful
each time I see you, or am I wrong?
Thank you very much, Sir.
Good evening.
At least pretend
to be happy to see me?
Evening, Mr. Thibaut.
Evening, Michael. My usual.
Good, Sir.
Thought I'd give you a surprise
by coming to tell you
that I just bought
all these old walls.
What do you say?
It's a good surprise, right?
Truly, you are pathetic!
You still need the illusion
I'm under your thumb?
That's not nice.
I really have no desire
to be, believe me!
You have your own little secrets?
I heard you had come back to...
your artistic vocation.
Our divorce gives you wings, right?
I regret not doing it sooner.
You're cute.
-How do you do it?
-What?
How did you change so much?
Please...
When I met you, you were
funny, brilliant, intelligent.
I gave up everything for you.
What happened, Paul?
What did you do to become this guy?
This is not the time or the place...
Until Clément left,
I'd forgiven everything.
All of it!
Your absence, your escapades!
Your mistresses!
Your mistresses too! All of it!
I was indifferent to it all!
Then Clément left
and I opened my eyes.
You are wrong.
But you are wrong!
How could you?
How could you sleep with...
your son's girlfriend?
What are you talking about?
And me, like an idiot...I...I...
Come on! You are crazy!
But I did not see anything, but...
Shut up!
Once our divorce is signed,
I never want to hear from you again.
Never!
Good evening. Pardon me.
So, what happened?
I think she cannot stand
the idea of our separation.
If I can do anything,
you know you can count on me.
Thank you, Luc, it is okay.
Why not stay and eat with us?
Miléna would be glad to see you.
I do not know, I...
Go on! Stay. This is sort of
your place now, right?
Good evening, Garance!
How are you?
At last, I am happy to see you.
-Yes?
-I want you to prepare my notice.
I will go at the end of the week.
I want to pay for it.
But of course. Will you tell me?
Thank you for your information...
Pardon me?
Paul's lucky to buy the hotel,
but believe me...
knowing him, you will very quickly
be part of the staff.
You see, Luc, I am a romantic!
I never viewed matters
in a Cartesian way, you see?
I am sure that
you're just like me, by the by.
What's that?
It is the adventure that seduces us.
Would you not agree?
You know how attached
I am to this place.
Without your loan,
I would never have got by...
Thank you, Jérémy.
I will take care of it.
Your new stockholder by your side,
you are still in charge.
And then from time to time,
the two of us
will look at the numbers.
Clearly, as soon as I can start
to buy parts back--
But no! Buying back?
No! I am very happy
with my investment.
-But it is--
-No, but wait, Luc, honestly!
No, forget it.
We are here to drink
a fine bottle of wine.
Believe me, I need it.
By the way,
where is your charming wife?
She will be here soon.
What was I telling you?
You say her name and she appears
as if by magic.
In business as in love,
you are a lucky man!
Paul, I am pleased to see you!
I return the compliment.
I would say you are the most
beautiful apparition of my day.
You are exaggerating.
Do you want a glass of wine?
With pleasure!
Paul, please!
Not here, not tonight!
Forget about it, Luc!
I will give you all of the shares
in the hotel! Okay?
The investment is for you!
It is yours!
I don't want to. Get it?
No, listen! You know,
as soon as I saw you,
I realized I could
no longer do without you.
Please! I was swept along
in this story.
But no more, Paul!
I love Luc, understand?
Leave me alone!
HOTEL LES BAINS
Justine, check the bath towels.
Yes, Madam.
Do not forget to smile at clients
when you enter rest areas.
Marie, when you finish your antics,
come to the treatment rooms.
Send a cleaner to balneotherapy.
I will take care of it.
Check the Kaolin mud bath room too.
Georges fixed it,
but I'm sure he's left it a mess.
I will go there now.
Stay here, don't move.
I'll tell Mr. Luc.
Chabu!
Léon, Zitrone! Heel, dogs!
Go on, heel! That is good!
That is good!
So, Brière!
What is going on?
You are pale!
Are you scared of dogs?
Yes, when I was little
I was bitten on my lip.
Yes, I see it. What is up?
Death, Hotel Les Bains.
What emergency?
A drowning in a mud bath.
Sat up in a bath?
That is not pratical!
It is not that I am getting bored,
but duty is calling out to me.
And "duty is power",
as an old friend of mine used to say.
A philosopher?
No, a bar regular, a real one!
Lucky, at least you knew
where to find him.
Hold on! I have nothing,
so grumpy soup tonight.
Come on, let's go.
My darlings.
And Léon and Zitrone.
They are both here!
Great youth hostel.
One night is at least minimum wage!
At least.
Sir. Comrades.
But as I say,
it is time for my mud bath!
You will calm down, Sir.
The Balnéo room
is currently not available.
I cannot say more.
Surely I can have an explanation!
Listen! It is not possible!
I was here this morning.
I intend to take advantage!
Can we know why the police
are invading this hotel?
I have no more details for you.
Management will contact you
in good time.
But for now, I ask you to be patient.
Thank you.
I will ask you
to go back to your rooms
for the morning, and go to see
the national gendarmerie.
See! Thanks!
And why is that, Madam?
Is it an emergency?
Absolutely! You see!
If you do not agree,
there are protests each Friday,
Republic Square.
It is charming! Voila!
If you'd like to return
to your Imperial and Royal Suites,
there is a little red carpet
that awaits you.
You have all the channels.
There is a good film tonight at 8.30.
I recommend it. Goodbye!
Captain, it is down here.
-Hello.
Captain Marleau.
Luc Férey, I am the hotel manager.
Congratulations.
Miléna, my wife.
Congratulations again.
Did you know the victim?
Yes, Paul Thibaut, a friend.
He dined here last night.
Does he live here?
No, he has a property
about six miles away from here.
He was a business man.
He traveled a lot.
But his wife
has been here for a while.
Is she being treated here?
No, they are divorcing
and he came to see her.
Have you told her?
No. She left early this morning.
She's not answering her phone.
I still can't believe it.
It's so awful.
Really awful.
Comrades! It's hot in here!
Hi!
Thank you!
So?
No fingerprints.
Oh no?
No exploitable trace.
The room's been fully cleaned.
Not even a mud stain on the tiles.
Like a big floating raspberry
meringue island.
Let's see his face.
Come on, roll over!
He's floating.
It's Kaolin.
-Of what?
-Of Kaolin.
You know stuff about this!
Like floating in the Dead Sea.
And here, dead floating in the sea.
Were the doors open like this?
Yes, the two staff who found him
didn't touch a thing.
Ah, yes?
In my opinion, he drowned.
Because with the cut on his head...
Even so, a suit for a mud bath,
you'd have to be stupid.
What's up, Brière?
-I am okay.
-You're all pale.
It is the...
Take him out of there,
then send him to forensics.
Hold this, seal the evidence?
I will do a tour of the property.
Can I let you take care of the body?
It is beautiful!
Feels just like Le Touquet.
I saw that there were
many video cameras.
A ploy for your vigilant clients.
They are CCTV cameras?
Creating the Thalasso,
we equipped the whole establishment.
That's great!
We can observe
your clients' lives in detail.
And tell me, the video files,
do you save them every day?
Sadly, no. They don't record.
They are only played in real time.
That's totally stupid!
That does nothing!
If you miss it live, you're done.
That's it.
So, who is it
that has access to the images?
The guy in front of the computer
in my office
and the night watchman.
And when does he start his shift?
-10 p.m.
What is that blockhouse for?
For Fukushima clients?
In case of a nuclear attack?
It is a mechanical room
where we treat the Thalasso water.
It is locked.
I don't care, I...
Where are you going? Come here!
He's gonna break his neck too.
He had a second set of keys,
it seems.
You had a spare?
Are you hurt?
Let me see. Show me that.
Do you have a first aid kit?
Here, is that all right?
It's better than looking like
the one-eyed man of Montretout.
Do you not want to tell me your name?
Marin.
Marin! Marin's a funny name!
Smells like the oceans, algae,
plastic bags in whales' stomachs.
How did you get here?
There is a sleeping bag
and some stuff inside.
Because you sleep here?
A homeless person?
Have you been here for long?
Have you run away, is that it?
You can say.
I won't tell your parents.
I was kicked out of all
the Nord-Pas-de-Calais foster homes.
Did you lose your tongue
at the same time as your boat?
Captain, come see.
I think we've got something.
Yes, I'm coming.
Don't move.
He set up at the back
just behind this tank.
What misery!
We're talking about a palace...
See what I found
in a pocket of this bag.
What? Paul Thibaut.
It seems our Marin
is drinking sea water.
Bring him here. Don't worry.
It's where
the victim's wife's dance class is.
That's good.
Want me to go down
as you continue the interrogations?
No, I will do it.
C'est pas tellement marrant,
I will go and see her.
Excuse me.
We wanted to let you know
just how grateful we are
that you have resolved this tragedy
so quickly.
Paul was above all a friend,
a remarkable man.
Yes, we say that at funerals,
and always finish with,
'He was nice, but..."
But Captain, we are deeply affected.
Oh, I would not dare.
In any case,
your aquatic park is closed.
Until further notice,
as the inquiry isn't complete.
Goodbye.
Two, three, four,
five, six, seven...
So, wait!
In ballet, the choreographer
and the dancers are 50/50.
A talented choreographer with
a performer who doesn't understand
cannot do anything,
and reciprocally.
Choreography takes two,
it's like love.
Let's restart.
Five, six, seven, eight, and...
-Excuse me! Garance Thibaut?
-Yes?
Marleau, national gendarmerie.
Can we talk in private?
Not too close together, yes.
That's good. Dynamic...
We found your husband's body
in one of the baths in your hotel.
He drowned himself?
Seems not. He was already dead
when he fell in the bath,
he was assaulted.
Very well.
My condolences, Mrs. Thibaut.
You were filing for divorce,
is that right?
Yes, we have been living separately
for nearly two months.
Why was it that your husband
came to see you last night?
We had some terms to agree upon
for the divorce.
I heard that it did not go very well.
In fact. I chose to cut it short.
I understand.
A slap can sometimes be a relief.
Hardly.
I came to say that his body is at
the morgue if you want to see it.
Do what you have to do.
You must know I'll inherit
an impressive fortune?
Yes, I heard.
Like a big lottery win, it seems.
In effect.
I imagine you will ask me
where I was last night.
No, it is not worth it,
there is no need.
Why?
Because we have already
arrested someone.
A young man in the hotel gardens.
He had your husband's wallet
amongst his things.
A young man? What young man?
A homeless man. Why?
And he has confessed?
No, we've not started
questioning him yet.
With a hit of the directory
it shouldn't take long.
Thank you for telling me.
I'd like to get back to my rehearsal.
This news doesn't seem
to have upset you very much?
My sorrow is not immense, Captain.
Any questions,
you know where I am.
Sorry, Madam.
Nothing serious?
I don't know.
No more divorce.
What? But why?
I am a widow.
So look.
Have a good look. Are you sure
you do not know this man?
Why did we find his wallet
among your things?
You are force-feeding me.
Do you realize what is happening?
You'll be charged for murder.
You got that?
It's not me. I never saw this guy.
Yes...
You are starting to annoy me.
I have never seen him,
but his son and his wife, yes.
How do you know
his son and his wife?
I opened the wallet.
There's a family photo.
In the wallet?
-This one?
-Yes.
Don't need to be smart
to get that, right?
Yes, okay.
Stop showing off.
And don't move from here.
Carpentier, watch him.
So, what does he have to say, Brière?
So his name is Marin Cibié.
Anonymous birth, 1996.
Been in a dozen foster families.
A dozen?
Social services say it was awful.
Mutism, rejecting authority,
violent communication...
That reminds me of someone.
He is also known to the police.
Shoplifting, car theft,
always violent.
Why was he walking in nature?
He was put in a home
until he's 18, then he disappeared.
Right.
Do you have news
about the night watchman?
He swears he did not see
that the kid was hiding here.
I also saw the hotel's clients.
And did you find anything?
Only retirees with nothing.
Wealthy people with nothing.
Keep looking.
If you find something
on the Thibaut family, tell me.
You should have canceled
the rehearsal.
No. Out of the question.
I am proud of you, Garance.
Proud of what you're doing!
If you knew the fear...
Fear of what?
Of something serious.
What?
I am scared Clément
might have seen his father.
I would say it annoys you
that it is so simple.
A corpse in the morning,
a culprit in the afternoon.
And a death sentence that night.
It will add to
police statistics is all.
What is bothering you?
Him, the kid.
He is a yob, but press his nose
and milk comes out.
You want to defend the orphan.
But no. I know what it is
to be discriminated against.
Then this kid, he is not that stupid.
He will go and kill someone,
clean the crime scene,
and go hide in a cabin nearby,
waiting for someone
to come and find him.
Whatever.
While we wait,
see this lovely side of beef!
It was a gift from Brière.
-Ah, yes?
-Yes.
His dad is a butcher. He even put
in the bones for Léon and Zitrone.
That was magnificent!
I really love the way
that you dance! Thank you!
Send directly to Mr.--
Hello!
Captain Marleau.
Here to serve, kind woman.
Sorry, you scared me.
That is all right, I am used to that.
Could I have a little bathrobe?
To test
your establishment's services?
For the treatments,
we have not reopened the Thalasso.
We are awaiting authorization.
And then everyone is still in shock.
Death at the Thalasso,
it is not great publicity.
Most clients
have cancelled their stays.
All emails are to cancel.
But that is normal.
There are better places right now.
Certainly.
I can't wait!
Show me what to do?
If you can handle it!
Follow me?
Thank you!
Paul was an easy contact,
disconcerting.
It felt like
you'd always known him.
And how did you find his wife?
She is... How would I say? Strange.
Strange how?
She is more reserved.
We aren't friends.
Not like Paul.
Yes, but still.
She came here when she was shut out.
Yes. She said she could
no longer set foot in their house,
or even stand that place.
Did he come to see her often?
Not really. I think he avoided it.
Why?
I think Paul couldn't handle
the idea of her leaving.
And as he had an excessive ego...
Little was denied to him,
I think.
Do you know their son?
Never saw him.
They didn't discuss him.
What do I look like?
A client?
Not very nice
Okay, what does this start with?
Over there. I will show you that
you have a wide range of choices.
Who opens the Thalasso
in the morning?
I do. I close it every evening
after the technician's check.
Thursday night, you closed.
Yes.
And the patio doors?
The door to the garden
was closed too?
Yes. I am sure.
Ah, yeah? Good, I will go.
It's hot!
Not bad, but it is hot
to a girl from the North.
It is not bad.
It stinks.
It smells?
Like the tide, mussels?
No, it's a Breton algae
essential oil.
And the technician is a plumber?
Yes, you could say that.
And does he have keys?
No, except those to
the machine room outside, but...
Is there a way I can see him today?
What I mean is,
Mr. Férey fired him
at the start of the week.
Why? Was there water in the gas?
Georges is in a trade union.
He questioned many things.
Mr. Luc got tired.
Yes, I think he drank.
Mr. Thibaut even noticed it,
and he told Mr. Luc.
Do you call him Mr. Luc?
Yes. I knew his father too.
Yes?
This establishment
is a family affair.
He inherited the hotel,
vowed his life to it.
And his wife?
Everything she does is for him.
Rarely have I seen
such a devoted wife.
In any case, the trade union member,
did someone see him here yesterday?
I saw him late afternoon, at closing.
He wanted to pick up his tools.
His toolbox?
Your thing is too hot.
Still, I am not a lobster, Christ.
Is there something to cool the meat,
after the double boiler?
I'm out. Too hot!
It's freezing!
Captain?
What's going on here?
After the widow Pinocchio,
we visit the syndicate
of drinkers and boozers.
Syndicated colleagues, hello.
National gendarmerie.
Captain Marleau.
I am looking for a plumber.
I was told I could find the king
of toilet de-blockers here.
Do you know a certain Jojo?
No, I do not think so.
No?
There is no Jojo here?
Georges. My name is Georges.
Jojo is for my friends.
And how is Georges?
Okay.
Does he know a certain Marin?
Yes, I opened the machine room
at the Thalasso for him.
Three days ago.
With those idlers, drunk on cash,
wasn't harming anyone.
Well, I thought.
But at the same time,
I imagine you like
pissing off your ex-bosses?
Yeah.
They booted me out like a leper.
Didn't even get my tools.
I looked all over, didn't find them.
I worked seven years in this hotel.
Without counting the whole year's
training for this Thalasso crap.
Crappy Thalasso. All that, why?
Surely due to a penchant for tea?
Careful. I never drank
a drop at work.
That's not what Mr. Thibaut
said to Mr. Férey.
Mr. Thibaut?
That was him?
Yes, apparently.
That does not surprise me.
The cash-stuffed, bloated hypocrite.
If you say so.
Do you know why
the boss got told that crap?
Surely because
you are a trade unionist.
That too, surely.
But it's mainly because
I caught him with Mr. Luc's wife.
How so?
I caught them together
in the Thalasso one evening.
Pretended it was nothing,
but I'm not blind!
He was groping her, little Miléna.
And did you tell Mr. Férey?
Have you seen me?
-I look guilty as sin?
-A little.
-Take care of yourself!
-Yes.
I shut my mouth very well!
Maybe I'd better open it.
What were you doing Thursday night?
I was visiting my mother.
She has Alzheimer's.
So in terms of testimony,
don't count too much on her.
I'll go back, this beer's bad.
That is a good idea.
Brière, what are you drinking?
-The same thing.
What do you think?
But I don't think, Brière, I observe.
And when fruit is ripe, it falls.
And who picks it up? Me.
It's good, this beer?
Yes, that's him. A big guy.
He opened the door
so that I could sleep there.
And the wallet?
I told you ten times.
The wallet
was on the patio in a coat,
and I stole it, I went through it.
That's all.
Except that the man in question
died that night.
I was inside. Didn't move.
Okay, let's admit.
That night, you didn't
notice anything odd?
Rack your brains!
If you don't help me,
I can't help you.
Once, I went out to pee.
And I saw a woman
run by the Thalasso.
Are you sure it was a woman?
If not, then a tranny with heels.
Does that make you laugh?
Give me my cigarette?
No! I don't fatten up
cigarette sellers.
I don't like trannyphobes.
So bring on your own lung cancer.
There it is.
Yes, hello?
Hello.
I'd like to know if Coralie Mons
still works here?
Why? Who's asking?
Garance, Garance Thibaut.
I really need to talk to her.
It's...
Excuse me, have you seen
Captain Marleau?
Monsieur!
Captain? So, are we relaxing?
No, I am thinking.
I thought you were
doing interrogations.
That's what I'm doing!
I have to do
transcendental meditation.
To know the human condition.
I have the autopsy report.
What does it say?
The death was between
midnight and 3 a.m.
He died as a result of
several blows to the head.
It's likely with a hammer.
Yes?
Residue of metal and wood in the cut.
High alcohol level.
Certain sexual activity
just before death.
Presence of foreign hairs
under DNA analysis.
Paul Thibaut possessed the hotel.
How is that?
A month ago he injected money
to save the Féreys from bankruptcy.
The Thalasso cost them a fortune.
Without him, they were done.
He is generous, this guy.
Generous, but dead. And his son?
Clément, 28 years old. Has been
living in Cameroon for over a year.
I bet all you want
that he musn't be so far away.
Can we slow down a bit
because I don't feel well?
So, my little nutcracker,
are you going to puke?
Okay, we'll slow down!
How long has it been
since you last had
intimate relations with your husband?
My husband collected mistresses
as others do stamps.
His powers of seduction
were without limit.
For years, he had the grace
to hide it and then...
time passed.
A sort of DSK.
And your son?
Clément? When did you last see him?
A long time ago.
It's true he lives in Africa.
You didn't see him in the hotel
gardens the night of the murder?
It's been more than a year
since I've seen my son.
That's a long time.
How did that happen?
Not your concern.
Why so many questions?
I thought you found the culprit.
And leaving a kid to rot in prison
for a crime
he may not have done.
Does that bother you?
I have a show to prepare.
And I'd like to get back to work.
Well, yeah... "Show must go on",
as that person sang.
Eddy Mitchell.
Madam Thibaut,
your son will hit the jackpot
with the death of his father?
It is a good alibi.
How dare you? I forbid you to--
Calm down, Garance, please.
The last few weeks
have been gruelling.
We would like some calm.
Have we been introduced, Sir?
He is Vladimir Lipinski,
a great dancer/choreographer.
I was lucky to see his Paris ballet
five years ago. It was magical.
Thank you.
My company will dance in Strasbourg
next week.
Can I invite you?
Thank you, that's kind.
Let's go, Brière.
"Les balais brosses", it's over.
I assure you,
he's a great choreographer.
Captain.
I have known Garance for years.
She'd have been a great dancer
if not for Paul.
She is a rare woman.
A beautiful person.
All the better for her.
I may dance like a potato,
but I have one big talent: my nose.
I smell lies a mile off.
Cyrano, next to me
is Michael Jackson!
Brière, can you stop
playing the raccoon?
It's not that.
-You don't get it?
-Yes.
You don't get that this deal
with Paul,
we are at his heirs' mercy.
And that if Garance
wants to sell the hotel
we cannot do anything?
We will lose everything, Miléna!
That will not happen.
How do you know that?
I will not let it happen.
I've always backed you.
I've always been by your side.
And this hotel is our project.
I won't let anyone interfere.
Believe me!
What would I do without you.
Do not worry.
We will get through this.
I promise you.
Yes.
I want a drink.
You know what? I want you.
Here?
Yes. Here, now. Right now.
Wait two seconds.
Clément, I have to talk to you.
Please call me back!
Yes?
It's Luc. May I come in?
Yes.
I wanted to...
I wanted to say again
how much Miléna and I--
You have, Luc.
But you should know
that Paul's death didn't cause
me great pain.
If you need anything, whatever it is,
don't hesitate. You can count on us.
My husband appreciated you a lot.
Let's say that without him,
we'd have been in great difficulty.
And with him too, I think.
Pardon me?
Be clear.
If Paul invested
in your establishment,
it's because he recognized
a good deal.
Yes.
I do not yet know
the ins and outs of your deal.
I imagine your hands are tied.
And you're no longer the master,
is that right?
Once Paul is buried,
I will sell
to the highest bidder, Luc.
Pardon me?
I don't want a hotel.
I will invest
in what deeply animates me.
Garance, I think--
I need to rest.
Thank you for your condolences.
They go straight to my heart.
What did she say to you?
Nothing.
Tell me, Luc?
She will chuck us out.
What? That's not true!
She'll take the best price.
And I assure you
she'll enjoy doing it.
No, she won't do that!
Yes? Why?
What do you want us to do?
You have an idea?
Listen, nobody will take this hotel.
Do you hear me, Luc? Nobody!
So we will find a solution,
don't worry!
Don't worry,
we will find a solution.
And go!
Spot on! Careful!
If we lose the hotel,
it'll kill Luc. Get it?
I don't know where she is.
And even if I did know,
I wouldn't tell you.
You're friends.
You've known her for ages.
Yes.
Try to talk to her.
Listen, Madam--
No, Miléna.
Garance is a big girl.
She can do whatever she wants.
So, ensure your friend
gets the message:
if she wants war, she'll have it.
Because I will do anything
for the man I love.
You were right.
The Thibaut son is in France.
His passport was checked at Roissy
four days ago from Cameroon.
Do you see what I was saying?
I have better still.
Careful, Brière!
You'll get a promotion!
And I think that I can say
why he went so far away.
Is it a love story?
Yeah, that's it.
His girlfriend chucked him.
My dad told me.
How's your dad know?
The girl's parents are clients
at the butcher's.
Last year, her mother came in
to buy cutlets, in floods of tears.
For her, it was a tragedy
her daughter'd never get over.
"There goes the money,"
she may as well have said.
It's familial prostitution.
Either the girl is lucid
or she's crazy.
But I do know one thing.
What?
-Her name is--
-Coralie Mons.
No! How do you know that?
Because the Thibaut's son
was getting married.
He published the banns. I saw them
on the town hall's website.
Not funny, Captain.
No, I'm not funny.
I am ugly, but I am intelligent.
What?
We have to talk, Coralie.
It's important.
I have nothing to say.
I want you to stop harassing
my dad over the phone.
Only reason that I came. That clear?
Do you have any news from Clément
recently?
It's important! Do you understand?
He's my son. My only son.
No, I haven't seen him since.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, not bad.
I... I...
A glass of water maybe.
Come in?
If I come in,
I'll ask you to tell me
what happened last year,
with Paul.
Doesn't look like I'm first.
Is there someone there?
I'm sorry, we're closed all week.
Even for a little sandwich?
-It's just me.
-Go on!
I can make you up
a plate of charcuterie,
but I have no bread.
Very good! No big deal,
nothing wrong with pork.
Are you Coralie?
Yes, why? Do I know you?
No, I am Captain Marleau.
What is it?
A draught beer.
-Here you are!
-Thank you.
Did you call off the marriage
with Clement last year?
What's it to you?
Long since you've seen him?
Since he left for Africa?
Separation is hard.
Especially when you're in love.
Never really goes.
By the by, my gran said,
"Lose one, lose one."
I'd like to close.
All right.
I imagine Garance Thibaut
asked you the same question.
She is scared for her child.
You know her husband just died?
That doesn't affect me.
And why is that?
When a predator disappears,
nature recovers.
I like your shoes.
Your heels are pretty.
Thank you.
What did you do Thursday evening?
I was on the train.
I live in Strasbourg.
I arrived that evening
to see my mum in hospital.
Very good.
I will leave you. I'm not hungry
and I don't eat meat.
In any case, I will
leave you my number.
That way, should you
find your tongue,
or if you have news of your ex,
call me. Okay? There we are!
I will rush because
I'm double parked.
I don't want to get a fine.
See you soon!
You've forgotten your shoes,
Captain?
No, they didn't have them in a 42.
Have you seen
Roland Petit's ballet?
Who's that?
A marvellous choreographer!
I was lucky to start with him
when I was a young dancer.
Petit loved beauty.
I thought he was
Zizi Jeanmaire's lover.
That's a nice formula.
Beauty Thibaut.
The polar opposite of my husband.
All he wanted to do was possess.
That cost me therapy.
Why did you marry him then?
At 30, when he looked at me I felt
like I was the center of the world.
He was handsome, thoughtful,
ambitious.
Ever been crazy in love, Captain?
Not really.
Time passes and people change.
Success, power, money...
All that turns heads.
And reveals people's characters.
Excuse me.
-Mrs. Thibaut?
-Yes?
What happened between
your husband and Coralie?
Who's talked about her?
Are you following me?
No. Shall we make a deal?
I'll stop playing Colombo,
and you tell me the truth. Agreed?
One night, Coralie
was alone here by the pool.
My husband got back
from New York. Thank you.
She told me she'd even thought
of bringing him a gift.
As thanks,
she jumps into his arms.
He offered her a drink, then two.
Then he finished
by trying to kiss her.
So Coralie pushed him away.
Paul laughed like it was nothing,
like it was not important.
In fact, for him, seducing a woman
became a game with no consequences.
A game?
Rape is not a game.
He turned into a big pig,
the old father-in-law, that it?
When Clément got in,
Coralie had left the house
without explanation.
So what did he do?
The next day he went to see her.
And Coralie finished
by confessing in tears
that she had slept with his dad.
And he left that same day
without a word.
To Cameroon?
Today, he works in a pepper factory.
In fair trade.
Fair, well that's an idea
that's never crossed
his father's mind.
And what burdens are there
in his mother's mind?
Me? Nothing!
My eyes had been closed
for a long time.
And then, Clément leaving
was like an electric shock.
Suddenly, I saw Paul
exactly as he was.
I realized I hadn't loved him
for a long time.
It was over.
And then three months ago
I saw Vladimir dance in Milan.
And I awoke as if
from a long sleep.
And Sleeping Beauty
ran to Coralie's house
to ask her if she knew where
to find her charming son, that it?
Because in fact, your son did come
to see you on Thursday night.
At the hotel?
I said I've not seen him
in over a year.
Liar. You're lying, Garance.
Your nose is growing.
Know what I think? You're scared.
You are scared for your son.
Scared he'll do something stupid,
Œdipus style.
There is no need to be Dolto
to understand.
Am I wrong?
Yes?
What's happening?
Captain Marleau sent me.
-Yes, and?
-She's at the Thalasso.
-The pool?
-She asked me to get you.
What does she want?
I don't know.
She asked me to tell you.
As if I don't have enough problems.
When I just see cancellation emails
for three days, I have vertigo.
We're not out of the woods.
-There she is.
-I saw her.
Thank you.
Mr. Férey.
Any trouble?
Yes. I have questions.
I'm listening.
I'm cold,
I will swim a little.
-So?
-So,
was it you that sacked Jojo?
Yes, it was me.
It seems that Mr. Thibaut
asked you to do it?
Paul highlighted his alcoholism,
that is more accurate.
But it's not the only reason.
What other reasons were there?
You don't like syndicalists?
You know,
we are a small business.
I think it's better
to resolve issues ourselves.
And it seems the staff
don't complain.
That's good!
They won't come and complain,
if they'll get the sack after.
They're really beautiful,
these pools. They're lovely!
But that must cost a lot.
Was it Mr. Thibaut who covered it?
How?
Is Mr. Thibaut the owner now?
It is not that simple.
I've kept the position of--
Don't care. He's dead.
Now that he lives on
the boulevard of death,
his widow now holds the reins
of the business. Garance, that it?
Was it you or your wife
that convinced Mr. Thibaut
to invest in "Aqualand"?
I don't think I understand.
Which one out of you two
used their charms
to save your hotel?
Miléna and I have
been married for 20 years.
We are still very much
in love with one another.
Well done!
At the same time, I understand,
she is good.
I'm talking about the water.
A little bit hot, but good.
You'd be pissed to lose all of that.
What are you trying to insinuate?
Nothing, never mind.
In fact,
do you know where Jojo's tools are?
What tools?
His tools!
He got fired,
he can't pick up his tools.
He needs them.
You know where they are?
I know nothing!
No, I don't know!
A big toolbox disappears
just like that!
It's a bit shady.
Well listen,
if he's really lost them,
I will reimburse him.
That's nice! You know
how the proletarians are.
As they say, "A good workman
is someone with good tools,"
so he wants his own tools back.
It'd be good to sort out
him getting back his big toolbox.
We could call it a severance payment,
seeing how now
there are no more labor laws.
Accroche à ton cœur...
Un morceau de chiffon rouge...
What's up?
Pardon me, sorry...
I scared you?
Yes.
I am looking for tools.
Georges' tools?
Yes. Mr. Luc asked me to find them.
Listen, I think these days
we have other things to do, right?
Yes, of course.
So go back home.
As long as there are no clients
it's no use being here.
Right?
-Yes, Madam
-Thank you.
I looked for you.
Elementary, my dear Brière!
The kid ran away.
What kid?
Marin. When we got
to the courthouse,
he asked to go to the toilets
and escaped.
But no, what an idiot!
We've got roadblocks up.
Comissioner wants helicopters.
But well, he is
incandescent with rage.
What an idiot. They'll kill him,
the trigger happy cowboys.
And another thing.
We got the DNA results
on the hair found on Thibaut.
And?
Nothing on file.
We just know it's a woman's hair.
Seeing the pedigree of
the old charmer, it's hardly a scoop.
What are we doing?
Move your ass, Brière!
What should we do?
You're funny.
In any case, when the fruit is ripe
and doesn't fall,
we give the palm tree
a good, hard kick.
Not the season.
Yeah, but we're in Alsace!
I saw this one coming.
I'll bet my head
she's going to kiss him.
Voilà!
Goodbye, my charming heir.
I will join you later.
I will get you from behind,
you won't be disappointed.
Nadia Comaneci ,1976!
Have to start yoga.
Jeannie Longo, 1985!
Go on, Marleau! Go on, Marleau!
Go on! Go on! Go on!
No, I didn't see him that night.
How could I know he came?
You swear?
Don't you trust me?
You think I killed him?
Je te demande pardon.
I am sorry.
If you knew how scared I was.
Scared of what?
Losing you again.
This time, I would not survive it.
Of course you would.
You're tough.
Today, I don't need you anymore.
You can't say that.
Everything I do is for you.
Everything!
I dance now,
to meet your expectations.
It's too late.
I felt betrayed, Mom.
I know.
At first, I hated them both.
Then, I wondered how she could have
managed to push him away.
Him! The father figure.
He who turned
all my female friends' heads.
It's not her fault.
He abused her.
She didn't succumb to his charm.
He made her drink and behaved
like the worst bastard.
I would not spit on his grave,
but today I know
I'm no longer his son.
Crap.
Come here!
Are you Clément Thibaut?
Yes. What do you want from me?
A little walk in the woods?
No, I'm joking.
Captain Marleau,
national gendarmerie.
Are you disappointed?
Would you prefer a walk in the woods?
I saw nothing that night.
I left my mom, I went into town.
Just wanted to drink.
You got drunk?
No, I went to see her.
Who, Coralie?
-Captain?
-Brière, what's going on?
I was told about a prowler
at Bois de Sambre on the D23.
Do you think it's Marin?
The description seems to match.
What shall we do?
Nothing! Don't mention it!
Where is the bois?
Six miles higher.
Thank you, Brière!
Crap!
Fuck!
Marin?
Marin? It's me.
It's Marleau. Can you hear me?
Come back, Marin!
This is not a joke!
There are Ninja Turtles
out looking for you!
They get you before me,
they'll take you out.
Marin!
Who we after?
A poor kid.
Not born on the right side.
He is part of the Gotha Ghetto
as Pinçon-Charlot would say.
What did he do?
He's accused of
your father's murder.
What?
And you think it was him who...
I don't think anything,
no more him than you, by the way.
Except there's a smear on his name.
You hear that, Marin?
Marin, respond!
It's night. He's run off.
You think?
You're right. I've missed him.
So then, you.
Why did you come back from Cameroon?
Is it for Coralie?
Yes. I needed to talk to her.
I left like a madman,
trying to forget, but...
You love her. Is that it?
Exactly. It's as stupid as that.
But no, it's not stupid.
It's silly, but it's not stupid.
Then when someone apologizes,
it's a relief.
It's not her that apologized,
it was me.
Ah, yeah?
And your mom?
Do you not think
she deserves one too?
Go on, think about it.
You going forward or back?
Forward or backward?
Running on the spot,
it's annoying.
Want a beer?
No, I want to go and run.
It'll do me good.
Move!
Hello, Captain!
You okay, Brière?
Mister.
Hi, how are you?
Go on.
How is it?
What's happening?
Police raid, Mr. Férey.
You already searched it all.
We will do it again
but it will not take long.
Luc? What is happening?
Perquisition.
What are you looking for?
The murder weapon. When there is
a murder, there's usually a weapon.
This is absurd.
Don't worry, they're trained.
No breakages.
By the way, I'd like to introduce
Mich. Well, Officer Michel.
He will supervise
this brilliant search.
Good day.
Do you know the chaos
that you are causing?
Yes, that... Miss,
tell me, what is
Garance Thibaut's room number?
-Room 208, Madam.
-208. Thank you very much.
Okay, let's see.
And you will do...
Are you sure you want to do this?
What do I say, Djokan?
-We shake the tree.
-And?
And we take care
not to get hit on the head.
No, I don't want you
to clean the room. Thanks.
If I leave my hoover in my pocket,
can I come in?
Come in.
Hi.
It's nice here.
That's funny!
You carpet's so thick!
Thought I was on the moon.
Hello, NASA ?
This is one small step for Marleau,
one giant leap for mankind.
What's going on?
Shouldn't you be rehearsing?
That's not so important anymore.
You know I met your son?
A handsome little wolf, Clément.
He knows nothing.
I know that.
Go on, put some flipflops
and a tutu in a box.
There's a show waiting for you.
And there are kids who count on you.
I do not know if I am...
Yes, you are! Of course you are!
Your friend is right.
The Slav in the leotard.
You are a beautiful person, Garance.
And you're a funny gendarme.
Not that I'm annoyed,
but duty calls.
Take care of yourself. Be careful.
Garance, I didn't tell you,
but I like your name.
It's a flower.
But it's also Arletty's character
in les enfants du paradis.
"Paris est tout petit pour
ceux qui s'aiment
comme nous d'un
aussi grand amour".
We're counting on you.
Vladimir, yes it's me.
I am sorry I'm late,
but I'm on my way.
It annoys you to start without me?
Comrades.
-So Brière?
-Nothing.
Nothing?
Okay, so let's pack up.
It's done!
-Hamdoulliah!
-Bismillah
I am disgusted we found nothing.
I hope we didn't ruin the souk.
Know that we remain
at your complete disposal.
You can tell your staff
we will call them in soon...
Yes.
...as we await the judge's sanction.
We will collect saliva samples.
For DNA testing.
DNA testing?
We have more than Sherlock Holmes'
magnifying glasses now.
"Progress doesn't stop," as said...
I don't know who. We don't care.
Very good! Super!
Okay? Yes, carry on.
Good, bigger.
Are you sure this crap will work?
I may be an old IT engineer
but I still know a few tricks.
And?
It's true.
You have beautiful relics, you know?
Is what we're doing legal?
To catch the bad guy
coming out of the woods
give him the means.
If not, you're like the little girl,
red coat, pot of butter.
And you'll do
the Last Tango in Paris.
And now?
Now, we breathe, we wait.
Yes, but if nothing happens?
It's harvest time!
As Yvette Horner used to say,
"Play the oboe,
make the accordion sing!"
-What are you doing here?
-And you?
Sooner or later,
these masks all fall.
Crap, my new trousers...
I always chase the stupid idiots.
Do not move! Put your hands up!
Hands up! Stop!
What does that mean?
-You all right, Brière?
-Yes, Captain.
It's over, Miléna.
In two or three days,
we will get the DNA results back.
They will surely confirm
that your hairs
were found on the body.
And? We ate together.
Yes. Your hair,
plus your prints, and the blood
on Jojo's hammer.
Even if you hire Dupont-Moretti,
your defense looks pretty bad.
And?
What exactly was there
between you and Mr.Thibaut?
Nothing. There was never
anything between us.
I love my husband, understand?
I love him so much.
He's the love of my life, and...
I didn't want this to happen
like this, I swear!
Was an accident.
You know what?
I will make you my princess.
We can't do this, Paul.
Why don't you want to?
I don't know. I just feel lost.
I regret it.
And the money I invested in
the business, do you regret that too?
Nothing to do with it.
What will your husband say?
When he learns you were my whore?
Kiss me.
How dare you?
Is that not what we've done?
You are really vile.
Get off me! No, get off!
I said come here! Shit!
See what I'm doing.
Calling Luc
so he can come join us.
No, please don't do that!
I won't be the only one
to suffer like a dog.
You have reached Luc Férey...
Give me the telephone!
Get help!
Call for help, fuck!
What are you doing? Stop!
I really wanted everything
to be how it was before.
That all that had never happened.
It's awful for me, for Luc.
I've screwed everything up.
You understand?
No, I don't understand.
A crime in real life
is not like at the cinema.
You don't leave saying,
"Get me some popcorn."
But get out of your bubble!
Real life is out there.
I pity you.
Yeah?
One minute.
Oh wow!
One comment, and it's a spin kick
in the plexus!
You are a beauty, Captain!
What did I just say? Poucave.
Who's that there?
Léon, Zitrone.
Come to heel, dogs!
No way!
Look who's back.
For a guy who dislikes trannys,
you don't leave the bush.
I wanted to thank you
for believing in me.
What do we do with him now?
We know the score. We go.
Got holiday.
Take it, won't be long!
If you're interested,
I won't lock the door.
There's beer in the freezer.
Coming? We'll be late.
Don't like late.
Nobody asked you.
GARANCE "PASSIONS"
It's not the moment,
but how did you know
it was Mrs. Férey?
I don't know.
Do you know Jean Marais?
Jean Marais said,
"If Lagardère won't come to you,
sort him out so he will!"
-I love you.
-I am so proud of you!
Well done!
Subtitling: Hiventy