Joséphine!
Joséphine, are you there?
Open the door, for God's sake!
I know you're in!
Come on, Jo!
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was angry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I'm sorry. Open up!
I can explain.
Shit.
BETWEEN WINDS AND TIDES
No to the marina!
These fanatics
could scupper the project.
They'll soon tire of screaming.
- No, they're not kids.
- You're right.
Kids wouldn't be such a pain.
A spanking and off to bed!
- You should talk to them.
- And say what?
That it will improve their lives?
That they can play golf
and paddle in the infinity pool?
This marina is a special place.
Do you see?
It's a bridge between sea and land,
between wind and...
Believe me, the guys outside
won't be won over
by your megalomaniac arguments.
Tell them it's going to create
many jobs.
You're aiming to swap their trawlers
for yachts!
They're not stupid.
Everyone knows
the marina isn't a charity!
Everyone can enjoy
the scenery.
Oh, that's good!
That's what you should tell them.
Your clients will throw them
peanuts
over the railings
of your fortified city.
I don't understand you.
Nadia, are you no longer
behind the project?
But of course.
Only I'm not deluding myself.
You're building the Tower of Babel,
I'm preparing the elections.
I don't claim to be doing it
for the good of mankind.
Listen... I still think
you should speak to them.
I don't know... To reassure them.
Meet their spokesperson.
Their spokesperson is your sister.
She's always been a pain.
Even when it comes
to the Christmas menu.
She's a loudmouth.
What can I do about it? Muzzle her?
There's a thought!
Even with a muzzle on
she could bite.
Bastards!
No to the marina!
If the mayor refuses to see us,
we'll smash everything up!
I'll smash everything!
Your sister-in-law can't ignore you.
You'd be surprised!
She despises me.
Think we might dirty your carpet?
Family meals must be a laugh!
She doesn't come to them.
She thinks I smell of fish!
Look at them! The king and queen
are at the balcony!
They might throw us some coins!
Sailor
Her skin is soft, take her with you
Make her relive
her childhood memories
What's Vincent up to?
He should be here already.
You look lost without him,
the providential man.
- Without him, no marina.
- Without his money, you mean.
Blood red suits you.
You'd think it was invented for you.
Hello, Vincent. How are you?
Look, I've finished the model.
I've done one too, in 3-D.
Look.
Your sister's boathouse.
Surprise...
The Kersaint-Gilly estate.
The five-star hotel.
The 18-hole golf course
and the lighthouse,
lit from the inside.
Wonderful.
Hello?
What?
Christian de Kersaint-Gilly has died.
No to the marina!
Am I late, Mum?
- We've been here an hour!
- What can I do?
Punch them?
We're in enough trouble as it is.
Yann, don't!
Are you scared the people
will chop your head off?
Someone's died at Kersaint-Gilly.
- Who is it?
- Christian de Kersaint-Gilly.
Two bullets.
Ingrid.
Ingrid!
Nan, you scared me!
Your grandfather has died.
The police are on their way.
The police? What's going on?
He was murdered,
shot twice with a rifle.
Who did it?
What happened last night
between your grandfather and me...
Don't tell anyone.
- No one.
- OK.
Hello.
It happened early this morning.
Could be a hunting accident.
Really?
What have we here?
The mayor, Nadia Quemener.
Some mare!
- Hello.
- Nadia Quemener, the mayor.
Captain Marleau, CID.
Sorry. I get my hands dirty
in my job.
What have you found?
It won't be easy.
There's mud everywhere.
Finding clues amid all the leaves
and bowels...
I know all the local hunters.
Some drink a bit,
but they'll own up if they did it.
That would be helpful.
Otherwise it'll be
premeditated murder.
That's not so good.
Tell me...
Christian de Kersaint-Gilly...
His estate is in the way
of your marina project, isn't it?
What are you trying to say?
Nothing.
I just thought I'd mention it.
I'm looking for his wife,
Joséphine de Kersaint-Gilly.
Do you know where she is?
At home, I guess.
It's big.
I'll start with the south wing,
then the west and east wings.
It's huge!
Hey, ma'am!
I've not found her.
Silly bitch!
Are you OK?
- How do you feel?
- I don't know.
He was an old fool.
You call everyone that.
Even your grandmother.
But there's a difference.
My grandma's a fool
with panache, humour, even cruelty.
My grandpa
was a fool soaked in whisky.
And your dad?
Thank goodness he's often away.
That makes him a bearable fool,
almost likeable.
Have you told him?
Is he coming back?
I guess so.
You look pissed off.
No, I'm fine. It's just that...
I think your dad could have won
the Route du Rhum this year.
Stop living the races vicariously
through him. Just do it!
My mum needs me on the trawler.
She can hire someone else!
And yes, my dad is still at sea.
Jo tried calling him,
but he didn't pick up.
Listen, I'm sorry.
Don't worry, I'm here.
You deserve credit.
My grandma's treated you
like you've got the plague for...
- Ten months.
- Ten months? How awful!
Remind me to dump you pretty soon.
- Really?
- Yes.
Yann.
Joséphine doesn't want to see him.
Jo thinks he's a lout.
But I know what she really means.
What?
She's stuck in the 17th century.
She thinks he's below
the Kersaint-Gillys.
Don't judge your grandma.
You can't understand.
I'd like to kiss my boyfriend
without her calling the police!
She's just lost her husband.
Well I've just lost my grandfather!
That kid's got a temper!
Captain Marleau.
I'd like to see
Joséphine de Kersaint-Gilly.
Are you the baby-sitter?
I am Ferdinand Lebovitz,
Joséphine's doctor.
That's what I thought.
You're some kind of baby-sitter.
Can you show me the way?
Thanks.
Hello.
Wow! That's some place!
Don't let appearances fool you.
Thank you.
Impressive.
Don't judge her
on appearances, either.
Oh?
- Are you coming?
- Yes. Nice rifles...
There are four.
Yes, come in.
Ferdinand...
Hello.
Marleau, CID.
Kersaint-Gilly... widow.
My condolences.
Joséphine, you've been smoking again.
I can smell it.
No, you can smell the wood.
I hope you won't lie that brazenly
when I question you.
But you won't question me
with as much frankness.
Right. Question number 1,
a standard one:
Did your husband have any enemies?
- Did he have...?
- Enemies.
Yes.
People loved to hate him.
Enough for him
to take a stray bullet?
I don't know.
I don't know...
We led separate lives.
He did his own thing.
Women? Men?
No, cards.
Women too, I think.
And alcohol.
Anyway, he...
He'd have thought this death
was quite stylish.
Sure. To die alone
in the woods at night
with a bullet in your chest
is very stylish, very classy.
What's that on your neck?
Are you hurt?
No. I was scraped
by a branch in the woods.
Looks like it was
a 5-fingered branch.
5.30. It's time for my series.
I can't miss an episode,
I don't know how to download it.
Goodbye, doctor.
Goodbye, ma'am. See you soon.
Is the questioning over?
She's not stupid.
Even though she tries to look it.
What is that on your neck?
Don't ask, Ferdinand.
Has your father been told?
We can't reach him.
Has something happened to him?
We'd have heard. You always do
when something goes wrong.
Yes.
- You OK?
- Yes. You?
Gwen, come and unload the crates.
No. Pretend I wasn't here.
- Please, honey.
- Mum...
I don't want to smell of fish.
No one'll notice,
other than your PC.
I don't want to revise
while stinking of the sea.
Don't be such a sissy.
You can shower later.
It's such fun to hobnob
with the common people
when you have a handle
to your name!
Your sister bites!
Drop it.
- How's the fishing?
- It's not great these days.
Still, it pays the rent.
I've even bought a caravan.
Not everyone's as lucky as me.
No.
Is your grandma bearing up?
She's not one to talk much.
As straight and pale
as an Easter candle!
When is she going to join in
a demonstration against the marina?
My grandma at a demonstration?
Are you joking?
Is she for it?
She just doesn't care.
When the Quemeners
and their corrupt property developer
come to buy her land,
what will she say?
She'll chase them out with a rifle.
Maybe we should slow things down.
Leave people time
to grieve for Christian.
- What's it got to do with us?
- Are you serious?
They're burying him today.
The solicitor will summon his wife.
Everyone will be watching us.
Who do you think they'll suspect?
His wife.
You're wrong.
Yesterday, the new cop,
the strange pale woman,
was waiting for me
outside my house.
- Did she ask you about Christian?
- No, actually.
No, she just ate her sandwich
and watched me leave.
- Did she speak to you?
- That's the thing.
She just stood there chewing.
I went over to see her.
Did you want to see me?
Who, me? No.
What are you doing here?
I'm eating my sandwich.
- Is that all?
- That's all.
I left and she stayed there
watching the car.
She might be a car enthusiast.
She's a cop.
If she was smart,
she'd be in a different job.
Your swimming pool,
your casino, your golf course,
your 5-star hotel...
your town on the water,
your glass lighthouse...
It would be a shame not to build it
because a bankrupt aristocrat
took a stray bullet.
Talking of which, Vincent...
Was it really a stray bullet?
- You don't think...
- Sorry, but...
You always insist on remaining
in the background.
What do you want me to do?
Show off my cash?
You'd need three lifetimes
to spend it all!
By the way, where does
all that money come from?
I made a pact with the devil.
No. Seriously, Vincent.
If it's not a matter of ego
or money,
what makes you tick?
That Marleau is a pain.
She's just called me in
to ask me
my nail varnish's
reference number.
I'm joking, but only just.
They're all over the place.
Now's the time to strike.
What do you mean?
Ever heard of shock strategy?
What are you doing?
Have you gone mad?
You get people in a state of shock
and you use their distress
to gain the upper hand.
You reassure them
and they're putty in your hands.
So what do we actually do?
Christian's time among us
has come to an end.
Lord, grant that he may
rest for ever
in peace by Your side.
In the name of the Father, the Son
and the Holy Spirit.
Hello. Do you want a handkerchief?
I don't have a cold, miss.
Your granddaughter doesn't look
very Catholic, like you.
I'm protestant
and she's a bit of a protester.
And where's your son?
- He's at sea.
- Ah... I don't like the sea.
Ah, the doctor. Hello.
Has he taken care of the nasty wound
you had on your neck?
What caused it?
A branch.
Nobody's touched it.
That's right. The 5-fingered branch.
That's funny.
The killer could actually
be at the funeral.
He must be tall,
judging by the firing angle.
Or average height, I don't know.
He's a nice kid.
I like him.
Why did you say
you couldn't stand him?
I said no such thing.
Oh...
The mayor and her husband.
They're a right pair!
- Friends of the family?
- No.
And who's the new chap?
I don't know him.
Vincent Salmon,
a property developer.
The marina was his idea.
He's very discreet.
What did your husband think
about them wanting your land?
He must have approved,
since he sold them some of it.
- It must have pissed you off.
- Yes.
- Post mortem.
- Post mortem...
Goodbye, doctor.
Ferdinand.
Sorry.
Ma'am...
My deepest sympathy.
Your husband was a dear friend.
My husband was surrounded
by bastards.
I forgot to ask you something.
The night your husband died,
where were you?
- I was asleep.
- That makes sense.
Didn't the shots wake you up?
I'm a deep sleeper.
I sleep with one eye open.
- Luckily, it's not a glass one.
- Yes.
Who was that woman at the funeral?
A cop.
A poor old cop.
If ever I die, don't bury me.
It drags on and on
and you get mud everywhere.
I wouldn't wish it on anyone.
You'd rather be cremated?
And have my ashes scattered
like Scarlett O'Hara's.
She wasn't cremated.
I'm thinking wide-open spaces.
What if you stink of fish
for eternity?
- Eternity has no smell.
- Whatever.
Do you think it was
a stray bullet?
Well he was no saint, but still...
I liked him.
You love anything that has to do
with Kersaint-Gilly.
You should hear yourself!
"Not too tired, Jo?"
"Can I hold your umbrella?"
"You're so elegant!"
Well, she is elegant.
And Christian was classy, too.
If you'd seen him reeling after
a poker game you wouldn't say that.
He played poker?
He frittered away his fortune.
He was addicted and always lost.
- How do you know?
- Eh? I forget.
- By hearsay.
- You've played with him?
- A couple of times.
- Honestly!
- You wasted our money!
- It's Mum's money.
- How dare you judge her?
- I'm not like him.
I win.
How come I'm not a criminal
with role models like you?
- It's not as if...
As if you'd ever smoked dope?
Only once. I was very stressed.
Sorry.
No.
- Does she have a boyfriend?
- I wish!
That's Etienne.
He calls every other day.
She never mentions it.
I don't know what they're up to.
- Do you want one?
- No, thanks.
I'm sorry.
I was dealing with another case.
Are you all right?
Have you seen this? Look.
I've just bought it.
It's an 1887 Chicago.
Watch it glow!
We've known each other a long time,
so I won't beat about the bush.
You inherit the castle
and its grounds,
but also the 140,000-euro debt.
I can't afford that.
Part of it is paid off.
Your husband has sold
part of the land.
Here's the bill of sale.
"In accordance with a deed, etc.
"Mr Christian de Kersaint-Gilly...
to Mr Etienne Quemener."
To Etienne Quemener?
What did he sell?
The clearing.
That can't be right.
He can't have sold the clearing.
Our granddaughter lives there.
All the properties are in his name.
The deed is legal.
The sale doesn't cover
the whole debt.
You still owe 80,000 euros.
My sincere condolences.
He was like this.
Bastard!
What are you doing on my land?
- Poaching? Setting traps?
- Outlining the lighthouse location.
- What?
- The lighthouse. Don't you know?
Quemener are building
a glass lighthouse.
It'll symbolize the marina.
You're on my grandma's land.
It's my boss's plot.
That's impossible.
Go and ask your grandma.
Now let me work.
A lighthouse?
You didn't know?
It's Etienne Quemener's crazy plan.
But why on our land?
That was your grandfather's
crazy decision.
Did he sell the castle?
Not the castle,
but the clearing.
That's where I live!
What are you going to do?
What can I do?
I'm drinking my tea.
That's all.
We must get the clearing back
and prevent them from building.
We can't.
They've signed.
Dad wouldn't let them do it.
But your dad's never been around.
You drink your tea.
I'm going to stop them fleecing us.
Do you want to do something useful?
Of course.
Pass your exams!
- OK, Arthur?
- Fine.
I've got red mullet today.
Listen...
Poach it with a shallot,
drizzle it with melted butter:
your wife will swoon.
Good. I'm not in her good books
at the moment.
- I'll have three.
- It's a deal.
Maurice, how would you like
to impress your mother-in-law?
Hello. Sorry...
Carry on, I don't want to interrupt.
Never. To what do I owe
the honour of your visit?
Don't be sarcastic.
I'd like to offer you
an interesting deal.
Maybe we could discuss it elsewhere.
- Richard, take over for a minute.
- It'll take longer than that!
Come on.
What's it got to do with Gwen?
Your daughter
is more sensible than you.
I don't want to sell my boathouse.
Where would I keep my trawler?
You would sell us your trawler too
and take shares
in the company with me.
"Quemener Brother and Sister"!
What's the plan?
I have it here, look.
Instead of your boathouse,
there'll be a spa
with an infinity pool and the like,
opposite the casino.
You can see it better here.
Look.
Who'll go to your casino
and your spa?
People here can't afford that.
It's going to attract
a more luxury clientele.
You'll be able to ditch the fish.
Who said I wanted to?
Don't you want to earn 5,000 euros
a month without lifting a finger?
To take some time for yourself?
I take time.
Before going home, I go for a walk
and look at the sea.
The sea is beautiful, and it's free.
Yeah. But don't you want to buy
your children apartments for later?
Do you think your son's
going to do that all his life?
If he likes it...
What if he was to end up
like his dad,
killed at sea?
- Have you ever thought of that?
- All the time.
When he goes out,
I worry he won't come back.
How will you afford your daughter's
studies to be an architect?
She'll do what I did,
she'll get a job.
That's why you never studied
and you can't make ends meet.
Stop thinking about yourself.
Think of your children. Don't let
this opportunity pass you by.
I mean it.
I was just talking to the kid
who's working there.
He's cute.
He told me your grandfather
had sold up.
Your grandma can't have known,
or she'd have been mad.
Of course. Wouldn't you?
My grandparents lived in a caravan.
My grandma used to say: "Only the fox
has silver to his name."
Whereas your grandma
wouldn't be pleased about it.
Jo doesn't let herself
be messed about.
Fair enough.
I wouldn't let my husband
sell my clearing.
I don't have a clearing or a husband.
But Joséphine is right to fight it.
Have you seen the marks
on her neck?
All for a clearing!
It wasn't just about the clearing.
Really? I thought it was
because of the clearing.
The bank had called her
and demanded 8,000 euros.
Joséphine told me.
She said to your grandfather:
"You're gambling away
your granddaughter's inheritance!"
He lost it and grabbed her throat
and said: "Shut up, woman!"
Not only that.
He shrieked so much I was scared.
I went out, he left,
and I never saw him again.
The next day he was dead.
See?
Your granddaughter
talks more than you do.
What did you say?
You didn't know?
- You tricked me?
- I didn't trick anyone.
People trick themselves.
Don't they?
Goodbye, ma'am.
- What did you say?
- I'm sorry.
Hey! You're a nutcase!
You're...
Do you enjoy scaring me
or what?
Creeping up on me like a cat.
Shock technique.
Remember?
Sideration. Now you'll be willing
to offer me a drink.
So, your sister?
She decided
she needed time to think.
Typical.
Anything to save face.
She has to sell.
As long as her boathouse is standing,
there's no project.
Don't exaggerate.
We don't need the infinity pool.
People will pay for the view.
Without that view, no marina.
That's the opposite
of what my sister says.
My sister says:
"You can't buy the sea."
She's naïve.
In Greece, tour operators
have accomplished a miracle:
they sell the sunset.
People could watch it anywhere.
But some guys in an office
had a brainwave:
they convinced tourists to pay
to watch it together in one place.
Genius!
That's a first-class con.
They're not forcing anyone.
My sister says the marina
will drive prices up,
and that the fishermen
will have to leave.
So she's not naïve.
But I think I hit a nerve:
her children.
Gwen, come here!
Gwen!
Come and do some housework.
Or is it too tiring?
Jerk!
That's enough!
Take a break.
We need to talk seriously.
Your uncle came to ask me to sell him
the boathouse and the trawler.
For the marina?
Never!
Wait, keep a cool head.
It's a generous offer.
Enough to start you off in life.
What about Richard?
He won't get another job at his age.
I know.
But your sister could concentrate
on her studies
without needing to get a job.
Tell her you'd rather work
than put a man out of work!
His wife's in a wheelchair.
His salary is hardly enough as it is.
I'm for the marina.
What? Are you having a laugh?
The world is changing.
We're not going to fish cod
forever!
You want to sail around the world,
and now's your chance.
So I sail to the Caribbean
and leave Richard to croak?
But Uncle's project
will create dozens of jobs!
Have you seen it?
It'll turn the village
into a fortress for millionaires.
Do you want to watch them
eating lobster
while we won't be able
to afford hake?
I'll be dining with them, jerk!
Who's the guy planting stakes?
One of your uncle's employees.
- Would you like a coffee?
- A small one, please.
My grandfather sold them this plot
to build a glass lighthouse.
But what about you?
I'm staying here
and I'm going to resist.
What if they throw you out?
I'll go on a hunger strike.
They'll never finish building it.
I'll do what Penelope did:
every night, I'll destroy their work.
Have you spoken to him?
He's cute, right?
- It's a joke.
- It's not funny.
What's up?
I'm really cross with my sister.
What has she done?
She wants Mum to sell
the trawler and the boathouse.
- I know.
- How? Did she tell you?
Not exactly.
She thinks the project may be good
for the town's economy.
Your sister's got great vision.
She's smart.
I know that.
My famous gifted sister...
Next to her, I'm considered
to be the family dunce.
But I love losers.
I'd told you not to
set foot here again!
I'll always be here
when Ingrid needs me.
- Leave her to revise!
- I've never stopped her.
You're a bad influence on her.
Now she wants to stop studying
and become a foreman!
You know very well
that she makes up her own mind.
Let me do what I'm good at,
which is dry her tears.
You should follow my example.
Go home now. Go on!
What are you doing here?
Hello?
Hello. I'd like to speak
to professor Ferdinand Lebovitz.
Yes. This is Jo.
Yes, he knows me.
Doctor, Joséphine de Kersaint-Gilly
is on the line.
Joséphine?
Ferdinand, I saw them.
They were kissing.
We need to separate them urgently.
After her baccalauréat,
send her to study in the UK.
She'll forget him.
She no longer wants
to sit her exams.
She won't want to leave either.
She's stubborn and...
No.
Then there's only one solution.
Tell them the truth.
No, never.
I've come to make you an offer,
a very generous one.
- For whom?
- The two of us.
It's simple: you need money
and I'd like to buy you out.
You've already got the clearing.
You can watch me from the lighthouse.
Don't try to be smart with me.
I know you're broke.
Excuse me, I have to pour myself
a whisky.
And I only share it with friends.
One million.
For the castle and the woods.
No one will offer you a better price
for this ruin.
Go.
Goodbye.
You can turn me down once or twice
to save your honour,
but you'll end up selling me
your castle.
I'm not for sale,
and neither is my land.
You've been very quiet recently.
The boss is getting worried.
The project is coming along well.
- Just a couple of details to settle.
- What details?
I've bought one plot at the castle,
and the old fool has to sign now.
Thanks to us,
she's piled up huge debts.
You mean she still hasn't signed?
It's a matter of days, honestly.
Cécile's more of a problem.
She's tough.
Wait.
So let me get this straight...
You've made no progress at all.
Right?
You do know the boss
needs this marina?
Eh?
You do know
we need to launder this money?
We've had enough of your excuses!
We're stepping it up. Today.
I understand.
- Hi!
- Hi.
- I've brought croissants.
- What's the occasion?
Tarek won't be laying
his concrete today.
- What have you done?
- I took his tools.
Your grandma'll be proud.
No. She's letting them do it.
It's as if she was stunned.
I want to move it up a gear.
What does that mean?
We can't just watch them
concrete over the coast.
I suggest we start
actively bugging them.
Oh, yeah? How?
We take their tools,
we ruin their work,
we put chewing gum
in their car locks,
we siphon their tanks...
- Yes...
- Yes!
- You're on!
Yes, we're on!
- You too?
- I'm too old for all that.
I'll resist differently.
I'll sign so the police release you.
Thanks.
You're very quiet, Gwen.
You just mess around.
I've got exams in four months.
A coffee? Come on.
Enough kissing, now.
We said coffee.
You again.
Hello, ma'am.
I have a question for you.
You said you were asleep
when your husband died.
But where was he?
He was sleeping, I guess.
I often sleep in my office.
He sleeps upstairs.
An upstairs room?
That's not good because...
The coroner says your husband
died around 5am.
He was going that way,
so he must have set off from here.
Yes.
Maybe he was going hunting.
That's not a bad idea.
Hunting...
Hunters get up
at the crack of dawn.
He didn't have a rifle.
You're Diana the Huntress,
aren't you?
What are you getting at?
Do you think I killed him?
I'm not accusing you
of having killed him!
Who mentioned murder?
Nobody. Not yet.
I'm talking about his shoes,
covered in mud.
I walked from your house
to where he was found.
It's about 100 metres.
My shoes didn't get as muddy as his.
I see.
What else do you want to say?
Not much.
I'm just saying
that as his shoes
were much muddier than mine,
he walked more than 100m.
He'd come from I-don't-know-where,
he knocked on your door...
He didn't have any keys.
So either you were there
and didn't open the door,
or you weren't there.
I was behind a bush
and I waited for him with a rifle.
- Is that what you think?
- I don't think, I'm a cop.
I look and listen, that's all.
I'm just a state employee.
What?
I'm telling you he came here.
- I counted. 1, 2, 3...
- Enough!
Don't go off in a huff,
Mrs de Kersaint-Gilly.
He was here. 1, 2, 3.
Just about here.
Or else he went to the chapel.
He went to...
Before the hunt,
he went to pray for game.
She's crazy. Crazy!
What if we ran off?
Just you and me?
What do you mean?
- Now?
- Well, yes.
Nobody cares about us here.
Gwen gets all Mum's attention,
your grandma hates me,
and your dad's away.
My dad did everything
when Mum died.
He changed my nappies,
fed me my bottle...
He even stopped sailing.
That's right. I'd forgotten
your father was a saint.
Do you know many men
who stay single for years
after their wife died
and they're left with a baby?
My dad was devoted to me.
He knew what ice cream I liked,
how hot I wanted my hot chocolate,
he plaited my hair,
kissed me better when I fell...
So yes, my dad's a saint.
I just need a change of scene.
It's stifling around here.
- Where would we go?
- Anywhere!
New Zealand, Australia...
Singapore...
- What do we have to lose?
- What do we have to gain?
We'd be free to love each other.
Wouldn't that be great?
But I love you here, too.
Forget it.
I get it.
You don't want to leave with me.
My dad took me with him on his boat
until last year.
We sailed round the world
for 4 years.
4 years without school,
without friends,
without lessons,
without a timetable.
And I get seasick!
Now I just want to stay here,
with my feet in the mud.
Come in.
Nadia.
It's nice to see you.
How long since you came to see me?
Six months?
Seven?
You've missed me? Really?
Oops! How about a beer?
At 10 in the morning?
Only kidding, Nadia.
I'll have a coffee.
Strong, three sugars.
Yvonne,
an espresso, no sugar,
and a strong one,
2 sugars, for my sister-in-law.
3 sugars.
Given it some thought?
Yes.
I won't keep you guessing.
- The answer's no.
- Come in.
Thank you, Yvonne.
You can't do that.
If you refuse, there'll be no marina!
That's right, there'll be no marina.
What about your children?
How kind of you to ask.
They'll be happy to hear from you.
- I wasn't elected to waste my time.
- Quite.
Nor were you elected
to put the fishermen out of a job.
Is that all?
Get out of here now!
Shit!
Shit.
- Are you moving out?
- Only my furniture.
The bailiff's here.
And you agreed?
I wasn't asked for my opinion.
Goodbye.
I think you should
leave us alone now.
I'll make a complaint.
I'll come back with the police!
Hey guys, leave the sofa.
This lady can't sit on the floor.
All right.
Come in.
I'll make some tea.
The privilege of old age.
- Thank you.
- That's all right.
I grew up seeing more bailiffs
than teachers.
Over time I developed
an allergy to them.
You're not talkative.
No.
I like that.
You seem to have problems.
Yes, and you're one of them.
Yes, I know.
Your granddaughter told me.
She told you that?
Ingrid's frank.
I noticed.
What are you going to do?
Wait for death,
listening to the wind in the trees.
No...
Just build your lighthouse
and I'll try and save
what's left to save here.
- And the bailiffs?
- I don't know!
I preferred it
when you didn't talk.
Why is the sofa outside?
You can't just burst in.
Be polite and say hello.
And thank the young man
who managed to save my sofa
from the bailiffs.
What's he doing here?
- I'll leave you to it.
- I'm sorry, Tarek.
Forgive her, Tarek.
Stop sucking up to my grandma.
You want to take
the rest of her land?
I've not taken anything from her.
I'm just an employee.
What's the problem?
- You like stopping me from working?
- Yes, actually.
I can't work without my cement.
If it goes on, I'll be fired.
That's your problem.
Good riddance!
- What have I done?
- You work for jerks!
- You got better to offer me?
- Get lost!
One more Arab out of work
won't change your cushy life!
Bye.
- Uncle, what a surprise!
- Hello.
- Were you just passing by?
- We need to talk.
Is something wrong?
- No, it's all good, don't worry.
- OK.
- Come on.
- Sure.
Hello.
Your wife has called 3 times.
- Hello, miss.
- Hello.
Look, Gwen. There's my project.
It's nice, isn't it?
The marina represents the universe,
the union of the four elements:
water, earth,
air and fire.
The lighthouse represents fire.
It's made of glass, it's lit up,
and it looks down on the marina
like the Tower of Babel on the world.
- Cool!
- You like it?
- Yes.
- Take a seat.
I've had a chat with your mum.
She told me.
I hear you're going to study
architecture in Rennes?
I'll have to work to pay the rent.
That's your mother's choice.
She can't afford much.
No.
She doesn't want to help you.
I asked her to team up with me
and she laughed at me.
And you're the one who suffers.
Don't worry, I'll manage.
I do hope so.
Thank you.
Your project is great.
Gwen,
I've got a proposal for you.
Would you be interested
in doing a training course with us?
Think it over.
We'll discuss it again.
I see the bailiffs have been.
They took my sofa out.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- You're my doctor, not my banker.
What will you do now?
I don't know.
It's going to be complicated.
Christian left me
an 80,000-euro debt.
Captain Marleau told me.
Since you know it all,
what do you suggest?
Come and sit down.
- Do you want to sell up?
- No.
I love this place too much.
We're attached to each other.
Do you remember when Renan
played down there?
He'd built a little boat.
He would salute
before casting off.
- You remember that?
- Yes.
And when he pretended
to be shipwrecked,
he'd shout:
"Women and children first!"
I miss him.
That, that, and that...
It's all that.
If it gets built, I'll lose my job.
I'm 58.
Do you think they'll hire me
as a waitress in their 5-star hotel?
Could I be a bouncer in the casino?
- We have to save the harbour.
- Of course!
Calm down, calm down.
Quiet, quiet.
We'll get organized.
Calm down.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
- Tell me.
- Leave me alone!
The boathouse!
Oh, no!
We'd better do something!
What happened?
- Come on.
- Yes.
Hello.
Nasty fire.
Thank goodness the firemen came.
Otherwise I'd have lost my trawler.
It's quite a coincidence.
It caught fire
while we were out.
Do you have many enemies?
Why?
Fires don't start themselves.
It wasn't in the engine?
It started underneath.
First source of fire.
Then a second one here
and a third behind you.
Three sources of fire in one night.
That's a hell of a coincidence.
How's the fishing?
Sometimes it's better than others,
but we survive. Why?
No reason.
I was just thinking...
When a business is struggling,
it's good
to claim off the insurance.
You think I burnt down
my boathouse to hit the jackpot?
Are you kidding?
I wouldn't dare accuse you.
I'm just saying
that it's been known to happen.
Well, I wouldn't destroy
my source of income.
Nor that of my partners.
Don't get angry.
Are you paranoid?
Having said that,
people are right to be paranoid.
So who do you think
would want to light a barbecue
in your boathouse?
- Salmon and Co.
- To build their marina.
- Salmon is linked to the Quemeners.
Would your brother
have approved?
Before he met Salmon,
I'd have said no,
but I'm no longer sure.
And what do you think?
I think they did it.
- How's it going with Gwen?
- Very well.
Don't worry, I'll be supervising
your internship.
Never.
Yes. It's settled.
I'm moving in with Yann.
Is it because he's not an aristocrat?
Don't try and understand,
just obey me.
Obey me and don't see him again.
I don't have to obey you.
You're underage and your dad's away,
so I'm in charge.
In 5 months, I'll be of age
and I'll leave.
You'll do what you want.
In the meantime,
pack your bags, we're going.
They want to live together.
The more you try and separate them,
the closer they'll get.
So we should just watch them
move in together, kiss,
and have kids?
Calm down, Joséphine.
It's a waste of time.
You're single
and you don't know
the first thing about love.
- I'd better go.
- I've hurt your feelings.
No, but I am a bit stunned.
That's the best solution.
We'll leave.
But they'll find each other again.
She'll soon be 18,
so she'll be off.
- We'll go far away.
- She'll catch a plane,
a boat, a coach, anything.
They'll meet up again.
The only solution
is to tell them the truth.
No. Never.
- Jo, please.
- No.
Never.
Never. Never.
Yes. But the terms have changed.
300,000 for the lot.
It's daylight robbery.
Value is not set in stone,
you know that.
Yesterday you threw me out,
today you want to sell.
Things change.
Can you bring us
the sales agreement please?
What are you doing here?
An internship.
Here?
What's it to you?
Well...
Ask your mum
how she kept her house
after your father died.
With her fish?
Don't insult my mum.
Ask her for her balance sheet
and how she managed.
I don't understand a thing.
Give me the papers.
She left her scarf.
Do you like your job?
Do you hate plants and flowers?
Do you prefer the sound
of the pneumatic drill?
Or do you never think?
Answer me, you bloody idiot!
Did you have an argument?
No. Well, a little.
- Do you know where he is?
- No.
Do you think my brother
confides in me?
I hoped so...
- You OK, girls?
- Yes.
- What will it be?
- Hot chocolate.
Thanks.
- What did you argue about?
- Nothing.
Answer me.
I'm a bit confused at the moment.
My mind's in a mess.
- Do you love him?
- Lots.
That's not what I asked.
Do you love him?
Yes. A lot.
- Did Yann not come?
- No.
I waited for half an hour,
then I had to leave.
Where can he be?
I don't know. Ask Ingrid.
Gwen says he left because of her.
A broken heart.
At that age you think
you'll never get over it,
and then you do.
Well, sometimes you don't.
What's the problem?
What should I do with the crates?
Where's your brother?
Richard waited for him all morning.
What's wrong?
Joséphine sold her estate
to Salmon.
They're leaving, Mum,
her and Ingrid.
So it's all over for us.
How do you know?
I brought her the papers to sign.
She implied that she
regularly gives you money.
Is that true?
Yes. When you were one,
she opened a bank account
to pay for your studies.
But why? Why for me?
- It's a long story.
- I have plenty of time.
I'll explain.
When you were born,
I was depressed.
I was in Ferdinand's clinic.
He treated me.
What's the link?
After your birth, I got worse.
One day, I decided to end it all.
I jumped out of the window.
Joséphine was there.
Nobody had heard
of postnatal depression.
She thought I might kill myself.
She wanted you to be secure.
But why me and not Yann?
She was your godmother.
You never told me!
We argued.
It was about Yann, in fact.
She said things to me
that a mother can't hear.
Joséphine took care of me
and you nearly killed yourself.
Any other secrets
that I should know about?
I recognized your footsteps.
How are you?
Well, I'm still standing.
I came as soon as I heard.
What happened to Dad?
God knows... I don't know.
A hunter must have
mistaken him for a wild boar,
or maybe it was a mistress.
With him, who knows?
Honestly, Mum! He's just died.
Yes. Sit down.
- Nice party.
- I'll go and see those arseholes.
Gwen.
Gwen! How lovely to see you!
You look radiant.
Hello, gorgeous.
- I love your earrings.
- Thanks.
Gwen, thanks for coming.
You sounded stressed.
Is everything OK?
I wanted you to share
our success.
This is Gwen, our new intern.
I'd like us to raise our glasses
to her.
Gwen, thanks for coming,
thank you for your smile.
Thanks for being here.
Could you say a word?
Today, thanks to the sale
of the castle,
we are on our way
to modernizing the coast.
We can bring it into
the 21st century at last!
- Bravo!
You shouldn't smoke.
It'll damage your perfect skin.
What is it to you?
There.
- Is that how you deal with things?
- You could say that.
What's up? You look sad.
Family issues.
I don't want to talk about it.
They don't want you
to do things your own way?
I don't want to go into it.
Family... a nest of vipers.
Relax, Gwen.
Live your life.
- What time is it?
- 9.
Already? I'm ashamed.
I never sleep this late.
My mum says the early bird
catches the worm.
She's wrong.
It's the bold bird that gets it.
Coffee?
- Croissant or chocolate bun?
- Croissant.
We've got to talk.
That was uncalled for.
A little gift.
Hey, what are you doing?
Preparing concrete.
Good.
And can you tell me why?
For the lighthouse.
Don't you live here?
I do, more or less.
And you?
Me too.
Well not really, no.
I came with the build
and I'll leave with it.
The locals
aren't very cooperative.
Do you mean the young girl
who lives there?
Yes, for instance.
- Do you know her?
- A little.
She's my daughter.
You're back!
- Look at me. You've changed.
- You always say that.
Because you're always changing,
getting even prettier.
What have we here?
- Are you an anarchist now?
- It's against Jo.
What's all this
about a lighthouse?
Grandpa sold the clearing.
And Jo wants us to leave
to take me away from Yann.
- Right.
We're making progress.
Joséphine has sold up.
And Cécile Prigent?
I set fire to her shed,
but unfortunately
her son turned up
just at the wrong moment.
The boss wonders
whether you're up to the job.
Stop it!
I've been working on this
for months.
- By playing poker?
- I ruined Christian.
His wife sold up thanks to me.
I'll get to Cécile through
her kids, her daughter.
Gwen!
What's happening?
Where's Yann?
It's not Yann, it's Gwen.
It's going to be all right.
Subtitles: Eclair Group