Oh, could Logan just get five?
Welcome. How's your dad?
Oh, pretty good. He hopes to make it
in person to the next one.
- Oh, sure. Send him my best.
- I will.
But still, you're here, and that's nice.
Thanks. I feel the same way.
Great. We're all over the fucking moon.
What is this?
Yeah. So we are in discussions
to acquire GoJo.
Okay. How advanced?
Oh, not that advanced.
Just getting to outline terms.
So pretty fucking advanced?
Well, we didn't wanna bother you
until we have some protein.
But we didn't wanna ambush you in the
boardroom. We wanted to let you know in here.
- But you are still ambushing us.
- No, no, no. We are not ambushing.
Well, no, I mean, if you jump out on someone
on the road in the middle of the night,
hit them on the head and shout "I'm not
ambushing you," it's still a fucking ambush.
I love my business. But we've had our throats
slit on ads for 20 years. We're bleeding out.
Another five of cord-cutting
and we'll be dead on the fucking carpet.
This is a transformative deal.
Yeah, but, uh, just obviously,
this is not okay.
We were supposed to be
inside deal-making.
Well, you know, we're moving very fast
and it's all very sensitive, but I assure...
- I think they're assembling.
- Right. Shall we?
Okay. How will you feel if Matsson starts
micro-dosing and tweeting about angels again?
- Matsson's a visionary.
- Sure. Because he's tripping balls.
Well, he has a team we can do business with.
This is bigger than anything
you've ever contemplated.
It will reshape the company entirely.
Well, if you guys really,
really don't like it...
sure. Kill it.
Well, we didn't say that.
- So? Shall we? Finally?
- Wait, where is Shiv on this?
- Why isn't Shiv here?
- Oh, because this is just inner circle.
That's a joke, I'm kidding. I think
"The President" will be joining us, so...
- Yeah?
- "Hey. So..."
I think they're gonna eat it.
Sandi is processing, Stewy loves it,
Roman led. No Karl, no Frank.
Um, Sandi wants your take,
Gerri's trying to fill your boots,
but I don't think Sandi's buying it, and I'm
just following them now to the boardroom.
You in the car?
No. I'm gonna call in.
Well, that works. Is everything okay, honey?
Yeah, I just, I'm feeling
the way I was feeling still, so...
What about your mom's wedding?
I'm not feeling great,
so there's nothing really to say.
Right. Right. Well, maybe
you don't even really need to go.
To mom's wedding? Oh, yeah. Fuck that,
I'd never hear the end of it. Can you imagine?
So, the board members not physically available
will be joining by phone,
including Siobhan Roy, who sends
her apologies, she's working on strategy.
- And Kendall Roy, Hey.
- "Hey."
And Kendall Roy who's not attending
due to illness.
- And we're gonna lead off...
- "That's, uh, not actually true."
And we're gonna lead off with an update
on the promising developments
in the ongoing investigation
from which portion of the meeting
Kendall and Logan Roy are recused. Hence...
and then we'll move on to discuss
acquisitions.
Is he gonna watch?
I feel like I'm taking a shit
in the Guggenheim, y'all.
Could we make a note in the minutes
that he's watching us?
Hey, I know you. Didn't you used
to be Siobhan Roy?
You sounded dumb at the board meeting.
At least I showed up. What were you doing?
Brunching with some other sock puppet
girl-boss presidents?
You haven't got a date?
Did no one on Raya wanna come to Italy
and sit on your Ricotta dick?
So? Just to say, I had,
uh, Peter Onions rat-fucked.
Oh, what a lovely wedding present.
The guy's a fucking slime badger.
Three bankruptcies, two marriages,
four children, and five shell companies.
He's a big investor in shitty nursing homes,
tipping applesauce down their gullets and
telling them they had a four-course dinner.
- All the hits.
- Yup. So,
I've asked Mum if we can talk to her,
and I think we should do it together.
Do what?
"Do what?" Uh, like, ask her
if she should be doing this, you know.
It's like, five months since Rory
was supposed to move in.
Whatever.
Or we can at least check that
she's getting a prenup.
You know, there's a lot of shit in there
from the divorce,
the holding company and everything.
And the guy is clearly on the make, so yeah?
Fuck it.
Fuck it?
Yeah. Hmm, she's probably
in sexual thrall to him...
he's driving her
wild with his sugar dick...
- Nice.
- So, there's nothing that we can do.
All right, fine. Let him kill her
for her emeralds
and screw us out of the fucking firm,
see if I care.
Hey, Rome? About the deal?
Um, I was talking to Karl and Frank.
Yeah, no, but you're not really
a part of that, either of you.
- Well, I am.
- Well, I can't quite fire you yet, Shiv,
because I'm still a little bit scared of you.
But my thinking is, when I take over,
I'm gonna put you in the office next to mine
and you're gonna be my sexy secretary.
The fuck is wrong with you?
I dunno. We're working on it. Ongoing process.
Welcome, welcome. Follow me.
Uh, just a minute. Hello.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hello, welcome all.
Goodness me.
Did you just come back from the front?
Yeah. Just felt like it.
- It's dripping down.
- It's nice.
Hello, darlings. How are you?
How lovely to see you.
Don't you look lovely. So, um, you're all
going to be taken up to the house.
I'll be there in a minute, guys.
You look rather tired.
Thanks. You wanted a word?
Right. Yes. Um, so listen,
what I wanted to ask you,
you'll see when you go up to the house that
Peter has printed out this awful sort of
itinerary of events.
Uh, the welcoming and the rehearsals,
and the ceremonies, and...
and, um, I wondered if we couldn't
slightly divvy them up?
- As in?
- As in...
your father would rather not,
as I understand it,
be together with you, uh, as far as possible.
And so, what is your son getting,
and what is your ex- husband,
who you hate, getting?
Oh. Please don't get on your high horse.
It's not me, I don't mind. It's "Bridezilla."
He's got his heart set on having
all the important people at his wedding.
- He's such a little tart.
- Well, I don't know if that works.
Please, have a think.
And I'll still see you tons.
Yeah?
Peter! Come and say hello to Kendall.
- Kendall, like the mint cake.
- Yeah. Pleased to meet you.
- Absolutely.
- Okay. Mom,
I'll check the schedule,
uh, maybe see you next month.
- Come on, don't be so dramatic.
- Nice to meet you.
It's gonna be about four hours, Kendall.
This is nice.
- Hello. Hello, I'm Gerri Kellman. How...
- I am Viola. Nice to meet you.
- This is very nice.
- Yes, you will enjoy this place.
Italy! Pizza, pasta, and Popes.
You ever met the Pope, Con?
Yeah, uh-huh. I met one,
couple of popes back, with Dad.
He was a real full-fat Pope.
Complete Pope. Very religious.
I guess he really drank the Kool Aid, huh?
Wow. It's pretty.
Everything okay, Con?
Yup. Yeah.
Just, uh, the guy from Politico,
uh, asking regarding his piece,
your full name and, like,
your employment history, and whatnot.
Oh, right. You think he's digging?
Might be friendly. But, you know,
probably not. What do you think?
Yeah, it's probably friendly.
Because journalists are so fucking friendly
in my experience.
- Okay.
- Hey. Going to the welcome drinks?
Sure. Uh, let me just, um, check on Laurie,
and then you and I can put our heads together
on the GoJo price.
- Okay.
- It's ticking up, but nothing scary.
Laurie, Laurie, Laurie. You just
will not stop going on about him.
I think you're obsessed,
and frankly, it's disgusting.
Um, Laurie? We're gonna walk down.
Can you catch up?
- Yeah. Okay.
- Okay. Cool.
- Okay. So, look, I need to talk to you.
- Hi.
- I need to ask you something.
- Okay.
I need you to stop sending me the, items.
The which?
The dick pics?
- You don't want pictures of my dick?
- No.
- Okay. Kind of offended. Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- Okay.
- I'm fucking serious, Roman.
I'm not so sure, I feel like you do want them,
but you're being kind of typically minxy.
I think this happens
when you're under pressure or...
but you need to find
some other outlet, Roman.
Look at you, trying to get inside my head.
Don't open Pandora's Box.
There's just more dicks in there.
- No, she has a lovely house, quite.
- Yeah.
- But it's just all the same sort of cycles...
- Hey, mother. Sorry.
- Roman!
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hi, Ma.
- Roman, you know Peter.
- Yup.
Peter, Roman's worried in case
I'm throwing myself away.
He thinks I'm in thrall to you.
Other way around.
- Well, how you doing?
- Very excited about all this.
Yeah, yeah, of course. Me too.
And, uh, how's, uh, business?
I hear you're big in the old Silvery Gulags?
Yes. Helping to, uh, turn around
a nursing home group.
We, It's very rewarding. Come in,
look at the operations, trim the fat.
Yeah. He means the nurses.
She's very rude. I don't know why I put up
with it. And I'm very rude to you too.
- He is awful, I can obviously see that.
- No. No, no, no, not at all.
He's actually just your type. Another
in the line of post-dad posh, English phonies.
He's not posh. His father's a doctor.
Bought all his own furniture.
- He's a grasping little scholarship boy.
- Well, take it easy there, Mother.
That's my stepfather you're taking about.
He's forcing me into all of this,
this Toscana bit.
But he is tremendous fun. I mean, look at him,
fizzing away over there
like a bottle of cheap prosecco.
Hmm, very cheap.
Uh, Mom? Um, well, you know that
I'm not a big one for saying things,
but I'm just gonna say, are you, are you sure?
The guy has, like, four kids.
- He's got a lot more than that, my darling.
- Oh, great. That's fantastic.
There's a prenup though, right?
- Oh, come on. Don't be so unromantic.
- Mom, just...
I'm concerned that maybe you're rushing this.
So what do you expect me survive on?
Macaroni and memorial services?
Uh, excuse me for a second.
- So?
- Uh, yeah,
she says she can't live off
macaroni and memorial services.
Oh, wow, poor old Eleanor Rigby wants to
eat dick and drink champagne
- for the rest of her life instead?
- Yeah.
Apparently we're meant to hate Peter because
he was smart enough to get a scholarship
and bought his own furniture.
What else do we got? Any, any requests?
- Any offers?
- No, not really.
There's a sit- down, like a podcast,
- Uh, that's basically like...
- Okay.
ex-Globe journalists
who are doing sort of like a...
kind of like the Kennedys.
Curse of the Roys, deep dive.
Uh, they're doing Connor's mom, and,
uh, your dad and someone named Rose
and then the tabloid suicides.
There's like a kid who was bullied and
was it an accident or did he kill himself?
He was the caterer at your sister's wedding,
I guess. You know about that?
- Uh-huh. Sure.
- Right, so,
they're spraying requests
around the whole family.
- Maybe keep tabs on that one. Okay?
- Okay.
- Fucking bottom feeders.
- So unless it's weird I might fuck off?
- Yeah. Whatever. Clock the fuck off.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Okay. Very nice. Uh, how we doing?
- Yeah. Good, great.
- Absolutely. Yeah.
- I'm great. Oh, shit.
- Phone stuff. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah. Sorry.
No, no, uh, go for it.
- Thank you.
- Well, congratulations, Greg.
Yeah. Punching above your weight?
- Oh, Comfry?
- Uh-hmm.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah,
I like her, I like her. I do wonder...
- Can you hold this?
- Is there depth there?
- Like is there substance?
- Depth? Oh, my God.
The man dying of thirst
is suddenly a mineral water critic?
Does Comfry not sate your lust
for wisdom, Greg?
Such a shame Sontag's not still alive.
- You could take her to the drive-though.
- Oh. Yeah.
Maybe I wonder when she gets to know
the quote-unquote "real me", uh,
- will she stick around?
- Well, I guess either way,
if doesn't work out,
she's a great date ladder.
Excuse me? As, as in...
Well, you know, people will see her with you.
And no offense, but they'll say,
- "What the fuck's going on there?"
- "Why is he with her?"
Yes. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm aware of what you're saying.
- Yeah. Okay.
- It still could work for you.
Date ladder. Play the date ladder game.
- What about her? She looks nice.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- I mean, yeah, why not?
- She's pretty.
- She is very pretty.
- She is also a princess
- or a duchess or something, but sure. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Why not?
- Why not? We put a man on the moon.
- Okay.
- Okay. Wow.
Poor woman, she probably...
She thinks she met a fun guy at a wedding.
He should be coloured red
like a dangerous lizard.
Oh, no, Scary Poppins is on manoeuvres.
Can you, you know, just...
- Just block me from her?
- Blocking you.
You know, she knows that I'm not
in a good place and then it's all
- house of flying daggers, you know.
- Sure.
"How's your marriage going?
And, are you gonna have children?"
How is your marriage going?
Are you gonna have children?
Okay. Ha-ha.
Karolina.
"Going to Macao, feeling lucky."
Uh, Tom. Matsson.
What? Going to Macao?
Feeling lucky? What the fuck is that?
You see this thing from Karolina?
It's off the radar and now this?
- Is it, is this a move?
- It, it could be...
it could be nothing, you know.
Fucking social media fireworks.
- "Going to Macao, feeling lucky."
- Is he, is he trying to boost his price?
Is he just rocking the boat
or trying to blow up the deal?
I mean, has he got a good subscriber
numbers coming in?
Maybe he's just going to Macao
and he's feeling lucky. Maybe...
Hey, Lukas, call me. Are you high?
I think you should put down
the venti ayahuasca Big Gulp.
Uh, we need to be inside track
on these Tweets, man, okay?
Call me. I don't know, it's like,
it's his thing. He's a, he's a trickster.
Okay. Well, sounds cool. Is he gonna, like,
steal our watches
- and saw the fucking deal in half?
- Maybe.
- You're supposed to be inside this, Rome.
- I am inside this. Leave it.
- Hey, nice work, Rome.
- Hey.
- Matsson going nut-nut.
- Uh-hmm.
- Keep hold of that shit, bro.
- It's all under control, motherfucker.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Where are you off to?
- Naples, score some junk?
- No, just our mother
- throwing me out of her party.
- Oh, nice. Good. Well, so long.
Where are my kids? Hey, hey, guys,
where the fuck are my kids?
What a surprise? Ken doesn't know
where his kids are.
So look, um, I've been thinking,
who knows what'll happen,
maybe I won't ignite?
Maybe the two party system
isn't as rotten as it looks.
But I have to plan for success. So, Willa,
this is a difficult conversation to have.
Oh, okay.
- So you're okay?
- Uh, yeah, I don't...
just, uh, no, go on and just...
We can go back underground, you know?
Me in my apartment in the city,
you come visit, it's kind of romantic?
- That doesn't work for me. No.
- Okay.
Maxim had an idea, which is...
will you make me the most happiest man
slash most bulletproof candidate in the world?
- Oh, okay.
- Okay?
No, I, no, I mean...
Baby, baby.
People are looking, Willa.
Well, then I'd be pleased to say
yes, yes, yes. Can I?
Can I have a little think on it?
If it's okay, I'm smiling now.
- Right.
- Like you said yes.
Okay.
- But take your time.
- Right.
- "Grazie mille."
- Wow.
- So GoJo's price is moving up and fucking up.
- Yeah. I think he played you, Rome.
SEC's gonna be all over this.
Oh, yeah, oh, my goodness, gummy love bite
from the fucking toddlers.
I think he likes us, I do,
I can feel that in my gut.
Okay. Uh, another one.
Emojis, controller, fingers crossed, eggplant.
Maybe he's trying to fuck
a gaming site something with...
- Rome, this is bad.
- I...
- I think we're good.
- Oh, yeah?
If he blows this deal
then who is left for us exactly?
We could become the fucking Pan- American
Waystar-Blockbuster Video dial-up Corporation.
Okay. Here he comes.
And here she comes.
- He does not give a single solitary fuck.
- No. No.
Maybe it's all fine. Maybe they just share
a big bed together
and they watch Friends reruns
and drink milkshakes. Oh, hi.
- Well, your father made it, it would appear.
- And you know the story?
What? The skunk, the porcupine,
and the concubine?
Probably the best wedding present
I'll ever get. But so disgusting.
Is he still fucking Marcia, do we think?
- Uh, I think not is the word.
- Hope not,
poor old fellow would probably keel over
with the effort.
Oh, well, I gotta go around telling everybody
to be very discreet. Oh, and Shiv...
- you know about this awful thing later on?
- Oh, uh, yeah, uh, Rome and I have got a big,
we're working on a big deal and so, um,
we just got hit by a torpedo
- and it's not okay, I think.
- Oh, Shiv, don't be silly.
Go have fun with Mom, I can manage.
She's not even that involved.
Yeah? See you later.
- You're welcome.
- Fuck you.
- Logan, you came.
- How you doing?
Staying ahead of the Inland Revenue?
- Welcome to Toscana.
- Oh, glad to be here.
Anything I can do, just let me know.
Very kind. When we get the chance, I wanted
a discreet word with you about, uh,
- your contacts in UK government.
- Uh-huh.
It's just I'd like to give something back,
you know, the chance to serve.
- Logan.
- Ah...
- And what did he want?
- He wants me to get the dipshits
on Downing Street to make him
Lord Fucking Seat Sniffer Pantyhose.
- Did you read the Tweet?
- Yup.
- Have you spoken?
- Uh, tried, but...
I'm not used to negotiating via eggplant.
I'm not sure he wants the deal.
- He might just run a fucking moussaka.
- You want to try calling him again?
Um, okay. As long as he doesn't come here.
No. Hey, hey, you okay?
Yeah. I'm okay. Hey, Dad.
Ken, he doesn't wanna see you.
He doesn't wanna talk to you.
- Yeah, well this is all total horseshit.
- Okay? We had a deal. Jesus Christ.
Let's just have it out, okay?
I wanna see you, Dad,
I wanna see you for dinner
and let's just nail this, okay?
8, on your own. Yeah?
- He's busy.
- Sure.
- We'll get back to him.
- We'll get back to you.
- Oh, you'll, you'll get back to me?
- Uh-hmm.
You prick.
- Should I go?
- I don't know, maybe wear a stab vest.
I mean, it'll be okay, maybe you should go.
Get him out of the firm.
- You want me to come with you?
- Oh, fuck off. I'm not scared.
Get me some rooms,
I wanna get Matsson on the phone.
Okay.
- Hello, welcome, welcome.
- We're almost there.
Hello, my sweetie.
Oh, my God,
I didn't realize you were so...
- Hey, I'm sorry.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey, just busy.
- Managed to tear yourself away?
What do you think of Peter's daughters?
They're both in interior design.
- They're unemployed.
- Yeah. They offered to take photos
and I think they exported my address book.
- No.
- Yeah.
The bachelorette party.
My mother would turn in her grave.
Hey, Rome is kind of concerned.
You do have a watertight prenup, right?
Do you think he's gonna do me in
for Granny's fake Rubens?
- You've got a good lawyer at least.
- Yeah. Sure.
I'm actually having to open up
the divorce agreement with your father
- because Peter loves Eaton Square flat.
- Does he not got one his own?
Uh, he had a bit of bad luck
with a salmon-smoking business
and he lost his place in Pimlico.
Ooh. Quite the business brain.
- Got a very big heart.
- Well, I supposed opposites attract.
Should we just enjoy a fag?
And not do any sniping for a bit?
- Or have you come to get some attention?
- Me? Attention from you?
Oh, no. That ship sailed long ago.
Yeah. I might have been a bit of
a spotty mother,
but you've been a shitty daughter, so...
You weren't a spotty mother,
you were just an absence, but I'm fine.
I moved back to bloody New York so I could be
near you and I never fucking saw you.
Mom, it's okay. It's fine, you let Dad take us
and it was probably best.
I gave him custody so you could keep your
shares and I could protect your interests.
You chose.
- "I'll have the carbonara and Daddy, please."
- I didn't choose anything.
- You tend to get what you want anyway.
- And you don't?
I don't think I've ever won
a single battle in my whole life.
I was 10, Mom. I was a fucking kid.
You were 13, and you knew
how to twist the knife.
You knew then and you know now.
And I might cry.
Oh, yeah, where's the onion?
You were quite a piece of work.
You were my onion. You are my onion.
Yeah. Well, you're my fucking onion.
Truth is, I probably should never
have had children...
You made the right decision.
Some people just aren't made to be mothers.
I should've had dogs.
- Well, you could've had dogs.
- No, not with your father.
He never saw anything he loved
that he didn't wanna kick it
just to see if it would still come back.
Okay, what's this?
Okay, so your dad called a bunch
and Matsson won't take the calls.
Matsson hates the phone.
That's nothing, I told Dad that.
He left me a voice memo,
the Tweets were just fucking around.
His lawyers have given him the Reg FD scares.
He's flying back to his Swiss place.
There's clarification coming.
Yeah. Well, your dad thinks
Matsson's trying to humiliate him.
Well, he's not. So Dad just
needs to ride it out,
- I don't think we need to panic, Gerri. Okay?
- I'm not panicking.
I think you are. Because
you're interrupting a great night,
I'm getting very pally with Laurie.
I might try to fuck him,
see how that fits into our disgusting mess.
Do not try to fuck Laurie. What do you think
about going to see Matsson?
- Yeah. Sure, does Dad want me to?
- Yes. Your dad wants the deal.
But, you know, they need a translator.
Logan needs reassurance
before the banker meet.
Okay, so you want me to save the deal?
Why didn't you say so? Piece of cake.
Save the deal, fuck Laurie,
lead the company into the promised land.
Fuck Gerri...
It's gonna be a great week.
Hey. I thought this was gonna be private.
I'm across a lot of shit and,
uh, she's monitoring.
Hang out wherever,
you guys can wait inside.
So I hear you were asking
all about the menu and my chef.
Some things are off the menu
for me health-wise.
You scared I'm gonna try
and Jim Jones you with an olive?
Well, I think they've brought some food
that's good for me.
Yeah. It seems a shame, you know,
Marco's a great chef.
So we checked in with your doc
and got the requirements.
Ah. So, what is all this?
You know, I got a lot to do.
- As ever.
- GoJo price is spiking
and your pal, Matsson, has got a screw loose.
So, I just wanted to talk to you, I suppose.
Look, I don't wanna get into it all right now
because if it's bullshit, I'll just leave.
Can we be civil and not pull our guts out
all over the table?
- Signore.
- Sure.
That one's for him.
- Where are the kids?
- They're inside.
- Iverson. I'd like to say hello.
- Sure.
Hey, kiddo. How you doing?
Good.
- You like mozzarella?
- Um, not much.
Try this.
There you go, try it.
Yeah. It's okay.
Off you go, go on. Kerry has got something
for you in there I think.
- Good night, buddy.
- Good night.
Who do you think I am?
You think I want you dead?
I'll be broken when you die.
How's the boy doing? Is he getting better?
He's, he's fine.
So look...
my thing is, I want out.
I think I thought I was
a knight on horseback, but...
- Yeah. that isn't panning out.
- Life's not knights on horseback.
It's a number on a piece of paper.
It's a fight for a knife in the mud.
Like, I don't really know
where my life goes from here.
Maybe I could...
I don't know. But I can't do Jack shit.
So, here it is, I wanna get a premium pay-out
from the holding. Two bill and a chunky asset.
Something you can realize
without shareholder input.
Maybe, I don't know, outdoor advertising,
podcasts, I keep Fikret, Jess, and I'm gone.
I'm a ghost, divested, off the board,
complete disinheritance.
Won't even speak at your memorial.
We're done.
Well, I need to think about it.
Well, you, you already,
you offered at my birthday.
- That was, uh, for fun.
- Dad,
we can't do this bullshit forever.
Maybe I want you close.
You can do the mail,
keep you rattling around.
I can't. I tried, but I thought
that I could change things, but I'm not as...
There's things you're able to do
that I can't, maybe.
Maybe.
You've won
because you're corrupt and so is the world.
- Well.
- I'm better than you. You're...
You know, I hate to say this,
because I love you, but you're kind of evil.
Don't talk about things you don't understand.
Well, you're smart, but what you've done
is you've monetized all the fucking...
The American resentments of class
and race and...
And I thought I was just
telling folks the weather.
You've turned black bile into silver dollars.
And you just noticed, did you?
- Yeah. Maybe I did.
- Oh, fuck off.
Fine, you know what?
I don't give a fuck.
Not everyone can live this life.
I'm a great revolutionary.
A bit of fucking spice. Bit of fun.
- Fun.
- A bit of truth.
Okay. Truth, okay.
I fucking know things about the world,
or I wouldn't turn a buck.
- Maybe.
- Not necessarily nice things.
Look, whatever, let me out, okay?
Pay up and let me out.
I don't wanna be you.
I'm a good guy.
How long was that kid alive
before he started sucking in water?
Yeah. Couple of minutes?
Three, four, five?
Long time, two minutes.
What were you even doing, huh?
Chasing a bit of tail?
Hey, are you queer? Did you try to fuck him?
Or was it just the drugs?
I'm better than you.
Sure. You're my son.
I did my best
and whenever you fucked up,
I cleaned up your shit.
And I'm a bad person?
Fuck off, kiddo.
Goodnight.
We're out of here.
- Hey!
- Hey. How was your night?
Awful. You?
Yeah. Roman implied that Peter
might have killed his first wife
and then he tried to goad Laurie
into talking indelicately about Gerri.
Let's have a baby.
- Yeah?
- Uh-hmm. Yeah.
- I'm gonna fucking fight, Tom.
- Okay.
Yeah. You don't just get given these things
in a house in the fucking Hamptons.
- Right. Right.
- No. You know, just get given the top job,
or ATN. I'm gonna have to fight for it.
Gotta fight Gerri and Roman and Ken.
But I can because I'm smarter than them.
- Yes, you are. Yes, you are. You are.
- I'm gonna fucking do it.
And fuck Dad, he can kick me
as many times as he wants.
Like ten or five years.
Get rid of Cyd, remake ATN.
- Yeah. Yes.
- And destroy it, raze it to the ground, yeah?
- Right. I mean, except me.
- Yeah. Yeah, except you.
You know, and Matsson's got dad spooked.
So I'm gonna have to find him a better deal,
a bigger one.
I'm gonna do it and
I'm gonna fucking nail it, too.
And what, what about me?
- In the...
- Together. Yeah.
Because we can't let
the dirty little pixie become king.
- No.
- Yeah. Blow up Roman,
and I'm the only candidate left in the field.
Let's do anything, yeah? What do you...
Yeah.
- What do you wanna do to me?
- You're so fucking hot.
- Just tell me anything, do anything to me.
No, you, you...
You say anything to me. Go on,
mistress Siobhan Roy. Go on.
You're not good enough for me.
Oh, right. Oh. I see.
- Well, let's see about that.
- Yeah.
- No, I'm way out of your fucking league.
- Yeah. Oh, you think so? Yeah?
- Yeah.
- That's why you want me.
- Maybe.
- That's why you love me.
Fuck you.
Even though I don't love you.
But you want me anyway.
Hey.
- You crept out.
- Yeah.
Sleep well?
Oh, yeah. Really good. Lots of sleep.
I'm sorry for waking you to ask,
but I'm curious obviously.
Yeah. No worries. Yeah.
- Yeah, still thinking.
- Still thinking?
Yeah. Big decision, real life decisions,
- so just...
- Yeah.
- Right. Right.
- Thinking away.
Just, this much thinking
could start to get unromantic.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Just saying.
- Hey. Oh.
- Hey.
- Wow. Is that the time?
- Excuse me?
Oh, just checking the old watch there.
I can't believe it.
Um, what are you up to today?
- I don't know, work shit.
- Work?
- Yeah.
- Or...
Okay, because, I thought, or I've overheard,
that you actually, not to intrude,
but I thought maybe you were part of
the titled monarchical, uh...
sort of situation if that's not
too bold to say?
No, sure, but I do a bit of, uh...
I'm an online brand ambassador.
A fermented yogurt drink.
- Fermented yogurt?
- Yeah.
Well, I've had that. Yeah. It's really good,
- It's a gut cleansing treat.
- Is it really?
- Hey, dipshit. Hands off.
- Hi.
Hey. I'm just off to save the world.
Should be back for dinner. Greg...
Would you please keep the Contessa company,
but don't look at her,
everyone knows what you're thinking
and it's disgusting, bye-ya!
Sorry about him.
Lorry, How the hell are you?
- I'm good.
- Yeah. Good to see you.
My cousin. A very rude man.
GoJo price has lurched, and held.
- Power of the Tweet.
- Yeah. By midweek,
their market cap is gonna be close to ours.
I don't think that Rome can find
a landing zone for this.
You okay?
That was pretty spicy pillow talk last night.
Yeah. Yeah. You ready?
Yeah.
Thank you.
But it did, it got pretty, um...
it got pretty, you know, when you said,
"Say something filthy"
or "Do something dirty."
Yeah. I was just being horrible for fun,
you know, dirty fun.
No. It was dirty, but this morning,
you know, I feel a little, um...
a little afterburn, you know.
Like I was thinking more like love beads,
or, you know, I'd be a sexy fireman and...
It was kind of got into the realms
of that you don't love me.
Okay. Well, what happens in Sex Vegas...
Right, right, yeah, no, I know,
but then sometimes I think, um...
Sometimes I think should I maybe listen
to the things you say directly in my face
when we're at our most intimate?
Tom, you can't...
Oh, my God, you can't ask someone
to say terrible things and then get all...
That's a bit manipulative.
- Right.
- Yeah.
But did you mean it about the baby?
Yes. Yeah, I...
Yeah, I think so. One way or another.
- You know, we should freeze at least.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
You know, embryos survive
way better than eggs.
So we should put it together
and then see where we are.
Okay. And when do you think that might be?
Well, I don't know, Tom.
I mean, it's important that
the host chamber is willing.
Well, they keep them for 10 years and then,
you know, you can do what you want,
but it's different if one of us dies
or is in a long-term coma.
And, no. That's, it's true, you decide
beforehand what you would want to happen.
And, you know, I don't just automatically
get them if we divorce,
or something like that,
if that's the thing that concerns you.
No, I just, I wouldn't have necessarily
thought about all of that.
Uh, well I just think it's smart
to bank some embryos
and then, you know,
we can see where we are.
So we could be looking at,
like, ten years? That's ...
Ten years is like two and a half Olympics.
When you put it like that it's...
No. It'll get clearer.
I just think it's a good option.
And then if something happens or, you know,
you change your mind,
they destroy them, it doesn't bind you.
I would want you to have my babies if I died.
- Aw, thank you.
- And if you died?
Would I want...
Yeah, I think so.
- Can I think about it?
- Sure.
You know, Tom, I do. I may not love you,
but I do love you.
- You know.
- I know, I do know. I do know.
- Well, baby popsicles, baby.
- Baby popsicles.
Don't fall in.
Nope.
Do you want me to hold your hand?
- Hey.
- Come on, I'll hold your hand.
Piss off.
Amazing place.
Yeah.
- No?
- I don't know.
It kind of freaks me out to be honest.
- Oh, yeah?
- Well, when I got it,
I wanted everything to be
absolutely perfect.
Now, I'm sleeping on a camping mat
on the floor
until I get a deep dive on
the best mattress in the world.
- So, It's great. It's great, but...
- Yeah.
I'm just not feeling great.
I mean, I'm fine.
- Well, but not really.
- Okay.
Maybe let's leave the little
feely-feelings out of it,
because I'm gonna give you nothing.
- Nothing.
- So you got a view here,
- of the lake.
- Sure. Water and boats.
- Yeah. Right. A lot of water.
- Have a gander.
Hey, what are you worst at?
- Me? Yeah. Worst?
- Success doesn't really interest me anymore,
it's too easy.
Like, analysis, plus capital,
plus execution. It's fucking...
Anyone can do that. But failure,
you know, that's a secret,
just as much failure as possible,
as fast as possible, just burn that shit out.
- Well, I...
- That's interesting.
I'm not telling you a single one
of my weaknesses, ever.
Ever, ever, ever. Never ever.
- That's smart.
- I know. I'm smart.
Because I ream people.
Juice them like oranges.
No, look, seriously
I get way too into people and,
and then they disappoint me.
Hey, I'm thinking of doing, like,
a quarterly up or outs at the company.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
Firing people is like 85% of why
I get up in the morning.
But, uh, do wanna ask you about
that Tweet, if you don't mind.
- Oh, that one?
- Yeah. Seriously. Yes.
You got, like, big shit coming your way?
Dude, are you, are you asking me
for material non-public information?
I mean, I don't know. Were you trying to
give your share price a pop
by Tweeting unverifiable information
outside normal disclosure channels?
No. You're not allowed to do that.
- Yup, yup.
- So mean.
The thing I need to know is, do you want
this deal? Are you into it at all?
- Yeah, I am.
- Okay.
I'm just a little Swedish, you know?
I'm, uh, into equality.
- Okay.
- I like getting into bed with people,
but I also like sharing it equally.
Okay. Okay. It's just, I'm heading to Milan
to lock things down with Dad and the bankers,
and...
The Tweet just didn't feel great.
And if you're hoping to just blow this
whole thing up, just tell me, okay?
I just wanna get myself
the best of everything.
Okay. Fuck yeah. I get that. Definitely.
- Hey.
- Hey. So?
- So I think it's over.
- What?
Yeah, I don't think Matsson's interested
in getting acquired.
I think he's angling for a merger of equals.
- Okay. Fuck. Well?
- So it's dead, right?
- Are you sure?
- Well...
I mean, I don't wanna pile
on the pressure, Roman,
and obviously there are always multiple ways
forward and I don't wanna overcook this,
but, in terms of deals that make sense,
if we don't beef up soon,
I think we end up someone's lunch.
Well, thanks, Ger. I'm already
so stressed I'm jerking dust.
You want to tell him together?
I'm not really inside the details, so...
Okay. Sure. Well,
it was nice knowing you then.
Yep.
So before we get the whole three- ring
circus in here,
just among friends, I wanna get
a sense of what's going on.
Is he a Twitter panty flasher?
Or is he a serious person?
- Well, he is a serious person.
- You're certain?
Yes, Shiv, he is serious. But,
Dad, he, um, he thinks there's value
that hasn't been priced in yet.
Matsson's gunning for a merger of equals.
So I guess, you know, that probably...
- Merger of equals?
- Yeah.
Like he's got 12 of the prime Asian
sports leagues signed up for GoJo,
and he's gonna fold it all in to the platform.
Live sports, games, betting.
It's a fucking growth bomb.
Okay. But, uh, full 50-50 board, all stock.
Dad, what, splits control?
Yes, Siobhan.
Well, I don't think, Dad?
But the guy isn't a fuckhead?
No. The Tweeting was a move.
Well, he's not some big baby
who shits for clicks?
No. No. He's on the snake.
You know, I know people, Dad.
I'm a people sniffer.
Because I can win any bout with a boxer fuck,
but I don't know how to knock out a clown.
He's not a clown. He's a motherfucker.
It's what you would have done, right?
He just maximized his leverage.
Yeah, but "merger of equals?" Like...
- No such thing.
- Always a top dog, right?
Sure. And I mean he wants the label, but
I think we could still be
the puppy fuckers here?
The family stake will be seriously diluted.
I think he'd let us craft it so that
we keep balance of the board.
I think he just wants the freedom
and the status.
GoJo Royco. I mean, who gives a fuck?
Let him have the logo, we take the wheel.
Yeah, I mean, it would be real scale.
It's a legitimate way of staying relevant.
It's a big upheaval.
Yeah, I mean the top team will, they'll...
You know, you'll be obviously be
fighting for your lives.
But I'm sure you can trust Dad, guys.
Obviously.
Merger's really a state of mind, right?
Dad, Gerri, you stay
with your hands on the tiller.
I mean, their price rise, it's real.
It's a proper fucking streamer.
And the future is movies, TV,
music, games, sports,
eSports, VR, AR, betting,
fucking everything, for everyone,
and Matsson knows how to get there.
- Logan?
- We can't afford to walk away right now.
Must be worth a conversation, son.
Bring them in. Let's get the banker
fucks in here on this.
Okay. Fucking A.
Right this way. This is Tom Wambsgans,
he's the Chairman of ATN News.
- Hi.
- Hello. How are you?
- Good.
- How are you?
- Shiv Roy, President of Domestic Operations.
- Glad you're here. Gerri Kellman.
- Sit wherever you're comfortable.
Nice to meet you.
I need five.
Dad?
Uh, Jesus. Fuck.
Um, yeah, that's his dick.
He's sent you a picture of
his dick by mistake.
Well, it's pretty obvious.
Yeah, he meant to send it to Gerri.
I don't get it.
Well, honestly, he's weird about Gerri,
everyone knows it. And frankly,
I think it's fucking disgusting.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, Gerri is probably just
not stopping it for leverage.
You know, banking it as ammo.
Isn't he just Roman being Roman?
No.
No, I mean, no, I think it's a
potential problem.
There's issues, you know?
Everyone says he used to get jerked off
by his personal trainer.
And now there's this Gerri thing.
It's a track record, you know?
- So I think, you know, moving forward...
- Okay, okay. Okay. Well, thank you.
- Thank you, Pinkie. Uh, go on.
- Okay.
- Roman!
- Jesus, fuck.
- Hey, put in a good word for you.
- Thanks.
- Are you a sicko? What is this?
- Oh, Jesus.
- Why do you send them?
- God, it's just, you know,
it's like, "Here's my dick."
Oh, what? Like a fuck you?
People just send each other pics
of their dicks.
- People send each other pics of their dicks?
- Yeah. Have you heard of dick pics, Dad?
Well, we do publish a number of popular
newspapers, so yes, son,
we probably invented the fucking words.
But why?
Why? I don't know. It's just like,
here's my dick, I guess.
You got a problem?
What happened to that nice
piece of tail you were with?
Tabitha? Yeah, she's amazing.
We're having some issues and, um...
What interests you in Gerri exactly?
Jesus, Dad. I'm fucking, I'm screwing around!
I don't like things going on
I don't know about.
She's a million years old. It's fucking
disgusting. You're a laughingstock.
Oh, go on. Oh, go on, fuck off.
So like what happens now?
I don't want her hanging around
like frozen fucking piss.
Gerri? Uh, I'm not a radical feminist, Dad,
but I think perhaps we should not fire her
for receiving pictures of my dick.
Are you gonna come back?
Sorry about all this, Gerri.
It's just something I wanna get, you know,
really clear about what's going on, you know?
And most importantly, to see if you're okay.
- Uh-huh. It's not a big deal.
- Okay. Yeah, I just wanna get things clear...
for my dad, you know?
God, this must be so hard for you.
- It's fine.
- Do you wanna...
No? Okay. So has this or something
like this happened before?
I can't recall.
And if it did, did you ask him to stop?
Let's talk about this tomorrow, okay?
I just need to check in with some people.
Okay. Well, sure. I mean, it's not...
It's not as if you were welcoming these
items, were you, Gerri?
Shiv.
Look, it's just something for your wellbeing
we need to get really clear about,
because, you know,
with all this potential upheaval,
and you being in such a delicate position
as interim CEO,
if you can't deal with your own sexual
harassment, then it's not a good look.
I can cope.
Okay. So do you wanna make a formal
complaint against him regarding this?
Well, that's for me to decide.
I just think, Gerri, that you should report
him to HR, because if you don't,
it could be argued that
you welcomed these photos,
and that just undermines
your position. It's just...
That's my concern for you here.
I wonder if we shouldn't just kick this
all the way up to the board?
Well, thank you for giving this
so much thought.
- And, uh, I'll think it over, okay?
- Okay.
- So I'll see you back inside.
- Let me know.
Hey, Dad, I think I'm gonna head
inside with Soph.
Okay, buddy.