Previously on This Is Us...
Rebecca?
I'm Matt. Matt Dickson.
Would you like to_ I don't know_
Grab a cup of coffee or something some time?
Uh, I'm-I'm gonna go pay.
You fixed the fridge.
Thank you for all you're doing to help.
You're too good to us.
RANDALL: You are still a junior in high school,
and you will not be going to visit your boyfriend
in Boston again
any time soon.
Well, that's gonna be a problem.
Oh, hey, you remember
Elijah, right, from book club?
Why are you calling me
in the middle of the night?
KEVIN: 'Cause I was about to
call my co-star for a booty call,
and you live across the country,
and I figured you were the better option.
♫
REBECCA: Okay, Bug, are you ready? All right.
Okay, find C. Ah. Perfect.
Here. Yeah. There you go. Ready?
♪ C, C, C.
♪ C, B, A, B, C, D...
JACK: Ladies and gentlemen,
-we are witnessing history in the making here.
-(giggles)
We've got the famous,
stunningly talented
and beautiful mother/daughter music duo,
Kate Pearson, Rebecca
Pearson, playing their very first
song ever together.
Here, this is where it all started.
-Daddy, you're distracting me.
-JACK: You know what?
You're gonna want this for
your Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
induction ceremony, trust me.
-Okay, Bug.
-You want to try it again?
-Mm-hmm. -All right.
♪ REBECCA: C, C, C...
♫
(sighs)
(audience laughing on TV)
I do that only because I'm not sure!
-(laughter)
-MIGUEL: Phone a friend!
-Phone a friend! (laughs)
-What? Phone a friend?
You do not phone a friend at the $16,000 level.
-MIGUEL: Really? I don't...
-REBECCA: Come on. Bug.
Bug, come, watch with us.
We just saw this teacher from the Midwest
...win $125,000.
-Yeah.
You know, sometimes, I lie in my bed,
and I think about how sad my life is,
and then I come out here, and I see you two
glued to this couch watching Regis
and his monochromatic ties five nights a week,
and I think to myself, "Huh, it could be worse."
I like Regis's ties.
I'm going to Molly's, so try not
to rage too hard while I'm gone.
Okay.
Geez.
We're not that sad.
No, no.
-Are we that sad?
-No.
I went out with my work friends last month.
-I had a margarita. And you...
-Wow.
...you're dating, right? You're
dating that woman you mentioned.
Marguerite, but it's not serious.
-Oh, but still.
-(♪ telephone ringing on TV)
-One margarita. One Marguerite.
-(laughs)
-See? We're fun.
Yes.
(laughter on TV)
(TV clicks off)
-You know, um...
Rebecca, you...
you mentioned that you'd be, um,
open to getting yourself back out there, right?
Well, a friend of mine from work
told me about this speed dating thing
going on at Petey B.'s this weekend.
15 guys, 15 girls
sitting across from each other
for three minutes at a time...
15 dates? That is way worse than one.
Rebecca.
It's time.
You can't just sit here with me
every night for the rest of your life.
♪
Okay, Hailey, you want some sweet potato?
-(babbling)
-(gasps) No sweet potato.
Thanks for putting the laundry away.
-You didn't have to do that.
-REBECCA: No big deal.
I know you have a lot on
your plate with Toby gone,
and I love doing laundry.
Mom, no one likes to do laundry.
I do.
I love folding baby clothes.
-It reminds me of when you guys were little.
-(♪ phone ringing)
Oh.
Hi.
Hey. How's my beautiful family?
KATE (over phone): We're
good. We're just drawing,
and sweet potato-ing. Are
you headed to the airport soon?
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
What's going on?
So, Amir invited a bunch of
us to watch the Giants game
from his yacht on McCovey Cove
tomorrow afternoon.
-Whoa.
Baseball with the boss.
Yeah. Apparently, it's a very modest yacht.
But I can still fly home.
No, no, no, no, um...
No, you should do it. You
know, get that time with Amir.
-Really? You sure?
-Yeah.
As long as you explain to me
what a "modest yacht" is. (chuckles)
I think it's just a canoe with a toilet.
Thank you so much.
This means a lot. I love you.
Love you, too.
You know, I can stay with
the kids tomorrow afternoon
while you go to school.
It's not a big deal.
You know what?
You haven't been to the school since last year.
Do you want to meet us there?
Yeah. I would love that.
(chuckles)
(knock on door)
That's it. I knocked. I'm coming in.
Listen, they're doing something
cute. Come here. Hurry.
Take a look. Come on. Hurry
up, hurry up. You're gonna miss it.
-What? What? What are they doing?
-Watch this. Look, look.
-Look at this. Watch this, watch this.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Nicky, Nicky. Hey, hey, bud.
Can you point to your sister?
-KEVIN: There she is!
-(Madison laughs)
That's very good!
Look at that. Oh, she's clapping for him!
-Oh, what a good sister you are. Yeah.
-KEVIN: Aw.
She's obviously such an empath, right?
-Proud of him, yeah.
-I mean,
-that's not normal how kind she is. Yes.
-No.
-Such a good sister, huh?
-ELIJAH: Hey, Maddy, I'm gonna order a smoothie.
Do you want one? I don't know. I'm just_
I'm feeling a little snacky.
-Uh, no, thanks. -ELIJAH: Hey, Kev.
-Hey.
You know what? I forgot.
You got a big weekend, huh?
Uh... It's just...
going to Pennsylvania for 48
hours to check on the house
that I'm building for my mother.
Wow.
That's the side of celebrities
that people don't get to see.
Eli and I were just hanging out.
You were hanging out in the bedroom?
Uh, yes, Kevin, because I am a grown woman.
Also we were mainly watching YouTube videos.
-Elijah, shush.
-(chuckles)
-But the kids are gonna miss their
daddy so much, aren't you? -Yeah.
Yes, you are.
Hey, um,
we were going to take them to the zoo tomorrow.
Are you okay with missing first zoo?
Yeah.
Yeah. No, it-it's fine, it's fine.
You can have first zoo.
They watched their first episode of Entourage
this morning with me, so I am all set...
-Oh.
...as far as formative experiences go.
-Hey, Kev.
-Huh?
Should you and I exchange numbers?
You know, just in case.
Yeah.
-That's a great idea. What's yours?
-No, no, no.
Just AirDropped it to you. Poof!
(imitates whooshing, chuckles)
(laughs) It's in your phone.
(line ringing)
(♫ phone ringing)
-Hey.
-KEVIN (over phone): Hey.
What're you doing?
Well, I'm officially at my lowest point
since the divorce was final last month.
Matty left for five days with Ryan, and...
currently cleaning up his Pokémon cards
and trying not to cry.
Um, listen, I have an idea.
Why don't you
come out with me to the cabin this weekend?
There's an extra room, and
Uncle Nicky's supervising
the construction. I'm sure he'd be...
happy to see you.
Oh, and he's bringing his new girlfriend.
Uh... I mean, yeah, I could...
I could do that, maybe.
Wait, is this a sex thing?
Oh!
(stammers) Um... No.
No? I mean,
we are both adults, right,
who have slept with each other in the past.
Uh, we're both very single,
both very lonely.
I don't know. What's-what's your temperature
on this being a sex thing?
I mean, I could go either way.
It'd be nice to know, though,
'cause it'll change my packing and grooming.
Of course. Yeah.
I mean, am I open to it? Yes.
Am I expecting it? No.
Did I ask you with that in mind?
No, but then-then you said,
"Is this a sex thing," and I-I...
-I perked up.
-Oh, my God.
Send me the address. I'll be
there by tomorrow afternoon.
See you there.
RANDALL: Hey! Greetings,
wife of mine.
-How's things?
-(inhales sharply)
Hmm...
Mm... Mm.
-Whoa.
-Mm.
-Good day?
Not really.
I'd say it was a borderline crappy day.
There's meetings and red tape,
lackluster lunch salad.
-I keep telling you, you have
-to have a carb at lunch, baby.
-Yes.
-I told you that. Get a potato in there somewhere.
-(chuckles)
But it is Friday night,
and I have the entire weekend ahead of me
with my beautiful, overworked wife.
Including a romantic dinner tomorrow night
at the Thai spot on 9th
Street with that branzino.
Ooh, the branzino. That's a sexy fish.
Okay, and after that, I'm thinking maybe we
do a little dancing. What? What?
-No. No.
I'm gonna have to burst this fantasy bubble
before I get too depressed.
We can't do tomorrow night.
Sí, se puede. We can, and we must. Why? Why?
Um, because Deja said that
Malik is in town for 24 hours
and wants to have dinner with us tomorrow night_
Correction, make dinner for us tomorrow night.
He wants to make us dinner?
-Mm-hmm.
-What's his game?
I don't know, but it smells
a little branzino to me.
Huh.
Well, maybe it's an apology
for participating in her secret trip to Boston
and the lying and the...
stuff I don't like to talk about.
I hope it's an apology, but I don't know.
-Hmm.
-Kind of feel like we need to...
"worst case scenario" this bish.
You go.
Okay.
Well, obviously,
-she's pregnant. Go.
-(scoffs) God.
-They went to Vegas...
-Mm-hmm.
...and eloped while we were sleeping.
-Not preggo, just married. You go.
-Okay.
Malik brings out dessert and
there's an engagement ring
in Deja's soufflé,
and he proposes to her in front of all of us.
He pulls me out onto the back porch
before he proposes to ask
for permission, and, uh...
I don't know, he chooses the back porch because
we've had some really good talks out there...
-Play the game, Randall.
-Um...
-(knocks on table)
You go.
Deja wants to adopt Malik's daughter,
and they move in here
together and live with us forever.
-We need a new game.
-Mm-hmm.
-(sighs)
All right.
What do you think?
Hat or no hat?
Uh, no hat.
Guys in hats are usually trying
to hide their hair, and you have
-great hair.
-Oh.
I really like your curls.
What about my lipstick, is it too much?
No. (stammers) You look, um...
very nice.
(groans) It's too much.
-Okay.
-(sighs)
-All right.
You ready for this?
Not at all.
-(♪ bell dings)
-Okay, let's see, um...
I have three children,
all the same age,
and I currently live with my daughter.
-(♪ bell dings)
-Actually, I'm-I'm not divorced.
I'm a widow, actually.
I know, sad, sad, sad.
-(♪ bell dings)
-There was a fire,
and our whole house burned down. (chuckles)
We lost almost everything.
-(♪ bell dings)
-He didn't even die in the fire.
He died of a heart attack in the hospital after.
-(♪ bell dings)
-He saved the dog. (chuckles)
-They call it a widowmaker.
-(♪ bell dings) -I wasn't even in
the room. I was eating a candy bar.
-(♪ bell dings)
-I don't think I'm doing great.
Yeah, me neither.
Oh, by the way, I'm Miguel,
and I'm divorced.
I live in a different state from
my kids, and they hate me.
Oh, hi, Miguel. I'm Rebecca.
I'm a widow who can't seem
to stop talking about her husband's death.
-(♪ bell dings)
-Oh, um,
if this next one's a dud,
can we just get out of here?
-Deal. (chuckles)
-Great.
See you soon.
-REBECCA: Hi!
-Rebecca.
Matt Dickson,
from the PTA.
-Oh
It's nice to see you again.
It's good to see you, too.
How are you?
(laughs)
Okay, so, today is officially
-take most of your family to work day.
-(laughs)
I brought Jack
and Hailey and my mom, Rebecca.
-Hi.
Yeah, and she's actually
a really great piano player.
-I'm okay. (chuckles)
-KATE: No, she's really great.
So, I figured, for our jam
session today, we could have
a guest musician.
What do you think, Mom?
Oh, my God.
They're gonna kill you.
When are you gonna tell them?
We're thinking right before dessert.
Malik's making blueberry pie.
Smart.
You got to butter them up beforehand.
Stroke their egos a little bit.
Ask about Dad's addiction initiative thing.
He loves talking about that.
Annie, you still got knock-knock jokes?
I feel like I've aged out of knock-knock jokes.
Well, if I need help,
I'll give you the signal, okay?
(footsteps approaching)
What are you ladies conferencing about?
-Algebra. -Knock-knock jokes.
-Nothing.
Oh, I miss your knock-knock jokes, Annie.
-(♪ phone rings)
-Hey, brother of mine.
(front door opens, closes)
KEVIN: Hey, so I'm in a car
headed to the mom house.
Uncle Nicky's there on the ground floor,
and Cassidy's coming this weekend, so...
RANDALL: Whoa, war vet Cassidy?
Like, Nicky threw a chair at her,
and then you slept with her?
Well, I mean, that's a bit reductive,
but... yeah, her.
Oh, man, I did not see that one coming.
Huh.
Coming down the home stretch,
seemingly out of nowhere,
beating out all the local favorites,
passing Sophie, passing Madison
passing Zoe, my African-American cousin.
Can she do it? Yes!
It's Cassidy by a hundredth of a second.
It's not like that at all.
Believe it or not, there are people out there
that are capable of having
casual, consensual, you know,
"we're both hot, so let's just do it" sex.
And you, my brother, are not one of them.
You try to have a one-night stand,
and you wind up with twins.
You are the world's strangest
serial monogamist.
Okay, well, I'm here, so, um,
thank you for the most useless conversation ever.
Yeah, man. You have fun at your couples retreat,
and do me a favor.
Try not to propose, okay?
You know how you get.
Thank you, Randall. (chuckles)
(♪ phone beeps)
NICKY: Hey!
♪
Good to see you.
EDIE: Married three times, but they never stuck.
You know, I wasn't that great at it
because I was always traveling for work.
Oh, thank you, sweetie.
But I do have two beautiful children that made
the divorces, you know, worth it.
-Hmm.
She has 3 marriages, and I have none,
so, I think between the two of us,
-we almost make a normal person.
-EDIE (laughs): Yes.
So, what do you think?
Ah, I think she seems
surprisingly lovely.
I mean...
Sometimes I worry, you know.
I mean, she's been a flight attendant, you know.
She's... you know,
been around all sorts of guys.
Oh, well...
I just, you know, sometimes I worry
that maybe I'm just a port
in her storm, you know.
Oh, here's a curveball,
she brought an overnight bag for tonight.
-Brought an overnight bag?
-Mm-hmm.
Wow. (chuckles)
-We're going there?
-Oh, yeah.
Ah, I mean, have you guys consummated yet, or...?
-Would you keep your voice down?
-I'm sorry.
-No.
-You know, she's not listening
to what we're saying.
-Shh!
-Sorry.
No, we have not.
It's been more than a little
time since I've, you know,
made love to a real, live woman.
A real, live woman?
What do you mean by that? That's just... Listen.
Just do it. Just do it.
-Right.
-I'm sure you'll remember, you know.
-It's not that complicated.
-Right.
Oh, so, what about, uh...
you and Cassidy, uh,
you guys gonna sleep together this weekend?
(exhales) It's complicated.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that salad looks great.
-Yeah, not bad, right?
-So, you guys met on the plane?
Yes.
He was belligerent and very, very disruptive.
And she was unhelpful and unfriendly.
-Hmm.
-(chuckles)
Got to love that initial first
spark, you know what I mean?
-Yeah.
-I always say my Uncle Nicky's an acquired taste.
EDIE: Tell me about it.
Hey, tell-tell Kevin
what you think of The Manny.
-Nicky. Nick_ No, that's terrible.
-Go on, tell him.
-She hates it.
-Oh, my God.
-She hates it. She thinks it's really dumb.
-I...
-So rude. Would you stop...
-(laughs)
...eating my chicken.
Can my Uncle Nicky be a closet lady killer?
They're very cute.
-Can you pass the salad?
-Yeah.
(indistinct whispering)
-Thank you.
-New love.
It's quite nice.
Yeah.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, so that's Randall, that's
Kate... Oh, um, and my son, Kevin,
is in Los Angeles trying to be an actor.
-An actor?
-Mm-hmm.
Wow, and how do you feel about that?
It seems impossible to me, but, um...
part of me is just proud that he
has the guts to do it,
-you know?
-Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I wanted to be a detective.
Really?
-Yeah. That was always my big dream.
Well, you-you could still be a detective.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
I mean, I don't want to brag,
but I am really good at guessing
-who did it on Law & Order.
-(chuckles)
See, I never know who did it.
I always just assume it's the first person.
No, you_ That's your first problem.
It's never the first person,
and also, it's never the person
that works at the pizzeria.
Ah.
I am learning so much right now.
-(Matt and Rebecca laugh)
-(♪ bell dings)
MATT: Ah...
-I-I have to...
-This was really fun.
It was nice to catch up with you, Matt.
-This was nice.
-Yeah.
Hi. I'm Ren. I like your vibe.
-Hi. I'm...
-MATT: Rebecca?
I'm-I'm so sorry to interrupt. Uh...
I don't know if the, you
know, speed dating police
are gonna arrest me for speeding or something,
but I was wondering...
do you want to get coffee with me
-after this?
-Um...
Yeah.
I'd love that.
-Me, too.
-REBECCA: Okay. (laughs)
(chuckles)
I have a ferret.
Oh...
WOMAN (on TV): Seriously?
-It's like you're Photoshopped.
-(laughing)
(groans)
You know what?
Makes me nervous just to imagine
what might be going on under that blanket.
(chuckles) I'm proud of the old man.
Listen, um...
Would you want to help
Nicky oversee the construction
here on the days you don't have Matty? I mean,
-I could pay you for it.
-I don't need your charity.
It's not a charity thing. It's a...
It's a "the contractor told me that Uncle Nicky
-threw a stapler at him" thing.
-(laughs)
And since you,
since you managed classified
operations in Afghanistan,
I figure maybe you could handle a contractor
and my uncle.
I'll think about it.
You'll think about it? Very
good. Well, you think away.
Thinking. Still thinking.
(laughs)
Thank you.
What?
Nothing.
Hey, do you want to go
get ice cream or something?
-Yeah, sure. Yeah.
-Yeah?
Let's go.
(sighs)
(water continues pouring)
MALIK: There you go.
BETH: Gnocchi looks...
excellent, Malik.
Thank you. Everybody, please, dig in.
(Beth clears throat)
MALIK: Um...
We had wanted to apologize
for the weekend that Deja came to Boston.
We should've handled that differently for sure.
I know that you guys have
already spoken with Deja, but...
I wanted to get a chance
to look you both in the eyes
and apologize myself as well.
It was definitely a mutual decision.
Thank you for saying that, Malik.
And may I just say
that, um... this is
the best butter sauce I've ever tasted, so...
Thank you. Brown butter.
Um, Mom, how's it going at the dance studio?
-I'd love to hear about it.
-What? -That's very nice, Tess.
It's unusually nice, Tess. Yeah, work is fine.
Busy, finding my way, but...
You know...
it's good. Thanks for asking,
for the very first time ever.
Does anyone want to hear a knock-knock joke?
-Okay, what's going on?
-RANDALL: Hmm...
-DEJA: What? What?
-MALIK: What?
You two are making eyes at each other,
and not the normal lovey-dovey eyes,
okay, it's the "we're up to something" eyes.
And Tess is showing
unusual interest in things she is
off-the-charts uninterested in, and I ain't heard
a knock-knock joke in this
house for a clean seven years,
so what's going_ You're tugging your ear.
-Why's she tugging her ear?
What's tugging that ear?
-RANDALL: What's she doing?
-I'm getting a C in Algebra.
-RANDALL: What?
But you've been working with a tutor. What the...
It's a tactic. It's all tactics.
-They're tactics. Spill it.
-Yeah, you right.
Now.
I'm finishing out this
school semester next month,
and I'm moving to Boston with Malik.
Knock, knock!
(engine turns off)
-Thank you for the coffee.
-Oh, you're welcome.
And I would've sprung for the muffin.
Oh, the muffin would've been moving
-a little too fast for me, but...
-(chuckles)
I had a lot of fun.
-Me, too.
-Mm.
A-And next time we go out,
I promise I won't make you
date seven guys beforehand.
(both laughing)
Deal.
I'll call you.
I'd like that.
(engine starts)
STUDENTS: ♪ But everybody's
like, Cristal, Maybach, diamonds ♪
♪ On your timepiece, jet planes, islands ♪
♪ Tigers on a gold leash, we don't care ♪
♪ We aren't caught up in your love affair ♪
♪ And we'll never be royals ♪
♪ Royals ♪
♪ It don't run in our blood ♪
♪ That kind of luxe just ain't for us ♪
♪ We crave a different kind of buzz ♪
♪ Let me be your... ♪
-Hey!
-KATE: Are you still on the boat?
No. I'm actually walking back
to the car, and for the record,
it was not a canoe. Legit yacht.
-Everything okay?
-Yeah.
No.
We're at the school with my mom, and she's...
so happy.
W-We're happy.
Finally in a good place and...
(sighs) It just took a long
time to get here, Tobe.
How many bumps in the
road? Like 30 years of bumps.
We just lost so much time.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You still have time.
Kate,
you-you still have a lot of time.
-(applause)
-REBECCA: Nice. Sounds so good.
Here... but, Tobe, I've got to tell her tonight.
I understand
(sighs) I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
Love you.
Okay.
-Bye.
(♫ Rebecca playing piano)
You're joking, right?
I took on three extra A. P. classes
this semester,
so, technically, that gives me
enough credits to graduate.
And I can take the G.E.D. in December,
-with your permission.
-Permission not granted.
-Take a breath, babe.
-Uh...
You two, go upstairs, please.
Harvard does offer classes
for current high school students
and students that are looking to take a year off.
It would essentially be like a gap year,
and then I'd apply to college in the fall.
Enough. You don't have to show us
the whole PowerPoint presentation.
BETH: You know what, Deja, you're 17 years old.
You're a junior in high school.
You're not dropping out to move in
with your boyfriend in another state.
It wouldn't be dropping out.
It would be graduating early.
MALIK: I promise, we would
be doing a lot of studying.
I-I mean, we hold each other accountable.
We encourage each other.
-(laughs) I bet you do.
-That's rude.
-I'm rude?
I'm sorry, this whole thing is rude.
Y'all are rude.
You are not old enough to
make this kind of decision.
-Oh, now I'm not old enough?
-RANDALL: What are you talking about, man?
All those times you told me
I'm "wise beyond my years"?
(chuckles)
It's because I am, Randall.
I've lived a lot more life in my 17 years
than a lot of people twice my age,
and you, out of anyone in this world,
knows that best.
(chair scrapes)
-Randall.
-Hmm?
Can you take a breath and have a conversation?
-Can we do that?
-No, we can't, Beth.
'Cause I have nothing to say about any of this.
(footsteps departing)
(door noises)
Hi.
I thought you were at Molly's.
Aunt Molly was tired.
Whose car was that?
Uh,
believe it or not,
I was on a date.
You went on a date?
Well, eh, kind of. (chuckles)
Miguel and I went and did
this silly speed dating thing,
and I ended up running into a man
that I actually knew there,
and we went and had some coffee.
You went and got coffee until, like, 10:00?
You were the one telling me to get a life.
No, no, I told you to stop
watching that stupid show
with stupid Miguel.
So, what, what, you're, like, dating now?
Uh,
I don't know.
Look,
Kate, I know it's weird,
but I have to...
start to try to move on.
Oh, right. Move on from Dad,
because he's dead. I'm aware.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, yeah. I, I'm_
I should have been a little
bit more sensitive with you
when I brought it up, but I really believe
that I deserve happiness.
I think it's what your father would want.
In fact, I know it's what your father would want.
Oh, by making out with some
random dude you just met?
Okay, you know what?
You are on some thin ice
with me right now, young lady.
That is not what happened, and
maybe one day you'll understand.
No, Mom. No, I won't. And neither would Dad.
And he wouldn't be happy for
you running around town like a slut!
You don't know what you're talking about.
(door slams)
(sighs)
-Mom.
-Hmm?
Thank you so much for all of your help today.
Oh, my pleasure.
I had a blast.
And I learned who "Doja Cat" is.
Not a cat, but a rapper.
(chuckles)
When does Toby get in?
Ah, in an hour.
You know,
you both have been working so hard.
If you ever want to go have a date night,
or, you know, go out for the afternoon,
I am...
so happy to come over and watch the kids for you.
Actually, that's...
what I wanted to talk to you about.
Toby and I talked, and...
What? What's wrong?
Well, given your last PET scan,
we just don't feel comfortable
with you taking care
of the kids alone anymore.
We know that you would
never do anything intentionally.
It's just without another adult around,
we just can't_ Mom, I'm really sorry.
Oh, so that's why you wanted
me to go to school with you today
instead of watching the kids here.
Not 'cause you actually wanted me to go with you.
No, I did want you to come.
Okay, um...
I think I'm gonna go home, Kate.
(cracks knuckles)
Apologies for walking out.
Didn't expect that conversation.
(scoffs)
I get it.
You know, you and I have
spent a lot of time together, Malik.
And, uh,
I feel like...
I've tried to impart some wisdom to you.
No, you-you've been great to me.
And you're on a path, man.
You are on a great path.
Deja needs to find her own path now, Malik.
She's got two big years ahead of her.
Two years that could
determine the rest of her life.
You need to end it, Malik.
-You need to do it for her.
-What?
I'm not gonna... I love her.
If you really love her, man, then you will do
what is best for her.
But leaving school, leaving her home...
Moving six hours away.
Moving in with an 18-year-old and his daughter.
That is not what's best for her, man.
You are a very smart young man. You know that.
I'm gonna go ahead and not tell Deja
about this conversation.
Because I really do love her.
And I care about you all's relationship.
And I can promise you she
would not feel good about this.
I'm just saying,
Bubble Gum is...
I've just never seen anyone over the age of nine
order that before.
It's the universal worst flavor of ice cream.
Well, maybe I... like an underdog.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I thought we
said that was on the table.
I said I might want to have sex with you.
I didn't say I wanted to hold your hand.
O-Okay.
Wait, hold_ Why?
Yes, we did, we came together
in a time of loneliness
and-and addiction.
But what if...
What if that inner darkness
actually turned out to be
something kind of wonderful?
You've watched too many rom-coms, Kevin.
I think you're scared.
-I...
I... (inhales sharply)
There's
no reality to a relationship working with us.
Your kids are in L. A. My kid is in Pennsylvania.
I know that, but look, you and
I obviously have a connection.
It's a false equivalency, Kevin.
Your... inner darkness... (clears throat)
is not the same as mine.
Have you noticed that when
you text at 3:00 in the morning,
I'm always awake?
Our darknesses are not...
the same.
You are chasing the wrong
blonde in the wrong city.
And if you want
that rom-com love story,
you should go make things right with her.
I'm not even sure I know which
blonde you're talking about,
to be honest with you.
You see how that's a problem?
-Yeah.
-Aw, Kevin,
you've been blowing up women's lives
for the better part of two decades.
-I know you mean_ Oh, come on.
-Ah!
I know you mean well, I do.
But, you know, you are, like, a big handsome
wrecking ball.
I'm not blowing people's lives up, no.
Okay. All right, you married one,
and then cheated,
and then nearly married her again.
The current one, you couldn't say "I love you,"
but now you're obsessed
with hating the new boyfriend.
Be careful, or you're gonna blow that up, too.
I'm too messed up already.
Leave me in peace.
(Dialing) (sighs)
(sighs)
(line ringing) -MIGUEL: Hello?
-Hi.
Hey, Rebecca!
How was the coffee?
Oh, Miguel...
Kate and I just got in this horrible fight.
She said some really terrible things to me,
and I lost it.
I mean, I really, really, really lost my temper.
God, Miguel...
I slapped her.
Hey, it's okay. I'm-I'm here,
and there's no judgment.
Every once in a while a parent loses it. Okay?
Yeah, I know, but it was
just so hard to go out tonight
in the first place, you know.
This grief, it's just so...
It's so... deep.
And, I don't know, it's just, (crying)
it's-it's unbearable, you know?
(crying) It's like I don't know how to do this.
I don't know how to do any of this.
(sobbing)
Worst Case Scenario game needs to be retired.
And where'd you go?
To the stoop.
Next time you want to leave
me with Romeo and Juliet,
give me a little heads-up, huh?
Sorry.
I ran into Malik on his way out.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. I talked to him.
Didn't go great.
What did you say?
I said that he should think about Deja here,
and that he should take a step back.
(laughs) Oh, babe.
That didn't turn out well for
Romeo and Juliet's parents.
It's not gonna turn out well for us.
What happened with the parents? I don't remember.
The kids killed themselves.
That's what happened to
the parents; The children died.
Because they tried to keep them apart.
I won't let her life go off
track when she's come this far.
-I think we need to be firm about that.
-Mm-mm.
I don't think you understand how dangerous
the position we're in is right now.
Imagine
that you were that age,
and somebody told you that you could not date me.
You're making a mistake, Randall,
and we'll lose our daughter.
♫
(phone ringing)
No, you're not supposed to
respond to a text with a call.
Yeah, sorry, man, I thought
it might be an emergency.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
Everything okay with my kids?
Yeah, I just left.
Franny did that thing where
she scoots over to Nicky,
you know, and kind of leans into him, like a hug.
That's the, uh, the hug tackle, I call it.
It's the_ it's the best.
Oh, it's the best.
Uh,
listen, I want to tell you something. Um...
When you're buying food, or ordering food,
like a smoothie or something,
don't ask Madison if she wants one.
Just get it for her.
You know, she's-she's got
her eating issues and all that,
and, um, sometimes she says
she doesn't want something,
but she really does want something,
and it's just easier that way
if you just, you just get it.
You called just to tell me that?
I texted you, but yeah.
♫
(doorbell rings)
-Hi.
-Hey.
Can I come in?
Of course. Yeah.
(Rebecca sighs)
Mom, I'm really sorry.
No, I overreacted.
I'm very sensitive about all of this and...
what can I say?
But I shouldn't have snapped at you.
Snap at me all you want.
I did it to you for years.
I took everything out on you.
And I'm really deeply sorry.
I feel like I wasted so much time with you
that could have been really great.
And now that we are finally great,
it's jus... the timing sucks.
Yeah.
Timing is everything, isn't it?
KATE (whispers): Yeah.
Your father walked into a bar
when I happened to be singing.
I mean, if not for that timing,
then none of any of this.
And then four gazillion
other things had to happen
in order for this to happen right now.
For me to be sitting here with you...
with my daughter.
My girl.
My best friend.
Wondering...
what the hell she has in that mystery folder.
I was wondering if you would be willing
to teach Jack piano.
It's braille sheet music.
I know that music is
good for memory function, too.
(♪ plays single note)
♪
I'm sorry.
I won't date anymore.
No.
No, you should.
(♪ plays single note)
(♪ repeats same note)
♫ (playing "Heart and Soul")
REBECCA: See if I can remember the other part.
Um...
(playing "Heart and Soul") ♫
♪
♫
-REBECCA: Ready to try it, Bug? Okay.
-YOUNG KATE: Yeah.
(♪ plays single note)
-
--
---
---o
---oO
---oOo
---oOo-
---oOo--
---oOo---