1
00:00:00,814 --> 00:00:03,225
Previously on This Is Us...

2
00:00:03,226 --> 00:00:05,878
-(chuckles) -STANLEY:
Jack! Where the hell are you?

3
00:00:05,934 --> 00:00:07,876
Hello, Mrs. Pearson.

4
00:00:07,877 --> 00:00:09,538
Oh. I'm such a klutz.

5
00:00:09,572 --> 00:00:11,373
You know what? Go pack your things, okay?

6
00:00:11,406 --> 00:00:13,208
-We're leaving.
-MARILYN: Jack, stop.

7
00:00:13,241 --> 00:00:14,943
JACK: You deserve more than what's in that house.

8
00:00:14,977 --> 00:00:16,622
Do you have a dream?

9
00:00:16,623 --> 00:00:18,993
I just want to make sure my mom is okay.

10
00:00:19,315 --> 00:00:21,384
Get her settled at her friend's place,

11
00:00:21,417 --> 00:00:22,651
and then...

12
00:00:22,685 --> 00:00:23,857
A decent job.

13
00:00:23,858 --> 00:00:25,098
A wife.

14
00:00:25,099 --> 00:00:27,290
A family.

15
00:00:27,323 --> 00:00:29,652
Okay. Um...

16
00:00:29,653 --> 00:00:31,827
Okay. Thank you.

17
00:00:32,821 --> 00:00:35,175
Who was that?

18
00:00:36,684 --> 00:00:38,501
My mom died.

19
00:00:58,328 --> 00:01:01,157
REBECCA: What about this gray one?

20
00:01:04,335 --> 00:01:07,004
It's light gray.

21
00:01:07,037 --> 00:01:10,159
I can't wear a gray suit. It has to be black.

22
00:01:10,457 --> 00:01:14,178
Um, well, maybe we can get a deal at Gimbels.

23
00:01:14,211 --> 00:01:17,014
-Suits are just so expensive.
-Doesn't matter what it costs.

24
00:01:17,047 --> 00:01:19,719
It's my mother's funeral. It's got to be black.

25
00:01:19,733 --> 00:01:21,018
Of course.

26
00:01:21,051 --> 00:01:23,354
-Of course.
-(Jack sighs)

27
00:01:23,622 --> 00:01:26,057
I just-- it doesn't seem real.

28
00:01:27,858 --> 00:01:29,243
I feel like...

29
00:01:29,244 --> 00:01:32,228
the phone's gonna ring on Sunday.

30
00:01:32,229 --> 00:01:35,032
She'll ask about the kids.

31
00:01:35,065 --> 00:01:36,701
After a few minutes of catching up,

32
00:01:36,734 --> 00:01:38,580
she'll say what she always says...

33
00:01:38,581 --> 00:01:40,830
BOTH: "Don't let me keep you."

34
00:01:44,675 --> 00:01:47,391
It doesn't seem real.

35
00:01:58,088 --> 00:02:01,258
<i>WEATHERMAN (on radio): With a cold
front coming across Lake Erie from Ontario,</i>

36
00:02:01,291 --> 00:02:03,327
<i>we're looking at eight to ten inches of snow</i>

37
00:02:03,360 --> 00:02:04,862
<i>and icy conditions on the roadways</i>

38
00:02:04,895 --> 00:02:07,031
<i>for at least the next 48 hours.</i>

39
00:02:07,064 --> 00:02:08,833
<i>We have a high of 33...</i>

40
00:02:08,866 --> 00:02:10,367
You know, I'm-a... I'm gonna hit the road

41
00:02:10,412 --> 00:02:12,703
before the snow gets too heavy.

42
00:02:12,704 --> 00:02:14,672
I really feel like we should go with you, babe.

43
00:02:14,705 --> 00:02:16,006
I mean, I could run upstairs

44
00:02:16,040 --> 00:02:17,575
and pack a quick bag for me and the kids.

45
00:02:17,608 --> 00:02:19,209
Bec, come on. We talked about this, all right?

46
00:02:19,243 --> 00:02:20,511
I've done the math.

47
00:02:20,545 --> 00:02:23,013
Three six-year-olds on a four-hour car ride?

48
00:02:23,025 --> 00:02:24,615
(scoffs) It ain't worth it.

49
00:02:24,649 --> 00:02:26,551
But you're our guy, Jack.

50
00:02:26,584 --> 00:02:27,945
You're worth

51
00:02:27,946 --> 00:02:30,120
10 hours in the car, in a blizzard.

52
00:02:30,154 --> 00:02:31,522
Only ten?

53
00:02:31,556 --> 00:02:33,458
Yeah, 10 is the maximum,

54
00:02:33,491 --> 00:02:35,829
but in a blizzard, in a torrential blizzard.

55
00:02:35,830 --> 00:02:37,404
Can blizzards be torrential?

56
00:02:37,405 --> 00:02:39,466
You know, I-I think that's just rainstorms.

57
00:02:39,467 --> 00:02:41,031
Jack, I'm serious.

58
00:02:41,065 --> 00:02:41,995
Hey, Bec,

59
00:02:41,996 --> 00:02:43,523
it ain't worth it,

60
00:02:43,524 --> 00:02:44,535
all right?

61
00:02:44,569 --> 00:02:46,333
I mean, the kids, they...

62
00:02:46,334 --> 00:02:47,738
they barely knew her.

63
00:02:47,772 --> 00:02:49,574
I mean, when was the last time she visited?

64
00:02:49,607 --> 00:02:51,408
They were, what, like a year old?

65
00:02:51,442 --> 00:02:53,377
Yeah, but they talked to her on the phone.

66
00:02:53,410 --> 00:02:55,901
And that's all she's been for years,

67
00:02:55,902 --> 00:02:58,603
just a voice on the other end of the telephone.

68
00:02:58,624 --> 00:03:00,268
Lookit, Bec,

69
00:03:00,269 --> 00:03:01,976
knowing my mom,

70
00:03:02,032 --> 00:03:03,943
I've got a funeral to plan

71
00:03:03,944 --> 00:03:06,719
and a lifetime of loose ends to tie up.

72
00:03:07,257 --> 00:03:11,374
Look, it's just-- it's better if I do this alone.

73
00:03:11,375 --> 00:03:13,631
(footsteps approaching)

74
00:03:13,664 --> 00:03:15,654
Which grandma died?

75
00:03:15,655 --> 00:03:17,670
KATE: Daddy's mommy died.

76
00:03:17,712 --> 00:03:20,137
Daddy's mommy is dead.

77
00:03:20,170 --> 00:03:21,806
RANDALL: Stop saying she's dead.

78
00:03:21,809 --> 00:03:23,908
But she is dead.

79
00:03:23,941 --> 00:03:25,409
Right, Daddy?

80
00:03:25,410 --> 00:03:27,777
Yeah, that's right, Katie girl.

81
00:03:27,778 --> 00:03:30,314
Uh, Grandma Marilyn passed away,

82
00:03:30,357 --> 00:03:33,583
and we're gonna miss her very much.

83
00:03:33,584 --> 00:03:34,985
Yes.

84
00:03:37,555 --> 00:03:40,024
Can we play in the snow?

85
00:03:40,056 --> 00:03:41,265
Uh...

86
00:03:41,266 --> 00:03:42,025
sure.

87
00:03:42,059 --> 00:03:43,360
REBECCA: Maybe after breakfast.

88
00:03:43,393 --> 00:03:44,698
Yeah, uh...

89
00:03:44,699 --> 00:03:46,697
why-why don't you guys wear the mittens

90
00:03:46,731 --> 00:03:48,833
-that Grandma made for you last Christmas?
-REBECCA: Yeah.

91
00:03:48,866 --> 00:03:50,501
But they're so scratchy.

92
00:03:50,557 --> 00:03:52,232
Yeah, they feel like there's,

93
00:03:52,233 --> 00:03:53,860
like, bugs crawling on my hands.

94
00:03:53,871 --> 00:03:55,673
KEVIN: Yeah, they're too warm. I don't like them.

95
00:03:55,674 --> 00:03:56,370
REBECCA: Okay,

96
00:03:56,371 --> 00:03:59,662
Well, we'll figure out the mittens situation.

97
00:04:15,560 --> 00:04:17,662
You didn't have to drive me.

98
00:04:17,663 --> 00:04:20,043
I could have taken the bus.

99
00:04:21,666 --> 00:04:25,381
It was nice of Cheryl to put
me up for the past few weeks, but...

100
00:04:25,382 --> 00:04:28,639
moving in with Debby will be good.

101
00:04:28,673 --> 00:04:30,803
She's family.

102
00:04:31,909 --> 00:04:34,786
And I need to get further away.

103
00:04:35,306 --> 00:04:37,848
From Dad. Yeah.

104
00:04:44,221 --> 00:04:45,890
Ohio looks nice.

105
00:04:45,923 --> 00:04:48,358
Looks the same as Pennsylvania.

106
00:04:52,262 --> 00:04:54,264
I'll miss you, Jackie.

107
00:04:54,298 --> 00:04:56,956
I don't like being this far away from you.

108
00:04:57,168 --> 00:05:00,004
Yeah, I know, Ma, but you can call anytime.

109
00:05:00,037 --> 00:05:02,707
No, I don't want to be a bother.

110
00:05:02,740 --> 00:05:04,709
The last thing you need is to sit around

111
00:05:04,742 --> 00:05:06,777
wondering when I'm gonna call.

112
00:05:06,811 --> 00:05:09,179
God knows I've already
caused you enough trouble lately.

113
00:05:09,213 --> 00:05:11,589
No, it's no trouble, Ma.

114
00:05:21,959 --> 00:05:23,928
Sunday nights.

115
00:05:23,961 --> 00:05:26,530
Every Sunday, 6:00,

116
00:05:26,563 --> 00:05:28,032
I'll be by the phone.

117
00:05:28,065 --> 00:05:29,934
You want to call, I'll be there to pick it up.

118
00:05:32,569 --> 00:05:35,105
-6:00, Sunday.
-Mm-hmm.

119
00:05:36,440 --> 00:05:39,576
And I'll visit, okay? I promise.

120
00:06:04,034 --> 00:06:06,671
(clicks tongue) Look who finally showed up.

121
00:06:06,704 --> 00:06:08,836
Only took you 13 years.

122
00:06:29,960 --> 00:06:31,929
(footsteps approaching)

123
00:06:31,962 --> 00:06:33,597
(Debby sighs)

124
00:06:33,630 --> 00:06:35,267
Well, it's been a while.

125
00:06:35,268 --> 00:06:36,896
I thought we'd see more of you

126
00:06:36,897 --> 00:06:38,171
over the years.

127
00:06:38,172 --> 00:06:40,405
Oh, I'm sorry.

128
00:06:40,406 --> 00:06:42,752
Yeah, I just, um...

129
00:06:42,864 --> 00:06:46,333
It's tough-- the triplets and work.

130
00:06:46,567 --> 00:06:47,869
Um...

131
00:06:47,870 --> 00:06:50,671
I mean, my mom and I, we spoke once a week.

132
00:06:50,704 --> 00:06:52,397
Oh, I know.

133
00:06:52,398 --> 00:06:54,430
Every Sunday, 6:00,

134
00:06:54,431 --> 00:06:56,510
world stopped spinning.

135
00:06:57,135 --> 00:06:58,779
Look, Cousin Debby...

136
00:06:58,812 --> 00:06:59,991
You don't have to call me that.

137
00:06:59,992 --> 00:07:01,504
I'm not your cousin.

138
00:07:01,505 --> 00:07:03,200
I was her cousin.

139
00:07:03,471 --> 00:07:05,758
I think that still makes us cousins.

140
00:07:05,759 --> 00:07:07,622
Debby's fine.

141
00:07:08,035 --> 00:07:10,371
Debby, I'm here to help, so...

142
00:07:10,404 --> 00:07:11,839
if you want to just point me in the direction

143
00:07:11,873 --> 00:07:13,741
of the nearest funeral parlor, I'll...

144
00:07:13,775 --> 00:07:15,376
buy the casket, organize the plot,

145
00:07:15,409 --> 00:07:18,454
-the service...
-Yeah. It's all been taken care of.

146
00:07:20,447 --> 00:07:22,050
The flowers?

147
00:07:22,051 --> 00:07:24,186
I own a flower shop, Jack.

148
00:07:25,252 --> 00:07:27,054
Right.

149
00:07:27,088 --> 00:07:28,671
Yeah.

150
00:07:28,939 --> 00:07:31,525
The funeral is the day after tomorrow.

151
00:07:31,559 --> 00:07:33,763
2:00 p.m.-- that way

152
00:07:33,764 --> 00:07:35,730
we don't have to serve a meal.

153
00:07:37,298 --> 00:07:39,734
Well, my mom was lucky to have you,

154
00:07:39,767 --> 00:07:41,769
figure all this out for her.

155
00:07:41,803 --> 00:07:43,549
I didn't do anything.

156
00:07:43,550 --> 00:07:47,476
Marilyn planned it all out herself ages ago.

157
00:07:47,833 --> 00:07:51,840
I guess she just didn't want
to be a burden to anyone.

158
00:07:57,418 --> 00:07:59,420
(takes deep breath)

159
00:08:02,990 --> 00:08:05,493
Is there anything that I can do?

160
00:08:07,061 --> 00:08:08,886
The eulogy.

161
00:08:09,673 --> 00:08:11,821
I'm not really good with giving speeches.

162
00:08:11,822 --> 00:08:13,134
Oh.

163
00:08:13,167 --> 00:08:15,036
Look, if you can't handle it,

164
00:08:15,069 --> 00:08:17,026
-I'm-I'm happy to do it.
-No, no, no.

165
00:08:17,027 --> 00:08:18,462
No. I got it.

166
00:08:20,401 --> 00:08:23,811
I was thinking maybe I
could read one of my poems.

167
00:08:24,168 --> 00:08:25,880
You write poems?

168
00:08:25,913 --> 00:08:27,581
Yeah, I do, a little.

169
00:08:27,615 --> 00:08:29,586
I mean, mostly just...

170
00:08:29,587 --> 00:08:30,885
for myself.

171
00:08:30,918 --> 00:08:32,654
Your mom loved poetry.

172
00:08:32,687 --> 00:08:36,323
She was always encouraging
me to write more, so...

173
00:08:36,357 --> 00:08:38,809
My mom loved poetry?

174
00:08:42,485 --> 00:08:45,922
I'm gonna do the flowers, obviously.

175
00:08:46,100 --> 00:08:49,403
Maybe you could find a dress for the burial.

176
00:08:49,436 --> 00:08:52,006
Whatever you think she'd like.

177
00:08:52,039 --> 00:08:53,540
No problem.

178
00:09:35,216 --> 00:09:36,650
(sets book down)

179
00:09:37,651 --> 00:09:39,053
(sighs)

180
00:09:46,494 --> 00:09:48,395
♪ (phone rings)

181
00:09:50,164 --> 00:09:52,533
Hey, Ma! How's Ohio?

182
00:09:52,667 --> 00:09:54,301
It's fine.

183
00:09:54,335 --> 00:09:55,302
Yeah?

184
00:09:55,336 --> 00:09:56,838
And you?

185
00:09:56,871 --> 00:09:58,539
You good? You...

186
00:09:58,572 --> 00:10:00,550
You settling in a little bit more?

187
00:10:01,575 --> 00:10:04,344
Jackie, I made a mistake.

188
00:10:04,779 --> 00:10:08,017
Wh-- What kind of mistake?

189
00:10:08,292 --> 00:10:11,295
I just wanted him to send me a few things.

190
00:10:11,296 --> 00:10:13,587
My mother's china teapot.

191
00:10:13,588 --> 00:10:14,807
Some pictures.

192
00:10:14,808 --> 00:10:16,357
You called Dad?

193
00:10:16,390 --> 00:10:18,259
I realized as soon as he answered

194
00:10:18,292 --> 00:10:19,426
that it was a bad idea.

195
00:10:19,460 --> 00:10:21,528
Does he know where you are?

196
00:10:21,562 --> 00:10:24,098
No. No. I don't think so.

197
00:10:26,067 --> 00:10:27,534
I'm sorry.

198
00:10:27,568 --> 00:10:29,771
You don't need to be sorry, Ma.

199
00:10:32,539 --> 00:10:34,208
How's Rebecca?

200
00:10:34,241 --> 00:10:35,442
Are you two still...?

201
00:10:35,476 --> 00:10:36,744
She's great.

202
00:10:36,778 --> 00:10:39,245
Yeah, no, we're-we're doing great.

203
00:10:39,514 --> 00:10:41,205
Good.

204
00:10:41,206 --> 00:10:42,750
That's good.

205
00:10:44,960 --> 00:10:46,835
Well...

206
00:10:47,054 --> 00:10:48,722
Don't let me keep you.

207
00:10:49,487 --> 00:10:50,619
Okay, Ma.

208
00:10:50,620 --> 00:10:53,630
I'll-I'll talk to you next Sunday. I love you.

209
00:11:05,150 --> 00:11:06,757
(cat meows)

210
00:11:18,152 --> 00:11:20,990
Nope. We're not serving a meal.

211
00:11:21,122 --> 00:11:22,150
Okay.

212
00:11:22,151 --> 00:11:23,573
All right. I'll see you there.

213
00:11:23,574 --> 00:11:24,758
2:00.

214
00:11:24,792 --> 00:11:25,927
Okay.

215
00:11:27,228 --> 00:11:29,663
-(receiver clicks) -Have you
been in touch with my father?

216
00:11:29,696 --> 00:11:31,001
To tell him about my mom?

217
00:11:31,002 --> 00:11:32,766
Stanley?

218
00:11:32,800 --> 00:11:34,869
No way I'm calling that bastard.

219
00:11:37,304 --> 00:11:39,495
-(meowing)
-Whoa.

220
00:11:39,540 --> 00:11:41,775
Hey, do you want to maybe feed your cat?

221
00:11:41,809 --> 00:11:43,477
-(chuckles)
-That's not my cat.

222
00:11:43,510 --> 00:11:45,312
That's your mom's cat.

223
00:11:45,346 --> 00:11:47,514
My mom had a cat?

224
00:11:47,548 --> 00:11:49,851
My dad hated cats.

225
00:11:49,884 --> 00:11:52,019
Exactly.

226
00:11:52,053 --> 00:11:53,046
Hey, cat!

227
00:11:53,047 --> 00:11:55,312
Why don't you go back to Mike's?

228
00:11:55,313 --> 00:11:57,214
Who's Mike?

229
00:11:57,215 --> 00:12:00,518
Uh, he is your mom's... boyfriend.

230
00:12:00,946 --> 00:12:02,696
Mike McCreary.

231
00:12:02,729 --> 00:12:05,199
Cat's living with him now.

232
00:12:05,232 --> 00:12:07,534
(scribbling on paper)

233
00:12:07,568 --> 00:12:10,204
Look, if you want to make yourself useful,

234
00:12:10,237 --> 00:12:13,140
maybe you can just bring the cat back to Mike's.

235
00:12:13,174 --> 00:12:14,767
His place is just up the road.

236
00:12:14,768 --> 00:12:16,510
Look out for his van.

237
00:12:16,543 --> 00:12:18,679
Yeah, sure.

238
00:12:18,712 --> 00:12:20,581
(grunts): Come on, cat.

239
00:12:21,548 --> 00:12:24,076
(sighs)

240
00:12:35,429 --> 00:12:36,898
(sighs)

241
00:12:41,302 --> 00:12:43,249
Uh, you must be Jack.

242
00:12:43,439 --> 00:12:45,307
You must be Mike.

243
00:12:45,341 --> 00:12:47,209
I was hoping you'd come by.

244
00:12:47,243 --> 00:12:49,077
-(meows)
-(chuckles)

245
00:12:49,110 --> 00:12:50,933
Well, come on in.

246
00:12:50,978 --> 00:12:52,780
Hey, there, Cat.

247
00:12:54,682 --> 00:12:56,151
Uh, here.

248
00:12:56,184 --> 00:12:58,619
(chuckles)

249
00:12:58,653 --> 00:13:00,288
Cat got a name?

250
00:13:00,321 --> 00:13:01,531
Yep.

251
00:13:01,532 --> 00:13:03,724
Cat Benatar.

252
00:13:03,758 --> 00:13:05,755
You know Marilyn's sense of humor.

253
00:13:06,056 --> 00:13:08,691
Yeah, keeps getting out

254
00:13:08,692 --> 00:13:11,355
and running back to Marilyn's.

255
00:13:11,433 --> 00:13:14,402
Just doesn't understand that, um...

256
00:13:14,435 --> 00:13:16,004
that, you know...

257
00:13:16,005 --> 00:13:18,202
that... that she's gone.

258
00:13:22,678 --> 00:13:24,145
JACK: Okay.

259
00:13:27,489 --> 00:13:29,817
Your mom was a good woman.

260
00:13:30,231 --> 00:13:31,866
Thanks.

261
00:13:32,867 --> 00:13:34,435
Um, how are, uh,

262
00:13:34,802 --> 00:13:38,556
Rebecca and the, and the kids holding up?

263
00:13:40,142 --> 00:13:41,305
Okay.

264
00:13:41,306 --> 00:13:43,245
Triplets, man, that's...

265
00:13:43,278 --> 00:13:45,780
-That's-- I don't know how you do it.
-Yeah.

266
00:13:45,813 --> 00:13:47,582
Yeah. Hey, you and, uh,

267
00:13:47,615 --> 00:13:49,584
you and your kids watch, uh, wrestling?

268
00:13:49,617 --> 00:13:51,419
You know, Hulk Hogan,

269
00:13:51,453 --> 00:13:53,442
uh, André the Giant, King Kong Bundy?

270
00:13:53,443 --> 00:13:55,656
No, I-I think they're a little young for that.

271
00:13:55,657 --> 00:13:57,359
Oh, no, but they're not. (stammers)

272
00:13:57,392 --> 00:13:59,461
I know a lot of folks complain that it's fake,

273
00:13:59,494 --> 00:14:01,796
but these guys, these guys are athletes,

274
00:14:01,829 --> 00:14:04,632
I mean, real athletes. The...

275
00:14:04,666 --> 00:14:07,035
(exhales) What am I...

276
00:14:07,069 --> 00:14:08,736
(chuckles)

277
00:14:08,770 --> 00:14:11,039
Sorry, man, um...

278
00:14:11,073 --> 00:14:13,241
I'm-I'm nervous.

279
00:14:15,577 --> 00:14:17,279
It's just that your mom

280
00:14:17,312 --> 00:14:20,297
talked about you and the,
and the kids all the time,

281
00:14:20,385 --> 00:14:22,195
and it's, uh...

282
00:14:22,196 --> 00:14:25,223
this isn't how I pictured us meeting.

283
00:14:25,687 --> 00:14:27,510
Yeah.

284
00:14:28,236 --> 00:14:30,787
So, um...

285
00:14:30,788 --> 00:14:32,260
want a beer?

286
00:14:33,328 --> 00:14:35,130
Sure.

287
00:14:35,163 --> 00:14:37,301
Take whatever's cold.

288
00:14:37,665 --> 00:14:39,834
I was, um,

289
00:14:39,867 --> 00:14:42,381
going through some photos of,

290
00:14:42,382 --> 00:14:43,805
uh, me and Marilyn.

291
00:14:43,838 --> 00:14:46,774
-Thought you might like to see 'em.
-Yeah.

292
00:14:55,883 --> 00:14:58,020
Will you look at that smile?

293
00:14:58,053 --> 00:15:01,889
Now, that, that is Marilyn through and through.

294
00:15:04,659 --> 00:15:06,261
She looks happy.

295
00:15:06,294 --> 00:15:07,865
She was.

296
00:15:07,866 --> 00:15:09,697
We were.

297
00:15:10,732 --> 00:15:14,936
Can I ask how you two met?

298
00:15:14,969 --> 00:15:18,340
Well, um, I was...

299
00:15:18,373 --> 00:15:20,342
-I was always a night owl.
-Mm-hmm.

300
00:15:20,375 --> 00:15:24,279
But, uh, one morning, I
wake up real early, no reason,

301
00:15:24,312 --> 00:15:27,015
but I can't fall back asleep, so I figure

302
00:15:27,049 --> 00:15:30,385
get a cup of coffee at the place down the way.

303
00:15:30,418 --> 00:15:31,639
So, I...

304
00:15:31,639 --> 00:15:35,342
sit down at my favorite
table by the window, and...

305
00:15:35,343 --> 00:15:37,872
this woman comes over and says,

306
00:15:37,873 --> 00:15:39,660
"You're at my table."

307
00:15:39,661 --> 00:15:41,607
Well, it turns out,

308
00:15:41,608 --> 00:15:44,366
we had the same favorite table.

309
00:15:44,399 --> 00:15:47,169
She always sat there early and I sat there late.

310
00:15:47,202 --> 00:15:48,364
So,

311
00:15:48,365 --> 00:15:51,906
I offer to share the table.

312
00:15:51,939 --> 00:15:53,911
The next morning,

313
00:15:53,912 --> 00:15:57,512
I got there when the place opened, so did she.

314
00:15:57,545 --> 00:16:00,924
And that was the end of the night owl.

315
00:16:02,550 --> 00:16:04,919
You know, it took, um...

316
00:16:04,952 --> 00:16:08,523
took some time to earn her trust, but...

317
00:16:08,556 --> 00:16:10,992
but I always knew how to make her laugh.

318
00:16:11,025 --> 00:16:13,195
(chuckles) She...

319
00:16:13,228 --> 00:16:15,292
she had a great laugh.

320
00:16:18,733 --> 00:16:20,535
JACK: Can't remember the last time

321
00:16:20,568 --> 00:16:22,304
I heard my mother laugh.

322
00:16:23,938 --> 00:16:25,940
I guess she was...

323
00:16:25,973 --> 00:16:27,653
she was always

324
00:16:27,654 --> 00:16:30,678
on high alert with my dad.

325
00:16:30,712 --> 00:16:32,127
Yeah.

326
00:16:32,625 --> 00:16:34,616
Well... (clears throat)

327
00:16:34,649 --> 00:16:36,884
...let me tell you this.

328
00:16:36,918 --> 00:16:40,755
Nothing was more important
to her than your Sunday calls.

329
00:16:40,788 --> 00:16:43,224
She looked forward to 'em all week.

330
00:16:45,948 --> 00:16:48,570
You were her hero, Jack.

331
00:16:48,849 --> 00:16:50,852
You're the one

332
00:16:50,853 --> 00:16:53,034
that got her out of that house.

333
00:17:00,075 --> 00:17:01,914
Not a hero, Mike.

334
00:17:02,444 --> 00:17:04,412
I mean, I...

335
00:17:04,446 --> 00:17:05,980
knew nothing about her life.

336
00:17:06,013 --> 00:17:08,428
I mean, I missed the whole damn thing, so...

337
00:17:08,429 --> 00:17:12,033
Thanks for showing me
the photos, and for the beer.

338
00:17:13,921 --> 00:17:15,994
(door opens)

339
00:17:26,072 --> 00:17:28,265
(shouts)

340
00:17:32,374 --> 00:17:34,376
(birds chirping)

341
00:17:36,791 --> 00:17:38,058
(grunts)

342
00:17:42,336 --> 00:17:43,504
(exhales)

343
00:17:52,473 --> 00:17:54,442
(grunts)

344
00:18:00,147 --> 00:18:01,616
♪ (phone ringing)

345
00:18:02,950 --> 00:18:05,653
Hey, Jack, it's 6:00!

346
00:18:08,188 --> 00:18:09,590
(sighs)

347
00:18:11,526 --> 00:18:13,994
Hi, Marilyn. Right on time. (chuckles)

348
00:18:14,028 --> 00:18:17,465
Oh, um, thank you so much
for the-the scarf you sent.

349
00:18:17,498 --> 00:18:19,781
-It's so great.
-Oh, you like it?

350
00:18:19,782 --> 00:18:21,168
I do, I love it. Thank you.

351
00:18:21,201 --> 00:18:23,671
Hold on, let me get Jack for you. Jack?!

352
00:18:23,704 --> 00:18:25,973
Jack?!

353
00:18:26,006 --> 00:18:27,675
-Here.
-(whispers): I got-- I got it.

354
00:18:27,708 --> 00:18:28,843
Hi, buddy.

355
00:18:28,876 --> 00:18:31,612
Hey, Ma! Hey, how, uh...

356
00:18:31,646 --> 00:18:33,013
How's it going?

357
00:18:33,047 --> 00:18:35,416
Oh, everything's fine.

358
00:18:35,450 --> 00:18:36,984
Tell me about the little ones.

359
00:18:37,017 --> 00:18:38,753
Uh, they're-they're good.

360
00:18:38,786 --> 00:18:40,655
Good-- You know, ev-everyone's good.

361
00:18:40,688 --> 00:18:42,590
-Jack.
-Oh, no. Oh...

362
00:18:42,623 --> 00:18:44,158
-He spit up. Here.
-Yeah.

363
00:18:45,192 --> 00:18:46,927
JACK: Get that. Okay.

364
00:18:46,961 --> 00:18:48,295
Hey, when, uh,

365
00:18:48,329 --> 00:18:50,264
when are you gonna come meet your grandkids?

366
00:18:50,768 --> 00:18:52,089
Oh,

367
00:18:52,090 --> 00:18:54,201
I'll come once things settle down.

368
00:18:54,234 --> 00:18:58,067
Mom, we got triplets, all right?
It's never gonna settle down.

369
00:18:58,115 --> 00:19:00,618
I'll come soon, Jackie.

370
00:19:02,783 --> 00:19:06,052
Well, it's a big city, Mom.

371
00:19:06,086 --> 00:19:07,921
I haven't seen the man in a decade.

372
00:19:07,954 --> 00:19:10,869
So I-I think it's safe to say
you can visit your family

373
00:19:10,870 --> 00:19:12,572
-without running into Dad.
-No, I know.

374
00:19:14,105 --> 00:19:16,741
But Debby needs help at the flower shop and...

375
00:19:18,743 --> 00:19:20,856
I-- Look, I'll plan a trip soon.

376
00:19:22,551 --> 00:19:24,179
Okay.

377
00:19:26,751 --> 00:19:28,619
There's this pond by the house.

378
00:19:28,653 --> 00:19:30,221
It freezes over in the winter,

379
00:19:30,255 --> 00:19:32,845
and everyone in the
neighborhood goes ice-skating.

380
00:19:32,846 --> 00:19:34,281
You should bring the kids.

381
00:19:35,426 --> 00:19:37,585
Kids can't really walk yet, Mom.

382
00:19:37,592 --> 00:19:39,063
No, of course not.

383
00:19:39,096 --> 00:19:40,454
I know that. I'm just...

384
00:19:40,473 --> 00:19:41,612
saying,

385
00:19:41,613 --> 00:19:43,073
one day.

386
00:19:43,074 --> 00:19:44,969
-Yeah, no, we'll...
-(distant crying)

387
00:19:45,002 --> 00:19:48,072
(shushes) ...we'll-we'll get the kids on skates

388
00:19:48,105 --> 00:19:50,142
as soon as we can.

389
00:19:50,941 --> 00:19:51,941
Well,

390
00:19:51,942 --> 00:19:53,244
don't let me keep you.

391
00:19:53,278 --> 00:19:55,496
Okay, Mom, I'll, uh,

392
00:19:55,601 --> 00:19:57,570
I'll talk to you next Sunday, okay? I love you.

393
00:19:57,571 --> 00:19:58,772
-I lo...
-(phone crackles)

394
00:19:58,773 --> 00:20:00,207
<i>(dial tone) ♪</i>

395
00:20:02,465 --> 00:20:03,734
(meows)

396
00:20:06,624 --> 00:20:09,059
Hi, sweetie.

397
00:20:26,411 --> 00:20:28,413
(horn honks in distance)

398
00:20:40,391 --> 00:20:42,660
Hi; Can I, uh...

399
00:20:42,693 --> 00:20:45,826
I-I'll have a coffee, please. Thanks.

400
00:21:02,347 --> 00:21:05,676
(overlapping chatter)

401
00:21:09,520 --> 00:21:11,020
Hey, Jack!

402
00:21:11,020 --> 00:21:12,602
Come on over.
-Mike.

403
00:21:14,592 --> 00:21:16,093
-(thumps seat)
-Right there.

404
00:21:16,126 --> 00:21:18,729
We are having a round of 7 and 7s

405
00:21:18,763 --> 00:21:20,365
in honor of our Marilyn.

406
00:21:20,398 --> 00:21:21,979
Okay.

407
00:21:21,980 --> 00:21:23,401
All right.

408
00:21:23,434 --> 00:21:25,886
-Hi. -Hey.
-MIKE: All right.

409
00:21:26,737 --> 00:21:28,706
-Everything good?
-Yeah, things are all right.

410
00:21:28,739 --> 00:21:30,608
It's a nice, a nice town.

411
00:21:30,641 --> 00:21:31,942
All right, here we go, here we go.

412
00:21:31,976 --> 00:21:33,444
Thank you, Shanice.

413
00:21:33,478 --> 00:21:35,212
-Nicely done. -Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.

414
00:21:35,246 --> 00:21:36,747
-WENDY: Thank you.
-MIKE: All right, guys,

415
00:21:36,781 --> 00:21:38,416
let's raise 'em up. Raise 'em up.

416
00:21:38,449 --> 00:21:40,084
To our Marilyn.

417
00:21:40,117 --> 00:21:42,609
-DEBBY: To our Marilyn.
-Yeah, baby.

418
00:21:46,123 --> 00:21:47,625
-(exhales)
-WENDY: Oh, that tastes...

419
00:21:47,658 --> 00:21:48,893
MIKE: Let me tell you something about your mom.

420
00:21:48,926 --> 00:21:51,562
You don't know this. She would make up terms.

421
00:21:51,596 --> 00:21:53,564
-DEBBY: Oh, no, oh, here we go.
-A whole thing. A whole fictitious...

422
00:21:53,598 --> 00:21:56,133
<i>-DEBBY: Her bad knitting.
-MIKE: She was a volume knitter.</i>

423
00:21:56,178 --> 00:21:57,380
<i>Not precision.</i>

424
00:21:57,402 --> 00:21:59,970
<i>(Mike speaking indistinctly)</i>

425
00:22:00,004 --> 00:22:02,873
<i>DEBBY: ...bridge term
called "the Jacoby transfer."</i>

426
00:22:02,907 --> 00:22:04,709
<i>MIKE (laughs): This is made up.</i>

427
00:22:04,742 --> 00:22:06,477
<i>This is not real, right? This is not real.</i>

428
00:22:06,511 --> 00:22:07,478
<i>(Wendy laughs)</i>

429
00:22:07,485 --> 00:22:10,114
<i>It's the Jacoby transfer.</i>

430
00:22:10,147 --> 00:22:12,149
<i>See, they don't even know. They don't even know.</i>

431
00:22:12,182 --> 00:22:14,619
<i>-I'm telling you...
-It's totally made up. It's a totally made-up thing.</i>

432
00:22:14,652 --> 00:22:16,220
<i>Okay, okay, maybe, maybe...</i>

433
00:22:16,253 --> 00:22:18,723
<i>-You looked it up...
-You made that up...</i>

434
00:23:09,407 --> 00:23:11,409
(sniffles)

435
00:23:15,145 --> 00:23:17,181
(exhales)

436
00:23:19,083 --> 00:23:20,818
(sniffles)

437
00:23:20,851 --> 00:23:22,720
(buttons clicking)

438
00:23:28,426 --> 00:23:30,495
(line ringing) ♪

439
00:23:32,697 --> 00:23:36,200
-STANLEY (over phone): Yeah?
-She's dead.

440
00:23:36,233 --> 00:23:40,004
Three days ago, Mom had an aneurysm and she died.

441
00:23:40,294 --> 00:23:42,329
(TV playing indistinctly)

442
00:23:47,745 --> 00:23:50,014
Aren't you gonna say anything?

443
00:23:50,194 --> 00:23:53,015
Ah, Jackie,

444
00:23:53,016 --> 00:23:55,019
I'm so sorry.

445
00:23:55,052 --> 00:23:58,355
That's terrible news. I-It's terrible news.

446
00:23:58,389 --> 00:24:00,357
When's the funeral? I-I mean,

447
00:24:00,391 --> 00:24:01,691
I should pay my respects.

448
00:24:01,692 --> 00:24:03,828
I wasn't inviting you.

449
00:24:04,895 --> 00:24:06,230
You know,

450
00:24:06,770 --> 00:24:09,351
even after she left you,

451
00:24:09,352 --> 00:24:11,536
you were always there.

452
00:24:11,569 --> 00:24:15,074
Just hanging over us, keeping us apart.

453
00:24:15,083 --> 00:24:18,709
My whole life, I never really knew her.

454
00:24:18,743 --> 00:24:21,045
I mean, she had a real life out here,

455
00:24:21,078 --> 00:24:23,514
and I never saw it and now she's dead.

456
00:24:23,548 --> 00:24:25,854
And I missed the whole thing because of you.

457
00:24:25,855 --> 00:24:29,119
Look, I don't, I-I don't want to fight with you.

458
00:24:29,153 --> 00:24:32,778
I never stopped loving her. She was my wife.

459
00:24:32,779 --> 00:24:35,912
When she left me, it was
the worst day of my life.

460
00:24:38,328 --> 00:24:40,130
You listen to me.

461
00:24:40,164 --> 00:24:43,278
Do not show up at that funeral.

462
00:24:43,568 --> 00:24:46,136
You hear me?

463
00:24:46,326 --> 00:24:48,394
She was my wife, Jack.

464
00:24:50,341 --> 00:24:53,381
I'll do what I damn well please.

465
00:24:53,490 --> 00:24:55,159
(phone clatters)

466
00:25:17,093 --> 00:25:19,062
(birds chirping)

467
00:25:19,095 --> 00:25:20,731
(grunts)

468
00:25:33,744 --> 00:25:35,779
(liquid pouring)

469
00:25:38,435 --> 00:25:41,272
How's the eulogy coming along?

470
00:25:44,876 --> 00:25:46,911
I made a mistake, Debby.

471
00:25:46,944 --> 00:25:49,243
I, uh...

472
00:25:49,622 --> 00:25:51,448
called my dad.

473
00:25:52,784 --> 00:25:54,418
Is he coming?

474
00:25:54,786 --> 00:25:56,919
I told him not to, but

475
00:25:56,920 --> 00:25:58,958
I don't know.

476
00:26:01,002 --> 00:26:02,904
(exhales)

477
00:26:44,184 --> 00:26:46,867
(baby babbling)

478
00:26:48,472 --> 00:26:50,550
It's so great finally having you here.

479
00:26:50,551 --> 00:26:53,645
I hope the, uh, sofa bed was comfortable enough.

480
00:26:53,979 --> 00:26:55,981
(running footsteps)

481
00:26:57,014 --> 00:26:58,382
Ma.

482
00:26:58,415 --> 00:26:59,851
Rebecca asked you a question.

483
00:26:59,884 --> 00:27:01,285
No, no, it's okay, Jack.

484
00:27:01,318 --> 00:27:03,288
MARILYN (laughs): I-I'm sorry.

485
00:27:03,289 --> 00:27:05,458
It's just...

486
00:27:06,860 --> 00:27:09,085
...do you think he knows I'm here?

487
00:27:09,093 --> 00:27:10,828
Of course not.

488
00:27:10,862 --> 00:27:13,826
I mean, I haven't talked to him in years.

489
00:27:16,000 --> 00:27:18,570
Why don't I start on lunch?

490
00:27:28,242 --> 00:27:29,847
Mom, listen.

491
00:27:29,881 --> 00:27:31,683
How about I make your favorite, Jackie?

492
00:27:32,597 --> 00:27:33,907
What's my favorite?

493
00:27:33,908 --> 00:27:35,776
Hot dogs and tomato soup.

494
00:27:37,021 --> 00:27:39,192
-Since when?
-Since always.

495
00:27:39,229 --> 00:27:41,874
You loved hot dogs and tomato soup.

496
00:27:41,875 --> 00:27:44,753
-Maybe Nicky. I-I don't remember...
-No

497
00:27:44,765 --> 00:27:47,935
It wasn't Nicky; It was you.

498
00:27:48,894 --> 00:27:51,335
You'd go out and you'd play in the snow,

499
00:27:51,368 --> 00:27:52,737
and when you came home,

500
00:27:52,770 --> 00:27:56,507
I'd make you hot dogs and tomato soup.

501
00:27:56,540 --> 00:28:00,377
We'd sit at the kitchen table
and we'd watch snow fall.

502
00:28:00,733 --> 00:28:04,048
It's one of my favorite memories.

503
00:28:04,081 --> 00:28:06,940
I know it's not much, but...

504
00:28:07,218 --> 00:28:10,287
it wasn't all bad, your childhood.

505
00:28:12,056 --> 00:28:13,657
I know.

506
00:28:15,993 --> 00:28:18,462
Next time, you'll come visit me.

507
00:28:18,495 --> 00:28:22,125
And we can take the kids skating on the pond.

508
00:28:22,236 --> 00:28:25,306
It's so pretty in the winter.

509
00:28:25,403 --> 00:28:26,904
Okay.

510
00:28:35,780 --> 00:28:37,248
(skate clatters)

511
00:28:41,187 --> 00:28:43,256
♪ (phone ringing)

512
00:28:47,859 --> 00:28:49,227
Hello?

513
00:28:49,228 --> 00:28:50,161
<i>JACK: We never took 'em to the pond</i>

514
00:28:50,194 --> 00:28:51,663
<i>by my mom's house.</i>

515
00:28:51,696 --> 00:28:53,791
To ice-skate.

516
00:28:55,574 --> 00:28:57,402
It was just such a long drive,

517
00:28:57,403 --> 00:28:59,638
and we could never really find the time.

518
00:29:01,172 --> 00:29:03,474
I know.

519
00:29:07,879 --> 00:29:10,181
I got to write a eulogy.

520
00:29:11,348 --> 00:29:13,785
-What are you gonna say?
<i>-I don't know.</i>

521
00:29:15,519 --> 00:29:17,521
Yeah, I don't know.

522
00:29:21,292 --> 00:29:24,086
I don't know what to say.

523
00:29:24,228 --> 00:29:27,266
I've never lost a parent.

524
00:29:27,364 --> 00:29:29,221
But...

525
00:29:29,435 --> 00:29:31,588
I'm here for you.

526
00:29:31,733 --> 00:29:34,847
And I love you very much.

527
00:29:36,073 --> 00:29:38,142
Yeah, I love you, too.

528
00:30:10,574 --> 00:30:12,609
Wish me luck.

529
00:30:16,013 --> 00:30:17,681
(sighs)

530
00:30:31,765 --> 00:30:33,807
(knocking on door)

531
00:30:42,850 --> 00:30:44,426
It's okay.

532
00:30:44,427 --> 00:30:45,919
We'll hide it away.

533
00:30:45,953 --> 00:30:47,955
I'll put aside some money to get you a new one.

534
00:30:48,031 --> 00:30:50,141
Your father will never know.

535
00:30:52,460 --> 00:30:55,396
(quiet chatter)

536
00:30:55,429 --> 00:30:57,431
(organ playing)

537
00:31:01,368 --> 00:31:03,659
-The flowers are nice.
-Yeah, don't start.

538
00:31:03,660 --> 00:31:05,973
-I know it's too much.
-Nah.

539
00:31:05,974 --> 00:31:07,803
She would've loved it.

540
00:31:12,180 --> 00:31:14,848
(chatter continues)

541
00:31:14,882 --> 00:31:16,817
<i>DEBBY: Do you think he's gonna show?</i>

542
00:31:16,850 --> 00:31:19,687
-I don't know.
-(organ stops)

543
00:31:19,720 --> 00:31:22,956
<i>PASTOR: If we can all take our seats.</i>

544
00:31:23,800 --> 00:31:25,316
We'll begin with a reading

545
00:31:25,317 --> 00:31:28,762
by Marilyn's beloved cousin Debra.

546
00:31:36,237 --> 00:31:38,306
(door closes)

547
00:31:40,850 --> 00:31:42,810
DEBBY: Um... (clears throat)

548
00:31:44,901 --> 00:31:47,737
I wrote... I wrote a poem.

549
00:31:49,683 --> 00:31:54,255
She always told me I should
write more poems, so...

550
00:31:55,923 --> 00:31:57,361
Five o'clock,

551
00:31:57,362 --> 00:31:58,726
six o'clock,

552
00:31:58,747 --> 00:32:01,837
seven, eight.

553
00:32:02,230 --> 00:32:05,733
Tell the morning, night's running late.

554
00:32:06,400 --> 00:32:07,706
Nine o'clock,

555
00:32:07,707 --> 00:32:08,702
ten o'clock,

556
00:32:08,736 --> 00:32:10,083
eleven,

557
00:32:10,084 --> 00:32:11,472
noon.

558
00:32:11,505 --> 00:32:14,099
That's not the sun up high,

559
00:32:14,100 --> 00:32:15,948
but the moon.

560
00:32:17,345 --> 00:32:20,881
Wake the stars for a double shift.

561
00:32:20,914 --> 00:32:23,984
It's dark, this night,

562
00:32:24,240 --> 00:32:26,510
and it won't lift.

563
00:32:27,788 --> 00:32:30,858
Because if I stay right here in bed...

564
00:32:34,295 --> 00:32:37,739
...I can still believe she isn't dead.

565
00:32:43,136 --> 00:32:44,438
(paper shuffles)

566
00:32:47,207 --> 00:32:49,076
Rest in peace.

567
00:32:53,547 --> 00:32:54,915
<i>PASTOR: And now I'd like to invite up</i>

568
00:32:54,948 --> 00:32:57,418
Marilyn's beloved son Jack.

569
00:33:14,768 --> 00:33:16,804
My mother was...

570
00:33:19,072 --> 00:33:20,741
...she was a good mother.

571
00:33:22,676 --> 00:33:24,244
She did her best...

572
00:33:26,179 --> 00:33:28,081
...and I loved her.

573
00:33:33,587 --> 00:33:36,590
W-What I want to say...

574
00:33:44,164 --> 00:33:46,351
What I want to say about her...

575
00:33:46,352 --> 00:33:47,935
is...

576
00:33:50,936 --> 00:33:52,638
(door opens)

577
00:34:17,230 --> 00:34:20,368
The house I grew up in

578
00:34:20,401 --> 00:34:23,871
wasn't an easy place to be a son.

579
00:34:25,839 --> 00:34:29,242
But it wasn't an easy
place to be a mother, either.

580
00:34:30,578 --> 00:34:34,515
We did our best, the both of us,

581
00:34:34,647 --> 00:34:38,184
and we were lucky because... we got out.

582
00:34:40,388 --> 00:34:41,742
But...

583
00:34:42,211 --> 00:34:45,225
when you live in a house like that,

584
00:34:45,379 --> 00:34:47,098
there's a part of you that...

585
00:34:47,099 --> 00:34:48,944
never gets out.

586
00:34:50,564 --> 00:34:51,983
So,

587
00:34:52,719 --> 00:34:55,002
you build a new house.

588
00:34:56,370 --> 00:34:59,740
A better house, for a better life.

589
00:35:00,088 --> 00:35:02,376
And you try as hard as you can

590
00:35:02,410 --> 00:35:04,269
to make sure that...

591
00:35:04,270 --> 00:35:06,414
part of you that still lives

592
00:35:06,447 --> 00:35:09,717
in that old house is as small as possible.

593
00:35:13,020 --> 00:35:16,890
I did my best to forget
everything about that house.

594
00:35:18,859 --> 00:35:20,035
But,

595
00:35:20,036 --> 00:35:22,262
there...

596
00:35:22,263 --> 00:35:25,637
there were so many little details.

597
00:35:25,866 --> 00:35:27,390
Uh...

598
00:35:27,901 --> 00:35:30,451
Heavy footsteps.

599
00:35:30,997 --> 00:35:33,518
Cracking of a beer.

600
00:35:33,596 --> 00:35:35,998
The creak of an armchair.

601
00:35:38,145 --> 00:35:41,633
I don't know if she was ever able to forget

602
00:35:41,815 --> 00:35:44,852
any of the details of that house, but I do know

603
00:35:44,885 --> 00:35:47,460
she filled up her life with new ones.

604
00:35:47,555 --> 00:35:49,657
Ones worth remembering.

605
00:35:51,091 --> 00:35:53,026
A dish of chocolates.

606
00:35:53,060 --> 00:35:54,463
A...

607
00:35:54,687 --> 00:35:56,764
basket of yarn.

608
00:35:56,797 --> 00:35:58,198
(laughs softly)

609
00:35:58,231 --> 00:36:01,068
A cat, that keeps coming back.

610
00:36:07,007 --> 00:36:09,877
There are four people here today.

611
00:36:09,910 --> 00:36:11,544
My wife,

612
00:36:11,545 --> 00:36:13,180
my children.

613
00:36:14,181 --> 00:36:16,584
her grandchildren.

614
00:36:17,806 --> 00:36:19,842
They gave me a new home.

615
00:36:22,255 --> 00:36:24,557
And Debby,

616
00:36:24,558 --> 00:36:26,097
Mike...

617
00:36:27,027 --> 00:36:28,880
...and everyone here today.

618
00:36:31,098 --> 00:36:33,501
You gave that to her.

619
00:36:38,038 --> 00:36:40,836
As her son,

620
00:36:41,041 --> 00:36:43,618
I am very grateful

621
00:36:43,830 --> 00:36:45,589
to you all.

622
00:36:47,615 --> 00:36:49,282
Thank you.

623
00:36:55,022 --> 00:36:56,690
Okay, Ma.

624
00:37:00,227 --> 00:37:02,129
Don't let me keep you.

625
00:37:13,640 --> 00:37:16,647
(whispers): Let's scoot you over, honey.

626
00:37:19,758 --> 00:37:21,850
All right, guys, now, this is
very important. It's probably

627
00:37:21,851 --> 00:37:24,688
the most important invention in human history.

628
00:37:24,689 --> 00:37:26,390
It is called, the skull crusher.

629
00:37:26,391 --> 00:37:28,894
Kate, do not do this to your brothers.

630
00:37:28,927 --> 00:37:30,128
Unless they really deserve it.

631
00:37:30,162 --> 00:37:31,664
The skull crusher, the skull crusher!

632
00:37:31,697 --> 00:37:33,699
-(laughter)
-Skull crusher! This guy's too heavy!

633
00:37:33,732 --> 00:37:35,200
He's too heavy. (shouts) I'm down!

634
00:37:35,233 --> 00:37:37,135
The champ is down. Oh, three on one!

635
00:37:37,169 --> 00:37:38,837
3 on 1! Ref!

636
00:37:38,871 --> 00:37:40,873
You know, I keep thinking
she never got to find out

637
00:37:40,906 --> 00:37:42,975
how the book ended.

638
00:37:43,008 --> 00:37:45,968
Clan of the Cave Bear. I mean,
she was only halfway through.

639
00:37:45,969 --> 00:37:47,591
That's what you're worried about?

640
00:37:47,592 --> 00:37:50,111
She read that stupid thing three times already.

641
00:37:50,151 --> 00:37:52,644
REBECCA: I've read Clan of the Cave Bear.

642
00:37:52,645 --> 00:37:54,480
It's got some...

643
00:37:54,481 --> 00:37:56,316
pretty sexy parts.

644
00:37:56,349 --> 00:37:57,192
Between us,

645
00:37:57,193 --> 00:38:00,253
I think Marilyn went for
Mike because, around here,

646
00:38:00,286 --> 00:38:02,922
he's the closest thing she
could find to a Neanderthal.

647
00:38:02,955 --> 00:38:04,274
Hey, hey, I heard that.

648
00:38:04,275 --> 00:38:05,915
And it's accurate.

649
00:38:05,916 --> 00:38:07,960
(laughter)
Didn't need to know that.

650
00:38:07,994 --> 00:38:09,829
I might have to reread this book.

651
00:38:09,916 --> 00:38:12,486
<i>MIKE: Give 'em the bottle opener! Bottle opener!</i>

652
00:38:12,641 --> 00:38:15,168
Hey, do you think the cat's gonna be okay?

653
00:38:15,201 --> 00:38:16,305
No, Jack.

654
00:38:16,306 --> 00:38:19,639
I think the cat is 100% gonna get hit by a car.

655
00:38:19,672 --> 00:38:22,175
(laughter)

656
00:38:22,208 --> 00:38:23,809
Ah...

657
00:38:23,843 --> 00:38:25,478
<i>(Mike shouting playfully)</i>

658
00:38:25,720 --> 00:38:28,522
(Kids laughing)

659
00:38:29,962 --> 00:38:31,893
MIKE: Just like that.

660
00:38:31,894 --> 00:38:33,653
That's the move. That's the move.

661
00:38:33,686 --> 00:38:35,388
Get back on your feet. Just like that.

662
00:38:35,421 --> 00:38:37,490
Like a champ. There you go.

663
00:38:37,523 --> 00:38:39,359
All right, zoom back down. Nicely done.

664
00:38:57,397 --> 00:38:59,312
All right. Who's hungry?

665
00:38:59,345 --> 00:39:00,813
KIDS: Me!

666
00:39:00,846 --> 00:39:02,815
Eh, I could eat.

667
00:39:02,848 --> 00:39:05,085
Okay, I'll get something started.

668
00:39:05,118 --> 00:39:06,557
No, no, that's okay.

669
00:39:06,558 --> 00:39:07,553
I got it.

670
00:39:39,252 --> 00:39:42,647
<i>I made your favorite, Jackie.</i>

671
00:39:43,189 --> 00:39:46,652
<i>This should warm you up.</i>

672
00:39:55,268 --> 00:39:57,891
JACK: All right, so my mom...

673
00:39:57,958 --> 00:40:01,574
...used to make this for me.

674
00:40:01,607 --> 00:40:03,276
Are these hot dogs?

675
00:40:03,309 --> 00:40:06,122
-Where's the bun?
-Just try it. Try it.

676
00:40:12,017 --> 00:40:13,586
How is it?

677
00:40:13,619 --> 00:40:15,343
It's so good.

678
00:40:22,295 --> 00:40:25,293
Here, let me have one of these.

679
00:40:27,967 --> 00:40:29,427
Mmm!

680
00:40:29,428 --> 00:40:31,703
It's not bad.

681
00:40:48,721 --> 00:40:49,955
(sniffles)

682
00:40:51,060 --> 00:40:53,128
(footsteps approach)

683
00:41:05,371 --> 00:41:08,737
I don't have a mom anymore.

684
00:41:12,869 --> 00:41:17,029
(crying)

685
00:41:41,993 --> 00:41:43,676
(Jack sniffling)

686
00:42:04,864 --> 00:42:06,999
<i>(Kids:) He dipped his hot dog in the soup.</i>

687
00:42:07,032 --> 00:42:09,769
<i>She did it, too.</i>

688
00:42:09,802 --> 00:42:13,105
That's okay. You know, tomato soup is...

689
00:42:13,138 --> 00:42:15,107
(voice fading)

690
00:42:15,140 --> 00:42:16,174
♪

691
00:42:16,175 --> 00:42:18,175
---oOo---

