"Previously onThis Is Us..."
First day of summer, we don't want to be
the last ones in the pool.
Hey, where you going?
Heard the pool closed down.
Just want to check it out before it disappears.
What are you doing?
I hate that I'm doing this over FaceTime,
-and I miss you.
-I miss you, too.
36 blissful hours
until I have to listen to the
Southwest flight attendants
turn the safety protocol
into a parody song again.
If you and Toby need your space, just tell me.
Yeah, Kev, it's...
that's not even our problem right now.
We have a lot more going on than that.
Hey, can you just, can you
help me instead of instructing me?
Yeah, Tobe, I can.
I'm here with them every day doing the hard work.
What do you want me to do?
Just not have any opinions about our kids
because you're overly
sensitive about everything I say?
We just keep having the same
argument over and over again.
You're upset that I'm not around more.
I'm sensitive about that.
Pointed jabs. Rinse and repeat.
Come on, guys, come on. First day of summer,
we don't want to be the last ones in the pool.
And guess what Mom and Dad have for you guys.
REBECCA and JACK: Swim goggles!
-I want one.
-REBECCA and JACK: Yeah?
-Okay.
-Come on, come on.
REBECCA: Hey, Bug, you want some goggles?
[splash]
-KEVIN: I want to go on the diving board.
-[whistle blows]
JACK: Don't you think we
ought to teach you how to swim
-first, Kev?
-REBECCA: Yeah, I know
you didn't like taking your swim lessons,
but they helped your brother
learn how to swim at the Y.
OLDER KID: Guys, I'm gonna touch the drain!
That girl is swimming upside down.
No. [chuckles] She's doing the backstroke.
And you would've learned how to do that, too,
if you stayed in class at the Y.
KEVIN: I want to dive off the diving board
-and touch the drain.
-JACK: Hey,
once more for the cheap seats.
We got to teach you how to swim first, okay?
RANDALL: There's Mr. Mike. Can I go see him?
-JACK: Hey, you got Kate?
-REBECCA: Yeah.
I got Kate.
Sweetheart, how about,
we try going in? Yeah?
-Yeah, let's take those shoes off. Come on.
-[whistle blows]
-REBECCA: Come on. Baby...
-It's too cold.
No, no, no, no, no, but we have to get in first.
It's not gonna be too cold once you get in.
Come on.
Come on, g_ Ow, Kate.
Come on, baby doll.
No? It's fun.
It's nice and warm. Try it.
Ow. You're hurting Mommy. You're hurting me.
Come on. Here. Take my hand. Come on.
Wow.
Can't believe we'll never be back here again.
I know. It feels weird.
Goodbye, pool. Thanks for the memories.
Because of you, pool,
Randall got to see our mother
in a bathing suit every summer,
and for that he is forever grateful.
-[chuckles] You're demented.
-Ow. You know it's true.
-Hey.
-Get help.
I... Where's the brick?
-What brick?
-The brick that propped open the door.
-Nice.
-Oh...
-Hmm?
-[chuckles] This brick?
[laughs] Great. Great, yeah, so we're locked in?
-[brick clatters] -KATE:
Oh, God, yeah, so this is how
my obituary will read-- um...
"Sunny Delight poster boy, valedictorian
and 'other' die trapped in pool."
No, come on, Kate. You know they're gonna mention
the fact I got cut out of Days of Our Lives.
-Stop.
-Ah.
KEVIN: Can you not hit me?
Hey, hey, hey; Can we look for another way out?
Come on.
How is this my life?
REBECCA: I need you all
to hear my voice right now.
Your mother's voice with all of her faculties.
You will not make your
lives smaller because of me.
This thing that's happening to me
will not be the thing that holds you back.
So, take the risks.
Make the big moves,
even if they're small moves.
Forge ahead with your lives
in any and every direction that moves you.
I'm your mother,
and I'm sick,
and I'm asking you to be fearless.
Safe travels, siblings.
Okay, we'll see you guys in L.A.
for Mom and Mig's anniversary party.
[car door closes]
-TOBY: All right, you ready?
-Yeah.
Hey, Tobe.
We can't sustain this,
living in two different cities,
so I'd like to go to San Francisco
with you for the weekend.
-See how it feels.
-Really?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, I'd like that.
Okay.
I'm really excited for this weekend.
I know. Me, too. Only four
more days till you come see me.
A whole weekend just you and me.
-When's the last time we did that?
-I don't know. One, two...
three lifetimes ago, at least.
-Oh, man, I am so excited.
-[cell phone chimes]
Oh, you know what, I got to run
All right, babies, I love you so much.
I'll see you soon. Be good to Mommy, okay?
You say bye to Daddy?
-Bye, babies. I love you.
-Bye.
-Bye. -Bye.
-Love you. Bye. -Bye. Love you.
-Love you.
Okay. Oh, 9:25. It's time to go to the park.
-Park.
-Yay, we're going to the park.
♪ Tuesday ♪
♪ In the park ♪
♪ Jack's excited for the swing set ♪
♪ And 12 steps to the sidewalk. ♪
And then what are we gonna do?
Then we make a turn to the...
-Left.
-The left. Exactly.
♪ To the lover of my youth ♪
♪ The solace for my age... ♪
You just wrote your first song, Courtney.
♪ From what harms ♪
♪ You will reach for me ♪
KATE [laughs]: Is that silly?
♪ On our darkest days ♪
♪ And I will come home ♪
♪ To your arms ♪
KATE: Can we do it? Can we do it?
♪ And I will hold... ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey, we're on our way ♪
♪ Wave to Gregory ♪
♪ How's your day? ♪
You know what? Stop putting me in your dumb songs
if I'm not getting a writer's cut.
Come on, you're part of the neighborhood.
You're a part of the song.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Slow down, bud. Slow down.
♪ Sheila's a jolly good fellow ♪
ALL: ♪ Sheila's a jolly good fellow ♪
[overlapping congratulations]
Thank you. Thank you, Kate.
You made an old gal feel very special.
KATE: Oh, good.
-Thank you.
-Yes.
Aren't you gonna have some, too?
No, I'm good. I'm just gonna have some water.
♪ There is time upon ♪
♪ Your faces ♪
♪ I will cherish you ♪
♪ Till you leave me for... ♪
[WOMAN on TV]: ...sensitive
side, then you turn into a total ass.
Is that a pretty accurate description
of our relationship, Tyler?
MADISON: So, Edward Norton
was just imagining Brad Pitt
the entire time?
[chuckles] Are you just now realizing that?
We've seen this, like, 18 times.
It's just so much shirtless Brad Pitt.
-I get distracted. [laughs]
-No, I...
Fair. Fair.
You know what's funny? Um...
Sometimes, I...
imagine
hanging out with Old Toby.
"Old Toby"?
Yeah.
You know, who he was
before he lost all the weight at the gym
and got his fancy job and better clothes.
I guess Old Toby's like my Tyler Durden.
I-I know that sounds crazy.
[sighs] You guys just need a good weekend.
Yeah.
We do.
You're right.
Which is why I'm just...
I'm gonna go to the Bay to be with my bae,
you know, with an open heart and mind.
Old Toby is still in there.
Go find him.
Yeah.
Okay.
[cell phone buzzes]
Hey, babe. Don't worry,
I'm already packed and leaving on time.
-Miracles do exist.
-TOBY [over phone]: There's a,
there's a, uh, slight hitch in our giddy-up.
Okay, my-my meeting for my
Tokyo project got rescheduled,
so I won't be able to be at the airport,
so I-I booked you the finest electric vehicle
that San Francisco has to offer to pick you up,
and I am... I am, uh, hustling here
to make sure I can get back to the apartment
to personally roll out the
red carpet for you myself.
No worries; We have the whole weekend.
Oh, I know it, Kate. I am very excited.
I have made plans. I've made so many plans,
my plans have plans.
Listen, I'm gonna try and clear my plate here.
Uh, I'm gonna text you the guy's info.
I'll leave my phone on, in
case there are any problems,
and I hope you have a safe flight.
-All right, I love you.
-Okay, love you.
♪ I know these days ♪
♪ Will pass away... ♪
Well, that sucks.
-You would've picked me up.
-Without question.
But do not fret, my sweet pet,
I will be with you the whole time.
It's gonna be fun.
♪ So I will hold ♪
♪ You dear. ♪
Come on, Kate, just take one more step in.
-I don't want to.
-But look.
Mommy took one more step in, and she's fine.
Just put your face in the water.
Pretend it's one giant bathtub.
You blow bubbles in the bath all the time.
Right? Watch.
Mommy'll do it.
Ooh, there's probably a lot of pee in here.
JACK: ...sinking to the bottom.
Hey, how about you swim to that wall.
-Think you can do that?
-[squeals] See?
-It's easy.
-JACK: Okay, here we go.
But, Kate, how will we know
that your brand-new bathing suit even works
if you don't get it wet?
Jack.
Yeah, I-I got him.
Jack!
Okay. I got you.
-He's just a child, Jack.
-Yeah,
-and someday he's gonna be a man.
-[coughing]
Hey, you're not ready for the deep end yet, bud.
Leave me alone.
[sighs] Okay, uh, hey,
Bug, you're gonna stay here with Daddy.
I'm trying to get her to
put her face in the water,
so good luck with that.
-Okay.
Great.
Hey, 'no problemo'. We got this.
Put your face in the water.
Daddy, it's not gonna happen.
All right; Why do they
make it so hard to get out?
They're trying to make it hard to get into
so teenagers like you aren't
wandering around drinking beer,
playing with safety equipment.
-Hey.
What? Oh.
[laughs]
I'm literally trapped.
Ah, don't worry.
We're not gonna be stuck here all night.
No, I'm not... I'm not talking
about the pool. Although...
...if I die where I had my first sloppy kiss
with Stuart, I will be pissed. Um...
No, I'm...
trapped in Pittsburgh.
What's so bad about Pittsburgh?
Nothing. Nothing's wrong with Pittsburgh. It's...
It's my life in Pittsburgh.
Yeah, I mean,
I wake up, eat breakfast,
go to the diner where I serve
greasy food to unhappy people,
then I go home and eat dinner, watch TV.
Oh, yeah, there's-there's the added bonus lately
of listening to Mom get flirty on the phone.
She has a flirty voice. It's... it's haunting.
Only thing I get excited about is
eating ice cream at the
end of the day, but, um...
we can all see where that's gotten me.
So...
Aren't you glad you asked?
You being here felt like cause for celebration.
This is some of the finest bubbly going.
-Well...
-I am so excited
that you are finally here.
I can hardly stand it.
-I can't believe it. You're here.
-[chuckles] I know.
-Cheers.
-Mmm.
-Très délicieux.
Come here. I want to show you something.
Over to the right is Coit Tower,
over the hill is North Beach,
and if you look right through
there, when there's not fog,
which is...
never...
-[laughs]
-...is the Golden Gate Bridge.
-Wow.
It's a really beautiful view.
It really is, isn't it?
Mmm.
It has been...
forever.
It sure feels like it.
I think I'm nervous.
-Oh...
-[chuckles]
Well, it's cute.
[sighs] Can we just...
promise to not let this much time go by?
I... promise.
Now, I think we have about 20 minutes
before the vegan barbecue arrives,
which I know doesn't sound
sexy, but I promise you that it is.
-Well, then, bon appétit.
-Mm-hmm.
-[giggles]
-[grunts]
[sighs]
I missed that. Mmm.
Well, I mean... you.
-W-Well, everything.
-Yeah.
-You know what I mean. [sighs]
-[laughs] Yeah.
-Is that offensive?
-Offensive?
I want those words written on my tombstone.
Oh, babe, The Great British Bake Offis back.
You want a little cake and a cuddle?
How about a little squeeze and a scone?
Ah, I would love to, my sweet profiterole,
but I have... I actually have
a work phone call that I have to make real quick
that I would've made earlier, were it not for
the eight-hour time difference in Tokyo,
so I'm gonna knock this out
real quick, I will not be long
Then it is just me, you, Paul and Prue; Okay?
Okay; Yeah, I'll just be here.
You know I'm always down
for a little Netflix and chill, right?
Wink!
-[laughs]
-Let's see what this guy's watching.
Oh, right,
Inside Bill's Brain: Decoding Bill Gates.
-What is this, school? Ick.
-Ew.
[grunts] Let's see here.
Oh, oh, oh, who-who-who are these
stranger dangers?
He doesn't even know how many quarters there are
in a baseball match.
-Ridiculous. And 5K is...
-[laughs]
Since when does he run without being chased?
Oh, and these-these fancy
pants, these fancy clothes.
Ooh! Look at me.
What, do you get poured into these pants? Ugh.
[blows sharply]
[Imitating James Bond]: Hello!
The name's Boring.
James Boring.
Oh, uh-oh, Kate, uh-oh.
Yeah.
It's a...
♪ a fat guy
♪ in a little coat. [gasps]
♪ A fat guy in a little coat. [laughs]
-All right, that's enough.
-Come on! You guys have sex
for, like, the first time in a millennia,
and dude gets up to take a phone call?
At least he waited to put his earbuds back in.
-Give me the jacket.
-Okay, all right, all right.
I took it too far.
I was just trying to have a little fun.
I was trying to make you laugh.
Do you have any idea how much I miss your laugh?
Fine.
But you're gonna miss me.
Good morning; Love of my life.
-Hi.
-What's this?
This is some of my favorite coffee
from my favorite coffee shop in the entire city.
I ran down and picked us up a...
-a couple of cups.
-Ooh.
"Brew Can Do It." [laughs]
You know I love a coffee
shop with a good pun name.
Yeah, and check this out. Okay.
So, I have marked
everything that I think we can do today.
You ready? Okay,
so after we enjoy our java, I'm going to take you
for a delicious brunch at the Fairmont.
After that, I thought we could go to this cool
photography exhibit at the de Young Museum
in Golden Gate Park.
I know how much you enjoy it
-when we pretend to understand art.
-I do.
For ten minutes at a time, of course.
Yeah, anything longer just,
like, defeats the purpose.
Then we're coming back here
to get all gussied up for my boss's
cocktail party tonight.
After which, I am taking you
to a very, very exclusive
dinner at the Top of the Mark,
where I have procured, using my wit, my charm,
and yes, my best friend Benjamin Franklin,
a table right on the window
with a view of the entire city.
-Wow.
-Yeah.
[sighs] Well, you got this city down.
I have been living here alone for three months,
so Mr. Frommer and I have become pretty tight.
-[chuckles]
-So, what do you say?
[sighs] It really... It sounds amazing.
-Yeah.
I was just... I don't know.
Babe, I was just hoping that
we could have an old-school
'KaToby day', where there's
just no fancy plans or pressure.
We could just go out and
see where the day takes us.
Oh. Um...
Okay.
Sure. Yeah.
Well, if that's what you want
to do, then that's what we'll do.
Really, babe? 'Cause I
know that you worked so hard.
-I'm just...
-No, listen to me.
Being together is the only
thing that matters, okay?
Plus, you said "KaToby,"
and you know well and good
that when you use our ship
name, you get whatever you want.
I love that.
[♫ "Deep In Love" by Bonny
Light Horseman playing]
-[bell rings]
-KATE: Yeah!
Didn't you love those Rice-A-Roni ads as a kid?
♪ Rice-A-Roni ♪
BOTH: ♪ The San Francisco treat. ♪
[imitates bell ringing]
Do you think they'll let me ring the bell?
Maybe.
Maybe. Let's ask. Here.
♪ Gathering flowers ♪
♪ Both red and blue ♪
♪ How little thought of what ♪
♪ What love ♪
♪ Could do ♪
♪ Don't you... ♪
Hi, babies. Hi.
We're having a great time, but we're missing you.
-We are.
-JACK: Where's Daddy?
-KATE: Daddy's here, too. Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah, if you guys
could just put all of that in an email, okay?
Yeah, I got to get on, uh, an important call.
Big VIPs on the other line. Yeah. Thank you. Bye.
We wanted to show you the
sea lions that are usually here,
but today they went somewhere else.
Not all of them.
[imitating barking sea lion]
♪ Break my heart ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Don't you ♪
♪ Break my heart. ♪
So, where are we now? Wait, let me guess.
Is this the neighborhood where they filmed
So I Married an Axe Murderer?
"Look at the size of that boy's head.
It's like a... an orange on a toothpick."
-[both laugh]
-N-not quite.
-Oh.
-I-I wanted you...
-Uh-huh.
-...to see this.
We haven't really mentioned
the elephant in the room,
and I think it's time that we
at least start talking about it.
I miss you.
I miss the kids, and I think,
I think that this would be
perfect for us.
To... buy?
To think about,
if you're willing.
Can I show you?
Come on.
There's three bedrooms upstairs,
each with their own bathroom.
And don't forget the converted ADU
off the garage for grandma.
-Good to see you, Toby.
-TOBY: How are you, Larry?
Thanks for seeing us.
-This is my wife.
-Kate.
So nice to finally meet you.
-Hi.
-[Larry laughs]
Toby, in answer to your
question, I found out the owners
updated the kitchen and the HVAC
five years ago.
-Great.
LARRY: And they'd be open
to leaving the trampoline for Jack and Hailey.
Yes!
[Toby laughs]
-I'll let you guys explore.
-Thank you.
Oh, yeah, there's a trampoline.
[chuckles]
How many times have you been here?
Just a couple. I run by here all the time.
I've always loved this house.
One day, a "for sale" sign
went up, and, I don't know,
it just got me thinking.
The great part is that
the kids' rooms aren't too far
from what would be our room,
so we'd be close but not
right on top of each other.
Come on, I want to show you.
Larry, thank you so much. I'll call you, okay?
I will. Don't do anything until I call.
[sighs]
So... so, what'd you think, huh?
I think it's overwhelming.
I'm... I am sure. I know that,
I know that this feels quick,
but don't panic, the owners
aren't accepting offers
until the day after tomorrow,
so we have plenty of time
to think about it and put
together a pros-and-cons list.
Uh, the day after tomorrow is not enough time
to-to make this... this huge decision.
I mean, Toby, can we even afford it?
Yes. We can.
Because I may have already gotten us
preapproved for a loan
and talked to a real estate agent back in L.A.
about what we could get for our house.
Toby,
I thought that we were just, like,
wrapping our heads around
the idea of San Francisco, and...
and now we're making this big decision
and putting an offer on a house
that I'm-I'm seeing for the first time?
-I know.
I'm sorry. I just, I-I didn't,
I didn't want to present you with hypotheticals.
Kate, trust me, I have put
a lot of thought into this.
There are these incredible hiking trails
that lead to an awesome park right on the Bay.
We're near the airport
for easy trips back to L.A.
Kate;
We can do this.
We can make a life up here,
together.
Come on, let me show you where
your mom and Miguel can stay.
Come on. You're gonna love it.
Okay, Katie girl. You ready to
get your face in the water, huh?
Come on, come on. Let's do
it together, let's do it together.
-We'll do it together.
-No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay, how about, uh...
How about a new tactic, okay?
How about... how about we float on your back?
Okay? I'll be right here so
that you don't go under, okay?
All right, here, just let go, just let go.
Okay, so...
you're in a bad spot,
but that's just for now.
Dad hasn't been gone that long.
-Everything's weird.
-Yeah.
And maybe instead of
focusing on what's not so great,
you can focus on what you want to happen next.
Like, what do you want to
do? What do you want to be?
God, you guys. Come on;
Guidance counselor's not
a good look on either of you.
If you could dream of doing anything,
what would it be? Anything.
That is the problem.
I can't think of anything.
Okay, I'm not like you guys.
You know,
you want to be an actor,
and you want to change the world.
We're the exact same age, and you guys are
way ahead of me.
Randall, you've already
met the love of your life.
And, Kevin, I mean,
you're so far ahead, you've
already ruined one marriage.
I just...
When I look into my future...
I literally see
nothing.
No job, no family.
Nothing.
TOBY: You know,
you wouldn't think it would
take this long to get a Lyft
in the town where the company was started.
Hey, listen, I'm sorry
that I sprung the house thing on you like that.
I-I meant for it to be a grand gesture,
and I think it might have been a grand mistake.
I'm just excited for you to be up here.
I know.
I am, too.
I'm just processing is all.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Yeah.
Everybody at work is really
excited to meet you tonight.
I think we're gonna have a really good time.
Me, too.
-The driver can cancel? That's a thing?
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
-Can we just walk?
Uh, it...
No, I'll just get another one.
Well, I thought you said
your boss lived close by.
Yeah, it's not far, but it's... it's...
-You know.
-But what?
It's-it's all up... uphill, so...
There we go. Casey is
gonna be here in eight minutes.
Why is the car spinning in circles?
Oh, this is so beautiful.
Yeah, my-my boss sold his first company
to Google for a boatload of money.
Like, literally, that's how he got his boat.
But he's surprisingly down
to earth, as is everyone,
especially for a bunch of tech weenies.
Oh, and here's a warning.
Do not ask anyone what they actually do
for work, trust me.
There they are. The couple of the hour.
Finally, I get to meet the famous Kate.
-Hi.
-Kate, this is my boss, Amir.
Nice to meet you, and you are way too young
to be the Amir that I've heard so much about.
What are you, like, 25?
I love her instantly, Toby.
-I knew you would.
-[Kate laughs]
-Well, thank you for having us tonight.
-Are you kidding?
I've been wanting to meet
you ever since Toby joined us.
-Come on, I'll give you a tour.
-Okay. -[Toby sighs]
So you've been with the company a while, then?
Yupper. Started here after Facebook,
-and just never left.
-Wow. And what do you do?
Uh, you know how most businesses can't afford
non-technical managers
ideating unrealistic features?
Mm-hmm.
And your kids are so cute.
Toby showed me the picture
of Hailey wrapped around Jack like a baby koala.
I called my wife immediately
and told her, "Let's have a baby."
-Oh.
-TOBY: Their cuteness is powerful.
-It really is. Thank you.
So, whether it's reporting or machine learning,
I automate tasks for the company
because no one wants communication
and product inefficiencies between the engineers
and everybody else, right?
-Right.
-Which is where I come in.
What do you know about infrastructure platforms?
-Um... -She thinks they're
overrated, just like Smash Mouth.
Have you tried this? Try this.
-Oh. Thanks. Sure.
-Thanks so much. Can I borrow her? Hey, come on.
-Enjoy.
-[laughs]
How you doing? You doing okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I really am.
-I mean, Toby, everybody's really great.
-Yeah.
-Hi, Kate. Sorry to interrupt.
-Hi.
But Warren said you agreed
to trade him Steph Curry.
-What? No!
-Is that true?
Why would I do that? Curry's
like the heart of my team.
Sorry. This is fantasy basketball.
I'll be back in one and a half seconds.
-Bro.
[laughing]: What are you...
What are you talking about, I give you Curry?
-WARREN: You said it.
-TOBY: I said it in a bar.
-WARREN: Oh, no.
-I said it in bar.
You can't believe anything anyone says in a bar.
-WARREN: That counts.
-That does not count.
-Not in the state of California.
-It's happening. I'm sorry.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm so happy you came. [laughs]
Toby's been a lifesaver up here.
Most popular at the company by multiple degrees
in an office where everyone
genuinely likes each other.
Well, the feeling is very mutual.
Thank God he turned down
the job offer back in L.A.
Losing him would've been a huge blow for us.
-Will you just excuse me for a second?
-Sure.
♪ That this is only night ♪
♪ This is only night, son ♪
♪ The setting sun ♪
♪ It has no tomb ♪
♪ The stars above us are angels ♪
♪ And that is the messiah moon. ♪
-Do you understand it?
-No, not at all.
-Uh... Warren might.
-We work here, and we don't understand it.
-Yeah.
-This is my point.
-We need to leave.
Uh, yeah, good-good call.
We got to... We have dinner reservations, okay?
Let's just find Amir, and we can say goodbye.
We're not saying goodbye.
We're not going to dinner. We need to leave.
Okay. I'll just call us a Lyft.
Hey, what is...? Okay.
Kate? Kate? Kate, Kate, Kate.
What is...? What's-what's the matter?
You got a job offer in L.A.?
Y-Yeah, I applied for that job
long before I got the job up here.
And the official offer came in
two weeks ago, and it was a joke.
It was, like, a big step-down
in title, and barely any money.
You made a decision that directly affects me
and our children without telling me?
-You lied to me.
-I didn't lie to you.
And you made a fool out of me in there.
Uh...
Can we just talk about this
before we get in this car?
No. I need a minute.
All right, how much?
How much what?
How much more does the job pay up here?
You want me to give you numbers?
-Yeah.
Yeah, Toby, I'd like numbers.
I need to know how much
is worth me giving up my job,
and a house where Jack feels comfortable,
not to mention being near
my family and my sick mother
in the same city as Hailey
has two cousins the same age
to grow up with.
-That's not a fair question.
It's not fair that you're not
thinking about our family?
I'm not thinking about our family?
Wow. That's awesome.
How have you been, then?
What do you think I have been doing up here?
Living out of a suitcase,
not-not sure which city I'm waking up in,
spending all these lonely
nights in this antiseptic apartment.
This is all for our family, Kate.
Do you know that we have a blind son?
Oh, really? I-I didn't realize.
I thought he was just clumsy.
He knows every inch of our house.
We're teaching him a song to get to the park.
Okay, you think it's easy to just, like,
uproot him and-and put him in a new environment?
Okay; You get to ask a bunch of questions.
Let me ask a few.
Have you penciled out how expensive it would be
to send Jack to a special school if he needs one?
Because I have.
Never mind all of the assistive
technology he's gonna need.
Do you know a braille
notetaker alone costs six grand?
And that-that-that... that's just
when he's living at home with us.
What if he wants to go off to college
or live on his own one day?
I have big dreams for our son, Kate,
and I'm gonna be damn sure
that he has whatever he needs
to live his life however he so chooses.
And we can't afford any of that
on an assistant teacher salary
and some middling job in Los Angeles
that doesn't pay me any real money.
Right. Money.
Still haven't told me the number.
It's not just about the money, is it?
It's kind of about you. Right?
Watching you up here; I don't know
You're pretty much the happiest
you've ever been, aren't you?
Kate; I am away from my family.
I'm-I'm on four planes a week. I am exhausted.
Yeah, but you're happy, right?
You're happy with your job, with your stature.
-[laughs]
-Personally, you're happy.
I-I don't know why you just can't admit it.
Yes, yes! I'm happy! I'm happy.
And this is gonna sound like a strange question
to ask my wife, but don't you want that for me?
Of course I want that for you.
Then why doesn't it feel that way?
You know, sometimes I look at you, Toby,
and I don't even know who you are anymore.
I don't.
You drink expensive champagne.
You know how to work a room.
You're not the guy
who wore those terrible Hawaiian shirts
or would make those loud, inappropriate jokes.
You're not the guy who'd ask for the wine list
and says, "Bring me the whole left side."
The goofy guy from our first date,
the Old Toby,
the guy that I fell in love with.
I miss him.
I miss him so much that I've been picturing him
this weekend here with me.
So this whole time that I've been thinking
that we're really connecting,
you've just been imagining yourself
with a different version of me?
That is not what I said.
That's not what I'm saying.
-Is he... is he here?
-Don't do that.
Is he here now? Oh, you
know, maybe we should just...
we should get him out here.
Hey, let's get Old Toby out here
to join in on this fun! Huh? Hey, you know...
you know what I'd love to say to Old Toby, Kate?
He was a mess.
He was miserable and insecure and self-loathing.
And all-all of that goofiness
and-and the loud jokes--
That was out of self-defense.
Kate, you fell in love with a coping mechanism.
And FYI, if that guy hadn't changed,
he would have jumped off a
bridge or died of a heart attack
making a joke at his own expense.
Wait. I almost did that last part.
What is so terrible about me right now?
That I don't want to dress like a clown?
That I want to buy a nice house for my family?
I don't know, Toby.
You're just different.
And you're not, Kate?
Why is this conversation all about me?
When-when... when we first got together,
it felt like you and me against the world.
And today, you couldn't go 20 minutes
just us, without FaceTiming the kids.
After shooting down an entire day
that I spent weeks planning for you.
Admit I'm happy?
Kate, what about you?
You love the life that you are living,
this life that you are building without me,
where you're the... you're the working supermom
who gets to live with her brother again.
You finally get to be the fully realized
version of yourself, and all you had to do
was get me out of that house.
When I was younger, I would...
well, I couldn't even think about the future
because it just was blank.
And... [sighs heavily]
I felt that way for a really...
a long, long time until I met you.
And you...
you took away a lot of that emptiness.
And so, yeah, Toby, now...
I have a full life
that I could have never dreamed.
And I feel healthy, I feel connected,
I feel like I have a purpose.
I love my life. I'm-I'm really, really happy.
Except for the one thing that's
making me really, really sad.
Thank you.
We should have talked about the L.A. offer
even if it wasn't a good one.
We probably should have also talked
about the fact that for most of my life,
I have been desperate,
desperate to feel valued at my job,
to not just feel like I'm taking up space.
I can relate.
And...
I'm not just taking up space here, Kate.
And neither are you.
As wrung out and as exhausted as I am,
I'm happy for us.
We have both figured out our worth.
We evolved.
I love you.
I love our family.
But there are some
real-world logistics at play here,
and we are gonna have to move to San Francisco.
That's how these logistics are gonna play out.
I need you to get on board because...
moving here is the only way
that we are gonna stay a family.
It is the only option.
[Kate sighs]
I'm gonna go get some air.
Okay.
[door opens]
All right, gang; It's time
to get the hell out of here.
How?
We climb.
Hey, Katie girl, look at me. Look at me.
I believe you can do it.
Okay, and Mommy, Randall and Kevin--
They believe you can do it.
Now the only thing that needs to happen
is that youbelieve you can do it.
Okay?
I'm gonna go over to the other side,
and then I'll help you down.
[grunting]
Just...
I'll meet you at the top.
One step at a time, Kate. No sweat.
[panting]
[breathing deeply]
Okay, Katie girl.
Here's the moment.
Just let go. Katie, just let go. Let go.
I will never let go, Daddy, ever!
Yeah? Why not?
Why would I?
RANDALL: Come on, Kate. Just grab it.
-Guys...
-You got this.
-You got this, Kate.
-You got it!
Okay!
-You got it.
-[grunts]
KEVIN: You're almost there, Kate. Let's go.
KEVIN: Almost there! Oh!
-[gasps, shrieks] No.
-Okay.
-Okay, relax.
-Uh-uh. No.
-We're gonna try it again.
-No, I can't.
I can't, no.
No.
This one.
How'd she do?
[scoffs] Today is not the day.
[panting]
[laughing]
[ ♪ line ringing]
PHILLIP: Hey, Kate. How's Frisco?
Is it foggy and expensive?
Did you, uh, fill Sheila's job yet?
Uh, no, but we're looking at applicants.
I'd like to be considered.
---oOo---