1
00:00:00,001 --> 00:00:02,126
<i>Previously on "This Is Us..."</i>

2
00:00:02,127 --> 00:00:03,961
Soph, I made a horrible mistake.

3
00:00:03,962 --> 00:00:06,464
It happened one time and it didn't mean anything.

4
00:00:06,465 --> 00:00:08,632
I'm so sorry.

5
00:00:08,633 --> 00:00:10,134
I heard the pool closed down.

6
00:00:10,135 --> 00:00:11,469
The one we went to growing up.

7
00:00:11,470 --> 00:00:13,370
Just want to check it out before it disappears.

8
00:00:13,371 --> 00:00:14,629
Kev, right now's probably not the right...

9
00:00:14,630 --> 00:00:16,397
Don't follow me. I'm not 12.

10
00:00:16,398 --> 00:00:18,052
Build me that house.

11
00:00:18,054 --> 00:00:20,454
The house he was gonna build for me.

12
00:00:21,413 --> 00:00:22,746
This is it, this is

13
00:00:22,747 --> 00:00:24,014
the land that will eventually become

14
00:00:24,015 --> 00:00:26,884
the Pearson family mecca.

15
00:00:26,885 --> 00:00:28,786
Hey, look at me!

16
00:00:28,787 --> 00:00:30,354
You give me that photo,

17
00:00:30,355 --> 00:00:32,790
or the entire village pays,
including you and your child.

18
00:00:32,791 --> 00:00:34,492
Would you want to help

19
00:00:34,493 --> 00:00:36,873
Nicky oversee the construction?

20
00:00:36,884 --> 00:00:38,462
I'll think about it.

21
00:00:38,463 --> 00:00:39,897
You'll think about it. Very good.

22
00:00:39,898 --> 00:00:41,398
Well, you think away.

23
00:00:41,399 --> 00:00:43,701
I'm a little nervous, so I wrote down some notes.

24
00:00:43,702 --> 00:00:45,069
Um...

25
00:00:45,070 --> 00:00:47,964
There is no easy way to start this.

26
00:00:48,073 --> 00:00:49,307
Um...

27
00:00:52,424 --> 00:00:55,525
---

28
00:01:02,854 --> 00:01:04,388
Come on, guys! Come on!

29
00:01:04,389 --> 00:01:05,656
First day of summer, we don't want

30
00:01:05,657 --> 00:01:07,258
to be the last ones in the pool.

31
00:01:07,259 --> 00:01:08,525
And you know what Mom and Dad have for

32
00:01:08,526 --> 00:01:09,476
-You guys.
-Oh!

33
00:01:09,477 --> 00:01:10,561
Swim goggles!

34
00:01:10,562 --> 00:01:13,130
-I want one!
-Share, share...

35
00:01:21,508 --> 00:01:23,684
I want to go on the diving board.

36
00:01:23,686 --> 00:01:25,442
Don't you think we ought to
teach you how to swim first,

37
00:01:25,443 --> 00:01:26,877
-Kev?
-Yeah, I know you didn't like

38
00:01:26,878 --> 00:01:28,746
taking your swim lessons, but they sure

39
00:01:28,747 --> 00:01:30,635
helped your brother learn to swim at the Y.

40
00:01:30,637 --> 00:01:32,938
Guys, I'm gonna touch the drain!

41
00:01:37,556 --> 00:01:40,591
I want to dive off the diving
board and touch the drain.

42
00:01:40,592 --> 00:01:43,394
Hey, once more for the cheap seats:

43
00:01:43,395 --> 00:01:46,330
We got to teach you how to swim first, okay?

44
00:01:48,233 --> 00:01:50,768
Let's say we do something about that, huh?

45
00:01:50,769 --> 00:01:52,736
Take your shirt off. Hey, you, uh, you got Kate?

46
00:01:52,737 --> 00:01:55,005
Yeah. I got Kate.

47
00:01:55,116 --> 00:01:56,803
You ready?

48
00:01:56,873 --> 00:02:00,209
Come on. Whoa!

49
00:02:04,983 --> 00:02:07,051
Yeah, I don't think he's here.

50
00:02:07,052 --> 00:02:09,286
He was drunk and said he was going to the pool.

51
00:02:09,398 --> 00:02:11,813
We don't have a lot of other leads.

52
00:02:12,490 --> 00:02:14,024
You know, Beth seemed really eager

53
00:02:14,025 --> 00:02:15,993
to take the early train back to school.

54
00:02:15,994 --> 00:02:18,528
Yeah, wouldn't you be, too, after that dinner?

55
00:02:18,530 --> 00:02:20,865
I wish I was on it with her.

56
00:02:22,266 --> 00:02:23,699
Kev?

57
00:02:28,318 --> 00:02:30,486
What are you doing?

58
00:02:33,945 --> 00:02:35,679
Oh, good, you guys are here.

59
00:02:35,680 --> 00:02:37,541
Working on my Triple Lindy.

60
00:02:37,543 --> 00:02:39,516
-Kev...
-Stop.

61
00:02:39,517 --> 00:02:41,018
-Kevin. Kevin! Hey.
-Come on. Hey... Wa... Hey.

62
00:02:41,019 --> 00:02:42,252
Please, can you just get down?

63
00:02:42,253 --> 00:02:43,454
-Please.
-Come on, man.

64
00:02:43,455 --> 00:02:44,822
-Stop.
-You literally just recovered

65
00:02:44,823 --> 00:02:46,056
from a broken leg.

66
00:02:54,399 --> 00:02:57,768
If I dive off, I can touch the drain.

67
00:02:59,904 --> 00:03:02,940
I need you all to hear my voice right now.

68
00:03:02,941 --> 00:03:06,844
Your mother's voice, with all of her faculties.

69
00:03:07,779 --> 00:03:11,682
You will not make your
lives smaller because of me.

70
00:03:12,100 --> 00:03:15,352
This thing that's happening to me

71
00:03:15,353 --> 00:03:18,555
will not be the thing that holds you back.

72
00:03:18,556 --> 00:03:21,592
So take the risks.

73
00:03:21,593 --> 00:03:26,430
Make the big moves, even if they're small moves.

74
00:03:26,431 --> 00:03:28,432
Forge ahead with your lives

75
00:03:28,433 --> 00:03:31,822
in any and every direction that moves you.

76
00:03:32,046 --> 00:03:34,538
I am your mother

77
00:03:34,539 --> 00:03:37,158
and I'm sick.

78
00:03:37,332 --> 00:03:40,944
And I'm asking you to be fearless.

79
00:03:45,750 --> 00:03:48,519
-Hey.
-Hey.

80
00:03:48,520 --> 00:03:50,888
Heard you had a rough
night in there. You all right?

81
00:03:50,889 --> 00:03:54,024
Eh, all part of being the parent of a teenager.

82
00:03:54,025 --> 00:03:56,727
As you'll see all too soon.

83
00:03:56,728 --> 00:03:58,896
Yo, safe travels, siblings.

84
00:03:58,897 --> 00:04:00,698
Okay, we'll see you guys in L.A.

85
00:04:00,699 --> 00:04:02,099
for Mom and Mig's anniversary party.

86
00:04:02,100 --> 00:04:03,333
-All right.
-Love you.

87
00:04:03,334 --> 00:04:04,935
Love you.

88
00:04:05,185 --> 00:04:09,504
Well, I am off to start my
fearless, best life for Mom.

89
00:04:09,506 --> 00:04:12,910
-Whatever that is.
-Do you, brother.

90
00:04:13,122 --> 00:04:15,356
You guys take care.

91
00:04:16,929 --> 00:04:20,984
♪ It does not bother me to say this isn't love ♪

92
00:04:20,985 --> 00:04:23,120
♪ If you don't want to talk about... ♪

93
00:04:23,121 --> 00:04:24,922
Come on, guys, it's, like, really...

94
00:04:24,923 --> 00:04:26,490
It's Counting Crows. It's like a lullaby.

95
00:04:26,491 --> 00:04:27,925
Don't you want to go to sleep?

96
00:04:27,926 --> 00:04:29,326
Huh? Do you want to get some sleep

97
00:04:29,327 --> 00:04:30,794
so Daddy can get some sleep?

98
00:04:30,795 --> 00:04:32,930
Huh? It's time to go to bed.

99
00:04:32,931 --> 00:04:35,432
Guys? It's...

100
00:04:35,433 --> 00:04:38,902
Do you think it's me or the Crows?

101
00:04:38,903 --> 00:04:40,460
-The combination?
-It's...

102
00:04:40,462 --> 00:04:42,539
I can never get them to sleep
when they're supposed to,

103
00:04:42,540 --> 00:04:43,741
you know, when Madison's not around.

104
00:04:43,742 --> 00:04:45,298
They're here with me and t-they're up

105
00:04:45,300 --> 00:04:46,605
all night, they're crying.

106
00:04:46,607 --> 00:04:48,812
You just got to parent with confidence, Kev.

107
00:04:48,813 --> 00:04:51,359
You know, they really
respond to that kind of energy.

108
00:04:51,361 --> 00:04:53,529
You can do it.

109
00:04:54,919 --> 00:04:56,653
I really want to be great at guitar.

110
00:04:57,133 --> 00:04:59,702
Yeah, well...

111
00:05:06,164 --> 00:05:08,799
Applesauce. Applesauce.

112
00:05:10,435 --> 00:05:12,674
Come on! Yeah, baby, you got this.

113
00:05:18,676 --> 00:05:19,777
Don't breathe in.

114
00:05:19,778 --> 00:05:22,112
Don't breathe it in.

115
00:05:22,113 --> 00:05:24,250
I can't get any in my mouth.

116
00:05:25,450 --> 00:05:27,384
Okay, home free.

117
00:05:28,887 --> 00:05:31,155
That's... I don't know how they linger like that.

118
00:05:31,156 --> 00:05:33,196
Legit, it's awful.

119
00:05:35,627 --> 00:05:37,694
Going anywhere over our break, Kevin?

120
00:05:37,695 --> 00:05:39,129
Uh, yeah, you know,

121
00:05:39,130 --> 00:05:41,098
Madison had the kids over Thanksgiving,

122
00:05:41,099 --> 00:05:43,333
so I thought I'd take them to our family cabin.

123
00:05:43,334 --> 00:05:45,469
-That sounds nice.
-Yeah, it'll be great.

124
00:05:45,470 --> 00:05:47,638
How many nannies you bringing?

125
00:05:47,639 --> 00:05:50,007
Well, our one nanny, actually,

126
00:05:50,008 --> 00:05:53,587
we gave her two weeks
off to visit her family, so...

127
00:05:53,589 --> 00:05:55,245
Wait, so...

128
00:05:55,246 --> 00:05:58,148
you're traveling east with the twins?

129
00:05:58,149 --> 00:05:59,316
I am.

130
00:05:59,317 --> 00:06:02,019
-Alone?
-I am?

131
00:06:02,020 --> 00:06:04,086
Are you insane?

132
00:06:04,088 --> 00:06:06,489
At least go on some trial runs first.

133
00:06:06,591 --> 00:06:08,659
I'm taking the kids to the cabin, okay?

134
00:06:08,660 --> 00:06:10,360
It's fine. Uncle Nicky will be there.

135
00:06:10,361 --> 00:06:12,663
So, family will be there.

136
00:06:12,664 --> 00:06:14,998
Uncle Nicky is your ace in the hole here?

137
00:06:14,999 --> 00:06:17,901
Okay, no.

138
00:06:17,902 --> 00:06:20,637
Fine. Listen, uh, Cassidy will be there, too.

139
00:06:21,039 --> 00:06:22,573
Cassidy.

140
00:06:22,574 --> 00:06:24,007
It's not like that.

141
00:06:24,008 --> 00:06:25,542
Okay? It's not like that. She's there supervising

142
00:06:25,543 --> 00:06:26,743
the construction with Nicky.

143
00:06:26,744 --> 00:06:28,579
Okay? And she's bringing her son Matty.

144
00:06:28,580 --> 00:06:29,913
So Nicky and Franny will
have someone to play with.

145
00:06:29,914 --> 00:06:31,915
-It'll be great.
-Wait, uh...

146
00:06:31,916 --> 00:06:33,717
-Isn't her son, like, 24?
-24?

147
00:06:33,718 --> 00:06:35,085
He's-he's, like, a 12-year-old boy.

148
00:06:35,086 --> 00:06:36,520
What are you... You know what?

149
00:06:36,521 --> 00:06:37,788
Enough, all right? Enough of this.

150
00:06:37,789 --> 00:06:39,223
I'm taking the kids to the cabin.

151
00:06:39,224 --> 00:06:42,192
You guys are underestimating me, as usual.

152
00:06:42,193 --> 00:06:44,494
All right...

153
00:06:44,495 --> 00:06:46,363
There we go.

154
00:06:46,364 --> 00:06:48,432
Celebrities, they're just like us, right?

155
00:06:48,433 --> 00:06:50,534
All right, so...

156
00:06:50,535 --> 00:06:52,236
Yeah, I'll be right back for you.

157
00:06:53,204 --> 00:06:54,872
Perfect.

158
00:06:54,873 --> 00:06:56,974
There for a second... Hey. All right.

159
00:06:57,131 --> 00:06:58,598
And...

160
00:07:00,945 --> 00:07:02,946
Oh, oh, that's-that's a special...

161
00:07:02,947 --> 00:07:05,983
You-you went there, you
went there before we took off?

162
00:07:05,984 --> 00:07:07,718
Oh, geez...!

163
00:07:07,719 --> 00:07:11,255
Sorry about the smell, you know?

164
00:07:11,256 --> 00:07:13,357
Got a bit of a, little bit of a blowout.

165
00:07:13,358 --> 00:07:16,059
Celebrities, they're just like us, am I right?

166
00:07:16,060 --> 00:07:18,362
You already said that and
I don't know who you are.

167
00:07:18,363 --> 00:07:19,930
Yeah, okay.

168
00:07:19,931 --> 00:07:22,012
Well... Hey, you know what I can... I-I...

169
00:07:22,014 --> 00:07:23,133
Why don't I buy everybody a drink?

170
00:07:23,134 --> 00:07:24,368
Who wants a drink?

171
00:07:24,369 --> 00:07:25,769
It's first class.

172
00:07:25,770 --> 00:07:28,272
-They already drink for free.
-Right.

173
00:07:28,273 --> 00:07:30,173
We're good, we're good.

174
00:07:30,174 --> 00:07:32,142
We're getting it.

175
00:07:32,143 --> 00:07:34,111
We can do this.

176
00:07:34,112 --> 00:07:36,246
We-we can do this, we can do this.

177
00:07:36,247 --> 00:07:38,348
Yeah. We can do this.

178
00:07:38,349 --> 00:07:39,917
Yeah, huh?

179
00:07:41,727 --> 00:07:46,135
<b><font color="#00ff00">This Is Us - S06e08</font></b>

180
00:08:05,643 --> 00:08:07,678
-Franny's sleeping.
-Oh, I know.

181
00:08:07,679 --> 00:08:10,414
They're babies. Hello.

182
00:08:10,415 --> 00:08:12,816
I can't believe you made it.
I said to Edie this morning,

183
00:08:12,817 --> 00:08:15,586
"I'll bet you five bucks the kid
doesn't even get on the plane."

184
00:08:15,587 --> 00:08:17,420
Oh, and that's why you don't bet against the kid.

185
00:08:17,422 --> 00:08:19,486
Don't call yourself that.

186
00:08:19,512 --> 00:08:20,713
It's-it's easier if you just lift

187
00:08:20,715 --> 00:08:21,925
the whole car seat like this...

188
00:08:21,926 --> 00:08:23,026
No, so they don't wake them.

189
00:08:23,027 --> 00:08:24,661
I got it.

190
00:08:24,662 --> 00:08:27,030
Yeah! Piece of cake.

191
00:08:28,299 --> 00:08:29,633
Oh, hey, you remember Matty.

192
00:08:29,634 --> 00:08:30,834
-Oh, hey.
-Cassidy's son.

193
00:08:30,835 --> 00:08:31,902
What's up, man?

194
00:08:31,903 --> 00:08:34,004
-You play guitar?
-I'm learning.

195
00:08:34,005 --> 00:08:35,506
You're taking guitar lessons?

196
00:08:35,507 --> 00:08:37,808
I'm, you know, I'm self-teaching.

197
00:08:37,809 --> 00:08:39,877
-Oh, boy.
-Here.

198
00:08:39,878 --> 00:08:41,478
-Oh.
-Case he gets cold.

199
00:08:41,479 --> 00:08:43,380
-Come on.
-Hey, Kevin.

200
00:08:43,666 --> 00:08:45,415
Hey. Edie.

201
00:08:45,416 --> 00:08:48,318
I bet this is the first peace
and quiet you've had all day.

202
00:08:48,319 --> 00:08:50,521
Oh, don't you know it. Good to see you again.

203
00:08:50,522 --> 00:08:51,989
-You look great.
-Thank you. Good to see you.

204
00:08:51,990 --> 00:08:53,190
Can I just ask you a question?

205
00:08:53,191 --> 00:08:54,758
Is he holding you here against your will?

206
00:08:54,759 --> 00:08:56,860
Because it's the only explanation as to why

207
00:08:56,861 --> 00:08:58,362
you'd still be with him. Just, you know...

208
00:08:58,363 --> 00:08:59,563
Blink twice for yes.

209
00:08:59,564 --> 00:09:01,632
-He slashed my tires.
-Oh.

210
00:09:01,633 --> 00:09:03,233
Help me.

211
00:09:03,234 --> 00:09:05,739
Hey, Matty. Matty, where's your mom?

212
00:09:05,804 --> 00:09:08,351
She's up at the site.

213
00:09:09,374 --> 00:09:11,808
Is that a jackhammer?

214
00:09:11,809 --> 00:09:14,845
Uh, yeah, we're doing some demoing.

215
00:09:14,846 --> 00:09:18,081
Doing some demoing? What...
We haven't built anything yet.

216
00:09:18,082 --> 00:09:19,883
So, how the hell do you pour
foundation wrong, anyway?

217
00:09:19,884 --> 00:09:21,318
-It happens. Relax.
-Yeah?

218
00:09:21,319 --> 00:09:23,153
Hey, uh, either one of you seen Cassidy?

219
00:09:23,154 --> 00:09:24,482
In the back.

220
00:09:24,801 --> 00:09:26,469
By the Bobcat.

221
00:09:30,094 --> 00:09:31,395
Hey!

222
00:09:32,964 --> 00:09:35,866
-What the hell happened?
-Oh, good to see you, too.

223
00:09:35,867 --> 00:09:37,801
I know, Matty's getting so big.

224
00:09:37,802 --> 00:09:39,803
It's just crazy, time just flies.

225
00:09:39,893 --> 00:09:42,205
-How was your flight?
-Cassidy.

226
00:09:42,651 --> 00:09:44,018
Hey.

227
00:09:45,643 --> 00:09:47,358
We had a little setback.

228
00:09:47,360 --> 00:09:49,313
A little setback... Oh, you
know, when I asked you to hire

229
00:09:49,314 --> 00:09:51,281
a couple of workers, I meant
real construction workers.

230
00:09:51,282 --> 00:09:52,950
You know? Not just some clowns off the street.

231
00:09:52,951 --> 00:09:54,818
Yeah, they're not clowns, they're vets.

232
00:09:54,819 --> 00:09:56,220
Yeah, who've done a lot harder jobs

233
00:09:56,221 --> 00:09:58,575
than building cabins with bidets for movie stars.

234
00:09:58,577 --> 00:09:59,844
What?

235
00:09:59,846 --> 00:10:02,336
Sorry, you just called Kevin a movie star.

236
00:10:02,794 --> 00:10:04,461
Your architect's scales

237
00:10:04,462 --> 00:10:06,463
were incorrect for the back room,

238
00:10:06,464 --> 00:10:08,098
but I should have caught
it before we started to pour.

239
00:10:08,099 --> 00:10:10,133
-It's my bad.
-Yeah, obviously.

240
00:10:10,134 --> 00:10:12,035
-Oh, come on, cool it.
-I am cool.

241
00:10:12,036 --> 00:10:13,704
Just what-what is this? What am I looking at?

242
00:10:13,705 --> 00:10:15,739
-Does this set us back a week, a month?
-Hey.

243
00:10:16,029 --> 00:10:18,109
You don't pay me enough to take this crap.

244
00:10:18,111 --> 00:10:20,519
I need to get back to work.

245
00:10:23,881 --> 00:10:25,582
-The hell's her problem?
-Her problem?

246
00:10:25,583 --> 00:10:28,385
Oh, I don't know. Kid's
not taking the divorce well,

247
00:10:28,386 --> 00:10:31,421
I hear her pacing the halls at
night when she crashes here.

248
00:10:31,422 --> 00:10:33,323
And she devoted her adult life to a war

249
00:10:33,324 --> 00:10:35,525
that just ended with an apology and a fart.

250
00:10:35,526 --> 00:10:37,861
So, you know, that kind of stuff.

251
00:10:37,862 --> 00:10:39,696
She's busting her ass for you, kid.

252
00:10:39,697 --> 00:10:42,132
-We're all busting our ass here.
-I know.

253
00:10:42,133 --> 00:10:43,133
I know.

254
00:10:43,134 --> 00:10:44,534
And you're right. I'm sorry.

255
00:10:44,535 --> 00:10:45,936
It's just...

256
00:10:45,937 --> 00:10:48,205
I'm sort of a stressed-out
parent myself, you know?

257
00:10:48,206 --> 00:10:50,140
No, no, you're an idiot.

258
00:10:50,141 --> 00:10:52,509
I mean, why-why didn't you just fly Mary Poppins

259
00:10:52,510 --> 00:10:54,767
out here on, you know, one of your Learjets?

260
00:10:54,769 --> 00:10:57,704
No, because I can do this.

261
00:10:59,651 --> 00:11:01,785
Oh, I'm sorry.

262
00:11:01,953 --> 00:11:04,455
I thought you were being cute.

263
00:11:12,630 --> 00:11:14,298
All right...

264
00:11:21,372 --> 00:11:23,106
Uhp. Which...

265
00:11:23,107 --> 00:11:25,809
You want to go... I'll go that way.

266
00:11:25,898 --> 00:11:27,966
Can't imagine why you two didn't work out.

267
00:11:27,968 --> 00:11:29,635
Uh-huh.

268
00:11:30,682 --> 00:11:34,384
Hey, listen, um, I just wanted to say...

269
00:11:34,731 --> 00:11:38,434
I'm sorry about, you know, being a dick earlier.

270
00:11:39,257 --> 00:11:42,820
Uh, you mean, like, an hour
ago, or, like, since I met you?

271
00:11:42,828 --> 00:11:44,362
Like, an hour ago.

272
00:11:45,439 --> 00:11:48,274
Mm. Sorry for the foundation screwup.

273
00:11:48,276 --> 00:11:49,943
Is that "sorry for the foundation screwup"

274
00:11:49,945 --> 00:11:52,892
or "sorry for the foundation, Screwup"?

275
00:11:52,894 --> 00:11:54,595
Can it be both?

276
00:11:59,877 --> 00:12:01,178
Oh, can I sit there?

277
00:12:01,179 --> 00:12:03,413
You want to sit here? Yeah, sure.

278
00:12:03,414 --> 00:12:06,516
All right. You know what I think we need to do?

279
00:12:06,517 --> 00:12:08,418
-Toast. Yeah? Cheers.
-Yeah.

280
00:12:08,419 --> 00:12:10,253
-Cheers.
-Thank you for coming.

281
00:12:10,254 --> 00:12:11,774
It's good to have everyone here, right?

282
00:12:14,859 --> 00:12:16,960
Uh... Oh, thanks.

283
00:12:29,707 --> 00:12:31,475
Okay. What you got?

284
00:12:33,444 --> 00:12:36,079
Pennsylvania Avenue. $320.

285
00:12:36,080 --> 00:12:38,215
Well, actually, that's my property,

286
00:12:38,216 --> 00:12:41,718
and it's $1,100, so you owe me $1,400.

287
00:12:41,719 --> 00:12:43,720
-Whoa.
-Okay. Cool...

288
00:12:43,721 --> 00:12:45,288
All right, Kev, your turn.

289
00:12:45,289 --> 00:12:47,124
Come on, bud.

290
00:12:48,033 --> 00:12:49,059
Oh!! What?!

291
00:12:49,060 --> 00:12:50,751
Stay, guys.

292
00:12:50,752 --> 00:12:52,989
$500, please.

293
00:12:54,265 --> 00:12:56,285
Can I play guitar?

294
00:12:57,635 --> 00:12:59,836
Yeah, that's a good idea. Let's do it.

295
00:12:59,837 --> 00:13:01,471
Here we go. All right.

296
00:13:01,472 --> 00:13:02,973
Nice and relaxed, there you go.

297
00:13:02,974 --> 00:13:04,098
-Remember that shape of a D?
-Oh, yeah.

298
00:13:04,634 --> 00:13:05,710
Yeah?

299
00:13:06,068 --> 00:13:07,702
Good.

300
00:13:08,780 --> 00:13:10,280
Ooh, almost there.

301
00:13:10,281 --> 00:13:14,117
Think you push a little harder.

302
00:13:14,118 --> 00:13:16,586
Oh, you know, I-I miss the jackhammer.

303
00:13:16,587 --> 00:13:19,122
I'm sorry, guys, that is enough.

304
00:13:19,123 --> 00:13:20,791
-You're kidding. It takes time.
-Let me find some real music.

305
00:13:20,792 --> 00:13:23,841
-It takes time to rip.
-Excuse me.

306
00:13:29,600 --> 00:13:32,029
Come on, dance with me, baby.

307
00:13:33,171 --> 00:13:36,339
-Oh, baby.
-All right.

308
00:13:36,340 --> 00:13:39,376
Let's show these youngins how it's done, honey.

309
00:13:39,377 --> 00:13:41,645
♪ Ooh, la, la, la, la ♪

310
00:13:41,646 --> 00:13:45,449
♪ I did you wrong ♪

311
00:13:45,450 --> 00:13:49,820
♪ My heart went out to play ♪

312
00:13:49,821 --> 00:13:53,290
♪ But in the game I lost you ♪

313
00:13:53,291 --> 00:13:57,360
♪ What a price to pay ♪

314
00:13:57,361 --> 00:13:59,463
♪ Hey ♪

315
00:13:59,464 --> 00:14:02,309
♪ I'm crying ♪

316
00:14:03,168 --> 00:14:07,537
♪ Ooh ♪

317
00:14:07,538 --> 00:14:09,973
♪ Baby, baby... ♪

318
00:14:09,974 --> 00:14:12,075
Come on, Smokey.

319
00:14:15,346 --> 00:14:19,015
♪ Baby, baby... ♪

320
00:14:44,675 --> 00:14:46,475
Hello?

321
00:14:48,278 --> 00:14:50,170
This is he.

322
00:14:52,116 --> 00:14:54,050
Car accident... A car accident?

323
00:14:54,051 --> 00:14:56,283
Wait, hold-hold on, that's impossible.

324
00:14:57,555 --> 00:15:00,490
Cassidy? I was just with...

325
00:15:07,698 --> 00:15:10,283
-Kick, kick, kick, kick, kick.
-I already know how to kick.

326
00:15:10,284 --> 00:15:13,161
-Just take one more step in.
-I don't want to.

327
00:15:13,162 --> 00:15:14,429
Okay.

328
00:15:15,081 --> 00:15:19,050
Now can I go off the diving board?

329
00:15:19,051 --> 00:15:21,086
You want to go off the diving board?

330
00:15:21,087 --> 00:15:23,522
You got to pass a swim test

331
00:15:23,523 --> 00:15:25,223
if you want to go into the deep end.

332
00:15:25,224 --> 00:15:27,192
All right?

333
00:15:27,193 --> 00:15:30,095
Look. Hey, you see these kids?

334
00:15:30,096 --> 00:15:31,396
You see them when they jump off the diving board

335
00:15:31,397 --> 00:15:32,864
and they're swimming to the side,

336
00:15:32,865 --> 00:15:34,666
they're swimming to the wall? You see that?

337
00:15:34,667 --> 00:15:36,535
They're not sinking to the bottom.

338
00:15:36,536 --> 00:15:38,370
So, hey, how about you swim to that wall...

339
00:15:38,371 --> 00:15:39,571
you think you can do that?

340
00:15:39,572 --> 00:15:42,440
Okay. Here we go.

341
00:15:42,441 --> 00:15:44,409
Go ahead.

342
00:15:46,078 --> 00:15:47,479
Jack?

343
00:15:47,480 --> 00:15:48,947
Yeah, I-I got him.

344
00:15:48,948 --> 00:15:50,282
Jack!

345
00:15:50,283 --> 00:15:51,283
Okay, okay.

346
00:15:51,284 --> 00:15:53,051
I got him.

347
00:15:53,052 --> 00:15:54,920
He's just a child, Jack.

348
00:15:54,921 --> 00:15:57,859
Yeah, and someday he's gonna be a man.

349
00:15:58,891 --> 00:16:01,793
Hey; You're not ready for the deep end yet, bud.

350
00:16:01,794 --> 00:16:04,729
-Okay?
-Leave me alone.

351
00:16:04,730 --> 00:16:08,099
Hey, hey, Bug? You're
gonna stay here with Daddy...

352
00:16:09,635 --> 00:16:11,768
All I ever wanted, um...

353
00:16:11,769 --> 00:16:15,607
when I was little was to touch this damn drain.

354
00:16:21,447 --> 00:16:23,898
Mission completed.

355
00:16:23,900 --> 00:16:25,750
And I feel nothing.

356
00:16:25,751 --> 00:16:27,719
Ooh, God.

357
00:16:27,720 --> 00:16:30,388
You're so depressing.

358
00:16:30,389 --> 00:16:33,060
-Ugh...
-I was just...

359
00:16:33,062 --> 00:16:34,926
scared my hair was gonna get caught in it.

360
00:16:34,927 --> 00:16:36,328
That's an urban legend.

361
00:16:36,329 --> 00:16:38,964
No one ever got their hair caught in...

362
00:16:38,965 --> 00:16:40,799
Randall! No!

363
00:16:40,800 --> 00:16:42,934
I thought I lost you.

364
00:16:45,705 --> 00:16:47,339
You...

365
00:16:47,340 --> 00:16:49,100
-You got me.
-I don't belong here.

366
00:16:52,190 --> 00:16:54,658
In the deep end.

367
00:16:56,215 --> 00:16:58,936
I-I belong in the shallow end.

368
00:17:00,232 --> 00:17:02,239
'C-Cause I'm shallow a-and stupid.

369
00:17:02,240 --> 00:17:05,443
-Oh, we got it, yeah.
-Yeah.

370
00:17:05,644 --> 00:17:07,611
Randall.

371
00:17:07,613 --> 00:17:09,514
You belong in the deep end.

372
00:17:10,282 --> 00:17:12,325
You're the brainiac.

373
00:17:14,152 --> 00:17:15,753
Kate, you do, too, you know,

374
00:17:16,043 --> 00:17:17,910
if you could ever get out of your own way.

375
00:17:19,491 --> 00:17:21,943
I just don't have what it takes.

376
00:17:24,763 --> 00:17:29,467
I'm not, uh... solid.

377
00:17:33,839 --> 00:17:35,673
The one solid thing I had in my life

378
00:17:35,674 --> 00:17:37,541
was Sophie and I blew it.

379
00:17:43,749 --> 00:17:47,151
I don't have the right stuff underneath me.

380
00:17:47,152 --> 00:17:50,054
I don't have the, uh...

381
00:17:50,055 --> 00:17:52,556
-uh...
-Foundation.

382
00:17:52,557 --> 00:17:56,362
The foundation. See, brainiac?

383
00:17:58,219 --> 00:17:59,686
Yeah.

384
00:18:04,057 --> 00:18:06,892
You know what?

385
00:18:06,894 --> 00:18:08,929
Maybe I'll quit acting.

386
00:18:11,242 --> 00:18:14,044
Maybe I'll stay here in Pittsburgh

387
00:18:14,046 --> 00:18:15,914
and I'll pound nails like Dad.

388
00:18:18,083 --> 00:18:21,619
'Cause Dad, Dad was solid.

389
00:18:26,291 --> 00:18:29,193
He put a roof over our heads.

390
00:18:30,829 --> 00:18:33,497
Maybe I'll do that.

391
00:18:33,498 --> 00:18:36,100
Okay, all right.

392
00:18:36,101 --> 00:18:38,936
Come on, Kev. Let's get out of here.

393
00:18:38,937 --> 00:18:41,439
No. I am going to...

394
00:18:41,440 --> 00:18:44,675
sleep in the deep end tonight,

395
00:18:44,676 --> 00:18:47,611
I want to feel what it's
like, just for the night.

396
00:18:47,612 --> 00:18:49,680
Yep. Mm-hmm.

397
00:18:57,622 --> 00:18:59,957
Hi. A friend of ours was in a car accident.

398
00:18:59,958 --> 00:19:01,358
Cassidy Sharp?

399
00:19:01,359 --> 00:19:02,717
Yes. She's in with the doctors now.

400
00:19:02,718 --> 00:19:03,794
Take a seat over there.

401
00:19:03,795 --> 00:19:04,995
When the doctors are done with her,

402
00:19:04,996 --> 00:19:06,397
they'll come out to you.

403
00:19:06,398 --> 00:19:08,833
Uh, we were told that
she's conscious and talking?

404
00:19:08,834 --> 00:19:12,036
A seat. Over there.

405
00:19:12,170 --> 00:19:13,894
Thanks.

406
00:19:14,339 --> 00:19:16,040
This whole thing could be my fault.

407
00:19:16,041 --> 00:19:17,241
-What?
-I mean, the way

408
00:19:17,242 --> 00:19:18,876
I jumped all over her about the jackhammering.

409
00:19:18,877 --> 00:19:20,544
You know, I'm an addict myself, I...

410
00:19:20,545 --> 00:19:21,679
should have known better than that.

411
00:19:21,680 --> 00:19:24,281
Maybe she, you know, couldn't sleep

412
00:19:24,282 --> 00:19:27,852
and caved in, had a few
drinks, got behind the wheel.

413
00:19:27,897 --> 00:19:29,806
Yeah, you give yourself too much credit.

414
00:19:30,889 --> 00:19:32,695
Here.

415
00:19:32,697 --> 00:19:34,492
You're friends of the patient Cassidy Sharp?

416
00:19:34,493 --> 00:19:36,794
-Yeah, how is she?
-She's resting now.

417
00:19:36,795 --> 00:19:38,496
Though uncomfortably.
She refused any painkillers,

418
00:19:38,497 --> 00:19:39,697
except Tylenol.

419
00:19:39,698 --> 00:19:41,832
Well, yeah, she's a recovering addict.

420
00:19:41,833 --> 00:19:43,968
Yeah, sh-she made that clear.

421
00:19:43,969 --> 00:19:45,636
And there was no alcohol involved?

422
00:19:45,637 --> 00:19:47,571
No, none in her system. She's gonna be okay.

423
00:19:47,572 --> 00:19:49,874
She suffered a fractured clavicle and broken arm.

424
00:19:49,875 --> 00:19:51,842
The humerus bone.

425
00:19:51,843 --> 00:19:53,511
Maybe she went to get ice cream.

426
00:19:53,512 --> 00:19:54,578
You know? It's late, nothing's open.

427
00:19:54,579 --> 00:19:56,847
She got tired and she...

428
00:19:56,848 --> 00:19:58,182
She's gonna be okay, though?

429
00:19:58,183 --> 00:19:59,783
Yes. Yes. From what I understand,

430
00:19:59,784 --> 00:20:02,720
the pole took the worst
of it. It was a direct hit.

431
00:20:02,721 --> 00:20:04,755
But we're gonna keep an eye
on her overnight, maybe two.

432
00:20:04,756 --> 00:20:06,190
She's sleeping now.

433
00:20:06,191 --> 00:20:07,791
And given that she didn't want a pain sedative,

434
00:20:07,792 --> 00:20:10,335
that sleep's gonna be very important to her.

435
00:20:10,337 --> 00:20:12,229
And her doctor.

436
00:20:12,230 --> 00:20:14,532
So I suggest you come back in the morning, okay?

437
00:20:14,533 --> 00:20:16,200
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.

438
00:20:16,201 --> 00:20:17,735
Very much.

439
00:20:18,937 --> 00:20:21,372
-Thank God.
-Yeah.

440
00:20:27,894 --> 00:20:29,811
Look, a broken arm, broken clavicle,

441
00:20:29,812 --> 00:20:32,772
it's not like it's nothing, but she's sober.

442
00:20:32,774 --> 00:20:34,845
And she's refusing her pain medications,

443
00:20:34,847 --> 00:20:36,481
so that's good, right?

444
00:20:39,330 --> 00:20:41,364
Lighten up. She's gonna be all right.

445
00:20:42,967 --> 00:20:44,567
"Lighten up," he says.

446
00:20:45,970 --> 00:20:48,705
Do you know what she did in Afghanistan?

447
00:20:49,707 --> 00:20:52,776
Human intelligence. That means

448
00:20:52,777 --> 00:20:55,779
every day that she went out in the field,

449
00:20:55,780 --> 00:20:59,364
she'd visit, uh, some poor villager's house,

450
00:20:59,365 --> 00:21:02,552
and she'd say, "As long as you help us,

451
00:21:02,553 --> 00:21:04,788
"we will protect you.

452
00:21:04,789 --> 00:21:07,079
We will get you out of the country."

453
00:21:08,370 --> 00:21:11,194
Sometimes she even meant it.

454
00:21:11,527 --> 00:21:13,561
But even if she didn't,

455
00:21:13,797 --> 00:21:15,998
that's the job.

456
00:21:16,100 --> 00:21:18,135
Um... you sell it.

457
00:21:18,469 --> 00:21:20,782
She-she didn't seem that off to me, honestly.

458
00:21:20,783 --> 00:21:23,673
Oh, that's right. I forgot. You went to Vietnam.

459
00:21:23,674 --> 00:21:25,441
You got yourself a little necklace, right?

460
00:21:25,603 --> 00:21:27,438
Yeah, you're the expert.

461
00:21:27,440 --> 00:21:29,245
Look, people like Cassidy,

462
00:21:29,246 --> 00:21:32,348
they don't give you a
heads-up when they're not okay.

463
00:21:33,017 --> 00:21:35,519
You find out the hard way.

464
00:21:35,521 --> 00:21:37,155
You understand?

465
00:21:39,367 --> 00:21:43,403
At dinner, she didn't sit
with her back to the door.

466
00:21:43,405 --> 00:21:45,006
Now, I've seen that before.

467
00:21:45,008 --> 00:21:48,043
I've been that before.

468
00:21:49,956 --> 00:21:52,090
You don't just...

469
00:21:52,092 --> 00:21:54,227
get better.

470
00:21:54,229 --> 00:21:56,639
And if you think I'm exaggerating,

471
00:21:56,641 --> 00:21:59,409
let me remind you that your father

472
00:21:59,422 --> 00:22:01,857
drank in secret trying to forget.

473
00:22:02,513 --> 00:22:05,348
Let me remind you when
you busted into my trailer,

474
00:22:05,349 --> 00:22:07,817
there was a gun sitting in front of me.

475
00:22:09,422 --> 00:22:13,024
That was 50 years after boots left Vietnam.

476
00:22:17,428 --> 00:22:19,462
Look, let's just go.

477
00:22:19,463 --> 00:22:22,131
I mean, you heard the doctor.
We'll go out, we'll come back

478
00:22:22,132 --> 00:22:25,200
-fresh and early.
-Whoa, whoa, I... It's... You know, maybe...

479
00:22:25,202 --> 00:22:27,457
Should one of us stay?

480
00:22:27,473 --> 00:22:29,505
You want to stay?

481
00:22:29,506 --> 00:22:32,508
-Me?
-Well, you're her friend,

482
00:22:32,509 --> 00:22:34,110
-right?
-Yeah.

483
00:22:34,324 --> 00:22:36,412
Course. I just...

484
00:22:36,780 --> 00:22:38,581
I understand it's the right thing to do.

485
00:22:38,582 --> 00:22:41,878
I just... I don't know if I'm...

486
00:22:41,899 --> 00:22:45,635
if I'm the right guy to-to do it.

487
00:22:48,792 --> 00:22:50,994
Don't try to help her, all right?

488
00:22:50,995 --> 00:22:54,631
Okay? You-you just being here, that's enough.

489
00:22:54,676 --> 00:22:57,711
Just do nothing. Just...

490
00:22:58,103 --> 00:23:00,104
Just be.

491
00:23:00,671 --> 00:23:02,105
Just be.

492
00:25:04,361 --> 00:25:07,361
At least we got the news to cheer us up, right?

493
00:25:08,489 --> 00:25:10,657
Yeah.

494
00:25:14,705 --> 00:25:17,373
I don't know why I didn't go home.

495
00:25:17,608 --> 00:25:20,009
It was literally the doctor's orders, you know?

496
00:25:20,010 --> 00:25:22,678
He said, "Go home. There's
nothing you can do here."

497
00:25:22,680 --> 00:25:26,883
But, you know, s-staying
here is the right thing to do.

498
00:25:28,152 --> 00:25:31,349
'Cause I don't... I don't have any...

499
00:25:33,279 --> 00:25:36,113
I don't have any real friends.

500
00:25:39,163 --> 00:25:42,765
Other than my family, she's...

501
00:25:43,166 --> 00:25:46,169
one of the only people I truly care about.

502
00:25:46,779 --> 00:25:48,337
So...

503
00:25:49,186 --> 00:25:51,655
So here I am.

504
00:25:52,342 --> 00:25:53,943
Here I am.

505
00:25:53,944 --> 00:25:57,013
Wearing the same clothes I
wore yesterday and drinking

506
00:25:57,014 --> 00:25:58,514
this hospital coffee.

507
00:25:58,515 --> 00:26:00,126
Even though I know there's a real coffee shop

508
00:26:00,128 --> 00:26:01,950
two minutes away, I won't go.

509
00:26:01,952 --> 00:26:04,823
I won't go. I refuse to leave.

510
00:26:12,354 --> 00:26:14,388
You ever feel like you're...

511
00:26:15,065 --> 00:26:17,433
Like you're performing

512
00:26:17,434 --> 00:26:20,269
in a movie that no one else is watching?

513
00:26:20,702 --> 00:26:23,072
You know what I mean? Like, like, um...

514
00:26:23,073 --> 00:26:24,407
Like you're always...

515
00:26:24,408 --> 00:26:26,330
You're trying to do the right thing.

516
00:26:26,332 --> 00:26:29,667
You're trying to be the right kind of person

517
00:26:29,669 --> 00:26:31,957
instead of just...

518
00:26:32,649 --> 00:26:35,303
...being that person.

519
00:26:36,820 --> 00:26:40,490
I want to be the kind of
man that does the right thing

520
00:26:40,830 --> 00:26:44,035
because it's the right thing to do.

521
00:26:44,037 --> 00:26:46,572
The kind of man that's just there, you know?

522
00:26:46,574 --> 00:26:48,441
Just there.

523
00:26:52,025 --> 00:26:53,925
Think maybe I am.

524
00:26:56,273 --> 00:26:58,608
Or I'm trying to be.

525
00:26:58,609 --> 00:27:02,478
But how do you know? How do you know if you are

526
00:27:02,480 --> 00:27:05,070
or if you're acting like you are?

527
00:27:05,072 --> 00:27:07,040
You ever think about that?

528
00:27:09,487 --> 00:27:11,941
I'm just waiting on my wife.

529
00:27:17,015 --> 00:27:19,083
Sir?

530
00:27:19,085 --> 00:27:21,940
You can see your friend now.

531
00:28:19,189 --> 00:28:21,313
Tell me what happened.

532
00:28:21,314 --> 00:28:23,415
Dad tried to drowned me.

533
00:28:23,416 --> 00:28:26,385
Your dad did not try to drown you.

534
00:28:26,386 --> 00:28:27,876
Yes, he did.

535
00:28:27,877 --> 00:28:29,411
No.

536
00:28:29,412 --> 00:28:32,047
Kev, the last thing your dad wants to do

537
00:28:32,048 --> 00:28:33,482
is drown you.

538
00:28:33,483 --> 00:28:36,385
The first thing he wants to
do is teach you how to swim

539
00:28:36,386 --> 00:28:37,953
before you jump on that board

540
00:28:37,954 --> 00:28:39,955
so you don't drown.

541
00:28:39,956 --> 00:28:41,356
I know those two things

542
00:28:41,357 --> 00:28:43,740
don't seem like they're
in the right order, but...

543
00:28:45,461 --> 00:28:47,629
It's like

544
00:28:47,630 --> 00:28:50,399
trying to put one of the
roofs on your Lego houses

545
00:28:50,400 --> 00:28:52,968
before you built the walls to support it.

546
00:28:53,103 --> 00:28:56,538
Your dad is really good at building things.

547
00:28:56,539 --> 00:28:59,541
And not just houses but character, too.

548
00:28:59,542 --> 00:29:02,377
So you would do well by listening to him.

549
00:29:02,378 --> 00:29:04,713
I'm not like Dad.

550
00:29:04,714 --> 00:29:06,415
Oh, believe me.

551
00:29:06,750 --> 00:29:09,818
You're exactly like him.

552
00:29:10,954 --> 00:29:13,088
-I'm right here to hold on to, sweetie.
-Why don't we go

553
00:29:13,089 --> 00:29:14,456
get back in the pool with your sister.

554
00:29:14,457 --> 00:29:16,158
And thank you for the Creamsicle, Mom.

555
00:29:16,159 --> 00:29:18,293
Thanks for the Creamsicle, Mom.

556
00:29:18,294 --> 00:29:19,962
Okay, come on.

557
00:29:22,098 --> 00:29:24,499
Hey. You know that thing you said

558
00:29:24,589 --> 00:29:26,791
-about being shallow and stupid?
-Yeah.

559
00:29:26,793 --> 00:29:29,394
You are shallow. And stupid.

560
00:29:29,396 --> 00:29:30,863
Really are, Kev.

561
00:29:30,865 --> 00:29:32,466
Yeah.

562
00:29:32,468 --> 00:29:34,235
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.

563
00:29:34,237 --> 00:29:37,073
Finally, someone understands me!

564
00:29:37,075 --> 00:29:38,575
Oh,

565
00:29:38,577 --> 00:29:41,546
and, also, you're gonna be a screwup for a while.

566
00:29:41,548 --> 00:29:43,716
But, um, I know you pretty well,

567
00:29:43,718 --> 00:29:45,118
and you'll figure it out someday.

568
00:29:45,120 --> 00:29:46,620
Not tomorrow.

569
00:29:46,622 --> 00:29:49,404
Yeah, definitely not tomorrow.

570
00:29:59,836 --> 00:30:01,536
Edie and Nicky are watching Matty.

571
00:30:01,537 --> 00:30:02,971
He's fine.

572
00:30:03,940 --> 00:30:07,142
He's a little worried, but he's doing better

573
00:30:07,143 --> 00:30:09,011
knowing that you're gonna be okay.

574
00:30:21,167 --> 00:30:23,269
I'm not gonna bug you with questions

575
00:30:23,271 --> 00:30:27,307
about what you were doing or what happened.

576
00:30:30,267 --> 00:30:33,203
I'm just gonna sit here with you.

577
00:30:35,716 --> 00:30:39,185
I want you to know that I'm here.

578
00:30:40,688 --> 00:30:43,567
I'm not going anywhere.

579
00:31:11,430 --> 00:31:14,245
I don't sleep well.

580
00:31:16,780 --> 00:31:20,085
Bad habit I brought back.

581
00:31:24,512 --> 00:31:27,255
So sometimes I go for a drive.

582
00:31:29,414 --> 00:31:32,748
Just to calm my mind, not...

583
00:31:33,930 --> 00:31:37,251
...think about all the people that I, uh...

584
00:31:39,780 --> 00:31:42,286
...left behind.

585
00:31:45,252 --> 00:31:48,345
The ones I betrayed.

586
00:31:54,984 --> 00:31:57,978
My friends who died.

587
00:31:58,988 --> 00:32:02,624
The ones who survived just
to come back here and die.

588
00:32:04,305 --> 00:32:06,412
It's all...

589
00:32:07,509 --> 00:32:10,711
...tightly wound together in a knot.

590
00:32:16,317 --> 00:32:18,351
Gets to be a lot.

591
00:32:21,333 --> 00:32:22,933
It's...

592
00:32:24,403 --> 00:32:26,836
...so much.

593
00:32:33,034 --> 00:32:35,068
It's at its heaviest when...

594
00:32:37,393 --> 00:32:41,318
...I'm alone and Matty goes back to his dad.

595
00:32:44,491 --> 00:32:48,186
It's like it's crushing me.

596
00:32:50,830 --> 00:32:52,831
But

597
00:32:53,000 --> 00:32:55,034
last night...

598
00:32:58,059 --> 00:33:01,061
It was really nice.

599
00:33:01,063 --> 00:33:04,065
It was wonderful with everybody.

600
00:33:04,067 --> 00:33:06,501
Family and friends.

601
00:33:09,560 --> 00:33:14,197
It's warm, and laughter is so light.

602
00:33:14,199 --> 00:33:17,635
Just want it to last forever.

603
00:33:19,981 --> 00:33:22,799
But I knew it wouldn't.

604
00:33:24,507 --> 00:33:26,074
So, I went for a drive

605
00:33:26,220 --> 00:33:30,496
'cause I couldn't sleep.

606
00:33:33,683 --> 00:33:37,415
And I lived in our happy night a little longer.

607
00:33:40,256 --> 00:33:43,091
Until I got tired.

608
00:33:43,862 --> 00:33:46,264
I got really tired.

609
00:33:47,530 --> 00:33:50,165
And I didn't fight the sleep.

610
00:33:50,757 --> 00:33:55,127
I just kept driving faster and faster.

611
00:33:57,540 --> 00:34:01,576
To somewhere I... I had never been, but...

612
00:34:03,369 --> 00:34:06,004
...I often thought about going.

613
00:34:16,626 --> 00:34:18,660
Hey.

614
00:34:22,231 --> 00:34:24,232
Hey.

615
00:34:24,824 --> 00:34:26,859
It's okay, kid.

616
00:34:27,637 --> 00:34:29,671
It's okay.

617
00:34:42,247 --> 00:34:44,280
Okay, well, where-where are you now?

618
00:34:44,625 --> 00:34:46,159
Okay. So, when you get to Mill Road,

619
00:34:46,160 --> 00:34:47,827
navigation's just gonna take you in circles,

620
00:34:47,828 --> 00:34:49,696
so just follow the instructions I text you.

621
00:34:49,697 --> 00:34:51,831
-Yeah.
-Come here, baby.

622
00:34:51,832 --> 00:34:53,667
-Thank you very much.
-Come here, sweetie.

623
00:34:53,668 --> 00:34:55,435
-Okay.
-Yes. Oh.

624
00:34:55,647 --> 00:34:58,148
Yeah. No, I'll-I'll go tell
him... I'll go tell him now.

625
00:34:58,797 --> 00:35:01,299
Okay. See you in a bit.

626
00:35:04,845 --> 00:35:07,414
All right. Look at you. You're sounding great.

627
00:35:08,849 --> 00:35:11,351
So, I just got off the phone with your dad.

628
00:35:11,352 --> 00:35:13,987
He said he's gonna come by and pick you up.

629
00:35:13,988 --> 00:35:15,622
I think you're gonna go by the hospital

630
00:35:15,623 --> 00:35:17,791
to visit your mom on your way out of town, okay?

631
00:35:18,150 --> 00:35:21,452
Your dad said it's cool.
Said he wants to see her, too.

632
00:35:21,828 --> 00:35:23,888
Does she look bad?

633
00:35:23,927 --> 00:35:26,023
Your mom? No.

634
00:35:26,024 --> 00:35:28,726
No, your mom... your mom could never look bad.

635
00:35:28,727 --> 00:35:32,197
And it's gonna take more than a
fender bender to keep her down.

636
00:35:32,199 --> 00:35:35,234
But I think it would cheer her up to see you.

637
00:35:39,438 --> 00:35:42,473
You know, when I was at the hospital last night,

638
00:35:42,474 --> 00:35:43,741
I was visiting your mom.

639
00:35:44,491 --> 00:35:46,621
And I was gonna buy her a get-well card,

640
00:35:46,622 --> 00:35:48,323
but everything they had was kind of lame.

641
00:35:48,324 --> 00:35:49,958
You know? It was cheesy.

642
00:35:49,959 --> 00:35:53,762
So, I was thinking maybe you and I

643
00:35:53,763 --> 00:35:55,764
work together, and we
build her a card of our own.

644
00:35:55,765 --> 00:35:57,933
What do you think about that? Hmm?

645
00:35:57,934 --> 00:35:59,267
All right.

646
00:35:59,268 --> 00:36:02,003
But I'm no good at painting.

647
00:36:02,004 --> 00:36:04,903
Oh, no, it doesn't matter.
You don't have to be good.

648
00:36:04,905 --> 00:36:07,008
You know, when I first started acting,

649
00:36:07,009 --> 00:36:09,978
every time I got a new role, I would paint.

650
00:36:09,979 --> 00:36:12,480
I would go buy a bunch of
paint and just-just have at it.

651
00:36:12,481 --> 00:36:14,015
Freed up my mind.

652
00:36:14,016 --> 00:36:16,151
But, uh, you know,

653
00:36:16,152 --> 00:36:19,810
then I got self-conscious, and I quit.

654
00:36:19,812 --> 00:36:22,614
Picked up other hobbies, like the guitar.

655
00:36:25,895 --> 00:36:28,159
Want to help?

656
00:36:29,110 --> 00:36:31,611
I said okay, like, an hour ago.

657
00:36:32,869 --> 00:36:34,870
Yeah. Yeah, don't be shy.

658
00:36:34,871 --> 00:36:37,005
Get in there. Blue?

659
00:36:37,006 --> 00:36:39,374
-You like blue? All right.
-Yeah.

660
00:36:39,375 --> 00:36:41,109
-Get some green.
-Green. Green and blue.

661
00:36:41,110 --> 00:36:42,911
-Let's do them both. Yeah.
-Yeah.

662
00:36:42,912 --> 00:36:44,379
-Ooh.
-Blue's my mom's favorite color.

663
00:36:44,380 --> 00:36:46,281
Get out of here.

664
00:36:46,572 --> 00:36:49,641
Blue is my favorite color.

665
00:37:08,871 --> 00:37:10,372
Be good.

666
00:37:11,374 --> 00:37:13,441
Thank you.

667
00:37:20,216 --> 00:37:23,852
So, how's the foundation coming, Studenmund?

668
00:37:23,853 --> 00:37:25,587
He's Studenmund. I'm Gross.

669
00:37:25,588 --> 00:37:27,455
Oh, no, you're not. You're just a little dirty.

670
00:37:27,457 --> 00:37:29,106
But, you know, you're working construction,

671
00:37:29,108 --> 00:37:31,961
so it's to be... figured. It was a joke.

672
00:37:31,963 --> 00:37:33,929
-Cute.
-Thanks.

673
00:37:33,930 --> 00:37:36,564
After the inspection, we'll
start framing by end of week.

674
00:37:36,565 --> 00:37:37,832
-Great.
-Good.

675
00:37:37,833 --> 00:37:39,134
Where'd you all learn how to build, anyway?

676
00:37:39,135 --> 00:37:40,402
Seabees.

677
00:37:40,403 --> 00:37:42,304
Navy Construction Battalion.

678
00:37:42,305 --> 00:37:43,672
If you decide you want to build

679
00:37:43,673 --> 00:37:45,507
another cabin, you know who to call.

680
00:37:45,508 --> 00:37:49,344
-Yeah? Okay. Thank you.
-All right.

681
00:37:49,489 --> 00:37:51,123
Wow.

682
00:37:56,719 --> 00:37:58,720
Guys, come on.

683
00:37:58,721 --> 00:38:00,255
I'll be fine. I've been through worse,

684
00:38:00,256 --> 00:38:02,157
-trust me.
-No.

685
00:38:02,158 --> 00:38:04,893
No, you haven't.

686
00:38:04,894 --> 00:38:06,461
I spoke to the VA.

687
00:38:06,462 --> 00:38:08,330
They have a specialist,

688
00:38:08,331 --> 00:38:12,067
a readjustment counselor that you can speak to.

689
00:38:12,068 --> 00:38:13,735
She's good.

690
00:38:13,959 --> 00:38:16,866
I spoke to her.

691
00:38:24,080 --> 00:38:26,982
Your grandpa used to love sitting up here.

692
00:38:26,983 --> 00:38:29,584
He'd sit out here, taking in the world, you know?

693
00:38:33,389 --> 00:38:34,823
You know your cousin was named after him?

694
00:38:34,824 --> 00:38:37,559
Did you know that? Huh? Can you say "Jack"?

695
00:38:37,560 --> 00:38:39,327
Can you say "Jack"?

696
00:38:39,328 --> 00:38:42,030
Anyway, for your grandfather,

697
00:38:42,031 --> 00:38:45,000
having the tough childhood
that he... that he did,

698
00:38:45,001 --> 00:38:49,104
I think building that cabin
was sort of a pipe dream.

699
00:38:54,699 --> 00:38:57,882
But he would have built it.

700
00:39:00,616 --> 00:39:03,651
He would have built it if he'd just had the time.

701
00:39:03,652 --> 00:39:06,688
-Up. Up.
-Thank you.

702
00:39:17,133 --> 00:39:19,334
There we go. There we go.

703
00:39:19,335 --> 00:39:21,236
All right.

704
00:39:21,237 --> 00:39:23,004
All right, yeah.

705
00:39:23,005 --> 00:39:24,539
We're gonna put it right up there.

706
00:39:24,540 --> 00:39:26,007
We're gonna put it right up there.

707
00:39:33,282 --> 00:39:35,476
-Hi. Straight back.
-Bring her in.

708
00:39:35,478 --> 00:39:37,056
-Careful, careful, careful.
-Here she comes.

709
00:39:37,058 --> 00:39:39,019
Okay. I'm all right. My legs aren't broken.

710
00:39:39,021 --> 00:39:41,101
Well, it's good to see the
hospital mellowed you out.

711
00:39:45,061 --> 00:39:47,095
It's awfully quiet. What'd you do, fire my crew?

712
00:39:47,096 --> 00:39:48,930
No. No, that's the sound of work being done,

713
00:39:48,931 --> 00:39:50,565
not redone.

714
00:39:51,190 --> 00:39:54,025
Ah, ah, ah. Where you going?

715
00:39:54,437 --> 00:39:56,104
You're this way.

716
00:39:56,105 --> 00:39:57,906
Go on.

717
00:39:57,907 --> 00:40:00,108
Got you set up here. You'll have

718
00:40:00,109 --> 00:40:01,742
-the whole room to yourself, so...
-Wow.

719
00:40:01,912 --> 00:40:03,845
Okay.

720
00:40:03,846 --> 00:40:05,880
Big Three Homes.

721
00:40:05,881 --> 00:40:07,615
What's this?

722
00:40:07,616 --> 00:40:10,819
Oh, that's...

723
00:40:12,421 --> 00:40:15,290
Did you know that your crew
built schools in war zones?

724
00:40:16,742 --> 00:40:19,127
Yeah. Why do you think we hired 'em?

725
00:40:21,564 --> 00:40:23,131
I think we should hire a few more.

726
00:40:23,132 --> 00:40:25,767
-Few more what?
-More of your guys and gals.

727
00:40:25,768 --> 00:40:28,303
I think we should hire more vets.

728
00:40:28,304 --> 00:40:30,205
That's great, Kev, but we've already got

729
00:40:30,206 --> 00:40:32,073
enough workers for the house.

730
00:40:33,488 --> 00:40:35,823
What if I got us more homes to build?

731
00:40:39,117 --> 00:40:41,993
How much money you got, kid?

732
00:41:02,771 --> 00:41:04,339
All right.

733
00:41:04,340 --> 00:41:05,974
Here we go.

734
00:41:06,942 --> 00:41:08,510
What's this? You want to clap?

735
00:41:08,511 --> 00:41:10,411
Patty-cake?

736
00:41:12,615 --> 00:41:14,036
Shh, shh.

737
00:41:16,452 --> 00:41:18,653
Want me to hold you? Want me to get you here?

738
00:41:18,654 --> 00:41:21,089
How about this? How about this? How about that?

739
00:41:21,100 --> 00:41:24,435
Huh? It's okay. What do you think? Huh?

740
00:41:25,861 --> 00:41:27,487
Hmm?

741
00:41:39,675 --> 00:41:41,910
-Get you anything, sir?
-Oh, um...

742
00:41:41,911 --> 00:41:44,325
No, I think we're fine.

743
00:41:48,316 --> 00:41:49,872
You're good.

744
00:41:50,527 --> 00:41:52,889
I'm getting there.

745
00:41:54,406 --> 00:41:56,784
I'm getting there.

746
00:41:58,903 --> 00:41:59,332
-

747
00:41:59,333 --> 00:41:59,761
--

748
00:41:59,762 --> 00:42:00,191
---

749
00:42:00,192 --> 00:42:00,620
---o

750
00:42:00,621 --> 00:42:01,050
---oO

751
00:42:01,051 --> 00:42:01,479
---oOo

752
00:42:01,480 --> 00:42:01,909
---oOo-

753
00:42:01,910 --> 00:42:02,339
---oOo--

754
00:42:02,340 --> 00:42:02,768
---oOo---

755
00:42:02,769 --> 00:42:05,974
---oOo---

