[Scully] One day, you'll ask me
to speak of the truth...
of the miracle of your birth, ;
to explain what is unexplained...
and if I falter
or fail on this day...
know there is an answer,
my child...
a sacred, imperishable truth...
but one you may never
hope to find alone.
Chance meeting your perfect other...
your perfect opposite...
your protector and endangerer.
Chance embarking with this other
on the greatest ofjourneys...
a search for truths
fugitive and imponderable.
If one day this chance
may befall you, my son...
do not fail or falter to seize it.
The truths are out there...
and if one day you should behold
a miracle, as I have in you...
you will learn the truth
is not found in science...
or on some unseen plane...
but by looking into your own heart...
and in that moment,
you will be blessed...
and stricken...
for the truest truths
are what hold us together...
or keep us painfully,
desperately apart.
[Servo Motor Whines]
[Camera Servo Whines]
Hey.
Tall coffee with milk?
Yes, thanks, and can I
get a warm-up, please?
[Computer Voice]
You have five new messages.
[Scully]
"I've resisted contacting you...
for reasons I know
you continue to appreciate.
But to be honest,
some unexpected dimensions...
of my new life are eating away
at any resolve I have left.
I'm lonely, Dana...
uncertain of my ability
to live like this.
I want to come home...
to you...
and to William. "
[Baby Crying]
Shh-shh-shh.
I'm physically shaking right now
seeing your words.
Wishing it were you speaking them to me.
I want so badly to see you, too...
but you are still not safe here.
[Baby Crying]
The child's mother, she was just here.
Where did she go?
I think that's her out there.
[Louder Crying]
I'm sorry.
[Door Opening]
We talk to you a second?
It's about Agent Mulder.
What about Mulder?
We got a guy contacting us
through intelligence channels.
He keeps saying
he wants to talk to Fox Mulder...
only he won't say why.
Well, who is he?
We don't know.
He always covers his tracks.
But this morning we finally
got him to tip his hand.
He says he has highly classified
military files.
Files on what?
These bioengineered soldiers
we've all come in contact with...
so-called Super Soldiers.
The same ones
threatening Mulder's life...
forcing him to live underground.
What does he want with Mulder?
Wants to give him the names...
of these Super Soldiers,
and Mulder's the only person...
he'll give them to.
Well, even if this was a good idea...
I don't know how to contact him.
I'm sorry about that.
I believe that last class
we were covering petechia...
and evidence of death by...
Agent Scully.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm trying to teach a class.
You understand
what we're being offered here?
If we know who
these Super Soldiers are...
we can go after them.
This is somebody giving us...
a way that can make it safe
for Mulder to come home.
That's the operative word here...
"somebody."
Somebody that we don't know.
And you don't want
to check it out.
What I don't want is Agent Mulder's life
to be endangered...
any more than it already is.
How long are you going to do this?
Do what, Agent Doggett?
Refuse to trust me...
or anybody.
How else you going to get him home?
[Man] When I said get in the car,
I meant right now.
[Woman]
Just leave us alone.
[Man]
I am not telling you again.
Get away. Get away from us.
Leave us alone.
[Man]
She's coming with me.
What are you doing?
Do you need help, ma'am?
- No!
- Hey!
Don't take her with you.
Do you need me to call the police?
Don't go.
Don't go!
Please!
Ma'am?
Are you all right?
Come on in.
The phone's over there.
I don't know
if it's such a good idea...
making out a police report.
[Baby Quietly Crying]
Well, you've obviously got a problem.
I saw you this morning at the café.
Is he your husband?
Yeah.
It's okay.
I understand.
I mean...
it's hard enough
caring for a child.
You don't have anyone, do you?
No.
But I wish I did.
Maybe he'll come back.
Do you have anywhere to go?
No.
I'm going to get you a blanket...
and something hot to drink.
All right?
Thank you.
My name's Dana.
I'm Patti.
What do you have?
This source of ours decided to
give my cell phone a call today.
I ran a trace.
Did you get a number?
No, but I got a node.
A sector of six city blocks.
The area's pretty vacant,
except for this building here.
Say this source is for real...
and this is Mulder's chance
to come home.
We spook the spook,
and maybe that chance goes away.
Or worse, it drives Mulder deeper.
[Car Pulling Up]
Where are you going?
Take a little look into his car.
I'll say it again.
What we risk is compromising
Mulder's return.
I don't plan on getting caught.
Good evening.
How are you?
Good.
You?
Your wife and kid?
They're good.
Good.
Everybody's good.
Monica, wake up.
What?
[Phone Humming]
Hello.
You awake?
Yeah.
I just laid down.
What time is it?
6:00 A.M.
Agent Reyes and I just
tailed a car onto your street.
We watched a guy
go into your building.
A guy we're guessing
you've got no business with.
[Baby Cries]
You there, Agent Scully?
Put him down now.
Oh, my God!
Put my baby down.
[Baby Fussing]
[Doorknob Clicking]
[Reyes]
Agent Scully! Agent Scully!
Agent Scully, do you know this man?
I wouldn't think so.
Not with him trying to
pick his way into your place.
Start with who you work for.
I'm not at liberty to say.
Is this your wife?
Maybe she's at liberty.
Maybe she don't want
to accompany you to prison.
[Scully]
You staged this, didn't you?
Arguing on the street.
Everything.
No.
It's a con job.
What are you after, my baby?
No, no.
I want to protect William.
[Man]
That's enough.
You want to get us killed?
You said...
You said that they could help us.
You told me that.
That's what you said.
What the hell is going on here?
They're watching.
They're watching?
You got something to say, say it.
I work for
the National Security Agency.
The name on my driver's license
is false.
If you were to call the police...
I would be detained
only long enough...
for another NSA agent
to authorize my release.
I don't exist as a citizen,
nor does anyone I work with.
So what are you doing here?
As you can see, my wife is upset.
I was coming to get her
to stop this very event.
What's she so upset about?
We have a daughter... Joy.
There's something about her.
Something different.
Just like there's something
different with her son William.
[Doggett]
Different how?
How do you know anything
about her or her son?
I know virtually everything
about you.
And you.
Several months ago...
you saw your son...
effect the movement
of the mobile over his crib.
He spun it as if with this mind.
It happened to us the same way.
[Reyes] So you've been
looking in this apartment...
with what, cameras?
Various forms of technology.
Then it's you
who's been contacting us.
Not directly.
My scope is limited.
I only look at what they tell me to.
But I have a supervisor
who I've told everything...
I'm telling you about
my daughter and your son...
and he started to look into it.
He learned things
about a Super Soldier program.
Things he won't tell us.
Crimes, he says,
against innocent people.
What does he want with Mulder?
Mulder's the only one capable of
making the connections, he says.
[Patti]
Maybe we can help you.
And maybe you can help us
find out the truth...
about what our babies really are.
[Phone Rings]
Hello.
[Altered Voice]
You've had quite an earful.
Who is this?
As my associate indiscreetly
told you, we don't have names.
You've been listening to us?
It's all I could do...
after you closed the shades,
Agent Scully.
You ever heard of the Constitution?
Yes.
It's what allows
foreign terrorists to live here...
and enjoy the American dream
until time comes to destroy it.
But my trespasses
are the least of your concern...
after what they've done
to you and Mulder.
What have they done?
Actually, it's what
they're prepared to do next.
I'd be happy to tell Agent Mulder.
Well, you're going
to have to tell me...
'cause I don't know
how to reach Agent Mulder.
You reached him yesterday.
You sent him an E-mail.
Would you like me
to read it to you?
Why should I trust you?
You're just a voice
on the end of the phone.
I'm not going to give you
anything unless I can meet you.
Unless l...
Unless I can see your face.
Are you still there?
If you think you can flush me out...
you're making a big mistake.
Bus bench, Internet Café.
Come alone.
You have 20 minutes.
[Receiver Clicks]
Agent Scully.
What are you doing?
I'm going to meet your contact.
I need you to watch William,
Monica.
I don't like this.
I don't like the feel of it...
and I don't like you
agreeing to it without backup.
You said I had to
trust someone, right?
Well, that's what I'm doing.
[Phone Rings]
Hello.
Are you armed, Agent Scully?
Yes.
Then you're prepared
to use your weapon...
should anything go wrong?
I'm not sure I follow you.
Then do exactly as I say.
If you vary my instructions
in the smallest way, we're over.
If I see or suspect
that you're not working alone...
I will terminate our communication.
If I believe a third party
is trying to use this meeting...
to prevent our exchange...
you must be prepared to use
your weapon in your own defense.
Am I clear?
Yes.
There's a green sedan
across the street from you.
The keys are in it.
I want you to get in the car.
All right, what next?
Start the engine,
put the car in drive...
and await my next order.
[Car Starts]
Pull out quickly! Go now!
[Horn Blares]
Agent Scully.
Is it absolutely necessary
to get innocent people hurt?
You're free to stop the car
and walk away at any time.
Up to you.
I'm doing this for your own protection
and for Mulder's.
So where am I going?
Turn right right now.
Stop the car.
Get out, Agent Scully.
Turn the engine off,
take the keys out.
Walk to the top of the alley.
There's another car there.
Get in and drive directly to
the interstate on-ramp heading west.
You will continue driving west
until I tell you otherwise.
That's far enough.
Get out of the car.
Leave it running.
Where are you?
Move around to the trunk.
You'll see a change of clothes
inside for you. Put them on.
Look, uh...
we're in the middle of nowhere!
There is no "middle of nowhere"
anymore, Agent Scully.
Put the gun in the trunk.
Your clothes, too.
[Engine Rewing]
Your watch.
Give it to me.
This is ridiculous.
This has gone far enough.
Do you want to see Mulder again?
These clothes that I'm wearing...
they're my size.
How the hell do you know my size?
Your size?
I know your blood type,
your resting heart rate...
your childhood fear of clowns.
I know the name of
your college boyfriend...
your true hair color,
your ATM PI N number...
favorite charities, pet peeves.
I know you spend
too much time alone.
And I know...
that on one lonely night...
you invited Mulder to your bed.
[Hoarsely]
Oh, my God.
I was as surprised as you are.
Who authorizes you?
I mean, what gives you the right?
Who are you?!
I'm the future, Agent Scully...
and I risked my life being here.
[Scoffs]
Well, then why do it?
I mean, why meet me?
Because you can reach Mulder.
Mulder needs to know what I know
or he may have no future.
Perhaps no one will.
Another car is parked on
the main road, half a mile out.
If I see that you haven't contacted
Mulder in the next 24 hours...
I disappear
and you never see me again.
Do you understand, lady?
Excuse me.
I'm teaching a class, Agent Doggett.
Is it something pressing?
Yeah.
I'm worried now about what it is
I've gotten you into.
You're right to be worried.
This guy that led you
all over town last night...
he says he wants to
talk to Mulder, right?
Why does he need you?
Why not go to Mulder directly?
'Cause this guy knows
Mulder resurfaces...
only if the one person
he trusts asks him to.
That guy didn't come to me,
Agent Doggett...
he came to you.
That woman that I took in
blew his cover.
He had no other choice.
Did you ever stop to think...
that this woman and her husband...
are in on this, too?
I don't believe that.
That woman is truly scared
for her child...
for the same reasons that I am.
How do you know they're not
being used by this shadow man...
to lure Mulder out?
To kill him?
'Cause that couple doesn't even
necessarily trust the shadow man.
I mean, for their own reasons.
You think about it.
This guy seems to know everything.
He even reads your E-mail.
I mean, how can you, or anybody...
hope to ensure for Mulder
a safe passage home?
Mulder and I
already considered that...
even before he left.
His return has been prearranged.
The place,
the mode of transport...
everything's been set.
Well, you can call
the whole thing off.
I can't.
I've already sent for him.
Mulder's on a train.
He'll be here at midnight.
- Maybe you can reach him.
- You can't do that to me.
- I'm sorry.
- I want to see him so bad.
I know.
And I want to make sure
that you get to, Dana.
That's the whole reason I'm here.
Well, it's too late.
And I have to go.
[Camera Servos Whirring]
Agent Boal? Edie Boal?
I'm John Doggett.
We spoke a few minutes ago.
You said if I came right down...
you might be able to help me out.
What'd I get myself into?
I've got some clothing here.
I'm looking for
anything you can find...
that might give me an I D.
Male or female?
It's a male who handled them...
and gave them to a female agent.
When do you need them?
I got a little over an hour.
Your staring over my shoulder
doesn't make me go faster.
[Announcer]
May I have your attention, please?
Southbound 112 now arriving.
Please stay clear of the platform
until the train comes to a full stop.
[Bell Clanging]
[Gunshot]
Two men shot!
Keep rolling!
Stop the train!
I'm a federal agent!
Keep rolling!
Mulder!
Agent Scully?
It wasn't supposed to happen.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
All we wanted was answers.
We never meant to harm you.
My husband was not a part of this.
I know.
I know that he was only
trying to protect me.
The man who he works for...
he's the one
who's responsible for this.
I know.
I'm sorry.
[Crying]
I'm so sorry.
What is it?
What I was afraid of.
[Scully]
Agent Doggett, what?
We can't find him.
Who?
The man I shot.
He fell in front of a moving train,
but he ain't down there on the tracks.
Well, where is he?
Nowhere.
It shouldn't make a bit of sense,
but it does.
I went to run the DNA
on the clothes he gave you...
only the man's DNA
can't be tested.
They say it's some weird DNA complex
with iron or some damn thing.
That doesn't make sense.
I think it does.
'Cause he's not a man.
He's a Super Soldier.
Mulder.
I've got to warn Mulder.
Get on the radio!
Get on the radio...
and alert them that there's
a situation on that train.
A situation?
The man who fell on the tracks,
he's gotten on that train.
[Man Over Radio]
This is the southbound 112.
We got a jumper.
A man jumped off the train
at the mile 19 connector...
ran into
the Manville Rock Quarry there.
Agent Scully, you drive.
Head down into the quarry...
and we'll meet you in the bottom.
Okay.
Agent Reyes!
Mulder!
Mulder, it's John Doggett!
Mulder?
Mulder!
[Panting]
Stop there!
Stop right there!
Why do you want to kill us?!
Mulder must die.
Mulder or your son.
What are you talking about?
What does this have to do with my son?
What's wrong with my son?
Answer me!
[Scully] I hold no hope
you can respond to this...
or that it reaches you.
I only hope that you are alive.
I cannot help believing
that you jumped off that train...
because you knew what I now know...
that these Super Soldiers...
if that's what they are...
can, in fact, be destroyed.
That the key to their destruction...
lies in the iron compound
at that quarry.
I'm scared for you, Mulder,
and for William.
The forces against us
are unrelenting...
but so is my determination...
to see you again,
to regain the comfort and safety...
we shared for so brief a time.
Until then,
I remain forever yours, Dana.
[Child]
I made this.!