Hey!
Hey, damn it!
My shoe...
[Groaning]
Give me my shoe!
Misunderstanding,
officers.
I'm the victim here!
The guy ripped me off.
Here, look.
Hey!
[Grunting]
Paper... paper.
Visa... passport.
What is your... name?
L-I... I don't know.
Hey, guard!
Come here!
Andale.!
Hey, guard!
Somebody come here!
[Chuckling]
Something funny?
Nice touch...
putting it back on.
Your one shoe.
Yeah, well,
maybe I like to hop.
You speak English.
Why didn't you say
something before?
You weren't
funny before.
Uh-huh.
Where are we?
What's the name
of this place?
What, the jail?
The town.
Tell me the name
of the town.
Tell me where I am.
Sangradura.
Mexico?
Man, if you
can't remember...
you must have had
one fine good time getting here.
What's your name?
Damn, you don't know
that either, huh?
[Chuckling]
Call you "One Shoe."
Senor Un Zapato,
huh?
[Men Laughing]
Hey, One Shoe,
what do you know?
I know I'm getting
the hell out of here.
You got money
to bribe the police?
That's what it takes.
I just need to get
to a phone...
and call
the U.S. Embassy.
Yeah, they can get
you home, I guess.
Where is home?
You know what I think,
One Shoe?
Maybe getting home is not
in your best interest.
How's that?
This isn't Tijuana
or Cabo.
We don't see Americans
in this town...
unless they're on the run
from something, somebody.
This town...
people like you
come here to disappear.
People like me?
You don't know me.
Hey... you
don't know you.
Daddy? Daddy?
[Keys Jangling]
Domingo Salmeron.
Hey, One Shoe...
nobody coming for you.
You want to hop
out of here with me?
I've got a job for you.
What kind of job?
What the hell do you care?
You work hard, maybe I'll even
buy you another shoe.
Right one, left one...
your choice.
Hey!
Right here!
Thanks.
Some other time.
Hey!
You watch your hands.
You're bought
and paid for.
You understand?
I own you like I own
that car.
I'll pay you back
your money.
You don't tell me
what you'll do.
I tell you
This makes one thing
we know about you.
You're not a man
of your word.
[Clattering]
It fit good?
What else of mine
you got?
My wallet,
my documents?
What else did you take
from me?
Show me what else
you got.
Show me!
Show me.!
I'm desaparecido?
What does that mean?
?? [Mexican Music Playing]
What's the job?
We're movers.
What do you move?
Mexicanos, Guatemaltecos...
sometimes even Chinese.
Drive them up north,
across the border into McAllen.
You're coyotes.
Don't turn your nose up at me.
For all you know, you've spent
your life fondling little boys.
No digas que quieres
trabajar con este hijo de perra.
You start tomorrow.
I'd invite you
to have a drink with us...
but Nestor hates you.
They'll rent you a room
upstairs.
I don't have any money.
First month's salary.
Don't try and leave town.
This mean anything to you?
Not a thing...
other than
the fact that...
you have silver
in your pocket...
and you still ask me for money.
I'm a marine.
Semper Fi.
A.D. Skinner, Agent Scully...
what's this I'm hearing
about Mexico?
Well, this came in last night...
from U.S. Customs.
It's a blowup from
a security camera...
at the border crossing
in Laredo, Texas.
It was taken at 12:50 a.m.
On the morning of the fourth.
We're sure this is Doggett?
It's been scanned
to Agent Reyes.
She also believes it is him.
I'd say this reshapes
the investigation.
It's our first solid lead.
Now, with your permission,
I'd like to contact...
our legate's office
and extend our task force...
south of the border.
I'm not extending
the task force.
I'm disbanding it.
Excuse me?
I see no other choice.
For the past 12 days I've had
40 agents working overtime...
scouring the entire state
ofTexas...
in what appears to be
a waste of effort.
I can't move them
lock, stock and barrel into Mexico...
not on the
strength of this.
Turn it over to the Mexican
federal police.
Doggett's in their
jurisdiction, not ours.
Sir, he could be injured.
Whether you
believe it or not...
I want to find him
as badly as you do.
But the FBI's resources
are already taxed...
by national
security concerns.
There are political realities
I have to account for.
Sir...
Agent Reyes is still
in San Antonio.
She was raised in Mexico.
She could offer the federal
police some on-site help.
She can help them all she wants.
But from this side
of the border.
Mr. Molina, you're a hard man
to get an audience with.
I've been trying for
the better part of two weeks.
What's keeping you so busy?
Selling tractors.
I own the biggest farm equipment
dealership in south Texas...
AGCO, John Deere,
New Holland, CAT.
Impressive.
I'm sorry,
I don't speak Spanish.
She says I sell drugs.
Please don't speak Spanish
anymore.
You know Hollis Rice,
don't you?
Vice president of
Pan American Mercantile?
Sure. I do business
with his bank.
I know he's missing.
My partner, John Doggett, was
investigating his disappearance.
I'm betting
my partner...
came to you
with questions.
When would this have happened?
Two weeks ago.
No, sorry.
I don't remember any person
named Doggett.
Agent, I don't quite know
what you're implying.
Mr. Molina's an upstanding
businessman...
and a pillar of the commun...
"Pillar of the community?"
Does anyone actually...
use that phrase
except Mob lawyers?
I'll tell you
what's clear to me.
You're some kind of middleman
in a smuggling operation.
Hollis Rice laundered money
for your cartel...
until something went wrong.
Maybe he got greedy,
maybe he talked too much.
Your cartel made
him disappear.
Agent...
My partner has disappeared, too.
He's in Mexico, I know that much...
and I will find him,
whatever it takes.
Your only personal
hope for the future...
is that I
find him alive.
Now where is he?
Unless my client
is under arrest...
this meeting is over.
No? Come on, Mariano.
[Whispering]
Daddy.
Hmm?
Get up, I want
to show you something.
Come on.
Let's go!
Daddy, come on! Please!
Can it wait another hour?
No.
Why, what is it?
A surprise.
Shh, don't wake your mom.
[Phone Ringing]
Senor? Senor?
Cabina tres.
[Ringing]
Marine Corps
Public Affairs Office.
Staff Sergeant McCormick
speaking.
Yeah, uh...
this is Detective, uh...
...Ladatel calling from Mexico.
I'm hoping you can give me
some help.
Yes, sir, if I can.
We've got a marine down here
who's been hit by a taxicab.
He's been messed up pretty good.
He doesn't remember
his own name.
He doesn't have any I D.
We need to contact his family.
I assume there's
somebody somewhere...
who's worrying about him.
Any chance you can give me...
a social security number
or a date of birth?
No, unfortunately, uh,
the only thing I have to go by...
is there's a tattoo on
his left shoulder that says...
"24th MAU. We Shall Not Forget."
You have any idea
what that means?
Yes, sir, I do.
The 24th Marine Amphibious Unit.
It refers to the Lebanon
barracks bombing in 1983.
That narrows things down.
Yeah, good, good.
This guy's, I don't know,
he's six feet, 190 pounds.
Brown hair, blue eyes,
about 40 years old.
If you could just
put a name to him.
If you could just tell me
anything at all about him.
Anything.
We'll definitely look into it.
[Door Opens]
Detective, do you have a number
where I can reach you?
Detective?
[Man Speaking Spanish
Over Radio]
Hey.
Sounding good.
Sounding better
than it was.
It won't sound good
until it gets new seals.
[Speaking Spanish]
Thank God I got somebody...
worth a damn.
If you'd only
drive for me.
You got a few
odd jobs, fine.
I'm not breaking
the law for you.
A man of principle...
as far as you know.
Found something out
about you today.
You're not going
to like it.
Says your name is
Henry Bruck.
The Federales are
looking for you...
in connection with
a double murder.
Doesn't give details...
but that description's
you as far as I can see.
Don't take it so hard.
A man does what he does.
I'm not judging you.
Just keep away from
the Federales, okay?
We'll keep you safe.
Monica.
Dana.
Surprise, surprise.
How did you escape Kersh's
cost-cutting regimen?
Did you see?
He shut us down.
Well, actually he doesn't
know that I'm here.
Nor does he know that
Skinner is headed to Mexico...
to consult with
the federal police.
Perfect timing,
I hope.
Look what just got
handed to me.
This says that
someone in Mexico...
is trying to track down
a former marine...
matching Doggett's description.
It says that he was
in an accident...
and possibly suffering
from amnesia.
Wait... Detective Ladatel?
Yeah, that's who
placed the call.
Does that sound
familiar to you?
Ladatel is a Mexican
telephone calling card.
We'll trace the call.
[Footsteps]
Domingo, is that you?
Siempre trabajo.
I speak English,
by the way.
Yeah?
Yeah.
See you in hell, FBI.
[Screaming]
[Gunshot]
Nestor?
Oh, God, no.
You?
Did you send him after me?
What? What's that mean?
Did you send him
to kill me?
Tell me who I am.
I don't know who you are.
Tell me who I am!
I don't know,
you son of a bitch!
But you killed my friend.
You're a killer.
That's who you are.
[Gun Cocking]
Desaparecido.
You're one of the disappeared ones.
What's that mean, disappeared?
Disappeared by who?
The Cartel.
They own the town...
everything and everybody.
People who make trouble for them
wind up dead.
Other people who make
more trouble...
dead than alive get this.
They took away
my memory?
How?!
How do I get it back?
You don't.
That's the point.
Daddy, Daddy...
Get up. I wanna show you something.
Come on.
It's a surprise. Come on.
[Groaning]
[Whimpering]
[Groans]
[Car Approaching]
John...
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
Who the hell are you?
I'm your partner Monica.
Your name is
John Doggett.
You're an FBI agent.
Do you remember?
John, trust me.
We got to leave.
I'll explain it
in the car...
but we're not safe here.
[Cars Approaching]
[Speaking Spanish]
They're telling us to come out.
Sure, they want us
to make it easy for them.
Cartel owns the cops
in this town.
They're going to kill us.
They're going to try.
Take cover.
It won't be long before they get
tired of waiting.
So, we're partners, huh?
How long we been
working together?
Not long.
But we've known each other
for years.
[Police Speaking Spanish]
They're giving us
one minute.
What's the name of my son?
It's weird.
It's the only thing I can
remember is I have a son.
I can see his face, but
I can't remember his name.
Luke.
How old is Luke?
I can't even remember that.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, no.
He's dead. He was murdered.
Is that right? Is that right?!
He was kidnapped.
He was just a little boy...
Oh!
The FBI got involved.
I was assigned
to the case.
That's when you and I met.
Oh, God!
[Glass Breaks]
God!
Oh, God, John,
they're smoking us out.
John, I need you here.
I need you to focus here, John.
[Coughing]
[Gunshots]
John.
John!
If we're going to die here...
you're going
to die on your feet!
You hear me?
Do you hear me?!
[Gunshots Continue]
Get in the bus.
Hang on!
[Yelling In Spanish]
You work for the Cartel.
You make their enemies
disappear.
Desaparecido.
You understand me?
I speak English,
but I don't understand you.
Like hell you don't.
You gave me these...
when you took my memory.
I have no idea
how you do it...
but everything I am,
everything I have...
my identity,
you robbed that from me.
I don't know who has been
saying those things to you.
How can you prove them?
I was searching for a man,
a banker from Texas.
Hollis Rice was the banker.
He was out
of his mind.
He didn't even
know his name.
You robbed him of that.
And then you tried to do
the same thing to me.
You failed, you son of a bitch.
I remember everything.
[Skinner]
Agent Doggett...
leave him to us.
Why would you want
to remember?
You can't tell me
you're happier now...
because you recall
your life.
I saw it all.
So much pain.
Why would you want to struggle
so long and hard...
to get that pain back?
Because it's mine.
Look, Daddy!
I can do it!
John...
I'm so sorry...
about Luke...
and about you
having to relive that.
I'll take the bad
as long as I remember the good.
[Child]
I made this.!