I always said there's three
kinds of people in the world...
them who make things happen,
them who watch things happen...
and them who wonder
what happened.
I made things happen.
The wrong things.
I caused pain
to anyone who came near me.
This tattoo, it used
to be my badge of honor.
But I'm a different man
since I've joined group.
A better man.
I never thought words like that
would come out of my mouth.
It's all because of the help...
and the love that
I found in this room.
You're new here.
Is it Ed?
Yeah, I'm new to this B.S.
Why do you think it's B.S.?
I mean, listen, man. I turned
my life around. A lot of us here have.
Our kind of lives go one way.
And you can't change any more than
you can undo the crimes you've done.
Well, I feel sorry for you, man.
Don't feel sorry.
You're going to hell
just like I am, brother.
Why are you here, Ed?
I drove Victor.
He knows I'm right.
Victor's been doing good.
Oh, yeah. Just look at him.
Victor, you wanna talk about it?
I've just been having bad dreams.
Really bad dreams.
[Woman]
What kind of dreams?
Oh...
seeing people skinned alive.
It's a hard road, Victor.
It's a shock to the system...
changing the way we think,
taking charge of our lives.
We're all afraid.
And that fear preys on us
night and day, brother.
In our minds and in our dreams.
You ever get enough of that crap?
"A shock to the system" crap?
This "fear preying on us
night and day" crap?
Those boys in there
are afraid of one thing...
themselves, their true natures.
You know what I'm saying, Victor?
- Sort of.
- What do you mean, "sort of"?
Don't tell me that bull
does you any good.
And don't tell me you feel any better
about yourself coming here...
that it makes
these nightmares go away.
No, it don't.
[Elevator Dings]
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
Sorry about the hour.
The way you sounded seemed like
something that couldn't wait.
No. I need another
set of eyes on it.
I called Scully in too.
A little late to be looking
for a sitter. What's so pressing?
"Victor Dale Potts."
Ex-con, three-time loser,
career criminal.
He was murdered five days ago.
Scully's got the crime report.
I'm sorry. What am I missing?
It's the way he was killed.
Agent Doggett.
Agent Scully.
I'd like him to see the body.
Damn.
I seen a bunch of these
when I was a cop.
It's a favorite of some
of the Pan-Asian gangs.
The difference is Victor Potts
had a premonition of his death.
And?
That was my question.
What I'm saying is,
this man was skinned alive...
just hours after describing it
in exact detail.
Maybe he could describe it because
maybe somebody threatened him.
He said it came in a dream,
or a vision according to the woman
who last spoke to him.
- Who's that?
- Dr. Lisa Holland.
She's a therapist who runs
an anger management group for ex-cons.
Lifelong criminal's bound
to have some bad enemies.
People capable of
this very thing.
I mean, unless there's something
here that I'm just not seeing.
Well, from what I could see
from my visual exam...
the skin was removed
with considerable skill...
by someone using
a hunting-type knife.
Arteries and veins
were left intact...
so as to prolong the period
that the victim would suffer.
Terrible way to die, for sure.
I know.
Is there anything else,
Agent Reyes?
Something special that brought
this case to your attention...
as a possible X-File?
No.
I just know I need to solve this.
And I'd appreciate your help.
You Reyes?
I'm Doggett. She's Reyes.
Detective Van Allen?
That's right.
I appreciate your help on this.
What help is that?
- On this investigation.
- There isn't a lot to investigate.
I mean, Victor Potts wasn't exactly
one of the FBI's ten most wanted.
I think she means your insight
into the way he died, Detective.
Don't have any.
But I'm sure you'd rather
talk to somebody who actually
gives a damn, right?
Hate to say it but he probably sums up
most people's feelings.
It's hard for the
Victor Pottses of the world.
Nobody cares much about them
in life or in death.
Victor told the group a story...
about a dream he'd had.
These men are haunted by their pasts.
That's why they're here.
But this dream came true.
Sometimes the past they want
to escape won't let them.
There was a man... Ed.
He drove Victor to group that night.
He was all over Victor's case.
You think he could
have killed him?
I try to help these men.
Some have been violent,
some still are.
It's not my place to judge them.
Dr. Holland...
there's justice to be served here.
You can't forget that.
I'm sure Agent Reyes
won't let me.
Probably won't let anybody.
Thank you for your help.
She contacted you with this case?
I think the police would have given up
on who murdered Victor Potts...
if it wasn't for her.
You know something, Agent Reyes?
You seem real familiar to me.
Excuse me?
You ever visited Novi before?
No, I never have.
You eyeballing me?
You got some kind of
problem or something?
Problem?
Your friend is dead.
I guess the good news is
I get to move up the ladder here now.
You know how it happened.
Now, why don't you
just back off.
FBI wants to talk to me now
because of the way he died.
Gonna want to talk to you too.
I got nothing to tell nobody.
You were messing with his head.
I'd watch what you go saying.
Or what?
You going to do me too?
[Loud Buzzer Blaring]
I got a ride to catch.
Yeah, that's right, walk away.
But just like you said...
you can't run from what you are.
Yeah, and I'll see you in hell.
[Car Door Slams]
Here you go, Dr. Scully.
Everything you ever wanted
to know about skinning people...
but were afraid to ask.
This is every case of removal
of the human dermis...
I could find
within the last dozen years.
Most of these are
postmortem skinnings.
That's all I could find.
And most of it's Asian gang-related,
like you mentioned.
Wait a minute. What's this?
I'm sorry. I probably shouldn't
have included that one...
because it's pretty much
ancient history.
There's a pattern.
The way the skin's been stripped off.
It's identical.
But how could it be?
Did you notice the date?
1960.
[Television Playing]
...Inca and Mayan peoples.
However, the priest thought
that souls survived on Earth...
as a living shrub,
tree or other foliage, and...
- [Knocks Softly]
- Excuse me.
Dr. Mueller?
[Music On TV Plays]
Dr. Bertram Mueller?
Yes?
My name is Dana Scully.
I'm with the FBI.
I want to ask you some questions
about a John Doe...
you did an autopsy on in 1960.
You honestly expect me to recall...
some case from way back when?
I'm 84 years old.
Sir, this particular victim
was skinned alive.
In all my days, I never saw
anything as inhuman as this.
Sir, I haven't located police records
from the investigation.
Was there ever a suspect
who was charged or arrested...
in this case as far as you know?
No suspects, no investigation
for that matter.
I don't understand.
The victim was a John Doe...
a nobody.
Carl Hobart, the county sheriff,
figured he was a drifter.
Hobart said he didn't want
to stir up the community.
And no one called him on that?
I tried. The sheriff had other
things on his mind, I suppose.
Why do you say that?
Well, it wasn't long after that
he put a bullet through his head.
What are you thinking, Doctor?
This is some copycat murder
40-odd years later?
If so, it's the most perfectly
executed that I've ever seen.
And why copy an obscure murder...
that nobody's ever even heard of?
A string of murders.
- I'm sorry?
- I thought you knew.
John Doe...
was only the first.
Hey, I'm working in here.
[Footsteps]
Is that you, Ed?
Come see what I got for you.
[Footsteps]
Tell you what. You best clear
the hell out, whoever you are!
Hey!
[Thud]
Oh, God! Oh, God, no!
Let me go! Let me down!
[Screams]
Dr. Holland?
Lisa?
[Doggett]
Monica?
What the hell
are you dreaming about?
Nothing.
It was a nightmare.
How did you know to come in here?
I was on the phone.
I could hear you
through the wall calling out.
Who were you on the phone to?
Dr. Lisa Holland.
That anger-management group she runs,
it's getting smaller.
It's okay. Let 'em through.
Go ahead.
- What happened to the lights?
- Somebody cut 'em.
Might want to watch your step.
We got some blood on the floor.
Not as much as you'd expect.
Oh, my God!
Hey, you okay?
Monica?
Agent Reyes, I got a call
from Agent Doggett.
He said there's another victim.
Monica, you okay?
I'm just catching my breath.
Well, if you're up for it,
I've got something to show you.
Case files from crimes back in 1960.
What are they?
More skinned bodies...
cut with the same precision
as the body I examined.
Can I see that light a second?
[Gasps]
Holy God, he's still alive.
Somebody get in here
and get him down!
We need a medic in here!
Can you hear me?
Do you understand?
Who did this to you?
Do you know who did this to you?
[Gagging Sound]
Are we going somewhere, baby?
You're not. Get out.
Eddie?
What'd I just say?
But I'm not even dressed.
What else is new? Get out.
Why are you such a jerk?
FBI! Stop right there!
What part of"Stop right there"
did you not understand?
So, what? He's just waiting for
his lawyer? That's what he's doing?
He's in a bad place.
I've been there myself once or twice
sitting right where he is now...
not thinking you have a chance.
Yeah? You ever murdered two men?
He's four years out of prison...
holding down a job,
showing up to work sober.
Why do it?
Kill a friend, then a coworker?
You're the one that said
he was a hothead, right?
Why run if you're not guilty?
Bag packed to hit the road...
packed with knives?
I don't think we're gonna find
the murder weapon on him.
What makes you say that?
Because I think this man here
is running from something else.
I want to talk to him.
Hi.
My name is Monica.
I know what you're thinking,
that I must be the good cop.
No such thing.
You didn't do it, did you?
Your friend, Victor...
he said he had bad dreams...
seeing things.
I think you're seeing them now.
How would you know?
Maybe I see them too.
Can I talk to you for a second?
You wanna explain to me what
you're doing in there, Agent Reyes?
I'm trying to make a connection.
Hell of a way to do it.
I can see this guy's defense already.
"Your Honor, I was having
bad dreams, seeing things.
Ask Agent Reyes,
she's seeing 'em too."
Something you're not telling me?
You two about finished?
With what?
The suspect.
- He's not our man.
- What are you talking about?
Girlfriend vouched for him.
Said they were getting hammered down
at the Bent Oak from 6:00 till closing.
Bartender confirms it.
I don't believe this.
I know where you live, partner.
You're always welcome at group.
[Phone Rings]
Agent Reyes.
[Scully] I need you to come
to Quantico right away.
Why?
I have something to show you.
Agent Scully?
Agent Reyes.
What are these?
I showed you files of men
killed in 1960...
skinned alive
like the current victims.
I had two of those bodies exhumed
looking for crossover forensic details.
- Are there any?
- Yes.
There are cuts in the bone...
on the tibias
and on the shoulder girdles...
that matched the cutting pattern
I found on Victor Potts...
using the exact same knife...
which left a signature pattern
of grooves.
Same knife, same killer.
That's what you're saying, right?
Well, it's even weirder than that.
I ran bios and backgrounds
from the victims from 1960.
[Reyes] They're both ex-convicts
like the current victims?
Mm-hmm. But look at the date
that they died.
March 8, 1960.
June 21, 1960.
Birth dates...
of Victor Potts and Terry Pruit.
Potts and Pruit were born
on the exact same dates...
that the previous victims died.
You knew that we'd find something
like this, didn't you, Agent Reyes?
How?
[Phone Rings]
John Doggett.
Where are you?
Sitting outside
the suspect's house...
wondering where
the surveillance is I ordered.
I need a birth date on him.
- Who?
- The suspect, Ed Kelso.
It's important.
He may be in danger.
He may be gone.
I'll call you.
Yeah, this is John Doggett.
I need to speak
to Detective Van Allen.
I'll hang on. Just get him.
[Knocking]
This house was supposed to be
under a 24-hour watch.
Patrolman says he wasn't gone
more than five minutes.
You see that man in there?
You think it takes five minutes
to do that to somebody, Detective?
I don't know how long it takes,
Agent Doggett.
Only know you said watch him
so he don't run.
Agent Doggett.
[Sighs]
I have something to tell you.
[Doggett] This thing with the
birthdays is weird, no doubt about it.
Looks to me like we're dealing
with a real sick puppy here.
I don't think so.
Choosing your victims because
of their damn birth dates...
it's the very definition
of a serial killer.
I think we should get the boys
from Behavioral Science out on this.
No.
That's not what's happening here.
It's the only thing
that makes sense.
To you.
[Sighs]
Okay, what do you think it is?
He knew he was going to die.
He had a premonition of his death.
Just like the first victim did.
So how do you figure that?
I'm involved in this some way.
I have some kind of memory of it.
It's all happened before
and now it's happening again.
You mean that it's a copycat
and you have some kind of recall.
These men...
were born to die this way.
The same way they died before.
The same way they died before?
Not the men, but their souls.
Their souls are murdered
over and over again...
from one lifetime to the next...
by someone who won't let them rest.
Now, how's this happening,
their souls coming back?
Reincarnation?
It doesn't strike you...
that these men were all born on the
dates of the previous victims' deaths?
Yeah, it strikes me.
It strikes me that
the killer is clever.
A rag is stuffed in his mouth.
A dirty rag.
Black with soot.
Coal dust...
from a coal mine.
How the hell did you know that?
I don't know.
So what are we looking for?
I don't know exactly.
But if the old files are correct...
there's going to be
a fourth victim.
[Doggett] It looks like housekeeping
hasn't been here in awhile.
You or me?
I'll check out the mine.
[Rustling]
[Thud]
[Man]
You shouldn't have come here.
I'm a federal agent. I'm armed.
Let go of the gun now.
You can't stop it.
You never do.
You always fail.
It's your lot.
Agent Reyes.
Monica!
[Coughs]
Agent Reyes.
Are you hurt?
Talk to me.
- He was here.
- Who?
Van Allen.
He's who's killing these men.
Van Allen?
He was skinned himself...
back in 1868...
by four men in a mining dispute.
His killers were never punished.
Now he's born to keep avenging
that injustice again and again.
Van Allen's the cop here.
That's why these cases
never get solved.
Every time, four murders.
Every time, four bodies.
Then he takes his own life so he
can just start it up all over again.
There's still a fourth victim,
and I think I know who it is.
[Phone Ringing]
Lisa Holland.
Dr. Holland, it's Monica Reyes.
You've seen the visions,
haven't you?
Just like the others in your group.
Visions of people skinned alive.
It's true, isn't it?
How did you know?
Where are you now?
I'm just finishing a session.
Is there anybody with you?
No, they've all left.
Why? What's this about?
Get out of there.
You're in danger.
It's Detective Van Allen.
He's coming after you.
[Footsteps Approaching]
Dr. Holland?
Dr. Holland.
Time's come!
You're the last.
No use running.
It always ends the same.
[Gunshot]
Get the paramedics out here.
You...
[Choking]
Always fail.
You're not dying on me.
Not until you tell me
what you mean!
[Monitor Beeping]
Doc says it's gonna be touch-and-go
tonight. That we should go home.
Go on, Monica.
Go on home.
There's nothing
you're gonna learn here now.
You still won't believe it,
will you?
My connection to this man.
However you did it,
however you knew what you know...
what matters here is
you saved a woman's life.
He's trying.
We all are.
It's just a long way to go from...
this...
to this.
Do you believe
in second chances, Dana?
A chance to correct the mistakes
we make in our lives?
You mean in a future life?
That's what these people
were trying to do.
All the victims, trying
to atone for their sins...
from what happened in that photo.
Only this man wouldn't let them.
And Lisa Holland?
What about her?
She was one of them.
One of the men
you see standing there.
And you?
Whoever I was, I failed.
In 1868.
In 1909.
In 1960, I failed.
I was always there,
but I couldn't stop the killings...
and he knew that.
Just like he knows
I'm here right now.
He feels me...
the way I felt him...
when I saw that picture
of the first victim.
And somehow he knows
my deepest fear...
that I'll fail.
Well, maybe in this life
you succeed.
Maybe.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Steady Tone]
[Baby Crying]
[Many Babies Fussing Noisily]
[Child]
I made this!