[Helicopter Whirring]
[Engines Rumbling]
Dr. Frett.
[Machinery Humming]
[Door Closes]
[Door Buzzing]
[Footsteps Approaching]
[Grunting]
No!
You're dead.
Go.
[Loud Thumping]
There's others.
[Klaxon Blaring]
Halt!
Sir? Sir!
[Both Grunting]
[Grunts]
[Gasps And Grunts]
[Screaming]
What are you thinking?
Where am I?
Wrong answer!
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking about getting
the hell out of here.
Wrong... answer.!
[Groans]
[Moans]
[Gasps]
No sleeping!
[Metal Door Clanging]
What are you thinking?
About my son...
about his mother.
Wrong answer!
Now, what are
you thinking?
What do you want from me?!
Wrong... answer!
I want answers, you hear me?
I want answers!
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
[Metal Door Clanging]
No sleeping!
Did you hear me?
Yes.
What are you thinking?
What should I be thinking?
You're a guilty man.
You entered a government
facility illegally...
in search of
nonexistent information!
You failed in every respect!
Yes.
Say it!
I'm a guilty man.
I failed in every respect.
I deserve the harshest
punishment for my crime.
[Door Clanging Shut]
[Door Buzzing]
How long has he been here?
I'm trying to get
someone to say.
Who called you?
Kersh's office.
Who called them?
I don't know:
I just know that...
Mulder's being held
here indefinitely.
What for?
For the murder of
a military man.
[Door Squeaks]
[Silence]
Mulder.
Dana.
[Gasps]
Oh, my God.
You okay?
Am I okay?
Mulder, I haven't seen you
in such a long time.
I was so worried.
Well, it's okay,
I'm all right.
They're treating me
really well in here.
What's happened to you?
Nothing.
I'm squared away.
Oh, hey, Walter.
It's good to
see you, man.
Have they told you
what the charges are, Mulder?
What you're doing here?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We're clear on that.
You're clear on what?
My crimes.
Mulder...
I murdered a man, Dana.
I went looking for something
that didn't exist, and l...
I made a terrible
mistake.
I should be
punished severely.
Whatever you were doing...
you have the right
to a lawyer...
to an inquiry
and process of law.
I don't think
you heard me.
All right.
Time's up.
We're going to get you
out of here.
Well, how is that?
I'm a guilty man.
Time's up. Let's go.
Uh... excuse me.
I don't understand.
Why are you helping me?
Because you can't do this alone.
Let's go.
You saw him? Mulder?
They've accused him of murder?
And they have him
believing that he did it.
Of murdering who?
Knowle Rohrer.
Knowle Rohrer? It can't be.
I watched Knowle Rohrer die.
He can't die.
Knowle Rohrer's a Super Soldier.
[Hangs Up Phone]
Mulder sidestepped security...
at a facility
known as Mount Weather...
a place where they say our so-called
"Shadow Government" is installed.
What about this murder charge?
30 government workers
are ready to testify...
they witnessed Mulder...
push a military officer
to his death.
Killing a man
who can't be killed?
Where you goin'?
To beg mercy with
the man upstairs.
[Man]
Come in.
Deputy Director Kersh.
I've just been going over my
notes on this whole business.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you.
We both got a problem...
with this man of yours,
Agent Mulder.
Mulder's been a running
problem for the FBI.
But nothing
this serious.
I would think...
I've been asked
by a female agent...
Mulder's closest associate...
to beg mercy
of the military court...
to give Mulder
every consideration...
based on his good character.
You've reviewed
the charges, yes?
Yes.
There's a charge of murder.
This would
look bad for the Marines...
if it didn't
look worse for the FBI.
What does Mulder
intend to plead?
You wanted a chance to clear up
this mess, Mr. Kersh...
and I'm going to give it to you,
give it to the FBI.
How?
A fair hearing for your agent
by his own agency.
Your prosecutor, your judges.
Held in my court.
That can't be legal.
Why do this?
I want a verdict.
A guilty verdict.
This man Mulder
has made a lot of enemies.
He's a crusader.
And a lot of people
do not like the crusade.
I can't do that.
Oh, you'll do it,
Deputy Director.
You and I
both know...
there are forces
inside the government now...
that a man would be foolish
to disobey.
Mulder.
Mulder!
[Sniffing]
I smelled you coming, Clarice.
[Chuckles]
Oh, my...
Damn it, Mulder.
It's not funny
to see you...
putting on
that act.
No, that is funny.
What's not funny is what
they do to you in here...
if you don't
put on that act.
Come here, you big,
bald, beautiful man.
The only thing you're going
to be kissing, Mulder...
is your sweet ass good-bye,
with the trouble you're in.
Uh-huh, I kind of
gathered that...
right around the 50th
brainwashing session.
Mulder, why are they
doing this to you?
They think they're
preparing me for my trial.
For my testimony.
Your testimony's
not going to matter.
Not with the case
they're building.
Not building. Rigging.
Yeah, I don't think
you understand...
the seriousness
of the charges.
This isn't some routine
wrist slapping.
You're on trial for your life.
My trial's
a forgone conclusion.
What they really want...
is for me to admit my guilt
and help them out.
What's really on trial
here is the truth.
Mulder, they're saying
you killed a man.
Have they produced a body?
You can't produce a body...
because you can't kill
the man who won't die.
Well, body or not,
they've got...
30 witnesses from
that government facility...
ready to testify
against you.
Mulder, we'll get you
the best lawyer.
To defend a man
who believes in aliens...
against the FBI
and the military?
It's never going to happen.
Skinner can defend me.
I can't represent you.
You know all the facts,
the details...
the whole government conspiracy.
More than that, I trust you.
Mulder...
They can't try me without
exposing themselves.
I know what I'm doing.
[Cell Door Opening]
Whoo, now it's a party.
Agent Mulder.
What's the matter?
We've been working off
what little we have...
but the military
just got back to us.
You ready for this?
I know this
is impossible...
but they're saying they
got Knowle Rohrer's body.
[Scully]
Mulder, it's me.
Is it time to go?
No. That's why I'm here.
[Sighs]
Mulder, I need you
to talk to me.
Confide in me...
or we'll lose.
We can't win, Scully.
We can only hope
to go down fighting.
You're scaring me.
Mulder, I'm so scared that
I've just got you back...
and now I'm going
to lose you again.
I know what I'm doing.
Well...
whatever you're doing...
you have no idea how much
has already been lost...
what I've had to do.
I do know.
Skinner told me.
Our son, Mulder...
I gave him up.
[Sobbing]
Our son.
I'm so afraid you could
never forgive me.
I know you had no choice.
I just missed
both of you so much.
God, where
have you been?
Where have you been hiding?
In New Mexico.
Doing what?
Looking for the truth.
[Laughing]
You found something,
didn't you?
Huh?
What did you find?
I can't tell you.
You found something
in that facility?
That's what
you were doing, right?
Mulder, what did you find
out there?
Scully, I can't tell you.
That doesn't make sense.
You've got to trust me, Scully.
I know things
it's better you don't.
[Door Creaking Open]
Assistant
Director Skinner.
Special Agent
Kallenbrunner.
I'll be handling
the prosecution.
I'm out of the
L.A. Field Office.
How did you get this assignment?
I was a federal
prosecutor in D. C...
before joining the FBI.
And you?
That's a good question.
Let's bring in the defendant.
This proceeding
is called to order.
Mr. Kallenbrunner...
you may proceed.
I have no witnesses to call.
I will submit to
the court, however...
the sworn testimony...
of 30 men and women
who saw the crime.
Assistant Director.
I move to dismiss these
proceedings on the grounds...
it violates the accused's
rights to a fair trail.
I'm not a lawyer.
You're not a judge.
This is not
a court of law.
[Kersh]
This is a military court of law.
You may want
to familiarize yourself...
with Title Ten
of the U.S. Code.
But I suggest
you call a witness.
Then I move to delay this trail.
My central witness,
Marita Covarrubias...
works for the
United Nations...
and I can't
locate her.
And I've received no help...
from the U.S. Government
locating her.
I have to deny that request.
Do you have another witness,
Mr. Skinner?
I'll call a witness...
but I would like to do so
under protest.
Both the panel's judgments...
and rulings are sovereign,
Mr. Skinner.
There is no record.
Excuse me?
This isn't a
secret tribunal.
As you've so kindly...
informed me, it's
a court of law.
Military court of law...
Mr. Skinner.
[Mulder]
It's okay.
Try your case.
[Skinner]
Please state your name for the court.
My name is Dana
Katherine Scully.
I was assigned nine
years ago to the X-Files...
to spy on Agent Mulder...
whose methods
the FBI distrusted.
Assigned not just as an agent,
but as a medical doctor.
A scientist.
And as a serious scientist...
you came to believe
in Agent Mulder's theories.
I came to believe...
in the existence
of extraterrestrial life.
[Gunshot]
And in a conspiracy
inside the government...
to keep their existence
a secret.
[Skinner]
The proof was...
overwhelming.
It was even scientifically
undeniable.
I believe...
as do many respected scientists...
that life came to Earth
millions of years ago...
from a meteor or a rock
from Mars.
So, what you're saying is,
life... human life...
is extraterrestrial...
by definition.
[Kallenbrunner]
Objection. What does this...
nonsense have to do with Mulder...
murdering a man
in cold blood?
Agent Scully will prove...
that a government conspiracy
exists to deny the existence...
of extraterrestrials.
You are not here
proving government conspiracies...
Mr. Skinner.
You are here to defend
Fox Mulder.
And I'm trying to do that.
It's your case, Mr. Skinner.
So, a meteor
crashed to Earth...
but along with the biological
building blocks on it...
there was something else...
an alien virus.
[Scully]
I believe...
there was a virus...
which thrived here
prehistorically.
I believe that virus
infected early man...
and transformed his physiology.
[Skinner]
Changed him into something else.
[Scully]
Into an alien life-form himself.
[Skinner]
And what happened...
to these aliens?
They died in the last ice age
35,000 years ago.
And the virus?
It lay dormant underground
until it surfaced once again...
during our current
geologic period.
And the government knows
of this?
The government learned...
of this virus in 1947
when a UFO crashed
in Roswell, New Mexico.
A UFO crash revealed the virus?
The virus thrived underground...
in petroleum deposits.
In black oil.
It has sentience.
It can think.
It has the ability
to communicate...
and it communicated...
with the UFOs.
And the government knows this,
too.
In Roswell, they
captured aliens...
from the spacecraft
wreckage.
They salvaged various
alien technology from them...
and from their data banks...
they learned of the alien plan
to recolonize the Earth.
[Kersh]
Is this all...
leading anywhere?
[Mulder]
Yeah.
The destruction of mankind.
I'll warn you once,
Agent Mulder.
[Skinner] And what did
the government do with this...
information
of an alien takeover?
They kept it a dark secret.
If it had gotten out...
there would
have been wild panic.
Mr. Skinner, are we finished?
No. There's the matter
of Agent Scully's own abduction...
in 1994.
Abduction by whom?
By the military...
working with the government
conspirators...
to develop a breed
ofhuman-alien hybrids...
that the aliens would use
as a slave race.
[Skinner]
Thank you, Agent Scully.
Your witness, Mr. Kallenbrunner.
All these E.T. S running around.
It's hard to keep these aliens straight
without a scorecard.
I myself have never
seen an alien.
Could we call one as a witness?
You're being facetious.
No, I'm not. I'd just like
to see some proof.
There are the Mars rocks...
No. I need something good.
Something amazing.
Something really cool.
I don't know what you mean.
Well, what I mean is,
you have no proof...
to back up one word
you just told us.
Agent Scully,
isn't it true...
that you and Mulder were lovers,
and you got pregnant...
and had his
love child?
Objection!
Thank you. Next witness.
Can you state
your full name?
Jeffrey Frank Spender.
Mr. Spender...
I know you didn't hear
Mr. Kallenbrunner...
but he'd like to make
a mockery of the X-Files.
You worked on the
X-Files yourself.
Yes, until three years ago.
When you were shot
in the X-Files office.
- Shot by your own father.
- [Gunshot]
Can I ask you to please
tell the court...
exactly who your father was?
He led the government conspiracy...
to exploit the existence
of aliens.
Objection.
There's no government
conspiracy...
that I've seen
established here.
I agree with Mr. Kallenbrunner.
I don't see where this is going.
If I can prove this conspiracy,
it will justify Mulder's actions...
and you will have no choice
but to acquit.
I hope
this isn't the entire basis...
of your defense, Mr. Skinner.
[Sighs]
You have a relationship
to Agent Mulder...
don't you,
Mr. Spender?
He's my half-brother.
His mother had an affair
with my father.
[Skinner]
But he never knew that.
Not until he met you
at the FBI.
He didn't know both his father
and mine were...
in the alien conspiracy.
His father was
a reluctant member.
When Agent Mulder began
to know the truth...
about this connection,
my father had his father killed...
by an assassin
named Alex Krycek.
[Skinner]
He killed him to silence him?
Mulder's father lived his life
in shame.
Not for the conspiracy...
but for a terrible decision
he made.
[Skinner]
Involving Agent Mulder's sister.
[Spender]
The aliens distrusted...
their human collaborators.
Members of the conspiracy
were made to surrender...
family members
as human collateral.
So, Mulder's father gave up
Mulder's sister.
His own
eight-year-old daughter.
[Spender]
Mulder witnessed his sister...
being abducted by aliens.
It haunted him to no end.
It's why he pursued
the X-Files.
What became of her? Samantha?
She was returned.
She was sent to California
where we were raised together.
She was taken many more times
and suffered horrible tests.
[Skinner]
Mulder spent years looking for her...
several times
thinking that he'd found her.
But he was tricked.
[Spender] Samantha was part
of the cloning experiment...
done by the conspiracy.
She herself died in 1987.
[Skinner]
By your own father's hand...
essentially.
[Spender]
When I went to work for the FBI...
I didn't know
of my father's crimes.
When I stood up to him,
he shot me.
When I didn't die...
he subjected me
to the same horrible tests.
Your witness.
[Kallenbrunner] Mr. Spender,
I'm sorry for your suffering.
I'm sure none of us can really
imagine what it's like.
Your father must be brought
to justice.
I believe my father
is dead.
Mr. Spender, you're here...
to speak for the character
of Agent Mulder.
In reports you filed
while an FBI agent...
I see here you describe Mulder
as "arrogant...
difficult,
a control freak...
widely disliked
by his peers."
Those reports were written
before I knew the truth.
This report calls him "unstable...
prone to violent outbursts. "
I have the report right here...
if your memory
needs refreshing.
Thank you, Mr. Spender.
[Young Man]
You found out about Mulder?
You found out he's in trouble.
I'll get ready now.
[Mulder] I know why you're
here and what you want.
I can't give it to you.
Make them a deal, Mulder.
Guilty on a lesser charge.
Maybe they'll go for it...
and they'll let you
walk out of here.
I'd rather die, Scully.
How can you say that?
How can you say that, Mulder,
to me?
Because this is greater
than you or me.
This is about everything
we worked for for nine years.
The truth that we both
sacrificed so much...
to uncover and to expose.
Well, then, expose it, Mulder!
Take the stand.
Whatever it is that
you're withholding...
take the stand
and hit them full force.
I can't.
Why?
I just can't.
You say this is greater than us,
and maybe it is...
but this is us fighting
this fight, Mulder, not you.
It's you and me.
That's what
I'm fighting for, Mulder.
You and me.
[Man]
Get up.
Who's that?
Who's there?
What are you doing here?
That's what I'm here to ask you.
I'm putting the truth on trial.
What truth?
Whose truth?
You think these men
will even hear it?
They're afraid to hear it.
They're not afraid.
They have too much power
to be afraid.
You're going to learn that
just like I did.
You'll die learning it.
I'm not afraid of that.
There's a truth...
even you're afraid to speak now...
because you know it's futile.
No.
Because I refuse to accept it.
Then you're going to need help.
How can you possibly help me?
They said this is where I could
find the body, at Fort Marlene.
Right.
The deceased's name
is Knowle Rohrer, former Marine...
last employed
by the D.O.D.
No, I don't want
to call back.
I want to talk to
your superior...
[Phone Disconnects]
Son of a bitch hung up on me!
Shh.
There's somebody in your yard.
Where is he?
He was at
the back door.
I got him.
He's coming around.
Stay where
you are!
Federal agent!
Hands in the air!
Who are you?
What are you doing
skulking around my house?
I didn't want
to be seen.
I don't want to endanger him.
Who are you talking about?
Someone who wants
to help Mulder.
State your full name
for the court.
Marita Covarrubias.
And your
former government title?
Special Representative to the
Secretary General of the U.N.
The United Nations.
Aposition giving you
unrestricted access...
to countries and leaders
around the world.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
How did you
use this power?
Basically, to further
the interests...
of a secretive group of men...
who called themselves
the Syndicate.
What were their interests?
Developing an
alien virus vaccine...
before the Russians
developed one.
And how'd they
go about that?
By testing innocent civilians...
all over the world.
Test subjects were tracked
through DNA identifiers...
in their smallpox
vaccination scars.
Without the subjects'
knowledge?
Mostly.
Some developed suspicions.
I saw Russians...
who cut off their arms
to prevent being tracked.
[Skinner]
As they did to an American man...
that you worked
quite intimately with.
[Covarrubias]
Yes. Alex Krycek.
Did you believe
in the Syndicate?
In their
international conspiracy?
No.
I was paid for my access.
In fact, you came
to hate them.
Yes.
It's why I helped Agent Mulder...
when he approached me.
But you were
found out.
And the Syndicate
punished you for this.
They turned me into a...
a test subject.
[Skinner]
Testing what?
They were pretending to work
with the aliens...
to infect the entire population
with an alien virus...
but the conspirators
were trying to save themselves...
by secretly and selfishly
developing a vaccine.
The conspirators believed
all life in the universe...
had been infected
with the virus...
including a race of shape-shifting
alien bounty hunters...
who policed the conspiracy
for the aliens.
But they were wrong...
and it led to the destruction
of the conspiracy.
And who destroyed it?
A group of renegade aliens
who had avoided infection...
with the virus
through self-disfigurement.
And the conspirators
themselves...
What happened to them?
They're all dead now...
killed by these same
faceless aliens.
Then what are you afraid of now?
Why resist testifying
here today?
Because the conspiracy continues...
just in another form
by other men.
Objection.
Mr. Skinner can't ask questions
and give the answers.
Sustained.
Fox Mulder's on trial
for murder here.
The man he's
accused of killing...
is one of these
new conspirators.
An alien replacement
for a human being.
What they're calling
a Super Soldier.
You can prove this,
can't you?
You know who these men are,
don't you?
Ms. Covarrubias?
They'll kill her.
Ms. Covarrubias,
I asked you a question.
I need an answer.
No.
It's okay.
Let her go.
What the hell
are you doing, Mulder?
She's the last best
witness that we have.
Doesn't matter.
Thank you, Ms. Covarrubias.
I got nothing else.
Assistant Director.
I have an unscheduled witness
that I'd like to call here today.
- No, not him.
- Mulder, sit down.
You don't understand.
I'm trying to protect that boy.
Well, now he's here
to protect you.
[Kersh]
Mr. Kallenbrunner...
do you have any objections
to this... witness?
Not like Mr. Mulder here does.
[Skinner]
Can you tell us your name?
Gibson Andrew Praise.
Do you know this man?
Yes. He's my friend.
I hid him in the desert
for the last year.
Mulder met you
as a chess prodigy.
Your life was endangered because of
your highly unusual brain activity.
Cut to the chase, Mr. Skinner.
Gibson Praise
can read people's minds.
Mulder and Scully
proved this scientifically.
There's a certain junk DNA
which all humans share...
but has no apparent function.
Gibson's junk DNA
is functional...
DNA which is believed
to be alien.
You're trying to tell us
this boy can read minds?
Yes.
He's reading your mind
right now.
And the minds
of the judges, too?
Yes.
Even his.
And what makes him so special?
He's not human.
He's one of them.
One of them!
I want that man examined!
Mr. Skinner, control him.
- Mulder!
- You're afraid!
You're afraid of what I know!
You're afraid of the truth!
Where's Gibson?
He's with Scully:
In good hands.
[Doggett]
We spent the night talking to him.
Gibson knows
you're concerned.
We're protecting him now.
He shouldn't have done
what he did...
exposing himself like that.
Well, the boy was
trying to protect you...
and it looks like
it may have worked.
He says three judges
are wavering.
They're leaning
in your favor.
It's going to take a little more
than that...
the way things
are going.
We were never going to win.
Take the stand, Mulder.
Testify.
No.
Then we'll testify,
me and Monica.
No.
Both of us have seen too much...
Listen to me,
they'll destroy you.
They'll put you out
on the street.
What's left for us
on the X-Files?
We came to this job...
to give it our best.
It's the way we're going
to leave.
It's not about how good you are.
They control the game.
They own it.
Then let's shove it up
their ass.
Mr. Skinner?
I'd like to call
John Doggett.
[Skinner]
Agent Doggett...
you've been on the X-Files
for two years.
And with all that you've seen...
how do you feel about this term
"paranormal"?
Well, the way I look at it,
calling something paranormal...
is just a way of avoiding
a real explanation.
You're a skeptic.
But I see here in your own
case reports...
some very detailed descriptions
of things...
that a skeptic would never
believe in...
these so-called Super Soldiers.
Well, that's a whole
different deal.
[Skinner]
In what way?
'Cause I've seen 'em...
with my own eyes, ;
shot... drowned...
even ground up
in a garbage truck.
And they just come right back
to life.
What are they?
Well, the best I can figure...
they're some kind
of secret military project...
ordinary men made invincible.
Objection.
What does this science fiction
have to do with anything?
[Skinner]
Agent Doggett is going to tell you...
that the man that Mulder
is accused of killing...
is a Super Soldier.
A man that Agent Doggett
served with in the marines.
Name of Knowle Rohrer.
Objection.
Agent Doggett was not
present at the murder...
nor has he seen or
examined the victim.
That's because I've been getting...
the bum's rush
from the government.
Objection sustained.
Well, then, let me ask you,
Agent Doggett...
if a Super Soldier
is invincible...
how could Mulder possibly
have killed this man?
He couldn't.
The way I
understand it...
they only way to kill
a Super Soldier...
is with some rare metal.
Agent Scully says it's a form
of magnetite from some meteor...
that fell to Earth.
And Mulder's not accused
of doing that, is he?
No, sir.
Your witness.
Agent Doggett...
in going over
your files...
I must say... it's an
honor to speak to a man...
whose record is distinguished...
by such duty
to his country.
Now, I'm not going...
to doubt a man
of your integrity...
Agent Doggett,
even if he tells me a story...
I find too incredible
to believe.
Thank you.
Just as you must not doubt
the integrity of Fox Mulder...
on whose behalf
you're here to testify.
Correct.
Even if Mulder...
believes these so-called
Super Soldiers are aliens?
He believes they're aliens,
you know.
You said you were a skeptic.
That's right.
So an alien conspiracy...
which Mulder has built
his defense on...
must be entirely unbelievable
to you, too.
[Sighs]
My name is Monica Reyes.
I've been with the FBI
since 1990.
Before coming onto the X-Files,
Agent Reyes...
you worked in the New Orleans
field office...
investigating cases
of satanic ritual abuse.
I did.
Did you ever prosecute
any of these satanic cases?
- No.
- For God's sake...
Mr. Skinner, we're
trying a man for murder...
not taking a trip
down memory lane.
I'm showing the court
that Agent Reyes...
is levelheaded and objective...
on strange
and extraordinary cases.
That her belief in aliens...
comes from firsthand
experience.
And she can offer
you hard proof...
that there is an
alien conspiracy!
I was called on last year
to protect Agent Scully...
who was pregnant
and whose life was in danger...
because of her pregnancy.
What does this have
to do with aliens?
I drove Agent Scully
to a secluded location...
in Georgia...
where it was believed
she could deliver safely.
But we soon discovered
we weren't alone.
I was attacked
and had to defend myself...
against an assailant,
who was shot...
at pointblank range.
Who should have died,
but didn't.
This assailant was then joined
by others like him...
who surrounded Agent Scully and me,
and witnessed her...
as she gave birth
to her son.
[Kallenbrunner]
Witnessed her?
What do you mean?
We were confused as well.
But we came to understand
that her son...
was a kind of miracle child.
Its birth was all important...
to these people:
These so-called Super Soldiers...
who I believe are humans
replaced by aliens.
Why would Scully's child...
be important to aliens,
Agent Reyes?
[Reyes]
We came to learn that Scully...
was one of a number
of random women...
who had miraculous childbirths.
And these women
all had been abducted...
as part of a government program...
to secretly manipulate
their biology...
operating offshore
on a navy ship...
using these women
as surrogates.
Surrogates?
For alien babies.
To create a slave race.
Yes.
A program...
conducted by the navy,
on a ship which is where?
The ship housing this program...
was exploded
on a Baltimore dock.
So, in other words,
we have no true evidence...
past your good word.
You claim Scully gave birth
to one of these alien babies.
How can you be sure of this,
Agent Reyes?
I saw her child
do things...
that could be explained
no other way.
I saw him display
amazing powers.
He'd move objects...
- with his mind.
- Really?
Do you think
we could arrange...
a demonstration for the court...
that we could
see that ourselves?
No.
The child was given up
for adoption...
to an anonymous family.
She gave up...
the miracle child?
The proof
of everything...
that she and Mulder claim
that they've risked their lives for...
over the last
nine years...
she just sent it off
to some strangers?
Yes, to protect him!
Thank you, Agent Reyes.
That's all.
You don't care about that child...
or what Scully
had to sacrifice.
You're only too happy she had to
give it up so there's no proof.
Agent Reyes.
You don't care...
what these people
have sacrificed...
over the last nine years...
what's been lost
to their cause.
You make a mockery of it,
gladdened it proves your point.
Agent Reyes, that's enough!
What is the point
of all of this?
To destroy a man
who seeks the truth...
or to destroy the truth
so no man can seek it?
Either way, you lose.
[Tires Screeching]
[Knock On Door]
Are you ready for this?
We may have found
Knowle Rohrer.
You found him?
His body.
What are you talking about?
There can't be a body:
He can't die.
Knowle Rohrer
is a Super Soldier.
Exactly.
But they're saying it's him...
the man Mulder killed.
Who's saying it's him?
I got some guy...
on the phone at Fort Marlene
who didn't know...
that he was supposed
to give me the runaround.
I got him to send
the victim's corpse to Quantico.
It's there now?
We got a car
out front.
[Gibson]
Agent Scully?
Agent Doggett can stay with him.
Oh, my God.
This is Knowle Rohrer?
That's what it says here.
Well, how could anyone tell
if it wasn't?
I need you to get me
Knowle Rohrer's medical records.
They'd have to come
from the military.
I don't know if I can.
You've got to, Monica,
whatever it takes.
I need those records
for Skinner.
I need them for Mulder.
Mr. Skinner.
Please call
your next witness.
[Door Opening]
Assistant Director...
I found it.
What?
What's going to get you off.
I want to move to dismiss again...
based on new evidence
I just received...
that there is no victim.
That the body of Knowle Rohrer...
is not Knowle Rohrer,
but that of...
a man who died
of a broken neck...
and whose body
was burned postmortem.
Motion denied.
- You can't deny it.
- You're out of order...
and in contempt of court,
Agent Scully.
You're in contempt...
of evidence proving
that Agent Mulder is innocent.
You have no authorization...
to examine the body,
Agent Scully.
Have her removed
from the courtroom.
If she's got evidence,
you've got to listen.
Order!
Remove
the defendant...
from the courtroom.
This trial
is adjourned.
Gentlemen...
we have a verdict.
If you'd rise.
Acting fairly...
and impartially, this panel
finds the defendant...
guilty
of first degree murder...
under aggravated
circumstances.
Is there anything
you'd like to say...
on your behalf, Mr. Mulder...
before we decide your sentence?
Yes.
I'd like to congratulate you...
on succeeding where so many
before you have failed.
A bullet between the eyes...
would have been preferable
to this charade.
But I've learned to pretend
over the past nine years...
to pretend
that my victories mattered...
only to realize
that no one was keeping score.
To realize that liars
do not fear the truth...
if there are enough liars.
That the devil
is just one man with a plan...
but evil, true evil,
is a collaboration of men...
which is what we
have here today.
If I am a
guilty man...
my crime is in daring to believe
that the truth will out...
and that no one lie
can live forever.
I believe it still.
Much as you try to bury it,
the truth is out there.
Greater than your lies,
the truth wants to be known.
You will know it.
It'll come to you,
as it's come to me...
faster than the speed of light.
You may believe yourselves
rid of your headache now...
and maybe you are...
but you've only done it by
cutting off your own heads.
[Phone Ringing]
Yeah.
I'll tell her.
[Hangs Up Phone]
Who was it?
Skinner.
Agent Doggett?
Death by lethal injection.
[Sobs]
Evening.
I D, please.
Master Sergeant Rohrer?
Go on ahead.
[Door Opening]
Get up.
Who's there?
I'm here with Skinner.
Get up.
Move it, Mulder.
What are you doing?
We're getting you out of here.
Come on.
Guard!
Where is he?
Seal the building.
Seal the base.
We have an escaped prisoner.
[Alarm Blaring]
You're never going
to make it this way.
Come on.
Mulder?
You've got to move out.
What's he doing?
What I should have done
from the start.
You want to go north
to Canada.
Get to an airport.
If you're not off
the continent in 24 hours...
you may never get out,
you understand?
None of you
will be safe now.
You let us worry
about that.
Good luck.
Mulder, Kersh told us
to head north.
You just got on a road
going south.
That's right.
Where are you going?
To see a man about the truth.
You can't hide me forever.
We can destroy
your files...
make it next to impossible
to find you.
You don't know
these people.
I'm going to protect you,
Gibson.
John...
What the hell is this?
What the hell is going on?
They can't do this.
Who authorized this?
I'm going to find out.
Skinner.
They've packed up
the X-Files.
I know.
It's out of control.
I'm trying to get
to the bottom of it.
I'm trying to get to Kersh.
[Knock On Door]
All I can think
is it's punishment...
for taking Mulder's side.
Unless they found out
that we helped him escape.
Then they know about the
deputy director's involvement, too.
I need to see
the deputy director.
And he needs to see you.
He knows.
Then we're all
in danger here.
No. He knows
about Mulder and Scully...
where they're going.
You mean the border?
No, that's not where they went...
and they know that.
They're going to find them
and kill them.
Where are they, Gibson?
Mulder and Scully...
where'd they go?
[Unzipping]
Hey, hot shot!
You might have the
common courtesy...
of doing your business
there downwind.
Oh, boy.
Why don't you just finish
draining the little lizard...
and then
we'll talk?
We're very worried
about you.
It's craziness,
man. Turn around.
Just hang a big U-ie
and never look back.
I can't.
Why risk perfect
happiness, Mulder?
Why risk your lives?
Because I need
to know the truth.
You already know the truth.
I need to know
if I can change it.
Change it?
For crying
out loud.
All you're going to do
is get yourself killed.
Mulder!
What are you doing?
I'll be right with you, Scully.
What are they?
Pueblos.
Anasazi Indian.
Abandoned 2,000 years ago.
Nobody knows why.
Yeah, Mulder, but what
are we doing here?
Hello.
My name is Fox Mulder.
Do you understand me?
Mulder,
what is this?
I was sent a message...
and a key to the government
facility at Mount Weather.
The Indians said
it was from a wise man...
who lived in the ruins.
A keeper of the truth.
[Helicopter Rotors Whirring]
Do you see anything at all?
What's the matter,
Agent Mulder?
You come to see the wise man...
but you look as if
you've seen a ghost.
You're no wise man.
You're a dead man.
Just like Krycek and X.
You see a dead man,
Agent Scully?
I hoped and prayed
you were dead...
you chain-smoking
son of a bitch.
You waste your time.
Ask Mulder.
He knows the futility
of hopes and prayers.
He knows the truth now.
You have told her
the truth...
haven't you, Fox?
I helped you find it.
You didn't help me.
You sent me
to that government facility...
knowing exactly what I'd find.
And now you refuse to speak it.
Not to Scully,
not to anyone.
You've even refused...
to testify what you learned...
even though it would have
saved your life.
You damned me
for my secrets...
but you're afraid
to speak the truth.
You call me afraid?
Look at you sitting here
alone in the dark like a fossil.
[Exhales]
It's the final refuge.
The last place to hide...
from those who are
insidiously taking power now.
Who?
The aliens.
They fear
this place...
its geology.
Magnetite.
Like that which brought down
the original UFO in Roswell.
Indian wise men realized this
over 2,000 years ago.
They hid here.
And watched...
their own culture die.
The original shadow government.
[Helicopter Approaching]
Agent Doggett!
Who the hell's that?
It leaves me to tell you...
what Mulder's
afraid to, Agent Scully.
Come on, let's go.
It's a scary story.
You want to come sit on my lap?
You don't scare me.
My story's scared every
president since Truman in '47.
You don't have
to hear this.
No, I want
to hear it, Mulder.
Ten centuries ago...
the Mayans were so afraid
that their calendar stopped...
on the exact date
that my story begins.
December 22, the year 2012.
The date
of the final alien invasion.
Mulder can confirm...
the date.
He saw it at Mount Weather...
where our own
secret government will be hiding...
when it all comes down.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, you smile...
feeling drunk with power.
The power to do nothing.
My power comes from telling you.
Seeing your powerlessness,
hearing it.
They wanted to kill you, Fox.
I protected you
all these years...
waiting
for this moment...
to see you broken.
Afraid.
Now you can die.
Run, Monica.
Get out of here.
No.
Knowle Rohrer,
that's far enough.
Shoot me, Agent Doggett...
if you think it'll make
a difference this time.
Agent Doggett!
Mulder, get
out of there!
They know
where you are!
Get out of here!
Get in the car.
No!
Go!
[Helicopters Approaching]
[Screaming]
What are you thinking?
Mulder?
I'm thinking...
I'm a guilty man.
I've failed
in every respect.
I deserve the harshest
punishment for my crimes.
You don't believe that.
[Sighs]
I believe that I sat in
a motel room like this...
with you when we first met...
and I tried to convince
you of the truth.
And in that respect,
I succeeded, but...
in every other way...
I've failed.
You don't
believe that, either.
Mm.
I've been chasing after monsters
with a butterfly net.
You heard the man...
the date's set.
I can't change that.
You wouldn't tell me.
Not because you were
afraid or broken...
but because you didn't
want to accept defeat.
Well, I was afraid of what
knowing would do to you.
I was afraid that it would
crush your spirit.
Why would I accept defeat?
Why would I accept it,
if you won't?
Mulder, you say
that you've failed...
but you only fail
if you give up.
And I know you...
you can't give up.
It's what I saw in you
when we first met.
It's what made me
follow you...
why I'd do it all over again.
And look what it's gotten you.
And what has it gotten you?
Not your sister.
Nothing that you've set out for.
But you won't give up,
even now.
You've always said
that you want to believe.
But believe in what, Mulder?
If this is the truth
that you've been looking for...
then what is left to believe in?
I want to believe that
the dead are not lost to us.
That they speak to us...
as part of something
greater than us...
greater than any alien force.
And if you and I
are powerless now...
I want to believe that
if we listen to what's speaking...
it can give us the power
to save ourselves.
Then we believe the same thing.
Maybe there's hope.
[Child]
I made this.!