[Police Radio. Indistinct]
[Radio Dispatcher]
This is Sector Station to Unit One.
Unit One, please report.
Unit One reporting.
No traffic or unusual activity,
Sector Station.
Tell her my ass is freezing off...
and I need someone out here...
to get the blood circulating.
Sector Station, Agent Daley here...
has a very special request.
The mike's off, man.
Don't scare me like that, man.
Aw, come on.
Keeps you awake, don't it?
Yeah.
Something moving.
Where?
Coming right through the trees.
Straight ahead.
See it?
Got it!
[Daley]
Unit One to Sector Station...
we are in pursuit...
in pursuit
of an illegal border crossing.
Rabbit's running for the hole.
End of the road, buddy.
Agent Scully.
He's expecting me.
Go right in, Agent Scully.
They're all waiting for you.
"They"?
Mm-hmm.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Have a seat, please, Agent Scully.
May I ask what this is about?
You can take a seat, please.
[Follmer] Deputy Director Kersh...
has called you here today...
to ask you a few questions,
Agent Scully.
All right, just a few...
routine questions.
[Kersh] Do you know what this is?
Should I?
It's a simple question, Agent Scully.
Do you know what this is?
I'm not sure.
But you've seen it before.
Am I under suspicion here?
Assistant Director Skinner...
led us to believe...
that you'd be able to identify
this piece of evidence.
And why is that?
Well, you once worked on the X-Files.
Well, if this is an X-File...
then why don't you ask somebody
who's working on the X-Files?
Because we're asking you.
Where did you get these?
They were found during
an illegal border crossing...
in North Dakota.
Canada to the U.S.
An illegal border crossing by whom?
As I said, we're asking...
the questions here today, Agent Scully.
What A.D. Follmer is saying is...
your cooperation is important...
to this investigation, Agent Scully.
I'd like to cooperate.
L-I'd be happy to cooperate.
I just wish that you would tell me...
who or what you are investigating.
[Elevator Bell Rings]
[Scully] Were you called about this?
Has A.D. Follmer been down here?
Brad Follmer?
Yeah. Going through the X-Files.
I doubt Agent Follmer...
even knows where we are...
down here, Agent Scully.
Why? What are you looking for?
These.
[Reyes]
What are they?
Rubbings.
Taken from the surface
structure of a craft.
A craft?
A spacecraft.
Agent Doggett...
if you can wrap your
brain around that.
[Sighs]
They were found by fishermen
off the western coast of Africa.
Two years ago, I traveled there
to study it and I took these.
What does this have
to do with Follmer?
This morning I was called...
into the Deputy Director's office...
and I was shown an exact
copy of that rubbing.
I was asked by senior staff
to identify it for them.
And where did they get them?
A guy running
the North Dakota border from Canada.
Or so they say.
What did you tell them about these?
Nothing.
And what aren't you telling us?
That they're powerful.
We're talking about pieces of paper
with marks on it.
They're not just marks, Agent Doggett.
It's writing.
Words.
Powerful words.
And if the FBI has them...
and they're keeping their
investigation of them a secret...
then they have a sense
of their power as well.
Special AgentJohn Doggett
out of Washington.
I'm looking for
the agent in charge out here.
Anybody point me to the ASIC?
Agent Doggett...
Assistant Director.
I don't recall asking...
for your help or assistance
on this case.
Well, the way it looks...
I'm the only agent outside
of D.C. You didn't ask.
What's the big attraction?
Last night, a man...
made an illegal border crossing
from Canada.
A chase ensued: Ended here.
You know anything about him?
About what he might
have been doing?
We're endeavoring to learn...
as much as we can, Agent Doggett.
Was he carrying anything interesting?
Like what, for example?
I don't know. Like, uh...
maybe something you'd find in an X-File.
If that's what you came looking for...
you came a long way for nothing.
Then what's with the cavalry?
Excuse me?
Lot of good shoes out here...
Iooking for what's got to be a dead man.
Guy was killed, right?
Man survives a fall like this, on fire?
Not very likely.
You got a body?
We will, Agent Doggett.
Like you say,
I got the cavalry out here.
You find that funny?
Dead man up and disappearing?
Happens every day, right?
At least it does on the X-Files.
Trust me, Mr. Doggett.
This has nothing to do with you.
Nothing to do with you or the X-Files.
Stick your nose in this case...
I promise you, you'll live to regret it.
[Coughs]
[Grunting]
Hi.
Thanks for coming.
I needed to talk to you
about this in person.
Well, what is it?
[Reyes] What I'm reading in your
field report on these rubbings, Dana...
there's something I didn't understand.
You say these were
taken off a spacecraft.
You determined they were words...
writings.
You didn't tell us
you knew what they said.
What little I read...
was through the help of an interpreter.
But you interpreted them as text...
from the Bible, from the Koran...
scripture from religions
around the world.
And science, too.
The periodic table of elements.
Yes.
And you wrote in your report...
they were millions of years old.
Based on radiometric readings...
from fossils that were encrusted...
on the surface of the ship.
Agent Scully, I know you've become...
more open-minded about these things...
but do you know what
it is you're saying here?
If it were true...
these symbols wouldn't
just be words...
they'd be the very word of God...
on the surface of an alien spacecraft.
It'd mean that everything
mankind believes in...
is in question.
And you believe this?
I didn't.
I mean, l-I refused...
to believe it.
But now I think...
I think there may be answers there.
Answers to what?
Answers about my son.
I know how that sounds.
I have no one else to say it to.
That I was meant to find these...
somehow.
These were meant for me.
But why would the FBI
keep that from you?
From us?
And what exactly do they want with them?
Those are questions I can't answer.
[Doggett]
You forget our extension?
Or you just can't be bothered?
Excuse me?
Returning calls.
Agent Reyes's, mine.
What the hell's that about?
Well, I've been tied up, Agent Doggett.
I just haven't had a chance.
That's not what your phone log says.
Your log says you've returned
everyone's calls but ours.
Agent Doggett, let me remind you...
who answers to whom here.
Oh, I think
you owe me an answer, sir...
and if you don't owe it to me,
you owe it to Agent Scully...
on this X-File case the FBI's got.
The one they're working so hard
to keep us from investigating.
You ready for my answer, Agent Doggett?
It's not an X-File case.
That's why you have 40 agents
combing the Canadian border...
for a dead man that ain't dead.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
I was out there.
Without any authorization!
I don't understand...
none of us do...
why you're keeping their secrets...
why you're keeping quiet.
Because I know things you don't, John.
And it's for your own good.
[Knock On Door]
Yeah. Who's there?
[Doggett]
It's me.
Open up, Monica.
I got it.
Got what?
What they've been keeping a secret.
What they won't tell Scully.
What they wouldn't tell us.
What am I looking at?
A file on a guy crossing...
the Canadian border last night.
Special Agent Robert Comer.
He's FBI.
I know this guy.
I worked a case with him
once in New Orleans.
Company man... straight as a ruler.
Well, according to his file...
last six months
he's been deep undercover.
Undercover doing what?
We got a pile of reading to do.
What's not blacked out.
Oh, and, uh...
picked these up in the bargain.
A.D. Skinner gave you these?
I sort of got it on loan.
We better call Agent Scully.
I already did.
Hey, need a hand there, bro?
How about I just help you out, huh?
Ohh!
[Engine Starts]
I'm on my way.
That was Agent Doggett again.
They're waiting.
Mom, I've got to go.
It's the middle of the night, Dana.
I just don't understand
what can't wait till tomorrow.
Mom, it's important.
I wouldn't go if it weren't.
Yes, I know, Dana.
You say it's about getting answers.
Answers about William, Mom.
I know you're worried about him...
that there are things about him
that you just can't explain...
but even if you were
to get those answers...
what would it change?
Mom, he's my child.
And you have to love him
and raise him...
in spite of everything.
Dana, God has given you a miracle.
A child that wasn't supposed to be.
Maybe it's not to question...
just to be taken as a matter of faith.
Mom, I can't take this on faith.
I need to know.
I need to know
if it's really God I have to thank.
Where did you get those?
I got 'em.
And the FBI's file...
on the man that was carrying them.
He's one of ours...
working deep undercover.
Infiltrating a religious group.
Some kind of wacked-out UFO cult.
A case they never told us about.
Where's this cult supposed to be?
North Dakota.
And at some point,
they up and disappear into Canada.
Agent goes right along with them.
FBI loses all contact with him.
What did they think
this guy was doing...
running across the U.S. Border
carrying these rubbings on him?
The FBI thinks he went over
to the dark side.
Became wacked-out himself.
And that's the secret...
they've been trying
to keep from everybody.
That's it? That's the big secret?
That and...
they can't seem to find him...
the best I can figure.
I was questioned this morning...
by the senior staff of the FBI.
Not about an FBI agent...
but about these rubbings.
There's got to be something more.
There has to be.
There may be, Agent Scully.
But I'm not sure even
the FBI is aware of it.
How could they be
without access to your files?
What are you talking about?
The set of rubbings...
the man smuggled over the border...
doesn't match the rubbings you took.
Wait a second.
How can that be?
It could only be...
that this wacked UFO cult...
found a second spacecraft.
[Gasps]
[Car Alarm Chirps]
Mom?
He wants to kill the baby!
[Blow Smacking]
[Baby Crying]
No!
No! Don't!
Please!
Don't!
[Grunting]
[Grunts]
[Loud Grunt]
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you if you touch my baby!
Dana!
[Baby Crying]
[Crying]
[Panting]
Oh, my God.
Mrs. Scully, are you okay?
What the hell happened here?
I need your help, okay?
Agent Reyes, I need you...
to take my mom and the baby.
Can you do that, Monica?
Of course.
[Scully]
Thank you.
[Man Moaning]
Who is that? Is somebody here?
You gonna tell me what this is...
who the hell this is, Dana?
That man... that FBI agent...
came here to kill my baby.
You gotta help this man.
No, not until he tells me why.
He's not gonna tell anybody anything...
unless you get him to a hospital.
This man is losing blood fast.
I am not gonna turn him over to the FBI!
I am not gonna let them cover
their tracks on this one!
- Why?
- [Groans Softly]
Why do you want to hurt my son?!
Agent Doggett, put down the phone!
He has to answer me!
[Man]
He ha-has...
What?
Say it!
[Gulps]
Your son...
Say it!!
...has to die.
Why?!
Who told you that?!
[Panting]
He's my son!
He's my son!!
I've got a medical emergency,
a man in critical condition.
This man have any
kind of a weapon?
A pillow.
Whatever brought him here...
I hope to God we figure it out.
[Sniffles]
[Metallic Clang]
What is it?
[Sighs]
This changes everything.
He can expose all this.
He's got proof he can show them.
What do you want to do?
[Sighs]
There's only one thing to do.
Agent Scully, Agent Doggett.
You can both have a seat.
If this is just going to be
another interrogation...
I prefer to stand.
[Sighs]
Agent Scully, a man was
shot in your apartment.
An FBI agent.
Trying to kill my son.
That is not in question here.
There'll be an investigation.
Another secret investigation
or one where I'm given...
advance warning that my
family's life is in danger?
[Follmer] It would help us
to help you if you could...
tell us anything this man
might have communicated to you.
I wouldn't tell him anything,
not until they explain...
why all the hush-hush over this case...
why the doublespeak...
the mincing words from Mr. Follmer...
'cause I want answers myself.
The man you shot had been undercover.
Which you've already found out through...
whatever unethical means.
His assignment was to
infiltrate a religious cult.
A cult led by a former military officer.
A very dangerous man by all accounts...
and who also believed
in very dangerous ideas...
about aliens.
And why wasn't I told?
Why not Agent Doggett?
Why not Agent Reyes?
Why wasn't this an X-File?
I asked them to put
somebody else on the case...
because I was afraid after all
that you'd been through...
it just might break you.
What are you talking about?
Agent Comer...
our undercover man...
was sent to infiltrate the cult...
based on a series of... threats.
What threats?
Threats to who? To me, to my child...
Threats...
on Agent Mulder's life.
That's what this is about?
Then why pull me in here
and show me those rubbings?
I don't understand.
Before losing all contact
with our undercover agent...
he sent us a communication.
A communication we've been
trying to confirm that, uh...
...that Mulder was already dead.
[Door Opens]
[Door Closes]
Here's your mommy.
Hi, honey.
Dana, what's wrong?
What's happened?
It's okay.
Just tell me what it is.
It's Mulder.
[Continuous Rattling Noise]
[Rattling Grows Louder]
What is it?
An artifact.
I got it from the man who
was trying to kill William.
Okay, but what the hell is it?
It's a piece of the spacecraft.
Where's Agent Scully?
She's still upstairs.
I want to talk to you
before you see her...
to explain what's happened.
You said it had something
to do with the kid.
A piece of metal these rubbings
were taken from.
A piece of that ship in Canada.
Oh, come on, Monica.
You're making an outrageous leap.
You're just guessing
there's any such thing.
It flew through the air
at the baby.
I saw it.
Just tell me the boy's okay.
I don't think you understand.
The boy has some connection
with this thing...
this piece of metal.
You saying this kid's an alien
or something?
You can believe or not...
but the man who tried to kill
Scully's baby believed it.
So must this cult he got involved with...
who are obviously more than willing...
to kill for their belief.
Where are we going?
I'll tell you on the way.
You drive.
What is it?
I'm right behind you guys.
Probably nothing.
[Slaps Door]
[Engine Starts]
[Tires Screeching]
Federal agent!
Stop the car!
[Gunshots]
Who are we meeting?
The only ones left we can trust.
[Crying]
Hey, little man.
It's okay.
Your baby's in good hands.
I need to know that you're
taking him to a safe place.
I need to know that you're...
that you're taking every precaution.
We understand.
Langly.
Now, there's a good chance...
that my phone lines have been tapped...
and if they're tapped,
they can trace you.
We thought about that.
Six cell phones...
their signals scrambled.
Use each one once
and then throw it away.
[Whispering]
Hey.
It's going to be okay.
Whatever you do, don't worry.
What's going on here?
I don't know.
What happened?
Is itJohn?
Agent Scully!
Scully!
My baby!
They're after my baby!
I have to get back!
[Tires Screeching]
What the hell is this?
What the hell is what?
[Crying]
[Child]
I made this!