Vodka rocks, please.
Hi, how are you?
Thirsty.
Uh, straight up,
and no ice this time.
I tell this guy...
about the ice,
and then he pours me...
a scotch rocks.
"About the ice"?
The water, actually,
in the ice.
I'm kind of an
expert on it.
Well, what's wrong with it?
No big secret.
It's been in the news.
A government additive.
Something they
call chloramine.
Yeah, they said
it's good for us.
It's like fluoride
or something.
Well, that's
what they say.
Look, um...
I didn't sit down
here to scare you.
On the contrary.
Would you like
to get some air?
A long way to go
for a drink, huh?
Do you like
living out here?
How much farther?
Just over the bridge.
[Alarm Blaring]
[Engine Revs]
What the hell you doing?
[Tires Screeching]
Let go!
You're going to kill us!
[Whoosh]
[Announcer]
Last season on The X-Files.
There was a rumored program
out of the Cold War.
Aplan to create
a Super Soldier.
[Doggett]
I didn't want to believe it.
Said Agent Scully's
a part of their program too.
Your baby was a miracle.
My baby is normal.
She may never make it
out of this building.
Get him off!
This is my baby!
Please don't let them
take it!
You got to push, Dana.
[Doggett]
This office...
is under
investigation...
for a late-night meeting...
between you
and an intelligence operative...
named Knowle Rohrer.
You investigate what I tell you.
And you put me
on the X-Files.
[Mulder] I think what we feared
were the possibilities.
The truth we both know.
[Baby Crying]
It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
[Alarm Clock Buzzing]
[Groans]
[Phone Ringing]
Hello?
[Man]
Monica, it's me.
Did I wake you?
Brad? Um, n-no.
No, I'm awake.
You're in town.
Yeah, l-I came in
on short notice.
Listen, if you're coming
to the Hoover Building...
can you stop by my office
on your way in?
Yeah. Sure.
I can do that.
Good. Looking forward to it.
[Whistling]
[Woman Over TV]
And now a story...
that may have long-term effects
here in Washington.
Metro Police are investigating
the bizarre death...
of a government employee
last night.
The body of 38-year-old
Carl Wormus...
a deputy administrator...
for the Environmental
Protection Agency...
was pulled from the Potomac
by rescue divers this morning.
It appears Wormus drove his car
through a barricade...
and off a drawbridge
into the river.
A police spokesperson says...
it appears
he was alone in the car...
Monica?
Hi.
What are you doing?
I was leaving you a note.
Your assistant was out,
and I didn't want to knock.
I was going to call you...
Hi, Brad.
Come on in.
[Door Closes]
What?
We're at work.
You used to ask me
to close the door at work...
back in New York.
Is that all you
called me here for...
Assistant Director?
I probably shouldn't tell you
how hot you look, either...
'cause you do.
How long has it been?
T-Two years?
Yeah.
We should catch up,
Brad, really.
I've got to
get downstairs.
I have got something for you.
Forgive me, but, uh...
it didn't take
a whole lot of digging...
to figure out why
you're here in D.C., Monica.
What are those?
Something you're going to see,
but I wanted to show you first.
They were taken from
the security cameras...
in the FBI parking garage.
One of them shows you arriving
in a cab meeting John Doggett.
Yeah, I'm working with him.
He called me up here
on a case.
I heard, believe me.
This whole thing about a chase
and a crash and a fire...
And now...
Doggett's internal investigation
of Deputy Director Kersh.
It's big news.
What's so important
to show me?
What's on the other tape?
[Elevator Bell Dings]
[Door Closes]
How's your investigation
going, John?
Have you turned up...
any incriminating evidence
on me yet?
It's only Monday
morning, sir.
It's nothing personal,
Deputy Director.
I hope you know that.
No, John. I think we've pretty
much always seen eye-to-eye.
[Door Opens]
I'm sure...
if you can't find anything
on me, John, nobody can.
Hi. How you doing?
That good.
I didn't ask to be put down
in the X-Files.
Deputy Director Kersh
put me down here.
I'm just doing my job.
What did he think?
That I'd be thankful?
That I'd do anything less?
It's not going to be easy, John.
Hell, no, it isn't.
We're going after
a Deputy Director.
One man removed
from the head of the FBI.
No, I mean,
it may be impossible.
What's this?
A security tape, two nights ago,
from the FBI garage.
You're not on it.
What are you talking about?
No.
This is the wrong damn tape.
I've been backwards
and forwards on it.
There's nothing there.
We were chased.
A.D. Skinner and I
were attacked and chased.
This man Knowle Rohrer drove
his car into the garage wall.
It blew up
in a ball of flames.
Not on this tape.
Where'd you get this?
From someone who
wanted to give me a heads up.
They can't just make this
all go away.
There's evidence down
in that parking garage.
There were victims.
I went down to that garage,
John.
Whatever happened, they've had
48 hours now to clean it up.
There were witnesses.
Witnesses who are going
to stand up to this tape?
[Door Shuts]
[Pounding]
Mulder!
Mulder, are you here?
[Man On Phone]
Naval Telecommunications Command.
Yeah, I need to make
a shore to ship call...
to the S.S.
Valor Victor...
Sir?
[Knocking]
What? What's the matter?
What's the matter?!
I've been trying to call you.
Yeah, but... the phone's off
the hook because of the baby.
Well, I got panicked
you weren't going to be here.
That you left, too.
Come in.
I went looking for Mulder.
I went
to his apartment.
I know.
Where did he go?
Dana...
where did he go?
He's gone.
He's just gone.
I don't know where Mulder is.
I don't know that I'd tell you
if I did.
[Door Opens]
I checked with movers,
airlines, car rental agencies.
No Mulder.
Somebody get to him?
That it?
Doesn't seem possible, does it?
Okay, so where does that
leave us?
It's just me and you.
Our word against Kersh
and the FBI.
You better sit down, John.
It's more complicated than that.
What's more complicated?
This investigation.
What about it?
I want to ask you to drop it.
No. Not from you. Not from you.
Not-Not after
what we've been through.
I mean, we barely escaped
with our lives.
That's something
worth thinking about.
I'm sorry, you're
not that reasonable.
What, did they get to you, too?
No one got to me, John.
They didn't have to.
That's the point.
You're afraid of them.
I'm not afraid of them.
Well, you're afraid
of something.
What?
The real tape showing up,
them calling you a killer...
for you having to shoot
Alex Krycek?
No, I'll stand by my actions,
Agent Doggett...
but I won't stand by yours...
if you're going to continue
to push and push...
until you get somebody killed.
You want to know
what I fear?
I fear for Mulder and Scully.
I fear for the life
of that child...
if you don't stop
pushing, John.
You don't think I fear
for those things, same as you?
If you did, you'd let it go.
So what I'm hearing is...
if I don't drop it,
I'm alone on this.
[Sighs]
John.
You're not.
[Door Shuts]
Hi.
I hope it wasn't
presumptuous of me.
I ordered you a martini.
No, the presumption's
all mine.
Anyway, I called
and asked you out, didn't I?
You, uh, actually
had me confused a little...
this morning in my office.
I had this crazy notion that,
uh, you were avoiding me.
Maybe I was trying
to avoid myself.
And those tapes you pulled out
of your desk drawer...
weren't exactly Pamela
and Tommy Lee, now, were they?
[Chuckles]
And I'd heard...
that, uh, that you
and John Doggett were tight.
You make it sound
like I go home from work...
with Post-Its on my ass.
It's nothing like that.
Then I don't get it.
Why risk your name
and your career...
getting caught up in this...
rabid investigation of his?
There isn't going to be
an investigation.
Not anymore.
I wouldn't have thought
Agent Doggett...
would be thrown off
so easy.
Not what I've heard about him.
Whatever you may think
about him, Brad...
he's not a fool, you know.
Now you're
pissed off at me.
No, I'm pissed off...
because this means
I'll be shipping back...
to the New Orleans Field Office.
What are you
talking about?
The way I heard it,
you're with the X-Files.
This investigation drops...
they're going to drop
the X-Files right along with it.
You know me...
where my interests lie.
This was my dream assignment.
Not to mention
how excited I was...
to be up here in D.C.
But you just got here.
Yeah, I know.
[Knocking]
I'm really sorry. I...
Dana, I need your help.
I don't how to find him.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Mulder leaving you here
all alone.
Just walking out on you?
Not telling you...
where and why?
It makes sense
in its own way.
That's all
I can tell you.
Then tell me why
you can't trust me.
Everything I did to
try to protect you...
when you thought your
baby was in danger...
what changed?
Why is it suddenly
I'm now the enemy?
Let it go, John.
Drop it. Please.
These people tried to kill me.
They tried to kill A.D. Skinner.
They would have killed Mulder,
too.
They're still out there, Dana.
Exactly right.
And they are unstoppable.
And they are inside the FBI.
You know something
you're not telling me.
Mulder knows something.
How long can you hide from it?
Knowle Rohrer...
this old military buddy of mine...
he told me your pregnancy
was a result...
of a government cloning
experiment to try and create...
what he called
a "Super Soldier."
I don't want to hear this.
Look, there is nothing
to any of this.
Knowle Rohrer... my buddy...
was one of the men that tried
to kill us in the FBI garage.
My baby... my son...
is fine.
I hope to God that's true.
I just don't want to pretend.
I'm going to ask you to leave.
I'm going to ask you to leave
and not come back here.
[Door Shuts]
[Woman]
Directory assistance, may I help you?
Let's try, uh, Maryland
or Virginia.
What listing, please?
The number for a Ryan Bracker.
B-R-A-C-K-E-R.
Yeah, hi, I was given this
number for a Roger Erickson...
formerly of
the U.S. Marine Corps.
Yeah, speaking.
Roger? Hey, it's John Doggett,
Bravo Company.
Hey, man, how you doing?
I'm good. It's good to hear you.
Listen, you remember
Knowle Rohrer?
Yeah, sure I remember him.
What's the story with him?
Didn't he get involved
in something...
when we got back stateside...
Special Ops?
I have no idea, man.
I never heard from Knowle
after we got back.
Hey, we should get together,
catch up.
Yeah, let's, um,
let's catch a beer sometime.
This is Shannon.
Leave a message and I'll
return it as soon as I can.
Yeah, hi, this is John Doggett.
I'm trying to reach
a Shannon McMahon...
who was with Bravo Company,
USMC.
If this is she,
could you please contact me...
through the FBI in Washington,
D.C., as soon as possible?
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Sleepy time, sweet William.
I'll see you
in a couple hours.
[Mobile Squeaking]
[Squeaking Continues]
[Sighs]
[Heavy Sigh]
[Footsteps]
Hello?
[Sighs]
[Baby Crying]
[Mobile Squeaking]
[Crying Continues]
[Crying Stops]
[Crying]
[Mobile Squeaking]
[Phone Rings]
Monica Reyes.
Uh, yeah, it's, uh...
it's Scully.
Dana?
What's wrong,
are you all right?
Is Agent Doggett there?
Yeah, he's right
here with me.
Dana?
Is something wrong?
Yeah... yeah, something.
Um... I think
I might have been wrong...
telling you to drop
your investigation.
No, I didn't drop it.
As a matter of fact,
we found something.
I'm not sure how it fits,
but we're working on it.
What is it?
A body.
Thanks for comin'.
The deceased's name...
is Carl Wormus...
Deputy Administrator...
for the Environmental
Protection Agency.
Drove through a barricade and
off a bridge two nights ago.
And?
And somebody at the FBI
thought it was important enough...
to stick his obituary
under our noses.
Who?
[Reyes]
We don't know.
Well, his blood alcohol level
was upwards of.15.
He was drunk,
he... crashed and drowned.
There's got to be
something more.
[Cell Phone Rings]
John Doggett.
What the hell are you doing?
Excuse me?
Do you know how many people...
are just waiting
to see you screw up?
To see you make
a mistake like this?
I didn't know
I made a mistake.
This EPA guy that you checked
out of the county morgue...
in Maryland...
without any jurisdiction...
Oh, come on.
All your friends, John.
All your former buddies
at the FBI.
What are you talking about?
They're not your pals anymore.
Not since this
investigation of yours.
Since you've launched an attack
on one of your own.
Just watch your back, John.
[Slams Receiver Down]
Definitive answer
how this guy died.
What would that take?
A careful autopsy.
How fast can you do it?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'd understand if you don't
want to do this, Dana...
but you're the only
person we can trust.
[Doorbell Rings]
Collecting for the needy
and unemployed.
Open the door.
Thanks for doing this, guys.
Yeah, like we've got
anything better...
to be doing these days.
Just to let you know...
we may need to hit
you up for some coin.
Why? What happened to you guys?
Don't ask.
We were able to hack...
into the Department
of Interior's mainframe...
and get the EPA
files you wanted...
on this man Carl Wormus.
And?
Hey.
What are we,
mind readers?
That's all
you asked us to do.
What exactly was it...
you were looking for,
if we may ask?
I don't know, I was hoping
you'd find something.
Well, if he had any secrets,
he took them to his grave.
Nothing hinky in his files...
except some kind of rabid
obsession with water.
With water?
Water. Asphyxiation induced by
the inhalation of water.
There are contusions on
the forehead and on the chest...
but the impact isn't
what killed him.
This man drowned.
You're looking at me...
like you hope
that there's something more...
but there isn't.
I'm sorry, that's not it.
I'm just impressed
that you can do this.
This is what I do, Agent Reyes.
But you're here doing it now.
Something did happen, didn't it?
I know what you're afraid of.
That there's something wrong
with your baby.
We can let our fears
get the better of us.
We can, uh...
imagine things, make connections
with things that aren't there.
Like with this man.
If you ever feel the need to
talk to someone, Dana, I'm here.
I'd never betray
a confidence.
There is something.
What?
Right here on the ankle.
Are those...
fingerprints?
Yeah, that's what
they look like.
From someone holding him down?
I don't know how or who.
[Follmer] I don't know if you're
aware of where Agent Scully is.
She's at Quantico.
Called in byJohn Doggett
to autopsy a body...
he's got no authority to touch.
If I may be blunt, sir...
Doggett's put his tit
in the wringer.
Maybe. So what?
A lot of us think...
that he's lost all judgment.
And one man's actions should not
affect the entire FBI.
We feel he should be called out
for this.
Punished.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Assistant Director.
It's a difficult
situation to be in.
I appreciate you doing this.
It was the right thing to do.
Let me know how it goes.
Me?
Oh, no, l-I can't, sir.
There-There's a conflict.
L-I can't do this myself.
I can't very well do it.
How would it look?
I'm under investigation
by Agent Doggett.
You have no personal ax
to grind.
[Doorbell Rings]
Hello, can I help you?
Hi, I'm looking
for Dana Scully.
I'm sorry.
She's not here right now.
Can I tell her who's calling?
We work together.
Do you know where
I can find her?
No. Um... would you like
to leave a message?
[Doorknob Squeaking]
I'll leave her
a note...
if you wouldn't mind
opening the door.
Why don't you just
leave your name...
and I'll have Dana call you.
[Sighs]
You need to get this body
into refrigeration...
if you're going to preserve
him as evidence.
Whatever he's evidence of.
Whatever it is, I can't reach
John to even tell him about it.
Monica, I don't
know what to say...
but good luck.
I've got to go.
I've got
to get home.
Third floor,
they have a cooler...
for the teaching
cadavers.
You might temporarily
put him up there.
Behind us.
Just keep walking.
Who is she?
I've never seen her
before this morning.
Now I've seen
her twice.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Excuse us.
Where's Agent Doggett?
What are you
doing, Brad?
What am I doing?
I'm doing my best
to cover your ass.
What are you
talking about?
This, this.
I'm talking
about these.
Let go of me.
What's going on here?
Okay, where'd
he go?
Who?
Where'd who go?
Where did Doggett
take the body?
You're not making
any sense, Brad.
Agent Doggett didn't take
any body anywhere.
What, you're
looking at me...
like you don't believe me.
Ask Agent Scully.
I'm going to go now.
I've got a child at home.
Body or no body, you were
here doing an autopsy.
Doggett was here...
without authorization.
Without authorization?
He's out of control,
you know, Monica.
Forget the X-Files.
He'll take you
down with him.
This was you, wasn't it?
You floated
that obituary to me...
to set Agent Doggett up.
Using me?
What obituary?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You came to me
for help, remember?
I'm only trying to help
you help yourself.
I know exactly what
you're doing, Brad.
Don't forget to piss on all
the corners before you leave.
I didn't float
any obituary.
What is she
talking about?
[Doorbell Ringing]
Son of a...
Yeah?
Oh. Hello.
Considering the recent violence
attempted on Agent Doggett...
you might want to know
who's at the door...
before you
actually open it.
Next time I'll get a chair.
Agent Doggett's gone.
What do you mean gone?
He and
Assistant Director Skinner...
split for Maryland together.
Show her what we found...
before she makes
any nasty remarks.
It took some
real hacking...
but Carl Wormus,
the man from...
the Environmental
Protection Agency...
who drowned in his car?
He'd been receiving
encrypted e-mail data...
from a water reclamation plant
in Maryland.
From a worker there
named Roland McFarland.
Encrypted data on what?
Don't know.
But whatever it is,
may have gotten...
both these
men killed.
There are
no nameplates.
Yeah, I see that.
This is madness.
Even if you're right...
and this guy connects
to your investigation...
we don't know we're in
the right area.
This has got to be
McFarland's area.
This might be his desk.
Let's just grab
the computer hard drive...
and get out of here.
We're not sure
if it's his.
Somebody's going to come
walking through...
one of these doors any minute
and it's not going to matter.
Just keep an eye out.
What's chloramine?
What?
Why are you asking
me about chloramine?
Because
this is McFarland's desk...
and he's got tons of files
on chloramine in it.
I'm betting it figures
into all this somehow.
Agent Doggett.
Grab the files and go.
Shh.
[Yells]
[Follmer]
Assistant Director!
Looks like you and I
are chasing the same man.
Agent Doggett?
[Child]
I made this.!