[Doggett]
Looking right at us.
Fifty bucks says that's Lukesh.
A hundred says
he knows we're here.
It's him.
Let's take him.
Let him get
to the mailbox.
[Doggett]
It's Lukesh.
I don't need him opening
the mailbox to prove it.
Patience, Agent Doggett.
We've got an agent alone
with a psycho...
who likes cutting out
women's tongues...
a guy known
for his vanishing act.
We've got the block surrounded.
He isn't vanishing anywhere.
And your partner volunteered.
Now...
open 4-D.
Agent Reyes...
[Over Radio]
Stand by.
What the hell is this?
Monica, don't.
[Follmer]
Agent Reyes...
keep your distance.
Don't let him see
you following.
Monica, where are you?
[Reyes]
Back stairwell.
I lost sight of him.
I think he might be here.
[Monica Screams]
Oh, no. Oh, no!
[Groans]
Agent down!
Back stairwell.!
Get EMS here now.!
Doggett, he's got her gun!
Erwin Lukesh!
Federal Agent!
Turn around,
you son of a bitch.
[Siren Wailing]
Back here!
[Garbled Radio Transmission]
[Gunshot]
Hey.
So this is how
the uptown crowd lives, huh?
This is it. Moving on up.
So, is there anything really
heavy that I can move for you?
A dresser, a fridge?
No, but thank you, John.
You've just missed the movers.
You don't say.
[Chuckles]
I brought you
a housewarming gift.
[Paper Bag Crinkling]
[Sniffing]
Hot dogs?
Polish sausage!
It's the best in the city.
There's a little stand
a couple of blocks...
over on M Street.
You'll be able to walk to it.
Wow.
Try one.
Mmm! Like I'm back in Gdansk.
Let me get some plates.
Plates?
For crying out loud.
Who eats Polish
sausage with plates?
[Phone Ringing]
[Beep]
Hello.
Agent Reyes,
it's A.D. Skinner.
Yes, sir.
There's no easy way
to say this.
I'm sorry to do it
over the phone.
What is it?
It's Doggett...
he's been found...
in an alley off Dillon Park.
He's been shot.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
[Skinner] They're taking him
to Washington Memorial.
Agent?
Sir, what you're saying is...
Agent Reyes?
Agent Reyes.!
[Elevator Bell Rings]
Excuse me.
[Follmer]
Monica.
Brad?
Skinner called you too?
He's staying
at the crime scene.
I'm sorry.
I've been put in charge
of the investigation.
I promise you...
it's my top priority.
I will find the
person who did this.
I just need to find out...
why your partner was in
that alley this morning.
He wasn't!
He was with me,
at my apartment.
He was with me
when Skinner called me.
I'm not sure I'm following.
Monica, I'm so sorry.
Agent Doggett is just
coming out of surgery.
They're moving him to the ICU.
How's it look?
If he pulls through this...
it's likely that he'll
be paralyzed for life.
I haven't understood
one single word I've heard...
since I got here.
Whoever you're talking about,
it's notJohn Doggett.
[Instruments Beeping, Hissing]
You found the bullet.
Nine-millimeter slug.
Found it in the alley
lodged in a wall.
Most likely
from a SIG Sauer P226 or 228.
Possibly FBl-issue.
I know what you're thinking...
but this didn't come
from Doggett's weapon.
Ballistics don't match,
and his gun was never fired.
Assistant Director?
I'd appreciate case updates
in a timely fashion.
For instance, this bullet...
How long have you had it?
An hour?
Two?
Thereabouts.
It's just that we need to keep
the lines of communication open.
That's all I'm asking, okay?
I want this slug run through...
our database
of FBl-issue pistols.
Like I told you...
the round didn't come
from Doggett's weapon.
You're not saying another agent
could have done this?
Just run it, please.
I just...
I don't understand how
any of this is possible.
He was with me, Dana,
in my apartment.
How can this be?
I saw something once.
It's only been
the last of couple years...
that I've fully come
to terms with it.
In '94, my father passed away.
And that night, I think...
that very moment that it
happened, he came to me.
I like to believe that
he came to say good-bye.
A visitation.
I think that's wonderful...
a blessing...
but that's not
what happened to me.
[Cell Phone Rings]
Scully.
It's me.
Is Reyes with you?
Yes, she's here.
We're both still at the hospital.
I need you to bring her
to the Sixth District Police Station.
I'm on my way there myself.
What's this about?
I'll tell you
when you get there.
What's going on?
Agent Reyes, would you mind
stepping inside, please?
Hi, Monica. Have a seat.
I wanted you and I...
to have a chance to talk alone...
to clear a few things up...
a few details of your story.
My "story"?
[Follmer]
Well, your assertion...
that you were with Agent Doggett
when he was shot.
What is this?
- Just wait.
- Is that a true statement?
Yes.
I mean... no, I wasn't
with Agent Doggett...
when he was shot,
but I was with him...
at the time A.D. Skinner called
to tell me he'd been shot.
Look, Monica...
you know how I feel...
you know I'm on your side...
but give me something here.
Give me some
mitigating reason...
for what you're
trying to cover up.
I'm going to put a stop to this.
[Reyes]
What are you saying to me, Brad?
Why are you saying these things?
[Sighs]
We've checked and rechecked
the ballistics tests.
The bullet that hit Doggett
came from your gun.
And furthermore...
we have an eyewitness...
one who's placed
you at the scene.
Is that why I'm here...
in this room,
so you can make an I D?
Agent Reyes,
I'm going to have to ask you...
for your FBI identification
and your gun.
Who's there?
Who's back there?
We appreciate
your cooperation, sir.
Anything I can do to help.
[Respirator Hissing]
[Door Opens]
Smart touch... posting a guard...
to make sure
I don't finish the job.
Do you really believe
I did this?
No. But it doesn't matter
what I believe.
You may still be arrested.
So what are they waiting for?
Follmer's case has a couple
of potential holes.
For starters,
there's the fact...
that when I called you...
you were at home...
14 miles from the crime scene.
Plus, there's the condition
of your gun.
It hadn't been fired.
However, the bullet...
does match your
gun... perfectly.
It doesn't make any sense.
None of it.
What about the eyewitness?
What can you tell me about him?
You know we can't discuss that.
Look.
Oh, my God. John?
Is he conscious?
I don't know.
It could just be a muscle spasm.
It's not uncommon
with this type of spinal injury.
No, it's not a spasm.
What is it?
It's Morse code.
What did he say?
"Lukesh."
What? What does that mean?
[Television Playing
In Background]
[Old Woman]
Who's there?
Is somebody there?
Erwin, is that you?
Who else would it be, Mama?
I thought maybe robbers.
I thought something terrible...
had happened to you.
You were gone so long.
I was gone two hours
and six minutes.
I'm back at noon...
just like I told you.
I was so scared.
Could you bring me
a glass of Clamato...
with two squirts of Texas Pete...
and two ice cubes?
Oh, God, I was all alone...
and I heard the knob rattle.
Somebody was rattling the knob.
It was the robbers.
I just know it was.
I don't know how
I got through it.
I was so scared.
[Announcer On TV]
Like sands through the hourglass...
so are the Days of Our Lives.
My show is on.
Could you make me
my hot sandwich...
so that I could
eat my sandwich...
while I watch my show?
What kind of sandwich is it?
Potted meat.
I don't think I like that.
Have I had it before?
Many times.
You love it.
I should be at the hospital.
Scully will call
if he regains consciousness.
Either way, I should be there.
Agent, you're still
under investigation.
Not to mention I will be too...
if it's ever found out
that I showed you this.
"Erwin Timothy Lukesh."
Have you ever seen him before?
"1995: Patient at the
State Psychiatric Hospital...
"at Gaithersburg.
"Diagnosed with
a delusional disorder...
"anger subtype,
which presented itself...
shortly after the suicide death
of his father."
After four months...
he was deemed fit for release.
He lives with his invalid mother...
in an apartment
adjacent to the crime scene.
What's the story he's telling?
That he heard a bang...
went downstairs to investigate...
and then he saw you exit the alley.
This is the one person
we know was in the vicinity...
at the time of the shooting.
Why would Doggett say his name?
You think Lukesh shot Doggett?
What if Doggett
was investigating Lukesh?
What if Lukesh is somehow
behind all this?
[Phone Rings]
- Skinner.
- It's Follmer.
Do you recall our discussion where
I asked you to keep me up to date?
I do.
Really?
And yet it's like
we never even had it.
I'm at Washington Memorial.
I'm assuming you're
with our prime suspect.
Bring her.
She's going to talk
to Agent Doggett.
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Oh, the gang's all here.
How is he?
Fully conscious.
We set up a communication device...
designed for spinal injury victims.
Speaking with him
should be much easier.
Just so we're clear...
you'll ask only
the questions I want asked.
You're not to try to shade
his testimony in any way.
If you're so concerned...
why let Reyes talk to him
in the first place?
Because he says he won't
talk to anyone but you.
He didn't mention you two.
John.
Hey, there.
That's right.
You're alive.
As if there were ever any doubt.
Why am I alive?
Is that what you're asking?
I'm fine, John.
Why wouldn't I be?
Have him say who shot him.
My throat wasn't cut, John.
What do you mean?
Wiggle your finger
if you feel anything.
Any sensation at all?
Pain?
Tingling?
Okay.
That's enough for today.
We'll see if you can
do any better tomorrow.
You kiss your mother
with that mouth?
It's coming along.
It's nowhere, basically.
There's so much that's
impossible to reconcile.
You say I was
on a stakeout with you.
I say you were at my apartment
bringing me...
John... do you know
a little stand on M Street...
supposed to be really good hot dogs?
John, what if we were both right?
What if you were at my apartment...
and I was on a stakeout with you...
at the exact same time?
What would it take
for that to be true?
[Tapping]
Except maybe we do.
Maybe all of us do.
You've heard of the idea
of a parallel universe...
one that's identical,
or nearly identical...
to our own...
one in which we
all have a double.
It's theoretical
physics, but...
what if it's real?
You said yourself,
Erwin Lukesh was known...
for his impossible escapes.
You said that in the alley...
you looked away
only for an instant...
and he was gone.
Back here!
And then somehow
he was behind you...
and he shot you.
With my gun...
my gun that never left...
my possession
that entire afternoon.
What if Lukesh can pass freely...
from one parallel world
to the other?
Like... like he's opening a door.
And what if somehow you
followed him through that door...
without even knowing it?
Maybe when you followed
Lukesh into this world, my...
my Doggett got forced out.
My Doggett would have
called that crazy too...
but give me another
theory that fits.
I'm kind of confused
as to why I'm back.
I already told you
everything I know.
We just had a few little,
uh... inconsistencies...
that we needed to clear up.
Sure.
Dot the i's, cross the t's.
Yeah, here's an odd one
for starters.
We have an eyewitness that says
you shot AgentJohn Doggett.
Well, that's surprising.
I can't imagine
who would have said that.
Agent Doggett.
Yeah, he's regained consciousness.
He's very chatty.
Among other things,
he says that...
you're a murderer.
That you enjoy killing women
with a straight razor.
And cutting out their tongues.
Yeah. Wow.
[Chuckles]
What a corker.
Mr. Lukesh...
would you consent to a GSR test?
GSR? What is that?
It can reveal
whether or not someone...
recently fired a gun.
You wouldn't mind
indulging us, would you?
I don't know.
I think I'd have to talk
to my lawyer about that.
Look.
My heart goes out
to your Agent Doggett...
but he's confused.
It's clear to me...
that your female agent,
Ms. Reyes, is responsible...
for this terrible tragedy.
Is there someone who can
corroborate your story?
No.
What about your mother?
You live with your mother, right?
She was sleeping.
She wouldn't have heard anything.
Huh.
Well, still, maybe
she can tell us something.
Would she be willing to come
down here and talk to us?
My mother's in poor health.
She gets confused easily.
Oh, we can go to her.
I won't have you harassing her
just because you're afraid...
to admit that
one of your people did this.
Now, if you're going
to arrest me...
do it.
Otherwise, I'm going home.
Say hi to Mama.
Agent Reyes, right?
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
How do you do it?
You know what I'm
talking about, don't you?
There's this world...
and there's the world where you
live out your sick fantasies.
When did it start?
Was it after your
breakdown in '95?
All that anger.
It's buttoned up so tight...
it had nowhere else to go.
It had to get released.
Not here...
but in a world
just like this one.
God, I enjoyed you.
You bled just like a pig.
Reyes?
You all right?
Mama, I'm home.
Mama, you want your Clamato?
Mama?
Have you been out of bed?
You don't tell me things, Erwin.
I tell you things.
You sneak out
of the house all night.
You leave me alone all by myself...
and then you think I don't know.
Well, I know.
I know... every time.
What is it that you do, Erwin...
that you don't tell me?
I don't.
I don't do that.
I don't know what you mean.
Why is that in my house?
I opened the drawer,
and it gave me a heart attack.
I don't know how
I even picked it up...
without it going off
and killing me.
I was so scared.
[Crying]
Mama.
I don't know how it got there.
If you won't tell me...
you can tell the FBI,
that's it.
Yes, the FBI
has left three messages.
They want to talk to me.
Can you imagine, Erwin?
Why would the FBI
want to talk to me?
[Tape Rewinding]
What are you doing?
Aren't you even gonna listen?
Are you gonna talk to them?
Well, of course I am.
It's the FBI.
Mama.
Oh, don't turn on
the waterworks, mister.
That's not going to wash.
I'm the one who's being lied to.
Erwin...
what are you doing?
Erwin.
What are you doing?
Erwin.!
[Screaming]
Did not.
Anyway, that's what you get
for hiring cheap help.
Thinking about what?
How?
Bad joke.
My theory is sound?
You don't believe
a word of it, John.
Never in a million years
would you believe.
This has nothing to do
with my theory.
I would do anything for you.
Anything but that.
[Cell Phone Rings]
Reyes.
It's Skinner.
Are you okay?
Yes, sir, I'm fine.
I can't say the same
for Miriam Lukesh.
What happened?
She's dead.
It's the exact M.O.
Doggett described.
Most likely a straight
razor was used.
Lukesh killed his mother.
Do you have any idea
where he is?
None.
But if everything
I've been hearing is true...
he's not going to be
easy to find.
I think he'll find us.
[Soft Clattering]
[Scully]
Are you all right, Agent Reyes?
Just a little jumpy, I guess.
It's understandable.
I don't think
you're the only one.
Try and take it easy, Monica.
We got you covered
coming and going.
Anything happening out front?
No, you moved into
a quiet neighborhood.
It's dead out there.
I think I'll check around
once more.
[Muffled Scream]
You want to scream
right now, don't you?
- Lukesh.
- Because of your friends outside...
parked in a van... might as well
say "FBl" in big huge letters.
Do it.
Try and scream out to them.
They can't hear you.
Where'd she go?
Monica, do you copy?
[Skinner]
Reyes?
Agent Reyes, do you read me?
He's in there.
He's gotta be.
- It's not possible.
- Well, what if it is?
You want to stick around
and find out?
You ruined everything, you bitch.
You made me.
You made me do it.
- Lukesh, don't...
- Shut up. Shut up.
But you know what?
This time I get
to bleed you slow.
You all right?
Monica, you all right?
It's okay. It's okay.
It's over.
[Beeps]
[Respirator Deflates, Stops]
[Dial Tone]
Monica, forget about
the plates, will ya?
What's wrong?
Monica, what's wrong?
I'm good.
[Child]
I made this.!