[Beeping]
[Buzzing]
I have an urgent communication
to deliver to Dr. Nordlinger.
I can deliver the communication.
I was asked
to confirm and verify...
he received the communiqué
and report back...
That's not
proper procedure.
Report back
Dr. Nordlinger's acknowledgment...
of the communiqué.
What's going on here?
There's some confusion...
as to the proper procedure...
Dr. Nordlinger.
I have a communication for you.
Communication acknowledged
and confirmed, Captain.
We're returning to base.
Officer Bamford.
Captain.
Prepare to transmit
to operations commander.
Transmit what, sir?
Sir...
what is the communication?
We're coming in.
Doggett?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Have a seat, Agent Reyes.
Agent Reyes...
I thought we might have
a little chat.
Mr. Skinner here...
has been trying to
help me put together...
the pieces of your
X-Files investigation.
Can we cut the crap, Brad?
I don't know.
Can we?
There's a lot of crap
to cut through.
Agent Reyes...
you probably want to zip it
and try to cooperate.
Like it or not...
I'm now charged
with the task of reining you in.
- Reining us in?
- Uh-huh.
For what?
Unauthorized autopsies:
Breaking and entering...
into a state water facility:
Willful misuse of your positions.
I really don't want
to go into any of this...
without my partner here.
Your partner.
Your so-called partner...
who's running this circus,
is right now nowhere to be found.
What are you doing, Brad?
Giving you and Mr. Skinner
the opportunity to put a nice spin...
on this mess
that Doggett's making.
Agent Reyes...
if you're not going to zip it,
at least recognize...
that he's the only one
who can help you.
We were given a tip...
we believe leads
to a larger conspiracy.
Conspiracy.
Involving the F.B.I.
John Doggett and I...
are running a legitimate
investigation into the F.B.I.
- Neither one of us feels...
- Agent Reyes...
I'm trying to help you
keep your job...
but that's not
going to happen...
if you insist
on chasing shadows...
chasing conspiracies.
How do you know
there isn't one?
You're taking on...
the entire F.B.I. Here, Monica.
This witch hunt...
isn't going
to expose anything...
but you.
That is...
unless you distance yourself
from John Doggett.
What are you doing?
I'm distancing myself, Brad,
from you.
From your political games.
You just want
to getJohn Doggett.
You're making
a big mistake here.
Yeah, I seem to make one
every time I walk in your door.
[Coughing]
[Gasps]
Lie back, John. It's okay.
What the hell is this?
It's Shannon.
Shannon McMahon.
We were together
in Bravo Company, U.S.M.C.
You were trying to contact me.
What the hell
are you doing here now?
[Coughing]
Your lungs were full of water.
You pulled me under.
I did what I had to.
You held me down. I remember.
They would have caught you.
They might have figured it out.
What you've started
to figure out.
What are you?
You know what I am.
I'm the product of 50 years...
of military science.
The program your old friend
Knowle Rohrer told you about.
I'm a bioengineered combat unit.
I have no weaknesses.
I don't sleep.
I can breathe underwater.
That's how I saved your life, John.
How do you know what I know,
what Knowle Rohrer told me?
Knowle Rohrer and I were drafted...
right out of Bravo Company together.
We were... Adam and Eve.
The program's first.
There are many more now.
Knowle Rohrer is dead.
You can't kill us.
We can't be killed.
Knowle Rohrer
and I are alike...
in almost every way.
The difference is,
I hate what I am.
Why are you here
telling me this?
The program's expanding in ways
no one ever dreamed of.
I need your help
to stop it, John.
You need my help?
What can I do?
Expose the deaths
of those two men I killed...
what they were doing.
What were they doing?
Preparing the water supply.
Preparing it for what?
What are you doing, Captain?
Where are you going?
We're under strict orders
not to leave ship.
Look at us.
They've got us tied up
at a civilian dock in Baltimore.
Why?
I think they may be on to us.
You're only drawing suspicion...
if they're not.
You can't leave this ship.
We can't risk waiting.
We can't risk
not making contact now.
I'll be back.
[Knocking]
Hi. I'm sorry about the hour.
I just put him down.
I couldn't talk on the phone.
Well, what is it?
I was told...
to leave this alone.
You and Mulder asked me
to leave it be...
to let Mulder disappear.
We were concerned
for the safety of the baby...
and for Mulder.
Why am I risking that now?
Why are you?
Why are you getting mixed up
with Doggett's investigation?
Something happened...
with my baby.
What?
I can't explain it.
It's, uh...
it's unexplainable.
It's, um...
it's not normal.
Whatever it is...
I think you've made
a terrible mistake.
Letting Doggett
pull you into this.
I mean, he's hell-bent.
And Agent Reyes
is following right in his tracks.
I need answers.
I need to know.
I can't just sit around...
wondering.
If you can't tell me,
then get to Mulder.
- Tell him what happened.
- No.
Mulder can't know.
He can't be
brought back into this.
He can't be brought back
to the F.B.I.
It's just too dangerous
for him right now.
It's too dangerous for everyone.
[Line Ringing]
[Woman] The E.P.A. Employee
you're trying to reach...
Carl Wormus, is not available.
If you want to leave
a voice mail...
stay on the line.
Evening, Captain.
Something's wrong.
Very wrong.
Sir?
What is this?
Where's Bamford?
Chief Petty Officer Bamford
has been relieved of his post, sir.
I'm your new second-in-command.
[Phone Rings]
Hello.
Dana? I'm sorry if I woke you.
It's Monica Reyes.
Dana...
there's something I think
you really need to be aware of.
Something you need to hear.
Something I'm not sure I believe.
I'm listening.
It's not me
you need to hear it from.
Agent Scully...
we may have some answers for you...
about your baby.
[Fussing]
[Knocking At Door]
Dana, this is Shannon McMahon.
Hi.
Let's start with the water.
Well, you're a scientist.
You'll appreciate
the science involved.
A new additive is being put
in the water supply.
It's called chloramine.
It's not news.
Well, let me say
it's been reported...
but no one's
asking questions yet.
And what should
they be asking?
If you want
to deliver something...
to everyone's home
in America...
what better way...
than through what's most
taken for granted... water.
Look, I've had my fair share...
of outrageous
conspiracy theories, okay?
So cut the mystery crap
and get to the science.
Chloramine is just...
a substitute for chlorine.
You can drink it,
and it's harmless.
Unless someone
were to quietly go...
and change
its molecular makeup.
Who and how?
I think you'd be more interested
in why.
All right, then, why?
To prime a population...
to breed a generation
of Super Soldiers.
By adding something
to our water?
Something which promotes
the mutation of offspring...
in fertilization, in pregnancy.
What you're saying is absurd.
Is it?
No more absurd than I am.
I am a first-generation prototype.
Now they're seven stages
advanced in the science...
which created me...
to the point where now
they have successfully given birth...
to a Super Soldier
from a mutated egg.
How can we trust any of this?
Or you?
What you say you are?
We all have
a standard mutation.
What are you looking at?
Ship's logs.
Those logs are classified.
As second-in-command...
I'm supposed
to know the ship, sir...
in case something
should happen to you.
What is the greater mission
of this ship...
if I may ask, sir?
I don't ask.
We don't ask.
[Klaxon Blaring]
What's going on?
[Sailor]
That's Bamford.
Officer Bamford.
It doesn't make any sense.
Yeah. Only it doesn't hold up...
to any argument, either, does it?
She drowned that man
from the E.P.A.
She's drowned two men.
She says they're part
of the program.
Two guys working to spike
the Maryland state water supply.
So she killed them
as a way of contacting you?
You believe that?
You saw that thing
on her neck.
You said you saw it before.
I think we're on
to something here, Monica.
It's freaky, it's mind-blowing...
but you got to admit that.
I'm not doubting
what she is...
only what she says
she's doing.
What? What'd you find?
Nothing.
Nothing more than
a small deformity of the spine.
Physically, she seems
absolutely normal.
As normal as you or I.
I don't believe this.
What don't you believe,
Agent Doggett?
I just examined her.
I'm standing here
with both of you...
telling me that you don't see
what's right in front of us.
She's the key to everything
in this case...
right to the F.B.I.
Well, for your sake,
I hope so.
But I hope not for mine.
[Phone Ringing]
John Doggett.
Agent Doggett,
I don't want to be making this call.
I really don't,
but I'm forced to.
What are you talking about?
You want to turf me now?
You going to take
my badge and gun?
Agent Doggett,
you just can't burst in here.
How's it going to look,
Deputy Director...
you suspending me
right before I nail you...
up against the wall
as a coconspirator?
Glad you dropped in,
Mr. Doggett.
Assistant Director Follmer.
You're Brad Follmer.
I was just explaining...
to the deputy director
the reasons why...
you were being suspended...
but I think your actions here
speak for themselves.
I see what this is.
This is just a little
bureaucratic pimp job.
I'd watch your mouth, John.
What this is
is a testament...
to your gross insubordination...
and reckless disregard
for the F.B.I.
The orders start here...
and then they come out
your wishy-washy mouth?
Paranoia must go
with the job.
You're starting to sound...
just like Fox Mulder, Mr. Doggett.
Don't you "Mr. Doggett" me.
I don't answer to you.
I answer to A.D. Skinner.
The job suspension stands...
Mr. Doggett.
Try and stop me.
[Door Closes]
[Knocking]
You just never know...
who's going to come
a-knocking, do you?
How'd you get in here?
Through the front door
with a big howdy do.
How'd you get in?
Through a security checkpoint.
Kid stuff.
What are you doing here?
You sent us hacking
on this investigation...
of yours...
only we had a small
funding fiasco.
They cut our Internet service.
Don't tell me
you breached F.B.I. Security...
just to log on.
I think you want to see this.
[Langly Gasps]
Uh, um, not this.
[Typing]
[Frohike] Okay, this is
what we meant to show you.
We are live
in the E.P.A. Phone system.
The numbers in red...
are calls to
Deputy Administrator Carl Wormus...
after he drowned.
Who'd be calling him at work...
after it's front-page news
that he's dead?
Someone who doesn't know it.
[Line Ringing]
Whoever it is,
they're calling him again as we speak.
Langly!
Hook up a patch cord.
Hurry!
[Typing]
Pick up the phone.
What?
Carl Wormus.
I've been trying to reach you.
They've ordered us to port.
One of my men is dead.
I think they suspect
what we're up to.
Right.
What's it you need from us...
me on this end?
Just like we talked about.
You're going to call the F.B.I.
Right.
You've got to get to the F.B.I.
Tell them about the lab
they've got on board...
about the horrors
and the inhumanity.
Expose these people
for what they are.
I need to talk to you.
I have an appointment.
Don't do this to me, Brad.
Give me two minutes.
Here you are again, Monica.
Walking through my door.
I need your help.
Ah.
I tried to help you.
I'm asking you again.
Okay. I'm listening.
There's a woman working
at the Department ofJustice...
Shannon McMahon.
I need her case files.
You say that
like it's something I can just do.
It's not.
It's important to me.
Important to you and to Agent Doggett,
in other words.
You're on the wrong side
of this fight, Brad.
- I can show you.
- Trust me.
I had it illustrated
by Mr. Doggett himself...
in the deputy director's
office today.
Would you listen to me?
People's lives are in danger here.
He's being set up.
We're being set up.
By who?
TheJustice Department?
It's why I need those files.
I'd ask you
to just do this for me...
but he's a good man.
He believes he's in the right.
And you?
You always are?
Where's Shannon McMahon?
She's back in my house. Why?
She's lying to you.
She's not who you think.
Where are you getting this?
Everywhere I look.
She works for
the Department ofJustice.
Did you know that?
I got a peek at her case files.
Those two men she killed?
They'd contacted her at D.O.J.,
as whistle-blowers.
She said they...
conspired with the government.
They were part
of the program.
They were killed
because they wanted...
to expose the program.
Why is she lying?
Why come to me?
Because there's
still one man...
she can't pinpoint...
and she wants you
to lead her to him.
How, when I don't even know
who you're talking about?
He's captain of a navy ship...
that spends
12 months a year at sea.
He had been
in guarded contact...
with both dead men
about a secret lab...
on that ship.
Right now,
Shannon McMahon's...
the only sure thing we have.
We cut out on her
and go to this ship of yours...
we risk coming up
with both hands empty.
Agent Doggett, if this is true...
about this ship
and about this lab...
there may be answers there
that I can't risk not knowing.
[Door Opens And Closes]
[Beeping]
Dr. Nordlinger?
A message for you, sir.
I want every hard drive.
All the data you've got...
in this butcher shop
you're running here.
Where is this captain
supposed to be?
We're supposed to meet him...
at a phone booth at 1:00 a.m.
It's ten to.
Somebody's already there.
Is he calling or meeting you?
I don't know.
It wasn't clear.
He sees us.
Hold up there!
I said hold up there!
This ain't no captain.
Who is it?
Knowle Rohrer. Run.
Now!
Freeze, F.B.I.!
You didn't trust me.
You see anybody?
Nobody.
This can't be right.
What happened to the captain?
[Reyes]
I think we found the captain.
[Beeping]
They're scuttling the ship.
Agent Scully... Agent Reyes!
This must be it.
Monica!
Dana!
[Doggett]
Agent Scully! Agent Reyes!
In here.
Move out.
We got to get out of here.
You see what this is?
Agent Scully, we got to go!
The ship's going to blow,
Agent Scully!
They're manipulating ova...
females eggs
for transplantation.
Look at these names.
These are test subjects.
Grab her, Monica.
We got less than a minute...
to get out of here.
Just give me a second.
We got no time!
No. Let go.
Let me do this, okay?
I just...
I have to see if I'm here.
My name, my baby's name.
You want to see
your baby again?
We got no time, Dana.
We'll find another way.
[Knocking]
Deputy Director.
My sources tell me...
you've wrapped up
your investigation, John.
I have my report ready, sir. Yes.
How do I come out?
"Super Soldiers, a navy ship...
"a woman at the Department of
Justice who drowned two men.
"All disappeared now,
but which constitute...
a conspiracy like a cancer
in the U.S. Government."
Not a mention of my name, John.
No, sir.
I found nothing on you.
Nothing damning
I could honestly include...
in my report, let me say.
And because I got
nothing to lose...
let me say that I know...
your hands are dirty
on this thing, sir... filthy.
That's why you're here.
Take a last wild punch
before the bell.
There's one thing I can't figure...
and then I'll be on my way...
is why you slipped
that obituary under my door.
You think I did that?
Over and over in my mind.
It had to be you.
You're the only one
that had a reason.
What's my reason?
You tell me.
You looking just to get me fired
or get me killed?
You ever hear
of King George III?
You answer my question!
He was King of England
when America declared independence...
in 1776.
King George III kept a diary.
On July 4, 1776...
he made an entry in it.
"Nothing important happened today."
What the hell does that
got to do with me?
Revolution started.
Things that changed
the world forever.
And even kings can miss them
if they're not paying attention.
Are you saying you left
that obituary to help me?
To help me find
the things that I found?
Nah... why would I believe
that you'd help me?
Agent Mulder believed me.
Mulder? What the hell
are you talking about?
Mulder's long gone.
Say I told Mulder that he
would be killed if he stayed.
Same people who threatened
to kill me if I didn't go along.
Would you believe that, John?
No. Mulder wouldn't hear it,
not from you, not from anybody.
I said I told him to go.
I didn't say I persuaded him.
Oh, my God.
It was Scully.
Scully made him go.
That's it, isn't it?
Going to the basement?
Heard you got
a stay of execution.
Congratulations.
I'm sure you mean that.
No, I'm sure
the deputy director...
has you just where he wants you.
Don't get me wrong...
I'm a friend to the X-Files.
Kind of a comfort
having you down there...
Mr. Doggett.
Hi.
Just so long as you know
where to reach us...
Mr. Follmer.
[Marine Mammal Sounds]
[Gasps]
[Baby Crying]
[Whispering]
Everything's going to be okay.
Go back to sleep, okay?
[Metallic Squeaking]
[Child]
I made this.!