[Whooping Wildly]
Yeah, dudes!
Welcome to your Dumb Ass Show.!
I am Sky Commander Winky
and this is the
beautiful Cap'n Dare!
Yeah, baby! Woo-hoo!
The biggest dumb ass I know.
Thank you, Sky Commander.
Yes, Captain Dare will show you
what a dumb ass he really is.
But be forewarned,
only a stupid dumb ass
would neglect to take
every safety precaution
in the stunts you're
about to witness.
[Grunts]
Now, the physics alone
took almost five minutes
of calculations.
Oh, oh... yes!
Yeah, dude, fire when ready.
Aah, mother[Bleep]!
What the [Bleep]!
[Groaning]
Now that's a dumb ass!
Oh, right in the [Bleep] target!
Hey, Natalie, come here.
How about a kiss for good luck?
Bill, why are you doing this?
His name's Captain Dare
and he'll be famous one day
for going where no dudes
have gone before.
Hey, if you won't
give me a kiss
how about throwing me
a magazine?
[Crowd Laughing]
[Goofy Retching]
[Whooping]
[Engine Accelerating]
[Crowd Cheers And Whoops]
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
[Whooping]
Hey, hey... that...
that is it! Whoo!
There it is!
There it is, yes!
That is a dumb ass!
[Whooping]
[Crowd Cheering]
[Groaning With Disgust]
[Laughter]
[Crowd Cheering]
[Whooping And Laughing]
And now, the awesome
Captain Dare
will make Dumb Ass history
in the scientifically modified
Shopping Cart of Doom...
rolling down this hill
hitting the launch ramp at
an estimated 24.6 miles an hour
sailing just over
the scrumptious Natalie Gordon
who will be holding this
flaming torch in her mouth.
Whoa, I didn't say I
was going to do anything.
What? This is the money shot,
Natalie.
We need you.
Captain, will you tell her?
Yeah, come on, Natalie,
what could go wrong?
What could go wrong?!
You mean besides landing on me
and crushing my head, Bill?
Would you...?
It'll be killer.
The Captain will jump her
her torch will set the cart
on fire... whoosh...
and our daring hero
rolling on to salvation
into the pool of life.
Triumphant.
Natalie, come on,
just do it for me, please?
Please? Please?
[Guy]
Yeah, come on, Natalie.
[Bill]
Come on.
[Crowd Goading]
[Crowd Giggling]
[Cheers And Applause]
[Bill Yelling]
[Grunts]
[Crowd Cheering]
Now, that's a dumb ass.
Come on, Bill.
Get up.
[Natalie Crying]
Hey, Bill!
[Crowd Gasps]
[Screaming]
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Thanks for coming so quickly.
Are you the medical examiner?
Yes, yes, I'm Dr. Fountain.
And you're the experts
from the FBI?
The experts?
Well, I was told
you were the experts.
We work on the X-Files.
Our expertise is the unexplained.
We were told you had
an unexplained death here.
Well, you're the experts.
You tell me.
So why don't you explain
exactly what happened here, Doctor?
Well, I can't.
That's the point.
You can't tell us anything?
Well, all things considered,
I'd prefer not to go on record.
Why is that?
Well, it's the kid's parents.
They're suing everyone.
For what?
Everything.
They're suing the county
for making the street too steep
the supermarket he stole
the shopping cart from
the company that made
the helmet he was wearing.
[Groans]
Off the record, Doc...
what the hell has that got to do
with a supermarket shopping cart?
You familiar with The Dumb Ass Show?
The Dumb Ass Show?
It's a cable TV show where the kids
act like, well, dumb asses.
They videotape themselves
doing stupid stunts.
You mean this was an accident?
I'd prefer not to get sucked
into a legal nightmare here.
You investigate the unexplained.
How about you explain it to me?
[Sighs]
Dr. Fountain, do you see this?
What the hell is that?
You're asking me?
[Screaming]
[Flies Buzzing]
[Elevator Bell Dings]
Thanks for coming so quickly.
The message said urgent.
What is it you want me
to look at here?
We were hoping you could tell us.
Is, uh, she the expert?
Well?
What do you think?
Well, I have to say that, uh...
I've never seen anything
quite like this before.
Well, something killed this kid.
Well, judging from the amount
of insect feces
in the ear and nasal cavities
it appears that they fed
at such a furious rate
that it caused the boy's skull
to collapse from the inside.
His helmet protected his
head during the crash.
There is no impact trauma here
whatsoever. None.
You're saying flies killed him.
[Doggett]
All the kids at the scene...
and the flies choose
to attack this boy?
Why?
Maybe they were attracted
for reasons we're not seeing.
What if somebody put
something in his helmet?
Insect pheromone.
You know, "Spanish Fly"...
that stuff you see advertised
in the back of magazines
that guys use to attract girls.
I glance at them for amusement.
I may have to brush up
on my "Spanish Fly"
but I don't think the science
works that way.
Anyway, before we start
looking for an M.O.
I want to find out
what kind of fly
would act that aggressively.
[Man]
The Musca vetustissima Walker.
The Australian bush fly.
It craves protein so much
it will actually crawl into
your open nose, mouth, ears
even your eyes
to feed on nutritious
blood and moisture.
Though the New Zealand
screw-worm fly
often kills its victims
in mere moments
by burrowing into
an open wound or cut.
I'm sorry.
I'm Dr. Rocky Bronzino.
Hi.
Rocky Bronzino.
Hello there.
Rocky Bronzino,
field entomological expert
Rutgers University,
at your service.
Dr. Bronzino...
Rocky.
These flies you mentioned
neither of them are indigenous
to North America.
Are you suggesting
that we've got
a virulent foreign vector here?
No. The specimens you collected
are your garden- variety Calliphorid.
Harmless as, well... flies.
What are you suggesting then?
Nothing.
Dr. Fountain brought me in
for my scientific expertise.
And I must say...
I'm glad he did.
Dr. Bronzino
you should know we may
be looking at a murder.
A murder?
Are there any suspects?
[Bell Ringing]
Natalie Gordon...
the lady in Captain
Dare's short life
and the last person
to see him alive.
Leave me alone, Winky.
It's for the Dumb Ass Memorial Video.
For our fallen hero.
Just a few words
for Captain Dare, come on.
You want a few words, Winky?
You're a jerk!
And so is your brother
for making Bill
do all those stupid stunts.
Hey, Captain Dare died
doing what he loved!
Pushing the envelope.
Maybe if you weren't
such a...
Hey, you!
Freaky-deaky.
You want your own memorial, huh?
You want to be in Dumb Ass?
Just leave her alone.
I'm talking to you now, freak.
[Laughter]
David Winkle.
In my office, right now!
Typical.
Lokensgard's gotta have
his mommy stick up for him.
Baby.
[Students Laughing]
[Winky Whooping]
[Engine Accelerating]
[Crowd Cheering]
...that is it! Whoo!
There it is!
I think I just solved this case.
This kid had crap for brains,
the flies couldn't resist.
Oh, and you were such
a choirboy growing up?
I mean, we did
some stupid stuff
but we didn't know
it was stupid at the time.
This isn't just stupid,
this is glorification of stupid.
These kids take enormous pride
in being sub-mental.
That's why they call it Dumb Ass.
[Cheering And Whooping]
Mr. David Winkle.
Sky Pilot Winky.
Just the man we want to see.
Come on in.
That's very entertaining,
Sky Pilot.
Sky Commander,
if you don't mind.
And you
can call me
SheriffJohn when I haul your
dumb ass off to jail, Winky.
What are you talking about?
We obtained a copy
of a recent E-mail you sent
offering to sell the video
of your friend's death
to the Fox Network.
What? No, no, no,
I wrote all the networks.
Fox was the only one
who had any interest in it.
I don't think you understand.
Wait... you think I killed him?
You think I killed
Captain Dare
to make money?
My best friend?
Well, looking at this video
you were the last person
to have contact with him.
You handed him his helmet
at the top of the hill.
I think you put
something in it.
[Grunting]
Sit down, Sky Commander.
I can't! I'm being attacked!
Oh, God,
it's happening to me!
[Grunts]
[Panting]
[Cheering On Videotape]
[Winky]
Now that's a dumb ass!
[Buzzing]
Where you been?
Dinner's been on the table
almost an hour, young man.
I'm not hungry.
Well, then, you sit down here
until you get hungry.
Dylan.
I have something
to talk to you about.
Dylan!
[Knocking]
Dylan?
[Music Volume Increases]
[Clicking]
[Buzzing]
[Clicking And Buzzing Continues]
[Buzzing Gets Louder]
[Door Opening]
I'm glad you're here.
I think we just got
our first real break.
What did you find?
Well, it's what the entomologist
Rocky Bronzino found.
The flies that ate
of the brain
and skull of the victim are
all female.
Every last one of them.
Exactly how is that a break?
Well, what are the chances of that?
You mean that the absence
of males suggests
there's a reason for the attack.
Behaviorally.
Well, something
biological is going on.
Whether it's hormonal or chemical
something has caused these bugs
to attack.
Or a need to express themselves.
To what?
This is a kid
that calls himself
"Sky Commander Winky."
Agent Reyes and I were
interviewing him
as a suspect when this happened.
The paramedics arrived
and treated him for
an aggressive attack of body lice.
Hmm.
Lice are not altogether uncommon
in a school environment.
Except that these are better
spellers than most of the kids.
So what are you saying?
That this is just
another Dumb Ass stunt?
[Reyes]
Well, that was my first thought.
But the victim here was just
too freaked out by this incident
to make me believe
he'd staged this.
Which leads me to think
that while you may be right
about this being a matter
of biology,
someone is directing the biology.
How does one direct bugs?
I don't know how
but we've been running down
a long list of witnesses.
[Reyes] A loner who was present
at every Dumb Ass stunt
and who had a run-in
with this kid Winky
at school just prior
to the lice attacking.
His name is Dylan Lokensgard.
We're going to want
to talk to him.
[Doorbell Ringing]
[Knock At Door]
Dylan?
[Knocking]
I want to have a talk with you.
Honey, can you come out here?
Dylan?
Dylan!?
Dylan!
[Car Engine Running]
Where are you going?
To school.
I know where you're going.
Well, what did Natalie want?
You stay away from her.
Dylan, she's no good for you.
She's only going
to get you into trouble.
Natalie and I are friends.
We've been friends
since we were kids.
But you're not kids anymore, Dylan.
Which is why we need to talk, honey.
[Frustrated Sigh]
You're going through changes.
Your body
is going through changes.
You don't understand anything.
I don't want to talk to you.
I wish Dad was still here.
You don't know anything about me.
Honey, I want what's best for you.
Dylan!
Come back here!
So many flowers...
so little time.
Excuse me?
Pheromones, Dr. Scully.
Heavy in the air.
Nature's natural attractants.
Driving the insect world
to go forth and pollinate.
I'm aware of how pheromones work.
But according to this device
there isn't a single pheromone
to be found out here.
Well, that can't be right.
The bio-sensor
we use is an actual fly antenna
over which the pheromones pass.
But I modified the EAG
to measure in picograms
which makes it sensitive
to traces a mile
in any direction.
But I'm still not sure
why you think
that pheromones might cause
an otherwise harmless fly
to attack a human
so violently, Doctor...
Rocky.
Bugs are small-minded creatures,
and therefore very predictable.
They don't have moods, per se.
They react to
circumstance and stimuli
as they have been doing
for millennia.
So what do you suppose
they're reacting to out here?
It may be the bugs are being
somehow driven crazy with desire.
You know, they say we humans
respond to pheromones, too.
Yeah, I tend to agree
with that, yeah.
"Women's Dormitory Syndrome."
It's believed
that pheromones are the reason
that women who live together
share the same menstrual cycle.
Fascinating.
You know, when a male
and female Calliphorid fly mate
they stay joined
for up to one and a half hours.
One and a half, Doctor.
You know, Rocky...
I'm a mother.
Mothers are women, too.
[Beeping]
Big hit!
What is it?
A high concentration
of C-13 calliphorone...
incoming.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Dylan]
Natalie!
[Screaming]
[Crashing, Branches Cracking]
Dylan?
[Gasping]
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What about your bike?
Um, I'll get it later.
I came by your house to see you.
Oh, really?
Yeah, your mom made it sound
like there was something wrong with you.
Me? I'm fine.
What-What did you want?
[Sighs]
I wanted to apologize
about what happened yesterday
in the cafeteria.
Winky can be such a jerk.
I was just worried about you.
W-W-What'd I say?
Nothing.
No one understands.
My mom and dad think
it's just going to go away.
What I'm feeling...
You-You mean about Bill?
I wish I could just
turn back time.
I wish I could just...
make everything go away
and start all over again.
I know.
Like-Like when we were kids.
[Quietly]
Yeah.
Remember the night
we played hide-and-seek
on your street?
Manhunt.
We hid in the tree together.
Our names are still carved in it.
[Awkward Laugh]
I'm-I'm going to get marked late.
[Reyes]
Dylan Lokensgard?
Can you come with us, Dylan?
[Winky On Video] And now the awesome
Captain Dare will make Dumb Ass history
in a scientifically modified
Shopping Cart of Doom.
Rolling down this hill...
Why are you showing me this?
What do you think of it?
You mean, the Dumb Ass Show?
That, and the kids who make it.
I know them, you know...
You ever have
contact with Bill?
The kid who played Captain Dare?
No.
You have anything against him?
Do you think
it's strange
that he was attacked
and killed by insects?
Who wouldn't?
What's going on in here?
We're talking to Dylan.
Oh, no, you're not.
Dylan...
Ma'am...
No one interrogates my son
in my office without my permission.
[Reyes]
Just calm down, Mrs. Lokensgard.
- [Flies Buzzing]
- He's not a part of that crowd.
What are you accusing him of?
[Doggett]
We're not accusing him.
Just trying to see what he knows.
He doesn't know anything.
He was at the crime scene.
Yeah, well, so were a lot of kids.
Dylan...
[Buzzing]
Too late, gentlemen.
Bugs are gone.
Bugs are all gone.
Whatever.
How's he doing?
He's unhurt, apparently.
Not so much as a
single bite on him.
Mrs. Lokensgard?
I don't think we've finished
talking to Dylan.
Oh, yes, you have!
We're going home.
I've said it before
and I'll say it again:
The whole reason this case
is attracting flies
is because somebody's
full of crap.
I think what we just saw
was a show.
Dylan Lokensgard caused
those bugs to attack him
to make himself
look like a victim
instead of the perpetrator.
Okay, but how?
This guy's the Horse Whisperer,
only for bugs?
I don't know how he's doing it
but I may know a way to find out.
Where did you get this?
Dylan Lokensgard provided it to us
when we interviewed him.
I have to warn you, there's
typically not a lot to be found
in a teenage boy's sweaty Kleenex.
You were looking for pheromones.
Aren't there pheromones
produced in adolescent sweat?
Yes, it's what causes B.O.,
but all too obviously
it's not all that attractive...
to anything.
[Slow Beeping]
[Faster Beeping]
I've got a reading here
that's going right off the scale.
[Bronzino]
Holy Toledo!
We've got pheromones
coming out the ying-yang here.
C-13 calliphorone, and how.
[Rapid Beeping Continues]
[Steady Tone]
What happened?
I think my electroantennogram
just... tilted.
What's C-13 calliphorone?
Insect pheromone.
Where did you find this mother lode?
A boy named Dylan Lokensgard.
That specimen came from him.
A boy... is secreting
bug pheromones?
That's impossible.
Preposterous.
[Doggett]
You're the expert
Dr. Bronzino.
How else do you explain it, then?
Rocky?
A boy is a boy, a bug is a bug.
You can't have it both ways.
Okay, so this boy's
going through puberty, right?
I mean, maybe his body chemistry
is somehow just going crazy
and it's his raging
teenage hormones
that are attracting
all these insects.
What if it's more than
chemistry or hormones?
More than biology?
Dylan's not just
attracting these bugs
he's using them to act out.
Yes, but against what?
We saw him talking to a girl.
The one in the Dumb Ass video.
Captain Dare's girlfriend.
[Rock Ballad Playing On CD]
[Volkswagen Engine Chugging]
Natalie...
[Whispers] Natalie?
Dylan?
What are you doing?
I need to talk to you, Dylan.
[Whispers]
You have to be quiet...
It's my mom, she's going
to hear you.
[Whispers]
I'm coming up.
What? No.
Hey...
You're going to
break your neck.
I needed to see you.
Shh.
I haven't been here
in so long.
Since 4th grade.
After school.
It was a Wednesday in April.
"A dream in a mist of gray."
That's from a Syd Barrett song.
How do you know all these things?
My dad told me.
Syd Barrett, he was in
the band Pink Floyd.
He was, like
this brilliant guy
that nobody understood.
Kind of like you?
Me?
I never said I was sorry
when your dad disappeared, Dylan.
I never said a lot of things.
But I want to say them now.
I know you've always cared about me.
We've grown apart, but...
I haven't forgotten you.
And... after we talked
this morning at school
I realized... how special
you really are to me.
I can't believe this.
After what happened to Bill...
I realized how important it is
to have someone who does
understand you
and...
I wanted to do this.
That... that was amazing.
[Chuckles]
[Whimpers]
What... What...
was that?
- What was what?
- Your... your...
Your mouth, your tongue...
there's something wrong with you.
No, don't-don't say that.
- I got to go.
- Natalie, please.
Please, don't. Just stay.
Let me talk to you.
[Engine Starting]
[Crying]
Natalie, listen to me!
Natalie, please...
Hey, Bug Boy!
How about we go for a little
buzz around the block.
[Winky]
So, Lokensgard...
how'd you do it, huh?
How'd you kill him?
I thought bugs
killed Captain Dare.
Yeah, bugs who do what you say.
You want to know how I did it?
I'll show you.
But maybe you should
get your camera ready.
What are you talking about?
I just have to open my mouth.
Oh, God!
[Tires Squealing]
[Glass Shattering]
Mrs. Lokensgard?
Dylan?
[Steady Beeping]
I'm getting a reading here.
Trace levels inside the house.
Well, I guess
that's probable cause.
Dr. Scully?
This is so exciting.
I've never had a partner before.
I have.
I'd like to think of it
as a hymenopteran
relationship.
Two scientists using
their special knowledge
reaching higher than either
of them could ever reach alone.
And if I may say so,
Doctor, you complete me.
I got upstairs, you take down.
All right.
[Steady Beeping Continues]
Hey!
[Winky]
Who's that?
Someone's coming.
Ow!
Get us out!
[Groaning In Pain]
[Moaning]
[Coughing]
Oh, God.
Ow! God!
David Winkle, is that you?
Yeah.
Now that's a dumb ass.
It wasn't a stunt,
it was, uh...
it was Dylan Lokensgard.
He attacked us.
He attacked you?
Yeah, the dude's a freakin' bug.
He chewed right out
the back window.
Ow!
[Groaning]
You stay.
I'll go see that Dylan didn't
head to that girl's house.
- [Phone Ringing]
- Scully.
Where are you?
I'm with Rocky
at the Lokensgard house.
But there's nobody here.
Yeah, well,
I'm afraid the kid's on a tear.
He's caused a car accident
out here on Glenhaven Road.
How'd he do that?
You better see for yourself.
[Beeping]
C-13 calliphorone.
I'm getting a stiff new reading
from up here.
Yeah, Dylan's bedroom's up there.
Unfortunately, he's not in it.
Where are you going?
The kid's on a rampage.
Whoa!
You got my number, partner.
Natalie?
Whoever you are, leave me alone.
Natalie, I'm Monica Reyes,
with the FBI.
I'm here because
I need your help.
It's about Dylan Lokensgard.
Don't say that name around me!
It's important.
You may be the key to
this, to stopping him.
Dylan Lokensgard is a freak!
I thought he was the normal one.
I think Dylan was normal,
just like any other kid.
Whatever it is
he's going through
it has to do with
what he's becoming.
He kissed me!
And it's probably what
he's living for.
And now it's probably why
he lost all control and attacked
David Winkle and his brother.
He attacked Winky?
They're going to be okay.
We just want to make sure
he doesn't hurt anyone else, Natalie.
All right?
[Whimpers]
Come with me.
[Shuddering Gasp]
[Natalie Whimpering]
Why did you run from me?
What is wrong with you?
I'm different, Natalie.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Somebody different
from Bill and Winky?
You killed Bill.
To keep you from being killed.
And now you're coming with me.
Just stay where you are, Dylan.
[Steady Beeping]
[Erratic Beeping]
[Rapid Beeping]
[Squeaking]
[Door Opens And Closes]
[Dylan]
Don't try and stop me.
That little talk that you wanted
to have with me?
It'll have to wait.
Where do you think you're going?
It's where we're going,
me and Natalie.
I'll be taking the car.
You'll be doing nothing of the sort.
You don't want to cross me, Mom.
I am not some kid everybody
can kick around anymore.
You think I don't know what you are?
It's what I've been trying
to tell you, Dylan
to save you from
what you are about to do.
These are the things
I couldn't tell you.
The things I couldn't tell
your father.
You are not like
the other kids.
You never will be.
Monica!
[Muffled Shout]
Holy Mother...
Monica, hold on!
Can you hear me?
Monica, can you breathe?
Monica, talk to me.
He's got the girl.
Where'd they go?
To Dylan's house.
That's where Scully is.
She lost phone contact
with the entomologist, Bronzino.
[Crickets Chirping]
[Whimpering Sobs]
Where are they?
[Whimpers]
Natalie!
[Whimpering]
[Muffled Moaning]
[Gasps]
[Bronzino, Muffled]
Help me.
Oh...
[Panting]
[Gasping]
[Scully] Four more bodies were
found in the Lokensgard attic
including that
of Michael Lokensgard
Dylan's father,
long reported missing.
It now appears that he,
like the others, fell victim
to Dylan's mother who,
in Dr. Rocky Bronzino's
expert opinion,
was neither human nor insect
but something in between.
A biological anomaly,
whose difference from the rest
ofhumanity could be hidden
only for so long.
However strong Dylan
Lokensgard's yearning
to fit in, to win acceptance,
to love and to be loved
he could not defeat the unseen
forces which direct behavior.
In the struggle between
our desire to determine
who and what we will be
and the identity
which biology defines for us
there can only be one outcome.
But even in victory, there are
forces biology cannot defeat...
the stirrings of the soul
the mysteries of desire
the simple truth
that the heart wants...
what the heart wants.
[Child]
I made this.