THE MANDALORIAN: This is the one.
ARMORER: It looks helpless.
THE MANDALORIAN: It is not helpless.
Its species can move objects
with its mind.
ARMORER: The songs of eons past tell
of battles between Mandalore The Great,
and an order of sorcerers called Jedi
that fought with such powers.
THE MANDALORIAN: What is it?
ARMORER: It is a foundling.
By Creed, it is in your care.
THE MANDALORIAN: You expect me
to search the galaxy
for the home of this creature and
deliver it to a race of enemy sorcerers?
ARMORER: This is the Way.
THE MANDALORIAN: I've been quested
with returning this Child to the Jedi.
I can lead you to one of their kind.
But first,
we need your help on our mission.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
We need to hold them off until
we can make the jump to hyperspace.
(GRUNTING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Where can I find the Jedi?
Take the foundling to the city of Calodan
on the forest planet of Corvus.
There you will find Ahsoka Tano.
Tell her you were sent by Bo-Katan.
And thank you.
Your bravery will not be forgotten.
This is the Way.
- Sync and corrections by Nipan_Grilli - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(PANICKED SHOUTING)
(ALARM GONG TOLLING)
(PANICKED CHATTERING)
(BLASTER FIRE)
(ALL SHOUTING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
-(GRUNTS)
-(GROANS)
(SCOUT GUARD 1 SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(SCOUT GUARD 1 SCREAMS)
(SCOUT GUARD 2 SCREAMS)
(SCOUT GUARD 3 SHOUTS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(RUSTLING)
SCOUT GUARD 4: (IN ENGLISH)
She's off the scope. Draw her out.
(SCOUT GUARD 5 SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE
OVER RADIO)
(SCOUT GUARD 6 SCREAMS)
SCOUT GUARD 4: (IN ENGLISH)
I've lost visual. Scan for movement.
(SCOUT GUARD 7 SCREAMS)
MAGISTRATE: Show yourself.
Jedi.
I've been expecting you.
Then you know what I want.
You will learn nothing from me.
I won't give you that choice.
How many lives
is the knowledge I possess worth to you?
One?
Ten?
How about a hundred?
The lives of these citizens
mean nothing to me.
Now, because of you,
these people will suffer.
They already suffer under your rule.
Surrender, or face the consequences.
You have one day to decide.
We will be ready when she returns.
-Cage him.
-(PRISONER GRUNTING)
(GUARD SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
THE MANDALORIAN: Corvus, this is the place.
I've detected a beacon.
(COOS)
I'm gonna start the landing cycle.
You better get back in your seat.
(COOS)
Hey, what did I tell you?
Back in your seat.
(COOING)
(CONTINUES COOING)
(METAL SCRAPING)
(CREATURE SCREECHES)
(SCREECHING)
(CREATURES LOWING)
(COOS)
THE MANDALORIAN: What did I say about that?
-This needs to stay in the ship.
-(WHINING)
Not much to see out here.
(LOWING CONTINUES)
Never had dealings with a Jedi before.
(COOING)
(GRUNTS) Let's head into town.
See if we can pick up a lead.
(SCOUT GUARD SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
State your business.
THE MANDALORIAN: Been tracking for a few days.
Looking for a layover.
Nice armor.
You a hunter, then?
That's right.
Guild?
Last I checked.
(SCOUT GUARD SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(IN ENGLISH) Open the gate.
(GATE OPENING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Pardon me, vendor,
have you heard of anyone...
(SIGHS)
Hmm.
You there.
I need some information.
I'm looking for someone.
(COOS)
(WHISPERS) Okay, bye.
Please, do not speak to them,
or to any of us.
THE MANDALORIAN: Look, I just need to know...
GUARD: The Magistrate wants to see you.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
MALE PRISONER: Help us.
(MALE PRISONER SCREAMS)
(PRISONERS WHIMPERING)
FEMALE PRISONER: She'll kill us all.
(FEMALE PRISONER BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MALE PRISONER SCREAMS)
MAGISTRATE: Come forward.
You are a Mandalorian?
THE MANDALORIAN: Yes.
MAGISTRATE: I have a proposition
that may interest you.
THE MANDALORIAN: My price is high.
This target is priceless.
A Jedi plagues me.
I want you to kill her.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's a difficult task.
MAGISTRATE: One that you are well-suited for.
The Jedi are
the ancient enemy of Mandalore.
THE MANDALORIAN: As I said, my price is high.
MAGISTRATE: What do you make of this?
(CLANKS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Beskar.
Pure beskar...
like your armor.
Kill the Jedi and it's yours.
Where do I find this Jedi?
(LANG BREATHES DEEPLY)
(THE CHILD COOS)
What is that thing?
(GRUNTS)
THE MANDALORIAN: I keep it around for luck.
You're gonna need it where you're headed.
(THE CHILD COOS)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
THE MANDALORIAN: Well, these are the coordinates.
Keep your eyes open.
We must be close.
(RUSTLING)
THE MANDALORIAN: You hear that?
Don't worry. Sit right here.
Let me see what's out there.
(THE MANDALORIAN SIGHS)
False alarm.
-(AHSOKA TANO YELLS)
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
(THE MANDALORIAN SCREAMS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
THE MANDALORIAN: Ahsoka Tano!
(THE MANDALORIAN PANTING)
Bo-Katan sent me.
We need to talk.
I hope it's about him.
(COOS)
(THE CHILD COOING)
(BABBLES)
THE MANDALORIAN: Is he speaking?
Do you understand him?
In a way.
Grogu and I can feel
each other's thoughts.
THE MANDALORIAN: Grogu?
(COOS)
AHSOKA TANO: Yes.
That's his name.
-THE MANDALORIAN: Grogu.
-(COOING)
He was raised
at the Jedi Temple on Coruscant.
Many Masters trained him over the years.
At the end of the Clone Wars
when the Empire rose to power,
he was hidden.
Someone took him from the Temple.
Then his memory becomes... dark.
He seemed lost.
Alone.
I've only known one other being like this.
A wise Jedi Master named Yoda.
(COOS)
Can he still wield the Force?
THE MANDALORIAN: You mean his powers?
The Force is what gives him his powers.
It is an energy field
created by all living things.
To wield it takes a great deal
of training and discipline.
THE MANDALORIAN: I've seen him do things I can't explain.
My task was to bring him to a Jedi.
The Jedi Order fell a long time ago.
THE MANDALORIAN: So did the Empire, yet it still hunts him.
He needs your help.
(SIGHS)
(GROGU COOING)
Let him sleep.
I'll test him in the morning.
(GROGU COOING)
Let's see what knowledge
is lurking inside that little mind.
(COOS)
(GROGU BABBLING)
Now, return the stone to me, Grogu.
THE MANDALORIAN: He doesn't understand.
He does.
(WHINES)
It's okay.
The stone, Grogu.
(STONE CLATTERS)
(SIGHS)
(AHSOKA TANO SIGHS)
I sense much fear in you.
(BABBLING)
AHSOKA TANO: He's hidden his abilities
to survive over the years.
Let's try something else.
Come over here.
-THE MANDALORIAN: He's stubborn.
-Not him.
You.
I want to see if he'll listen to you.
THE MANDALORIAN: That would be a first.
I like firsts.
Good or bad, they're always memorable.
Now, hold the stone out
in the palm of your hand.
Tell him to lift it up.
THE MANDALORIAN: All right, kid.
Lift the stone.
Grogu.
-Grogu...
-(COOS)
Come on, take the stone.
-(GRUNTS)
-THE MANDALORIAN: You see?
I told you, he's stubborn.
Try to connect with him.
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Grogu...
(GRUNTING)
Do you want this?
Well, go ahead.
That's right, take it.
Come on. You can have it.
Come on.
Good job!
Good job, kid.
You see that?
-That's right.
-(COOS)
I knew you could do it.
Very good.
AHSOKA TANO: He's formed
a strong attachment to you.
(GROGU BABBLING)
I cannot train him.
THE MANDALORIAN: What?
Why not?
You've seen what he can do.
His attachment to you
makes him vulnerable to his fears.
His anger.
All the more reason to train him.
No.
I've seen what such feelings can do
to a fully trained Jedi Knight.
To the best of us.
I will not start this child
down that path.
Better to let his abilities fade.
I've delayed too long.
I must get back to the village.
(GROGU WHINING)
THE MANDALORIAN: The Magistrate sent me to kill you.
I didn't agree to anything.
And I'll help you with your problem,
if you see to it
that Grogu is properly trained.
(BABBLING)
THE MANDALORIAN: She has a small army
of guards armed with A350 blaster rifles,
two HK-87 assassin droids,
and a hired gunfighter.
He reads ex-military to me.
Combined, not even your laser swords
would be able to protect you
from all that firepower.
True.
But don't underestimate
the Magistrate either.
THE MANDALORIAN: Who is she?
She offered me a staff
of pure beskar to kill you.
Morgan Elsbeth.
During the Clone Wars,
her people were massacred.
She survived
and let her anger fuel an industry
which helped build the Imperial Starfleet.
She plundered worlds,
destroying them in the process.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah, it looks like
she's still in business.
When you were in the city
did you see any prisoners?
THE MANDALORIAN: I saw three villagers
strung up just outside the inner gate.
We must find a way to free them.
THE MANDALORIAN: A Mandalorian and a Jedi?
They'll never see it coming.
It's her! Sound the alarm!
(GONG TOLLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GUARD YELLS)
(GUARD SCREAMS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(PRISONERS WHIMPERING)
Your bounty hunter failed.
Tell me what I want to know.
Where is your master?
Kill her.
Love to.
I'll take care of this.
Take them with you.
(MALE PRISONER GROANING)
Execute them.
Then go door to door.
(MALE PRISONER SCREAMS)
Please, don't!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FEMALE PRISONER GROANING)
(GUARD SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(GUARD SCREAMS)
(CREATURE CHITTERING)
(SCREECHES)
(GUARDS SCREAMING)
(CONVERSING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUARD SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(IN ENGLISH) Get up there!
(GUARD SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
THE MANDALORIAN: Get inside!
WOMAN: Go.
(PANICKED CHATTERING)
So, you threw in with the Jedi.
THE MANDALORIAN: Looks that way.
(CLANGS)
(MAGISTRATE GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH YELL)
(DISTANT GRUNTING)
LANG: Who do you think's gonna win?
Could be your side...
could be my side.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(DISTANT GRUNTING)
(DISTANT GRUNTING CONTINUES)
LANG: I got no quarrel
with you, Mandalorian.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's far enough.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
LANG: You and I, we're a lot alike.
Willing to lay our lives down
for the right cause.
Which this is not.
(AHSOKA TANO SNARLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Sounds like you win.
(SCREAMS)
Behind you!
Now, tell me.
Where is your master?
Where is Grand Admiral Thrawn?
(EXCITED CHATTERING)
(CITIZENS CHEERING)
I believe this was your payment.
THE MANDALORIAN: No.
I can't accept.
I didn't finish the job.
No.
But this belongs with a Mandalorian.
Where is your little friend?
THE MANDALORIAN: Back at the ship.
Wait here, I'll go get him.
THE MANDALORIAN: Wake up, buddy.
It's time to say goodbye.
(COOS)
(WIND HOWLING)
(BABBLING)
(WHINING)
AHSOKA TANO: You're like a father to him.
I cannot train him.
THE MANDALORIAN: You made me a promise,
and I held up my end.
(SIGHS)
AHSOKA TANO: There is one possibility.
Go to the planet Tython.
You will find
the ancient ruins of a temple
that has a strong connection to the Force.
Place Grogu on the seeing stone
at the top of the mountain.
Then what?
Then Grogu may choose his path.
If he reaches out through the Force,
there's a chance a Jedi may sense
his presence and come searching for him.
Then again,
there aren't many Jedi left.
(BABBLES SADLY)
THE MANDALORIAN: Thank you.
May the Force be with you.
- Sync and corrections by Nipan_Grilli - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44