THE MANDALORIAN: I am told that
you can lead me to others of my kind.
Come on. It's uncouth
to talk business immediately.
(ALL GRUNTING)
All right, stop!
I'll tell you where he is.
The city of Mos Pelgo.
I swear it by the Gotra.
Oh! This little thing
has had me worried sick.
I need your help. Where is Mos Pelgo?
PELI MOTTO: It's an old mining settlement.
Not much to speak of.
THE MANDALORIAN: Where did you get the armor?
Bought it off some Jawas.
THE MANDALORIAN: Hand it over.
I'm sure you call the shots
where you come from,
but 'round here,
I'm the one tells folks what to do.
Help me kill it, I'll give you the armor.
THE MANDALORIAN: That's the krayt dragon.
COBB VANTH: It's bigger'n I guessed.
(COOS)
(CHEERING)
COBB VANTH: This was well-earned.
Thank you.
- Sync and corrections by Scooby74 - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
- Get the Child!
- (SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(THE CHILD COOS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (YELPS)
- (BOTH GRUNT)
THE MANDALORIAN: Wait! Don't hurt the Child.
If you put one mark on him,
there's no place you will be able
to hide from me.
We can strike a bargain.
There's a lot of value in this wreckage.
Take your pick.
(THE CHILD COOS)
But leave the Child.
(SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
THE MANDALORIAN: Okay.
Here. It's yours.
Take it.
It's okay.
(SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(COOS)
- You okay?
- (COOS)
(COOS)
(SNORTS)
(INDISTINCT JAWAESE CHATTER)
I don't know. Looks like someone's
gonna be goin' home empty-handed.
(DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
You finally found a Mandalorian
and ya killed him?
THE MANDALORIAN: He wasn't Mandalorian.
I bought this armor off of him, though.
- What'd that set you back?
- Killed the krayt dragon for him.
Oh. Is that all?
THE MANDALORIAN: He was my last lead
on finding other Mandalorians.
(DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Okay. Well, you might be in luck.
Dr. Mandible says he can connect you
with someone who can help you,
if you cover his call this round.
It's what he said.
THE MANDALORIAN: What's the bet?
- Five hundred.
- That's a high-stakes game.
Hey, he's on a hot streak.
- (DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
- (THE MANDALORIAN SIGHS)
- Is the pot right?
- (DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Ha! Idiot's Array! Pay up, thorax!
(DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
THE MANDALORIAN: I thought you said
he was on a hot streak?
Oh. stop your cryin'. You'll rust.
(DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
All right. He says the contact
will rendezvous at the hangar.
(DR. MANDIBLE SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
They'll tell you where to find
some Mandalorians.
That's what you wanted, right?
- Yes.
- All right, well, stop your mopin'.
More importantly, did you bring back
any of that dragon meat?
Better not have any maggots on it.
I don't like maggots.
(COOS)
Hey, don't overcook it, Treadwell.
I like it medium rare!
I'm not some Rodian, for crying out loud.
(EXHALES) All right, here's the deal.
A Mandalorian covert is close.
It's in this sector, one system trailing.
Are they the ones that left Nevarro?
Don't know. All I know is that the contact
will lead you to them.
- How much will it cost me?
- Well, that's the great news. It's free.
Aside from a finder's fee, of course.
- What's the not-great news?
- Nothing. It's all great.
Okay.
However, there is one small skank
in the scud pie.
- Which is?
- The contact wants passage to the system.
- Do you vouch for them?
- On my life.
- Fine.
- And...
no hyperdrive.
You want me to travel sublight?
Deal's off.
It's one sector over.
Moving fast is the only thing
keeping me safe.
These are mitigating circumstances.
What do you mean "mitigating"?
(FROG LADY GRUNTS)
- I'm not a taxi service.
- I know, I know, I hear you.
But I can vouch for her.
(FROG LADY SPEAKING FROG)
- THE MANDALORIAN: What's the cargo?
- (SPEAKING FROG)
It's her spawn. She needs her eggs
fertilized by the equinox
or her line will end.
If you jump into hyperspace, they'll die.
She said her husband has settled
on the estuary moon of Trask
in the system of the gas giant Kol Iben.
- She said all that?
- I paraphrased.
THE MANDALORIAN: Is she sure
there are Mandalorians there?
(BOTH SPEAKING FROG)
She said her husband has seen them.
(COOS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Do you know the husband?
No. I met her ten minutes
before you walked in.
I thought you said
you vouched for her on your life.
What can I say,
I'm an excellent judge of character.
Now, I'm gonna ask you to stay strapped in
whenever you're seated.
Traveling sublight
is a bit dicey these days.
Whether it's pirates or warlords,
someone either ends up
with a nice chunk of change or your ship.
(SPEAKING FROG)
I don't speak whatever language that is.
You speak Huttese?
(THE MANDALORIAN SPEAKS HUTTESE)
(THE MANDALORIAN SIGHS)
(COOS)
So, I'm gonna hit the rack.
I've set the nav for our course.
It's gonna take a while.
I recommend you get some rest.
- Kid?
- (SLURPING)
- No, no, no!
- (SLURPS)
- That is not food. Don't do that again.
- (BURPS)
Nap time.
(COOS)
(BEEPING)
CARSON: Razor Crest, M-One-Eleven.
Come in, Razor Crest. Do you copy?
THE MANDALORIAN: This is Razor Crest.
Is there a problem?
CARSON: We noticed your transponder
is not emitting.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yes, I'm pre-Empire surplus.
I'm not required to run a beacon.
CARSON: That was before. This sector
is under New Republic jurisdiction.
All craft are required to run a beacon.
Thank you for letting me know.
I'll get right on it.
CARSON: Not a problem. Safe travels.
THE MANDALORIAN: May the Force be with you.
CARSON: And also with you.
- Just one more thing.
- THE MANDALORIAN: Yes?
CARSON: I'm gonna
need you to send us a ping.
We're out here sweeping
for Imperial holdouts.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'll let you know if I see any.
CARSON: I'm still gonna need you
to send us that ping.
THE MANDALORIAN: Well, I'm not sure
I have that hardware online.
CARSON: We can wait.
THE MANDALORIAN: Yeah, I...
Doesn't seem to be working.
CARSON: That's too bad. If we can't
confirm you're not Imperial,
you're gonna have to follow us
to the outpost at Adelphi.
They'll run your tabs.
- Oh, wait. There it is. Transmitting now.
- (FROG LADY GASPS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Be quiet!
CARSON: What's that?
THE MANDALORIAN: Uh, nothing. The hypervac
is drawing off the exhaust manifold.
(FROG LADY GRUNTING)
WOLF: Carson, can you switch over
to channel two?
CARSON: Copy.
Was your craft in the proximity
of New Republic Correctional Transport,
Bothan-Five?
(FROG LADY SCREAMS)
- We got a runner.
- I'm on it.
CARSON: Razor Crest, stand down.
We will fire. I repeat, we will fire.
WOLF: I don't know where he thinks
he's goin' in that thing.
CARSON: That thing's gonna
break apart in this atmosphere.
(SCREAMS)
CARSON: He's headin' down
into that canyon.
I got 'im. Target computer active.
CARSON: Come on, Razor Crest,
don't make us do it.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Hold on.
- (GRUNTS)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
CARSON: I've lost visual.
He's got to be around here somewhere.
You head north. We'll cover more ground.
(FROG LADY GASPS AND GROANS)
(FROG LADY GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
- (FROG LADY SCREAMS)
- (THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FROG LADY GROANING)
(WHIMPERS)
(GROANS)
(SPEAKS FROG)
I'll find your eggs, don't worry.
(WHIMPERS)
Gotta get you some blankets,
keep you warm.
Damn it.
Where are you?
(FROG LADY SPEAKING FROG)
Hang on, I'm looking for your eggs!
(THE CHILD SLURPING)
(COOS)
No! I told you not to do that.
(SPEAKING FROG)
Found them!
(SLURPS)
How many did you eat?
(BURPS)
If you hadn't guessed,
we're in a tight spot.
The main power drive is not responding,
and the hull has lost its integrity.
I suspect the temperature
will drop significantly when night falls.
(COOS)
I'll have a better idea
of our prospects at that time.
(SPEAKING FROG)
I'm sorry, lady. I don't understand Frog.
Whatever it is, it can wait until morning.
I recommend you get some sleep.
(THE CHILD COOS)
(WHIMPERS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
FROG LADY: Wake up, Mandalorian.
This cannot wait until morning.
Do not be alarmed. I bypassed
the droid's security protocols
and accessed its vocabulator.
THE MANDALORIAN: What the hell are you doing?
That droid is a killer.
FROG LADY: These eggs are the last brood
of my life cycle.
My husband has risked his life
to carve out an existence for us
on the only planet
that is hospitable to our species.
We fought too hard and suffered too much
to resign ourselves to the extinction
of our family line.
I must demand that you hold true
to the deal that you agreed to.
(WHIMPERS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Look, lady, the deal is off.
We're lucky if we get off this frozen tomb
with our lives.
FROG LADY: I thought honoring one's word
was a part of the Mandalorian code.
I guess those are just stories
for children.
(COOS)
(SIGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN: This was not a part of the deal.
(WIND HOWLING)
(THE CHILD SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
How 'bout you come over here,
give me a hand? Make yourself useful.
(SIGHS)
Hey, kid.
I said hey! Where are you going?
Come back here!
(THE CHILD SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
When did she go?
(THE CHILD SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(FROG LADY GRUNTS)
There you are.
You can't leave the ship.
It's not safe out here.
(FROG LADY SPEAKS FROG)
(SPEAKING FROG)
Let's gather these up.
I know it's warm. But night's coming fast,
and I can't protect you out here.
(SPEAKING FROG)
(COOS)
No. No!
(WHINES)
(COOS)
(SNIFFS)
(INDISTINCT RUMBLING)
(CRACKLING)
(THE CHILD COOING)
(SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING FROG)
(GASPS)
(INDISTINCT PATTERING)
(FROG LADY GASPS)
(INDISTINCT GROWL)
(GROWLS)
Go, go, go! Back to the ship!
(THE MANDALORIAN PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(GRUNTING)
(FROG LADY GASPS)
(COOS)
(GRUNTS)
(WHINES)
(SPEAKS FROG)
(THE MANDALORIAN PANTING)
Strap yourselves in. This better work.
I've got limited visibility.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
We ran the tabs on the Razor Crest.
You have an arrest warrant
for the abduction
of prisoner X-Six-Nine-Eleven.
However, on board security records
show that you apprehended
three priority culprits
from the Wanted Register.
Security records also show
that you put your own life in harm's way
to try to protect that of Lieutenant Davan
from the New Republic Correctional Corps.
Is this true?
THE MANDALORIAN: Am I under arrest?
Technically, you should be.
But these are trying times.
THE MANDALORIAN: What say I forego
the bounties on these three criminals,
and you two help me fuse my hull
so I can get off this frozen rock?
What say you fix that transponder,
and we don't vaporize that antique
the next time we patrol the Rim?
All right. I'm gonna repair the cockpit
enough for us to limp to Trask.
There's nothing I can do
about the main hull's integrity,
so we're gonna have to get cozy
in the cockpit.
It's the only thing I can pressurize.
If you need to use the privy, do it now.
It's gonna be a long ride.
(FROG LADY SPEAKS FROG)
Okay, repair's all done.
Let's see if we can get this thing going
once and for all.
(SQUEALING)
(GRUNTS)
Wake me up if someone shoots at us.
Or that door gets sucked off its rails.
(SPEAKS FROG)
I'm kidding. If that happened,
we'd all be dead. Sweet dreams.
(THE CHILD GRUNTS)
(FROG LADY SPEAKS FROG)
(COOS)
(SLURPS)
- Sync and corrections by Scooby74 - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44