Oh.
Is that me?
There must be some mistake.
-I can get you more credits.
-I can bring you in warm...
Or I can bring you in cold.
(GROANING)
THE CLIENT: Yes, yes, yes!
-Very healthy.
-What are your plans for it?
This asset
was of extreme importance to me.
-(DR. PERSHING GASPS)
-What did you do to it?
Don't hurt him. It's just a child.
THE MANDALORIAN: Cara Dune here was a veteran.
She was a drop soldier for the Rebellion.
-(METAL CLACKS)
-(GROANS)
-(ALARM BEEPING)
-(YELPS)
THE MANDALORIAN: You're staying here?
Nevarro is a very fine planet.
And now that the scum and villainy
have been washed away,
it's very respectable again.
THE MANDALORIAN: Hang on, kid.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride,
but I finally know where I'm taking you.
- Sync and corrections by Nipan_Grilli - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44
(SIGHS) All right, let's try this again.
Okay, did you... Do you have the wire?
(ALARM BEEPING)
No. Nothing.
(SIGHS) Hey...
Oh. (CLEARS THROAT)
Okay. Did you get the wire out?
The red wire?
Huh?
No, no, no. No, the red one.
Show me the red wire.
The red one.
-(COOS)
-Yes, good.
Now, you're going to plug that red wire
where the blue wire goes in the board.
(COOS)
Put the red wire where
the blue wire goes in the board, okay?
But don't let them touch.
(COOS)
You see where you took the blue one off?
-Yes, now put the red one...
-(GRUNTING)
No, don't put the blue one back.
Put the red one where the blue one was.
And put the blue one
where the red one was.
-But be careful.
-(COOING)
They're oppositely charged,
so keep them away from each other.
Make sure you hold them apart from...
No, hold them apart.
Oh! Uh-uh...
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(SIGHS) Oh...
Are you okay?
(COUGHS)
(WHINING)
(SIGHS)
Well, it was worth a shot.
There's no way
we're making it to Corvus in this shape.
(THE MANDALORIAN EXHALES)
I think we need
to visit some friends for repairs.
So, how'd you like to go back to Nevarro?
(ALL SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(SCREECHING)
(ALL ARGUING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(DISTANT CLATTERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SNARLING)
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CHITTERING)
Hey!
Okay. Oh. Oh...
Okay, little guy.
No one's eating you today.
(CHITTERS)
Go on, you're free.
Go on. Git.
(CONTINUES CHITTERING)
Okay, look.
Here you go.
That's all I got.
Now, I need to return
all these things to the rightful owners.
(SCOFFS)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(ALARM STOPS)
(RAZOR CREST SPUTTERING)
(METALLIC CREAKING)
GREEF KARGA: Looks like someone
could use some repairs.
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
THE MANDALORIAN: How's my credit around here?
I think something could be arranged.
Isn't that right, Marshal?
(THE CHILD COOS)
I'm sure we can work somethin' out.
I'll get my best people on it.
Hey, fellas!
Let's fix this man's ship!
I want it as good as new.
(SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
And you, come here, little one!
(CHUCKLING)
Has Mando been
taking good care of you, huh?
-Have you been takin' good care o' him?
-(THE CHILD COOS)
Yeah? Yeah! He said "yeah!" Oh, yeah.
(CHUCKLING)
Yes.
Come on. Yeah.
Yeah, look at you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Looks like you two have been busy.
GREEF KARGA: I myself have been
steeped in clerical work.
Marshal Dune here
is to be thanked for cleaning up the town.
Your ship's not lookin' too good.
I had a run-in with the New Republic.
GREEF KARGA: They should leave the Outer Rim alone.
If the Empire couldn't settle it,
what makes them think they can?
Here we are.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm surprised to
see this place is still standing.
Wait till you see inside.
FEMALE PROTOCOL DROID: Who can name one of
the five major trade routes in the galaxy?
Anyone?
How about the Corellian Run?
-BOY 1: The Hydian Way?
-Yes, the Hydian Way. That is correct.
-A school?
-Things have changed a lot around here.
We'll leave the little one here
so we can talk business.
-Wait. Wherever I go, he goes.
-Mando, please.
Where we're going,
you don't wanna take a child. Trust me.
He'll be fine here. You have my word.
...be transported from the Outer Rim
to as far away as the Core Worlds.
-(COOS)
-(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
However, there are
several other regions within our galaxy.
They are the Mid Rim...
-Come on.
-...the Expansion Region, the Inner Rim,
the Colonies, Core, and Deep Core.
All right, class. Settle down.
Back to the lesson, shall we?
The capital of the Old Republic
was within the Core
on a planet called Coruscant.
-The capital of the New Republic...
-(COOS)
...is currently on the planet Chandrila,
which is also within the Core region.
-So, back to the start.
-(COOS)
The system also contains
the Akkadese Maelstrom.
The Maelstrom surrounds Kessel
and its three moons.
-As you learned yesterday...
-(WHISPERS) No!
-...there are many systems in this galaxy.
-(WHINES)
How many orbits are in the Kessel system?
Do we at least remember that?
BOY 2: Ooh, I know!
Uh... Two?
FEMALE PROTOCOL DROID: Yes, very good.
As the third moon of Kessel
rotates the outer planet,
you see the moon here
travels in its same orbit.
Now who can track the path
of the orbit here?
Do I have any volunteers?
Anyone?
(COOS)
There's no registration on the ship,
but I'm pretty sure it belongs...
GREEF KARGA: I believe you two have met.
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm surprised to see you here.
Right back at ya.
Mythrol here's taken care
of my books since he was a pollywog.
But then he disappeared one day
after a bit of "creative accounting."
Magistrate Karga was generous enough
to let me work off my debt.
Thank you, by the way.
Three hundred and fifty years,
but who's counting?
Well, if he runs off on you again,
let me know.
Let me assure you, I do not wanna
spend any more time in carbonite.
Still can't see outta my left eye.
CARA: Can we talk business?
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm only here for repairs.
Which'll take a while.
Which means you'll have free time
on your hands, right?
And we could really use your help.
Help how?
This is Nevarro.
We're here.
This entire area's a green zone.
Completely safe.
But over on this side is the problem.
It's an old Imperial base.
It's where all those troops came from
when we defeated Moff Gideon.
This base has been here
since the Imperial expansion.
It's got a skeleton crew, but for
some reason, it hasn't been abandoned.
There's a lot o'
heavy weaponry in that place
the black market would love
to dismantle and get their hands on.
And you wanna mop up the last
of the Imperial force before they do.
Mando, I just want them off my planet.
If we could take out that one last base,
Nevarro would be completely safe.
We could be a trade anchor
for the entire sector.
And the planet would finally be free.
What are we looking at?
The whole base is powered by a reactor.
We sneak in, overload the reactor,
and get the hell outta there.
THE MANDALORIAN: Let's be fast.
And keep the speeder running.
There it is, right there.
You see it?
How close you want me to drop you off?
How 'bout the front door?
It's a little close
for a civilian, isn't it?
I got two choices for ya.
You take us in and I knock
a hundred years off your debt.
Or?
Or I leave ya out here
in the lava flats to walk home
with whatever's left
in your humidity vest.
It's not much of a choice, is it?
MYTHROL: All right.
We can't go any further than this.
GREEF KARGA: Let's go.
Controls are useless. They're melted.
Well, it's probably not rated for lava.
Imperial trash.
All right, I'm headed back.
Hit me up on the comm,
we could set up a rendezvous time.
You park your gills right there
until I say otherwise.
I'm startin' to dehydrate, boss.
Okay, how does 30 more years
off your debt sound?
Can you at least be quick about it?
You wanna be quick?
Grab the flange cutter and help us out.
-(GROANS)
-(LANDSPEEDER BEEPS)
MYTHROL: Okay, fine. I don't like
leaving my speeder like this,
just so you know.
Come on, hurry it up.
MYTHROL: All right, I'm coming.
GREEF KARGA: Hurry up.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Hold tight.
How long is this gonna take?
Look, lady, this is rated
for light plumbing and such.
You're lucky I even packed it at all.
-CARA: (SIGHS) Dank farrik.
-(STORMTROOPER SCREAMING)
-(THUDS)
-(DOOR BEEPS)
Are you comin' in or what?
I'll take my chances here,
but thank you.
Well, when the lava tide comes in,
give us a holler. We'll drop you a rope.
Empty base, huh?
(WIND HOWLING)
GREEF KARGA: The reactor should be set
in the heat shaft.
If we drain the cooling lines,
this whole base
will go up in a matter of minutes.
MYTHROL: Look.
It's a mint Trexler Marauder.
We can get a lot for this
on the black market.
THE MANDALORIAN: And it's gonna get vaporized
like the rest of this base.
Now, let's go.
MYTHROL: (SIGHS) Such a waste.
Shuttle bay, this is command.
Shuttle bay,
the security feed just went down.
Can you check your relay hub?
(STATIC)
Shuttle bay? Shuttle bay, this is...
(CHOKING)
(CLICKING BUTTONS)
This will come in handy.
THE MANDALORIAN: I found the heat shaft.
Let's go.
The access corridor
should be right past this junction.
STORMTROOPER 1: Must've blown a transformer over there.
STORMTROOPER 2: All right. We'll check it out.
STORMTROOPER 1: Section-Four? TK-1-4-7.
STORMTROOPER 2: Scan control has been
unreliable since last rotation.
Send a technical crew to check it out.
THE MANDALORIAN: There, Mythrol, slice that door.
GREEF KARGA: Use the code cylinder.
MYTHROL: Whoa!
GREEF KARGA: Yeah, "whoa" is right.
That's it.
Get on the reactor controls,
drain the coolant lines.
We'll watch the doors.
-Me?
-Yes, you!
I'm afraid o' heights. And heat. And lava.
How 'bout if I put ya back in carbonite?
Get over there!
-There's no guard rail on this.
-Come on!
(MYTHROL GRUNTING)
Oh, boy.
-(KEYPAD BUZZES)
-GREEF KARGA: Come on, hurry up, hurry up.
-Hurry up!
-(KEYPAD BUZZES)
(STAMMERING)
(BEEPING)
MYTHROL: Oh, dear.
(ALARM BEEPING)
All right, she's gonna blow.
Let's go! Let's get outta here!
CARA: How long do we have?
Ten minutes at the most.
(ALARM BLARING)
STORMTROOPER: 5-3-8-7 and 5-3-8-9, follow me.
Call in reinforcements!
IMPERIAL SCIENTIST: Hurry up, purge the drives.
Destroy it!
Ahh!
(SCREAMS)
What the...
I thought you said
this was a forward operating base.
I thought it was.
CARA: No,
this isn't a military operation.
This is a lab.
We need to get into the system
and figure out what's going on.
-What about the reactor...
-Do it! Do it.
THE MANDALORIAN: I don't like this.
Pardon me.
DR. PERSHING: Replicated the results
of the subsequent trials,
which also resulted
in catastrophic failure.
There were promising effects
for an entire fortnight,
but then, sadly,
the body rejected the blood.
I highly doubt we'll find
a donor with a higher M-count, though.
I recommend
that we suspend all experimentation.
I fear that the volunteer
will meet the same regrettable fate
if we proceed with the transfusion.
Unfortunately, we have exhausted
our initial supply of blood.
The Child is small,
and I was only able
to harvest a limited amount
without killing him.
If these experiments
are to continue as requested,
we would again
require access to the donor.
I will not disappoint
you again, Moff Gideon.
THE MANDALORIAN: This must be
an old transmission. Moff Gideon is dead.
No. This recording's three days old.
THE MANDALORIAN: If Gideon's alive then...
STORMTROOPER 1: Over there!
(STORMTROOPER 1 GROANS)
(SCREAMS)
STORMTROOPER 2: We have them!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
I need to get the kid.
Jet back, you're faster that way.
We'll head to the speeder
and meet you in town.
GREEF KARGA: Come on, let's go!
When did you say
this place is gonna blow again?
STORMTROOPER: They're on the move!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(MYTHROL YELPING)
GREEF KARGA: Let's go!
STORMTROOPER: We think they may be moving to the... Hey!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(GROANS)
STORMTROOPER: This way!
(BOTH GROAN)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(BEEPS)
(BEEPING)
STORMTROOPER: All right, men, load your weapons.
There they are! Blast 'em!
MYTHROL: We're trapped!
Is that so?
Cover me!
What does she think she's doing?
All right, baby girl,
let's see what you got.
What are you guys waiting for,
an invitation? Let's move!
Go! Go, go, go, go, go! Go!
You're not considering
going over...
Hang on!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GRUNT)
(ALL PANTING)
MYTHROL: Wait. Was that my speeder...
(YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
Man the guns.
Copy that.
(SCREAMS)
One down.
I've lost him!
(MYTHROL YELPING)
(GREEF KARGA AND CARA GRUNT)
(SCREAMING)
Whoo!
(GRUNTS)
(BEEPING)
(LAUGHING)
Yes! We did it!
Headed home, boss.
(BEEPING)
That may have been premature.
Take evasive! I got this!
(GRUNTS)
What is going on back there?
You wanna come back here
and try this? Be my guest!
Can't you get this thing to go any faster?
(GRUNTING) Come on.
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
We're almost there!
-Yes! Yes!
-(MYTHROL LAUGHS)
-Hang on, kid.
-(COOS)
(THE CHILD GIGGLES EXCITEDLY)
(WHOOPS)
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
(GIGGLING)
(SCREAMS)
-Yeah!
-(BOTH WHOOPING)
Yes! (WHOOPS)
-Yeah!
-(EXHALES)
Not too bad, huh, kid?
Oh, boy.
GREEF KARGA: That was some
pretty impressive flying, Mando.
What do I owe ya?
With the repairs, let's call it even.
(WHINES)
(CHUCKLES)
Can I at least buy you a drink?
THE MANDALORIAN: Sorry. I have some
onboard maintenance I gotta take care of.
Then we gotta hit the road
before Gideon catches wise.
Well, good luck flying, my friend.
So, is there anything else
you can remember before the base exploded?
No.
How long after
the Razor Crest jumped out...
(SCOFFS)
I never said anything about a Razor Crest.
Your transponder log has a...
"Transponder log."
Come on, give me a break.
The control droid
can't tell apart anything pre-Empire.
This isn't Coruscant.
Do you have anything else to add?
Not that I can think of, Officer.
But if somethin' does come to mind,
I'll be sure to send you a 'gram.
That is,
if you're ever out this far again.
What?
(CREATURE CHITTERING)
You did a hell of a job
cleanin' up the system.
According to records,
you're quite a soldier.
We could really use you.
I'm not a "joiner," Blue.
There's something going on out here.
They don't believe it
on the Core Worlds, but it's true.
These aren't isolated incidents.
They need to be stopped
before it's too late.
But we can't do it without local support.
Says here you're from Alderaan.
I served during Alderaan.
Did you lose anyone?
I lost everyone.
I'm sorry for your loss.
(SYSTEM BEEPS)
What do you have for me?
The device has been planted,
as you requested.
Good.
You'll be well-rewarded in the new era.
OFFICER: Moff Gideon.
The tracking beacon
has been installed on the Razor Crest.
Does he still have the asset?
Yes. Our source confirmed it.
And we will be ready.
- Sync and corrections by Nipan_Grilli - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI by GoldBerg_44