[Jughead] A lot can happen
in seven years.
[Rick grunting]
[Jughead] But in Riverdale,
the more things change...
That was...
That was hot, yeah.
[Jughead] ...the more they stay
exactly the same.
Hey, I'm Rick.
-What's your name?
-Come on, no names.
See ya.
[Rick] Yeah.
[Rick sighs]
-Hello.
-Hey.
Hey, babe.
How was the store?
I had to go to
a couple different places,
but I got regular milk,
oat milk, almond milk
and two varieties
of sugary cereals.
You're the best, Kev.
I'm sorry about
all these crazy cravings.
-It's all good.
-Are you okay?
Totally.
Not nervous about
the big announcement?
Not at all.
Why would I be?
-[Archie] Okay, you ready?
-I'm ready.
Wow, I was so
not ready.
Now, what do you think?
I think you've come
a long way from
when you were eight
and said you wanted
to be a firefighter.
[both laugh]
♪ Pulling down a backstreets
Deep in your head ♪
♪ Slipping through dreamland
like a tourist... ♪
[Jughead] Thanks for coming
to meet us, Dr. Whitley.
You mentioned
having a specimen
that needed examining.
May I see it?
Um...
it's the damnedest
thing, Doc.
Someone stole it.
Uh-huh.
I was babysitting it,
and then...
[sighs]
Suddenly, this blinding light
appeared in the sky,
and the last thing I remember,
I was looking up at it.
But then I lost
several hours.
-Next thing I knew,
the Mothmen mummy--
-The specimen?
The specimen was gone.
Hmm.
Mr. Jones,
I'm an anthropologist
with an interest
in extraterrestrial phenomena,
not a psychologist.
But in the majority of cases
like you're describing,
when a person claims
to have had a close encounter,
they are, in fact,
often repressing a
traumatic experience.
You said in the
majority of cases.
What about the other ones?
The other cases,
I believe they're
telling the truth.
If you'd like, I can perhaps
help you determine what
you're dealing with here.
Truth or repression.
There's a
support group I lead--
We're so sorry for making you
drive all the way from
your university, Doctor.
But I don't need
a support group.
If I am repressing something,
I think I prefer to keep
it repressed, you know?
Should you
decide otherwise,
here's my card.
Just in case. You take care.
Juniper, Dagwood,
this artwork is so beautiful.
Your mom's going to love this
when she gets home.
-[Alice] Good morning, honey.
-Morning, Mom.
[phone vibrating]
Hey, Mr. Keller,
is everything okay?
Okay, I'll be
right there.
What is it?
They found another body
in Swedlow Swamp.
Another one?
But is it Polly?
No, Tom says it looks like
the other bodies. It's like
it's been there for a while.
Okay. Call me the second
you know?
-Okay. Love you.
-Okay. Love you, too.
Your lats are looking
huge, babe.
Oh, thanks. Trying to
keep up with you.
Well... [scoffs]
Fangs, we should talk
about stuff.
Us. Before things
get crazy.
I know we've been
in an open relationship and...
Remember, that was when
I was on the road mostly.
Now, things are different.
I get it and I want to be
monogamous too.
Also I'm seeing what
we're about to do...
as a fresh start
for the both of us.
Clean slate.
And I hope you do too.
[line ringing]
Hey, Mom, it's not her.
It's not Polly.
Are you sure?
100%. Dr. Curdle says
the remains are over
a year old.
Oh, thank God.
This means that your sister's
still out there.
It means she's still alive,
don't you think, Betty?
Hopefully. I love you, Mom.
Hang in there, okay?
[line disconnects]
[message chimes]
Ugh, not now, Chad.
Clear the deck, Smithers.
We're starting a remodel
of this apartment, ASAP.
Very good, Ms. Veronica.
Oh, I can assemble a list
of contractors for you.
Oh, that won't
be necessary.
I already hired
my contractor.
So what do you want
to have done to your apartment?
One word.
Demolition. I want it all
torn out, down to the studs.
That's a big job, but, yeah,
I think my buddy Eric would
be up for helping out.
What's your timeline?
I want it done yesterday.
I need changes
in my life, Archie.
Big changes.
How big are we
talking about?
[Jughead] Hey,
that's very cool.
What is this?
Like, plans for your very own
Shangri-La, Veronica?
It will be the new
and improved Pembrooke.
Looks swanky, V.
Hey.
-Hey.
-[Cheryl] The Four Musketeers.
Pray tell, why for have
we been summoned?
Hey, guys.
Thanks for gathering
on such short notice.
Um, Fangs and I have
announcement to make.
We're engaged.
[Betty] Oh, my God.
That's such good news.
But wait, there is more.
Yeah. We're having
a baby.
Guys, that's great!
Wait, Archie,
there's still more.
-We're having the baby.
-With me.
I'm having our baby.
We're planning on raising
this child together.
-Just the three of us.
-Just one big, happy,
nontraditional family.
What in the actual...
And they call me
Cherry Bombshell.
Cheryl, good.
I actually wanted to talk
to you about stepping back
from the Vixens.
Tell me, did it really
not occur to you
to give me any advance warning
about your offspring's lineage?
Well, to be honest, Cheryl,
I wanted to tell you.
Not just as my co-captain,
but as my friend.
But based on your recent
behavior, I...
didn't even know if we had
that relationship anymore.
And did this harebrained idea
originate with Kevin or--
Me, Cheryl.
When I was a junior
in Highsmith College,
I found out that I have
a medical condition
that makes it hard for me
to get pregnant,
the older I am.
Oh.
Toni, I had no idea.
I'm so sorry.
Anyways, the doctor said that
if I really want to have kids,
I need to do it
while I'm young.
Okay.
-But Kevin and Fangs?
-Fangs is like family to me.
We got initiated into
the Serpents together.
And when Fangs and Kevin
started talking about
adoption or looking
for a surrogate mother,
I volunteered.
Splendid.
So you've got an insta family
while I'm withering away
at Thornhill.
Look, I'm having a baby
with Kevin and Fangs.
But I still care
about you deeply.
And if you want,
maybe we can still try
and make this work.
I don't see how
that's possible anymore.
But congratulations.
I'm very happy for you.
[school bell ringing]
You know, it's funny.
I always figured the first
baby would be
yours and Jughead's
or Archie and Veronica's.
How times change,
I guess.
Yeah. You're not kidding.
That sounded loaded.
What gives?
You have to keep it
a secret though, okay?
Oh, God.
Please don't tell me you
and Jughead
are getting back together.
No! It's...
It's me and Archie.
We've been doing this casual
friends with benefits thing.
Shut the front door.
Yeah, it's an...
It's an escape.
And we're in this bubble
and I don't want it to burst.
And I also don't want
to get in too deep
with him, you know.
Why?
Because Archie's this
lit window in the dark,
and I don't want
that light to ever go out.
The importance of sight,
the way we see the world
or how we interpret what
happens to us is one
of the biggest themes
in the Slaughterhouse-Five.
Now Billy has "discovered"
the truth, and that's why
he can, at any one point,
be at his daughter's wedding,
be fighting the Germans
or he could be millions
of light years away
as a captive in some alien zoo.
Billy has
"achieved true sight."
Or at least that's
one interpretation.
-[gunshot]
-[dramatic music playing]
[boy] Mr. Jones?
Mr. Jones, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Uh...
What was I saying?
You said that there was
another interpretation.
Yes, that Billy is crazy.
[dramatic music playing]
[school bell ringing]
[Jughead] Hi, Dr. Whitley?
Yeah. Uh, it's Jughead Jones.
Sorry to bother you.
Upon further consideration,
I think I might be interested
in joining that group.
Making progress? Or are you
too distracted by my beauty?
I'm painting you as Diana
with Actaeon, the stag.
I'm sure you'll find
it satisfactory.
You have a unique talent.
I recognized it right away.
I had to have
an original Cheryl Blossom.
Once this painting is finished,
will you leave me in peace?
I haven't decided yet.
Oh, who cares?
After the dagger
my beloved Toni stuck
in my heart,
what does anything
else matter?
Go on.
She lured me
out of the house
where I feel safe
just to torture me
with her happiness.
It's cruel,
don't you think?
As an outsider, it seems to me
that fate has put an obstacle
before you, Ms. Blossom.
This Toni person's
happiness.
And you must either rise
above it, or...
Throw a little chaos at it.
[cell phone ringing]
Katy Keene?
How are you, girl?
[Katy] Oh, my God, girl,
I'm reeling.
So I'm having lunch
with Francois
in the Lacy's Cafe
and who strolls in
with the heiress to
the Spiffany's fortune?
Chad. Your Chad!
V, what the hell
is going on
with you two?
Well, clearly, he's trying
to make me jealous.
[Katy] Totally. Which means
I'm about to pour hot coffee
into his lap.
Perfect!
And I, Katy Keene,
will be fighting
fire with fire.
Wow, you boys made
some real progress.
Well done.
Oh, you know what
we should do?
Document our reno journey.
Let me get
between you two.
Come on.
Perfection. Now flex
for my followers.
[Archie chuckles softly]
[cell phones chiming]
Is yours from Cheryl too?
She wants us to gather
at the Whyte Wyrm for drinks.
Well, shall we, boys?
I'm buying.
[music playing]
You know, I thought
you had a thing
going with Betty.
It's just a casual thing.
Okay, but what
about Veronica?
The looks, the smiles,
the banter?
-Dude. She's married
to Jackson.
-[laughs]
Sarge juggling two ladies.
-[Toni] Cheryl,
what's this all about?
-I wanted to apologize
for being so cuckoo to you
earlier. Will you let me
have a do-over?
Of course, Cheryl. You know
your support means
the world to me.
So, will you let me host
a modest celebration
for you, Kevin and Fangs?
Okay, sure.
Amaze.
[clears throat]
[Cheryl] Hear ye, hear ye,
fellow friends and fiends.
Now that everyone
is swan-diving
into sad adulthood
with babies and marriages
and arthritis, etcetera,
I'm throwing a party.
One last hurrah
to celebrate our wild
misspent youth.
One final chance to recall
our reckless teenage selves.
I mean, who could forget
my iconic spin the bottle
parties of yore?
Aren't we a little
old for that?
Which is why this little fete
will be a key party.
You heard me right.
A classic American
and oh-so-adult round
of sexual switcheroo.
We'll draw keys and pair off.
And if the spirit moves you,
you are strongly encouraged
to act on any and all
animal impulses.
I'm texting you the deets now,
but bring keys for my bowl
and your well-oiled libidos.
[cell phones chiming]
Oh, my God, Polly!
When did you get back?
Is Mom... Does Mom...
No, no, you can't, you can't
be here. He'll find you.
-What? Who will?
-TBK.
-Wha... [gasps]
-[screams]
You shouldn't have
gone in alone.
[screaming]
Oh, my God.
[breathing heavily]
[typing on cell phone]
Good thing your mom still
leaves that spare key
under the gnome.
Beats climbing the trellis.
[mysterious music playing]
What's wrong?
Just a nightmare.
I don't want to talk about it,
though. I just want to forget.
Is that okay?
Yeah. Whatever you want.
Nice spread, sarge.
And you're up before me.
Not bad.
I actually haven't
gone to bed yet.
I was over at Betty's.
[sarcastically] Uh-huh.
-Shut up, Jackson.
-[chuckling]
I thought it was going
to be a booty call. Which I
was more than fine with.
But this time
it felt different.
It didn't feel great.
And if I'm being
completely honest,
you were right about
me and Veronica.
I mean, I would never
do anything about it...
but there's definitely
something still there.
So about Cheryl's party,
I was thinking.
It's like she said,
one last night of
carefree abandon, right?
So what if you brought one
of your hot trucker beaus
to spice things up?
I mean, you must have
a regular hookup, right?
Yeah, maybe.
Why would I
do that, Kevin?
We just closed
our relationship
like, yesterday.
Well, I've always been curious
about the company you keep
on the road,
and you never brought
a friend home per our rules.
Yeah, exactly.
So, why now?
What's going on with you?
Nothing. But before we become
husbands and fathers,
let's get every horn dog
impulse out of our systems
once and for all.
No strings, no guilt,
no secrets.
Betty. Oh, thank God.
Your sister. She called.
She's alive.
What? When?
Are you sure
it was Polly?
Yes, of course. I'm sure.
I know the sound
of my own daughter's voice.
What did she say? Walk me
through everything.
Okay. Um, the phone rang,
the landline. I picked up
and it was Polly.
She was hysterical.
She was talking
a mile a minute.
Um, I tried to keep her
on the phone, but she was...
she was scared.
Mom, are you sure it wasn't
just some crank?
Yes. She was scared.
Uh, she couldn't...
she couldn't see anything.
She was being kept somewhere.
It was dark. Everything was
cold and smooth, like metal.
Quite frankly, it sounded
like a spaceship.
In most of the
missing persons cases,
after two days, the chances
of a victim being found alive
are almost nothing,
Mom, Polly's been gone
for weeks.
No. You know
what? No.
My daughter is alive.
She called and she's
calling back.
The lights were as bright
as the sun hovering
a few hundred feet above me.
That was the last thing
I remember.
I woke up six hours later
by the side
of the Lost Highway.
No idea how I got there.
Thanks for
sharing that, Bill.
Mr. Jones.
Didn't you have an experience
similar to the one
that Bill described?
Uh, I was working late.
Diner was empty, jukebox
was playing, and then things
just kind of got crazy.
There were these lights
from outside the window.
They were so bright,
I should've been blinded.
But then I...
[sighs]
Were you missing time, too?
Yeah. I mean, I probably
just fell asleep.
Blackouts are fairly common
during supposed encounters
with extraterrestrials.
Have you ever
blacked out before?
[voice distorts]
[mysterious music playing]
[Tabitha] Jughead, are you...
You okay?
Uh, no, sorry.
This was a mistake.
Sorry.
Jughead.
Listen, I've been through
enough in my life to know
when someone hits a nerve
about something real.
I have blacked out. I just
didn't want to talk about it in
front of a group of strangers.
Okay, well,
it's just me now.
When did it happen?
I was in New York City.
I was going pretty hard,
I was drinking a lot.
Partying and doing drugs,
Jingle-Jangle, some
harder stuff, and I, uh...
I just did some things
I don't even remember.
I lost a lot of time.
Look, maybe you shouldn't go
to Cheryl's key party tonight.
I mean, we could go
to a movie instead or,
I don't know, hang out.
No, I think a night
at Cheryl's house with
some wanton debauchery
is precisely what I need
to forget about
all this alien crap.
[Archie] Veronica Lodge
spreading plaster.
[laughing]
Since my jewelry store
remains closed, tragically,
I'm happy to help.
Where's Eric,
by the way?
He ran down to the VA
to collect his disability.
Seems like a nice guy.
How'd he lose his leg?
On our last mission.
You'll never hear him
complain, though.
The strong
and silent type.
Sounds like somebody
I used to know
back in the day.
[both chuckle softly]
So how about Kevin and Fangs
and Toni's announcement?
Yeah.
Sort of makes you take stock
of your own life, doesn't it?
I'm starting to realize
all the things
I'm missing in my life.
And am I crazy,
or have you been
feeling the same way, too?
I'm not sure what
I'm feeling, Ronnie.
Things are changing. Fast.
What happens
if we get matched
at the key party?
I honestly don't know.
Is Chad coming?
Yes, he is.
As a matter of fact,
he should be on
the train right now.
Good.
I think that's
a good thing.
Yeah, me too.
["Everything
and Nothing" playing]
♪ You make me feel like
I am everything and nothing ♪
[speaking French]
[in English]
Keys, please.
-Where's the booze?
-Straight ahead, the bar's
in the gallery.
Hi.
Oh, good. Reginald, you got
my message. Welcome.
Where's Fangs?
Um, he is bringing a date,
I guess.
One of his
caszh hookups.
-Okay.
-It was my idea.
Okay. Why?
I don't know.
Maybe because I wanted to see
what he's given up for me
to get married.
Or maybe because I wanted to
see if he'd actually go through
with it and bring someone?
-Or maybe because I am
an emotional masochist.
-Oh, Kev.
♪ You get me fucked up
Save me with your loving ♪
♪ You make me feel like
I am everything and nothing ♪
Archie Andrews.
Chad Gekko. You made it.
Tell me, bro to bro. How is it
that in a podunk town
like Riverdale,
all the females are
so smoking hot?
♪ You make me feel like
I'm a million bucks ♪
Oh, my God. Fangs' date
is my cruising crush.
-[Fogarty] Hey, Betty.
-Hi, Fangs.
Betty, Kevin, this is
my friend Rick.
We, uh... well,
we both drive rigs
along the same route.
-It's nice to meet you both.
-[Betty] Nice to meet you.
Likewise. [chuckles awkwardly]
Anyone, uh, care
for a drink? I'm buying.
[Cheryl] I see we have
a surprise guest.
Yes. Seems like your ex's
rather handsome baby
daddy's brought a friend.
Oh, well, if he's
collateral damage,
then so be it.
Shall we gather everyone?
It's time for some
party games.
You're here. You came.
Which means you all feel it.
The impending crush
of true adulthood.
Our 30s. And soon after,
mortality. The big sleep.
Tonight's key party, then,
is a bold rejection of death.
So since none of us are
much for foreplay,
let's get into it, shall we?
Some quick house rules,
first and foremost.
Whatever happens tonight
must be 100% consensual.
And because we're all
a progressive, fluid,
inclusive group,
there will be no
redrawing of keys.
But the main rule is
you're allowed to do anything
you and your partner desire.
No one can
hold you accountable.
It's a free pass to do anything
you've ever wanted. Ever.
Are we clear?
Perf.
Who wants to go first?
Minerva, the bowl?
[suspenseful music playing]
I never like to be the second
person to do anything, so...
[upbeat music playing]
Well, you know what they say.
Everyone's a winner
in a bull market.
No, not with your ex.
Chadwick, don't be rude.
Those are the rules, okay?
Get your hands off her.
Excuse me?
She's my wife.
Exactly.
So why don't you show her
some respect?
No, no, no.
We're not going
to do this.
I'm not going to be some
passive heroine to be fought
over by two Tarzans.
Oh, look.
I got Chad's key.
Come on, babe.
We're leaving. Now.
Veto. That's breaking
the rules.
Call my lawyer, Cheryl.
Are you ready?
Fine.
Always good to knock a few
pieces off the chessboard.
-And married people are
supremely boring. Who's next?
-[Jughead] I'll go.
[exhales]
[grunts]
I'll take him home.
No one else is leaving without
picking a key.
I don't care how inebriated
Jughead is. He has to draw.
No, no. I want to. Let me,
let me do it.
Ah! Those are
my keys.
I guess it's meant to be.
Now can I take him home?
Whatever. Get this
American pickle the hell
out of my sight.
-Charming as ever, Cheryl.
-Come on, Jones.
Party's over.
You're next, soldier boy.
You mean me?
Get up here, GI Jackson.
Do your duty.
Those are mine.
How good are you
at following orders?
-No one better, ma'am.
-[laughing]
Before the pickings
get too slim.
-Toni?
-No. Guess again.
Actually, those are mine.
Are you sure that you're
down with this?
It's no fun if you leave
with the guy you came with.
-Right.
-Great.
No promises, but we'll see
what happens, stud.
On that note.
Imagine that.
Figured you'd end up
at our house one way
or another tonight.
Well, I'm still traumatized
from spin the bottle
sophomore year.
Cry me a river, cousin.
Perf. Bye!
Well, well.
Looks like fate
has brought us
together yet again.
-Antoinette.
-How did I know this
was going to happen?
Destiny has manifested.
I could feel it.
After making this night
all about you, I knew we
would end up together.
I don't believe
in fate, Cheryl.
But I do believe in
your ability to be
a master manipulator.
Hush, Toni.
And follow me, I have
a super-surprise.
A gift to you
and your little one.
A nursery.
Cheryl, what the hell
is this?
A place where
we can be together.
With or without
Kevin and Fangs.
Depending on whether
or not they survive
the night's festivities.
So is this why
you threw a key party?
So you could
hurt Kevin and Fangs?
To show you how fragile
some unions can be, yes.
And to show you
a path forward.
Don't you see? All these years,
I've been compelled to work
on restoring Thornhill without
ever truly understanding why.
But now,
I see it so clearly.
It was to make a sanctuary
for your child, if not, ours.
Cheryl, you've got
to be kidding me.
I'm not bringing my baby
into this house of horrors.
The last two months,
all you've been trying to do
is draw me out of Thornhill.
Yeah, and as my reward,
you're trying to trap me here
like you did at Thistlehouse
with your
two dead brothers?
Well, it's not
going to work.
I'm done trying to bring you
down from the mountain.
I'm done trying to have
a normal friendship with you.
That was my mistake.
I should have just left
our relationship where
it belongs. In the past.
Look, I'm sorry I led you on.
And I'm sorry I agreed
to this stupid party.
I really, really am.
So how long have you
and Fangs been together?
Coming up
on eight years.
-Open for the last three.
-Hm.
But that door's closing,
I hear.
Yeah, it's been discussed.
Well, I'm rooting
for you guys.
I mean, I don't really
know you, but Fogarty,
man, he's a keeper.
He'll make a great dad too.
Rick, did Fangs
ever mention me
when he was with you?
Not really.
Then again, it might have
been awkward, considering
the context, you know?
Yeah, yeah,
that makes sense.
[Tabitha] All right, okay.
Whoops, okay. [laughing]
Oh...
I think the world
turned sideways
for a minute there.
Yeah, it does
that sometimes.
Tabitha, you think I actually
had a close encounter or...
I don't know.
But I do think that there is
something from your past
that you are trying
to avoid dealing with.
You know something with those
blackouts back in New York.
Some friendly advice.
You should talk to someone,
like a therapist
who specializes
in cases of trauma.
[exhales sharply]
Yeah, maybe you're right.
But, for tonight...
just...
sleep.
[snoring]
All right.
[door closes]
-You're home.
-Mmm-hmm, yeah.
Turns out Reggie
is 100% straight.
-Who'd you
get paired with?
-Rick.
Mmm.
Nothing happened, but...
Fangs,
I gotta tell you something.
I love you so much,
but I'm not ready
to get married.
[Fogarty] What?
Why?
Because you don't
want to give up
cruising in the woods.
Okay, so don't,
that's fine.
It's not about
the woods.
Uh, it's about me.
Where I'm at.
Where you're at.
[laughs sarcastically]
What about Toni?
Hmm?
What about the fact
that we're having
a baby together?
I'm not sure yet.
Kevin, why are you
imploding us?
Especially when you pushed
for all of this. Being open,
starting a family,
getting married.
Yeah, it's messed up.
[Kevin] I know, I know.
I'm so messed up.
I'm, I'm...
I'm just sorry.
I'm sorry.
-[Betty] Here we are.
-[door slams]
With a free pass
to do whatever we want.
So, why aren't we?
I think 'cause we're
right on the edge.
That's what
it feels like, yeah.
Betty,
before we do anything,
I have to be honest
with you.
I, uh...
I still have feelings
for Veronica.
I shouldn't, but I do.
Shouldn't?
Archie, you and I
should make sense.
The all-American boy,
the girl next door.
But deep in our cores,
we are such different people.
And getting closer to you,
the one thing I know is that
I don't want my darkness
to overtake you.
Betty.
And don't
get me wrong.
It's been saving my sanity
to escape with you.
But what's coming next with
my mom and Polly is probably
going to be the darkest thing
I've ever faced.
So, you get to face
whatever's coming alone?
-No way.
-No
[sniffles]
Not alone.
Still with you,
as a friend,
because that's what
I think I'm going to need.
More than a lover,
more than an escape.
A friend.
A window of light
in the dark.
And that's what I'll be.
Did you invite
me here specifically
to make me jealous?
-To humiliate me?
-[sighs] Neither.
But I really did think it was
time to stop playing games,
and avoiding the truth.
As ill-advised as Cheryl's
party was tonight,
it confirmed something
I've been feeling
for a really long time, Chad.
[suspenseful music playing]
[intense music playing]
[panting]
[Minerva] It's sublime, Cheryl.
Thank you, Minerva.
Considering so much
of my life is sheer ugliness,
I'm relieved
-you think so.
-Oh, Cheryl...
You made me beautiful
because you're beautiful.
No, I'm not.
I'm repulsive.
No. Cheryl,
you are...
You're gorgeous.
[pleasant music playing]
Hey.
I went by your house, but Eric
told me you were on duty the
next couple of nights, so...
Yeah. Serves me right
for starting a fire department.
Archie...
Chad and I are
getting a divorce.
He's on his way
back to New York for good.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't be.
I think,
in my heart of hearts,
I knew it had to happen.
You know, I was devastated
when I found out
you were married.
But that was nothing
like the pain I felt
seeing you unhappy.
More than anything,
Ronnie, I just...
I want you to be happy.
Good.
Because I might know
a way that you can
help me with that.
Wait, I...
I need to tell
you something.
Betty and I,
we didn't hook up after
the key party, but we...
we have hooked up a few times
since we got back to Riverdale.
I wondered about that.
What was it? Just two
lost lonely souls
-looking for a connection?
-Something like that.
We're just friends
is the truth.
I thought you should know.
The way I see it,
the past is in the past.
I'm only interested in
what we want.
Now. In the present.
♪ Carry me over
♪ Carry me through the night
♪ I need your hand
♪ To pull me through the fire
♪ Hold me tight
[phone ringing]
-Hello.
-This is a collect call
for Alice Cooper.
Yes. I'll accept
the charges.
[Polly] Mom, are you there?
-Polly.
-Betty, you have
to help me.
I'm at some pay phone
in the middle of nowhere.
-Where? Where are you?
-I don't know.
I ran as fast as I could,
you have to come get me.
-I'm on the highway.
-The Lonely Highway?
-Yeah. Yes, it looks like it.
-What?
[Betty]
Here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna hang up,
you're gonna call me back on my cell, okay? Mom and I are about to get in the car.
[Polly] Okay, but hurry.
They're coming.
Wait, there.
There, Betty.
[suspenseful music playing]
Polly!
[music intensifies]