Well, Jug,
you ever think we'd have
a night before the first day
of school again.
No, not in a million years.
Cramming to finish this book
my students were assigned
for summer reading.
Of Mice and Men.
Feel like I'm living
The Twilight Zone.
Well, I'm gonna hit the sack.
Big day tomorrow.
On behalf of Lennie,
George and myself,
good night, sweet prince.
You know after all these years,
it's still kind of adorable
to witness your
back-to-school jitters.
Well, I'd be there already
if I wasn't waiting
on our house diva.
You tell Queen T my truck
is leaving without her.
This outfit is a masterpiece
that can't be rushed,
as we all know.
And we're taking my motorcycle.
["Back to School Again"
playing]
♪ Gettin' lots of action
And a lots of fun ♪
♪ Scorin' like a bandit
'Til the bubble burst ♪
Ms. Topaz, Mr. Keller,
nice to see you.
Good morning, Waldo.
I'll never get used to that.
♪ All summer long
I was happy and free ♪
♪ Save my soul ♪
♪ The board of education... ♪
[bell ringing]
♪ I gotta go back, back
Back to school again ♪
♪ You won't find me
'Til the clock strikes three ♪
♪ I'm gonna be
There 'til then ♪
♪ I gotta go back, back
Back to school again... ♪
I thought economics class
was just for seniors.
Um, some of us are auditing.
Hm.
Well, as long as you're
taking it seriously.
We will absolutely talk about
my experiences overseas,
but the RROTC's focus
is on physical fitness,
and military history.
So I'll ask again,
what year was the
United States Army founded?
So this semester
our main project in Shop Class
will be taking apart
this classic car.
A 1954 Crestline
and putting it back together.
Any questions
before we get started?
Wasn't your dad
like the Black Hood?
He was.
As a matter of fact,
he taught me everything
I know about cars.
So, any relevant questions?
[Jughead] Who did
the summer reading?
Who can tell me what it was?
This is gonna be great.
[Hiram] By all rights,
that school
should be shut down.
Instead, I'm told
there are over
100 students enrolled.
What do you care, Mr. Lodge?
You got what you wanted.
Riverdale doesn't even exist
since you unincorporated it.
Reggie, a high school
offers hope,
and people are sentimental
about Riverdale High
for reasons that elude me.
And as long as it remains open,
there's a slight chance
the town will grow
back around it like a weed.
And that
is bad for our business.
I hear you.
So what are you thinking, boss?
As you can see,
this used to be a video store
back in the day,
but with a little TLC,
it'll be the perfect spot
for my new jewelry store.
I cut my teeth
in the Diamond District
as you know, Smithers.
I think I could bring
a little Manhattan magic
to this town
formerly known as Riverdale
in the form of exquisitely
high end bling.
And will Mr. Gekko, be involved
in this business enterprise?
I haven't decided yet.
He knows I'm in Riverdale,
teaching temporarily,
but the permanence
of opening a shop,
might send him spiraling.
Well, Miss Cooper...
how was the first day?
Well, they're terrified of me.
Being that I'm the daughter
of the Black Hood and all.
Oof. That sucks.
Yeah. On top of which I can't
stop thinking about Polly.
Didn't your mom say
she does this sometimes?
Takes off for a couple days
then reappears.
Yeah, that's why
I'm trying not to panic.
Well, in the meantime,
maybe I can distract you.
Tonight, my new roommate's
working at Pop's.
It's too risky.
And it's not like
we can go to my house
-with my mom and the twins.
-We're in our 20s.
It's supposed to be easier
to find places to hookup
not harder.
Wait. I actually think
I have a crazy idea.
[Tabitha] It is dead
as a doornail in here, Jones.
If you wanna write,
by all means.
At least until
we get some customers.
You know, I was actually
kind of hoping I could
interview you for my book.
Me?
-Why? What's your book?
-It's about Riverdale.
People who live here.
Portrait of a small town
type of thing.
Okay.
What do you wanna know?
You left a six figure
a year job in Chicago
to come run Pop's?
You must have had every CEO
offer that you wanted.
Or I could become the CEO
of my family business
and take everything I learned
at my fancy schools
and invest it
in something meaningful.
I am not
playing around with Pop's.
I put in
that gas pump out front
to attract truckers
driving the night shift.
I have ideas for merchandising,
franchising.
[doorbell jingles]
Just great.
Wait, aren't you,
uh, one of our teachers?
Yeah, I am.
Why don't you guys take a seat?
I'll get the menus.
["Mine" playing]
♪ Oh, you look so precious
when you smile ♪
♪ Hit it from the back and
drive you wild ♪
♪ Girl, I lose myself up
in those eye-eye-eye-eyes ♪
♪ I just had to let you know
you're mine ♪
♪ Hands on your body
I don't wanna waste no time ♪
♪ Feels like forever even
if forever's tonight ♪
♪ Just lay with me ♪
[fire alarm blaring]
What the hell?
[gasps]
Archie, get the hose.
[Toni] Thank God you were...
Wait, what did you say
you were doing again?
Well, Luckily, I was out, uh...
Night jogging
and I heard the alarm go off.
And when I ran over,
I saw some Stonewall Prep
students rushing off,
some real bruisers.
Probably football players.
The Stonewall Stallions,
Hiram's team.
He sponsors them,
and in return,
they do odd jobs for him.
Like setting
our school on fire?
I could try arresting them,
but Hiram'll have them out
in bail within the hour.
'Cause Hiram's got the DA
in his back pocket.
That's part of it
and the other part is--
Stonewall Prep Stallions
are the county's
best football team.
The only ones who win games.
As much trouble as they cause,
they're the only thing
people have to root for
these days.
Bulldogs, Bulldog Pride
are things of the past.
They're star football players.
So what?
They can't be above the law.
Who's their Coach?
-Hiram?
-Not quite.
[whistle blowing]
Very good, boys.
Quick feet. Quick feet.
What's up, Andrews?
Coming to watch
a championship squad in action?
Reggie, you scumbag.
Pack of your boys
paid Riverdale High
a visit last night.
Yeah, I heard
you're having some trouble.
Damn, you're not even
denying it.
Why would I?
Unless there's proof.
You send your squad
to my school again
and I'll give you a beat down
like you've never had.
As for you boys,
I'm looking forward to kicking
your asses on the field.
Wow!
Inspired.
Yes, it's true.
I work at Pop's.
I would love to say that
working at Riverdale High
paid a livable wage,
but alas,
I had to take a second job.
But aren't you supposed
to be some kind of like
big time writer?
The only writing
I wanna talk about today
Of Mice and Men.
So can anyone tell me
what this book's about?
Okay.
Plan B. Pop quiz.
Hand these out.
Supply and demand
is the foundational principle
of economics.
So I'm going to make sure
that you all--
Special delivery
for Miss Gekko.
Chad, what are you doing here?
Surprising my wife.
But I'm in the middle
of a class.
I'll just wait
quietly at the back.
[Veronica exhales]
[Archie] Mr. Weatherbee.
Uh, Waldo.
I want to bring
Bulldog football
back to Riverdale High
as a coach,
I think having a football team
would be huge for school pride
and would help bring
what's left of this town
back together.
You know where
we're at financially.
I'll get the money somehow.
We even have enough players?
I only need eleven.
All right, Mr. Andrews.
Let's see what you can do.
[Chadwick] As you can imagine,
my wife tells this guy
exactly where he can
stick his designer loafers.
[all laughing]
Archie, This is Chadwick,
my husband.
He surprised me with a visit...
[Kevin] ...and some
delicious cupcakes.
[Chadwick] So you're
the famous Archie.
Nice to meet you.
[Toni] Well, we've survived
two days of the school year.
How about we
celebrate tonight?
It's karaoke Tuesday
at the Whyte Wyrm.
Obviously, I'll be
defying gravity.
As long as I can
get a vodka tonic,
I will be watching.
I don't know if we...
That sounds good.
[surprised] What?
You hate karaoke.
[Chadwick] What's that
expression, uh, when in Rome,
embarrass yourself
in front of a group
of total strangers?
[Toni] Betty, do you
have a minute?
Sure. What's up?
Earlier, Kevin mentioned
that your sister's missing.
Yeah. Why? Have you
heard something?
Well, you know how Fangs
and some of the other Serpents
are truckers now?
Yeah.
Well, I asked around,
and some of the guys
have occasionally
seen Polly
hanging out
at this sketchy truck stop
right off
the Lonely Highway.
[Betty] Doing what?
Dealing for the Ghoulies
or hooking up with truckers.
[Betty sighs] Or both.
[Toni sighs] Yeah.
Well, sadly,
Polly's not the only
young woman in Riverdale
making a living that way.
Fangs said that
some of the truckers
arrange meetings
with these women
by posting on Nedslist.
I don't know
if Polly has an account.
Yeah, Okay.
Thank you, Toni.
I'll look into it.
Do you know where exactly
this truck stop is?
The thing is,
Miss Blossom,
the men have been
threatening to quit.
[Cheryl] Under
no circumstances.
Constant hammering of nails
and buzzing of saws
is the only thing that quiets
my troubled soul.
Tell your brutes
they'll get their blood money
and a bonus
for their patience.
Now be gone from my sight.
Thanks to that
charitable donation
Toni squeezed out of me,
the Blossom coffers
are empty, Nana.
It's time
for Operation Goldfinch.
Call Krespy's
and have him send
an appraiser over
whilst I finish my copy
of this portrait of Jay-Jay.
[sighs] And pray my subterfuge
will save us
from financial ruin.
[Betty] According to my mom,
Polly doesn't have a laptop,
-but I asked the twins...
-[Kevin sighs]
...and they said,
sometimes, she uses theirs.
So Polly doesn't have
a Nedslist account.
But Patty does.
[Kevin] Oh, my God.
Check sent messages.
Who was the last person
she contacted?
Someone named
"TruckerBoy69".
And apparently,
they arranged to meet up
the night she disappeared.
Okay, so, either
he knows something,
or he did something.
Send him a message
asking to get together again.
[Betty typing]
Okay. Sent.
Okay. Now we just wait,
I guess.
Can we karaoke
while we wait?
[all] Cheers!
[rock music playing]
[dart thuds]
By the way, Jones,
I have the next subject
for your book.
[Tabitha] A real character.
Oh, yeah? Who's that?
Old Man Dreyfus.
Lives on and runs a junk yard
off the Lonely Highway.
He came in today
for a plate of pork chops
and I asked if you could
interview him for your book.
He said yes.
Did you get his number?
Oh, no. [laughs]
Dreyfus does not have a phone,
but I do have
his address, though.
Okay, what's his story?
Oh, you've gotta
ask him about "The Mothman."
-The Mothman?
-[Tabitha] Mmm-hmm.
[Toni on mic]
All right, all right!
We've got a special treat
for you guys.
She used to
own this place
back in the day.
So let's give an extra
loud Whyte Wyrm welcome
to Veronica Lodge!
-[people cheering]
-She probably
forgot it's Gekko now.
All good. Knock 'em
dead, babe.
[Veronica] Thanks.
[guitar music
playing "Shallow"]
♪ Tell me something, boy ♪
♪ Aren't you tired
Trying to fill that void? ♪
♪ Or do you need more? ♪
♪ Is there something else
You're searching for? ♪
[Chadwick singing]
♪ Tell me something, girl ♪
[people cheering]
♪ Are you happy
In this modern world? ♪
♪ Or do you need more? ♪
♪ Ain't it hard
Keeping it so hardcore? ♪
♪ I'm off the deep end
Watch as I dive in ♪
♪ I'll never leave the ground ♪
♪ Crash through the surface
Where they can't hurt us ♪
♪ We're far
From the shallow now ♪
♪ In the sha-ha, shallow ♪
♪ In the sha-ha
Sha-la-la-la-low ♪
♪ In the sha-ha, shallow ♪
♪ We're far
From the shallow now ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Whoah ♪
♪ In the sha-ha, shallow ♪
♪ In the sha-ha
Sha-la-la-la-low ♪
♪ In the sha-ha, shallow ♪
♪ We're far
From the shallow now ♪
[crowd cheering and applauding]
Good morning, lover.
Good morning, Ms. Gekko.
Man, I haven't slept
that well since...
...forever.
I know. Same.
It's fun having you here, Chad.
So...
Why don't I stay
in Riverdale for a few days?
What do you think?
I think that would be nice.
Mm-hmm.
[Archie] Congratulations.
You are the newest recruits
to Riverdale High's
legendary football program,
which will fulfill
your physical education
requirements for this year.
-[Archie] All good?
-[students in unison]
Sir, yes, sir!
Six down, five to go.
Who here wants
to play football
for the Bulldogs?
Welcome aboard.
And that's eight.
I'm looking
for football players.
No previous
experience required.
I just need
a few more bruisers.
That's ten.
Who here wants
to play football
for the Bulldogs?
Awesome.
One more
is all I needed.
What's your name, bro?
I'm Britta.
Is that cool?
As long as you don't mind
playing both sides
of the ball, Britta,
you complete my team.
Now I just need funding.
How much funding?
Twenty thousand.
There's gotta be
some kind of sports budget.
There is, but the little money
that's available
is already been earmarked
for something else.
What about Cheryl?
Can you ask her?
No way.
I already called in
my one favor.
Nobody's stopping you.
[Cheryl] You need more money
from me, you say?
Yes, for the football team.
Well, I've already
done my part for the school
and at a great
personal cost.
Cheryl, I just thought...
[sighs] given the fact
your brother was a Bulldog,
that you might want
to honor him.
How dare you
play my brother
as if he were
a red king card, Archie?
[Cheryl] Be gone!
And never darken the halls
of Thornhill again.
Leave!
When did the Krespy's
appraiser say he was
coming again, Nana?
Oh, she, dear. Minerva Marble,
and, um, tomorrow, she said.
Truckrboy69
responded.
He said, "So good to hear
from you, Patty.
I was afraid you were
still mad at me.
How's tonight?"
-Mad about what?
-That's exactly what
I'm going to find out
when you and I go
stakeout the truck stop,
he suggested, right off
exit 42.
[owl hooting]
Hi, there. I'm Jughead Jones.
I work at Pops with
Tabitha Tate.
She told me that you'd be
that you'd be willing to tell
me the story about the, uh,
Mothmen.
[Dreyfuss] About thirty,
forty years ago, me
and some buddies got hired
to dig out a collapsed
mine not far off
the Lonely Highway.
One night, we went to bed.
The next morning when we
woke up, one of the guys,
Ramos was missing.
We worked he whole day
but Ramos never showed.
Until the next morning
when Ramos was back,
but Raymond was missing.
Ramos told us that some
Mothmen had taken him
up in their ship,
and now they had Raymond.
Did you believe him?
Not at first.
[Dreyfuss] But the next
morning, Raymond
was back.
But Arnold was missing.
And sure enough, Raymond
said the Mothmen had
taken him up in their ship.
Now when you see Mothmen,
are you talking...
Aliens, Angels, Mothmen,
call 'em whatever you like.
They live in the woods
and the caves off
the Lonely Highway.
Mr. Dreyfuss, I've lived
in Riverdale almost my
whole life.
Why have I never heard
of the Mothmen before?
There were some articles
back in the day. Ask around.
Some people remember.
Well, aren't you worried
that they're gonna come back
for you living out here
all by yourself?
[Dreyfuss] I'm not afraid.
I'm hopin'.
I'm hopin' they come back
for me.
I want to go up in their
ship like the others.
[engine whirring]
This is definitely
the place.
[Betty] Franview Freight Lines.
That's him in the blue rig.
-That's truckerboy69.
-What? Betty, are you sure?
[door opens]
You're not Patty.
No, I'm her sister
and I'm with the FBI.
You're coming with me.
I keep saying I didn't
do anything wrong.
You arranged to meet
my sister at that truck stop.
And that's the last time
anyone's seen her.
Look, I did meet Patty
three nights ago.
She'd scored some
Jingle-Jangle
and reached out.
-We met up at
the truck stop.
-And then what?
I told her that we should
take a drive
to clear her mind.
She was down with that plan,
but about a half a mile up
the highway, she freaked.
Jumped out of the truck,
started running.
I tried to get her back
in my cab, but she
wouldn't listen.
She just kept running.
That's the last time
I saw her.
Honest to God.
So you just left her there
on the side of the road.
I didn't have a choice.
Patty was scared.
I didn't want to make it worse.
What part of the highway?
I need you to be very specific.
Hey, honey. What's going on?
Why are you getting home
so late?
It's about Polly, mom.
I have a lead
I need your help with.
But you should sit down.
[bell ringing]
Look, I'm sorry, team.
The thing is, I should've got
my ducks in a row first
-and secured the funding.
-And the school really can't
give us any money at all?
No. There's no funding
for sports, clubs, extra...
[music playing]
[cheering]
Toni, since when are
the Vixens back?
Since I made it a priority
in the budget last year?
There isn't even a sports thing
for them to cheer for.
Uh, get over yourself Archie.
The Vixens are a sports team,
and this year we're gonna be
competing against
other cheer squads.
I'm not even sure I'll manage
to do that.
Forget the school.
Isn't there anyone else
who could sponsor the Bulldogs?
It's Doris Bell.
You told me to keep you
apprised of goings on at
the school.
Well, there's something
I think you should know.
I see.
Thanks, Miss Bell.
So sorry for the interruption,
Miss Marble.
How are you finding that
portrait of my beloved brother?
I mean, figurative is back in
vogue, and the artist who
painted your brother
was chosen for next year's
Venice Biennale.
I believe this portrait
could easily fetch
-a quarter of a million dollars
at auction.
-And worth every penny.
I wonder...
might I get to keep
my JJ for
one more night so we can say
our proper ta-tas?
I understand. I'm staying at
the Five Seasons in town
overnight,
but I'll be around
first thing in the morning.
Even better, I'll have my men
pack it up and deliver it to
your hotel.
Well, Miss Blossom, it was a
pleasure dealing with you.
Should you decide to sell
any other items in your
collection, do let me know.
I will indeed, Miss Marble.
Now that she has authenticated
our original,
we can swap in your
perfect copy and Marble
shall be none the wiser.
What's the matter, child?
Oh, nothing. You know...
Just some upsetting news from
Riverdale High.
I'll be fine.
Betty.
Oh, my God.
[gasping]
These are her things.
These are Polly's things.
[Jughead] More coffee, champ?
Yeah, sure. Thanks, Jug.
How goes it with the Bulldogs?
It doesn't.
The kids don't have
any equipment.
They can't afford
And the school doesn't have
any money.
Well, if you promise to never
bring up
the epic highs and lows
of high school football again,
I can ask Tabitha
if she's willing to sponsor
the team.
That can't hurt.
There is one more person
I can ask.
Veronica.
But that would be weird, right?
I just interviewed a guy who
wants to be abducted by
Mothman aliens.
I think weird is relative.
I say go for it.
Embrace the weird.
What do you think,
Chad?
I know it's a tad sleazy
at the moment,
but it's the perfect spot
for a jewelry store.
Good foot traffic,
close to SoDale.
Only bad thing is it's not in
New York. But maybe that's
the whole point, huh?
Cards on the table, Chadwick.
Being back in Riverdale,
seeing my friends,
working on a new business,
it's been good for my soul.
So we would have a place in the
city and a place in Riverdale
where I'd be welcome?
Yes, but I need your support
on this Chad, and love.
You have it.
Just curious.
Are we going to buy a new house
or stay at the Pembrooke?
Bite your tongue.
I'm never leaving
that apartment, but it could do
with a remodel.
It's time for a change,
starting with a clean slate.
What happened to her Betty?
What happened to Polly out on
that highway?
I don't know, Mom.
But I do know one thing,
if that creepy guy in jail had
hurt Polly,
he wouldn't have told us
exactly where to go.
So we have nothing.
We have no leads.
We have...
She could be anywhere.
We didn't find Polly's
cell phone,
so we can trace it
through the phone company.
Or if they can't do it,
maybe the FBI can.
[sobbing] And if not?
We wait...
and we hope.
[Chadwick] So I need to be
back in the city
on Monday, the 19th.
That's fine. We have your
niece's birthday party
that weekend.
So Mondays through Thursdays,
I'm in the city, then here
every other weekend.
And I'll be in New York
[chuckles]
You know, there is one other
option that your father,
of all people,
suggested. Um, I could move
to Riverdale full time
and help him manage the
SoDale properties.
You're in finance,
not real estate.
And wait, have you and
my father been talking
behind my back?
[knock on door]
-Archie.
-Hey, Veronica.
-Sorry to come by unannounced.
-Don't be. Come in.
Archie, this is unexpected.
Chad. Hey, you're still here.
Um, listen, the thing is,
I'm restarting
the football team at
Riverdale High, and there's no
budget for anything.
Say no more.
As a former Vixen, I made an
oath to always support my
beloved Bulldogs.
I will absolutely cover
the startup costs.
Thank you, Veronica.
And I promise I'll pay you back
one hundred percent.
You mean, pay us back
Of course.
Pay you guys back.
Thank you, Chad.
You know, actually,
now I think about it.
You're a vet, a proud guy.
You don't want to be taking
handouts, do you?
So how's this for an idea?
Instead of us loaning you
the money,
what if you renovate
our apartment?
-This apartment.
-Babe, what are you
talking about?
We help out Archie's team,
he does this job for us and
gets paid.
I'm sure Archie has
a million other things,
-he's got to be doing
right now.
-[Archie] No, it's fine.
I definitely don't want
to be taking handouts.
I'll call some of my dad's
old crew and see if any of them
can help out.
Awesome-sauce.
-Thanks again, Ronnie.
-Of course. I'll see you at
school tomorrow.
Okay. What the hell was that?
He's my friend.
A guy like that, I'm sure he'd
rather do a little work than
crawl to you for charity.
You didn't have to be
such a dick about it.
Excuse me?
Have I not been accommodating
to your every whim since
I've been here?
I've been nice to your friends.
I even sang karaoke.
I didn't realize
those were such chores for you.
They weren't.
I wanted to do them for you.
If I came across dickish
with Archie,
um, I'm sorry, but it won't
happen again, okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
What's for dinner?
-Can we get Pop's take out?
-Ugh, I don't think
I can handle
another greasy burger and
onion rings.
Let's go out.
There's this Italian place
that your dad mentioned.
Mia's?
Sure. Let's go to Mia's.
Are you working on your
Mothmen chronicles?
It is so bizarre, Tabitha.
So I ended up
talking to old man Dreyfus,
and he did tell me the names of
the people that he used to
work with.
All his buddies from back in
the day.
-Tracked them down just so I
could corroborate his story.
-Uh-huh?
Get this.
They're all dead.
Couldn't that just be
a coincidence because
they're old?
Well, curiously,
they all died from cancer.
And, yeah, that could be a
coincidence, but maybe,
just maybe,
they were all exposed to the
same radiation on
the spaceship. Hm?
Uh, is that what happens when
you go aboard a spaceship?
Oh, I have no idea.
But it makes a great story.
What's the next step?
Dreyfus said that some articles
were produced after their
close encounter,
so just tracking those
ones down.
I'm in.
If you want some help,
unless you're like
the lone wolf type or whatever.
Sure.
More the merrier.
[knock on door]
-Betty.
-Hey.
-Is Chuck at home?
-No, he's working.
My mom and I are waiting
to hear something.
Anything about Polly and she's
driving me crazy.
Yeah. I'm feeling pretty crazy
and frustrated myself.
Let's go upstairs.
[sighs]
[cell phone ringing]
-Is that me?
-It's me, I think.
Yeah, it's my friend, Todd
from the academy.
It's probably about
Polly's phone.
I should go, but this...
was really nice.
-What's this?
-Chad.
Upon reflection, I think
we need to pump the brakes.
Back in New York,
I had the instinct
that we should take some time
to be by ourselves.
And as fun as the last few days
have been,
-I still think we need a break.
-Because of Archie?
No, Chad. Because of me.
Because I need real time and
space to figure out
if I'm a Pop's girl or
a Mia's girl or both.
It's not gonna be a problem,
is it?
Not at all.
Just let me know
when you're ready to talk.
Cheryl.
Hi, Toni.
I was going to give you a call
and then I thought, mmm no.
Stealing my Vixens warrants
a visit in person.
You're playing
a very dangerous game, Topaz.
All right. You've each been
assigned a locker.
That's to go along with your
new cleats, your new uniform
and pads.
I'm also psyched to announce
our generous sponsor
for all this stuff
and other Bulldog expenses
is Veronica Gekko.
Lodge, actually.
Veronica Lodge.
Okay. Well, you heard the lady.
Let's give Veronica Lodge
a round of applause.
[all applauding]
You asked me to call if
anything interesting or
important happens.
Well, you should know what's
going on in the boys
locker room right now.
I see.
Well, thank you, Miss Bell.
Your information is, as always,
very much appreciated.
We'll be in touch.
You see, now I'm angry.
-What happened?
-Archie Andrews made good
on his promise to you
and started a football team...
with my daughter's money.
So maybe this time,
we pay him a visit.
I heard from my friend
Todd at the FBI.
He traced the call to
somewhere in this region.
Swedlow Swamp?
I don't understand.
What was Polly doing there?
And how on earth are we going
to find her? That's acres and
acres of marsh land.
We'll just have to keep calling
her cell phone until we
hear it ring.
[Kevin] Assuming it's
still charged.
We've been out here for hours.
We're freezing.
-Maybe we should pick it up--
-Shh.
I hear something.
Let's split up.
Guys, guys over here.
[Jughead] Archie,
there's a fire!
It's on the back porch, too.