Here you go, Betty.
- These are on the house.
- Thank you, Fangs.
Thank you guys for rallying.
Of course.
How are you holding up, Bee?
As good as I can be, I guess.
How are the twins?
They're okay, surprisingly.
Cheryl volunteered
to take them for a few days.
They have been asking
about their mom though.
And I told them
that she's somewhere beautiful
and close by.
We hung up a hummingbird feeder
in the rose garden,
and they wait for their mommy to visit it.
Beautiful, Cheryl.
- How's your mom?
- She's not good, Jug.
She won't leave the house.
She's listening
to this Next to Normal cast album
on repeat.
What's Next to Normal?
It's a Broadway musical
that she took Polly and I to see...
one year for Mother's Day in the city.
What's it about?
This family.
To be honest, watching it,
it felt like it could have been...
about us.
The mom, she wants this normal...
perfect family.
But she's lying to herself.
She and her husband don't love
each other anymore.
She fights with her daughter a lot.
And one of her kids is... dead.
- Jeez, Betty.
- It's actually a really beautiful show.
And we had the best day.
Just the three of us
walking around New York.
So your mom is just listening
to this album?
Over and over again.
I don't even know
what she's thinking or feeling.
Mom.
- The record was skipping.
- I, uh...
I'm just tired. That's all.
I'm gonna go take a nap.
Okay. I'm gonna clean up down here.
Poor Betty and Alice. It's heartbreaking.
Yeah.
What can we do for them?
I think we're just on standby
for whatever they need.
In the meantime,
Archie, I've been thinking.
Those seven years
we lost after graduation...
- I don't wanna lose any more.
- Yeah, me neither.
So, what do you think
about us moving in together?
Wow, seriously?
I think it's an amazing idea.
I'm surprised you're okay
with living with roommates.
Oh, I just assumed
we'd live here at The Pembrooke.
My house has a little more room.
We'd be able to grow into it.
All right, yeah.
Let's give it a go, lover.
Waldo, what's going on?
We have a bit of a situation
with one of our students, Britta Beach.
Oh, no, is she okay?
Oh, she's fine.
But our janitor, Mr. Poppins,
found her in a closet under the stairwell.
- She's been living there.
- Well, sadly, I can guess why.
- Where is she now?
- In the cafeteria, getting hot breakfast.
- Can you help?
- Of course.
And I know who to call.
Britta, this is a friend, Miss Weiss.
She's a social worker like me.
You wanna tell us what's been going on?
My parents basically kicked me out.
They blamed me getting kidnapped
by those crazy brothers
on my deviant gay lifestyle.
Britta, there's nothing deviant
about you or your identity.
Matter of fact, you're perfect.
And we support you.
I have a full house of foster kids,
and I'm happy
to offer you a place to sleep,
anything else you might need,
at least for a few nights.
It'll give me more time to find you
a permanent, safe and loving home.
Thank you, Miss Topaz.
Hey, Mom. I'm gonna go for a hike.
Do you wanna come with me?
I don't think so, honey.
Mom.
I know you're grieving,
but you need to find a way to move on.
Do you remember our ski trip
to the Catskill Mountains?
You and Polly didn't wanna
come off the bunny hill.
I know you miss Polly, Mom.
We both do.
It's not... just that. It's...
Those are all of the kitchen updates
I've made since I took over.
Anyway, uh, Mom and Dad,
I thought it would be nice for us
to have dinner at Pop's tomorrow night.
For Mother's Day?
No, darling, we made reservations
at a nice Italian restaurant.
Um... Cucina Sacasa.
You really don't want to eat at Pop's
while you're here?
Dad, you practically grew up
in this place.
- And I couldn't get away fast enough.
- Okay.
Cucina Sacasa sounds perfect.
Jones, does that work for you?
Yeah, sure. That sounds great.
Great.
And, uh, why would your busboy come
to dinner with us?
Oh, because he's also my boyfriend, Dad.
So, uh... your parents are
pretty intense, huh?
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
And I'm your boyfriend now?
It would be great
to have a buffer at dinner.
Will you do it?
Pretend to be your boyfriend? Yeah, sure.
You know, if you want, you could...
You could just ask me
to be your real boyfriend.
Jughead, as you know,
that is an intriguing possibility to me,
but your timing couldn't be less perfect.
Riverdale and the rest of the world
are in a perpetual state of crisis.
There's no such thing as perfect timing.
Unbelievable.
Mom, where did the piano come from?
I ordered it on Glamazon.
Remember when I gave you girls lessons?
You loved them so much.
Oh, Mom, Archie and Veronica
invited us over for dinner tonight.
What if we went? It's just next door.
No, I'm cooking tonight.
Polly's favorite. Meatloaf.
For all of us. Will you join?
Sure. I just have
to go pick something up first.
Wow, Ronnie, this looks amazing.
It's chicken cordon bleu.
Remember, boys, when Ina Garten tells you
to keep your rolls tight, you listen.
Ina Garten, the Barefoot Contessa?
- Fire off Main.
- I'll grab the keys.
- I'm so sorry, babe.
- No apologies, Superstud.
- Duty calls, city needs you.
- We'll nuke it up when we get back.
Don't wait up, okay?
Sir, yes, sir.
- I'll eat in the garage.
- Sounds good.
Mom, what is this?
Oh, Betty, perfect timing.
I know I went a little overboard,
but isn't this so nice?
All of us together around one table again?
Mom, stop.
You are freaking me out.
Tell me, is your plan to just never leave
the house ever again?
Why would I?
I have everything I need right here.
All of my children.
Mom.
You know Charles
and Polly aren't really here, right?
- What's that?
- Polly's ashes.
I thought having them
might bring you comfort or closure.
That can't be right.
I'm sitting right here.
Tell Betty to stop being such a brat.
Hey.
I have an idea.
Why don't you and I go into the city?
See a Broadway show?
That'd be really good for you.
For both of us.
- Yeah, I'd like that.
- Okay.
Thank you, honey.
Didn't hear you come in last night,
Mr. Inferno.
Oh, my God, redacted.
Hey, Jug, pass me a loofah.
- Um, where's Archie?
- He slept at the station,
so the guys could go home
and take a power nap, clean up.
Guy's a prince, right?
So they all left you.
All your congregants.
It was bound to happen.
Forget your cruelty, Mother. I'm praying.
Yes, to your false gods.
You said my ministry was a scam
and that yours was genuine,
when, really, it was the pathetic attempt
of a narcissist to prop herself up.
Enough!
My ministry is real.
My God is Gaia.
And now I see plainly,
my devil, Mother, is you.
An exorcism, nightmare child? That's rich.
Toodle-oo.
Hey, by the way,
thanks for helping me cram
for the Series 7 exam, Ronnie.
You must think
it's nuts that I wanna pursue
- being a licensed stockbroker.
- Not at all.
Trust me, if anyone understands
the thrill of Wall Street, it's me.
Or it was.
Okay, next question:
"A broker who lives in Greenwich
decides to work
from her Miami pied-à-terre.
How long can she do so
without violating regional law?"
Thirty days. Then she must report back
to her original branch office.
Boom, Mantle the Magnificent for the win.
I'm telling you, Ronnie,
in five years,
I'm gonna have the swankiest penthouse
in New York City
and a killer job on the stock exchange.
How does that sound?
Sounds like heaven, Reggie.
Our Smardi's reservation is at 6:30,
our Moulin Rouge tickets are at will call,
I have our Tramtrack confirmation,
and I splurged
and got us two business class seats.
Why only two?
What? Mom, are you okay?
You're leaving me behind?
No, honey, let me explain.
Mom, no, don't go there.
Whatever this is,
okay, it's just memories.
Mom, please, let's just go.
It's not real.
It's just your guilt or grief.
They don't exist.
But I do.
- No, I need them and they need me.
- I need you.
You weren't here.
I begged you to stay and you left.
For seven years, you were gone.
And when you did finally come back...
all of this started with Polly.
You drove her away.
She died.
She's dead because of you.
Jughead Jones.
Join me a second?
Jughead, you seem
like a nice enough fellow,
so you should know
my daughter's going through a phase.
Whatever this is between you,
it's a passing fancy.
Well, I can assure you, sir,
I really like your daughter.
And I'm pretty sure
she feels the same way.
Son,
man to man,
she's out of your league.
I'm not trying to belittle you,
I'm simply being realistic. My advice?
Do all of us a favor and don't show up
to that Mother's Day dinner.
You remind me of Hiram Lodge.
I don't know who that is.
But, please,
have a Swellegrino for the road.
Sorry I missed dinner again.
It's like the entire town's on fire.
Actually, Archie...
can we check in?
About us and where we're going?
- This sounds serious.
- I just wanna know...
I just want to know where you see us...
and yourself, in the next five years.
You know I would never do anything
to hold you back, from any opportunity.
But in my...
heart of hearts,
in five years, I see myself in Riverdale.
Is that a deal breaker?
Of course not, Archiekins.
I just...
I think it's important for us...
to have these honest conversations.
Toni, you've been going at it all night.
You want to take a break for lasagne?
I can't, Fangs.
I've spent all day
trying to find a place for Britta to live.
I tried group homes,
youth shelters, other social workers.
No one will take her.
You know, this might be a terrible idea,
but there is one more person
you could ask.
Someone with a newfound penchant
for helping people.
No. No way.
Why not? Cheryl really has changed.
And any port in a storm.
Right?
Hey, Betty. What's going on?
- I could've come to your house.
- No, Kev.
Home is bad and getting worse.
I'm just petrified for my mom.
She's in this cocoon
where Polly and her normal,
perfect family are thriving.
I'm just lost.
We both are.
Maybe my mom was right.
And it's my fault Polly's dead.
Betty, it's not.
And you still have a choice.
Sometimes when we're in free fall...
...we test our loved ones' love.
We push people away.
Hold on tighter.
Make the commitment to your mother.
Go back, pick up the pieces.
Catch each other.
What's keeping
your boyfriend, Tabitha?
Too much ketchup
to scrape off the countertops.
Guys, please stop being mean
about Jughead.
If you're still upset
that I left Chicago for Riverdale
to run our family business, Dad,
then just say so.
You had a wonderful career.
You could have worked with me.
Hold that thought, Dad.
My date just showed up.
Tee-Tee for tea time.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I have a favor to ask, Cheryl.
There is this girl that needs a home.
Britta Beach.
Her story's similar to yours.
Didn't go so well with her family
when she came out.
So I thought, if you had the space,
maybe you could offer her a place to stay?
Poor cherub.
But I must admit, I'm surprised
you'd trust me with such precious cargo.
I loved you.
And I felt your love.
And I know the huge capacity for love
your heart has.
It's exactly what Britta needs.
Well, then I'd be honored.
Archie, can we talk?
Okay.
In my marriage with Chad...
I felt like I was muted.
Like I was fading.
And it happened so slowly,
I didn't even notice it at first.
And the thing is,
I'm starting to feel that way again here.
Like I'm not myself.
Like I'm losing myself.
I am sorry. I...
I had no idea.
Archie, I think...
I think...
we should take a beat
until we figure out what we're doing.
We shouldn't rush this.
Or maybe we just go back to dating
and having fun like we used to.
That's a sweet idea.
But we're not in high school anymore.
Betty.
- What are you doing here?
- I took the record player out.
You won't need it anymore.
Years ago,
I made you a promise
that I would come back to Riverdale,
which I broke.
But right now I'm making you a new one.
I'm not leaving you alone.
Ever.
I love you so much, Mom.
I'm here.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean
that horrible thing I said to you,
that Polly was your fault.
It's okay, Mom.
The irony is...
all I ever wanted was for us
to be a normal family.
I'm glad they decided
to do a memorial and bury the ashes.
It was really beautiful,
everyone coming together like that.
As the bard once said,
"We cannot hold mortality's strong hand."
But we can hold each other's.
Remember what's really important.
Seemed like Britta
and Cheryl were getting along well.
She's already got Britta in a cape.
You did a really good thing, Toni.
For both of them.
Fangs...
I think I love you.
If I'm being honest...
I think I love you too, Toni.