Our story is about a town...
No, scratch that.
Our story is about three young women,
bursting with talent.
They were the best of friends until,
sadly, they weren't.
Our story is about how they parted ways,
found their own unique voices,
and then rediscovered each other.
But not without some drama.
Okay, I would like to make a toast.
To my roommate and my best friend,
Melody Valentine,
who, against all odds, left law school
in order to, uh, write and publish
her very first novel, Summer Storm.
I'm so proud of you.
You fearlessly chased your dream.
And you're a badass for it.
I love you.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Thank you, Val.
I love you. I love you so much.
As my best friend mentioned,
I was gonna be a lawyer.
But when I started looking for my voice,
I knew I wasn't gonna find it
inside of Harvard's Law Library.
It was inside of me,
in the form of this book.
I just... I guess I just had
to be brave enough to listen to it.
And it's not just gonna be a book.
Tell everyone the good news, babe.
Okay, well, uh,
it's not "official" official,
but my book's been optioned.
By Tyler Perry.
And it's gonna be a movie,
and the best part is...
Well, I'm really excited
because it looks
like Valerie's gonna play the lead.
Yeah!
Yes!
Cheers to that.
That was such a fun party,
my love.
I'm so glad we celebrated you.
Me too, baby.
I do wish you didn't bring up
the whole movie thing.
And why is that?
Tyler wants a big star to play the lead.
Someone splashy,
like Keke Palmer or Amandla Stenberg.
Not Val.
No.
Not if we want the movie
to get made, he says.
- That was a fun night.
- It was amazing.
I'm so proud of Melody.
She's like a real adult.
You, too, movie star.
We're not there yet.
I'm still a barista.
Oh, please.
Hey, you're so much more than that.
You are a poet. An actress.
An activist.
- The love of my life.
- Alan, you're making me blush.
Speaking of...
I know you said you needed some time
to think it over, but...
I was wondering
if maybe you have an answer for me.
Yeah, I have been thinking, I promise.
But I'm still unsure.
Getting married is such a big step.
Okay, well, no pressure.
Because I'm fine either way.
Just let me know when you decide.
I will.
And until then,
just know that I love you, Alan Mayberry.
No matter what.
I love you too, Val.
That was "Kiss My Hand,"
the latest number-one single
from the multi-platinum
recording artist Josie McCoy.
Even as the mystery surrounding
the superstar's whereabouts continues
after failing
to appear on-stage this weekend in Berlin.
The world wants to know:
What happened?
Where did Josie vanish to?
Excuse me, uh,
I'd like to place an order to go.
Double cheeseburger,
cheese fries, and a chocolate shake.
Wait, where's Pop Tate?
Oh, that's my grandpa. He retired.
Oh, my God, are you...?
Are you Josie?
Are you the Josie McCoy?
In the flesh and the faux fur.
Unbelievable. Josie McCoy in my diner.
This is such an honor.
At the risk of fangirl-ing even more
than I already am, I...
I have to ask.
What brought you to Riverdale?
Just needed
to take a little break for a while.
You know, some me time,
to recenter myself and to write.
Well, what's it like being back?
Is...? Is it how you remember?
I thought I told the front desk,
no autographs.
I am so sorry, Ms. Newmar,
but hotel policy,
no live music in our rooms after 9 p.m.
There have been complaints.
Damn, Mr. Lodge,
nice to know you're still a little bitch.
Excuse me? What makes you think
you can speak to me that way?
Uh, well, for starters,
you're here in your jammies,
whining that my music's too loud.
To me that screams, once a little bitch,
always a little bitch.
Move him
if he's got a problem with my music.
- Excellent idea, Ms. Newmar...
- Just turn it down.
Veronica, do you have a minute?
For you, Tabitha, I've got five.
So I just had an encounter
with someone who really inspires me.
I won't say who, but...
She reminded me
of why I came to Riverdale.
My dream, my ambition,
which is to franchise Pop's.
But to do that, I need more capital.
So I thought maybe
I could give you my nest egg to invest?
Right now probably isn't the best time.
Why's that?
Chad pulled me into financial quicksand.
A Ponzi scheme I'm trying
to dig myself out of by trading again,
but it'll be months before I can cover
what Chad stole
from his clients in our name.
And should
any of our investors start pulling out,
the whole house of cards
comes crashing down.
Got it.
Enough said.
Good luck to you.
Thanks.
Waldo, look who's visiting.
Ms. McCoy!
As fabulous as ever!
Aw. Thanks, Mr. Weatherbee.
What brings a star like you
back to our humble halls?
Yeah, inquiring minds wanna know.
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
I'm here to do some songwriting.
I was wondering
if I could use the music room to record.
Of course, I'd pay top dollar.
Just name your price.
Can your payment be teaching
a music class at Riverdale High?
It hasn't been
the easiest year for our students.
For you guys, I'll happily do it.
That's fantastic news.
They'll be so excited.
Smithers, what's going on?
Uh... send her in.
Alexandra Cabot.
What are you doing in Riverdale?
Veronica Lodge.
Well, I could ask the same thing.
But I'm here about some investments
that I made with your squirrely husband.
I've been calling Chad, but he's MIA,
so I made a day trip to pull my money out.
I'm feeling fiscally antsy, you see.
Of course.
And I could absolutely give you
the money back right now.
- Or...
- Or?
Well, I just stumbled across
this new investment opportunity
that I'm extremely,
extremely excited about.
Out of curiosity,
how do you feel about diners?
Tell me more.
No way.
- Yeah!
- Really, really good.
Oh, my gosh.
Archie Andrews.
Josie. I knew it was you.
Oh, hi.
And now I'm back in Riverdale
to work on this new album.
You should come to the Whyte Wyrm tonight,
formerly the speakeasy.
Everyone would love to see you.
I actually, uh, have
some songwriting I need to do.
Just for a drink or two.
It's been seven years.
Yeah, something like that.
Okay.
Can I meet you there?
I have some phone calls to make.
Give you two guesses
who Josie calls.
I freaked and sent her to voicemail.
At which point,
a phone
in the living room started to ring.
Hey, Josie.
What's up?
No, we even made
this sexy firemen's calendar
to raise money for the fire station,
but, anyway, enough about me.
- What about you, Josie?
- Well, it's been a whirlwind.
Oh, don't worry, Josie,
I've kept them all apprised,
from your special
on Entertainment Tomorrow
to your Vanity Flair cover.
It's so great that you're here.
You can help us save Riverdale.
We've been needing a face,
a celebrity to help get people excited.
Give her a minute. She just got here.
Oh, we should do a benefit concert.
That would be so much fun,
just like old times.
Old times?
I don't mean to offend you, Veronica,
but I didn't have
much of a say in our old times.
And now we're more acquaintances
than friends.
Yikes.
Oh, Jughead, the last time I saw you,
you were robbing Pop Tate's
at gunpoint in a Serpents mask.
Everybody on the ground!
- No.
- Get down!
- Uh...
- That was so many years ago.
Uh-uh. Betty, you and I have spoken
all of, what, one time in high school?
If I could jump in for a moment,
none of you deserve to be in the presence
of such musical greatness.
Cheryl, you once sent me a pig's heart.
Something that still haunts me,
so jump down off that soapbox, shall we?
I came to Riverdale to make an album,
not to cause trouble,
so if you'll kindly excuse me...
Josie McCoy?
- Sweet Pea?
- What are you doing at Pop's?
Leaving.
You want a ride?
Wherever you're going?
Sneaking out of your own hotel room?
Sweet Pea.
Last night was exactly what I needed.
But I've got things to do
and people to meet.
Of course.
You're a busy star.
Bye, stud.
Val, Mel,
thank you so much for meeting me.
How have you both been doing?
What are you doing?
I've been doing a lot of art
and getting into political activism.
Val's gonna save the world
one peaceful protest at a time.
That's really amazing, Val.
How about you, Melody?
I stay busy. I'm a YA novelist.
I just had my first book published.
I heard something about that.
Tyler Perry's producing a movie of it?
- It's, um, starring...
- What about you, Josie?
What brings you to Riverdale?
I needed a break from my tour.
Thought I'd finally write
about my hometown.
And since you guys were
a big part of my experience here,
I'd love to have you join me
on one of the tracks.
I don't know
if either of you do any performing still.
Nice!
Yeah, we still do a bit
of performing on the side.
- Music was my first love, so...
- Mine too.
Which is why it was so hard
when you just disappeared on us.
I know. I know I did.
But when I got the opportunity
to tour with my dad...
We're not talking about that, Josie.
We're talking about before you left town.
You stopped calling us.
We stopped hanging out, playing gigs.
- We thought we'd done something wrong.
- The irony is that your dad was like us.
A sideman.
You'd think you of all people
would've respected your sidewomen more.
I'm sorry.
Truly, I am.
I know the value of what you both did
and what you brought to the table.
I understand if you don't wanna record
this song, but it's an open offer.
We'll think about it.
But either way,
it was good catching up with you, Josie.
I like to think of myself as a connector.
My friend, Tabitha Tate, wants
to franchise her family's diner.
My other friend, Alexandra Cabot,
is always looking for a smart investment.
Tabitha, why don't you tell Xandra
what you told me last night?
I believe
that America is ready for a new start.
The face of that new start
should be Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
Small-town feel, even in big cities.
Look through our packet.
It details our expansion strategies.
No need. I've already made my decision.
I love diners,
and I'm feeling your homespun vision.
But may I suggest a tweak or two?
What kind of tweaks?
You may not know this,
but I am a performer
as well as a businesswoman,
and I've always
romanticized singing diners.
We have a proud tradition
of singing here at Pop's.
Singing is something
we can definitely talk about.
Yeah, talking isn't exactly
what I had in mind.
Well, I always say, going out for a meal
isn't just about the food,
it's about the experience.
Singing clearly enhances
the Pop's experience.
Agreed.
Toni, thank you so much
for jumping in on such short notice.
Also, what, pray tell, is in that bag?
The most adorable baby jeans
from Old Navy you've ever seen.
Thanks for asking me.
I thought it would induce labor.
But no such luck.
- Bye.
So, Xandra, do we have a deal?
Almost.
The creative is there, but now I need
to see your books and finances.
Everything from the last 20 years.
Sure.
I can make that happen.
Mom.
What are you doing in Riverdale?
How did you even know?
A mother always knows.
When I heard you had disappeared,
I had a hunch
you might find your way to Riverdale.
Ms. Newmar.
What happened, Josie?
When I got your call
with the news about Dad, I was in Berlin.
Seconds from stepping onto a stage
in a stadium filled with 80,000 people.
Mom? What's going on?
I just got word.
Your dad passed away, baby.
It was sudden. A heart attack.
Oh, my God. Mom.
I'm in Berlin,
in the middle of a world tour.
I know, and that's why I don't want you
to worry about anything.
We'll meet up right after.
It'll go by in a flash.
After that call, I...
I couldn't perform.
I just turned around
and walked away from everything.
And you came to Riverdale.
I haven't been back in years.
Just thought I could disappear here.
Like in high school.
Josie, I...
I brought your father's ashes.
His last request was
that they be scattered around the country.
All the little spots he toured and loved.
Sounds about right.
And that's not all.
Some songs he wrote or reorchestrated,
but never got a chance to record.
Val? Hey.
Do you have a minute to talk?
Sure, Mel. What's up?
Well, I've been thinking a lot about Josie
and how she didn't do right by us.
And how I wanna do right by you, Valerie.
But that means being honest
with each other.
I don't think we'll be making Summer Storm
into a movie anytime soon.
What happened?
Tyler Perry wants a star to play the lead.
That...
I mean, that makes sense.
If it means your movie gets made,
I wouldn't wanna hold you back.
I told him no.
What do you mean, no?
I just sent Tyler an e-mail that said.
I wasn't interested
in making Summer Storm into a movie...
unless it starred you.
Val, that role is yours.
We'll get it done, Valerie.
The two of us together.
The right way.
Is that Josie again?
It's her mom.
Well, I've dug through your books,
and, uh, first off,
we literally need to reprice everything.
I think bringing prices up to date
is totally doable, right?
- Yeah.
- And then there's the milkshake.
Oh, it's divinity in a glass.
You're losing money on them.
However, if we adjust the recipe
to replace real milk with instant milk,
we can save a ton of money.
Pop's milkshakes are
our signature product,
developed by my great-great-grandfather.
I can't change the recipe.
Girl, relax. It is just a milkshake.
Alexandra, you may not know this,
but Pop started off selling one thing,
chocolate milkshakes,
hence the name Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
That was back when this was the first
and only Black-owned business in town.
It was open 24/7,
a safe place for people like us
when those were few and far between.
So, no, it's not just a milkshake,
and this isn't just a business.
It's a legacy.
I can't give that up for a bottom line.
This doesn't feel right anymore. Sorry.
Well, Veronica,
I'm assuming you're prepared for me
to withdraw my money
from your portfolios ASAP.
If that's what you wanna do.
But the banks are closed,
so you'll have to wait until tomorrow.
See you bright and early.
Thought you'd be here.
What are you doing here?
Your mom called us.
We're so sorry about your dad, Josie.
Why didn't you tell us?
If we'd known, Josie, we would have
never said any of those things to you.
It's okay, Mel.
You both were 100% right.
You know,
sometimes I think
watching my dad spend his entire career
just outside of the spotlight
is why I became so obsessed
with getting it for myself.
But now I would give anything
to play with him just one more time.
With you guys one more time.
Then let's do it, Josie.
That's why we came.
To tell you, if you still wanna record
that song together,
we're totally down.
Oh, my gosh, that's...
That's amazing.
- What?
Nothing, nothing. I just...
How would you feel about playing
a one-night-only concert?
That would be incredible, Josie,
but what's the occasion?
You guys giving me another shot
makes me think that maybe
some other people might deserve one too.
Josie, Melody, and Valerie.
I feel like I'm
in sophomore year again.
What's going on?
- Hi, Archie.
- Hey, Archie.
We're gonna help you
and the gang save Riverdale.
Are you sure? You didn't exactly...
Please.
When a superstar offers to help,
you don't try to talk them out of it.
What are you thinking?
Well, we're thinking,
a one-night-only Josie and the Pussycats
reunion concert at the Whyte Wyrm.
With proceeds going
to a fund to reincorporate
the former town of Riverdale.
Josie and the Pussycats reunited.
If that doesn't save Riverdale,
nothing will.
Toni, how overdue are you?
A week.
I thought it'd be good
for the baby to see the Cats live.
Plus, I wouldn't miss this.
Dr. Curdle Junior? Hey.
Did someone die?
No, Ms. Cooper.
- I'm a huge Josie fan.
- We both are.
- Yeah!
- Oh, yeah!
Let's give it up
for Valerie Brown and Melody Valentine.
Listen.
I've played a lot of venues.
The Sydney Opera House,
Dodger Stadium,
the Apollo.
But there is no better spot
to play music than here.
Riverdale nourishes artists
like myself and Valerie and Melody.
And, heck, even Jughead Jones.
So this next song is something
my dad wanted to hear me perform.
It's originally sung by one
of his favorite artists, Nina Simone.
This is for him.
- Toni?
- I'm sorry. I think I'm having my baby.
Oh, crap.
Um... Okay.
Is there a doctor in the house?
- I'm a doctor.
- I can do it.
We prepared for a home birth.
I need another pair of hands.
I'll do it.
- Let's go, go, go.
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
As exciting as a random birth
in the back of a diner is,
not to mention the coincidence
of crossing paths with Josie in Riverdale,
my mind naturally turns back
to business, as always.
- Oh, really?
- Josie's little speech got me thinking.
With her celebrity endorsement of Pop's,
a franchise seems like
an even more lucrative prospect.
We're not changing the milkshake recipe.
Pop's original milkshake recipe and all.
Typical Riverdale.
The Pussycats always getting upstaged
by something.
Better a new baby than a dead body.
Still, it felt pretty great
performing together again, didn't it?
Agreed.
Well, would you ladies
ever consider going on tour with me?
I wanna drive around the country
and visit all
the small cool places my dad played,
to honor his final wish.
What do you say?
Intriguing.
But wait. Would we be like
your opening act or something?
No, all three of us would be headlining.
I can't believe this.
I mean...
I have to talk to Alan,
about a lot of things, including the fact
that I'm not ready to get married.
- Wait, what?
- I'll fill you in later.
But, Josie, I'm in.
Yes, yes!
Melody?
God, I mean, I...
I have to talk to Nancy about it.
But now that my movie's on the backburner,
I guess it could be like a book tour?
Absolutely.
- Are we doing this?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Well?
- It's a boy.
Finally some good news in this crazy town.
Not gonna lie, Josie.
We were hoping you'd stay
and be Riverdale High's new music teacher.
Ha. Uh, my destiny lies elsewhere.
Have an amazing tour, Josie.
I'm gonna call you, okay?
I'm gonna live vicariously through you.
Deal. But you guys should come out
and see me sometime.
We will 100%, Josie.
Especially if we can get backstage passes?
Uh, hell, yes, you can.
Look who came to say bye.
Oh, my God.
What is this cutie patootie's name?
Tony.
Anthony, after my grandfather.
Congratulations again, Toni, Fangs, Kevin.
He's really beautiful.
You know, Alan,
you don't have to come with us.
I still love you, Val.
I'm in it for the long haul,
married or not.
In case I haven't told you today,
I'm crazy about you, Alan Mayberry.
See?
Plenty of time.
I don't know how I'm gonna handle
being on the road without you, Nance.
You'll be fine.
We'll check in every night.
I know. I just...
It's not gonna be the same, you know?
Hey, Josie.
Hi.
- Can I talk to you for a second?
- Uh, yeah.
So I've been thinking, and, uh...
Is there any chance
that I can tag along with you?
I'd pull my weight. I could...
I could drive the bus,
or I could be your roadie.
I could be your...
I could be your anything.
It'll be a tight squeeze, but yes.
Great. I'll, uh... I'll load my stuff.
- You almost ready, honey?
- I think so.
Unless this town has
any more surprises for me.
Josie McCoy.
Yes?
My name is Toots Sweet. I am a musician
who toured with your father.
We've always had each other's backs.
That's why I'm here.
I was with Myles
in New Orleans before he passed.
He was mixed in bad stuff.
Debts, petty crimes, even voodoo.
I don't believe
your father died of natural causes.
Are you saying
that my father was murdered?
I'm sorry. This must come as a shock.
Mr. Sweet,
we've lived long enough in Riverdale
to know that when someone passes away,
foul play is always on the table.
I know where the first stop
of my tour's gonna be.
New Orleans.
It is.
Let's get out of here
before we run out of room on the bus.
And there you have it.
The story of three young women,
old friends who found
their way back to each other
and who set off together towards magical,
musical mysteries unknown.
- We love you guys!
- We love you!
Do yourself a favor
and remember our names, all three of them:
Josie McCoy,
Valerie Brown, and Melody Valentine.
'Cause you'll be hearing from us again.