Our old-pal-turned-superstar,
Josie McCoy, had come and gone.
Leaving us all to our haunted existences.
No one more so than Archie Andrews.
The guilt over the deaths
of his platoon members
hanging on him like a shroud.
Veronica Lodge was also being haunted
but by a flesh-and-blood mistake
from her past.
What, Chad?
I have some great news.
I'm gonna be able to pay back
the funds I borrowed in one fell swoop.
I've been working on a little
something-something quietly,
but it's about to go public,
and with that comes a big payday.
Considering you always
screw things up?
No, Chad. I don't want or need your help.
At the rate Pearls and Posh is going,
I'll have our investors' accounts
restored in a month.
At which point, I'll divorce your ass
so fast, your head will spin.
Goodbye, Chad.
Brothers and sisters,
thank you for joining us today.
To conclude, Brother Kevin and I
will be performing a medley
from the iconic musical Joseph
and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat.
Stop.
I have just had a revelation.
Okay.
Jason himself commands it.
No more singing.
Really?
As you know,
he was a young man of few words.
Hi, uh, my name is Jughead Jones,
and I am seven days sober.
- All right.
- Good job, man.
I think I'm ready
to start my apology tour.
- Hey, Alice.
- Hey, Jughead.
Uh, Betty's not here.
She's, um, working the Lonely Highway,
doing God knows what.
That's okay.
- Will you tell her I stopped by?
- Sure.
You guys seen this crap?
The front page of today's Brave and True.
General Taylor is retiring
with full honors
and a 21-gun farewell salute.
Doesn't that burn you
after the crap he pulled?
- You said Taylor was under investigation.
- He was.
A reporter was looking
into some dirty missions
the general orchestrated, like ours, Eric.
I called her. Her editor killed the story.
Not enough evidence, she said.
Maybe take that as a sign, sarge.
Let it go. Move on.
Like hell.
You've missed weeks of work.
You didn't even arrange for a substitute.
I know. I'm sorry, Waldo.
I really am. I...
I was going through
some intense personal stuff.
I'm trying to get my life back together.
When you do,
maybe we can have you teach again.
But right now,
you're on administrative leave.
Pearls and Posh, this is Lodge.
Ms. Lodge, this is Diane Nelson.
I'm an agent with the SEC.
We'd like to schedule a time to come in
and review your books and finances.
Oh, why is that?
To ensure that Pearls and Posh is not
engaged in any financial malfeasance.
- Can we plan on tomorrow?
- Uh...
Ooh, I'm traveling tomorrow.
Can we try top of next week?
Sure. Top of next week is good.
I'll follow up with an e-mail.
Great. See you then.
The SEC wants to look at our books,
which are not yet kosher.
Yes. It had to have been Chad
who tipped them off.
Wouldn't he be torpedoing himself too?
What he wants is for me
to ask for his help,
so he can balance our books
before the SEC reviews them.
I'd rather go to white-collar jail
than do that.
What we need is an influx of cash.
- My mind turns to...
- my father.
What? Like a short-term loan?
Remember those escaped prisoners
who were convinced
my father had a stash of palladium?
If we got our hands on that,
we could sell it,
and finish repaying
what Chad stole in my name.
If it was in his safe,
he would've moved it, but...
I have an idea who might know where.
Your old man's been in touch with Hermosa.
She's still in deep with him.
- I'll call her.
- Actually, uh...
Let me.
While you were at Barnard...
we had a thing.
- What kind of thing?
- You... You know what kind.
You know what kind. Okay.
Hey, baby.
Long time no talk.
Yeah.
I miss you so much.
Why does my demon of a mother
always have to rain on my parade?
You're young, beautiful and a star.
And she isn't.
Which is why you need to prove
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that there is no higher authority than you
within this ministry.
You're not wrong.
So how do we put Mumzie
in the shade forever?
It's all about showmanship, Cheryl.
You need to upstage your mother.
Little-known fact:
If you perform three miracles,
you qualify for sainthood.
Being canonized has always been
one of my life goals. Go on.
In junior high,
I was obsessed with David Copperfield.
The magician. So...
I may have a trick or two up my sleeve.
Oh, I hope
you have at least three, Brother Kevin.
I need my halo and my wings.
That was some call, Reggie.
How's Hermosa doing?
A better question:
Did she just tell me
where the palladium is?
The answer is yes.
You're carrying a heavy weight, Archie.
It's not gonna get lighter
unless you share the burden, so...
What happened over there?
Ready to tell me?
We were ordered into a fire zone
to deliver medical supplies to civilians.
But that mission was just a cover-up.
General Taylor was determined to take down
a warlord controlling that region.
A chance to get that final star
on his uniform.
When he gave me the order, I pushed back.
I told him we weren't a strike force
and that it was a suicide mission.
Taylor didn't back down, so I... I caved.
And we were lambs to the slaughter.
My platoon got caught in some trenches.
We needed air support.
We couldn't get any signal.
Someone needed to reach higher ground,
so I told my men that I would go.
I thought I was protecting them
because I was taking the risk.
And when I got back...
...everyone was dead.
Aiden? Aiden?
Except Bingo.
Who died before the choppers reached us
and Eric, who lost his leg.
And now Taylor is walking away
with honors.
That's not right.
- That's not right, Uncle Frank.
- I know it's not.
But the Army's just gonna
circle the wagons around the general.
I wish I could tell you
this is a war you could win.
- But I don't know that it is.
- Maybe not.
But it's a war worth fighting.
And I'm gonna do everything that I can
to take Taylor down.
Lucky your father didn't change
all the security codes after he fired me.
Lucky that he doesn't keep
his palladium in a bank.
Jackpot.
We have to give Hermosa
a cut of whatever we make.
But if we can sell
the palladium off-market,
our profits should be enough
to fill in where we're short.
Question is, how do we sell it?
Well, first,
we'd have to smelt the palladium
down into something new
and unrecognizable.
I'm thinking Spanish doubloons.
Then I'll host an auction,
but for that to work...
there's one more person
we need to bring in.
What do you think?
I think that one can never have
too many spider brooches.
- So, yes, I'll help you, Veronica.
- Perfect.
As I said, I'm hosting
an exclusive by-invitation-only auction.
The centerpiece of which will be
some palladium doubloons I've acquired.
My guests have been asking
about the palladium's origins,
and I wanna say
that it came from your mines.
Not a problem. I'm always happy
to let you name-drop my family
in order to screw over your father.
Now, if that's all,
I'll be on my merry way.
Kevin and I are performing
our first miracle.
- Hey, Samm.
- Finally!
You've been ducking my calls.
- Yeah, no, sorry. I've been...
- Save your excuses.
The publisher is demanding
a manuscript ASAP.
If you don't deliver,
you will be blackballed.
Your career will be over. Over!
I have pages. I'll send them to you
by the end of the day.
This is your last chance, kiddo. Okay?
Don't disappoint me.
Hey, so...
Before you say anything else,
I just... I wanna apologize.
I promised to keep an eye on you
while you were tripping,
and the moment things got weird, I just...
- I abandoned you.
- You didn't do anything wrong.
I never should have even put you
in that position.
And I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry
I dropped off the face of the earth.
And that I made you worry.
I'm sorry for everything, really.
It's okay.
I forgive you.
Great. So...
not to relive that horrible night,
but I dimly recall writing something
that resembled a novel before I yanked
my hand out of the handcuffs.
Jughead, you did write
your book that night.
I did? Okay, well, that's great.
- You know where it is?
- Yeah, um...
Betty gave it to Jessica
when she asked for it.
Wh...
Why would Betty...? Why would she do that?
Jess was trying to heal
and move on with her life,
so it seemed like
the right thing to do at the time.
- Wow, okay.
- I'm really, really sorry.
But, Jughead, your sobriety is
what's most important right now.
I don't think you should reach out
to Jessica. That could be triggering.
And if writing is gonna stress you out,
then maybe ask your agent
for another extension.
I don't have any more time, Tabitha.
I either write something new,
or I am not a writer anymore.
If I ever was.
Instead of my usual homily,
I thought today we might all benefit
from a demonstration
of my absolute authority in this ministry.
To that end,
as Jesus once changed water into wine...
Jason has granted me
the ability to turn water into...
maple syrup.
The nectar of the gods.
Truly.
- General Taylor.
- Sergeant Andrews.
I take it you're not here
to congratulate me.
No, sir. We both know the truth, general.
You sent me and my men into a war zone
without adequate support or intel.
Because of your recklessness,
good men died.
You're dishonoring the military
by pretending to be some kind of hero.
So...
I'm asking you, soldier to soldier,
to stand down and retire quietly.
"Soldier to soldier"?
You're just a kid from some Podunk town
who joined the military on a whim.
You might as well have gone
backpacking through Europe.
You don't understand the Army
or how it works,
and you certainly don't know
what it means to be a real soldier.
Don't cross me. You will regret it.
My men paid for your order with blood.
If you don't step down, general,
I'll demand a military tribunal.
I'll tell them everything.
Then I'll be forced
to put forth my version of events.
Highlighting how you,
Sergeant Andrews, went rogue
and led your platoon directly
into an ambush.
There's no paper trail
to support your claim.
So, as I said before,
it's my word against yours.
Pursue this and you'll be a traitor.
No.
You're the traitor, general.
I buried good men because of you.
I won't bury the truth any longer.
Regardless of the consequences.
Taylor left us no choice.
He won't back down,
so we need to take him out.
I don't know, sarge.
A trial would reopen wounds,
especially for the families
of those other guys.
We have to think about them
and what they would want us to do.
So let's say this,
I won't go after the general
unless I have the support and the approval
of our platoon's families.
How does that sound?
Would you mind reading my novel?
If you like it,
maybe you could give it to your agent?
My son trusted you
and you didn't protect him.
And now you expect us
to go through a trial
to relive his death all over again.
Ma'am, I know what Travis stood for,
what he believed in.
He fought for ideals
like truth and justice,
for betterment and human dignity.
He sacrificed his life for those things.
Let me ask you,
do you sleep soundly at night, sergeant?
Because I don't.
Not since the moment...
I received that folded-up flag.
Know why? Because you were supposed
to bring my Travis back to me.
Now, for the main event,
a collection of doubloons
smelted from grade-A palladium,
excavated from the Blossom mines.
With that in mind, let's begin at 150,000
to the gentleman in the fedora.
Do I have 170? One hundred seventy.
Nope. One hundred eighty.
No, 190,000 to the madam
in the front row. Shall we go to two?
Two hundred thousand to Mr. Sand.
Do I have 225?
Do I have 250?
Two fifty. Two seventy-five.
Two ninety against you, Mr. Sand.
Three hundred thousand.
That's $300,000
for these precious doubloons.
Going once. Going twice.
Sold to Mr. Sand for $300,000.
What a coup for such rare wonders.
Excuse me.
It's almost as if you wanted to sell
those doubloons to Mr. Sand for less,
so I wouldn't get the palladium.
But that would be so petty
and ridiculous of you, wouldn't it?
In fact, that's exactly what I did, Daddy.
Next time, don't crash my auction.
I never wanted Jim to join the Army.
I was afraid he wouldn't even make it
through basic training,
but he really believed that he had a duty
to protect and serve his country.
That there was no greater honor than that.
There isn't. No.
Jim knew what he was fighting for.
I remember I was incredibly relieved
when he started
sending me letters about you.
About the kind of leader you were. So yes.
Whatever you feel is right, you should do.
You have my full support.
You've already witnessed
one miracle.
Now, brothers and sisters, watch in wonder
as Cheryl manifests the collective pain
of our congregation.
Behold her alabaster hands,
how they bleed
with the blood of the stigmata.
Mimicking the holy wounds of Jason!
Ma'am?
I'd like to honor your husband's memory
by having General Taylor answer
for his actions.
But I'd like to do so with your consent.
To be honest, I've made peace
with what happened, Sergeant Andrews.
I loved Aiden more than anything.
We were high-school sweethearts, but...
my son is my focus now.
I need to start thinking about his future.
I'm trying to make it through the day
and even that's a struggle.
So I leave it to you, sergeant.
Ma'am.
You do what you see fit.
Who knew spreading light and love
could be this exhausting?
Yeah, it's the Broadway grind.
I got a list of potential third miracles,
although my strong preference is
that we do the staff and the snake trick.
Those snakes are unquestionably biblical,
I already know
what I want my third miracle to be.
Do you remember when I got revenge
on Mr. Honey years ago?
When he tried to ban
my back-to-school party?
Yeah. But, Cheryl,
bees are not in my repertoire.
I'm highly allergic.
Fear not, Kev. As a girl,
Nana Rose was an avid beekeeper.
She taught me all her apian secrets.
Okay.
- What do you want, Chadwick?
- I just got wind of your auction.
It pains me
to see you so desperate for funds.
So I'm double-checking.
Are you sure you don't want in
on my amazing deal?
Surely you've heard of CopterCab.
The helicopter taxis that fly 1 percenters
to Marcia's Vineyard for private parties?
- That's you?
- It is.
I'm more of a silent partner.
So do you want in or not?
Your father's also working with me.
I killed it at my auction.
So much so that all of
your swindled investors are paid in full.
Just in time for the SEC.
So, no,
I don't want in on your little scheme.
Well, listen, CopterCab's going public,
and we're celebrating at your father's HQ.
Why don't you come by,
blow off some steam?
You know what? I might just do that.
- Text me the deets, will you?
- Happy to.
And we'll toast to the future.
Looking forward to it.
Goodbye, Chadwick.
You're partying with that smug nitwit?
What am I missing?
Me, Reggie.
You're missing the old me.
I've been playing defense,
reacting to Chad's every move.
Well, now that I don't have
to worry about the SEC,
it's time I go on the offensive
and take Chad Gekko
off the chessboard of my life
once and for all.
And if Daddy gets caught
in my crosshairs, so be it.
Damn. It's good.
Hey, Jones.
Hey, I finished the novel.
Not a chapter, not a draft,
I mean, the whole thing.
It is about a budding young writer at NYU
just making their way through the world,
having a lot of sex and partying.
Sounds terrific.
Send it to me ASAP.
Yeah, okay.
Keep an eye out for it.
You're really
going through with this?
Telling our business
to a military tribunal?
There's no easy path through this, Eric.
So I'm doing what feels most right.
Going on behalf of myself
and the families that want me to advocate
for their brothers,
their sons, their fathers.
- I hope you'll go with me.
- You don't understand.
You weren't the only grunt Taylor brought
into his tent because of that mission.
He said it was gonna be
our moment of glory
and that there'd be
a big promotion in it for me.
All I had to do was
what I was trained to as a sniper.
Find a clear line of fire
and take out that warlord.
In our briefing, General Taylor said
our target was the only thing
that mattered.
But my platoon's safety
should have been my top priority.
We were vulnerable. And I knew it.
And when you went in to call for support,
I left our unit unprotected
to carry out Taylor's orders.
And I gotta tell you, sarge,
part of me thinks that
that's why I lost my leg.
As punishment
for how I betrayed you and the others.
No, you didn't do anything wrong.
I'll keep you out of it, Eric. I swear.
You were used
by the general the same way I was.
But you're done fighting, corporal.
Let me bring this home for you.
It'd be my honor.
Behold Cheryl Blossom
as she prepares her third
and final miracle,
the taming of the bees.
Witness as her purity keeps
her porcelain skin safe
- from these vicious, spiteful creatures.
- This is nothing but a farce.
I pray ye,
do not fall victim to her deceit.
For if ye do, this ministry shall
become nothing but a sham.
Brothers and sisters,
we find ourselves at a crossroads.
- Allow me to be your guide.
- Do not listen to this heretic.
Who are you going to put your faith in?
Cheryl, who shared the womb
with Jason the Divine?
Or her mother, a whoremonger,
an escaped convict?
Lies. Lies, all of it!
Mother, enough!
Begone from my temple...
or I will smite thee.
For I am Cheryl Blossom,
Queen of the Bees.
You look ready for action.
I feel like I'm about to be walking
into a firing squad.
Taylor should be worried.
You tell the tribunal the truth.
And I'll be there to back you up.
Eric.
You don't have to do this.
I couldn't sleep, thinking I left
my brothers high and dry once.
I won't desert you again.
I wanna testify.
Don't even try to talk me out of it.
Wouldn't dream of it.
Boys, we did it.
In one hour, CopterCab will be
the publicly-traded future
of aero-entertainment
and we will be richer men.
Cheers.
Amen to that.
Veronica.
- What is this?
- Oh, Chadwick.
If you're gonna be one of the big boys,
you need to party like a big boy.
Isn't that right, Daddy?
So I invited some good-time girls.
I hope that's all right.
Differences aside, CopterCab is
a brilliant business idea, Chad.
And for the first time in a long time,
you've impressed me.
But for now, who wants some bubbly?
Cheers.
Uh, your mom tells me you're working
on the Lonely Highway?
Yeah. By dressing like Polly
and pretending to be a hitchhiker.
Is that safe?
Probably not,
but I'm running out of ideas, so...
What'd you wanna talk about?
I wanted to apologize, actually,
for that voicemail that I left you.
I don't remember all of it or...
even most of it.
But I know it was horrible.
And, uh...
Just... I'm sorry.
Why now after half a decade?
It's one of my steps.
Trying to clean up
my side of the track and I...
I'm in recovery, in case it's not obvious.
I'm an alcoholic.
An addict.
I think I'm an addict too.
Maybe a better word is "compulsive."
Because I can't stop hunting
for the trucker killer.
I'm on the highway 24/7
when I should be at home with my mom.
- Yeah, but your sister's missing.
- No, it's not that. It's, um...
It's more than that.
And it's sort of been...
my MO lately.
- What do you mean?
- Even when I was at Yale,
I was trying to be a normal... freshman.
Go on dates, make friends,
do extracurriculars.
But it just all felt so...
empty.
Classic Cooper.
You solved eight mysteries in high school
and you were still valedictorian.
But the void
I was so desperately trying to fill
didn't go away when I got to Quantico.
Which is when I...
really realized that...
I am more comfortable...
studying serial killers
than I am socializing with normal people.
And, um...
And then I read about TBK.
Trash Bag Killer.
That was, uh...
That was a nasty piece of work.
That's why I wasn't
at your book release party.
I wanted to go, but, um...
I got the offer that night
and I had to choose, you...
or the TBK task force.
That's all ancient history.
I'm consumed by them.
TBK and the trucker killer.
Betty, I think...
I think you should probably take a break
from all that, you know?
- Maybe stop hunting for a bit.
- I don't think I can.
I'm sorry. Can I...?
Just real quick.
- Hey, Samm.
- I just finished your book.
It's incredible!
Best thing you've ever written by far.
Uh, I can't do this, Samm.
I didn't write that book.
A grad student named Cora
gave it to me to read.
Wait. What are you saying to me right now?
- That there's no novel?
- Not even a wisp.
And a plagiarist to boot.
Listen, I know you got some life things
going on right now, but, um...
- I'm gonna have to drop you as a client.
- Yeah. I figured as much.
You're a good writer, kid.
I hope you can pull it together.
Hey, um, I'll send you Cora's info.
I'm sure she'll be thrilled
to hear from you.
Okay.
Sorry, that was...
You really struck a gold mine here.
I should have never doubted you.
- I don't know what I was thinking.
- You weren't. But that's okay.
'Cause you're here now
for probably my finest hour.
Gekko, we have a problem.
My Boysenberry's blowing up.
Something's wrong
with the CopterCab stock.
It's crashing.
- It's in free fall.
- What the hell is going on?
Were you in a helicopter crash
that you paid to cover up?
The Wall Beat Journal just published
an article about it.
You can't be a part of CopterCab
if you crashed a helicopter.
It's a bad look, yes.
Which is why you were a silent partner.
What did you do?
Planted the story with a reporter friend,
then came here
to distract you and your entourage
while CopterCab went down in flames.
- Veronica, you little...
- I'm gonna stop you right there, Chad.
Because whatever you think I am
doesn't come close to what you are,
which is scum.
A worthless, pathetic, little worm.
You stole money from your investors
to what, finance CopterCab?
But what a surprise.
In the end, you couldn't pull it off.
That's your problem
in a nutshell.
You can't land anything.
You'll never be an alpha, Chad.
You're a born beta.
And everybody who invested in this scheme,
you backed a losing horse, boys.
- You too, Daddy.
- Oh, please, mija.
I only invested a modest sum in CopterCab.
You may have destroyed
these clowns... but not me.
Oh, Daddykins.
You're in for a rude awakening.
Later, when you're alone,
give your SoDale model another look-see.
I think you'll find that you've lost
much more than you realize.
Come on, ladies. Let's get out of here.
This party's over.
Hey, Jughead.
You okay? I just mentioned "free food"
and you didn't salivate.
Yeah, um...
- I'm just worried about Betty, you know?
- Yeah.
I can imagine.
But I'm also... worried about you.
And your recovery.
I smelled booze on your breath
when you came in.
Yeah, I had a backslide.
Jughead, I know that you wanna help Betty,
but you need to focus on you.
She's out there alone.
I'm sure, but don't worry about Betty.
I'll take care of her.
Your priority is you.
Okay?
You know I'm a drunk, right?
And I'm a terrible busboy.
- Why are you so nice to me?
- Because you're my friend.
And I care about you.
So will you promise me
that you'll keep going to your meetings?
Yeah. Yes. Yes, I promise.
Good.
So tell me, what's going on with Betty?
Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Hello?
Yeah, this is Archie Andrews.
Okay.
Understood. Thank you so much. Bye.
That was the JAG officer with the verdict.
Hurry up before I hurl.
"The tribunal has determined
that Corporal Eric Jackson
was following
the direct and explicit orders
of his commanding officer,
and therefore, is not guilty
of any wrongdoing and remains
in good standing with the U.S. Army."
What about General Taylor?
His actions were determined
to be reckless and of poor judgment.
He was driven by his own self-interest,
and therefore, he is being discharged
without honors.
- The Army got it right.
- So... it's over?
It's over.
- Tabitha.
- Jughead told me what you're doing.
And it's dangerous and it's reckless,
and no matter what I say,
you're not gonna stop, I know that.
So...
- I'm going with you.
- Come again?
I'm getting changed
and I'm going with you.
Oh, and by the way,
my participation is not negotiable.
You boys did it.
You should be proud.
I am. Proud to have served
with the bravest men that I've ever known.
Here's to our fallen band of brothers.
To their service...
to their sacrifice.
Gone but never forgotten.
- Never.
Cheryl, I have to ask.
How did you manage those bees
outside the tank?
Did you rub
some special insect-repelling ointment
all over your body?
The truth?
I didn't have any ointment
on any part of my body.
What are you saying?
Something inside me has shifted.
Kevin...
something powerful, something...
I can't explain.
But...
I'm feeling more connected to things
than I have in years.
I'm not saying
I'm the first-ever living saint...
but what if I am?
What if I, Cheryl Marjorie Blossom...
am the holiest of holies?
Wouldn't that be miraculous?
My name is Jughead Jones.
- Hey, Jughead.
I used to be seven days sober,
but now I'm back down to one.
Hoping to make it to eight this time.
I'm worried about a couple of friends,
but I'm also trying to accept the things
that I cannot change.
And I'm grateful to you all.
And if there is some higher power, man,
I hope it's looking down on them tonight
and keeping them safe.
I don't know why.
I got this really bad feeling
about what happens next.