This one's
for all you night owls
burning the candle at both ends.
Stay hungry, my friends.
Aw, this one is
one of my all-time favorites.
Duran Duran? Top five for me.
For sure.
- Sorry. I should go.
- I'll... No, I'll go.
- I have school tomorrow. So I gotta...
- Yeah.
...get to those damn kids.
Totally. I will see you later, then.
Hey, I was thinking since I'm in town,
it might be nice
to get to know your family.
Well, with Polly missing, my mom is
pretty much my family. And the twins.
But I wanted to tell you, I asked Jughead
Jones to meet us at the FBI office.
He's been helping me with the case.
This is an official FBI investigation now.
No Jugheads allowed. Tell him.
Okay. So, what is your strategy
moving forward?
The Lonely Highway is 200 miles long.
How many rest stops are along it?
How many stretches of beaches or marsh?
- How many cul-de-sacs?
- I get it.
There's ground to cover.
Let's start covering it.
We already have.
I've got ten agents on the Lonely Highway,
searching every lot, field and ditch.
Okay. Shouldn't I be canvassing with them?
No, I need your expertise here
with something I'm surprised
you haven't brought up yet...
your father.
Some of the remains date back
to when he was still alive
and actively killing people.
There have been murders since he died.
We should be looking
for someone in their 50s or older.
Or you buy my theory
that it's an assortment of killers.
- What if your dad's one of many?
- What do you want me to be doing?
Didn't your father undergo extensive
analysis at the Sherwood Asylum?
- Yeah.
- Let's start with reviewing those tapes.
Parent-Teacher Night
is always nerve-racking.
But this one is make it
or break it for us.
We need to show the parents
that we can educate and protect their kids
during these troubled times.
Archie, I'd like you to join Kevin
in giving tours of the school.
Good idea. With Toni out
on bed rest for her pregnancy,
- we're short on tour guides.
- I can do that.
Oh, Chadwick.
Since you picked up, does this mean
you've signed the divorce papers?
No, Veronica. I'm your husband
and you're my wife.
And what we went through
binds us for life.
For God's sake, Chad.
Stop wasting my time
and sign the damn papers.
Cheryl Blossom, have you lured me
out here to seduce me?
Hmm. Mayhap, Minerva.
But it's also time to harvest
our sweet, sweet sap,
which will become
this year's bounty of maple syrup.
What is it?
I'm shooketh.
Our maple trees have always provided.
This is your fault.
You are not meant to be happy.
The curse won't allow it.
The maple groves will be nothing
but a burden on us, barren.
We must pray for deliverance.
The only praying that needs to happen
is for sanity,
which you seem to be sorely lacking.
Ta-ta, Nana.
- Samm, what's the good word?
- I got great news, pal.
Pop Culture Weekly wants to publish
an excerpt from your new book.
That's great exposure.
What are we sending?
That's the rub. Pop Culture Weekly
wants something more...
sensational than what you've been writing.
Yeah, aliens as a metaphor for trauma.
I'm still trying to get underneath that.
Great. But they usually give this slot
to Stephen King.
Maybe you can channel him
instead of Raymond Carver.
Bye, Jones.
You betrayed me at that game.
Mr. Lodge, you're right.
It won't happen again.
You have my loyalty.
That's a lovely mea culpa,
but that football game
sparked some life
into the former town of Riverdale.
You can feel its broken spirit rebuilding.
Riverdale High, which should be rubble,
is hosting a Parent-Teacher Night.
What can I do to redeem myself?
- Do you know what palladium is?
- It's like gold, right?
Only rarer and more valuable.
I've been digging for it
behind my prison walls.
But the palladium vein beneath it
is completely tapped
and is yielding next to nothing.
Now we need to move to the vein
underneath the Blossom Maple Groves.
Luckily, I have an idea
that will take care of the prison
and help bring about
Riverdale's ruination.
What do you need me to do?
I'll handle the prison.
You get me those groves.
On it, boss.
- General Taylor.
- At ease, sergeant.
I didn't want to say anything
until top brass signed off on it,
but I nominated you for a Silver Eagle
Medal for your last mission.
For acts of bravery under enemy fire
and overwhelming odds.
All due respect, sir, but that mission
was a disaster. I lost ten men.
So did I.
But you saved Corporal Jackson's life.
- Carried him 14 miles on your back.
- I appreciate this, truly.
But accepting an honor for that mission
just doesn't feel right to me.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But you will be accepting
the Silver Eagle.
And that's a direct order.
Now, brief me on how
your recruitment efforts are going.
Screw you, Stephen King.
- What's up?
- There's something on this tape.
How were relations
between you and your wife Alice?
We weren't in a good place.
She wouldn't touch me or even look at me.
So I started connecting
with women on Nedd's List...
That's how women working the
Lonely Highway make their connections too.
Ms. Veronica, this arrived for you
at the Pembrooke. It's from Mr. Gekko.
From Chad?
Ugh. Pray to God
these are my divorce papers.
I'd like to pose a question that goes
to the heart of being a soldier:
When issued an order,
do you follow it without question?
Sir, yes, sir.
Good answer.
What if you don't believe in that order?
What's your responsibility then?
What do you do?
You follow the order, Sergeant Andrews.
No questions asked.
Anyone, even a general,
is capable of making a wrong call, sir.
My granddaughter is not at home.
And you, dear boy,
are certainly not her type.
I'm actually here to see you, Ms. Blossom.
About your lovely groves.
May I come in?
I don't know why Juniper
and Dagwood can't share a cake.
Cooper residence.
Are Juniper and Dagwood all right?
What kind of accident?
So I have a favor to ask.
Can I j...? Can I say something first?
I'm sorry that I tried to kiss you.
That was totally inappropriate of me.
Well, I leaned in too.
I'm sorry. Things are just complicated
for me right now.
I know you've met Betty.
She and I had a terrible breakup
back in high school,
and I never really recovered.
And my most recent relationship
was more toxic than nuclear waste.
Define "toxic."
It's this girl, Jessica.
Um, she's also a writer.
We would drink a lot, party a lot.
We'd fight, break up, get back together.
Got it. Well, then, as they say,
let's just be friends.
So as your friend, can I ask you my favor?
Sure.
So Pop Culture Weekly wants to run
an excerpt on my new book,
which is great,
but I'm having bad writer's block.
Like when I was back in New York
before I finished The Outcasts.
Well, what'd you do back then?
Maple mushrooms.
Yup. I took a trip,
had some psychedelic visions,
and when I came to,
I had written 500 pages.
By ingesting magic fungi?
I have, uh, some personal trauma
that I can't access.
I'm hoping that these maple mushrooms
will allow me to break through.
So I need someone that I trust
to just watch over me,
make sure I don't get into any trouble
while I'm under.
I'm sorry, Jughead,
but I can't help you with this.
As your friend, I don't think
you should be doing psychedelics,
alone or with me.
Why do you have to go back?
You don't owe him anything.
I do.
A few years ago, Chad and I went
to a party on Marcia's Vineyard.
We had too much to drink
and got into a terrible fight.
And I was so angry that I...
I wished he would just die...
put me out of my misery of a marriage.
Okay, so you had...
You had a dark thought.
So has everyone.
True. But that night, we left.
We got into the helicopter
to fly back to the city.
Chad was at the stick,
something malfunctioned,
and the next thing I know,
I'm waking up
in Columbia Presbyterian Hospital.
What?
The helicopter crashed?
- You didn't do anything wrong.
- I did.
I wished him dead.
And then I stayed with him out of guilt.
Now I have to face him, Archie,
if only to get closure.
And then I'll be on the first train
the next morning.
The next morning? Does that mean...?
No, no. I'm staying with Katy
in Washington Heights.
And once all of this is behind us,
we'll be free to be together.
Sweethearts, what happened
at school today?
Your principal seems to think
that you pushed your classmate
down some stairs on purpose.
Jerry said Mommy was dead.
Jerry got a concussion
and he broke his shoulder.
And it could've been much, much worse.
Juniper, Dagwood. He could've died.
How dare you, Nana.
These groves were my birthright.
- You had no right to sell them.
- The groves are worthless.
Now we've passed them on,
the curse shall be upon them.
There is no curse!
Hey, Speedy. Yeah, it's Jones.
Yeah, I know, it's been a while.
How are you? Good.
How is that stock
of maple mushrooms holding up?
Great. No, but I moved.
I'm in Riverdale now.
Could you send a runner?
That's awesome, man.
Cool, you are the best. Thanks.
Hello?
Sergeant Andrews, this is
Sara Bellum with The New York Times.
I'm calling about
your last tour of duty. In Uzbekistan.
What about it?
I've been investigating your CO,
General Taylor,
who I believe sent you
on a dirty mission. Can we meet?
They pushed a kid down the stairs, Glen,
on purpose.
And they had no remorse, none.
I'm worried that they're bad seeds, like...
I'd like to meet them.
- Especially after what you've told me.
- Why?
I mean, you're also trying to get
to know my mom better.
What gives?
I guess you'd find out eventually.
"Family of Darkness:
Varying Displays of the Serial Killer Gene
in the Cooper Family Tree."
Glen, what is this?
It's my dissertation.
About me and my family?
Yeah. Betty, the Coopers
are a perfect case study
of nature versus nurture.
Look, you and Charles both have the genes.
He's a serial killer, you're not.
Your father didn't have the genes,
but he was a murderer. Why?
Glen, people are dying...
People are dying on the Lonely Highway,
and you're working on a... A term paper?
Is this why you came to Riverdale?
I came for both reasons.
Okay, fine. Then I quit.
You're not gonna do that.
You need me to find your sister.
And besides,
aren't we having a good time here?
Does that answer your question?
It's messed up, Uncle Frank.
My CO, General Taylor,
arrived in Riverdale,
wanting to award me the Silver Eagle Medal
for my last mission.
Then I got a call from a reporter
at The New York Times
who's investigating that mission, among
others, all ordered by General Taylor.
I think General Taylor's trying
to get ahead of this investigation.
And I think that mission I led was shady,
and now he's trying to turn it
into some kind of heroic event.
Yeah, well, it'd be harder to discredit
a mission that's celebrated
and splashed all over the news.
Taylor wouldn't be the first general
trying to buy a soldier's loyalty
with a medal.
So, what do I do?
Do you wanna be the guy
who helps sell the cover-up
or the guy who stands up against it?
I won't disrespect
the sacrifice my men made.
Good, you hold on to that.
Even if you're called before the Senate.
I appreciate the counsel.
By the way, how are you holding up?
It's, uh, kind of strange in here, Arch.
Something's brewing.
You can feel it. Like a riot.
Keep your head down and lay low.
I gotta run.
It's, uh, Parent-Teacher Night.
All right. Good luck out there, soldier.
I asked for the groves and you delivered.
Welcome back to the fold, Reggie.
So when do we start to dig?
Let's say two weeks.
But first, we savor
tonight's fireworks at my jail.
Nice try, you simpletons.
But you'll be shocked to learn
the contract you have
is totally devoid of meaning.
I had Nana Rose declared legally senile
half a decade ago.
She has no power to do anything.
Now it's time for you to accept the fact
that you will never get
my precious groves.
Toodles.
- Mr. Lodge, I th...
- No. No, no. No excuses. Just fix it.
Jess. What are you doing here?
Surprised to see me?
Guess Speedy didn't mention
that I'm his new runner.
No, he didn't.
Yeah, when he told me you asked
for maple mushrooms, I got nostalgic.
What do you say, Jones?
One last trip for old times' sake?
- Baby, are those the shrooms we're doing?
- Excuse me, who are you?
I'm his new girlfriend.
Yeah. I'll take it from here.
Thanks.
All right, then.
That'll be 500 for the fungi.
Is there any way you can spot me?
Typical, Jones. You have a week.
Or else I'll come looking for you.
Did I miss something?
Clearly, there's no talking
you out of this.
But only this once.
Chadwick, I distinctly remember
making reservations at Fukumomo,
so whatever game you're playing...
Thought this would be more fun.
Like those early days
when we didn't have any furniture.
Chinese food by candlelight.
You said you'd have dinner with me.
Since this might be the last night
I see you, I wanted it to be special.
That's sweet. But you left out the part
where you blackmailed me
into coming with compromising photos.
Veronica, please. It's just dinner.
We can talk about the good times too.
It wasn't all bad, was it?
We had our moments.
All right, dinner here is fine,
but only because I haven't had
proper Chinese food in months.
Okay.
Voila.
I cooked the maple mushrooms into a sauce.
Pop's very first psychedelic cheeseburger.
I like it.
Delicious.
You don't have to stay with me
the whole time,
you can just check in periodically.
Okay. See you later.
Look what I found.
Our first date.
I can't believe you thought
a tour of the London Dungeons
was the way to woo me.
Our wedding song.
The first time we danced
as husband and wife.
Would you do me the honor
of making it our last too?
We've been through so much, Veronica.
I genuinely thought
we'd be together forever.
Chad?
That night...
the night of the accident...
I always wondered...
you didn't crash on purpose, did you?
Why would you ever think that?
We almost died.
Because then we'd be together forever...
in a different way.
Veronica, all I ever wanted to do was
just make you as happy as you make me.
I signed the papers
right before you walked in.
I told you,
I just want one last night together.
Thank you, Chad.
Tonight's making me happy.
Tick, tick,
boom.
If you won't sell them now, maybe
you will after they're burnt to a crisp.
And here is where I lead
your shining stars in song.
Kevin is an amazing glee club director.
As a matter of fact...
Not to worry, folks.
It's probably just the circuit breaker.
Why don't you wait here
and I'll be right back.
He was in the Army. He's got it.
Juniper, would you mind
getting the door for Grandma?
Were you expecting anyone?
No, I may have forgotten
to invite the Blossoms.
Charles.
Hey, Mom. Little sister.
Hi, Betty. Have you missed me?
Okay, I'm gonna need you
to explain what's going on.
I've been, uh, visiting Charles in prison
over the years.
They have guns, Mom.
I see that. They're not gonna hurt us.
Let's just get through whatever this is.
Why are you here, Charles?
Destiny.
There was an explosion at the prison.
While the other prisoners
headed off for the hills...
We came here,
to celebrate with our family.
Chic and I would like to be married,
with our family present.
How? You don't even have a minister.
Um, about that, Betty,
Charles had me get ordained online
- so I could marry them in prison.
- But this is so much better.
I mean, at home sweet home.
Watches, wallets, cell phones,
jewelry in the backpack.
Come on, hurry up.
What's going on out there?
Okay, okay, okay.
Drop it.
There's two more by the circuit breaker.
The school's under some attack.
Yeah. My dad texted me, said there was
a breakout at Hiram Lodge's prison.
- We need to move out.
- There are 11 civilians in here.
We don't know how many armed inmates
are out there. We stay put.
Then we barricade all entrances
and secure all access points.
Kevin, hold down the fort.
In front of these witnesses
and by the power vested in me
by the Universal Life Church,
I now pronounce you husband
and husband.
Juniper, don't get that.
Hey.
Glen, what are you doing here?
Glen, as in Glen Scot?
Charles? It can't be.
It is.
Right, you two went
to the Academy together.
Is that why you're writing
your dissertation about us?
- He's doing what?
Yeah. Yeah. He's writing a paper
about serial killers.
You know, nature versus nurture.
How it relates to the Cooper family.
What the hell, I don't count?
Of course you do, babe.
Since my old rival from the Academy
is interested in learning
what makes a serial killer tick,
I think we should play a game.
Would you put that gun away?
We're in a high school.
As far as I'm concerned,
we're behind enemy lines, sergeant.
- Hello? Anyone in here?
- Uncle Frank.
Archie, open up.
It's a good thing you told me
about Parents Night.
Kev's dad said there was a prison break.
Maybe not. I overheard inmates saying
they're getting paid to trash the town,
especially this school.
Only Hiram Lodge would be
crazy enough to do that.
He's made us a target, we gotta go.
You only have six bullets in that gun.
What are you gonna do when you run out?
The smart play here is to withdraw.
You want us to lead civilians out
into open hostile territory?
I went to this school,
I grew up in this town.
We can slip out through a tunnel.
I can get everyone
to the sheriff's station.
Sounds like a plan, sergeant.
So this fun game is called Pincushion Man.
Where the youngest member of a family
takes a pin and sticks it
in the Pincushion Man.
Tonight, that man is Glen.
- No.
- And if memory serves,
Juniper is the youngest member
of our family by three minutes?
Here's your pin, little lady.
All you have to do is stick it
in the Pincushion Man, nice and deep.
Please, please, Charles, I'm begging you.
She's 9 years old, okay?
This will scar her
for the rest of her life.
Me and you, we're lost causes,
there's no hope for us.
But there's still hope
for them, okay? Please.
Please let there be hope for the twins.
Please.
You're right.
Juniper doesn't need
to lose her innocence tonight.
That means you have to take her turn.
One round of Pincushion Man...
then we'll get back to the wedding.
And then we'll be gone in the dark.
Fine.
Juniper, Dagwood, get upstairs.
Please don't do this.
I don't have a choice.
Trust me.
Rot in hell, Glen.
I can't believe she did it.
Mom.
Mom?
Glen.
We need to get him
to a hospital right now.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, no!
Jughead?
Tabitha. Oh, you're here.
Oh, my God, it's my muse.
Guess the shrooms kicked in, huh?
Shouldn't you be writing?
I've already completed it. The first part.
Who cares? Will you just dance with me?
- You have no idea what you're missing...
- I'm good, thanks.
- Don't be such a Betty.
- A what?
First sign of fun, you try to kill it.
Yep. Okay. Time for my contingency plan.
Bondage. Nice.
I'm sorry, but this is for your own good.
You have to get some real writing done.
I'll be back in the morning.
Wait, you're not serious, are you?
- Write. Write.
- Tabitha. Tabitha.
Tabitha, don't!
I can help you
out of this jam, baby.
Jess?
Oh, I knew you'd come back.
Of course.
Now calm down and let's get lit.
I'm in the mood to fool around.
I wish I could, but...
That won't be a problem.
Betty?
Shh. It's okay, Jug. I'm here now.
It was really awful what I did to you
senior year, wasn't it?
Can you ever forgive me?
Yeah. Yeah, I can forgive you.
It was really awful what I did to you
senior year, wasn't it?
Archie and I kissed...
I can help you
out of this jam, baby.
Mumzie?
- What are you doing here?
- Nightmare child,
I've escaped that hideous prison,
and praise God I did.
Flames are encroaching upon Thornhill.
Quickly, to the window.
Our groves...
The curse.
The curse of our ancestors demands
that all living Blossoms must die.
Unless...
Unless?
We sacrifice the interloper.
Oh, hell, no.
No, Min-Min, wait!
There's no time to give chase.
We must pray.
Pray for what?
We must pray for wind, to divert the fire.
What the hell?
You lied to me, Chad.
I can explain.
You told me you signed the divorce papers.
All that talk about not wanting to fight
- about closure?
- Hear me out.
Over the past year, I got involved
in an investment scheme.
It was supposed to be a sure thing,
an easy way to get us out of debt.
What debt?
I made some bad investments,
but I figured out a way to get us out.
It just meant borrowing
from other investors.
Tell me you didn't.
I had to make the investments
in the name of an existing company.
So I used your new jewelry store,
La Petite Bijoutière.
This is unbelievable.
You need to sign
those damn divorce papers right now.
Why would you want me to do that?
If we divorce,
I can testify against you in court.
No one would believe
that the She-Wolf of Wall Street
didn't know about the dirty dealings
going on in her business.
Don't worry, babe.
I'll make it all back. I just need time...
and a little help from you.
Sergeant, you have something
to discuss with me?
I do, sir.
I won't be accepting your commendation.
If I'd trusted my instincts
over your orders,
my men might still be alive.
And I know there's
some sort of cover-up going on.
I wanna make you a hero, Andrews.
But if you're not gonna play ball,
then I'll make you the scapegoat.
You have a choice,
dutiful soldier or traitor.
I'm at peace with my decision.
And if you do force me
to take the stand, I'll speak my truth.
Yes.
And we'll see who Washington believes.
"The Transubstantiation"?
Hey, how are you guys doing?
Uncle Frank's gonna lay low
here for a bit.
My mom will talk to the parole board
about how he helped us.
Yeah, fingers crossed
Mary Andrews comes through.
Hey, you on the train yet?
Archie, I'm staying in New York.
Why?
I have some business things to sort out.
I'll explain everything when I get back.
Ronnie, don't do this.
I have to. Just for a few days.
Fine. Have fun.
Thornhill didn't burn
because of that freak windstorm
but a lot of the groves did.
Cheryl will be begging us
to buy them from her now.
And the way my inmates left
Riverdale High, it won't reopen for weeks,
if ever.
You've done well, Reggie.
And today, today's a good day.
Okay, thanks for letting me know.
Bye.
That was Glen. He's okay.
Just a flesh wound, like I intended.
And Charles is still in the ICU
at Shankshaw,
but it seems like he's gonna make it.
There is something else though, Mom.
Um, the FBI has decided to...
relocate the Lonely Highway case upstate,
closer to their northern office in Derry.
But I'm not going
to stop looking for Polly, Mom.
As Glen so helpfully reminded me,
I do have an instinct for these things.
I will get justice, Mom.
Jughead, I brought you food...
Oh, my God.