Previously, on
"Riverdale"...
I just have to ask.
When you were pretending
to be with Betty...
you didn't feel anything,
did you?
I can't stop thinking
about you, Betty.
I've tried,
but it's impossible.
I wanted to share
something with you.
It's a song I wrote for you.
Stop. Whatever this is,
it's just over.
Hey, Mom, I'm ready to get
serious about the Naval Academy.
He's dying, Archie.
And I don't know what to do.
- What is this?
- Footage of their houses
being watched
from across the street,
for hours upon hours.
Maybe it's just a prank.
This is clearly an escalation.
It's a warning or a promise
of violence to come.
This was on our doorstep.
Maybe it's another copycat?
I've seen this place before.
Oh, my God.
Are they stabbing Mr. Honey?
Hey, did you
reach out to Mr. Honey?
We did, he's fine.
No one's tried to kill him.
Well, for now, at least.
In the meantime, you mind
breaking this down for me?
Well, it's the Auteur again.
Seems like they've moved on
from recreating a killing
to re-enacting
a metaphoric murder.
Us and our friends
getting Mr. Honey fired.
And there is one other thing.
I wrote a story
Killing Mr. Honey,
within which was a
fictionalized version of this cabin.
I don't think
that's a coincidence.
All right, uh, who else knew
about that story?
- Just us.
- Yeah.
Me and Betty.
I mean, unless
I'm being watched or hacked.
This is interesting.
It's four ticket stubs.
From, like,
the movie theater?
Admission to watch the tapes?
Stubs have the letters
"B" and "V" on them.
The hell?
Like Betty and Veronica?
No, Blue Velvet.
Like Blue Velvet Video?
As in the one place that all
roads keep coming back to,
that video store
and that crypt-keeper, David.
If he's not the Auteur, he's
connected to the Auteur somehow,
- or at least he's a fan.
- We'll bring him in.
I'll call you in the morning.
Get some rest.
Okay, good night.
Early morning run, Archiekins?
I got my physical for the
Naval Academy this week.
Well, I find it hard
to believe
they wouldn't be impressed
by my teenage Thor.
You could always serve
your country in the USO.
- What are you talking about?
- Oh, nothing.
This new song you've written.
- Oh.
- Mmm-hmm.
That is nothing. Just
something I'm kicking around.
Play it for me.
No, Ronnie,
I stink and so does this song.
Trust me.
Okay.
I do like the idea of you
getting back into music, though.
Right now, my focus is on
impressing the Commandant.
And you will.
Because I'll be there
to make sure of it.
It's Daddy.
- He wants me home for breakfast.
- That's too bad...
'cause I was gonna ask you if
you wanted to join me in the shower.
Hey, there you are.
Come, sit, join us.
I have news.
Please don't tell me you and
Mom are chaperoning prom?
We are, but no.
My news is that
according to my doctor,
my core strength
is building back up.
In fact, my grip is almost as
strong as it was pre-diagnosis.
- What are you saying, Daddy?
- I'm beating it.
I'm beating this damn disease.
Honey, that's incredible.
It is, assuming it's true.
Forgive me
if I call your doctor
to confirm that this isn't
another one of your stories?
Fine.
Does he know why
you're bouncing back?
I've been trying this new workout
regimen that seems to be helping.
Thank you, Doctor. TTFN.
Well, it seems to be true.
Well, this calls
for celebration.
Cheers.
Salud.
Huh. He's not talking.
Unless you count movie quotes.
Well, what did he have to say about
his store's initials on those ticket stubs?
- He's never seen them before in his life.
- Right.
You know, I don't know if this creep
is responsible for making the videos,
but I can't shake the feeling that
somehow he is profiting off them.
Same.
Where's your partner-in-crime?
She's following up
on another lead.
What exactly are you
accusing me of, young lady?
I'm not accusing. I'm asking.
If I made a videotape of you and your
classmates murdering poor Mr. Honey?
Things haven't changed much,
I see.
- Mr. Weatherbee, you're back?
- Indeed.
Just in time for senior prom
and graduation.
How... How are you?
I told Edgar I wasn't the mole.
He cut it off.
I make it through most nights
without waking up screaming.
Two businesses? Another
besides this community center?
Yes, Commandant. Archie is also
the owner of Andrews Construction,
a business he inherited
after his father's passing.
Well, I have to say, I am truly
impressed by you, Mr. Andrews.
Thank you, sir.
However,
when it seemed like you
were no longer
interested in the Academy,
I started looking
at other candidates to appoint.
Is there someone else
you're considering, sir?
Yes, a young man from Queens,
who's been training rigorously
for the Academy.
He's also a boxer like I was.
And, as you know, we have a
proud boxing tradition in the Navy.
I'm looking for a champion.
Crazy idea,
if you're considering Archie
and someone else,
how about deciding it
with an exhibition bout?
Right here at the El Royale.
You know, I do feel
that Archie and this young man are
otherwise evenly matched.
Okay. I'll have my office
reach out to K.O. Kelly,
to see how quickly he can
hop a train to Riverdale.
Wait a minute. K.O. Kelly
is your other candidate?
Yes. Why? You know him?
Um, yes.
He's only dating
one of my BFFs, Katy Keene.
Well, Ms. Bell was a bust.
Yeah, well, Charles
didn't have much luck
with the video store's
owner, either.
You know, I do have an idea
of someone we could talk to
who might be able
to give us dirt on David.
The only caveat being
he's tried to kill me.
Our momentous best day
is almost upon us, T.T.
Can I ask, why do you want
to be prom queen so badly?
Want, T.T.?
Does Elizabeth want
to be the Queen of England?
A better question is why don't
you wanna be prom queen?
Listen,
if it's important to you,
it's important to me.
But the only royalty I care
about is being Serpent Queen,
which I will be, again.
You'll see.
Hey, Cheryl, Toni. Is this where
I sign up to run for prom person?
Oh, no, Kev, I don't think
you wanna do that.
Yeah, no, I don't, actually, but Fangs
has always wanted to be prom king,
- so here we are.
- Well.
I hate to rain
on Fangs' parade,
but Toni and I are campaigning
to be co-queens,
and it has been my destiny to
wear that prom crown since birth.
I have spent my entire life
fantasizing about being prom queen,
and a part of that fantasy
is that I exist in a world
where everyone wants me
to be prom queen
and certainly not themselves.
Does that make sense?
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you, Kevin. As my
friend, I knew you'd understand.
*RIVERDALE (US)*
Season 05  Episode 01
Episode Title:
"Chapter Seventy-Seven: Climax"
Whatever happens
with your fight,
I've booked us the presidential
suite at the Five Seasons
for our apres-prom rendezvous.
It'll be just you, me,
a bathtub full of rose petals and...
K.O. Kelly!
- Ronnie.
- Hi.
Hey.
Welcome to Riverdale.
K.O., this is Archie Andrews.
- Archie, this is K.O. Kelly.
- Ah...
So, you're my competition.
No offense, but are we
even in the same weight class?
I'm bigger
than I look, bro.
Boys, boys! Save the sparring
for the ring.
I promised Katy I'd show
K.O. a good time tonight.
Yeah, I'm down. But first, Ronnie, do
you know where I can drop my stuff?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Archie has graciously agreed to have
you stay with him and train at his gym.
- I'm heading there now if you need a ride.
- All right.
Play nice, boys.
Well, well, well. Never
thought I'd see you two again.
What brings you
around these parts?
Look, Bret, we know you sold
your sex tapes to Blue Velvet Video.
Now, the owner, David, keeps
coming up in an ongoing investigation
that we're conducting,
but he's not talking to us.
We need a way in.
We need leverage.
Yeah. I know David.
But if he's not talking,
why should I?
See, I happen to have a friend
in there with you.
His name is War Baby. Mmm-hmm.
Do you know who he hates
more than anyone?
Preppies.
What's the investigation?
Someone is making videos
of us and our friends
doing disturbing,
violent things.
We think this David person
is connected to them.
Did he ever mention or host any
screenings with the videos in stock?
Some of David's customers
prefer... shared experiences.
Underground, immersive
red-band screenings.
If we wanted to attend one of these
screenings, what would we need to do?
You'd have to be on the list.
Or you'd have to prove to David
that you're the real deal.
Bring him a tape.
Something to make him sit up
and take notice,
like, say, a snuff film.
Holy moly! That guy's
gotta have 50 pounds on you.
Yeah, no joke.
What am I gonna do, Mr. Keller?
He's gonna cream me
tomorrow night.
Well, honestly, Archie,
I think a little psychological
warfare might be your best bet.
You're smaller than he is,
but I'm willing to bet
you're stronger.
Let's go show 'em.
- You got a mean left hook on you, K.O.
- Thanks.
Been punching bag
since I was a baby.
Look, I promised Ronnie
no betting on our actual match,
but how about you and me
make a little side bet?
That, pound for pound,
I'm stronger than you are.
Unless you're too scared.
Twenty... 21...
27... 28... 29...
91... 92... 93...
122... 123... 124...
129... 130...
131...
Okay, I'll admit it.
You got more endurance.
But when it comes to brute
power, we'll see who's stronger.
The Heavyweight Heartbreaker
or the Red Hope.
Yeah, we will.
And tomorrow
your ass is grass.
But, tonight, Ronnie wants us
to show you a good time
so we're going
to her speakeasy.
Her what?
Okay, I know this is Riverdale,
but where do we get
a snuff film
in which someone
gets murdered on screen?
But those are just
urban legends, I thought.
Well, not according
to Nicolas Cage movies.
- Maybe we can make one.
- A snuff film?
Well, a facsimile of one.
It just has to be
convincing enough
for David
to let his guard down.
We could even borrow the
equipment from the AV club.
And Jellybean probably still has that
fake blood left over from Halloween.
Who's our murderer?
Who's our victim?
We just need a brute
and a scream queen.
No, I won't help you.
No, no, Cheryl,
it's not an actual snuff film.
It's an act. It's a way
to get closer to the Auteur,
the person who's been creating
those re-enactment videos,
including the one
with Jason and your father.
I do want to expose
that defiler.
What's this movie about anyway?
Uh, it's a classic tale,
one as old as time.
Girl meets a boy, boy
promises to make girl a star,
and then the boy
kills the girl.
Charming.
Okay, but I'll need a wig.
I don't want anyone to recognize
me by my signature red mane.
Okay.
Well, how do I look?
Oh, my God,
you look incredible.
What about me?
Terrifying, Reg.
- What happens next, Mr. De Palma?
- Yes.
Now, Reggie
is going to kill you
in the most brutally
exploitative way imaginable,
and I am going to film
the hell out of it.
Veronica speaking French...
Is everyone
having a good time tonight?
Excellent.
In honor of my friend
K.O.'s visit,
I thought I'd share
a little tune for you tonight.
It was written by someone
very special to me.
This one's for you, Archiekins.
♪ There's no warning
When everything changes ♪
♪ You let down your guard
And I saw something strange ♪
♪ I thought he's not made
For this world ♪
♪ And neither am I ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me ♪
♪ Wanna be stronger than I am ♪
♪ And maybe I'm reaching
This place in a feeling ♪
♪ There's no way to know
But to try ♪
♪ So give me tonight ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
All right now, it's straight
to bed, my burly boys.
You've got a big day tomorrow.
K.O., please tell Katy that I'm
sorry she's not gonna be here
when my boyfriend
beats up her boyfriend.
I'll let her know.
Good night.
Wait.
Yeah?
I love you.
I love you, too.
I have a proposal
I'd like to share with you.
I'd like us to host a din-din
before the dance.
I'm down. Who should we invite?
Mmm, the Vixens,
- Kevin, Fangs...
- I was thinking our families.
Specifically yours, my love.
Cheryl, even though I'm out
to my grandparents
and I'm their
favorite grandchild,
I don't think they can handle
some big gay prom dinner party.
Well...
what happens when I meet them
at graduation?
Do I just pretend like
you're not my girlfriend?
Honestly, that's probably
a good idea.
T.T., you can't be serious.
I know it's crazy
and backwards,
but that's my reality, babe.
Hey, I'm curious, Archie.
What made you seek out
the Naval Academy?
Well, all my friends
applied to college.
I kind of missed the boat
on that.
And I got a second chance
with the Commandant.
The Academy, it feels like it
could be a good place to start over.
Completely.
Well...
not completely.
You and Ronnie are in it
to win it, Katy says.
I don't know, bro,
sometimes I worry
that I'm holding her back,
you know?
I feel you.
But that is
for the ladies to decide,
not lugs like us.
We lucked out.
Good night, bro.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Kev.
We have a favor to ask.
We are trying to sell a
snuff film to this video store,
but I can't go in there because
the owner's gonna recognize me
from the time I raided
the place with the FBI.
But I don't want Betty
to go in alone, so...
- You had me at snuff film.
- Thank you, Kev.
We just have to
stop by my house.
I need to grab a backup,
just in case.
Cool.
I need to talk to you
about something, Nana,
and I'm really hoping
that you'll keep an open mind.
I think I know
what this is about.
Your girlfriend stopped by
for a visit, Antoinette.
My girlfriend did? What?
When were you gonna tell me
that you were dating a Blossom?
Nana, it's not what you think.
Cheryl isn't what you think.
That family, over the decades,
has taken everything from us.
- And from our people.
- That's ancient history.
And I promise you Cheryl
is nothing like her family.
If that's true, then why have you
kept her hidden like a dirty secret?
It's because you know
it's wrong.
No, it's because I knew this
would be your irrational reaction.
About this? Yes.
I will not allow you
to date a Blossom.
You look familiar to me.
Both of you do.
You come in here before?
- Nope, never, shockingly.
- Mmm-mmm.
A classmate of mine from prep
school said that you buy videos.
Underground videos.
My friend and I saw this video
at a party last weekend.
And we boosted it. It's of
a girl getting killed for real.
A snuff film.
Let me take a look.
Sorry, kids, you were conned.
Or you're trying to con me.
But this snuff is a fake.
We were worried that this tape might
not be authentic, so I brought a backup
that I know for a fact
is the real deal.
I'm making
this movie so we never forget
what your daddy
sacrificed for us.
You do love your daddy,
don't you, Harold?
- Yes, Mommy.
- What is this?
And you want your daddy
to keep living with us?
The birth of a serial killer.
Yes, Mom.
The Black Hood as a little boy.
Is that really him?
- The Black Hood?
- Yeah.
That's my dad.
This is insane.
Could I screen this at a little
film festival/rave I'm organizing?
Yeah, as long as
we're invited to the screening.
because we don't want Daddy
to be taken away from us, do we?
- No.
- But you,
you will do better.
You must do better.
That a boy. Go get him, Arch.
Welcome to
the Film Society, girlie.
We got your daddy's movie
playing in Room 317.
Welcome to the Film Society.
My dad's playing
in Room 317, apparently.
Awesome.
So, what exactly are we
supposed to be looking for here?
To see if any of the Auteur's
movies are playing
or if any of these people
are fans of his.
Let me just get
a lay of the land first.
Can you
do that, Harold? Convince him?
You're a good boy, Harold.
Your father made a mistake.
But you, you will do better.
You must do better.
- Betty.
- Hmm..
These are
all the Auteur's films.
Well, then
he's gotta be in here.
Do you know who the director
of this is?
of this...
Are you the director?
- Hey!
- Oh, I'm actually such a big fan.
- If I'm lucky, I'll get an autograph.
- Who is that?
Ponytail Playmate.
You're even hotter in person.
Whoa, whoa, hey!
Jug, we're leaving, we're
leaving, we're leaving.
Go, go, go.
Here.
Give me
two big breaths.
Jug, look.
Oh, that's him.
That's gotta be him.
Come on, Arch!
- Jellybean?
- Jughead?
Betty, go. Let me stay
with Jellybean. Go, after him!
-What are you doing here?
Doing here?
My friends and I heard
there was a party.
Am I in trouble?
No, no, you're not in trouble.
Come on, let's go.
Stop, stop, stop!
Fight's over.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
first judge has scored the fight
in favor of K.O. Kelly.
Our second judge has scored
the fight for Archie Andrews.
And our third judge,
the Commandant,
has scored the fight in favor
of K.O. Kelly,
your winner tonight.
You're a hell
of a fighter, Archie.
I'll tell you what,
why don't we stay in touch,
and, come fall,
you reapply to the Academy,
we'll see if we can't
make it happen for you then.
No, thanks, I'm good.
Archie, don't be disrespectful.
Your blood's still boiling.
I understand, son.
I'm not your son.
And I'm not applying
to your school again.
Cheryl, what the hell
did you do?
What the hell, indeed, Toni.
I thought you didn't want
me to meet your nana
because I'm a lesbian.
But, surprise!
It's me and my family
she hates
with a fiery vengeance.
Cheryl, you have to admit that
your ancestors were horrible to mine.
And now, my nana is begging
me not to go to prom with you.
She says that it would
dishonor our family.
Look, I'm truly, truly sorry
I went to see your nana.
But I really hope we're still
going to prom together, T.T.
I hope that when I'm posing
for pictures in my amazing dress,
that you're there with me,
looking equally undeniable.
How did you even know
where to go, Jellybean?
My friend, Lauren, from soccer.
Her older brother
heard about a rave.
- From who?
- I don't know. He's on some email list.
Jug, I swear, I've never been
to a rave before.
Will you just promise me
you're not gonna go
to any more X-rated raves
from now on?
Especially if I end up
in the University of Iowa.
- Okay?
- Yes.
- You promise me?
- I promise.
Archie.
I'm sorry about the fight.
I wish I hadn't suggested it.
And I know
this sucks right now,
but the Naval Academy
wasn't your only option.
Yeah, it kinda was, Ronnie.
Hey, listen.
Do you wanna blow off prom?
We could do something.
Anything you want.
Just the two of us.
No, this will be the last dance
we have with our friends.
Can't miss it.
Are you sure, Archie?
I'm in.
I still wanna take a picture
of you, dear.
You look like an angel.
Thank you, Nana.
Perhaps your camera will capture
the sublime tragedy of my life.
- Okay.
- Don't start crying yet, Cheryl.
Toni, you came.
Was there ever any doubt?
Ready?
Oh, that's nice.
Looking sharp, Archie.
Thank you, sir.
You know, uh, Veronica told me
about the Naval Academy.
- Unlucky break.
- It wasn't meant to be.
Well, look, um...
if you decide to stay
in Riverdale, Archie,
it just so happens
I'm in need of a deputy mayor
to oversee community outreach.
I think
you'd be perfect for it.
Well, Archiekins,
what do you think?
Am I dazzling?
Wow.
Okay, you two, snuggle up
for a picture.
This is a memory you're
going to treasure forever.
Smile and say, "Endgame."
Three, two, one...
Damn, boy, you're handsome.
Like father, like son.
Oh, my gosh. Betty.
Betty Cooper,
you take my breath away.
Jughead Jones,
the feeling's mutual.
Okay, guys, picture time.
Smile.
♪ Kiss me
Out of the bearded barley ♪
♪ Nightly
Beside the green, green grass ♪
♪ Swing, swing
Swing the spinning step ♪
♪ You wear those shoes
And I will wear that dress ♪
♪ Oh, kiss me
Beneath the milky twilight ♪
♪ Everybody one ♪
♪ Everybody two ♪
♪ Everybody free ♪
♪ Everybody wants to live
Like they wanna live ♪
♪ And everybody wants to love
Like they wanna love ♪
♪ And everybody wants to be
Closer to free ♪
I'd like to propose a toast...
to surviving this crazy town
and making it a night
that we'll never forget.
Cheers!
♪ Has our conscience shown? ♪
Happy prom night, lover.
Did you and Daddy
have a nice chat?
Did you know he was gonna
ask me to be his deputy mayor?
He might've mentioned it.
But did he tell you
about my big idea?
No.
I'm going to defer Barnard
for a year
so you and I can work together,
side by side.
Ronnie...
No, I... I don't think
that's a good idea.
I couldn't live with myself if I knew
I was holding you back that way.
But you're not.
I'm choosing to be with you.
This is my decision.
I'd be dragging you down.
I don't want that.
I'd rather lose
one meaningless year
than be out of sync with you,
maybe forever.
Ronnie, I wrote that song
for Betty.
Come again?
The song that you found
and sang at the speakeasy.
It was for Betty.
I don't understand.
- Did you guys...
- We kissed.
Hedwig,
but that's it, and we didn't
wanna hurt you and Jughead.
Well, the votes have been tallied
and double-checked by Ms. Bell.
It is now my honor to announce
this year's prom king and queen.
Actually, make that
prom queens.
Congratulations
to Miss Cheryl Blossom
and Miss Antoinette Topaz.
Your new prom queens,
let's hear it!
Mr. Weatherbee,
fellow classmates,
tonight, Toni and I
are being named
Riverdale High's first
openly gay royal couple.
However, no queenship is
complete without their court.
So would my dear cousin
Betty Cooper, Jughead Jones,
Veronica Lodge
and Archie Andrews,
please join us for the traditional
promenade court dance.
♪ I wanna hold
The hand inside you ♪
♪ I wanna do... ♪
What the hell's going on?
If this is another
Reggie Mantle prank, I...
♪ Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya
Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-yeah ♪
♪ We are vain and we... ♪
I don't think this is Reggie.
♪ I hate people
When they're not polite ♪
♪ Psycho killer
Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa, fa-fa-fa-fa-fa
Far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run
Run, run, run, run away ♪
♪ Psycho killer
Qu'est-ce que c'est? ♪
♪ Fa-fa-fa-fa, fa-fa-fa-fa-fa
Far better ♪
♪ Run, run, run, run... ♪
Stab him! Stab him!
Did they just kill that guy
from Blue Velvet Video?
Yeah, come on. Let's go.
What the hell just happened?
Well, we didn't get to finish
our ceremonial dance,
but we did win our crowns.
Come, fair T.T.,
our carriage is waiting
to whisk us back
to Thistlehouse.
What's wrong, my sugarplum?
I can't go home
with you, Cheryl.
Because of your nana.
But I don't understand.
I thought you picked me.
For tonight, I did.
My nana said that if I
didn't get home by midnight,
that she would never
speak to me again.
I hope you can understand.
Of course, Toni.
Family is
the most important thing.
Go and be with your nana.
And thank you for tonight.
Despite those moments
of video horror,
I will treasure these memories.
Always.
Thank you, Cheryl.
I'm sure we'll be able
to work it out.
- She just needs time, okay?
- Okay.
I don't wanna finish
this conversation, Archie.
But we have to.
I know.
Did Betty tell Jughead about
what happened between you two?
No.
We both swore we wouldn't.
Well, we should keep it
that way.
No need to blow them up, too.
I agree.
So, what do we do now?
Clearly, our last two weeks
of high school
are going to be fraught.
And I don't want them
overshadowed by...
this.
So, after graduation,
we go our separate ways,
Archie.
No big drama,
no fireworks,
I'll go to Barnard,
and you do whatever
feels right to you.
Where did they go?
- Where's the creepy video store guy?
- And our doppelgangers.
Why does every one
of our dances
turn into
a Jamie Lee Curtis movie?
Veronica?
What's wrong?
Was it that horrible video?
No.
It's not that, Mom. Um...
Something happened
between Betty and Archie.
Oh, honey.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It'll be okay.
There, there, my child.
It shall all be fine
in the end.
- Not this time, Nana.
- Oh.
Today, I realized Toni and I
won't end up together.
Once again, I'm a victim
of this family's curse.
I can no longer outrun
my fate.
I am a Blossom...
destined to be alone.
We got an APB out for David.
If he's behind the videos
and he is fleeing,
- he's not gonna get far.
- Okay, but what if he wasn't the Auteur
and he was really killed?
Well, then, the video shown at
prom was an actual snuff film.
What do we do?
We do?
- Continue our search for David.
- Or wait for the next video to drop.
Pray that it's not the straw
that breaks the camel's back.
Synchronized by srjanapala