There's an old adage:
"You can't go home again."
Which was certainly ringing true for us.
Archie had been in a war.
Betty was an FBI agent.
Veronica was married.
Toni was Queen of the Serpents.
And I was a published writer.
So why were we only talking about
how the town of Riverdale had fallen?
And Archie's pipe dream
to somehow save it.
Probably because it was easier
than the conversations that awaited us.
Why didn't you reach out?
I didn't think you wanted me to,
after you left me that voicemail.
On the night of your book launch.
After that, I just assumed
you didn't want to hear from me.
It wasn't my intention.
Sorry if it came off that way.
It is nice to see you.
Even if it's strange to be back here.
It's just deeply uncanny.
Same old Archie though,
trying to save everyone.
Good luck with that, dude.
I mean, I have a book to write.
After Pop's retirement party,
I have to get back to Quantico.
It's good to see you too, Jug.
Even though it is a bit weird.
That's some rock on your finger.
Must be a great guy.
Chad?
Yeah, he is.
Underneath the bluster and bravado.
What about you, Bugle Boy?
I'm sure you've had a swarm of lovers.
I don't know about that.
The last real relationship
I was in was while I was with you.
A devil-may-care fling never hurt anybody.
You should be having fun
at this point in your life.
Once you're married...
Well, that's why this is just
a quick jaunt for me.
I have to get back to my life, my husband.
Yeah, for sure.
Mom?
I brought you a vanilla milkshake.
Oh, thanks, sweetheart.
Will you put it in the fridge?
Keep your voice down,
the twins are asleep.
Sure. Is Polly home yet?
Nope. Not yet.
It's late. Where is she?
Out and about. At work.
You know your sister.
Jones, it's Samm.
Where the hell are you?
And where are your pages?
- Scribners is...
- Forsythe Jones,
you currently owe $9876
to Premiere Credit.
If you do not pay
the outstanding balance within 24 hours...
So how did the Bughead reunion go?
As well as it could have, considering.
Not all of us can be shacked up
with our high school sweethearts.
- Uh, FBI agent. High-school drama teacher.
- I'm technically not an agent yet.
- Oh, my God.
- What? What is it?
Charles. He kept files of everyone
in my family, including me.
And tapes
of our phone conversations, I think.
Edgar?
- Is it really you?
- No, bitch. It's your sister.
- What?
- You're as good as dead to me now.
What? Betty...?
- Is that...?
- Me.
Calling Polly on Halloween, years ago.
Let's get right to it. I want back in
on the family businesses.
Don't you live in New York?
As it so happens, Chadwick and I
are looking for a weekend home.
Possibly here in Riverdale.
I see.
Well, unfortunately for you,
Hermosa moved the rum business to Miami.
And I sold La Bonne Nuit
to Toni Topaz years ago.
- Without telling me?
- It must have slipped my mind.
Like how you forgot to tell me
that you were marrying Chad.
If you're truly interested
in a weekend home,
may I suggest a property in SoDale?
Oh, you mean Stepford
for bougie mobsters? No, thanks. I'm good.
You want me to give you a job?
I need cash. I was hoping you could
set me up with some short-term.
You're lucky
I'm even willing to serve you.
What? Why?
What the hell is he doing here?
No way, Toni.
Gathering some research
for your next book there, Jones?
Hang on. Are you guys actually upset
about my novel?
- You made the Serpents look like fools.
- You mean, the Vipers?
The Vipers were the good guys.
I didn't use your names.
You think people around here
couldn't figure out who...?
What was
that one character's name? Toothy?
Yeah, or Popeye?
You mocked our traditions and codes,
and now you're asking for our help?
Toni.
- Guys.
- Okay, I'll help.
I'll give you some advice.
Watch your back, Jones.
You've made a lot of enemies in this town.
Principal Weatherbee,
as I wrote in my e-mail,
I'm here to relaunch the RROTC program.
Archie, I meant to reply,
but it's been chaotic.
What's up?
Riverdale High might not be opening up
its doors next Monday.
Like everything else in this town,
- our budget's been cut, thanks to...
- Hiram Lodge.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Alice, you're on the PTA.
Any word on which way
the school board's leaning?
The board has some serious doubts.
We're a skeleton crew.
Kevin, you're teaching,
what, five classes?
Drama, debate, biology, gym, and...
And sex ed.
- Are we dead in the water?
- Not yet.
Some board members would like
to see the school stay open,
if we can prove that we have
the personnel and resources,
which is questionable.
The board will hear arguments
before the vote, right?
We should all be there. I'll speak.
In the meantime,
let's target the board members
who are still waffling and work on them.
If we lose this vote, we lose the school.
Another nail in Riverdale's coffin.
It's Tabitha, right? Tabitha Tate?
It is.
And you're Jughead Jones.
Yeah, I am. I noticed that you're looking
for a new waiter. I'm interested.
Thanks, but this isn't
the right job for you.
You don't even know me.
Also, you can't sit here all day.
You have to order food, not just coffee,
and then you have to pay for said food.
My grandfather did things his way
and I do them mine.
And the first rule of my diner
is no running tabs.
Toni Topaz.
- You lost, old man?
- It's okay, guys.
I got this.
You can save your breath.
If you're here to bribe me or threaten me
into giving up Riverdale High...
- How many students do you have?
- A hundred or so.
What if I offer them all
a scholarship to Stonewall?
They'd get a world-class education
at zero cost.
Except that you're on the board
at Stonewall Prep.
Which means
the school must reflect your morals,
which I'm not okay with.
What if I told you
that there was an open position
with a corner office
and a big, fat paycheck?
Thanks but no thanks.
- So we're playing hardball, huh?
- I guess so.
Kevin and I used to sneak peeks
through that window,
hoping you were shirtless.
And now you're spying on...?
Ghoulies. They've turned
my house into a drug den.
That tracks with everything
my mom says about this block.
I'm sorry, Arch.
It's only temporary.
Like Hiram Lodge trying
to close down Riverdale High.
I'm taking this town back.
- Building by building, if I have to.
- Well, I can help.
I mean, I trained with the FBI.
I may just take you up on that.
But first, I need
a little more information.
Where's the rest of your team?
You're looking at him.
Mayor Lodge cut my budget.
I've got no support staff and no deputies,
and I'm covering
a whole damn county by myself.
Unless, of course,
you count Hiram's private security force.
They're connected to SoDale?
They work out of SoDale.
They're corrupt as hell.
You should know
who's running the force. Reggie Mantle.
Maybe Reggie can help me
with my Ghoulie problem.
No. You call him, he'll tip them off.
He's getting a kickback from them.
- You won't get any help from Reggie.
- Not knowingly, anyway.
You may not have any deputies left,
but you still have their gear, right?
Kevlar vests, batons?
You might wanna dust them off.
I gotta do some recon first,
but after that...
we're going in.
I've been thinking about your offer,
Trudy. Is that job still on the table?
Hell, yes, it is.
The Morris William Agency would love
to have you as a sports agent.
But what about the whole L.A. of it all?
I've been wanting to give
the West Coast a try for a while.
Let me make some arrangements
and I'll get back to you, okay?
Okay.
- First class, of course.
- Yes, of course, Miss Lodge.
But I'm having a little trouble
with the credit card on file.
Really?
That doesn't make sense.
Let me get back to you.
It's so weird, Chad.
I was doing some online shopping
and our American Excess card was declined.
All of our credit cards were declined.
The same thing happened to me.
But don't worry.
I'll have it sorted
by the time you get back.
Which is when exactly?
The retirement party is in two days
so probably the day after that.
Well, hurry.
I miss you.
I will.
I miss you too. Bye.
Miss Veronica, excuse me for interrupting.
No problem. What is it?
I've noticed the same car
parked out front for two days.
A black sedan with tinted windows.
I fear you're being watched.
Followed.
I wouldn't be surprised.
Is it a "welcome back to Riverdale" gift
from my father
or a not-so-subtle message
from my over-possessive husband?
It's time to get creative.
And bring an old friend out of mothballs.
How high are you willing
to jump for these?
Let's say 20 grand for both.
I'll take 30.
But it has to be in cash.
Like, right now.
Also, you wouldn't by chance
happen to have any...
tasteful, discreet,
ladylike revolvers
tucked away somewhere, would you?
- This being Riverdale and all.
- I might have something.
Oh, my God. Polly.
You gave me a heart attack.
- You're the one pointing a gun at me.
- Sorry.
Old habits.
It's also 3 in the morning.
You can go back to bed. I'm not a burglar.
Hey, can I...
make you a cup of tea, at least?
Polly, I wanna apologize to you.
I wasn't there for you...
on the other side of The Farm
when you needed me most.
Also, for prank-calling you
that year on Halloween.
I really didn't mean what I said.
Wow.
- It's a deep cut.
- Yeah, I know.
I haven't forgotten.
If it's not too late, I'd like for us
to be real sisters to each other.
- How long you in town for?
- Just a couple days.
Once I finish at the academy,
I'll be home a lot.
I'm surprised
you're not already running the FBI.
I don't know about that.
I've missed you.
Ma, the twins...
We've all missed you.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, honey. How'd you sleep?
Well, I woke up when Polly got home.
Does she usually stay out that late?
She's working at that nightclub,
the Roving Eye.
She waitresses a few nights a week.
Is that a good thing?
She helps with the mortgage,
gets the twins everything they need.
She's doing her best.
We all are.
No, I know. I just remember
the Roving Eye can be sketchy.
Okay, that's not fair, Elizabeth.
You don't get to pop in
and judge your sister.
Or me, for that matter.
Ooh. Can you get that? Might be Toni.
You see the morning paper?
"Local school counselor runs seedy bar
and snake-dances."
It's a hit piece.
Hiram's trying to ruin my credibility
with the school board.
I'll run damage control.
I'll call each board member.
Good.
If Hiram is trying to drag
the Serpent Queen down to his level,
he's gonna get himself bit.
- Archie. What's up?
- Jug.
How's the Five Seasons?
Room service every meal?
Morning, noon and night.
I got an idea
for Pop Tate's retirement gift.
But I was wondering
if one of us should say something.
Give a speech about Pop Tate.
- Since you're the world-famous writer...
- Yeah. Yeah, I'd love that.
Okay, great. Thanks, Jug.
Reggie. Good to see you.
I appreciate you coming out.
Duty calls, Mantle answers.
You're having trouble with your tenants?
I'm having trouble with the gangbangers
using my house as a drug den.
Let's see if there's any merit
to your claims.
It's messy, but I'm not seeing
any evidence of drug paraphernalia.
Okay if we keep looking?
- Nothing here but stale cereal.
- Let's check upstairs.
Sorry, but I didn't see
any contraband anywhere.
Yeah.
It's almost like
somebody tipped off the Ghoulies.
There's nothing more for me to say or do.
- But thanks for your help.
- My pleasure.
Feels strange to think
of not working at this place.
You won't have to deal
with annoying customers like me.
Now, you know I had a lot worse
than you in here, Jughead.
It all worked out, didn't it?
I lived to see my retirement.
And you're a bigtime writer now.
- Always knew you'd make good.
- I'm sorry.
Uh... Those are debt collectors.
Hi there. Counter or booth?
We're looking for someone.
Been known to hang around here.
Jughead Jones. Seen him?
No. I think I'd remember
a weird-ass name like that.
What do you want with him?
Give us a call if he comes in.
Okay, sweetie?
Oh. I'll be sure to do that, pumpkin.
Bye now.
Thank you.
It's not the greatest first impression.
How much you need?
I can loan you some. I've been saving up...
I'm not low enough
to take your retirement money.
I'll figure something out.
Thanks for the interview.
- See you tomorrow.
- Hey, Jones?
If you still want it,
the waiter job's available.
Okay.
In a couple days, could you just call them
and vouch for me and say I have a job?
I'll send them half of my weekly salary
so they don't break my legs?
Yeah. I think I can do that.
Long time no see, Ronnie.
Reginald.
You've been working for my father,
so let's skip the pleasantries.
- Fair enough.
- I need to buy a car.
Nothing flashy, just in good shape
and with excellent gas mileage.
- I'm paying cash.
- Who you running from?
Your husband? Is that how you roll now?
I'm not running from anyone, Reggie.
I'm taking the path of least resistance,
and I'd rather not leave a paper trail.
Now, will you sell me a car or not?
If you're in trouble, talk to your dad.
Really. Talk to him.
He'll help you, even now,
with whatever you need.
- You're sure you saw Polly?
- No doubt about it.
She's hanging with the Ghoulies,
probably using.
Seems like that's a safe bet.
I'm sorry, Betty.
I'm not sorry.
I'm pissed.
So my question is,
when do we kick their asses?
Thanks to Reggie Mantle,
I have intel to sweep and clear the site.
- How many Ghoulies are in your house?
- I counted a dozen.
We hit them hard. We hit them fast.
It's been too long since
the Serpents rumbled with the Ghoulies.
Calm down. I don't want anyone dying,
especially not my boyfriend.
Hopefully, they've dropped their guard
and we find narcotics.
And like Kev said, no one gets killed.
None of us and none of them.
Wouldn't mind breaking a few bones though.
Hell, yeah.
Ready? Three, two, one. Go.
You good?
- Yeah, you?
- Yeah.
Jingle-jangle. Just like the old days.
They've got a lab set up in the bathroom.
Will that be enough to put them
behind bars, Agent Cooper?
Yeah, Kev. That should do it.
- The Roving Eye.
- Hi, this is Polly.
I'm just calling to get my schedule.
Polly Cooper?
You haven't worked here for over a year.
Who is this?
Bad news.
Two more teachers
have defected to Stonewall Prep.
Miss Crouton and Mr. Cedars.
Damn, Miss Crouton! That backstabbing...
We've got a bigger problem.
One of my girls broke into Hiram's office
to see what dirt we could use against him,
and she found his agenda
for the town hall meeting.
It feels like we're in an episode
of Succession.
And besides
deciding about Riverdale High,
Hiram's also putting forth a vote
to unincorporate the town.
Based on the receipts,
he has enough people bribed
or terrorized into passing the motion.
Unincorporate? What does that mean?
It means that all the money
that the town gets from the state
for public services, for maintenance,
for education, it goes away.
It means that Riverdale,
as a town, ceases to exist.
Hiram will get what he's wanted
for years, the death of Riverdale.
So his SoDale can thrive.
If that happens, would we be able to keep
the school open with the board's support?
- Yes, but it will be much harder.
- We need to fight harder.
Alice, go on RIVW
and blow the whistle on Hiram's plan.
He was trying to keep it secret
so no one would oppose him.
We need the public there
so they can vote against his plan.
- What about our teacher problem?
- I can maybe help with that.
How? Do you know
any qualified teachers with degrees?
That's what it takes
to be a schoolteacher.
What if Riverdale went private?
We could choose who we wanted.
Yes, but we'd lose all public funding.
If the town unincorporates,
we lose funding anyway.
We need an investor.
I think I might know someone.
Archie,
if you have any favors to call in,
now's the time.
Reggie suggested I see you again.
I've been running around town,
trying to vamp my way out of a problem,
when, really,
I should be facing it head-on.
With, maybe, your help.
Go on.
Chad is threatened by my "alpha-ness."
Because of that, he can be somewhat
possessive and controlling.
He was having me followed,
but I shot out his goon's tires, so...
Ah. Young love. I remember those days.
I knew you'd relate.
Which is why I'd appreciate
you having a little chat with him.
As only you can, Daddykins.
Nothing too draconian.
Just tell him to stop trying to manage me.
- Or track me when I leave town.
- Why don't you tell him yourself?
He's not taking my hints.
But I'm betting the Hiram Lodge...
could be a lot more persuasive.
And then you don't get your little
Barnard-educated hands dirty, right?
Hmm. So, just to be clear,
you're officially asking me for my help?
Sure.
Yes, I am.
Well, in that case...
no.
Come again.
Remember you called me a dog?
That I needed to be taught a lesson?
It was about seven years ago.
You were cruel, Veronica.
Brutal.
When my body was a mass of bruises.
Well, now it's my turn
to teach you a lesson.
I warned you, from the start,
that no one outside of this family
would understand the Lodge ambition.
You made your bed.
You'll have to deal with Chad yourself.
If that means you have to crawl
into the mud to do it, then so be it.
You're a Lodge after all.
You never had any intention of helping me.
You just wanted to hear me beg.
Hmm. I assume you don't need
my help finding the exit.
But, Polly, it's not every day
that Pop Tate retires.
- We can bring the twins.
- I have to work.
- Can't you take the night off?
- Get off my back.
Polly. Give Mom a break.
It's fine. Polly has to work.
I'm not so sure she does, Mom.
I know you don't waitress
at the Roving Eye.
You've been hanging out with the Ghoulies.
- Elizabeth, stop it!
- How are you making all of this money?
To help out with the mortgage
and support the twins.
- Are you dealing? Tricking? Both?
- It's none of your business.
Actually, it is. Because I care about you.
You don't live here. You deserted us.
Being a sister doesn't mean
coming in for one day
and telling me how to live my life
when you don't know anything about it.
Wait, Polly...
- Samm. How are you?
- At the end of my rope.
Scribners wants pages or their money back.
Yeah, I know. I'm working on something.
What have you been working on?
Actually, uh, let me send it to you.
Let me know what you think.
It might convince Scribners
I'm not a one-hit wonder.
Okay, I'm e-mailing you right now.
I'm grateful for your help.
I'd rather be dealing with this mess
than the one I made at my own house.
Sorry to hear about that.
That's okay.
It'll be okay. I hope.
After Pop's party, I thought you, me,
Jughead, and Veronica could hang out.
Just the four of us.
We haven't done that yet.
No, yeah, that's a nice idea.
Let's do that.
Cool.
Hey, do you want some pizza?
It's the least I can do.
- Yeah. Pizza. Yeah, that sounds great.
- Okay.
- Gonna take a shower first.
- Oh, I should...
I... Me too.
- Wanna go first?
- Should I go home first?
Betty, what just happened?
I don't know.
Something we've been wanting to do
since high school but never got around to.
Yeah. Sounds about right.
- Just to be clear, we're...
- Friends.
Just good old friends.
We're both single adults. We're allowed
to have fun every now and then.
Yeah.
And it's okay
if we keep this to ourselves?
Yeah. Veronica's a married woman.
And Jughead and I haven't dated
for seven years, so...
I think it's okay.
Okay. Good.
What a gift.
Thank you, Archie.
It's from all of us, Pop.
A small token to show
how much you mean to us.
- To Riverdale High. To the whole town.
- Yeah.
You know, I had to drop out of school
to take over this place after my pop...
The original Pop passed away.
I never got to graduate.
This means the world to me.
Jug's gonna say a few words.
Sometimes it can be hard
to put our faith in this town.
But I think Pop created
something really special here.
A place for the lost and wayward souls
of Riverdale to come to.
And I think that's more
than a jukebox or vinyl booths.
It's like a lighthouse in a storm.
Now, Pop himself is many things.
He's a joker.
He's a soldier.
He's a cook.
He's a really good listener.
He's also a father.
He's a son.
And a grandfather.
And to many of us...
and to me personally...
he's about the only reason
that I made it through.
You gave us a home, Pop.
Thank you.
To Pop Tate.
- Who never let the lights go dark.
- To Pop Tate!
I'm glad you came.
I wasn't sure you would,
after I sent you my message.
It sounded rather dire.
Plus, Pop always added a drop
of human kindness to my order.
Have you considered my ask?
To fund Riverdale
and the new teachers it needs?
It's the only thing that might...
Might save the school.
Look, I came here to celebrate Pop,
not get caught up in small-town politics.
I can barely afford
Thornhill's renovations as it is.
I know you think you're cursed
and the sins of your family are so great,
you can't atone for them.
But you're wrong.
There's a war going on
in Riverdale for Riverdale.
We need you.
Sorry. I can't.
It will start as something good and end up
corrupted like everything I try to do.
If you won't do it for the town,
would you do it for me?
Please?
If our love ever meant anything to you,
help us.
If I gave you the money,
who would these new teachers even be?
You're really gonna do this?
You know, run the RROTC
out of your old high school, huh?
If I get a chance to, yeah.
It's why I wanted us to sneak in here,
the four of us.
Hiram's trying to shut this place down.
He's pushing to unincorporate the town,
which would wipe out Riverdale.
My father is nothing if not consistent.
We can stop him.
Or at least slow him down.
How?
We become teachers here.
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's a way to keep the school going.
Which means, if Hiram wins the vote,
we still have a defendable position.
This school.
And if we can save it,
we can give people
one more reason to stay in Riverdale.
In time,
we can bring this town back to life.
Archie, I'm married.
I have a life back in New York.
Yeah, and I have a novel to write.
Veronica,
plenty of people commute to the city.
Jug, you always said,
you do your best writing
in a booth at Pop's.
And it's not gonna be long.
A month or two.
Just to give Weatherbee enough time
to find permanent replacements.
I'm in.
Quantico can wait a couple months.
And I need to be here right now
for my mom and Polly.
Thanks, Betty.
Jug?
I'd have to clear it with my new job.
But why not?
I'd like to shape
some impressionable, young minds.
I'm in too. I'll make it work with Chad.
Considering that what's happening here
is all my dad's fault,
I need to give back more than anyone.
I didn't really wanna be
a sports agent anyway.
That's awesome.
So Bulldogs forever?
Bulldogs forever!
Before the school board votes
on the fate of Riverdale High,
Toni Topaz has asked to say a few words.
Good afternoon.
My name is Toni Topaz, and I am
a guidance counselor at Riverdale High.
"The point of a school board is
to make sure there is equity.
That kids of all ages,
from all different backgrounds,
have equal access to education.
Well, with the help
of one very generous donor,
I'm happy to announce that Riverdale High
will be able to do that
as a private school.
And, unlike other private schools,
Riverdale will be tuition-free.
And we're bolstering our teaching staff
with notable alums,
like Sergeant Archie Andrews,
FBI trainee
and Yale graduate Betty Cooper,
businesswoman
and Barnard grad Veronica Gekko,
and acclaimed author Forsythe Jones III.
So spread the news far and wide
that Riverdale and its children
will not be at the mercy
of Hiram Lodge's destructive whims."
Thank you.
That's very nice.
That was better than Kendall Roy's speech
at the end of Season 2.
And now I'd like to introduce what I hope
will be my last motion as mayor,
a proposition to unincorporate
the town of Riverdale.
All those opposed?
All those in favor?
Majority wins.
The township of Riverdale
is hereby dissolved.
What had taken decades to build
was toppled in the blink of an eye.
With the rap of a gavel,
Riverdale was no more.
And yet, life continues.
Samm, I was gonna call you.
Scribners loved
your story about the old man.
- They what?
- Yeah. They think it's your next book.
There's a huge market right now
for tragic Americana.
Dying community,
all of the miserable people
who live there.
We'll call it Elegy for a Small Town.
What do you think?
- I don't wanna write about that.
- You don't have a choice.
This is your ticket out
of the literary grave you dug.
- Now you need to deliver. Understood?
- Yeah, understood.
Thank you.
Hey, Mom. I checked upstairs.
The twins are playing,
but Polly's still not home. I'm worried.
You know your sister.
She gets angry, storms off.
God knows when she'll be back.
This is what happens.
But this one's on you.
I'm not coming home yet.
I'm gonna stay in Riverdale
a little bit longer, Chad.
Why's that?
My alma mater, Riverdale High, has fallen
on hard times and needs my help.
I'll be teaching there.
- That's absurd.
- No, no.
What's absurd is you freezing
our credit cards.
Especially since I made
most of the money in our joint accounts.
Yeah.
So, if they're not unfrozen
in the next, say, 30 minutes,
I'll consider it an act of aggression.
Like you having me followed.
And the next time you see me,
it'll be on Wall Street, on the floor,
when the markets open Monday morning.
This She-Wolf will tear out your throat
in front of all the other alpha dogs
with zero hesitation.
Is that it, then? Are we done?
You have 30 minutes
to reactivate our cards.
Jug.
Hey. Yeah. Sorry, it's late.
Wondering if you could use a roommate,
now that you're in this big house
all by yourself.
- What happened to the Five Seasons?
- It's a little rich for my blood.
Come in.
- It's Polly. Leave a message.
- Polly, it's me again.
I'm sorry about what I said before.
I really had no right to judge you,
especially after being gone for so long.
It wasn't my place, so...
I wanna tell you that I love you
and that I'm here for you,
so just call me and I'll come find you,
wherever you are.
Or I'll see you when you get home.
Just, please, please, please, come home.