It's been almost a year.
Like the grown-ups in It,
we returned to our haunted hometown
and confronted the darkest monsters
we'd ever faced, ourselves.
We'd survived.
But surviving isn't the same as thriving,
and none of us, it seemed, were thriving.
So?
How did it go? Did you pass?
I... almost passed.
Oh, Reggie, no, I'm so sorry.
But you can take the Series 7 exam again.
You'll be a fully licensed stockbroker.
Yes, or I was thinking...
we could open a casino here in town.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't you remember how much fun we had
running games out of La Bonne Nuit?
I hold very fond memories of that time,
but I've decided
that after the school year ends,
I'm going back to New York.
Really?
What about Carrot Top?
Archie and I are no more.
He understands my future's in New York.
Glad to see
I'm not the only one day-drinking.
Are you here alone?
You just missed Jackson.
He moved back home.
Oh. Thank you. Eric's such a good guy.
Yeah.
Is that why you look so sad?
No, I'm happy for him.
I'm sure we'll see him again.
I, uh...
I don't know if you heard,
but Veronica and I broke up.
For good this time.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
- What happened?
- Seven years happened.
- Yeah.
- We became different people.
Ronnie belongs in New York,
and I belong here in Riverdale.
I'm reopening Andrews Construction.
Oh, looks like we're gonna be neighbors
for the foreseeable future.
I just got permission
to reopen the Riverdale FBI office
because, by the way, you're now talking
to Special Agent Betty Cooper.
- Officially.
- Wow.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah.
When's the graduation?
And can we go?
I missed it.
But I got my diploma in the mail.
Well, damn.
- Can I at least pay for the next round?
- Sure.
And here I thought your days
of summoning me were over, Waldo.
The worm turns, Mr. Jones.
Some of the students are interested
in restarting the student newspaper.
The Blue and Gold.
Trouble is, none of our current faculty
have the bandwidth to supervise it.
- You want me to?
- Yes.
- What do you say, Mr. Jones?
- I say get me that rewrite.
Cameron, put the word out.
The She-Wolf of Wall Street is coming back
to take a bite out of the Big Apple.
What, right now?
I wouldn't do that, Ronnie.
Why not? You said
I could come back whenever I wanted.
Yeah, that was before
you killed Chad in cold blood.
That was self-defense.
I'm sure.
But I doubt any firm would be willing
to hire the Black Widow of Wall Street,
which is what everyone's calling you now.
Maybe call me again in six months.
Are you sure you're not scared
to be toiling away down here?
Not at all, Miss Blossom.
Physical labor will keep me
in shape for football.
Glad to hear it.
Palladium is the missing piece
in my ministry.
The fabled fifth element,
the bridge between the physical
and spiritual worlds
that will grant me power.
- That sounds so cool.
- Indeed.
All right, come.
It's time to wipe the soot off our faces
before we're late for the big surprise.
Keep them closed. Keep them closed.
You know I don't like surprises.
Well, that really sucks because...
Surprise!
Oh, my God, you guys.
Here's to Quantico's latest
and greatest field officer,
Agent Betty Cooper.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Speech! Speech! Speech!
Oh, wow, okay. I was not expecting this.
But it means more to me
than I could ever express,
so... thank you.
It's been a rough year, but...
I love you all.
You've given us a lifetime of reasons
to be proud of you.
This one takes the cake.
And speaking of cake...
- So, what does this mean?
- I'm staying in Riverdale.
Just like I promised my mom.
God knows, there's enough crime here
to last me several lifetimes.
Well, I don't know
if you've heard about me and Archie.
I did, Vee. I'm sorry.
But I'm sure you're excited
to get back to your old life in New York,
even though we'll miss you.
Should we head back to the diner?
I actually asked Delores
to cover the night for us.
Oh, really?
And why is that?
Well, I figured that we didn't actually
get to have our date at Cucina Sacasa.
Oh, true.
- I could go for some Italian.
- Right now?
- I'm glad you're doing better, Alice.
- Yeah.
It doesn't get any easier,
but every day it hurts a little less.
You, um...
You getting out of the house at all?
I'm trying to.
Do you have something in mind?
I have news.
Weatherbee asked me to come back
and run the school paper.
And as long as I don't mess it up,
he said that I could start possibly
teaching again in the fall.
Wow!
Maybe then you'd be able
to move out of Archie's garage.
Oh, man, I was just starting
to love the smell of mold and turpentine.
You know, um, if you're gonna be working
full-time in the fall,
that's when my apartment's lease is up.
You and me? Cohabitating?
- It's Delores.
- Probably the ice machine on the fritz.
Hey, Delores, what's up?
What?
Got any threes?
Go fish, bish.
Holy crap, Pop's is on fire.
- Aw, what the hell?
- They're slashed on this side too.
Guys, get the spares. Fangs, get the jack.
I'm so sorry, Tabitha.
We should've gotten here faster.
Archie, come on,
you did everything you could.
You and your firemen are the only reason
this place is even standing at all.
It's true.
I've never seen tires changed so fast.
How do I call my grandpa in Florida?
What do I tell him?
That our family business went up
in flames?
Delores said it was a Ghoulie
who threw the Molotov cocktail.
- A Ghoulie? What's his motive?
- It wasn't his motive.
I can guarantee that Ghoulie was acting
on someone else's behalf.
Give you three guesses who.
Your dad.
I can't believe
I worked for that sorry SOB.
If the scumbag
who torched this place is a Ghoulie,
Fangs and I will take care of it.
- We'll get confirmation.
- Do that, Toni.
But I don't need confirmation.
I don't think any of us do.
Who else would set fire to Pop's
and slash our truck's tires?
I don't remember ordering room service.
Hiram Lodge, you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an attorney,
one will be provided for you.
I can afford one,
and he'll have me out before dinner.
Woodward and Bernstein.
Seymour Hersh. Ronan Farrow.
- What do these people have in common?
- All journalists.
Yes, they are journalists.
More specifically, they are journalists
who courageously spoke truth to power.
Freedom of the press. This is one
of the most basic building blocks
in a healthy, functioning society and...
we take it for granted out here,
but there are places around the world
where information is controlled
by dictators.
And the truth is shaped
to serve those who are in power.
Kind of like
what the Lodge Ledger does in Riverdale.
Yes.
Yeah, exactly like that.
Hiram's booked.
He's right, he'll beat the charges.
There's nothing we can do
to link him to the arson.
Not yet.
Toni's gonna find that Ghoulie.
In the meantime...
Let's search his office.
There's gotta be something in there
that ties him to this crime
or literally,
any other crime at this point.
And we'd be looking for...?
Shady contracts,
financials, illicit receipts.
- It's not my bailiwick.
- Me neither.
- We need someone who speaks that language.
- Who also wants to take Hiram down.
- Veronica.
The sooner you tell us who paid you,
the sooner it'll be done.
Fine.
- Fangs, turn up the radio again.
- Okay, okay. Okay.
Okay. Fine, I'll tell you.
It was Hiram Lodge.
Not surprised.
Why would you agree?
Torching Pop's, which is right on top
of the Whyte Wyrm, my place.
Why would you risk a war
with the Serpents to help out Hiram Lodge?
A war?
Come on, the Serpents are a joke now.
Driving trucks and having babies.
You've gone soft.
Hiram said
that as soon as Pop's was razed,
Ghoulies would be able to take back
the town, get what we deserve.
You're gonna get what you deserve.
Fangs, the radio!
- I found something.
- What are we looking at?
According to these documents,
my father incorporated SoDale,
even though it's only a muddy field.
Great. So he's done with Riverdale?
On the contrary,
now that SoDale is legally a town,
he can petition the courts
to redraw its borders
and absorb all unincorporated lands.
He's going to annex
the former township of Riverdale,
claim eminent domain,
and grab it for himself.
Including the palladium mines.
He thinks this is the wild, wild west.
Let me take this back to the FBI office.
We'll see if this is legal. If it isn't,
we'll start building a case against him.
- It's Toni.
- Like we suspected,
Hiram paid the Ghoulie to burn down Pop's.
Not just Pop's but all the fires
that have been breaking out recently.
Hiram promised the Ghoulies
the burned husk of the town.
- All he cares about is...
- The mines.
I'm sorry.
Toni, Fangs, Archie.
Yet again, I find myself apologizing
for my father's actions.
Yeah, we don't want an apology.
We want justice.
Serpent justice.
- We'll take care of him.
- No offense,
but I don't think you're gonna be willing
to do what needs to be done.
Yes, we will.
Archie and I both will.
What are the Serpents supposed to do?
Sit back?
Fangs, what we need is someone
to go out and collect signatures.
- So we can reincorporate the town.
- Are you kidding me?
The Serpents don't run errands, Archie.
Of course not.
But this is a different kind of fighting.
As long as Riverdale is unincorporated,
we're sitting ducks.
I'm not sure we've done enough
to inspire the families
that Riverdale is still worth
resurrecting.
So we got to make our play.
That means getting 51% of people living
in our borders to sign an endorsement.
Fine. We'll rally the troops.
But if you two don't take care of Hiram,
we will.
Our way.
Toni's right.
Something drastic needs to happen.
I thought my dad would stop
after he blew up the mines, but...
he refuses to give up.
- He doesn't know how to.
- What do you wanna do?
The only thing that's left.
Let's say my father were to...
go missing.
Let's say he escaped from his jail cell.
Who would go looking for him?
Certainly not my mother.
And not Hermosa.
She feels betrayed by him too.
Sheriff Keller wouldn't.
And Betty would make sure
the FBI doesn't either.
We could take Hiram out
to the maple barrens.
It could be the last thing we do together.
Somehow that would be... fitting.
I'll call Tom.
Tell him to take a long lunch.
What's up?
We're in the middle of something.
Yeah, it looks like you're wrestling
with a Hiram-sized problem, am I right?
Far be it for me to intrude,
I thought you might be interested
in this smoking gun I managed to acquire.
What's on it?
Irrefutable proof.
Riverdale Field Office,
this is Agent Cooper.
Pretty Betty.
It's you.
Don't bother with a trace,
we won't be on long enough.
What do you want?
To congratulate you on graduation.
And to tell you that I have no plans
to come calling on you.
I hope you extend me the same courtesy.
You know I can't make that promise.
Pity...
Betty.
Hello?
- How's the burger?
- Good.
- Well, the kitchen is still operational.
- True.
That's a good thing, right?
- Did you call your insurance company?
- Yes.
But they are not covering this.
Why?
Because the last couple of months,
I've had to choose
between paying my insurance premiums
or paying my waitresses.
I chose my waitresses.
Exactly what they teach you
not to do in business school.
What, be compassionate?
Care about your staff?
On top of which, did you see
what the Lodge Ledger published today?
No. But I was just thinking
about Hiram's fish-wrapper.
- What's it say?
- It's an editorial: "Out with the old.
Like the asteroid that wiped
the dinosaurs off the face of the Earth,
nature or fortune has struck again,
toppling another dinosaur:
Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
The struggling diner
has held on for far too long.
We can only hope that its charred remains
will be swept away quickly,
lost to the winds."
Hey, I've got an idea.
It won't bring back Pop's, but it would
hurt Hiram's stranglehold on the town.
And it might make us feel better.
If you're intrigued,
we'd have to act quickly
and move under the cover of darkness.
Let me guess.
You're not here to give me my phone call?
No. We're not.
Stand up.
The Fire Department's
on standby.
They'll arrive in time to keep the fire
from spreading, but this Ledger is toast.
Assuming you still wanna do this.
You know, Jughead, I pride myself
on always taking the high road.
But a person can only be pushed so far.
It's Archie.
I can't stop thinking
about what that Ghoulie said.
The Serpents are over.
The Serpents aren't over.
They've been on the back burner.
All I've been focused on is the school,
my guidance counseling work, Baby Anthony.
You and I,
we've been Serpents since birth,
and no dumb-ass, freaky-deaky Ghoulie
can take that away from us.
You're right.
But as queen of the Serpents,
I can and I should be doing more.
Every year, our numbers dwindle.
And if the town reincorporates,
I want the Serpents to be a big part
of its reconstruction.
I'm down. What are you thinking?
We start by taking the Serpents
off the roads and back into Riverdale.
Find them a gig
that pays just as well as truck driving.
And we start building up our ranks,
starting with Baby Anthony.
He'll be the symbol
of the next generation of ass-kickers.
Future king of the Serpents.
Exactly.
But we need a current one too.
And that's you, Fangs.
I'm here for it, Toni. All of it.
In unity, there is strength.
It's Veronica.
You ready, Daddy?
What is this?
A public execution?
What are you, my executioners?
You deserve death
for everything you've done.
But, no, Daddy, this is not an execution.
This is an exile.
Yours.
After we show you something.
Where'd you get that?
- Reggie?
- Yeah, it was me.
The point is, we have it.
We've all seen it.
Irrefutable proof that you're a murderer.
You can't wriggle your way
out of this one, Daddy.
In one hour exactly, Betty will turn
that video over to the FBI.
I'd start walking, Daddy.
And I wouldn't stop for a long, long time.
You're turning against your own blood?
I blame Archie. This is his influence.
Don't.
We broke up.
This is all me.
What about my possessions?
We'll sell what we can,
use whatever money we make from it
to rebuild Pop's and the town.
Tick tock, Daddy.
Tick tock.
So, uh, tonight got me to thinking.
What would you say about being
my deputy full-time, son?
That would be an honor, Dad.
I can't.
Because I've decided
once the school year's over,
I wanna give Broadway another shot.
I've been thinking about it
since Josie visited.
It's something I've gotta do now,
or I'm gonna regret it
for the rest of my life.
- To new beginnings.
I just drove past the town hall,
and it is a firetrap.
So we'll host the community meeting
at the El Royale.
- How's it going with the signatures?
- We're not at 51% yet,
but we got a crew out
pounding the pavement.
Okay. Great.
But a lot of the Serpents
have been reporting back.
People are asking what kind of town
the new Riverdale's gonna be.
And they'll wanna know
before they agree to reincorporate.
Like, is there gonna be a mayor?
And if so, who?
I've been turning that over too.
I know who I would vote for.
You, Toni.
- Would you do it?
- What?
Mayor? I mean, Archie, I can't.
- I don't have the bandwidth.
- I understand.
- Fangs?
- Hell, no.
- I just got crowned Serpent King.
- Oh, congratulations, bro.
Why don't you focus on getting people
to the El Royale for the town hall.
And we'll have answers
for people's questions, Toni. I promise.
Miss Blossom?
Miss Blossom.
Look what I found.
Skeletons, Nana. Human skeletons.
Our mines are choked
with God-and-Jason-knows-how-many.
Brittania and I discovered
a veritable boneyard.
Since you seem to know
where all the bodies are buried,
I'm assuming you know about these.
Yes, I was wondering
if they'd ever be found.
The Forgotten.
The Forgotten?
It all began with an ancestor of ours,
one Abigail Blossom.
The year was 1890.
Thornhill still stood, of course,
but it was a girls' school then.
Riverdale was a hateful
and backward place then.
The townspeople were suspicious
of Abigail,
who had no husband
and no intention of taking one.
They'd harassed Abigail
and the girls in her care for months.
They knew there was palladium
to be found in the mines under her groves
and wanted to buy them from her,
but she refused.
So they decided to steal it instead.
They came to Thornhill,
armed with pitchforks and torches.
No!
No! No! No!
- This way.
- Move!
Oh, they had it all planned out.
They accused her of being a witch.
And they burned her at the stake,
in the groves surrounding Thornhill.
Who, Nana?
Who were these vicious hooligans,
these killers?
Brace yourself, child.
The primary conspirators were
the ancestors
of your so-called compatriots.
Archibald Andrews,
Jedediah Jones and Beatrice Cooper.
With her dying words,
she cursed them and the others,
damning them to tragedy as well.
After her death,
the townspeople claimed the mines
and began to dig for palladium.
But there was a collapse,
killing and entombing an entire generation
of Riverdale's fathers and sons.
Some say the collapse was caused
by Abigail's curse.
- Nana, how do you know all this?
- Why...
it's written in Abigail's journal.
Would you like to read it, child?
I shouldn't have called you, Grandpa.
It wasn't my intention
that you would come up from Florida.
The worst part of all this is
that I feel like I've let you down.
What are you talking about?
You defied your father
and took over a struggling business.
And don't forget,
I know the debt you assumed
when you took over the diner.
You've been paying it down every month.
None of that matters
if we can't pay for repairs.
We'll try to get
some of Hiram's leftovers.
And I'll cover the rest
with my retirement money.
What? Grandpa, no,
I am not letting you do that.
I'd be doing it for me as much as you.
I miss the adrenaline of working.
I miss my customers.
So I'm giving you my nest egg,
on the condition...
that you let me come back to Pop's
and work with you.
Grandpa, I would love that.
We could propose a civil council.
It's a system that works and it's fair.
If fair is the criteria,
then we should govern by committee.
We can hold town meetings
for every big decision.
It's purely democratic,
everyone will get an equal say.
That would be anarchy.
What if we had a mayor who had to answer
to a council? Best of both worlds.
I think a mayor is a nonstarter
for a lot of people,
after the way my father abused his power.
How ironic yet fitting.
The descendants of those
who committed Riverdale's original sin
debating its future.
Well, I refuse to allow you four
to perpetuate any further cycles
of violence and bloodshed.
What are you talking about?
So, to be clear,
- none of my ancestors were involved?
- No.
The same can't be said
for your three conspirators
who killed my dear Abigail.
Therefore, I'm demanding a formal apology
and acknowledgment of this travesty.
Publicly and immediately.
Cheryl, this story really is tragic.
But those are our ancestors, not us.
We need everyone's support
at tomorrow's meeting.
If we lead with this crazy story,
it might distract people
from the task at hand, reincorporation.
I've spent years
atoning for the sins of my ancestors.
And now you want me
to forget about it and move on?
Only until the town is stable.
Cheryl, please, this is Riverdale's
one chance to be reborn.
Reborn? This town sits
over a vast graveyard of dead miners.
The roots of the trees in my groves have,
over time, become entwined
with those corpses.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
For decades, the trees have been
nourished by the poisonous dead.
My sap, my syrup,
the very lifeblood of Riverdale
has been polluted by the remains
of so many fathers and sons.
The only chance
this town has of being reborn
is for you to come clean
and beg for my, my forgiveness.
See you at the meeting.
And I pray you do the right thing.
Okay, today, our families
and neighbors are going to decide
on whether or not
to reincorporate this town.
Whether Riverdale lives...
or whether Riverdale dies.
Regardless, we will be ready to publish.
But not as The Blue and Gold.
We are now The Riverdale Choice,
a new, free press for all of Riverdale.
Whatever happens in our town,
we are gonna be there to report on it
truthfully and without bias.
And whoever is in charge,
we will hold them accountable,
even if they're our friends.
Especially if they're our friends.
Okay, we have a town meeting
to cover. Let's go.
Reginald, I've been thinking about
your idea for a casino in Riverdale,
and I think we should go for it.
Really? What about New York?
We could go back to New York
and be two nameless, faceless traders
on Wall Street, yes.
Or we could stay in Riverdale
and be king and queen of the roost,
working for ourselves, calling the shots.
You're preaching to the choir.
And I was thinking maybe we can use
Pearls and Posh as a cover.
We may not even have to do that.
Could I get everyone's attention?
We'd like to begin the proceedings.
Some of you knew my father.
And he believed in Riverdale,
not because it was perfect,
but because he saw the potential in it.
We're not looking
to reincorporate a town that was
but a town that might one day be
with the proper leadership.
Which is why, as of tonight,
we're hoping that it won't be a mayor
who leads us into the future,
but instead a Council of Four
- who will guide us every step of the way.
- Halt. I've heard enough.
And who, pray tell, will comprise
this Council of Four Narcissists?
Let me guess.
You, Betty, Veronica, and Jughead.
Actually, we were going
to propose the council be...
Tabitha Tate,
Toni Topaz,
Alice Smith,
and my Uncle Frank.
I see.
And what about the past, Archie?
Tonight's not about the past,
but I promise you...
No.
No more empty promises.
Let the official public record show
from this moment on,
Thornhill and her lands shall cede
from the corrupt township of Riverdale.
Whatever happens tonight,
you lot will have no jurisdiction over it
- or its blessed inhabitants.
- Cheryl, come on.
Nay, cousin.
What is decreed is decreed.
Ta-ta. Come along, Brittania.
Just to be clear, these four nominees
have deep roots in Riverdale.
They'll fight to make it better, stronger,
and more inclusive than ever.
They will each swear an oath
to put Riverdale's collective needs
before any single individual.
Is there anyone here tonight
that opposes these four nominees?
All in favor to reincorporate
the township of Riverdale
under this Council of Four.
Unanimous.
Along with the signatures collected,
the ayes have it.
Riverdale is officially back on the map.
At the risk of putting the cart
before the horse,
Reggie and I have an idea
for Riverdale, a big idea.
That we think you're gonna love.
- Okay. What is it?
- Picture, if you will,
a stunning, full-service, white-glove,
family-friendly casino
within Riverdale's borders.
Which will provide
a slew of new jobs for our residents,
as well as a fresh, robust cash flow.
With our expertise and your support,
our little town could be the next...
Atlantic City.
So you're wanting to turn Riverdale
into the modern-day Sodom and Gomorrah?
We really appreciate your enthusiasm.
We have traffic lights
and potholes to fix first.
Not to mention Pop's.
What we're saying is that we're intrigued.
But how about you bring a full proposal
to next month's meeting
and we'll take it from there?
Okay. See you next month.
So...
Riverdale lives to fight another day.
- Nice job, Arch.
- Yeah, we'll see.
- What about Cheryl? Should we be worried?
- Nah, she'll come around.
What are you doing later?
How did it go?
Was our Abigail avenged?
- Hardly, Nana.
- Oh...
They don't give a whit
about the sins of the past.
- Will Riverdale ever learn?
- Perhaps.
But they will need help.
And Abigail must be honored.
What's that?
The last words she ever spoke
as she was being burned alive
at the stake.
You mean, the curse?
Speak the speech, child.
It will be a fitting tribute
to our ancestor.
It's only fitting that these words spoken
at the end of one Blossom chapter...
shall be uttered as a new one unfurls.
From this day on, Thornhill will
no longer be a home to a ministry
but to a school modeled after Abigail's,
an academy for lost and wayward girls.
As Abigail herself once said these words:
"Archibald Andrews,
Jedediah Jones, and Beatrice Cooper,
I repudiate you with my dying breath.
And in Satan's name, I curse you.
Burn me,
but you will never escape my wrath,
nor Satan's.
The unchained elements of the power
of darkness are lying in ambush.
Beware.
My revenge will strike down you
and your accursed houses.
And I will bathe in the blood
of your sons and daughters.
Immortal, I shall return again and again
to torment and destroy you."
...and destroy you!
- What do you guys think?
- I think it's your best work yet.
Thanks, Alice.
But, I mean, it's just a plywood sign.
Nah.
It's everything you've done this year.
That's bizarre. RIV weatherman
didn't call for wind today.
Oof. This wind...
Yeah. It feels like someone's walking
on my grave. Come on.
Very good.
From a classroom to a boiler room.
Only in Riverdale.
- How are we looking back here, partner?
- Well, it's not Caesars Palace, but...
we'll get there.
Of that, Reggie, I have no doubt.
Betty.
I...
I wanna try again.
Us.
Not as friends with benefits, but...
But for real.
All in.
I mean, can we try again?
We can.
I wanna be with you too, Arch.
Can you hear that?
Yeah. What is that?
The clock?
- Betty.
- What? What is it?
Tick, tick, boom.