I'm not gonna
lie to you.
What awaits us
out there
is like nothing
we've ever
faced before,
but we will
not be afraid.
Do you know why?
'Cause
we're Bulldogs!
And Bulldogs
never give up.
Men, your mission
is to penetrate
the enemy's defenses,
retrieve your
fallen brother
and return
safely to base.
-Are we clear?
Sir, yes, sir!
Let's do this!
Twenty-two!
Reggie!
Let's go, Bulldogs,
let's go!
One more time!
Let's go, Bulldogs,
let's go!
I say "bull"
you say "dogs."
-Bull!
Dogs!
-Dogs!
I say "bull"
you say "dogs".
Bull!
Dogs!
I need
a little help.
Come on!
Archie!
Rise
and shine, Sergeant.
At ease, Andrews.
You ready to
go home, son?
Home?
No, sir. No.
-I'm ready to get
back in the fight.
-Sergeant,
you've given
seven years
to the army.
Seven good years.
Every man in
your unit will
attest to that.
They're alive
because of you.
Not all of
them, sir.
I've done
some digging.
Turns out
the RROTC program
at your old
high school
has been inactive.
I can't think
of anyone
more qualified
to bring it
back to life.
With all due
respect, sir,
I didn't join
the army...
to be a desk jockey.
This is not a
request, Sergeant.
It's an order.
Sign your papers.
And by the by,
Corporal Jackson
just transferred in.
"In the late summer
of that year,
we lived in a house
in a village
that looked across
the river and the plain
to the mountains.
In the bed
of the river,
there were pebbles
and boulders...
dry and white
in the sun,
and the water
was clear and
swiftly moving
and blue in
the channels."
Look who
cleans up respectable.
Give me a break.
How you feeling,
brother?
Actually, they got me
on so many pain meds,
I'm good.
You?
-Going somewhere?
-Yeah, home.
Riverdale.
Taylor wants me
running the RROTC,
working enlistment.
Dude, that's
messed up.
Look, Jackson.
I just want
to tell you
how sorry I am.
I really wish it was
me in that bed
instead of you.
I do, too.
Sarge...
the only reason
I'm still breathing
is 'cause of you.
Riverdale, huh?
It sounds nice.
This is my address.
When you get
out of here,
look me up.
Thanks, Sarge.
Will do.
Something wrong,
soldier boy?
Uh, no, no,
everything's fine.
Well, if you're hungry,
grab a stool.
Coffee's fresh.
Or if you want
something
a little stronger,
you can always
head downstairs.
♪ In her eyes
♪ The distant firelight
♪ Burns bright
♪ Wondering why
♪ It's only after dark
♪ I find myself in a room
♪ Feel the fever of my doom
♪ Falling, falling
Through the floor ♪
♪ I'm knocking on
The devil's door ♪
♪ Burning, burning
In the flame ♪
♪ Now you know
My secret name ♪
♪ You can tear
My temple down ♪
♪ But I'll be back
And rule again ♪
♪ After dark
Damn, Toni,
it's good to see you.
Yeah, you, too.
You're all
grown up.
Well, I don't know
about that.
But you,
-you're, uh...
-Pregnant.
Yeah, I am.
Still a bad ass, though.
Who's the dad?
Can I ask?
You can,
but I'm not gonna
answer you.
It's...
It's a secret.
Just for now.
But I'm glad to see
you're back
in one piece.
Yeah, yeah.
No, I'm good.
So, who owns
this place now?
Me and the Serpents.
We, uh, all put
our cash together
and bought it
from Hiram Lodge.
A girl's got
to be creative
to survive
in Riverdale
these days.
Toni, the bus ride
into town...
I can't explain it.
It...
Everything felt,
-feels...
-Different?
-Weird?
-Yeah.
I mean,
to be honest,
it doesn't even
feel like Riverdale
anymore.
Yeah, well, a lot
has changed
in the world
since we graduated
high school, Archie.
Yeah, no kidding.
I mean, for starters,
where's Pop Tate?
Well, haven't
you heard?
I thought that's
why you came
back to town.
No, I was
reassigned here.
Toni, what happened
to Pop Tate?
How are
the nightmares,
Betty?
Are they still
keeping you up
at night?
No, I haven't
had one in weeks.
Good.
I'm more than ready
to get back to work.
You are working,
I thought.
I've been assigned
to cold cases,
which means
I'm filing all day.
Betty, you suffered
severe trauma.
You were
and still are
only a trainee.
I caught serial killers
in high school, Dr. Starling.
Not like The Trash
Bag Killer.
You'd be surprised.
I found something, Glen,
a connection.
There was a set
of multiple murders
in Odessa, Texas
that just stopped
without the killer
getting caught.
-No explanation.
-Mm-hmm.
Two months later, in Fargo
in North Dakota,
there's a similar
string of killings.
The victim
profiles match
as well as the methods used,
and again, the killings just
stopped for no reason.
Let me guess,
you're thinking we have
a migrating serial killer.
Yes, Glen, I have a hunch.
Betty, stop.
You're supposed to be
logging in cold cases,
not sewing
the crazy quilt
out of them.
And the last
time you followed
a hunch...
Yeah, The Trash
Bag Killer.
I get it.
I messed up big time.
But how am I supposed to
make up for it
if I'm locked
in a basement?
How am I
supposed to
redeem myself?
Listen, it's late.
How about
we call it a day?
I can pick up some
pizza and beer.
We could meet
at my place.
I can't tonight.
I have plans.
Oh... Do you?
I'm meeting
friends for Thai.
Watch as the hunters
take off
chasing down
their prey.
The gazelle,
while badly wounded,
tries to run.
But after a long
and meticulous set-up,
the hunters
show no fear
as they chase down...
...with their sharp
teeth and claws...
Where are you, kitty?
Any nightmares
this week, Betty?
No.
Sleeping like a baby.
Unless you're
willing to
open up to me
about your feelings,
about what you
went through
while you were held
captive by TBK,
I won't be able to
help you, Betty.
You know, when I
got to TBK's lair...
Teresa was
already dead.
It wouldn't
have mattered
if I'd gone in there
with an entire
SWAT team.
He'd already
killed her.
That's true.
But if you had
waited for backup,
you might not
have been captured.
And the Trash Bag Killer
might not have escaped.
Yeah.
That was a mistake.
I regret that.
You haven't
said much
about your time
in captivity.
Two weeks.
Do you think
about a lot?
I think about
where TBK
might be right now.
I think about
the people
he might...
he might hurt...
because of me.
I'm sorry, I usually
have it turned off.
I have to go home
for a few days...
-to Riverdale.
-Okay. Yeah, sure.
And hey, while
you're there,
you can pack up
-the FBI
satellite office.
-Okay.
The one where you
and your serial killer
brother worked.
Yes, I will pack
up the office.
No problem.
You have to watch
my cat Toffee.
Sure. Yeah,
I can do that.
But I will
need a key.
And since I won't
be seeing you
for a few days,
do I at least get
a kiss goodbye?
Mm-hmm.
To one glorious
year of marriage,
to you and me
forever, babe.
Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary,
Chadwick.
The only thing
we're missing is
a little Chad
or a little Veronica
running around.
But I have a feeling
this could be the year.
Don't you think?
Hopefully.
Maybe it's time to...
think about cutting
back your hours
at Lacey's.
It's 2021, Chad.
Haven't you heard?
Women can
have it all now.
I just...
I don't want
you to be
unduly stressed.
I'm not stressed.
Actually, I miss
being on the trading
floor with you.
I miss all
that adrenaline.
The highs of
a filthy huge sale,
talking smack
with the guys.
They called me
"the she-wolf
of Wall Street."
[announcer
indistinctly chattering
on TV]
Wrap this one
up for me,
will you, doll?
You want us to put
a dime on it?
With that spread?
Vinny, Vinny,
Vinny.
-Hold up.
-There's no way
I'm letting you
walk out of here
with this
pathetic excuse
for an apology gift.
You know
you're insulting
your own store's
merchandise, right?
Not at all.
But you're looking at
display counter,
off-the-rack items
when you've committed
a specialty showcase,
haute couture offense.
Trust me on
this one, Vinny.
You got to go big...
or your wife will
never forgive you.
T Dubs,
how are you?
Good, Ronnie.
That tip
you gave me
took my portfolio
through the roof
this year.
You've got
the magic touch.
I just call 'em
like I see 'em,
T Dubs.
Oh, by the by,
did Kendra
like the bracelet?
Uh...
So, about Kendra...
Ugh, T, not again.
One sec.
-Hey, stud.
How's work, babe?
Great.
Katie and I are just
a little slammed.
You want to meet us
for dinner later?
That's funny
because I went
to Lacey's
to surprise you,
and I'm standing
next to Katie
right now.
Hi, Katie.
You, however,
are nowhere
to be seen.
Do you have
any idea how
embarrassing it is
not even knowing
where my own wife is?
Forget that you've
been lying to me,
Veronica.
What happened
to Lacey's?
-I thought we decided
you'd work--
-I tried Lacey's,
but I needed
something with
a little more edge.
I thought we were
working towards
having a baby.
-Oh, my God.
-Or did you
forget that?
No. No, Chad,
you forgot.
You forgot
who I am,
who you married.
Remember how
it was in
the beginning?
Things were
so good.
You and me
working side by side
on the floor.
We were the power
couple to beat.
And the sex...
The sex was amazing.
What happened?
The accident.
Chad...
You use the accident
as an excuse to
try and control--
-You almost died.
-So did you!
You didn't want me
going back to Wall Street
after the accident
because it was
too stressful,
and I didn't want
to keep having
the same argument
over and over again,
so I agreed.
But that
was a mistake,
that's not
who I am.
And the sooner
you accept that,
the better off
you'll be.
Ready, everyone.
And action!
From small town
to big city,
my killer instinct
always gets me
what I want.
Hermione,
my one-take wonder.
-You're my angel,
you know that?
-Thank you.
I wish all the housewives
could be as real as you.
Well, I try.
Wow, Mom,
you make it
look so easy.
Well, please, for women
who've been through
what we've been through,
this is
a cakewalk, mija.
Oh, which reminds me.
Andy wants to
know when you're
gonna come
join us for
an episode or two.
Mom, no.
I can't put
my life on display.
Especially not when
it's in utter turmoil.
What's wrong
with your life?
You're married
to a successful,
handsome man
who gives you
whatever you want.
I mean, you don't
even have to work
if you don't want to.
I love working.
That's the problem.
Chad wants
to turn me
into a baby-making machine.
So, you don't
want to have kids?
I mean, since when?
We have plenty
of time for that.
Right now,
I don't want
to be a mom.
-No offense.
-Mm-hmm.
I want to be
the she-wolf
of Wall Street.
Okay, let me
ask you something.
When you and Chad
worked together,
you outperformed him,
isn't that right?
Almost every week.
Okay.
That's threatening
to an alpha
like Chad.
He's vain,
like Hiram.
Every marriage
has its ups
and downs.
And as for
believing that
you have plenty
of time to start
a family,
honey, I think
the accident might
have shown you
that's not
necessarily
the case.
Let's try this again.
Happy anniversary.
I hate it when we fight.
Especially when
it's my fault.
We never used to.
What happened?
The accident.
When our helicopter
went down
on the way
to Marsha's vineyard,
I said a prayer,
Veronica.
If only one of us
will survive this crash,
I thought...
Please let it be my wife.
Let it be the woman
I want to build a life with.
The woman I want to be
the mother of my children.
And then we both survived,
and all I could think is
now we can do those things.
I don't wanna
waste a minute.
Does that make any sense
to you, at all?
It does.
But we're partners.
If I tell you that
I wanna do something,
and that I can handle
the stress of that thing,
you have to trust me, Chad.
I will.
Hold on,
you... have got to open
your gift first.
A new one comes out
each year,
so you can start
collecting them.
Well, Yvonne, I can see
that Josh was absolutely
right about you.
You are a woman
of exquisite taste.
Yes, I am.
I think I have
just the thing.
We usually don't carry items
that are so... high-end.
But I know a guy.
And best of all,
a new Glamerge egg
is released each year.
So you could
start a collection.
Oh, my God.
It's perfect.
Archie?
Is everything okay?
What the hell, Jones?
Hey,
Samm Pansky, please?
-Hey, hey.
-Jess, please.
Hey, Samm, it's me.
Can we talk?
Okay. So you'd rather
talk to your agent
than your girlfriend.
-That's awesome.
-Uh...
Can we actually meet
for an early lunch
at that place that you like?
Yeah, great.
All right.
I'll see you soon. Bye.
Jess...
-I have writer's block.
-So do I.
But I'm not
punishing you for it.
Can we talk about this
when I get back, please?
Samm, just give it
to me straight.
Am I still in the running
for the staff writer job
at the New Yorker?
No, kid. I'm sorry.
Just found out this morning.
But you shouldn't be
tryin' to get a job
as a reporter anyway.
I mean,
you're a fiction writer.
You should be workin'
on your book.
How's that goin',
by the way?
-I have writer's block.
-Mmm-mmm.
You got a lousy work ethic.
And a toxic relationship.
-And you drink too much.
-So did Kerouac
and Hemingway,
-and Fitzgerald.
-You want it straight?
Whatever heat you had
coming off of your first book
is long gone.
A year ago you could've had
a story published anywhere,
but now,
you're spoiled goods.
-Passed your sell-by date.
-I just need more time.
Scribner's called.
They're threatening to
take back their advance.
Well, did you hold 'em off?
They wanna see pages!
It all comes down to,
"Do you want a career?
Or do you want to be
a one-hit wonder?"
I can't hear you.
What?
Hey.
Hey, Jess.
Did you see this?
Did--
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What's goin' on?
I'm gonna go stay with Hailey
until I find my own place.
Why?
This isn't working anymore.
We haven't been working
for a really long time.
Also, literal debt collectors
are pounding at the door.
Je-- Wait. When?
Today.
After you blew me off
to meet with your agent.
Okay. Just...
Jess, please wait.
Don't, don't, don't
do this right now.
-All I need is--
-I don't know what
you need, Jones.
But I'm definitely not it.
Good luck with your book.
It's the only thing
you care about anyway.
Excuse me.
This is you, isn't it?
It is you.
Oh, my God.
I was just sitting over there
reading your book,
and then I look up,
and there you are.
Forsythe Pendleton Jones III.
My friends just
call me Jughead.
Cora.
I'm a grad student at NYU.
English, of course.
It's wonderful,
by the way... your book.
The Outcasts,which is
obviously an homage...
The Outsidersby S.E. Hinton.
And the love story
between the Viper leader
and the homecoming queen.
It's just so...
Romantic?
Sexy,
I was gonna say.
It's a very sexy book
you've written.
♪ Doo wop a doo wop
Shoopi doobi doo wop ♪
♪ She give me Katchi! ♪
♪ Doo wop a doo wop
Shoopi doobi doo wop ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ Doo wop a doo wop
Shoopi doobi doo wop ♪
♪ She give me Katchi! ♪
♪ Doo wop a doo wop
Shoopi doobi doo wop ♪
♪ All night long
-Morning.
Where'd you get that?
In one of your drawers.
Is that okay?
Yeah, no.
It's not a big deal.
Uh, there's coffee brewing.
Hey, I remember this.
New York Magazine,right?
-They called you the--
-New Brat Pack.
Yeah.
The wunderkinds.
The season's best
and brightest young writers,
with so much potential.
Full disclosure...
I've read the article
like a hundred times.
It's how I knew
that bar last night was...
is... your usual hangout.
What?
Okay, so I really am a fan
of your book. Honestly.
But I do have
an ulterior motive.
Would you mind
reading my novel?
It's only 342 pages.
And if you like it...
Maybe you could
give it to your agent.
Okay, hold on...
Last night was a ploy
to get me to read your book?
Forsythe Jones,
open up!
-Who are they?
-Debt collectors.
-Are they gonna hurt you?
-Forsythe Jones,
we know you're in there.
-Uh, uh...
We can see your shadow,
we can hear you...
-Let's go. Open the door.
-I'll read your book, I swear.
Could you, uh,
just do me a favor?
We're not going
anywhere, Jones.
-Please.
Can I help you, gentlemen?
Where's Forsythe Jones?
Uh, he's not here.
I'm apartment-sitting for him.
He got a job writing
for a TV show in LA,
just left this morning.
Can I give him
a message for you?
Tell him to call us.
It's urgent.
You got it.
Will do.
Oh...
Thank you.
No problem.
But I'll expect
to hear from you
by the end of the week.
The end of
the week?
About my novel.
-And about you
giving it to your agent.
-Mmm.
And if I don't hear from you...
I know exactly
who I'm gonna call.
This is nuts.
I haven't seen you guys,
in what, six years?
Actually,
it's been seven.
Wow. Lots of
catching up to do.
Well, I had a job lined up
after graduation
with Riverdale Social Services,
but their offices
got shut down.
Lucky for her, we needed
a guidance counselor
at Riverdale High.
You're looking at
the new Mrs. Burble.
Wait. You're working at
Riverdale High, too, Kev?
Mmm.
Yep. I'm the drama teacher.
Got my BA
from Carnegie Mellon,
in Pittsburgh, where...
I've graduated from
the University of Pittsburgh.
Okay.
Whoo!
We stayed boyfriends,
believe it or not.
-And now,
we live together here.
-Mm-hmm.
With me.
In an apartment
on Cloverfield Lane.
-That's amazing.
Sweet Pea,
what about you, bro?
Mostly held down the fort here
while these guys were gone.
-And then when Toni got back...
-We decided
to revive the Serpents,
under my leadership.
I was crowned
the Serpent Queen.
Well, I gotta say,
this place is sick.
Pulls in a different
crowd, though.
What's with all the truckers?
Serpents drive trucks
to make cash.
Including me and Fangs.
-Toni had the hookup.
Impressive.
Hey, what about Cheryl?
It's cool, guys.
As you know, after graduation,
Cheryl and I broke up.
RIP, Choni.
After I got back
from Highsmith,
I... went to go check on her
a couple times
Hello, Antoinette.
Cheryl, I, uh...
thought we could talk.
I'm afraid now
isn't a good time.
As you can see,
we're in the midst
of renovating Thornhill,
and I've got
my painting to finish.
Perhaps another day?
Yeah... Sure.
Cheryl, are you okay?
I'm perfectly fine.
Do I appear
to be otherwise?
My mistake.
And did you go back?
I did.
Not too long ago.
But this time I wasn't
Thornhill's only visitor.
Hiram Lodge was there
with his new
righthand man, Reggie.
Wait, Reggie's working
for Hiram Lodge?
I will never sell you
my maple groves, you vulgarian.
Nana and I plan to be buried
amongst those trees.
-We can make that happen.
Goodbye, would-be usurper.
Business with Hiram Lodge?
No. He comes by
every other week
offering to buy
my maple groves.
But...
I'm really glad to see you.
Toni...
I wonder
if you would do me the honor
of letting me paint you.
I...
Cheryl, no one's seen you
in town in years.
Don't worry about me,
Nana and I are just fine.
There's no reason for us
to leave Thornhill.
Okay.
Well, after all this time,
don't you wanna hear about me?
Let's see.
You graduated with a 3.9 GPA.
You majored in Social Work,
with a minor in Photography.
And you did extensive charity
and social work.
Am I missing
anything important?
Well, other than the fact
I'm having a baby...
I'd heard that, yes.
Congratulations, Toni.
I won't be gauche
and ask who the father is.
Oh, and I'm completely
out and open with my family.
We've talked about you.
And they recognize
and acknowledge
everything you've done
to make up
for your ancestors' sins.
And Cheryl,
I think that they'd approve
of us being together.
I'm so happy
to hear that, Toni...
But it...
it's not nearly enough.
The Blossom curse runs deep.
I'm doomed to a life
of unhappiness.
You think you're cursed.
Beloved TT...
Are you familiar
with the Winchester House?
I have seen the movie
with Helen Mirren.
Sarah Winchester came
from a family of rifle makers.
Winchester rifles.
One by one,
family members suffered
painful, horrific fates.
Cursed by the deaths brought on
by their family's stock
and trade... rifles.
Only Sarah survived.
And so she started
to build a house.
The Winchester House.
And she believed
that as long as it remained
under constant construction,
the curse couldn't consume her.
Is that why
you're rebuilding Thornhill?
Toni...
I'm glad you're doing so well.
You deserve to be happy.
She didn't say
another word.
She just painted me
for 12 hours,
and when she was done,
I left.
And a week later, a package
showed up in the mail,
and it was my portrait.
She didn't keep it
as a reminder
of what you guys had?
I guess she didn't want it.
Well done,
my dear.
It's exactly like the original.
It's a perfect copy.
You've learned well.
Now, the question is...
Would you be able to replicate
the work of a master?
Like, say, um...
Rembrandt.
Toni, earlier you said
the town had changed.
I'm probably gonna
regret asking this,
but can you tell me how?
I think it might be better
to show you.
Okay.
Where you staying?
I'm crashing at the El Royale,
since my mom's
renting out our house.
Right.
The renters.
Um... I'll pick you up
at the gym.
Okay. Thanks, Toni.
Hey, do you mind if I stay here
to make a few calls?
Yeah. Go for it.
-Archie?
Toni.
I figured a steel gate
would be enough
to keep this gym intact
but this place
is like a war zone.
Well, wait till you see
the rest of the town.
Come on.
My bike's out front.
This was the fire station,
remember?
It was already
a burned-up shell
by the time
I got back from college.
No one's trying to rebuild it?
The town's entire funding
has been completely
stripped by--
-Hiram Lodge.
-Bingo.
And not only
is the fire department gone,
but the sheriff's office
is now down to one man...
Kevin's dad.
I don't understand.
What are people doing?
Fending for themselves.
The town's lawless now, Archie.
This was Pickens Park.
Where is everybody?
Whoever could afford
to leave is long gone.
Only the people
who are too poor,
too proud to move on,
are still here.
This was Sketch Alley.
Now we just call it
what it is...
Skid row.
-And those dogs are everywhere,
packs of them.
Some are rabid.
This is the fifth bus stop
that's been trashed, melted.
Five of dozens.
Nowadays, there's always
a fire burning in Riverdale.
Why burn a bench
for no reason?
Where are people
gonna sit for the bus?
Well, that's the thing, Archie.
Buses don't pass by
here anymore.
Sometimes my trucks do.
But only if they have to,
and rarely at night.
Bad things happen here
after dark.
They call this
"The Lonely Highway."
Why destroy an entire town
for nothing?
What does Hiram Lodge
have to gain?
I'll show you.
I don't get it.
So, where are the houses?
This isn't SoDale proper.
This is where Hiram's
building a turnpike
that leads to SoDale
about half a mile due east.
Hiram's catering
to the rich folk
who can commute into the city.
So he's strangling Riverdale
to boost SoDale.
And let me guess,
their kids will go
to SoDale High.
Actually, Stonewall Prep.
That place is the same.
Except Hiram bought himself
a seat on the board.
And so the nightmare continues.
Archie, there's actually
one more place
I think you should
see on the tour.
But you're gonna have to
brace yourself.
The Ghoulies moved
into my house?
Do you wanna go in there
and knock some heads?
As a matter of fact,
yeah, I do.
But first things first, Toni.
Can we go back to Pop's?
See if any of them
actually came?
Okay.
Archie, I heard you were back.
Pop... It's good to see you.
-I missed you.
-Say, I missed all of you.
Archie. Toni.
-Veronica, Betty...
-Hi.
Jughead. I'll, uh,
leave you guys to it then.
No.
You're as much a part of this
as any of us.
Oh, guys.
Toni gave me a tour
of Riverdale today, and it's...
It's a hellscape.
I know I called you here
for Pop's retirement
party, but...
We have a much
bigger agenda now.
Riverdale's dying.
And we might be
the only ones who can save it.
Are you sure I can't
convince you to stay, Squeaky?
I'll give you more shifts
if it would help.
I appreciate that, Tabitha,
but...
Riverdale is done with me.
And I am done with Riverdale.
Well, take care of yourself.
Will do.
Her name
is Lynette Fields.
Squeaky, to her friends.
Not that she has many,
mostly she keeps to herself.
She came to Riverdale
two years ago
for a fresh start
that never happened.
Now, she was 21,
and it was time to go.
"Maybe things will be different in San Francisco," she thought.
"Maybe I'll be happy there."
Unfortunately for Lynette,
she'll never make it
to California.