The science-fiction writer
Arthur C. Clarke said this about aliens:
"Two possibilities exist.
Either we are alone in the universe
or we are not.
Both are equally terrifying."
Mom, it's almost time for the game.
Polly's out there.
We don't know
if that was her blood on the phone booth.
She called us from it
a half hour before we got there.
Who else's blood would it be?
We'll find out when the FBI calls me
with their analysis.
Maybe get back into your support group
with all those other moms.
Let's go, Derek! Go, Derek!
Come on, Derek!
All right, bring it in.
We lost again.
We could have been practicing
for Regionals
instead of wasting our time here.
I couldn't agree more, Cassandra.
Could not agree more.
All right, that was another tough one.
But the Ravens
are number two in the league.
You fought hard out there.
Keep fighting. We'll break through.
While I do believe
Coach Andrews is the best motivator
a gridiron gang could ask for,
as your de facto team owner,
what can I do to incentivize you?
How about 10 grand?
To whichever Bulldog scores first
this season.
Yeah.
- All right?
- Yeah.
- You okay, Derek?
- I'll be all right.
- It sucks to lose. I'm giving it my all.
- I hear you.
There was no better player than you
out on that field today.
What do we do? Push them more?
I'm already running them ragged.
Not to mention zero fan support.
The Bulldogs were supposed
to inspire the town.
Riverdale was supposed to rally behind
the Bulldogs. No one comes to our games.
In that case, I'll get the town
to back our Bulldogs again.
Just keep those kids motivated.
And what about me?
Don't coaches need motivation too?
Chin up, Andrews.
The incidents
go back decades, Samm.
Dozens of people seeing things
they can't explain. Even support groups.
Slow down.
You're writing about aliens now?
It's not just about aliens,
it's about personal trauma.
If I'm right,
it's about a town's collective trauma.
Could you take the idea to Scribner's?
- Yeah. I'll let you know what they say.
- Thank you, I appreciate it.
Tabitha, how do you feel about
Pop's hosting a pancake breakfast
so that folks can mingle
with the new Riverdale Bulldogs?
Sounds fun. And if it brings in
warm bodies, then great.
Amazing.
And what if, hypothetically, Pop's became
the official sponsor of the Bulldogs?
Let's give it a shot.
I like supporting underdogs.
I will order the pancake mix
and the syrup.
Oh, no. No. Don't order the syrup.
I have a special supplier for that.
I cannot donate
my precious maple resource to help fund
that collection of tatterdemalions
you call a football team.
And the Vixens can no longer continue
cheering for the Bad News Bulldogs.
Please, stick around for one more game.
And maybe help get more people
in the stands.
My Vixens are cheerleaders,
not boosters, Archie.
Fine. I'll do it myself.
Hi, Miss Bell. Can you turn this on?
Attention.
This is Coach Andrews.
A bunch of your classmates are out there
busting their asses on the football field
to represent this school and to represent
each and every one of you.
Why don't you show some school spirit
and support your team?
Starting with the free pancake breakfast
that Pop's is hosting tomorrow morning.
Give them your support.
And, hell, you might even get
something out of it yourselves.
And what about the Vixens?
One more game.
I'll even come out of retirement to give
the people something they'd like to see.
Namely, moi.
First, there's something broken
I need to fix.
And don't forget to turn in
your assignments on the way out.
Thank you.
Good job. Thank you.
Glen. Did you get the blood results
from the phone booth back?
I did.
The recovered blood is AB negative.
The rarest type.
Under 1% of the population.
And a match for Polly.
So she...
She's really...?
I'm so sorry, Betty.
No, you're not.
If you had cared at all about me
or my sister,
you would have done something to help me.
- Betty, look, I realize you're upset...
- Screw you, Glen.
I must admit, it is a bit disturbing.
Waldo, a kid is held captive
by mole people,
only to escape and be abducted
by a family of Mothmen,
who operate on him in a spaceship,
in graphic detail.
- Doesn't ring any alarm bells for you?
- The child survives.
He's found on the side of the highway.
- What do we know about Lerman?
- Good student. Average grades.
Any trouble at home?
He has sustained
a substantial number of injuries.
A broken arm, a black eye.
He was on crutches for a while.
I know what you're thinking.
But I spoke to Lerman and his parents.
- They couldn't be nicer people.
- He's just accident-prone?
- What about the story?
- Some kids get hurt a lot.
And, yes,
sometimes a story is just a story.
Order up!
- Behold. 'Tis the nectar of the gods.
- Ah. Amazing. Thank you again.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
We're feeling optimistic
about the rest of the season.
Your son plays a huge part in that,
which is why, Derek,
I want you to be captain of the team.
And what's the team gonna do
for my son, Coach Andrews?
- Um, I'm not sure I understand.
- Derek's a good player.
Football could be
his ticket out of this town.
- He could get a scholarship...
- Mom, chill.
I have to think of my son's future, coach.
Not just your team's.
Excuse me.
No, I understand.
So sorry to interrupt.
Coach, we have a situation.
I take it you didn't come
for the hotcakes.
No.
I'm here on behalf of the Greater Rockland
County Football League.
The other teams in the conference
and our commissioner saw fit
to send me as a representative.
We're in agreement.
We'd like for the Bulldogs to withdraw
from the league, like, yesterday.
You guys suck.
Screw you, Reggie.
Riverdale has a right to play.
Come on.
The Bulldogs are an embarrassment.
They're tainting the league's prestige.
So can we tell the league
you're withdrawing?
Like hell. I want the names
of every member of this so-called league.
Doesn't it kill you...
to watch the Bulldogs lose
week after week?
Yeah, well,
it's not all about winning, Reg.
Keep telling yourself that, loser.
Loser, loser, loser.
You wanna talk about it?
A few days ago, you were getting married
and having a kid.
- Now we're moving you out.
- It was my decision.
You know?
Maybe you're right. Maybe... I'm not
the kind of guy who deserves a family.
Now hold on. You don't really believe
that you don't deserve happiness, do you?
I actually don't wanna talk about it.
Given how invested you are
in seeing Riverdale High
fail on all fronts, I find it hard
to believe you're not behind
the league's attempt to oust the Bulldogs.
All I know about the Bulldogs is
that they're garbage
- and they haven't even scored this season.
- They will.
- Against your precious Stallions.
- Oh, please.
We'll be wiping Bulldog blood
off our cleats for weeks.
You seem so sure.
How about a wager?
What are the terms?
If your Stallions keep
my Bulldogs off the scoreboard,
we'll withdraw from the league,
voluntarily.
If, however, we do score,
you'll have to convince your friend,
the commissioner, and his Legion of Doom
to stop trying to muscle out the Bulldogs.
I will take that bet.
Great.
Lerman, could you hang back for a sec?
Story's great.
It's very vivid. It's intense.
I wanted to ask you what inspired it.
- Uh... Just a series of dreams I had.
- Really? Recurring?
Yes. It... Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
Some experts believe that stories
about aliens and the like are
really about traumas
that people have experienced.
And these stories are cries for help.
You know... What...? What do you mean?
I mean, is this story real, Lerman?
Any part of it?
Did someone hurt you,
like what you wrote about,
- or tie you up or keep you locked up?
- Mr. Jones,
it's... It's just a story, okay?
I... I never should have written it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Sweet cousin. What a surprise.
Any news on your sister?
Yeah. As a matter of fact,
that's why I'm here.
When Jason first disappeared,
for a long time, no one knew
where he was or what had happened to him.
But when you learned that he had died,
was it helpful to know the truth?
To say it was soul-crushing
would be an understatement.
So, what if you'd never learned the truth?
If you had had hope
that he might still be alive?
When I learned the truth,
I was able to grieve for my brother.
From my experience,
it is better to know the truth.
And make your peace with it.
Does this mean Polly's...?
I don't know what it'll do to my mom.
Why aren't you guys dressed for practice?
Derek transferred.
He got recruited to play
for Stonewall Prep.
We're doomed.
As much as I hate Stonewall Prep,
I can't blame Derek.
Enrolling there,
playing for the Stallions...
it's his best shot at college.
And they're a team that wins games.
The Bulldogs will be too.
You've only just relaunched them.
Not to mention we're down a player.
The league won't even let us
on the field with ten.
The Bulldogs just need
a little motivation.
Something to get them energized.
Luckily, I just came up with
one of my genius ideas
that will rally the troops
and maybe even recruit some new ones.
Mom.
We got the blood results back.
Is it Polly's?
No.
No, it...
It was O positive. It wasn't a match.
Oh, thank God.
Thank God.
Oh, thank you, Betty.
Hey! You're awake.
Perfect timing. I ordered
a platter of cold cuts from Pop's.
Would you get it?
What's happening?
I decided you were right about me
getting back into the support group.
I'm hosting today. Would you mind
running to get the cold cuts?
Yeah, no. Of course.
- What's the buzz, Waldo?
- This him?
Mr. Jones, these are the Logans.
Lerman's parents.
Hi.
They've come in to discuss
a conversation you had with their son.
In what world do you think
that it's appropriate
to encourage these wild fantasies
that Lerman is obsessed with?
Death and aliens and underground monsters?
What's wrong with you?
Well, I'm sorry, I...
I had figured it was my responsibility
as Lerman's teacher.
The story he wrote might have been
alluding to some troubles at home.
Then why didn't you come to us?
Instead, you ambush our child?
Mr. and Mrs. Logan,
Mr. Jones's behavior
was wildly inappropriate.
I can promise you,
it'll never happen again.
Oh, we know it won't.
We don't want him teaching our child.
- Wait. I didn't reach out to you...
- Not a problem at all.
We'll move Lerman
to another English class.
How dare you break protocol
in such a reckless manner!
I had already vetted the Logans.
I know. No, I'm sorry.
I felt like something was off.
My instinct was something was going on.
One more misstep...
I mean, even just a little one.
...and you're done at my school.
Kevin, Fangs.
Thank you both
for agreeing to this tête-à-tête.
Toni may never forgive me,
but I will never forgive myself
if I don't try to repair
what my antics have torn asunder.
Namely, hashtag "Kangs."
Your games brought up deeper issues
between Kevin and I.
- Agreed.
- See? Consensus.
- Go on, Fangs.
- Now, you've never been all-in, Kev.
You've always, always held back.
I don't know if that's because of me
or because you're ashamed of being gay.
I am not ashamed of being gay.
You go to the woods,
you hook up with anonymous strangers.
You don't wanna be in a real relationship
with a real gay guy.
Fangs, don't.
You're not me.
You don't know my experience, okay?
We were about to get married, Kevin.
I wanna know everything about you.
The good and the bad.
I think it's too late for that.
- Kevin, please.
- I gotta go.
Um, Cheryl, please butt out of our lives.
What, are you having a party?
And I wasn't invited?
- No, it's for my mom's support group.
- How's she doing?
There have been developments...
in Polly's case. Um...
Apparently...
the blood they recovered
at the phone booth...
is a match for hers,
which means most likely that, um...
Oh, God. Betty, I'm so sorry.
And the worst part is,
she disappeared four weeks ago,
which means she has or had been alive...
that entire time,
somewhere along the Lonely Highway.
So I just didn't do enough.
Hey, I met someone that lives
on the Lonely Highway.
He's an eccentric kook,
but he sees a lot
of what goes on out there.
Maybe he might have seen or heard
something about the missing girls?
If you want, I can put this tray on ice
and I can take you to go meet him.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Bring it in.
What's the point in practicing?
We don't have enough players.
The Bulldogs are a team.
We play for each other
and the love of the game.
Yoo-hoo. Got room for one more?
I wanna introduce you to a friend of mine
who plays professional football
for a little team called
the New York Goliaths.
Holy crap.
It's T Dub.
Wow. A pleasure to meet you.
You're one hell of a player.
I appreciate it.
Heard you're one hell of a coach.
- How are you even here?
- Ronnie and I go way back.
T Dub was one of my most loyal clients
when I was selling jewelry in New York.
Hey, is it cool
if I say a few words to the team?
Yeah. Please.
Some of you have seen me play
for the Goliaths.
But my career started off
in a small town just like Riverdale.
With a coach who pushed me
to be what I could be.
He believed in me.
Just like Coach Andrews believes in you.
But you gotta be the ones
to make it happen on the field.
You're not underdogs.
- You're the damn Bulldogs!
- Yeah.
- Y'all ready to prove these haters wrong?
- Yeah!
You must be Britta.
Heard you got a cannon.
Come on. Let's see it.
Might be the shot in the arm we needed.
I wish T Dub could suit up for us.
- We're short a player.
- Oh, Archiekins, not for long.
Behold. A group of Bulldogs to be.
Hey! Who wants to play football?
Yeah!
We have a problem.
The interest in the Bulldogs is growing,
not waning.
I do not want people rallying around
this team or that school or that town.
I want you to target their weakest link
and knock some heads.
We don't need to go there.
We're gonna crush the Bulldogs
on the field. Fair and square. Easy.
Your loyalty lies with me at Stonewall.
I'm not gonna break
some kid's legs for no reason.
Yeah.
Consider yourself benched, Reggie.
I'll be leading the Stallions
into battle against Riverdale High.
So be it. I'll be standing
with the Bulldogs then.
What were you doing out here?
Just working on a book.
So the old-timer that owns this place
has been here for decades.
Mr. Dreyfuss, hi.
- Jughead Jones. You remember me?
- Of course I do.
Great. This is Betty Cooper,
a friend of mine from the FBI.
- We were hoping you could help us.
- Come on up.
We're 100% certain
that my sister made a call
from the pay phone on the Lonely Highway,
but when we got there, it was destroyed.
Shredded? Like a tin can?
Exactly, yeah. Have you seen that before?
Back in the summer of '77
and again in '82.
I know what happened to your sister.
She's had an encounter.
Yes, right, but with who?
The Mothmen.
I'm sorry. The Mothmen?
What makes you say that?
The phone booth.
You see,
their ships use antimatter fusion reactors
that create a gravity field
that allows them to levitate,
like a balloon.
But anything that gets caught
in that stasis, well, it...
It gets crushed
like it's made out of papier-mâché.
I knew our friends were back in town.
I've been picking up their chatter
on my radios.
That was a colossal waste of time.
A lot of people believe this.
There is some evidence.
My sister went missing.
She was taken by someone, not some thing.
What are you even saying?
Things happen, especially in Riverdale,
that you and I can't explain.
Sometimes there isn't
a logical explanation.
- Sometimes unexplained phenomenon...
- No. Someone is...
kidnapping, torturing and murdering women.
That's not a phenomenon.
It's just pure evil.
But I'll be damned
if I let it happen to anyone else.
Can you hurry up?
I need to get back to Riverdale.
- Because I care about you.
- You don't live here.
You deserted us.
Being a real sister
doesn't mean coming in
and telling me how to live my life.
Especially when you don't know
anything about it.
My daughter is alive!
- She called.
- -Betty, you have to help me.
I ran as fast as I could.
You have to come get me.
Polly, I wanna tell you that
I love you and that I'm here for you.
Just please, please, please come home.
Hey, how's it going?
Good, good.
I haven't seen you in here before.
Name's Shane. I'm visiting from L.A.
Oh. Well...
Guess it's true
what they say about L.A. guys.
Oh? What's that?
That they're... hot.
What do they say about guys in Riverdale?
Why don't you tell me?
What are you doing?
Uh, sorry. I misread the situation.
I thought...
- You thought I was like you?
- No.
- That I wanted you?
- Think I came here to be groped by you?
- No! No.
- What the hell?
- Hey. What are you doing?
Saving your life,
whether you want it saved or not.
Get the hell out of here.
You're leaving these girls alone
and never coming back here again.
Hey, these girls are looking to trick.
Tell your dirtbag friends
the party's over.
Put a little ice on it.
Those bruises will settle down
in a few days.
And keep those cuts clean.
- Thanks, Dad.
- You're a grown man.
And, as your father, I'm...
I'm terrified for you right now.
What's going on?
I think...
I'm ashamed of myself.
Of being gay.
Is this something that I did? That I...?
No. No, Dad. No.
This isn't your fault. Okay?
You've... You've always accepted me.
You've never judged me.
- But Mom...
- What?
What happened?
There was this one time.
We were back-to-school shopping.
And she made some off-hand comment.
Like... about needing to buy me...
husky clothes.
I don't know.
Man, I just felt, like, so ashamed.
So I...
I told her I was meeting Betty,
and I went to Fox Forest.
To be alone.
I didn't even know it was a cruising spot.
And there was this other guy there.
And he was telling me I was cute.
Or whatever.
It was like...
all the stuff Mom said just washed away.
And ever since then, I...
I've been cruising.
It's like I'm hardwired this way.
Or something. I don't... I don't know.
I don't know.
Get out. Now.
You...
- You're not Patty.
- No, I'm her sister.
You can't do this.
You can't arrest me again.
- You let me go. You got nothing on me!
- You're right.
I'm not gonna arrest you.
But you are coming with me.
- Waldo. What's going on?
- Is Lerman with you?
What? No, definitely not.
I've been steering clear of him. Why?
His parents just called me.
They think Lerman ran away.
- Any idea where he might be?
- God, no. I haven't talked to him.
Tell the Logans
that I'm calling in some help.
Come on.
Please don't do this.
I told you,
I don't know where Patty is. Why?
Why are you doing this?
You really have to ask me that?
You are still preying on these girls.
Exactly the same way you preyed on Polly.
I have a family.
I had a sister.
No one looked out for those girls.
No one was protecting them.
I couldn't even protect Polly.
But I can deliver justice.
- Jughead.
- Hey. This is an emergency.
One of my students is missing
on the Lonely Highway.
I'm on the highway.
I'm ten miles north of town.
I'm leaving now. I'll meet you halfway.
- Who is it?
- Lerman Logan. He's 14.
I'm on my way.
I'll send someone to untie you tomorrow.
If I remember.
Here are the Stonewall Stallions
versus the Riverdale Bulldogs.
Let's go.
Go, go.
Lerman.
Thank God.
Yeah, he was walking
on the shoulder in a daze.
You okay, bud?
Mr. Jones.
Did it happen again?
Thank you for finding Lerman.
We'd hoped he wouldn't have
to go through this again.
- Again?
- Lerman's a sleepwalker.
Has been since he was little.
We thought he grew out of it,
but then he started hurting himself.
He walked into a door.
Another time
he burnt his hand on the stove.
Even fell out of a window once
and broke his arm.
We started locking
his bedroom door at night.
Now, we gave him
the whole basement to himself.
We just made sure he was safe.
So you were the mole people
keeping him locked up.
All we've done is try to protect him.
I remember we were so terrified
after that morning
we found the front door open and...
Lerman was just gone.
That whole week,
we thought we'd lost my boy.
Wait. He was missing for a week?
Where did he go? What happened?
A Good Samaritan found him
wandering the Lonely Highway.
With no memory of the prior week.
That's why we were so upset with you.
We thought your questioning might trigger
something like this happening.
God only knows
what draws him to that highway.
I don't think it's a coincidence.
Polly and Lerman both end up
on the Lonely Highway? No way.
I agree.
But what are the other connections?
When Polly escaped
and made that phone call, my mom said
she described being in what sounded like
- an alien spaceship.
- Seriously?
Could have been abducted
by the same person.
Why keep Polly but let Lerman go?
Maybe he escaped.
Which is why we need to find out
what Lerman knows.
We'll have to exhaust every option,
no matter how insane.
Yeah.
Bring it in. Come on. Circle up.
Circle up. Come on.
Look at me. Hey! Look at me.
Don't worry about the scoreboard.
I don't care what it says.
You're playing with heart.
That is all I could ever ask from you.
But listen. This is your moment.
The whole town is behind you.
The people in those stands
are here for you.
Your teammates are here for you.
I'm here for you!
We won't give up on each other.
If you don't give up on yourself,
then guess what? You can't lose.
you can't lose. Keep your head up.
Let's make this a night
we'll remember forever.
This game is not over. Bring it in.
- Britta, on you!
- Bulldogs, on three!
One, two, three, Bulldogs!
- Come on!
- Get out there and make something happen!
- Break!
- Let's go, Bulldogs!
Let's go, Bulldogs!
Down! Set! Hut!
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, Britta!
Yes!
Archie!
- Heck of a game.
- What game were you watching?
The Bulldogs may not have
triumphed on the scoreboard,
but we've started to win over
the hearts and minds of the town.
Thanks to a side wager with my father,
the rest of the league will no longer
demand that we withdraw.
Ronnie for the win.
I just, uh...
I just wanted to say, "Good game."
Hey, thanks, Derek.
You played great out there.
What do you think?
- Kids got wheels, huh?
- He sure does.
Just remember, keep working.
Keep getting better.
I promise I will. Just like you taught me.
Waldo. This is becoming
a regular thing for us.
So it seems.
I just wanted to let you know
that Lerman's parents
have pulled him out of school.
- They've left Riverdale.
- Oh, my God.
- Where'd they go?
- They left me a message
but no forwarding address
or contact information.
Suppose they wanted a fresh start.
Yeah, don't we all?
- Hey. What's wrong?
- Agent Cooper.
- Glen, what's going on?
- I came to check on you.
Why is my mom upset?
Because you lied to me, Elizabeth.
You made me feel
like she might still be out there.
That there might still be hope.
You told your mother that the blood wasn't
a match for your sister's?
- Mom, I'm so sorry.
- No, don't.
How could you?
How dare you.
Can't imagine what you must be
going through, Mrs. Cooper.
I will be personally
taking over this case.
No, no, no. I'm working this case, Glen.
This is my sister!
I'll make sure that this investigation
is handled thoroughly. By the book.
I'll leave no stone unturned.