Michael Corleone,
Tony Soprano, Scarface.
All ruthless gangsters.
All heroes of their own story.
And every hero...
...has an origin story,
including Hiram Lodge.
Even though he's been Riverdale's
chief tormentor for ten years now,
shockingly little is known about him...
how he came to be...
and why he's obsessed
with destroying our poor town.
What is his "Rosebud" as it were?
And why does he collect
lost souls like Reggie Mantle?
And why are
the Reggie Mantles of the world...
drawn to Hiram Lodge like moths to flame?
- That was a short day.
- I have an errand, Dad. I'll be back.
Well, you better be back by 10.
- We got...
- McPharlins coming in. I know.
I said I'll be back.
And you are certain it's him?
There is no room for error here.
Wow.
Great work.
No. This is personal.
I'll handle it myself.
Tonight.
Reggie. You are not on my calendar.
That's my father's debt to you.
All of it.
Mr. Lodge,
I appreciate you bailing my old man out
when his business was in trouble.
But this makes him square, right?
That it does.
The only question I have is:
What does this mean for our arrangement?
Well, the truth is,
I'd like to keep working for you.
But I want real advancement.
I'm good with numbers.
And I have ideas.
Some big, big ideas.
Okay, I tell you what, Reggie,
I will find a privileged place for you
if you do me one last favor.
I need you to get me a gun.
A ghost gun, one that can't be traced.
- Is that a problem for you?
- No, sir. No problem.
I'll bring it to you
after my last shift at the lot.
You will not find a better deal
in all of Riverdale.
Come on, Sam, you're not gonna
cheap out on your son, are you?
Excuse me?
Let's go, Sean.
Let me ask you, Mr. McPharlin.
Do you remember your first car?
Mine was a 1970 Chevelle.
I named her Bella.
And boy, oh, boy, the memories
Bella and I made together...
Cruising, going on dates,
late nights at the drive-in.
Mine was named Red Ruby.
She was an '84 Challenger.
Mr. McPharlin,
this is the car
your son will pick up his prom date in.
The car he'll take with him to college.
The car he'll get laid in.
We'll take it. Right, Dad?
I was gonna close that deal.
You didn't need to step in there
with that trash talk.
You're getting rusty.
- I have a half a mind to...
- To what?
Beat me like you used to?
Go ahead and try, old man.
I'm not in high school anymore.
It's the sale that matters.
Set some of that money aside
for this month's payment to Hiram.
I took care of Hiram. It's over.
We're paid off.
Is that true? You don't have
to work for that gangster anymore?
That gangster pulled your ass
out of the fire.
- I'm still gonna work for him.
- Why?
What about our dream
about being partners? Full partners.
That's your dream, Dad.
From where I'm standing,
my future is with Hiram.
I gotta go.
Hiram, I'm asking you,
just leave my son alone.
The debt's paid. Just let him go.
Reggie is a grown man
who makes his own decisions.
Reggie is a fool.
He's blinded by your money.
Doesn't care how you get it.
Maybe you're failing
to see your own son's potential.
If he were my son, I'd be proud of him.
Hiram, I swear, if you don't let him go...
Choose... your next words wisely.
Or better yet...
get the hell out of my office.
Untraceable, like you asked.
Excellent.
Reggie, your father came to see me.
He, uh, stormed in, made wild demands.
If you're gonna work for me,
get your house in order first.
- I'm so sorry...
- Don't apologize. Fix it.
Then meet me back here tonight.
You went to see Hiram Lodge
behind my back.
Dad, you don't get
to speak for me. Not anymore.
Can't even look at you. I'm so ashamed.
Me...?
Nothing I ever do is good enough
for you, is it?
But just because your life is crap
doesn't give you the right
to take it out on me.
You beat me.
You punched down at me my whole damn life.
But I stayed.
After all you did...
I stayed.
Not anymore.
You know...
Hiram has done more with his life...
than you ever will.
And as far as I know,
he never laid a finger
on his wife or daughter.
- How'd it go with your father?
- I don't have a father anymore.
- That's a rather bold statement.
- I mean it.
Of that, I have no doubt.
It reminds me
of my relationship with my father.
He didn't approve of your business either?
To put it mildly.
Where is he now?
Therein lies a tale.
All done.
I must have left my wallet
in my other jacket.
- It's okay. Just pay me double next time.
- No, no, no.
I tell you what,
I got something better than cash.
That, my friend, is palladium.
It's a precious metal
worth more than gold.
That tiny piece alone
would fetch you $100.
- Where'd you get it?
- An old buddy of mine told me
there are unmined veins
of palladium upstate,
in a small Rockland County town
called Riverdale.
- Riverdale? On the Sweetwater River?
- Yes, sir.
You head north to Riverdale,
it might just change your life.
The promise of buried palladium had...
captured my father's imagination.
So we moved...
- Me, my father, my mother.
- -to an apartment in Riverdale.
- And was there palladium?
- There were mines.
My father got a job at one,
but after six months,
there was a collapse.
He survived, but the mines were shut down.
And no palladium?
Rumors of it. But no.
But my father decided
we would stay in Riverdale,
make our American dreams come true.
My mom got a job waiting tables at Pop's.
- She's not going yet?
- She's not.
Here's some hot dogs for you.
Pancakes for you. Anything else?
No. Thank you.
While my father and I returned
to our old line of work.
- All done. Five dollars, sir.
- Gotta be joking.
- They're still all scuffed up in front.
- I've done my best, sir.
Not good enough, pal.
Hey! You need to pay us.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
Jaime, just let it go.
It's just one shine, that's all.
After the mine collapse,
my father seemed somehow diminished.
You know, the...
The light in his eyes had dimmed.
In time,
we became fixtures outside of Pop's.
Our customer base grew. I was polishing
as many shoes as my father.
That's good enough, kid.
I don't know
if I can make change for this.
- Consider it a tip for a job well done.
- Thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
Listen, if you're ever looking
for extra work,
you come see me at Cucina Sacasa.
I might have something for you.
Have a good evening, gentlemen.
Ah-ah. Don't be fooled, Jaime.
That man is a gangster.
His money is blood money.
All right?
Hey, Hermione.
You can ask me out every day, Jaime,
but my answer will always be the same. No.
Come on. Why not?
My mother sort of forbids it.
She doesn't want me to date the son
of a man who shines shoes for a living.
With all due respect,
your mom cleans toilets
and changes bedsheets at the Five Seasons.
What's the difference?
I'm really sorry.
She just wants what's best for me.
But for what it's worth,
I do think you're cute.
Hermione's words
cut me to the bone.
As long as I shined shoes for a living,
I was a second-class citizen.
But I refused to accept that.
- Is that what I have to know?
- Yeah.
I'd like to work for you, sir.
- Sure.
- Why is that?
Because you have two things I don't.
Money and respect.
It's not respect, kid. It's fear.
- There's a big difference.
- I wanna be feared too.
- What's your name?
- I'm Jaime Luna, sir.
I'm Vittorio Alto.
My friends call me Vito.
Your pop know you came to see me?
No, sir.
You got guts.
All right. I got a delivery for you
to make. Think you can handle it?
Yes, sir. Absolutely, sir.
- What do you want?
- I have a delivery from Vito Alto.
Good.
You don't look like
one of Vito's typical employees.
- What's your name?
- Jaime Luna.
You people.
You work twice as fast for half the pay.
This is for Vito.
Thanks, kid. Any problems?
The guy I delivered to made comments
that didn't sit well with me.
About my background, you know?
Where I come from.
Join me.
This guy, that's Louie.
Everybody knows Louie's a clown.
You don't take that personally.
I try not to,
but sometimes it makes me really angry.
Still, you kept your cool.
And in this business,
that means everything.
- Understand me?
- Yes, sir.
Cheer up, kid.
Easiest money you're ever gonna make.
And there's plenty more...
if you wanna keep making deliveries.
- You can count on me, boss.
- Good boy.
Vito was right. The money I earned
delivering packages in one week
eclipsed what I would've made
shining shoes for two months.
Whoever said
money couldn't buy happiness was a sucker.
- Hey, Pop.
- Hey.
I haven't seen much of you.
Where you been?
Got a job at that fancy Italian place.
- I make deliveries.
- Very nice shoes for a delivery boy.
You know.
Pays well...
and I get good tips.
With money also came confidence.
And I needed every ounce of it
to win over Hermione Gomez.
So how about that date, gorgeous?
You know I'm nothing if not persistent.
Perhaps to a fault, Jaime.
You know what?
You twisted my arm.
I'll allow you to buy me dinner
at Pop's tonight. How does that sound?
Sounds great. Seven?
Order anything on the menu.
Order it all if you want.
Didn't realize there was money
in the shoeshine business.
Well, there isn't.
But that doesn't stop my dad
from working like a dog,
day in and day out,
to provide for my mom and me.
I can relate.
My mother's sacrificed so much
working at the Five Seasons...
all to make my life easier.
- I wish there was a way to repay her.
- Exactly.
It's the reason I got this other job.
Oh, yeah? Where? Doing what?
Making deliveries for Vittorio Alto.
You mean, Vito, the gangster?
Mr. Alto's a businessman.
Working for him is gonna be
my ticket out of Riverdale.
What can I get you two?
A hamburger
with a side of onion rings, please.
And same for me, Pop.
And a chocolate shake. Two straws.
And if you did make it out of Riverdale,
where would you go?
I'd be living in a penthouse
in New York City,
running my own business.
- What, did I say something funny?
- No.
In fact, as it so happens...
- ...I wanna live in Manhattan too.
- Are you Jaime Luna?
Yeah. What's the problem?
You're under arrest
for trafficking of a Class II narcotic.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
This is no joke, kid.
We know what operation's being run
out of that Italian place.
Look, give us the name of your supplier,
and you can walk out of here
and get back to your date at the diner.
How does that sound?
I've got nothing to say to you.
Mr. Alto?
- How can we help you?
- I'm here about Jaime Luna.
He's in trouble.
Your bail's been posted.
You're free to go.
Did you talk?
Not a word.
- Who'd you call?
- No one.
- Not even your family?
- Especially not my family.
They'd be so ashamed of me.
Sit down.
You're a good boy, Jaime.
You protected me.
In turn, you protected my business.
I'm proud of you.
- Here.
- Thank you, sir.
You've proven yourself. I'm gonna give you
a bump up. No more deliveries.
From now on, you're gonna be collecting.
That makes you part of the inner circle.
Thank you, Vito. Really.
- Can I impart a friendly advice, kid?
- Always.
You afraid to call your folks at home?
Way I see that, you're still worrying
about other people's expectations
when you should be worrying
about yourself.
You gotta be your own man,
especially if you wanna make it
in this business.
- You understand what I'm saying?
- Yes, sir.
Good. By the way, you better marry
that pretty girl who came by here earlier.
Hermione? She came here?
She's got her head screwed on right.
And she had your back when you needed it.
You don't let her get away.
- I might have blown my one shot with her.
- I wouldn't be so sure of that.
Especially since I got you something,
a bonus to go with your promotion.
Hey.
I thought
tonight we could finish our date.
- Don't even try.
- Fine.
Well, if not that,
then at least let me give you a ride home.
I'm thinking about
changing my name.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I'm tired of living
in someone else's shadow.
I wanna be my own man.
What are you planning to call yourself?
Well, I was thinking Hiram Lott.
As in, I'm gonna have a lot in life.
Hiram sounds nice.
Strong.
Unique.
But Lott?
I think you can do better.
How about something statelier like Lodge?
Hiram Lodge.
That's not half bad.
"Fred Andrews."
Here.
"Jaime Luna"?
I go by a different name now.
You can call me Hiram Lodge.
Uh-huh. Have you filled out the paperwork?
It's being processed
at the courthouse as we speak.
Luna or Lodge, you'll still be shining
my old man's shoes for burgers, Jaime.
What's my name, Mantle?
Say it!
I wanna hear you say it.
- Hiram Lodge.
- That's right. Don't you ever forget it.
I got a call from your school.
You beat up two students
'cause they wouldn't call you Hiram Lodge?
Are you crazy?
You forsake our family name
for what? For vanity?
You think I'm a fool?
I know
where you're getting all this money.
It's from that damn gangster.
So what?
It's dishonest!
More than that, it's criminal.
- That man will ruin you, Jaime.
- It's Hiram.
I'm doing what I'm doing for you and Mom.
To give you the things you deserve,
things you can't afford.
You sad, stupid boy.
Working for the likes of Vito, are you...?
It's gonna cost you everything.
Everything you love, Jaime.
You brought shame to this family.
Then it's a good thing
I'm not a Luna anymore, Dad.
I don't wanna be like you,
spending my days shining
the shoes of men who look down on me.
You can lecture me
all you want about shame,
but you can't buy Mom a dishwasher
or new shoes for yourself.
It's embarrassing.
Being your son... is embarrassing.
Mr. Vito, with all due respect,
I want you to leave my son alone.
He's a good boy but impressionable.
Tell me, Javier,
do you not want your son to be successful?
He's got nice things, a pretty girlfriend.
Seems to me your son's old enough
to make his own decisions.
I think you misunderstand me.
I'm not asking you.
I'm telling you.
Whatever arrangement exists
between you and my son, it's over.
Or what? What are you gonna do?
I'll call the police...
and tell them everything about you
and your dirty business.
I see.
Well, in that case, maybe you can, uh,
let me think it over, compadre.
I'll be in touch.
My... My father was a smart man.
He believed human nature was good.
But...
he was wrong.
- How you doing today, Javier?
- Hey. Morning, Pop.
It's gonna be a good day. I can feel it.
Hit it!
Hiram,
Lourdes, I'm Apollonia, Hermione's mother.
- I'm very sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Javier seemed like a warm and caring man.
Thank you for coming, Mrs. Gomez.
He was a good man.
Even for a lowly shoe shiner.
I, uh...
I misjudged him.
I'm not proud of that.
- My deepest apologies, Hiram.
- Thank you.
He seems so calm.
It's shock, I think.
He hasn't said much since it happened.
Mm. Such a tragedy.
I suppose, but you know
what they say about playing with fire...
- What are you getting at, Penelope?
- I'm just pointing out.
One day,
he can't rub two nickels together.
The next, he's driving a sports car
and taking you out on the town.
We all know the truth.
Your boyfriend is a gangster.
What did Jaime think would happen
when he started working with criminals?
His name is Hiram.
As for what he thought would happen,
he thought he'd be able
to make a better life for his family.
Family is more important to him
than anything.
Can either of you skanks say the same?
- Hey.
Are you hanging in there?
Hmph. Trying.
I just want you to know,
whatever you need, I'm here for you, okay?
Thank you.
Mrs. Luna, I wanted to come
in person to pay my respects.
Your husband, he was a good man,
an honest man.
His kindness will be missed.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Take as much time as you need, kid.
When you're ready to come back to work,
come see me
and we'll pick up where we left off.
No disrespect for the dead
but now, at least,
you can become the man
that you were destined to be.
Forget about that. Right now,
I want you to focus on your mother.
Okay? Whatever she needs,
whatever you need, you come see me.
Capiche?
Thanks, Vito.
I am so lucky
that I still have you, Jaime.
But I beg you,
please be done with this nasty business.
I promise you, I will.
Hey, kid, heard about your old man.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I'm looking for Vito.
He came by my house earlier.
Well, he ain't here.
But pull up a chair. We'll deal you in.
Sonny's on a losing streak...
Did Vito have my father killed?
I never found out why Vito wasn't
at the Cucina that night.
Probably dumb luck.
But I made my point.
I'm gonna put the shakes in the fridge.
Vito skipped town and never came back.
He knew if he did,
he'd meet the same fate as his underlings.
What happened to Vito?
Word is, he went abroad to visit family.
But from now on,
you should consider me the new Vito.
- Hiram Lodge. Understood?
- Yeah. Works for me.
From that day forward,
I was Riverdale's new boss.
People paid me their dues, and soon...
I was moving up in the world.
I was the biggest fish
in a somewhat small pond.
- Then what happened?
- I got married, Reggie.
I became a father.
And I knew true happiness.
Remember when you told me
that we would move to New York together?
It's time, Hiram, to leave all this behind
and keep your promise.
Not only for us but for your little girl.
Whatever you want, mi amor.
So we moved to New York
and the rest is history.
That's one hell of a saga, Mr. Lodge.
But what brought you back to Riverdale?
Turns out that my father was correct
about the palladium.
He was simply looking in the wrong place.
I did discover a vein of palladium.
It was thin, but it was a sign that...
I would succeed
where my father had failed.
I built a prison over that vein,
so that behind the walls,
I could do whatever I wanted
and nobody could see.
As a smokescreen.
- You had your prisoners doing the digging.
- Yes.
But now that vein is tapped
with a disappointingly small yield.
So I need to get to the one that I found
under the Blossom maple groves.
If I fail...
all my efforts in Riverdale, all my gains,
all my losses, will be for nothing.
I will not let that happen.
I will finish what my father began.
You're unstoppable, Mr. Lodge.
You started with nothing
and got everything you wanted.
Is that what you take away from my story?
You have money. Respect. A business.
What more could a man want?
I want you to drive me somewhere.
I'd like to visit an old friend
in a nursing home.
Mind if I ask who?
Not at all.
Vittorio Alto.
The man who murdered my father.
Hello, Vito.
It's me, Hiram Lodge.
Son of Javier Luna.
It's taken me years to find you...
but my luck finally turned.
Do you remember when we first met?
I said I wanted to be feared like you?
Yeah.
You tell me, Vito, at this very moment...
you afraid of me?
Adiós, Vito.
Reggie, I wanna thank you
for your help and your discretion tonight.
I won't be needing you any longer.
- For the rest of the night?
- No.
You're done, Reggie.
I no longer require your services.
Mr. Lodge, hold on, I want this.
I want what you have.
Yeah, you don't see it, Reggie.
But from where I'm at...
if I could go back...
spend a few more years
shining shoes with my dad...
I'd do that in a heartbeat.
But I can't go back to that car lot.
I left so I could prove to my father
what I can do, who I can be.
Just give him one more chance.
Or not.
But your debt is paid.
I'm giving you an out, Reggie.
Do not insult me, and accept it.
What are you still doing here?
Why aren't you home?
I'm sorry, Reg.
I'm ashamed.
I've never done right by you.
Not ever.
But I wanna start, son.
Your timing's good, Dad.
I'm done with Mr. Lodge.
Thank God.
- If you're serious about your offer...
- I am.
Then you gotta let me run
with the ball a little bit.
Trust that I can take care of things.
Listen to my ideas.
I have good ideas sometimes.
If you can do that, then we can try.
One more time.
How does that sound?
Mantle and Son?
It's okay, Dad.
It's okay.
I cannot believe Dorinda.
When I told her
I was coming back to Riverdale,
she referred to it as my ex-husband's
"crime-infested hellhole."
Which is accurate but it still
makes you want to strangle her.
Mom,
can't we just have a nice lunch?
I invited you here to see the renovation,
not trash-talk the people on your show.
Come on, it's reality television.
What do you think we do,
bring each other cups of sugar?
How's your father? Have you seen him?
Oh, you know.
- Only when he wants to cause trouble.
- Which is always.
- You know what his problem is?
- What?
He's never satisfied by what he has.
Never.
He will never be happy.
Sadly, that tracks.
He should've retired
when he had the chance.
Seven years ago. Remember?
Please, he would sooner die.
Was he ever even
really sick back...?
Hermosita...
it's done.
I don't know how you found Vito,
but your grandfather has been avenged.
A bullet to the head.
I saw it when I went to do cleanup.
- Did you find any security cameras?
- Yes. They've been wiped clean.
Good. Very good.
I've sacrificed so much to get this far,
I can't stumble now.
And when I've mined
all the palladium that eluded my father...
I'll get back everything else
I've lost too.