Portrait of a town in flames.
Thanks to a fire extinguisher
Mr. Andrews kept stored in the hall closet
and another one under the kitchen sink,
what could have been a suburban inferno
was, instead, merely the latest indication
of how far the now non-existent
town of Riverdale had fallen.
An arsonist on the loose,
and no firemen to battle the fires.
Archie.
You see this guy in the front?
That is my Grandpa Artie.
He was a fireman back in the day.
Oh, jeez,
I think I know where this is going.
The best counterattack
is not to fight fire with fire,
but to fight fire with a fire department.
What, no mano a mano with Hiram Lodge?
I called Ronnie. She's gonna talk to him.
Oh, Ronnie is. That's interesting.
You see this rookie?
He ended up becoming
Riverdale's fire chief for 20 years.
He's retired now,
but he still lives in Riverdale.
Well, go get him, soldier.
I'm hoping we already know
the answer, Dr. Curdle Junior, but...
is this my sister's body?
Your sister's been missing for a week.
These remains have been in Swedlow Swamp
for approximately three years.
The bog preserved her.
Well, do you have a cause of death yet?
At first blush,
blunt-force trauma to the head.
What happens to the body now? To... To her?
Without identification, she'll be sent
to the crematorium for disposal.
Dr. Curdle, will you just wait a beat
while I do some digging for her identity?
Of course.
All right. I'm going back
to Swedlow Swamp.
Polly, or at least her phone,
is still out there.
Daddy. Someone set fire
to Archie's house last night
and this attack
has your fingerprints all over it.
Why would I wanna burn down
the Andrews family home?
The rash of arson cases around town
is meant to drive
any remaining long-term residents away
so your precious SoDale
becomes the only game in town.
Am I getting warm, Daddy?
Riverdale can't be saved.
Your high school is a joke.
Heck, you haven't had garbage pickups
in months. The place smells like a corpse.
It's not coming back to life.
We'll see about that, Daddy.
This just became personal.
Wow. Was I ever that young?
Feels like a lifetime ago.
It doesn't have to be, Chief Russell.
I mean, you could come out of retirement.
This town needs a fire department.
Hiram Lodge
didn't just shut down the department,
he firebombed the firehouse.
Then we'll operate out of my gym.
And I'll be the first volunteer,
following in my Grandpa Artie's footsteps.
It was an honor
working with your grandpa, Archie.
But this is a young man's battle.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Miss Winchester herself.
Come for another surprise visit, Cheryl?
Thank you for taking care
of the River Vixens
whilst I was self-isolating,
but, as Elton John likes to say:
"The bitch is back in town."
And this squad is my birthright.
Wrong. The Vixens are mine now, hon.
I restarted them,
I'm financing them,
and we've been doing all the work.
So, what are you gonna do about that?
What every Vixen throughout history
has done to settle a dispute:
- Challenge you to a dance-off.
- I'm pregnant.
- Does that mean you forfeit?
- I'll dance for Miss Topaz.
As her proxy.
You know, I usually have a rule
about annihilating high school students,
but you seem particularly insufferable.
Now, let's decide this.
All those in favor of moi as your HBIC?
And all those for me?
A tie.
In that case, I'd be willing
to share control of the Vixens...
if your ego could handle that.
Agreed. For now.
Why are you buffoons just standing there?
Take it from the top!
Well, I spoke with my father,
and, of course, he denies
having anything to do
with setting your porch on fire, Archie.
Figures. And I spoke
to the old fire chief,
and he won't help.
So, now I have no fire engine,
no volunteers, and no one to train them.
I could maybe help with that.
My best friend Katy Keene's
roommate, Jorge,
his ex-boyfriend
is an actual New York firefighter.
Let me see if I can get him
out here for a day or two.
Ronnie, that would be amazing. Thank you.
In the meantime,
after my tête-à-tête with dear old Daddy,
I came up with a crazy idea
to bolster Riverdale's struggling economy.
Listen up, guys.
This week, you're going to learn
how to revive a dying economy.
Namely, ours.
Step one, create jobs.
Who wants to renovate a seedy video store
and turn it into a jewelry shop?
And be exempt from the midterm exam?
Tabitha. Check this out.
Spent the afternoon at the library.
Found an article
about Old Man Dreyfuss and his crew.
"Four of the five miners
detailed an encounter
with the frightening humanoid creature
they described as a Mothman."
Well, he wasn't lying.
Or he was lying to you now
and they were lying back then.
Except I kept looking for more articles
and I found that one
written two months after the Mothman one.
"A group of residents in the town
of Riverdale were stunned late last month
as they watched a mysterious sight unfold.
Unexplained lights materializing
and hovering in the dark sky."
Read the last paragraph.
Do you see who's quoted as an eyewitness?
No way.
You think you can get me an interview?
Hey, sarge. Nice digs.
What? Jackson. When did you
get released from the hospital?
A couple of days ago.
I signed up
for the program the VA was offering,
the therapeutic housing.
Why? You don't need that, do you?
Some of us need help
transitioning to civilian life, yes.
I'm sorry. No, I'm happy for you.
Figure I'd take up your invitation
before I go.
Well, your timing's perfect. I'm about
to go to the bar to meet some friends.
Come inside,
drop your stuff off, and we'll go.
So, I went through all the archives
in the sheriff's office, Dr. Curdle,
and there was only one
missing person filed
in the last seven years, Margaret Harper.
I'm sorry, Miss Cooper,
but Margaret Harper isn't a match, either.
According to this police report,
Margaret had braces
at the time of her disappearance.
There's no evidence of braces
on our Jane Doe.
Okay. So, she's not Polly or Margaret.
She's a third missing girl.
And three's a pattern.
Guys, this is Eric Jackson.
We served together.
I trust him with my life.
- Eric, these are the guys.
- Nice to meet you, fellas.
Jackson, thank you for your service.
My dad served as well.
No greater honor.
So, I'm looking for a few good men.
Story of my life.
I'm hoping
to assemble a volunteer fire department
to replace the one Hiram Lodge disbanded.
Guys who aren't afraid to run
into a burning building and save lives.
So... I figured I'd start with you guys.
We don't know the first thing
about firefighting.
Except for what I learned watching
Backdraft over and over in junior high.
And that is why Veronica's
getting an expert from New York.
It's gonna be fine. Trust me.
So, who's with me?
Civilians.
Thank you for coming in,
Miss Harper.
I don't want to reopen old wounds,
but I was working
on another missing person's case
when I came across your daughter's file.
Margaret was... a bright girl.
But she fell in with the wrong crowd.
Were you and Margaret close?
Not so much.
I think she...
felt like she couldn't talk to me.
Once she...
She started going with the truckers.
Miss Harper, what do you believe
happened to your daughter?
I...
I have no idea.
Which, in a way, makes it so much worse.
Yeah. I understand.
Sheriff Keller did what he could.
But he was one man.
And the whole town was falling apart.
There was a social worker... named Toni.
She was a godsend.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Cheryl Blossom.
I'd heard rumors that Queen Elsa
had come down from the mountain.
It was a Vixens emergency.
Well, how are your art skills these days?
Flawless as ever. Why?
I want you to design something for me.
Something that would fit
on this printing plate.
I was a Cavalry Scout
before being selected for sniper school.
By the time I graduated, I could
bull's-eye a playing card at 500 meters.
All right, guys.
Last question for Corporal Jackson.
Ask him anything.
What was the commander like in the Army?
I'll show you.
I got this nifty hunk of metal
from a grenade on the battlefield.
But if it weren't for your commander,
I'd have been sent home in a body bag.
Sergeant Andrews is the kind of man
that never stops giving back.
Hell, that's why he's trying to start
a volunteer fire department on his own.
Wait. Can we help with that?
What, with the fire department?
No, you got school and football.
Due respect, so do you, sir.
Damn.
My own friends turned me down,
and you guys are in?
- Yeah.
Okay then.
But you have to be 16 to sign up
and you need your parents' permission.
What's this, Miss Lodge?
Prototypes.
The real money will be printed,
not photocopied.
So... There was a town in Oregon
on the verge of economic collapse,
much like our beloved Riverdale.
Until they started printing
their own money.
Money they could use as actual currency,
but only in their town.
So, it keeps getting reinvested
in the town.
- How does that work?
- Simple.
I pay you for remodeling my jewelry shop
with Riverdollars,
which you then funnel back
into Riverdale's economy
by spending it at Pop's or the Bijou.
And they'll accept it?
Yes. Which they can either redeem with me
or hopefully use it
to pay their own employees
to keep the flow going.
I've already sold one
of my Glamergé eggs for $50,000,
which will serve as collateral
for the new currency.
It's an investment I'm happy to make,
especially if it gets people in the habit
of spending more and supporting
local businesses in Riverdale.
Any questions?
Yeah. When do we get paid?
Mom?
I found Polly's phone.
No sign of her,
but... I found this in the swamp.
That means Swedlow Swamp
is exactly where we should keep looking.
Betty Cooper. What can I get you?
Toni, does the name Margaret Harper
mean anything to you?
Yeah. She went missing a few years ago.
Yeah. I've been looking for Polly,
as you know,
and I came across Margaret's file.
And I talked to her mom,
who said that you really helped her.
I mean, I tried to.
The truth is there's a lot
of Margarets in Riverdale.
She's just one of the few
that went missing and got reported.
- Yeah.
- I tried to set them up with jobs
or a support group,
but it's hard, you know?
Of course.
Toni... I found a body in Swedlow Swamp.
Oh, my God.
It wasn't Polly.
It wasn't Margaret, but...
my mom found Polly's phone there.
Something really bad
is happening... in that swamp.
And we need your help searching it.
Well, the Serpents
are at your disposal, Betty.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming
to meet with us, Pop.
No problem. Any excuse to visit
the Chock'lit Shoppe now that I'm retired.
So, about that article we called you for,
the one with the lights,
you were quoted, I was wondering
if you remember what happened.
Clear as day.
It was one night about 50 years ago.
It was late.
There were probably five
or six people in the diner.
Here you go. And here you go.
Two world-famous burger combos. Enjoy.
When all of a sudden, you could feel this,
I don't know, electricity in the air.
We all walked out
to the parking lot to take a look.
Then, a few minutes later...
the lights were gone.
And it was just a beautiful autumn night.
That's incredible, Grandpa.
- What do you think it was?
- We all had theories.
Some said aliens.
But the most credible explanation I heard
was that it was military testing
from an army base outside Riverdale.
Did it ever happen again?
The lights?
No.
But I'll tell you,
a part of me wished
the lights would come back.
I just got goose bumps.
You know who else was here
that night you should talk to?
- Who?
Cheryl's grandmother.
- Nana Blossom.
- Yeah.
Welcome to day one
of Riverdale's Volunteer Fire Academy.
Today's our first day of training with
a real firefighter from New York City,
who's gonna help get us into shape.
Bernardo Bixby from Engine 141,
the floor is yours.
Thanks, Archie.
So, a show of hands, how many of you
have had prior experience fighting fires?
That's okay. We're gonna start
with the most important lesson.
You must work as a team.
No one goes into a burning building alone.
Now, a team is only as strong
as its weakest link.
And on my crew, there are no weak links!
Yeah.
Why's Veronica printing Monopoly money
with her face on it?
Relax.
You will still get your normal paycheck.
This is mad money, to spend in Riverdale.
Like here or at the Bijou or...
Whiskey. We better make that a double.
I've seen a porcelain doll
possessed by my deceased brother
move faster than you lot!
What the hell is this, Cheryl?
Vixens practice, obvi.
We need to be doing two-a-days
if we want to avoid public embarrassment.
We're supposed to be coaching together.
Clearly you went behind my back
and scheduled a practice.
Well, I knew you would cause
a scene like this, Toni. Duh.
- Oh...
- Vixens, call Nurse Nightingale.
Cheryl, this ends now.
Vixens, like Blossoms, are forged in fire.
Hmm, wow. Sounds like
something your mother would say.
Careful where thoust treads, Toni.
You're on thin ice.
Polly!
Hey, Polly?
That's far enough!
Every one of you
is trespassing on private property.
Retreat immediately
or face the consequences.
Hiram.
My daughter's missing.
She might be somewhere in your swamp.
Alice, as a father, I feel your pain,
but I can't have people
wandering through here.
All of this is gonna be my new turnpike.
Well, it's also a crime scene.
Well, if it is,
it's not your jurisdiction, sheriff.
Well, I'm with the FBI, so the FBI
is declaring this a crime scene.
Oh, I think you're gonna need better
than that badge you got out
of a JackerCrack box, Betty.
In the meantime, off my property.
Now.
Nana Rose,
my grandfather claimed
that you were at the Chock'lit Shoppe
50 years ago
when a bright light appeared in the sky.
Oh, yes. I remember it well.
My suspicion is that the light came
from the Mothmen ship.
"The Mothmen"? Again.
A few weeks after the incident,
I found a hideously misshapen body
in the maple forest.
A Mothman corpse?
An autopsy was performed.
An autopsy...? Like an alien autopsy?
Nana Rose, why has no one heard
about this before?
Oh, the Mothmen
didn't want us talking about it.
You spoke to them?
Well, they came to Thornhill
looking for their missing friends.
They... don't like to be known.
And they didn't like me
keeping their deceased, either.
I told them it had been cremated.
Had it been cremated?
No. I kept it.
Perfectly preserved
in a barrel of maple syrup.
I could try to find it
for you if you like.
Congratulations.
We've successfully introduced
50,000 Riverdollars
into our town's economy.
Yeah!
So, what's next?
We pump more money in.
Exactly. But how much more?
Another thousand? Ten thousand?
Ten thousand!
Wrong. If we flood the market
with new bills, we risk inflation,
or triggering a run
on the bank, which is me.
And... since I'm the one on the hook,
I say we build our economy
slow and steady.
Very clever, mija.
Daddy.
I'm in the middle of a class.
I'm sorry for interrupting,
but I had to congratulate you
on your newest enterprise.
Plastering your face over currency.
Even at my most audacious,
that thought never occurred to me.
Well, it's a good thing I've never limited
myself to what you thought possible.
- Mm.
- Now, if you'll excuse me...
Oh, wait. You and Archie?
Printing money.
Starting a fire department.
Who does such things?
We believe in Riverdale.
And we're bringing it back.
Now, really, Daddy, take a hike.
Where were we?
So, then sarge over here decides
to try and feed this stray dog
outside the outpost.
Now, this dog looked more
like a wolf to me.
- Don't believe him. It was a dog.
- How big are we talking?
Oh, timber wolf-size.
Anyways.
Sarge pours out this MRE
out onto his hand,
sticks it through the fence,
and then the dog
almost bites his arm off, and...
Show them your scar, sarge.
Afternoon, sir.
How can we help you?
- Thought this place was shut down.
- It was. We reopened it.
Now it's gonna house
the new volunteer fire department.
- Do you live on Sketch Alley?
- I do. Name's Earl.
We haven't had a fire department
in a long time.
Lot of buildings burned down 'cause of it.
Well, things are changing.
We're gonna make this town better
for you, your friends.
For everyone.
Heard that talk before.
Hope you can back it up.
Come on, Glen. There has to be
someone you can send my way.
Betty, you have a Jane Doe
and two missing girls
with problematic histories. Look, you
gotta let the local police handle this.
It's one sheriff, Glen.
Up against a rich psychopath
who won't let us search his land.
- So, I'm begging you...
- Betty.
He's back. The Trash Bag Killer.
- What?
- TBK's re-emerged.
- In Tulsa, we think.
- How man...?
- Are there any victims?
- Two. So far.
Look, why don't you send me what you got
and I'll see what I can do.
No, Glen.
Uh... You focus on TBK.
Catch that bastard, okay?
I'm gonna handle everything here myself.
And I'll check in with you.
Damn it, Betty, we warned you.
You're trespassing on private property.
I'm not going anywhere.
My sister is missing.
Other girls, too.
My mom is suffering,
and it's because of your boss
that I'm the only person out here
who can do anything about it.
So, if you wanna stop me,
you'll have to shoot me.
Wait.
I found something
while patrolling the swamp.
But cone of silence,
Hiram can never know I told you.
Okay, you have my word. Cone of silence.
What is it?
Another body.
Cadet Burns!
When O2 rapidly enters
an oxygen-depleted environment
causing an explosion,
what is that phenomenon called?
A backdraft, sir!
Correct! Your reward is 30 more pushups.
Next question!
- You guys the fire department?
- Trying to be.
- The pool hall's burning down!
- What, here on the alley?
- Let's move!
- Grab the hose! Go, go!
- We got eyes on a connector!
- Get the hose! Archie, get everyone back!
Earl's in there!
My friend Earl's still inside.
Sarge, don't even think about it.
- Sarge, no!
- Archie, stop!
Mija. Has the Treasury Department
shown up to arrest you yet?
Daddy, that Riverdollar bill you had
in your fist, where did you get that?
It's amazing what you find in the trash
when there's no one around to collect it.
I knew it.
So, now you're printing fake Riverdollars
to sabotage me?
You accusing me
of counterfeiting your counterfeit money?
My numbers aren't adding up,
and my numbers always add up.
Someone is flooding the economy
with money I didn't print.
Which devalues the money you did print.
Funny how economics works, isn't it?
As Archie would say, Daddy, you suck.
Where did you find this body, Miss Cooper?
I didn't... exactly. An associate did.
In the swamp. And I kn...
I know it's not Polly, but is it...?
Margaret Harper. Yes.
The tell-tale braces
are present on her teeth.
Likely cause of death, trauma.
The left side of her body was pulverized.
As if... with a wrecking ball.
Oh, my God.
Wherefore are my precious Vixens?
I canceled practice.
We need to talk.
For starters, they're our Vixens,
as we agreed.
Fine, fine, fine.
They're our Vixens. Happy now?
No. I wasn't gonna do this, Cheryl,
but I'm officially calling you out.
You've gotten away
with murder in this town
because of your money and your privilege.
And I know you've been
through hell and back time and again.
But that doesn't give you a right to be
a holy terror in this town for no reason.
As if you have any idea
what it's been like for me,
holed-up in Thornhill
for the last seven years.
Oh, spare me. This isn't Drag Me to Hell.
You cursed yourself.
And what you're doing
isn't some grand sacrifice, it's selfish.
Oh. So, now funding the school is selfish.
Money alone isn't gonna solve
the problems of this town.
There are people out here
every single day putting in real work.
And I'm not gonna let you
take over the Vixens
for reasons of vanity or revenge.
Cheryl, I want you out here with us,
on the ground, one of the good guys.
But you're gonna have to take
a good hard look in the mirror
and get it together first.
Your cruelty... is beyond words.
Nana Rose! I need your wisdom.
My heart has once again been shattered.
Oh. Miss Marble.
To what do we owe this pleasure?
Miss Blossom.
I went to sell your brother's portrait
and made the most disturbing
yet fascinating discovery.
It was a forgery.
A very skillful forgery.
And before I call the authorities,
I thought we should chat.
Don't you agree?
What did Bernardo say, sarge?
Rule number one,
don't run into a burning building alone.
Never gonna let me live this down,
are you?
No, sir.
Well, the good news is you're okay,
and you managed to save that man's life.
We know what started the fire yet?
Well, I mean, it's an old building.
It wasn't up to code.
- Still, it's hard not to think it was...
- Arson.
Probably started by Hiram Lodge.
Wait. Who's Hiram Lodge?
Well, he used to be mayor.
Now he's building a new town next to here
and doing everything he can to try
and run the rest of us stragglers out.
Another fat cat lining his pockets
by gaming the system.
Welcome to Riverdale.
All right. I'll see you, fellas.
- Bye, sheriff.
- Yeah.
Man, screw that Hiram guy.
It's okay, Eric.
This is just how life is. For now.
No, it's how life always is.
Guys like us are just cannon fodder
for scumbags like Hiram.
That guy you pulled out of the building,
Earl, he's one of us. A vet.
Another grunt who got chewed up
and spit out by corporate greed.
Man. What the hell
are we fighting for over there
if this is what happens to us
when we come home?
A second body.
They found a second body in the swamp?
How do you think they did that, Reggie?
I don't know, boss. It's a big swamp.
But this is not the hill to die on.
No, no, no. The turnpike,
just like the rest of SoDale,
is a necessary smokescreen.
I know.
But... you could either be a villain
and pour concrete over the swamp,
or you could be a hero...
and let them search it properly.
Sure, the turnpike gets delayed.
But who cares?
We both know that's not the real endgame.
You make a good point, Reggie.
We'll acquiesce to the Cooper ladies.
Let them... wade into the muck a while.
I'll make the call.
We're so, so sorry, Deanna.
But you're... You're...
You're sure it's my Margaret?
Yeah. It's her.
No question.
All these years.
At least...
At least now I know where she is.
I can say goodbye.
Who hurt her?
We don't know yet, Miss Harper.
And my sister is also missing.
Other girls, too.
And so, I swear to you...
we will find out who did this.
- Wait, that's not...
- It is. Yeah.
A special delivery,
courtesy of Nana Rose Blossom.
Straight from the Twilight Zone.
Damn, the smell alone.
That's maple syrup and decay.
It's like a rotting tooth.
It could be anything, Jughead.
It could be... It could be human bones
mixed with fake synthetic bones or...
Or it's a Mothman.
It's...
- It's...
- We're not experts.
This person is, though.
- Who?
- This is Dr. Diane Whitley.
She's an anthropology professor
at Centerville U.
She specializes in ancient cultures
and urban legends
and extraterrestrial phenomena.
I say we call her
and see if she'll come here
and examine this
and tell us what we're dealing with.
So what? In the meantime, it's just...
It's business as usual
while a Xenomorph melts
in my diner's back room?
I'll take the night shift. I'll make sure
no one stumbles upon our little friend.
We have to get
to the bottom of this.
I suspect my father has flooded the market
with counterfeit bills.
So we'll have to do
an in-depth forensic accounting,
recall all the Riverdollars in circulation
and determine how deep a hole we're in.
But for now, sadly...
we'll have to shut down our operation.
Where did you get those ink stains
on your paws?
And don't say "art class."
I want the truth. Now.
We printed up ten grand instead of one.
Wow.
So it wasn't my father
who screwed me over, it was you guys.
You got greedy
and triggered an economic collapse.
Well done, class.
F's for everyone.
We're sorry.
What can we do?
Well...
you're responsible
for that money you printed.
Ten thousand dollars.
And unless you've got a secret stash
of baby Glamergé eggs,
you'll have to work it off.
By providing Riverdale
a much-needed service.
Jackson.
Earl didn't make it.
No.
Yeah, and I found out more
about your pal, Hiram Lodge.
That bastard's done plenty
to deserve what's coming to him.
Jackson.
You put that rifle down. Now.
That's an order!
Sorry, sarge,
we're not in the army anymore.
No.
I'm sorry. I won't let you do this.
I won't let you ruin your life
over Hiram Lodge!
My life's already ruined!
I lost my leg fighting in a war
that didn't change a damn thing!
None of us mattered.
Eric, I know this is dark now,
but when you get into that VA home,
they'll help you see
that things can get better.
They canceled my slot.
I found out this morning.
I needed help. A lifeline, man. I'm lost.
Damn it, I'm lost, Eric!
The only reason I'm fighting so hard
to save this town
is because it's the only thing
keeping me sane.
I'm white-knuckling it out here, too.
I promise you.
And my friends don't know...
because they wouldn't understand.
What are we gonna do, sarge?
For a start?
I think you should stay in Riverdale.
The fire department needs a new commander
and I can't think
of a better man for the job.
And maybe...
Maybe... we can help each other stay sane.
It was exactly as Pop said.
Things started to shake.
The jukebox turned on.
It was 2 a.m. I went outside.
There was this bright white light.
And then I woke up in a booth
and it was 6 a.m.
Hours had gone by. I lost time.
It was a dream.
Prompted by my grandpa's story.
Or is it possible
that you were sleepwalking?
Or... had you been drinking?
That's... besides the point.
I haven't gotten to the craziest part yet.
Will you follow me?
Please?
After I woke up, the first thing I did
was come in here.
Oh... my God.
- I don't understand.
- Me neither.
But something very strange happened
in Riverdale last night.
Paying off your debt
while cleaning up the town.
If there ever was a teachable moment.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a delivery to make.
So, what's up, guys?
Gossip around the teacher's lounge
is that Weatherbee nixed your RROTC cadets
from being volunteer firefighters.
Yeah, well, he was pretty pissed
I brought them to a burning building.
Well, we wanna sign up. Like we
should have done in the first place.
I appreciate that, guys, but it's
too late. Bernardo's back in New York.
No one left to train us.
Maybe I can help on that front.
Chief Russell.
Word got around. About a crazy hero
running into a burning building.
Alone.
Gotta say, it inspired me.
Okay, chief. You're the expert.
What do we need first?
Well... a firetruck might be nice to have.
You gotta be kidding me.
Ronnie, what the hell?
What? I wanted to do my civic duty.
To help you and hurt my father.
- How...? How much do we owe you?
- Oh, don't worry.
We'll be putting out
a "Firefighters of Riverdale" calendar
to defray the costs.
But in the meantime,
I just wanted to help.
Anything for you, Archie.
Two young women went missing
on the Lonely Highway:
Margaret Harper and Polly.
We found Margaret's remains
in Swedlow Swamp.
Where I found Polly's phone.
And we also found
another set of remains in the swamp,
belonging to an unidentified young woman.
And I reached out to sheriffs' offices
in the counties that touch
along the Lonely Highway
asking about any unsolved
missing persons reports,
specifically young women.
And they came back with 13 names.
And I've been in touch
with a network of social workers
in towns the Lonely Highway runs through,
and I got 11 names back.
Five of which overlap with Tom's list.
So, we're talking about 21 missing girls.
How many of them
are we gonna find in Swedlow Swamp?
At least Hiram has agreed
to let us search it now.
Twenty-one girls.
- They can't all be runaways.
- What do you think?
Human trafficking?
Or a serial killer.