There's an old adage,
"You can't go home again,"
which was certainly ringing
true for us.
Archie had been in a war,
Betty was an FBI agent,
Veronica was married,
Toni was Queen of the Serpents
and I was
a published writer.
So why were we
only talking about
how the town of
Riverdale had fallen
and Archie's pipe dream
to somehow save it?
Probably because
it was easier
than the conversations
that awaited us.
Why didn't you
reach out?
I didn't think you wanted
me to after you left me that voicemail.
On the night of your
book launch?
After that,
I just assumed
you didn't
want to hear from me.
That wasn't my intention.
I'm sorry if it came off
that way.
It was nice
to see you,
even if it's strange to be
back here, just deeply uncanny.
Same old Archie, though.
Trying to save everyone.
Good luck with that, dude.
I mean I have
a book to write.
Yeah, after Pop's
retirement party,
I have to get back to
Quantico.
It's good to see you, too,
Jug,
even though it is
a bit weird.
That's some rock on
your finger, Ronnie.
- He must be a great guy.
- Chad?
Yeah, he is,
underneath
the bluster and bravado.
What about you, Bugle Boy?
I'm sure you've had a
swarm of lovers.
I don't know about that.
The last real relationship I was
in... was, well, it was with you.
Devil-may-care fling
never hurt anybody, Archie.
Besides, you should be
having fun at this point in your life.
Because
once you're married...
Well, that's why this is
just a quick jaunt for me.
I have to go back to my life,
my husband.
Yeah, for sure.
- Mom?
- Shh.
I brought you a vanilla
milkshake, extra thick.
Oh, thanks, sweetheart.
Will you put in the fridge?
Keep your voice down.
The twins are finally asleep.
Sure.
- Is Polly home yet?
- Nope. Not yet.
It's pretty late. Where is she?
Oh, you know, out and about
at work. You know your sister.
Jones, it's Samm.
Where the hell are you?
And where are your pages?
Scribners... Forsythe Jones,
you currently owe $9,876
to Premiere Credit.
If you do not pay the outstanding
balance within 24 hours...
So, how did the
Bughead reunion go?
As well as it could have,
considering not all of us
could be happily shacked up
with our
high school sweethearts, Kev.
Uh, FBI agent,
high school drama teacher.
I'm technically not an
agent yet.
-Oh, my God.
What? What is it?
Charles. He kept files of everyone
in my family, including me and...
tapes of our
phone conversations, I think.
Edgar, is it
really you?
No, bitch,
it's your sister.
- What?
- And you're as good as dead to me now too.
What the...
- Is that... - Me, calling Polly
on Halloween years ago.
Let's just get right
to it, Daddy.
I want back in on the
family businesses.
I'm confused.
Don't you live in New York?
As it so happens, Chadwick and
I are looking for a weekend home,
possibly here in Riverdale.
I see.
Well, unfortunately for you, Hermosa
moved the rum business to Miami.
To
Toni Topaz years ago.
Without telling me?
It must have slipped my mind.
Like how you forgot to tell me
that you were marrying Chad.
By the way, if you're truly
interested in a weekend home,
might I suggest a property
in SoDale?
Oh, you mean Stepford
for bougie mobsters?
No, thanks. I'm good.
So you want me to give
you a job?
I just need some quick cash.
Kinda hoping you could hook me
up with something short-term.
You're lucky I'm even
willing to serve you, Jones.
What? Why? What
the hell is he doing here?
No way, Toni. No way.
Gathering some research for
your next book there, Jones?
Hang on. Are you guys
actually upset about my novel?
You made the Serpents look like
fools in it.
You mean the Vipers?
The Vipers were the good guys.
I didn't use your actual names.
You think people around here
couldn't figure out
who, what was that one
character's name, "Toothy" was?
Yeah, or Pop Eye?
You mocked our Serpent
traditions and codes,
and now you're asking for
our help?
Toni, guys.
Okay, I'll help.
I'll give you some advice.
Watch your back, Jones.
You've made a lot of enemies in
this town.
Principal Weatherbee,
as I wrote in my email, I'm here to
relaunch Riverdale High's RROTC program.
Archie, I meant to reply, but
it's been chaotic, to say the least.
What's up?
It's looking like
Riverdale High might not be
opening up its doors
next Monday.
Like everything else in this town, our
budget's been cut almost to nothing.
- Thanks to...
- Hiram Lodge.
Is there anything
I can do, sir?
Alice, you're on the PTA. Any word on
which way the school board's leaning?
The board has some serious doubts.
I mean we're a skeleton crew here.
Kevin, you're teaching what,
five classes?
Drama, Debate, Biology, Gym and
Sex Ed.
So are we
dead in the water?
Not yet. There are some members
of the board
that would like to see
the school stay open
if we can prove that we have
the personnel and resources
that are required,
which is questionable.
Well, the board will hear
arguments before the vote, right?
So we should all be there.
I'll speak, and in the meantime,
let's target the board members
who are still waffling and
work on them.
If we lose this vote,
we lose this school.
And that's another nail in
Riverdale's coffin.
*RIVERDALE (US)*
Season 05  Episode 05
Episode Title: "Chapter Eighty-One:
The Homecoming"
Aired on:
February 17, 2021
It's Tabitha, right?
Tabitha Tate?
It is. And you're
Jughead Jones.
Yeah, I am. Hey, I noticed that
you're looking for a new waiter.
I'm definitely interested.
Thanks. But this definitely
isn't the right job for you.
You don't even know me.
Also, you can't just sit here
all day using my internet.
You have to actually
order food, not just coffee.
And then you have to pay for
said food.
My grandfather did things
his way, and I do them mine.
And the first rule of my diner
is no running tabs.
Toni Topaz.
You lost, old man?
It's okay, guys. I got this.
Look, you can save your breath.
If you're here to bribe me
or threaten me into giving up
the fight to save Riverdale High...
- How many students do you have?
- A hundred or so.
What if I offer them all a scholarship to
Stonewall? They'd be getting a world-class
education at zero cost.
Except for the fact that you're
on the board at Stonewall Prep,
which means on some level, the
school must reflect your morals,
which I'm not okay with.
What if I told you that there was an open
counselor position with a corner office
and a big, fat paycheck?
Thanks, but no thanks.
So we're playing hardball, huh?
I guess so.
You know, it used to be Kevin
and I would sneak peeks
through that window,
hoping you were shirtless.
- And now you're spying on?
- Ghoulies.
They've turned the house into a
drug den.
Well, that tracks with everything
my mom says about this block.
I'm sorry, Arch.
It's only temporary.
Like Hiram Lodge trying to
close down Riverdale High.
I'm taking this town back, Betty,
building by building, if I have to.
Well, I can help.
I mean, I trained with the FBI.
I may just take you up on that, but
first, I need a little more information.
Where's the rest of
your team, Sheriff Keller?
You're looking at him.
Mayor Lodge cut my budget to
the bone.
I got no support staff and
no deputies.
And I'm covering the whole damn
county by myself.
Unless, of course, you count
Hiram's private security force.
They're connected to SoDale?
No, they work out of SoDale,
but they're corrupt as hell.
You should who's
running the force.
It's Reggie Mantle.
Well, maybe Reggie can help me
with my Ghoulie problem.
You call him,
he'll tip 'em off.
I mean, he's probably getting
some kind of a kickback from them.
You're not gonna get any help
from Reggie.
Well, not knowingly, anyway.
You may not have any deputies left,
but you still have their
old gear, right?
Kevlar vests? Batons? Now you
might want to dust them off, Tom.
I'm gonna do some recon first,
but after that, we're going in.
I've been thinking a lot about your offer,
Trudy. Is that job still on the table?
Hell yes, it is.
The Morris William Agency
would love to have you as a
sports agent.
But what about the
whole LA of it all?
Well, I've been wanting to give
the West Coast a try for a while now.
Let me make some arrangements
and I'll get back to you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
First class, of course.
Yes, of course, Miss Lodge.
But I'm having a little trouble
with the credit card on file.
Really?
That doesn't make sense.
Let me get back to you.
It's so weird, Chad.
I was doing some online
shopping, and
our American Excess card
was declined.
In fact, all of our
credit cards were declined.
Yeah, the same thing happened
to me.
But don't worry. I'll have it sorted
by the time you get back to New York.
Which is when, exactly?
The retirement party's in two
days, so probably the day after that.
Well, hurry.
- I miss you.
- I will. I miss you too.
Bye.
Miss Veronica.
Excuse me for interrupting.
No problem, Smithers.
What is it?
I've noticed the same car
parked out front for two days now,
a black sedan with
tinted windows.
I fear you're being watched
followed.
I wouldn't be surprised.
But is it a "Welcome back to
Riverdale" gift from my father
or a not-so-subtle message
from my overpossessive husband?
Either way, it's time to get creative
and bring an old friend out of mothballs.
How high are you willing
to jump for these?
Let's say twenty grand
for both.
I'll take thirty, but it has to
be in cash. Like, right now.
Also, you wouldn't by chance,
happen to have any
tasteful, discreet
ladylike revolvers tucked
away somewhere, would you?
You know, this being
Riverdale and all.
I might have something.
Oh, my god, Polly!
You gave me a heart attack.
You're the one
pointing a gun at me.
Sorry.
Old habits.
It's also 3:00 in the morning.
Well, you can go back to bed,
I'm not a burglar.
Hey, can I...
make you a cup of tea,
at least?
Polly, I want to apologize
to you.
I wasn't there for you on
the other side of the Farm
when you needed me most.
Also for prank calling you
that year on Halloween,
I really didn't mean
what I said.
Well, it's a deep cut, Betty.
Yeah, I know.
I haven't forgotten.
If it's not too late, I'd like for us
to be real sisters to each other.
How long you in town for?
Just a couple days.
But once I finish at the
Academy, I'll be home a lot more.
I'm surprised you're not
already running the FBI.
I don't know about that.
I've missed you, Betty.
Mom, the twins...
we've all missed you.
Good morning.
Good morning, honey.
How'd you sleep?
Well, I woke up
when Polly got home.
Does she usually stay out
that late?
She's working
at that nightclub,
The Roving Eye.
She waitresses
a few nights a week.
Is that a good thing?
She helps with the mortgage,
gets the twins
everything they need.
She's doing her best.
- We all are.
- Oh, I know.
I just remember
the Roving Eye can be
- sketchy.
- Okay, that's not fair, Elizabeth.
You don't get to pop in,
take a look around
and judge your sister.
Or me, for that matter.
Ooh.
Can you get that?
It might be Toni.
Did you see
the morning paper, Alice?
"Local school counselor runs
seedy bar and snake dances."
It's a hit piece.
Hiram Lodge is trying
to ruin my credibility
in the eyes of
the school board.
Well, I'll run damage control.
I'll call each board member
if I have to.
Good. In the meantime,
if Hiram Lodge is trying to drag
the Serpent Queen down to his level,
he's gonna get himself bit.
- Archie, what's up?
- Jug.
How's the Five Seasons?
Room service every meal?
Morning, noon and night.
Look, I got an idea
for Pop Tate's retirement gift,
but I was wondering if maybe
one of us should say something.
You know, give a speech
about Pop Tate.
And since you're
the world famous writer...
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd love that.
Okay, great. Thanks, Jug.
Reggie,
it's good to see you, bro.
I appreciate you coming out.
Duty calls, Mantle answers.
You having trouble
with your tenants, you said?
No, I'm having trouble
with the gang bangers
who are using my house
as a drug den, I said.
Well, let's see if there's
any merit to your claims.
It's messy, but I'm not
seeing any evidence
of drug paraphernalia.
Okay if we keep looking?
Nothing in here,
but stale cereal.
All right,
let's check upstairs.
I'm sorry, Andrews. I didn't
see any contraband anywhere.
Yeah.
You know, it's almost like
somebody tipped off the Ghoulies.
All right. Well, there's nothing
more for me to say or do.
But thanks
for your help, Reggie.
My pleasure, bro.
Feels strange to think
of not working at this place.
Well, on the bright side,
you won't have to deal
with annoying customers
like me anymore.
Now you know I had a lot worse
than you in here, Jughead.
And it all worked out,
didn't it?
I lived to see my retirement.
And you, you're
a big-time writer now.
- Always knew you'd make a good...
- I'm sorry, Pop.
Uh, those are debt collectors.
Hi there, gentlemen.
Counter or booth?
We're looking for someone.
Been known to hang around here.
Jughead Jones. Seen him?
No, I think I'd remember
a weird-ass name like that.
What do you want with him?
You just give us a call
if he comes in,
okay, sweetie?
Oh, I'll be sure
to do that, pumpkin.
Bye now.
Thank you.
It's not the greatest
first impression.
How much you need, Jug?
Maybe I can loan you some.
I've been saving up...
I'm low, but I'm not low enough
to take your retirement money.
I'll figure something out,
I always do.
Thanks for the interview.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Jones.
If you still want it,
the waiter job's available.
Okay.
In a couple days,
could you just call them
and vouch for me
and say I have a job?
I'll send them half my weekly
salary so they don't break my legs.
Yeah, I think I can do that.
Long time
no see, Ronnie.
Reginald, I know you've been
working for my father,
- so let's skip the pleasantries.
- Fair enough.
I need to buy a car.
Nothing flashy,
just in good shape
and with excellent gas mileage.
I'm paying cash.
Who you runnin' from?
Your husband?
Is that how you roll now?
I'm not running
from anyone, Reggie.
I'm taking the path
of least resistance,
and I'd rather not leave
a paper trail.
Now, will you sell me
a car or not?
If you're in trouble,
talk to your dad.
Like really, talk to him.
'Cause he'll help you.
Even now, still,
with whatever you need.
You're sure you saw Polly?
No doubt about it.
So she's hanging with
the Ghoulies, probably using.
Seems like that's a safe bet.
- I'm sorry, Betty.
- I'm not sorry.
I'm pissed.
So my question is,
when do we kick their asses?
All right, thanks
to Reggie Mantle,
I have enough intel
to sweep and clear the site.
How many Ghoulies
are in your house?
I counted a dozen
in these zones.
We hit 'em hard,
- we hit 'em fast.
- Nice.
It's been too long since the
Serpents rumbled with the Ghoulies.
Calm down, Sweet Pea.
I don't want
anyone dying today,
especially not my boyfriend.
Hopefully, they've
dropped their guard
and we can find
some narcotics in the house.
And like Kev said,
no one gets killed.
None of us and none of them.
Wouldn't mind breaking
a few bones, though.
Hell, yeah.
♪ Don't you ever feel sad ♪
♪ Lean on me... ♪
Okay. Three, two, one. Go.
What the hell?
Get 'em.
You good?
- Yeah, you?
- Yeah.
Jingle Jangle.
Just like the old days.
They've got a lab set up
in the bathroom.
Will that be enough to put
'em behind bars, Agent Cooper?
Yeah, Kev, that should do it.
The Roving Eye.
Hi, this is Polly.
I'm just calling to get
my schedule for the week.
Polly Cooper?
You haven't worked at the
Roving Eye for over a year.
Who is this?
Bad news.
Two more teachers have
defected to Stonewall Prep,
Ms. Crouton and Mr. Cedars.
Damn it, Ms. Crouton!
-That backstabbing...
We've got a bigger problem.
I had one of my girls
break into my Hiram's office
to see what dirt
we could use against him,
and she found his secret agenda
for the town hall meeting.
I love that it feels like we're
in an episode right now.
And besides deciding
about Riverdale High,
Hiram is also putting forth a
vote to unincorporate the town.
Based on the receipts, seems as
though he has enough people bribed
or terrorized
into passing the motion.
Wait, unincorporate the town,
what does that even mean?
It means that all the money
that the town gets from
the state for public services,
for maintenance,
for education, it goes away.
It means that Riverdale
as a town, ceases to exist.
So Hiram Lodge will finally
get what he's wanted for years...
- The death of Riverdale.
- So his precious SoDale can thrive.
But if that happens,
would we even be able
to keep the school open
with the board's support?
Technically, yes.
But it's going to make it
much, much harder.
So we need to fight harder.
Alice, I'm going to need you
to go on RIVW
and blow the whistle
on Hiram's plan.
He was trying to keep it secret
so no one would show up
and oppose him,
but we need the public there so
they could vote against Hiram's plan.
Okay, but what about
our teacher problem?
I think I can maybe help
with that.
Oh, do you know any
qualified teachers with degrees?
Because that's what it takes
to be a public school teacher.
What if Riverdale went private?
That way we could choose
who we wanted.
Yes, but we'd lose
all public funding.
Well, if the town
unincorporates,
we lose funding anyways.
We need an investor.
I think I might know someone.
Archie, if you have any
favors to call in, now is the time.
Reggie suggested
I come see you again.
I've been running around town
trying to vamp my way out of a problem,
when really I should be
facing it head-on.
With, maybe, your help.
Go on.
Chad is threatened
by my "alpha-ness."
Because of that, he can be
somewhat possessive and controlling.
He was having me followed,
but I just shot out
his goon's tires. So...
Ah, young love.
I remember those days.
I knew you'd relate.
Which is why I'd appreciate
you having a little chat with him,
as only you can, Daddykins.
Nothing too draconian,
just tell him to stop trying
to manage me
or track me when I leave town.
Why don't you
tell him yourself?
He's not taking my hints.
But I'm betting the Hiram Lodge
could be a lot more persuasive.
And then you
don't get your
little Barnard-educated
hands dirty, is that right?
Hmm.
So,
just to be clear, you're
officially asking me for my help?
Sure.
Yes, I am.
Well, in that case...
No.
Come again?
Remember you called me a dog
and you told me that
I needed to be taught a lesson?
It's about seven years ago.
You were cruel, Veronica.
Brutal,
when my body
was just a mass of bruises.
Well, now it's my turn
to teach you a lesson.
I warned you from the start
that no one
outside of this family
would understand
the Lodge ambition.
You made your bed.
You're gonna have to deal
with Chad yourself.
And if that means you have to to
crawl into the mud to do it, then so be it.
You're a Lodge, after all.
You never had any intention
of helping me, did you?
You just wanted to hear me beg.
Hmm. I assume you don't
need my help finding the exit?
But Polly, it's not every day
that Pop Tate retires.
- We can bring the twins.
- I told you I have to work.
Can't you take the night off?
Oh, my god. Mom,
I said get off my back!
Polly, give Mom a break.
It's fine. Polly has to work.
Actually, I'm not so sure
she does, Mom.
I know you don't
waitress at the Roving Eye
and that you've been
hanging out with the Ghoulies.
Elizabeth, stop it!
So how exactly are you
making all of this money
to help out with the mortgage
and support the twins?
Are you dealing? Tricking?
- Both?
- It's none of your business.
Actually, it is
because I care about you...
You don't live here.
You deserted us, okay?
Being a real sister doesn't
mean coming in for one day
and telling me how
to live my life,
especially when you
don't know anything about it.
Wait, Polly.
- Samm, how are ya?
- At the end of my rope.
Scribners wants pages,
or their money back.
Yeah, I know, I know.
-I'm working on something else.
What?
What have you been working on?
Actually...
Let me send it to you.
Let me know what you think.
Might be enough
to convince Scribners
that I'm not a one hit wonder.
Okay, I'm e-mailing you...
...right now.
I'm grateful
for your help, Betty.
Believe me, I'd rather be
dealing with this mess
than the one I made
at my own house.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
No!
I'm grateful
for your help, Betty.
Believe me, I'd rather be
dealing with this mess
than the one I made
at my own house.
I'm sorry to hear about that.
It's okay.
I'll be okay, I hope.
Hey, after Pop's party,
I thought you and me,
Jughead and Veronica
could hang out,
just the four of us.
We haven't done that yet.
No, yeah, that's a nice idea.
Let's do that.
Cool.
Hey, do you want some pizza?
It's the least I can do
to thank you for everything.
Yeah.
Pizza. Yeah, that sounds great.
I'm gonna take a shower first.
Oh, I sh...
I... me too.
- Do you wanna go first?
- Should I go home first?
♪ Say my name now ♪
♪ Don't make me wait now ♪
♪ I knew you weren't ready
For a girl like me ♪
♪ My honey's only sweet
If you can take the sting ♪
Betty, what just happened?
I don't know.
Something we've been wanting
to do since high school,
but never got around to.
Yeah,
sounds about right.
- Just to be clear, we're...
- Friends.
Just good old friends.
We're both single adults.
We're allowed to have fun
every now and then, right?
Yeah.
And it's okay
if we keep this to ourselves.
Yeah. Veronica's
a married woman,
and Jughead and I haven't dated
for seven years, so...
I think it's okay.
Okay, good.
What a gift!
Thank you, Archie.
Oh, it's from all of us, Pop.
It's a small token to show
how much you mean to us,
to Riverdale High,
to the whole town.
Yeah!
You know, I had to
drop out of school
to take over running
this place after my Pop,
the original Pop, passed away.
I never got to graduate.
This means the world to me.
Jug's gonna say a few words.
I think sometimes it can be
hard to put our faith in this town.
But I think Pop created
something really special here,
created a place for
the lost and wayward souls
of Riverdale to come to.
And I think, that's more than
jukebox or vinyl booths.
It's... like a lighthouse
in the storm.
And Pop himself,
he's many things.
He's a joker.
He's a soldier.
He's a cook.
He's
a really good listener.
He's also a father.
He's a son, and a grandfather.
And to many of us
and to me personally...
it's about the only reason
that I made it through.
You gave us a home, Pop.
Thank you.
To Pop Tate
who never let
the lights go dark.
Pop Tate!
Cheryl, I'm glad you came.
I wasn't sure you would,
after I
sent you my message.
It sounded rather dire,
plus, Pop always added
the drop of human kindness
to whatever my order was.
Have you considered my ask
to fund Riverdale
and the new teachers it needs?
It's the only thing that might,
might... save the school.
Look, I came here
to celebrate Pop,
not get caught up in small
town politics, Antoinette.
And I can barely afford
Thornhill's renovations
as it is.
Cheryl, I know you think
you're cursed,
and the sins of your family
are so great,
there's nothing you can do
to atone for them.
But you're wrong.
There's a war going on
in Riverdale for Riverdale.
We need you.
I'm sorry. I can't.
It will start as
something good,
and end up corrupted,
like everything I try to do.
If you won't do it
for the town...
would you do it for me?
Please?
If our love ever meant
anything to you,
help us.
If I gave you the money,
who would these
new teachers even be?
So you're really gonna
do this, huh?
Well...
Run the RROTC
out of your old high school?
If I get a chance to, yeah.
It's kinda why I wanted us
to sneak in here,
the four of us.
Hiram's trying to
shut this place down.
And he's pushing to
unincorporate the town,
which would wipe Riverdale
off the map.
My father is nothing,
if not consistent.
Oh, I think we can stop him,
- or at least slow him down.
- How?
We become teachers here.
Mm...
I know it sounds crazy,
but it's also a way to
keep the school going,
which means
if Hiram wins the vote,
we still have a defendable
position, this school.
And if we can save it,
we can give people at least
one more reason
to stay in Riverdale.
And in time,
we can bring this town
back to life.
Archie...
I'm married.
I have a life back in New York.
Yeah, and I have
a novel to write.
Veronica, plenty of people
commute to the city.
And Jug, you always said,
you do your best writing
in a booth at Pop's.
And it's not gonna be long...
a month or two,
just to give Weatherbee
enough time
to find permanent replacements.
I'm in.
Quantico can wait
a couple months,
and I need to be here right now
for my mom and Polly.
Thanks, Betty.
Jug?
I'd have to clear it
with my new job.
But why not?
I'd like to shape some
impressionable young minds.
I'm in, too.
I'll make it work with Chad.
And considering that
what's happening here
is all my dad's fault...
I need to give back
more than anyone.
And I didn't really wanna be
a sports agent anyway.
That's awesome, Veronica.
So... Bulldogs forever?
Bulldogs forever!
Before
the school board votes
on the fate of Riverdale High,
Toni Topaz has asked
to say a few words.
Good afternoon!
My name is Toni Topaz,
and I am a guidance counselor
at Riverdale High.
The point of a school board
is to make sure there's equity,
that kids of all ages,
from all different backgrounds
have equal access to education.
Well, with the help of one
very generous donor,
I'm happy to announce
that Riverdale High
will be able to do that
as a private school.
And unlike other
private schools,
Riverdale will be tuition-free.
And we're bolstering
our teaching staff
with notable alumnus
like Sergeant Archie Andrews,
FBI trainee and Yale graduate,
Betty Cooper,
businesswoman and Barnard grad,
Veronica Gekko
and acclaimed author,
Forsythe Jones III.
So spread the news
far and wide,
that Riverdale
and its children,
will not be at the mercy
of Hiram Lodge's
destructive whims.
Thank you.
That's very nice.
That was better than
Kendall Roy's speech
at the end of season two.
And now, I'd like to introduce
what I hope will be
my last motion as Mayor,
a proposition to unincorporate
the town of Riverdale.
All those opposed?
All those in favor?
Majority wins.
The township of Riverdale
is hereby dissolved.
What had taken
decades to build
was toppled in
the blink of an eye.
With the rap of a gavel,
Riverdale was no more.
And yet, life continues.
Samm, I was gonna call you.
Jones, Scribners loved
your story
about the old man.
- They what?
- Yeah.
They think it's your next book
and a slam dunk.
Apparently, there's,
there's a huge market right now
for tragic Americana,
dying community,
all of the miserable people
who live there,
you know, we'll call it
Elegy for a Small Town.
What do you think?
Ah...
No, I don't wanna
write about that.
You don't have a choice, Jones.
This is your ticket
under the literary grave
you dug for yourself.
Now you need to deliver.
Understood?
- Yeah, understood.
- Thank you.
Hey, Mom. I checked upstairs.
The twins are playing,
but Polly's still not home.
I'm worried.
You know your sister.
She gets angry, storms off.
God knows when she'll be back.
This is what happens.
But this one's
on you, Elizabeth.
I'm not
coming home just yet.
I'm gonna stay in Riverdale
a little bit longer, Chad.
Oh... why is that?
My alma mater, Riverdale High,
has fallen on hard times
and needs my help.
So, I'll be teaching there.
That's absurd.
No, no. What's absurd is
you freezing our credit cards,
especially since I made
most of the money
that's in our joint accounts.
Yeah.
So, if they're not unfrozen
in the next, say, 30 minutes,
I'll consider it
an act of aggression.
You know, like you
having me followed.
And the next time you see me,
it'll be on Wall Street,
on the floor,
when the markets open
Monday morning.
And this she wolf
will tear out your throat
in front of
all the other alpha dogs,
with zero hesitation.
Is that it, then?
- Are we done?
- You have 30 minutes
to reactivate our cards.
- Jug.
- Hey... Sorry, it's late.
Wondering if you could, uh...
use a roommate, now that you're
in this big, empty house
all by yourself.
Yeah, what happened to
the Five Seasons?
It's a little rich
for my blood.
Come in.
Hey, it's Polly.
Leave a message.
Polly, it's me again.
I wanted to say that I'm sorry
about what I said before.
I really had no right
to judge you,
especially after being gone
for so long.
It wasn't my place.
So, I wanna tell you that
I love you,
and that I'm here for you.
So just call me.
And I'll come find you,
wherever you are
or I'll see you
when you get home.
Just please, please, please,
come home.
Synchronized by srjanapala