I'm not gonna lie to you.
What awaits us is like nothing
we've ever faced.
But we will not be afraid.
- Do you know why?!
- 'Cause we're Bulldogs!
And Bulldogs never give up.
Men, your mission is to penetrate
the enemy's defenses,
retrieve your fallen brother
and return safely to base.
- Are we clear?
- Sir, yes, sir!
Let's do this!
Let's do this thing! Yeah!
Hut 32! Hut 32!
Reggie!
Let's go!
Let's go, Bulldogs, let's go!
- One more time!
- Let's go, Bulldogs, let's go!
When I say "bull," you say "dogs."
-Bull! Bull!
-Dogs! Dogs!
When I say "bull," you say "dogs."
-Bull! Bull!
-Dogs! Dogs!
Archie. Just a little help.
Archie!
Rise and shine, sergeant.
At ease, Andrews.
Ready to go home, son?
Home?
No, sir. No, I'm ready
to get back in the fight.
Sergeant, you've given
seven years to the Army.
Seven good years.
Every man in your unit
will attest to that.
They're alive because of you.
Not all of them, sir.
I've done some digging.
The RROTC program
at your old high school has been inactive.
I can't think of anyone
more qualified to bring it back.
All due respect, sir, I didn't join
the Army to be a desk jockey.
This is not a request, sergeant.
It's an order.
Sign your papers.
And by the by,
Corporal Jackson just transferred in.
"In the late summer of that year,
we lived in a house, in a village
that looked across the river
and the plain to the mountains.
In the bed of the river,
there were pebbles and boulders.
Dry and white in the sun.
And the water was clear
and swiftly moving.
And blue in the channels."
Look who cleans up respectable.
Give me a break.
How you feeling?
Actually, they got me
on so many pain meds, I'm good.
You? Going somewhere?
Yeah, home.
Riverdale.
Taylor wants me running the RROTC,
working enlistment.
Dude, that's messed up.
Jackson...
I just wanna tell you how sorry I am.
I really wish it was me in that bed.
I do too.
Sarge,
only reason I'm still breathing is
'cause of you.
Riverdale, huh?
Sounds nice.
This is my address.
When you get out of here, look me up.
Thanks, Sarge.
Will do.
Something wrong, soldier boy?
No. No, everything's fine.
If you're hungry, grab a stool.
Coffee's fresh.
Or if you want something stronger,
head downstairs.
Damn, Toni. It's good to see you.
Yeah. You too. You're all grown up.
I don't know about that.
-But you, you're, uh--
-Pregnant?
Yeah, I am.
Still a badass though.
Who's the dad? Can I ask?
You can.
But I'm not gonna answer you. It's--
It's a secret. Just for now.
Glad to see you're back in one piece.
Yeah. Yeah. No, I'm good.
-Who owns this place now?
-Me and the Serpents.
We all put our cash together
and bought it from Hiram Lodge.
A girl's gotta be creative
to survive in Riverdale these days.
Toni, the bus ride into town...
I can't explain it. It--
Everything felt or feels--
Different? Weird?
Yeah. To be honest,
it doesn't feel like Riverdale.
Yeah. Well, a lot has changed
since we graduated high school.
Yeah, no kidding.
For starters, where's Pop Tate?
Well, haven't you heard?
I thought that's why you came back.
No, I was reassigned here.
Toni, what happened to Pop Tate?
How are the nightmares, Betty?
Are they still keeping you up at night?
-No. I haven't had one in weeks.
-Good.
I'm more than ready to get back to work.
You are working, I thought.
I've been assigned to cold cases,
which means I'm filing all day.
Betty, you suffered severe trauma.
You were, and still are, only a trainee.
I caught serial killers
in high school, Dr. Starling.
Not like the Trash Bag Killer.
You'd be surprised.
I found something, Glen.
A connection.
There was a set of murders
in Odessa, Texas,
that stopped without the killer
getting caught, no explanation.
Months later, in Fargo, North Dakota,
there's a similar string of killings.
The victim profiles match,
as well as the methods used,
and, again, the killings stopped
for no reason.
You're thinking
we have a migrating serial killer?
Yes, Glen. I have a hunch.
Betty, stop.
You're supposed to be logging cold cases,
not sewing a crazy quilt out of them.
-The last time you followed a hunch...
-The Trash Bag Killer.
I get it. I messed up bigtime.
How am I supposed to make up for it
if I'm locked in a basement?
How am I supposed to redeem myself?
Listen, it's late.
How about we call it a day?
I can pick up some pizza and beer,
meet at my place.
I can't tonight. I have plans.
Oh. Do you?
I'm meeting friends for Thai.
Watch as the hunters
take off, chasing down their prey.
The gazelle, while badly wounded,
tries to run.
But after a long and meticulous stalk,
the hunters show no fear
as they chase down and kill their prey.
With their sharp teeth and claws,
they are bred for violence.
Where are you, kitty?
Any nightmares
this week, Betty?
No. Sleeping like a baby.
Unless you're willing to open up to me,
about what you went through
while you were held captive by TBK,
I won't be able to help you, Betty.
You know, when I got to TBK's lair...
Theresa was already dead.
It wouldn't have mattered if I'd gone
in there with a SWAT team.
He'd already killed her.
That's true.
But if you'd waited for backup,
you might not have been captured.
The Trash Bag Killer
might not have escaped.
Yeah.
That was a mistake.
I regret that.
You haven't said much
about your time in captivity.
Two weeks. Do you think about it a lot?
I think about
where TBK might be right now.
I think about the people he might--
He might hurt
because of me.
Sorry. I usually have it off.
I have to go home for a few days.
To Riverdale.
Okay. Yeah, sure.
While you're there,
pack up the FBI satellite office.
-Okay.
-Where you and your killer brother worked.
Yes, I will pack up the office.
No problem.
You have to watch my cat, Toffee.
Sure. Yeah, I can do that.
But I will need a key.
And since I won't be seeing you
for a few days,
do I get a kiss goodbye?
To one glorious year of marriage.
To you and me forever, babe.
Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary, Chadwick.
The only thing we're missing is
a little Chad
or a little Veronica running around.
I have a feeling this could be the year.
Don't you think?
Hopefully.
Maybe it's time to think about
cutting back your hours at Lacy's.
It's 2021, Chad. Haven't you heard?
Women can have it all now.
I just-- I don't want you
to be unduly stressed.
I'm not stressed.
I miss being
on the trading floor with you,
all that adrenaline,
the highs of a filthy huge sale,
talking smack with the guys.
They called me
"The She-Wolf of Wall Street."
Wrap this one up for me, will you, doll?
He wants to put a dime on it?
With that spread?
Vinny, Vinny, Vinny.
-Hold on.
-I'm not letting you walk out of here
with this pathetic excuse
for an apology gift.
You know you're insulting
your own merchandise?
Not at all. You're looking
at off-the-rack items
when you committed a specialty-
showcase haute-couture offense.
Trust me on this one, Vinny.
You gotta go big.
Or your wife will never forgive you.
-T Dubs! How are you?
-Good, Ronnie.
Your tip took my portfolio
through the roof.
-You got the magic touch.
-I call them like I see them.
Oh, did Kendra like the bracelet?
-So about Kendra...
-Oh, T. Not again.
One second.
- Hey, stud.
- How's work, babe?
Great. Katy and I are
just a little slammed.
-You wanna meet us for dinner later?
-That's funny.
'Cause I went to Lacy's to surprise you,
and I'm standing next to Katy.
Hi, Katy. You, however,
are nowhere to be seen.
Do you have any idea
how embarrassing it is
not even knowing where my wife is?
Forget that you've been lying to me.
What happened to Lacy's?
-We decided you would work--
-I tried Lacy's,
but I needed something
with a little more edge.
-We were working towards having a baby.
-Oh, my...
-Or did you forget that?
-No. No, Chad.
You forgot. You forgot who I am.
Who you married.
Remember how it was in the beginning?
Things were so good.
You and me working side by side.
We were the power couple to beat.
And the sex?
The sex was amazing.
What happened?
The accident.
Chad...
you use the accident as an excuse
to try and control me...
-You almost died.
-So did you!
You didn't want me
going back to Wall Street
because it was too stressful,
and I didn't wanna keep having
the same argument, so I agreed.
But that was a mistake.
That's not who I am.
And the sooner you accept that,
the better off you'll be.
Ready, everyone.
And action!
From small town to big city,
my killer instinct always
gets me what I want.
And cut!
Oh, Hermione, my one-take wonder.
-You're my angel, you know that?
-Thank you.
-I wish all the Housewives could be you.
-Well, I try.
Wow, Mom. You make it look so easy.
Oh, please. For women who've been
through what we've been through?
This is a cake walk, mija.
Which reminds me, Andy wants to know
when you'll join us for an episode or two.
Mom, no.
I can't put my life on display.
Especially not when it's in utter turmoil.
What's wrong?
You're married to a successful man
who gives you whatever you want.
You don't even have to work.
I love working, that's the problem.
Chad wants to turn me
into a baby-making machine.
You don't wanna have kids? Since when?
We have plenty of time for that.
Right now? I don't wanna be a mom.
No offense.
I wanna be the She-Wolf of Wall Street.
Let me ask you something.
When you and Chad worked together,
you outperformed him. Right?
Almost every week.
Okay. That's threatening
to an alpha like Chad.
He's vain. Like Hiram.
Every marriage has its ups and downs.
And as for believing that you have
plenty of time to start a family?
I think the accident might have
shown you that's not the case.
Let's try this again.
Happy anniversary.
I hate it when we fight.
Especially when it's my fault.
We never used to.
What happened?
The accident.
When our helicopter went down
on the way to Marcia's Vineyard...
I said a prayer, Veronica.
"If only one of us will survive,"
I thought...
"Please let it be my wife.
Let it be the woman
I wanna build a life with.
The woman I wanna be
the mother of my children."
We both survived, and all I could think
is now we can do those things.
I don't wanna waste a minute.
Does that make any sense to you at all?
It does.
But we're partners.
If I tell you that I wanna do something
and that I can handle
the stress of that thing...
you have to trust me, Chad.
I will.
Hold on.
You...
have got to open your gift first.
A new one comes out each year,
so you can start collecting them.
Well, Yvonne, I can see
that Josh was absolutely right about you.
-You are a woman of exquisite taste.
-Yes, I am.
I think I have just the thing.
We usually don't carry items
that are so high-end.
But I know a guy.
Best of all, a new Glamergé egg
is released each year.
You could start a collection.
Oh, my God.
It's perfect.
Archie?
Is everything okay?
What the hell, Jones?
- Hey, Samm Pansky, please.
- Hey.
-Hey.
-Jess, please.
Samm, it's me. Can we talk?
You'd rather talk to your agent
than your girlfriend? That's awesome.
Uh, can we meet for lunch
at that place you like?
Yeah. Great. I'll see you soon. Bye.
I have writer's block.
So do I. But I'm not punishing you for it.
Can we talk about this when I get back?
Samm, just give it to me straight.
Am I still in the running for
the staff writer job at The New Yorker?
No, kid. I'm sorry.
Just found out this morning.
You shouldn't be trying
to get a job as a reporter.
You're a fiction writer.
You should be working on your book.
How's that going, by the way?
I have writer's block.
You got a lousy work ethic
and a toxic relationship.
You drink too much.
So did Kerouac
and Hemmingway and Fitzgerald.
You want it straight?
Whatever heat you had coming off
of your first book is long gone.
A year ago, you could've had
a story published anywhere,
but now you're spoiled goods,
past your sell-by date.
Just need more time.
Scribner's called. They're threatening
to take back their advance.
-Did you hold them off?
-They wanna see pages!
It all comes down to, do you want a career
or be a one-hit wonder?
I can't hear you!
What?
Hey. Hey, Jess!
Did you see this?
Did--?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's going on?
-I'll stay with Hailey.
-Why?
-This isn't working anymore.
We haven't been working for a long time.
Also, debt collectors are pounding
at the door.
Wait. When?
Today. After you blew me off
to meet with your agent.
Okay. Jess, please, wait--
Don't do this. All I need is just--
I don't know what you need, Jones.
But I'm definitely not it.
Good luck with your book.
It's the only thing you care about anyway.
Excuse me. This is you, isn't it?
It is you. Oh, my God.
I was sitting there,
reading your book, then I look up,
and there you are.
"Forsythe Pendleton Jones III."
-My friends just call me Jughead.
-Cora.
I'm a grad student at NYU.
English, of course.
It's wonderful, by the way. Your book.
The Outcasts, which is an homage--
To The Outsiders by S.E. Hinton.
The love story between the Viper leader
and the homecoming queen?
It's just so...
Romantic?
Sexy. I was gonna say.
It's a very sexy book.
-Morning.
Where'd you get that?
In one of your drawers. Is that okay?
Yeah. Not a big deal.
There's coffee brewing.
Hey, I remember this.
New York Magazine, right?
-They called you the--
-"New Brat Pack," yeah.
"The wunderkinds."
"The season's best
and brightest young writers
with so much potential."
Full disclosure, I've read the article
like a hundred times.
It's how I knew that bar was--
Is your usual hangout.
What?
Okay, so I really am a fan
of your book. Honestly.
But I do have an ulterior motive.
Would you mind reading my novel?
It's 342 pages. If you like it,
maybe you could give it to your agent?
Okay. Hold on.
Last night was a ploy
to get me to read your book?
Forsythe Jones, open up!
Who are they?
-Debt collectors.
-Are they gonna hurt you?
Jones, we know you're in there.
We can see your shadow.
-We can hear you shuffling. Let's go.
-I'll read your book, I swear.
Could you just do me a favor?
- Not going anywhere, Jones.
- Please?
-Can I help you?
-Where's Forsythe Jones?
Uh, he's not here.
I'm apartment-sitting for him.
He got a job writing in L.A.,
just left this morning.
Can I give him a message for you?
Tell him to call us. It's urgent.
You got it.
Will do.
Thank you.
No problem. But I'll expect to hear
from you by the end of the week.
-The end of the week?
-About my novel?
And about giving it to your agent?
And if I don't hear from you,
I know who I'm gonna call.
This is nuts. I haven't
seen you guys in, what, six years?
It's been seven.
Wow. Lots of catching up to do.
I had a job lined up after graduation
with Riverdale Social Services,
but their offices got shut down.
Lucky for her, we needed
a counselor at Riverdale High.
You're looking at the new Mrs. Burble.
Wait. You're working
at Riverdale High too, Kev?
Yep. Drama teacher.
Got my BA from Carnegie Mellon
in Pittsburgh, where...
I graduated
from the University of Pittsburgh.
We stayed boyfriends, believe it or not.
And now we live together here.
With me. In an apartment
on Cloverfield Lane.
That's amazing.
Sweet Pea, what about you, bro?
Mostly held down the fort here
while these guys were gone.
Then, when Toni got back...
We decided to revive the Serpents.
Under my leadership.
I was crowned the Serpent Queen.
Well, I gotta say, this place is sick.
Pulls in a different crowd though.
What's with the truckers?
Serpents drive trucks,
including me and Fangs.
- Toni had the hookup.
- Impressive.
Hey, what about Cheryl?
It's cool, guys.
-After graduation, Cheryl and I broke up.
-RIP, Choni.
After I got back from Highsmith,
I went to check on her a couple times...
Hello, Antoinette.
Cheryl.
I thought we could talk.
I'm afraid now isn't a good time.
We're in the midst
of renovating Thornhill.
And I've got my painting to finish.
Perhaps another day?
Uh... Sure.
Cheryl, are you okay?
I'm perfectly fine.
Do I appear to be otherwise?
My mistake.
And? Did you go back?
I did. Not too long ago.
But this time,
I wasn't Thornhill's only visitor.
Hiram was there
with his right-hand man Reggie.
Reggie's working for Hiram Lodge?
I will never sell you
my maple groves, you vulgarian.
Nana and I plan to be buried
amongst those trees.
-We could make that happen.
-Goodbye, would-be usurper.
-Business with Hiram Lodge?
-No.
He comes by every other week,
offering to buy my maple groves, but...
I'm really glad to see you, Toni.
I wonder if you would do me
the honor of letting me paint you.
Cheryl, no one's seen you
in town in years.
Don't worry about me.
Nana and I are just fine.
-There's no reason for us to leave.
-Okay.
Well, don't you wanna hear about me?
Let's see.
You graduated with a 3.9 GPA.
You majored in social work
with a minor in photography.
And you did extensive charity
and social work.
Am I missing anything important?
Well, other than the fact
I'm having a baby.
I'd heard that, yes.
Congratulations, Toni.
I won't ask who the father is.
I'm completely out
and open with my family.
We've talked about you.
They recognize and acknowledge
everything you've done
to make up for your ancestors' sins.
I think that they'd approve
of us being together.
I'm so happy to hear that, Toni.
But it's not nearly enough.
The Blossom curse runs deep.
I'm doomed to a life of unhappiness.
You think you're cursed.
Beloved Tee-Tee...
are you familiar
with the Winchester House?
I've seen the movie with Helen Mirren.
Sarah Winchester came
from a family of rifle-makers.
Winchester rifles.
One by one,
family members suffered
painful, horrific fates.
Cursed by the deaths brought on
by their family's stock and trade, rifles.
Only Sarah survived.
So she started to build a house.
The Winchester House.
She believed that as long as it remained
under constant construction...
the curse couldn't consume her.
Is that why you're rebuilding Thornhill?
Toni...
I'm glad you're doing so well.
You deserve to be happy.
She didn't say another word.
She just painted me for 12 hours,
and when she was done, I left.
A week later, a package showed up,
and it was my portrait.
She didn't keep it as a reminder
of what you guys had?
I guess she didn't want it.
Well done, my dear.
It's exactly like the original.
It's a perfect copy.
You've learned well.
Now, the question is...
would you be able to replicate
the work of a master?
Like, say, um...
Rembrandt?
Toni, earlier you said
the town had changed.
I'll regret asking this,
but can you tell me how?
-I think it might be better to show you.
-Okay.
Where are you staying?
I'm crashing at the El Royale.
My mom's renting out our house.
Right.
The renters. Um...
-I'll pick you up at the gym.
-Okay. Thanks, Toni.
-You mind if I stay to make a few calls?
-Go for it.
- Archie?
- Toni.
I figured a steel gate would be enough
to keep this gym intact,
but this place is like a war zone.
Wait till you see the rest of the town.
Come on, my bike's out front.
This was the fire station,
remember?
It was a burnt-up shell
when I got back from college.
No one's trying to rebuild it?
The town's funding has been stripped by--
-Hiram Lodge.
-Bingo.
Not only is the fire department gone,
but the Sheriff's Office is down
to one man, Kevin's dad.
I don't understand. What are people doing?
Fending for themselves?
The town's lawless now.
This was Pickens Park.
Where is everybody?
Whoever could afford
to leave is long gone.
Only the people who are too poor
or too proud to move on are still here.
This was Sketch Alley.
Now we just call it what it is. Skid row.
Those dogs are everywhere. Packs of them.
Some are rabid.
This is the fifth bus stop
that's been trashed, melted.
Five of dozens.
There's always a fire
burning in Riverdale.
Why burn a bench for no reason?
Where will people sit for the bus?
That's the thing.
Buses don't pass by here anymore.
Sometimes, my trucks do,
but only if they have to
and rarely at night.
Bad things happen here after dark.
They call this the Lonely Highway.
Why destroy an entire town for nothing?
-What does Hiram Lodge have to gain?
-I'll show you.
-I don't get it. Where are the houses?
-This isn't SoDale proper.
This is where Hiram's building
a turnpike that leads to SoDale,
about half a mile due east.
He's catering to the rich folk
who can commute into the city.
So he's strangling Riverdale
to boost SoDale?
Their kids will go to SoDale High?
Stonewall Prep. That place is the same.
Except Hiram bought a seat on the board.
And so the nightmare continues.
There's one more place
I think you should see on the tour.
But you'll have to brace yourself.
The Ghoulies moved into my house?
-Wanna go in there and knock some heads?
-As a matter of fact, I do.
First things first, Toni.
Can we go back to Pop's?
-See if any of them actually came?
-Okay.
Archie. I heard you were back.
Pop. It's good to see you. I missed you.
Same. I missed all of you.
Archie. Toni.
Veronica.
-Betty. Jughead.
-Hi.
I'll leave you guys to it, then.
No. You're as much
a part of this as any of us.
Look, guys.
Toni gave me a tour
of Riverdale today and it's--
It's a hellscape.
I know I called you here
for Pop's retirement party...
but we have a much bigger agenda now.
Riverdale's dying.
We might be the only ones who can save it.
Are you sure
I can't convince you to stay, Squeaky?
I'll give you more shifts
if it would help.
I appreciate that, Tabitha,
but Riverdale is done with me.
And I am done with Riverdale.
Well, take care of yourself.
Will do.
Her name is Lynette Fields.
"Squeaky" to her friends,
not that she has many.
Mostly, she keeps to herself.
She came to Riverdale two years ago
for a fresh start that never happened.
Now she was 21, and it was time to go.
"Maybe things will be different
in San Francisco," she thought.
"Maybe I'll be happy there."
Unfortunately for Lynette,
she'll never make it to California.