From the start,
this story has been about a town.
And the people who lived in that town.
And the darkness that lived
in some of those people.
Clifford Blossom.
The Black Hood.
The Gargoyle King.
The Stonies.
Add to their ranks my sister, Jellybean,
who had been the voyeur-slash-auteur
making the videotapes that had been
disturbing our town for months.
This isn't your fault, Jug.
Just feels like it.
I was the one that convinced her
to move out here,
away from everything she ever knew.
Then I ignored her.
You were in the fight of your life
at Stonewall Prep.
JB's tough.
She'll get through this.
Hey. How is she?
I don't know. I really don't know.
Don't know if you're gonna like this.
I've been looking into child therapists.
I found one that has excellent references.
Well, I hope they're in Ohio
because that's where I'm taking Jellybean.
- Back to Toledo.
- Maybe you're right.
- She might need her mother.
- And her father.
What does that mean?
Alice...
she's my little girl.
If this isn't a cry for help,
I don't know what is.
Can we at least have a conversation
about this?
Yeah. Yeah, we will.
But first things first.
Jellybean finally told me where her
accomplices are hiding out most nights.
Jug? Mr. Jones? What's going on?
- We need you to open up your gym.
- Right now?
After we make a couple stops.
Gentlemen.
To what do I owe this late-night call?
You need to reinstate Tom Keller
as sheriff. Right now.
Asleep,
they almost looked innocent.
It's just messed up.
We survived the death of Jason,
the Black Hood and the Gargoyle King,
but I didn't even consider
how the fallout of all that
would affect the generation
coming up behind us,
including Jellybean.
Unless a meteorite strikes this town
in two days,
we'll have survived graduation.
But will they?
Are we just doomed to be haunted
by this town for the rest of our lives?
Dad. Dad.
What gives? Take the picture.
- The ceremony starts in ten minutes.
- What's taking so long?
I... I just can't believe we're here.
Archie, you're graduating.
Didn't think I'd live to see this day.
- It's not even graduation yet.
- No, but it is your last day.
- Well, we don't know that yet.
- I do. I have a really good feeling.
You've been applying yourself
so much lately.
- Yeah, we'll see. Love you, Mom.
- Love you.
As honorary chairperson and
de-facto queen of tonight's semi-formal,
this one's for you, Jay-Jay.
Presents? For moi?
It's been a while since
you've worn any pearls from me,
so maybe you'll wear them
for the last day of school.
Is it true what they say about your dad?
That he's the devil incarnate?
I stand by my father.
Please stop crying.
I was already picturing
Thanksgiving break.
You were gonna come home
on the train from Yale
and everyone would be here.
FP, Jughead, Jellybean.
You, Charles, Polly and the twins.
Yeah, that would have been nice.
- Now it's just gonna be me, alone.
- Hey.
Even if it's just you and me
having turkey meatloaf at Pop's,
I will be here for Thanksgiving, okay?
And Christmas. And whenever you need me.
I love you so much, Elizabeth.
I love you too, Mom.
Seventy-five years ago,
the first senior class of Riverdale High
buried a time capsule
just before they graduated.
Now, as our seniors prepare for their
own graduation, it's time to open it.
Ladies.
A copy of The Riverdale Register
from June 12th, 1945.
A copy of The Blue and Gold,
also from that same year.
This one's for Jughead. A Pop's menu
from when hamburgers only cost 15 cents.
A baseball card
of Ambrose "The Rocket" Pipps,
Riverdale's hometown hero.
Ew. A Red Circle comic book.
And lastly, a photo of four seniors,
and it's written here that this was taken
days before the boys headed off to war.
These will be on display for
closer inspection during graduation week.
And, fellow seniors,
enjoy your last day of high school!
Guys, doesn't this feel so weird?
Like, this is the last time
we'll all be hanging out together.
- Except for reunions.
- Yeah, and homecoming, Kev.
- It won't be the same.
- What exactly are we waiting for again?
Hot off the presses, chums.
Yearbooks.
- But Honey banned those, didn't he?
- Yes, but Honey is gone.
Brava.
Well done, ladies. This is amazing.
There's even an entire page
dedicated to the Serpents.
- And a shout-out to the Pretty Poisons.
- And the musicals.
Despite the fact that...
Archie Andrews and
Jughead Jones to the principal's office.
Archie Andrews and Jughead Jones
to the principal's office.
Dead teens walking.
- Guess who's graduating.
- Holy crap. You're a legend.
What about summer school?
No more pencils, no more books,
no more teachers' dirty looks.
- I'm happy for you, Jug.
- Archie.
He's ready for you.
It's gonna be all right.
- All right?
- Yeah.
I get no pleasure in telling you this,
Mr. Andrews,
but despite your efforts, you will not be
graduating with your classmates.
So, it's summer school for me.
Unfortunately,
that's not going to be enough.
You'll have to repeat your senior year.
I understand this is a shock.
But no one is going to hold this year
against you.
Yeah, I appreciate you saying that, sir.
- Can I still...?
- Walk with your classmates?
Of course you can.
In fact, though it's last-minute...
I was hoping you might record
the graduation song for us.
Yeah, I'd be happy to, sir.
What's the verdict?
Summer school? Yea, nay?
Summer school, as expected.
But Weatherbee's letting me walk
with you guys.
- I'll have my diploma by the end of June.
- That's a relief.
- You can enjoy the last day of school.
- Yeah. Definitely.
Working on your speech?
Well, don't keep me in suspense.
What's it about?
Considering I haven't written any of it,
I guess you'll just have to wait and see.
Well, I'm sure you'll crack it.
You always do.
Ronnie. What's, uh...? What's going on?
I was cleaning out my room,
and I came across some choice items
that you've left
over the past three years.
And I wanted to give it back to you.
Also, despite everything
that's happened between us...
I wanted to be with you tonight.
If only for one last time.
- Is that crazy?
- No.
Not at all.
In fact, I can't think of anything
I want more in this moment.
At school yesterday...
I spied you looking at that picture
from the time capsule.
What gives?
I was just wondering what...
What must have been going
through their minds.
Most of their classmates were heading
to college or in their family businesses.
These guys were going out to fight a war.
You're not getting any crazy ideas,
are you?
Not unless you consider
summer school crazy.
Hey, I was thinking, uh,
after graduation, I...
- I'd go to Toledo with you and Jellybean.
- No. Uh-uh.
Well, you said it yourself,
family is what's most important right now.
You're the first Jones man
to get into college. You're going.
And you're old enough to be on your own.
You understand?
Right, boy?
And this, Nana, has been my locker
since the end of sophomore year.
Hmm. It's a lot nicer than the one you had
at Southside High.
But all your things are still in it.
I know.
I'll clean it out over the weekend.
A lot of special memories
with a lot of special people.
Including my girlfriend.
We're so incredibly proud of you, Toni.
The whole family is.
You've honored the Topaz name.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay, Mom.
I'm just missing Dad.
I wish he was here.
He's here, honey. He's here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it imbues me with such pride and joy
to invite to the stage
the senior class's valedictorian,
Miss Elizabeth Cooper.
Hi.
I admit, I've been struggling
with what I wanted to say today.
High school is supposed to be
this amazing, safe time.
But our years were co-opted
with heartache and drama.
And even death.
It's not fair that so many
of our classmates aren't here
to walk with us today.
It's not right
that some of our parents aren't here
to watch those of us who are.
Those younger than us
have known no Riverdale
other than the one steeped in violence.
Our class is lucky enough to remember
a time before the era of tragedy.
When this was just a small...
sleepy, slightly boring town.
That's the Riverdale I wish upon
the generation coming up behind us.
And the one I want us, our class,
to remember as we head into the future.
So, please...
stay young...
for as long as you can.
Stay innocent for as long as possible.
Even if it's only for one more moment.
Thank you.
- Cheryl. Cheryl.
- Mother?
What's going on?
Well, I wasn't about to miss
my only child's graduation,
so I snuck in the back at the last minute.
Also, I wanted to tell you
about a decision that I've made.
With you being a grown woman now, I'm
gonna turn myself over to the authorities.
To pay for...
Well, some of the crimes I've committed.
What?
- But, Mumzie, you're a hothouse flower.
- I've spoken to Hiram Lodge.
He's promised to take proper care of me
in his private jail.
And with good behavior,
I may even be out in time to see you
graduate from Highsmith College.
Oh, Mumzie. If that's even happening.
Nightmare child, what do you mean?
Gotta hit the road
if we wanna make it by sundown.
Dad.
Boy, I know you would've given up Iowa
for Jellybean,
and I promise you,
she's gonna know it too, but...
But you going to college,
being a success...
that's good for us Joneses.
I love you.
I love you too, Jug.
So is this it?
The end of our story?
God, I hope not.
But you know, for now, I...
I know.
I know what you have to do.
And I love you for it.
- It's not too late, is it?
- No, it's not too late.
We're happy to discuss options with you,
but this isn't a decision
to be taken lightly.
I understand.
I'd love to hear what you have to say.
Hey, Pop.
Can I grab a clean menu?
It's for something Betty has planned.
I've been doing this a long time.
It's never easy watching you kids
head off to college.
Which reminds me, Pop,
the paperwork's coming your way,
but the gist of it is...
I'm signing over full ownership
of Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe diner to you.
Veronica.
I don't know what to say,
except... thank you.
You know, it's funny.
When I first came to Riverdale...
I never imagined I would call it home.
Ever.
And then I came here,
to Pop's.
And that's exactly what it felt like.
Home.
Did everyone bring an item?
I am putting in today's copy
of The Riverdale Register
and The Blue and Gold.
My last edition as editor-in-chief.
And a bobby pin, in case anyone needs it.
I'm putting in a football
signed by all of the Bulldogs.
Long may they roar.
I am putting in a Pop's menu
and a La Bonne Nuit matchbook.
I am putting in the programs
from my musicals,
as well as a pair of Josie's cat ears.
I wish she was here with us.
Oh, HBIC shirt,
I found no one deserving of you.
Therefore, toodles!
The Pretty Poisons were fun,
but, uh, I'm gonna keep my Serpent jacket.
'Cause I'll always be one at heart.
Well, it's getting pretty full
in there, but...
Finally.
I'm putting in a guitar pick
and a hammer from my dad's toolbox.
You guys are the best friends
anyone could ask for.
Uh-oh.
Sounds like another vow is coming on.
So let's make a vow. Really.
The four of us right now.
That in one year,
no matter what's going on in our lives,
we'll meet back at Pop's.
One year from today.
And every year after that. Deal?
Deal.
Good.
Okay.
There's... There's something else.
You're very dramatique
this evening, Archie.
I'm joining the Army.
I know it's sudden.
But I enlisted and I leave
for basic training in the morning.
It's kind of the same plan I had
going to the Naval Academy.
Hardly. In fact,
it's nothing like the Naval Academy.
I can get my degree without repeating
senior year, which I was gonna have to do.
I'd be set up for college.
Look, guys.
For the first time in a long time...
I don't feel scared or uncertain
about my future.
Well, if that's what you feel is
the right thing for you, Arch, then...
Sorry, but no.
I won't sit here and support this.
Wait. Ronnie, wait, wait. Ronnie.
- You know there's a war going on, right?
- Of course.
You don't have a plan.
And I get that. That's scary. But this?
This is just straight-up lunacy, Archie.
And I won't indulge it.
Ronnie.
Toni.
I have something to tell you,
and it's not going to be easy.
I'm not going to Highsmith College.
I'm confused.
Because it doesn't have cheerleading?
That and...
- it just doesn't feel right anymore.
- If you don't go, I'm not going.
No. You must.
You will thrive there.
But I have to fix things here.
What are you talking about? What things?
The Blossom family name conjures
a horror show in this town,
and rightfully so.
But now that I have control
of the maple factory and groves,
I have a chance to lift up this town
and rehabilitate our family legacy.
But I need to be here...
where the damage was done.
If this is about my nana,
you need to get that out of your mind.
She's starting to come around.
She asked me if we were gonna
be living in the same dorm room
so she could send us care packages.
That's progress, right?
Toni.
You know I love you
with every ounce of my soul.
But I don't want you to have to choose
between your family and me.
Perhaps if I'm successful,
you won't have to.
And we can be together
with their full blessing.
But...
in the meantime...
Don't say it.
I don't wanna hear you say it.
Then you never shall.
How's Veronica doing?
Confused,
angry, worried.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Don't you think it's crazy that she had
no idea what Archie was planning to do?
Maybe it's me, but it seems like the two
of them have been squirrely since prom.
Did you notice that? I just don't know
what the problem could be.
What could have got them derailed?
I think I may know what happened, Jug.
- I have to tell you something.
- Oh, no.
During Hedwig...
Archie and I kissed.
Once. Only once, I swear.
I'm guessing Archie told Veronica,
that's why they've been acting so weird.
I didn't tell you, Jug, and I'm so sorry.
I should have told you
when it happened. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
All right. I better get going
if I'm gonna get Archie to the bus stop.
Yeah, I should go see
and be with Veronica.
Hey, when I get back, can we...
talk about us?
Yeah. Of course.
I love you, Jug.
I love you too, Betty.
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, just about.
Hey, come here.
You be a good boy, okay?
Look after Mom.
I love you, buddy.
- I love you, Mom.
- I love you.
Thank you for everything.
Vee.
I have to apologize to you
about something.
I know, Bee.
And I'm not mad at you.
I can't be. Not today.
I'm too upset.
I'm sorry.
Listen, Jug.
Before I leave,
I have to tell you something.
Archie, I know.
About you and Betty? She told me.
It's okay.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, seriously.
I know neither of you did it
to hurt me or Veronica.
And maybe a little normal
high-school angst is good for us.
So, yeah. We're okay.
Seriously.
We always will be.
I feel so responsible for what's
happening between you and Archie.
It's not that, Betty. It's not.
It's how it's all ending.
So sudden and unresolved.
I wish I had said goodbye to him.
You know?
More than anything, I wish...
I wish I had hugged him one more time.
Let's do that. His bus may not have left.
I know how we're gonna get there.
- Guys.
- Jughead, where's Archie?
- The bus left a minute ago. He's gone.
- Well, not yet he's not. Get in.
No. Just I love you, Ronnie.
I love you, Archie!
I love you too, Ronnie.
Sir, can you pull the bus over? Please.
It's my girl and my friends.
You stay safe, Archie Andrews. I mean it.
I will.
I love you.
Later, bro.
Don't "bro" me.
- See you in a year, Arch.
- See you in a year, Betty.
We'll rebuild here, Nana.
And not just our ancestral mansion,
Thornhill,
which I burned down in my youth,
but the Blossom name and legacy.
Once Archie had left,
it was as if the glue that held our group
together had begun to dissolve.
First to go was Veronica.
Guys, I'm gonna take a little time off
before school starts.
Spend the summer with my mom
and Andy Cohen in the Hamptons.
Your mom will love that.
She was gone within a week.
As for Betty and me, things had changed.
We never talked about her and Archie,
about the growing distance between us.
Not even when she announced...
I'm going to New Haven early.
My mom and I are taking a road trip
before she drops me off.
You guys deserve the R & R.
What's gonna happen to us?
I still love you.
I'll always love you.
I'll always love you too.
But for now, you should focus on Yale.
And I'll focus on Iowa.
After Betty left, it didn't feel right
to keep living at the Cooper's anymore.
So I moved into Archie's house,
which was empty for the time being,
waiting to be sold.
Then they cut the electricity.
Which was fine, but then the gas was
shut down and with it the hot water.
So I sought refuge in a place
I knew all too well.
Honey? I'm home!
I stayed there until August,
when it was finally time to go where
no Jones man had gone before, college.
But I couldn't leave town
without one last burger.
I'm gonna miss seeing you
in here every day.
I'm gonna miss you too, Pop.
As I paid the check and headed
towards my future, I wondered,
would we keep the vow that we made?
To return to our booth at Pop's
one year later?
Only time would tell.
Another refill, Jug?
Uh... No, I'm good.
I think it's time I take off.
I'm sorry they didn't make it.
They're probably just busy.
Yeah, probably.
It would be six years
before I saw my friends again.
We'd be different people, each of us.
Brought together by, of course,
a new crisis and mystery.
But that's another story
for another day.