A lot can happen in seven years.
But in Riverdale,
the more things change...
Oh, that was... That was hot, yeah.
...the more they stay exactly the same.
Hey. I'm Rick.
- What's your name?
- Come on. No names.
- See you.
- Yeah.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hey, babe. How was the store?
I had to go to a couple different places,
but I got regular milk,
oat milk, almond milk
- and two varieties of sugary cereals.
- You're the best, Kev.
- Sorry about all these crazy cravings.
- It's all good.
- Are you okay?
- Totally.
You're not nervous
about the big announcements?
Not at all. Why would I be?
- Okay, you ready?
- I'm ready.
Wow. I was so not ready.
Yeah, what do you think?
I think you've come a long way
from when you were 8
and said you wanted to be a firefighter.
Thanks for coming to meet us,
Dr. Whitley.
You mentioned having a specimen
that needed examining. May I see it?
It's the damnedest thing, doc.
Someone stole it.
I was babysitting it and then...
Suddenly,
this blinding light appeared in the sky.
Last thing I remember
I was looking up at it,
but then I lost several hours.
- Next thing I knew, the Mothman mummy...
- The specimen.
The specimen was gone.
Mr. Jones, I'm an anthropologist
with an interest
in extraterrestrial phenomena,
not a psychologist.
But in the majority of cases
like you're describing,
when a person claims
to have had a close encounter,
they are, in fact,
often repressing a traumatic experience.
You said in the majority of cases.
What about the other ones?
In the other cases,
I believe they're telling the truth.
If you'd like, I can perhaps help you
determine what you're dealing with here,
truth or repression.
- There's a support group I lead...
- We're sorry for making you drive
from your university,
but I don't need a support group.
If I am repressing something,
I think I'd prefer to keep it repressed.
Should you decide otherwise,
here's my card.
Just in case. You take care.
Juniper, Dagwood,
this artwork is so beautiful.
Your mom's gonna love this
when she gets home.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Mom.
Hey, Mr. Keller. Everything okay?
Okay. I'll be right there.
What is it?
- They found another body in Swedlow Swamp.
- Another one?
But is it Polly?
No.
Tom says it looks like the other bodies,
like it's been there for a while.
- Call me the second you know?
- Okay. I love you.
Love you too.
- Your lats are looking huge.
- Thanks. Trying to keep up with you.
Fangs, we should talk about stuff.
Us. Before things get crazy.
I know we've been
in an open relationship and...
That was when I was on the road, mostly.
But now things are different. I get it.
And I wanna be monogamous too.
Also, I'm seeing
what we're about to do as...
As a fresh start for the both of us.
A clean slate.
And I hope you do too.
Hey, Mom. It's not her. It's not Polly.
Are you sure?
A hundred percent.
Dr. Curdle says
the remains are over a year old.
Oh, thank God.
Your sister's still out there.
It means she's still alive.
Don't you think?
Hopefully.
I love you, Mom.
Hang in there, okay?
Not now, Chad.
Clear the decks, Smithers.
We're starting our remodel ASAP.
Oh, very good, Ms. Veronica.
I can assemble
a list of contractors for you.
Oh, that won't be necessary.
I already hired my contractor.
What do you wanna have done
to your apartment?
One word, demolition.
I want it all torn out, down to the studs.
That's a big job.
But, yeah, I think my buddy Eric
would be up for helping out.
- What's your timeline?
- I want it done yesterday.
I need changes in my life, Archie.
Big changes.
How big are we talking about?
That's very cool.
What is this, plans for your
very own Shangri-la, Veronica?
- It'll be the new and improved Pembrooke.
- Looks swanky, Vee.
Hey.
The Four Musketeers.
Pray tell, whyfor have we been summoned?
Hey, guys. Um, thanks for gathering
on such short notice.
Um, Fangs and I have an announcement.
- We're engaged.
- Oh, my God!
That's such good news.
- But wait, there is more.
- Yeah, we're having a baby.
Guys, that's great.
Wait, there's still more.
We're having the baby.
With me. I'm having our baby.
We're planning on raising
this child together, the three of us.
As one big, happy, non-traditional family.
What in the actual...?
And they call me Cherry Bombshell.
Cheryl. Good.
I wanted to talk to you about
stepping back from the Vixens.
Did it not occur to you
to give me any advance warning
about your offspring's lineage?
Well, to be honest, Cheryl,
I wanted to tell you.
Not just as my co-captain
but as my friend.
But, based on your recent behavior,
I didn't even know
if we had that relationship anymore.
Did this idea originate with Kevin or...?
Me, Cheryl.
When I was a junior in Highsmith College,
I found out that I have
a medical condition
that makes it hard for me
to get pregnant the older I am.
Toni, I had no idea.
I'm so sorry.
Anyways, the doctors said
that if I really wanna have kids,
I need to while I'm young.
Okay.
But Kevin and Fangs?
Fangs is like family to me.
We got initiated
into the Serpents together.
And when Fangs and Kevin
started talking about adoption
or looking for a surrogate mother,
I volunteered.
Splendid. You've got an insta-family
while I'm withering away at Thornhill.
I'm having a baby with Kevin and Fangs.
But I still care about you deeply, and...
if you want, maybe we can still try
and make this work.
I don't see how that's possible anymore.
But congratulations.
I'm very happy for you.
It's funny, I always figured
the first baby would be
yours and Jughead's
or Archie and Veronica's.
How times change, I guess.
Yeah, you're not kidding.
That sounded loaded. What gives?
You have to keep it a secret, okay?
Oh, God. Don't tell me you and Jughead
are getting back together.
No. It's...
It's me and Archie.
We've been doing this
"casual friends with benefits" thing.
- Shut the front door.
- Yeah. It's an...
It's an escape, and we're in this bubble
and I don't want it to burst.
I also don't wanna get in
too deep with him.
Why?
Because Archie's this lit window
in the dark.
And I don't want that light
to ever go out.
The importance of sight.
The way we see the world
or how we interpret what happens
is one of the biggest themes
in Slaughterhouse-Five.
Now, Billy has "discovered" the truth.
And that's why he can, at any one point,
be at his daughter's wedding,
be fighting the Germans,
or he can be millions of light-years away
as a captive in some alien zoo.
Billy has "achieved" true sight.
Or at least that's one interpretation.
Mr. Jones?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm sorry.
- What was I saying?
- That there was another interpretation.
Yes.
That Billy is crazy.
Hi, Dr. Whitley?
Yeah, it's Jughead Jones.
Sorry to bother you.
Upon further consideration, I might
be interested in joining that group.
Making progress?
Or are you too distracted by my beauty?
I'm painting you
as Diana with Actaeon, the stag.
You'll find it satisfactory.
You have a unique talent.
I recognized it right away.
I had to have a Cheryl Blossom.
Once this painting is finished,
will you leave me in peace?
I haven't decided yet.
Oh, who cares?
After the dagger
my beloved Toni stuck in my heart,
- what does anything else matter?
- Go on.
She lured me out of the house,
where I feel safe,
just to torture me with her happiness.
It's cruel. Don't you think?
As an outsider,
it seems to me that fate has put
an obstacle before you.
This Toni person's happiness.
And you must either rise above it or...
Throw a little chaos at it.
Katy Keene. How are you, girl?
Oh, my God, girl, I am reeling.
So I'm having lunch
with Francois in the Lacy's café
and who strolls in with the heiress
to the Spiffany's fortune?
Chad. Your Chad.
What the hell is going on with you two?
Well, clearly,
he's trying to make me jealous.
Totally. Which means I'm about
to pour hot coffee into his lap.
Perfect.
And I, Katy Keene,
will be fighting fire with fire.
Wow. You boys made some real progress.
Well done.
Oh, you know what we should do?
Document our reno journey.
Let me get between you two.
Come on.
Perfection.
Now flex for my followers.
Is yours from Cheryl too?
She wants us to gather
at the Whyte Wyrm for drinks.
Well, shall we, boys? I'm buying.
I thought
you had a thing going with Betty.
That's just a casual thing.
Okay, but what about Veronica?
The looks, the smiles, the banter...
Dude, she's married, Jackson.
Sarge juggling two ladies...
Cheryl, what's this about?
I wanted to apologize
for being so cuckoo to you earlier.
- Will you let me have a do-over?
- Of course, Cheryl.
Your support means the world to me.
So...
will you let me host a modest celebration
for you, Kevin and Fangs?
Okay. Sure.
Amaze.
Hear ye, hear ye,
fellow friends and fiends.
Now that everyone is swan-diving
into sad adulthood
with babies and marriages
and arthritis, et cetera,
I'm throwing a party.
One last hurrah to celebrate
our wild, misspent youth.
One final chance to recall
our reckless teenage selves.
Who could forget my iconic
spin-the-bottle parties of yore?
Aren't we a little old for that?
Which is why this little fete
will be a key party.
You heard me right.
A classic American and oh-so-adult round
of sexual switcheroo.
We'll draw keys, pair off,
and if the spirit moves you,
you are strongly encouraged to act on any
and all animal impulses.
I'm texting you the "deets" now,
but bring keys for my bowl
and your well-oiled libidos.
Oh, my God.
Polly. When did you get back?
Does Mom even know...?
- No, you can't be here. He'll find you.
- What? Who will?
- TBK.
- What?
You shouldn't have gone in alone.
Oh, my God.
Good thing your mom still leaves
that spare key under the gnome.
Beats climbing the trellis.
What's wrong?
Just a nightmare.
I don't wanna talk about it.
I just wanna forget. Okay?
Yeah.
Whatever you want.
Nice spread, sarge.
And you're up before me. Not bad.
I haven't gone to bed yet.
I was over at Betty's.
Shut up, Jackson.
I thought it was gonna be a booty call,
which I was more than fine with...
but this time it felt different.
It didn't feel great.
And if I'm being completely honest...
you were right.
About me and Veronica.
I would never do anything about it...
but there's something still there.
So about Cheryl's party, I was thinking,
it's one last night
of carefree abandon, right?
What if you brought one of your
hot trucker beaus to spice things up?
You must have a regular hookup, right?
Yeah. Maybe.
But why would I do that?
We just closed our relationship,
like, yesterday.
I've always been curious about
the company you keep on the road
and you've never brought
a friend home, per our rules.
Yeah, exactly.
So why now?
- What's going on with you?
- Nothing.
But before we become husbands and fathers,
let's get every horndog impulse
out of our systems, once and for all.
No strings, no guilt.
No secrets.
Betty. Oh, thank God.
Your sister. She called. She's alive.
What? When? Are you sure it was Polly?
Of course I'm sure. I know the sound
of my own daughter's voice.
- What did she say? Walk me through it.
- Okay.
Um, the phone rang. The landline.
I picked up, and it was Polly.
She was hysterical.
She was talking a mile a minute.
Um, I tried to keep her on the phone,
but she was scared.
Mom, are you sure
it wasn't just some crank?
Yes!
She was scared.
Uh, she couldn't see anything.
She was being kept somewhere.
It was dark. Everything was cold
and smooth, like metal.
It sounded like a spaceship.
In most missing persons cases,
after two days,
the chances of a victim being
found alive are almost nothing, Mom.
Polly's been gone for weeks.
No. You know what? No.
My daughter is alive!
She called, and she's calling back.
The lights were as bright as the sun,
hovering a few hundred feet above me.
That was the last thing I remember.
Woke up six hours later
by the side of the Lost Highway.
- No idea how I got there.
- Thanks for sharing, Bill.
Mr. Jones, didn't you have an experience
similar to the one described?
Uh, I was working late.
The diner was empty. Jukebox was playing.
And then things just kind of got crazy.
There were these lights
from outside the window.
They were so bright that I should
have been blinded, but then I...
Were you missing time too?
Yeah, I mean, I probably just fell asleep.
Blackouts are fairly common
during supposed encounters
with extraterrestrials.
Have you
ever blacked out before?
Jughead. You okay?
Uh, no, sorry. This was a mistake. Sorry.
Jughead!
I've been through enough in my life
to know when someone hits a nerve.
About something real.
I have blacked out. I didn't wanna talk
about it in front of strangers.
Okay.
Well, it's just me now.
When did it happen?
I was in New York City.
I was going pretty hard.
I was drinking a lot and partying
and doing drugs and jingle-jangle.
Some harder stuff.
And I, uh...
I just did some things
I don't even remember.
I lost a lot of time.
Look, maybe you shouldn't go
to Cheryl's tonight.
We could go to a movie instead or,
I don't know, hang out.
No, I think a night at Cheryl's house
with some wanton debauchery
is what I need
to forget about all this alien crap.
Veronica Lodge, spreading plaster...
Since my jewelry store remains
closed tragically, I'm happy to help.
Where's Eric?
He ran down to the VA
to collect his disability.
Seems like a nice guy.
How'd he lose his leg?
On our last mission.
You'll never hear him complain.
The strong and silent type.
Sounds like somebody
I used to know back in the day.
So how about Kevin
and Fangs and Toni's announcement?
Yeah.
Sort of makes you take stock
of your own life, doesn't it?
I'm starting to realize
all the things I'm missing in my life.
And am I crazy or...
have you been feeling the same way too?
I'm not sure what I'm feeling.
Things are changing. Fast.
What happens
if we get matched at the key party?
I honestly don't know. Is Chad coming?
Yes, he is, as a matter of fact.
He should be on the train right now.
Good. I think that's a good thing.
Yeah, me too.
Keys, please.
- Where's the booze?
- Bar's in the gallery.
Hi.
Oh, good. Reginald, you got my message.
Welcome.
Where's Fangs?
Um, he is a bringing a date, I guess.
- One of his "cazh" hookups.
- Okay.
- It was my idea.
- Okay, why?
I don't know.
Maybe because I wanted to see
what he's giving up for me.
To get married.
Or maybe because I wanted to see if he'd
go through with it and bring someone.
Or maybe because I am
an emotional masochist.
Oh, Kev.
Archie Andrews.
Chad Gekko.
You made it.
Tell me, bro to bro,
how is it that in a Podunk town
like Riverdale,
all the females are so...
smoking hot?
Oh, my God.
Fangs' date is my cruising crush.
- Hey, Betty.
- Hi, Fangs.
Betty, Kevin,
this is my friend Rick. We, uh...
We both drive rigs along the same route.
- It's nice to meet you. Both.
- Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Anyone care for a drink?
I'm buying.
- I see we have a surprise guest.
- Yes.
Seems like your ex's rather handsome
baby-daddy's brought a friend.
Oh, well. If he's collateral damage,
- then so be it.
- Hm.
Shall we gather everyone?
It's time for some party games.
You're here.
You came.
Which means you all feel it.
The impending crush of true adulthood.
Our 30s.
And soon after...
mortality.
The big sleep.
Tonight's key party, then,
is a bold rejection of death.
Since none of us are much for foreplay,
let's get into it. Shall we?
Some house rules, first and foremost,
whatever happens tonight
must be 100% consensual.
And because we are all a progressive,
fluid-inclusive group,
there will be no redrawing of keys.
But the main rule...
is you're allowed to do anything
you and your partner desire.
No one can hold you accountable.
It's a free pass to do anything
you've ever wanted.
Ever.
Are we clear? Perf.
Who wants to go first?
Minerva, the bowl.
I never like to be the second person
to do anything, so...
You know what they say,
everyone's a winner in a bull market.
No.
Not with your ex.
Chadwick, don't be rude.
Those are the rules, okay?
Get your hands off her.
Excuse me?
- She's my wife.
- Exactly.
- Why don't you show her some respect?
- We're not gonna do this.
I'm not gonna be some passive heroine
to be fought over by two Tarzans.
Oh, look. I got Chad's key.
Come on. We're leaving now.
Veto. That's breaking the rules.
Call my lawyer, Cheryl. Are you ready?
Fine. Always good to knock
a few pieces off the chessboard.
And married people are supremely boring.
- Who's next?
- I'll go.
I'll take him home.
No one else is leaving
without picking a key.
I don't care how inebriated Jughead is,
he has to draw.
No, no. I want to. Let me do it.
Ah. Those are my keys.
I guess it's meant to be.
Now can I take him home?
Whatever. Get this American Pickle
the hell out of my sight.
- Charming as ever, Cheryl.
- Come on, Jones. Party's over.
You're next, soldier boy.
- You mean me?
- Get up here, G.I. Jackson.
Do your duty.
Those are mine.
- How good are you at following orders?
- No one better.
Before the pickings get too slim...
- Toni?
- Nope. Guess again.
Actually...
those are mine.
Are you down with this?
It's no fun if you leave
with the guy you came with, right?
Agreed.
No promises but we'll see what happens.
On that note...
Imagine that.
Figured you'd end up at our house
one way or another.
I'm still traumatized
from spin the bottle, sophomore year.
Cry me a river, cousin.
Perf. Bye.
Well, well...
Looks like fate has brought us
together yet again, Antoinette.
How did I know this was gonna happen?
Destiny has manifested. I could feel it.
After making this night all about you,
I knew we would end up together.
I don't believe in fate, Cheryl.
But I do believe in your ability
to be a master manipulator.
Hush, Toni.
And follow me.
I have a super surprise.
A gift to you and your little one.
- A nursery.
- Cheryl, what the hell is this?
A place where we can be together.
With or without Kevin and Fangs.
Depending on whether
they survive the festivities.
So is this why you threw a key party?
To hurt Kevin and Fangs?
To show you how fragile
some unions can be, yes.
And to show you a path forward.
Don't you see?
All these years,
I've been compelled to restore Thornhill
without ever truly understanding why.
But... now I see it so clearly.
It was to make a sanctuary for your child.
If not... ours.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I'm not bringing my baby
into this house of horrors.
All you've been trying to do
is draw me out of Thornhill.
And as my reward, you try to trap me here
like you did at Thistlehouse
with your two dead brothers?
It's not gonna work. I'm done trying
to bring you down from the mountain.
I'm done trying to have
a normal friendship with you.
That was my mistake.
I should have just left our relationship
where it belongs, in the past.
Look, I'm sorry I led you on,
and I'm sorry
I agreed to this stupid party.
Really, really am.
So how long have you
and Fangs been together?
Coming up on eight years.
Open for the last three.
- Hmm. That door's closing, I hear.
- Yeah. It's been discussed.
Well, I'm rooting for you guys.
I mean, I don't really know you
but Fogarty?
Man, he's a keeper.
He'll make a great dad too.
Rick...
did Fangs ever mention me?
When he was with you?
Not really.
It might have been awkward,
considering the context.
Yeah, that makes sense.
All right. Okay.
Oops. Okay.
I think the world turned sideways
for a minute there.
Yeah, it does that sometimes.
Tabitha,
you think I had a close encounter?
I don't know.
But I do think that there is
something from your past
that you are trying to avoid dealing with.
Something with those blackouts
back in New York.
Some friendly advice:
You should talk to someone.
Like a therapist
who specializes in cases of trauma.
Yeah.
Maybe you're right.
But for tonight...
just...
sleep.
All right.
- You're home.
- Mm-hm.
Yeah.
Turns out Reggie is 100% straight.
Who'd you get paired with?
- Rick.
- Mm.
Nothing happened, but...
Fangs...
I gotta tell you something.
Okay.
I love you so much.
But I'm not ready to get married.
What?
Why?
Because you don't wanna give up
cruising in the woods? Okay, so don't.
That's fine.
It's not about the woods.
Uh, it's about me.
Where I'm at.
Where you're at.
What about Toni?
Hmm? What about the fact
that we're having a baby together?
I... I'm not sure yet. I...
Kevin, why are you imploding us?
Especially when you pushed
for all of this.
Being open, starting a family.
Getting married.
Yeah. It's messed up.
I know. I know. So messed up.
I'm... I'm...
I'm just sorry.
I'm sorry.
Here we are.
With a free pass to do
whatever we want, so why aren't we?
I think because we're right on the edge.
That's what it feels like, yeah.
Betty...
before we do anything,
I have to be honest with you.
I, uh...
I still have feelings for Veronica.
I shouldn't,
but I do.
"Shouldn't."
Archie, you and I should make sense.
The all-American boy, the girl next door.
But deep in our cores,
we are such different people.
And getting closer to you,
the one thing I know is I don't want
my darkness to overtake you.
Betty...
Now, don't get me wrong.
It's been saving my sanity
to escape with you.
But what's coming next
with my mom and Polly
is probably gonna be the darkest thing...
I've ever faced.
So you get to face
whatever's coming alone?
No way.
No.
Not alone.
Still with you.
As a friend.
Because that's what I think
I'm gonna need.
More than... a lover.
More than an escape.
A friend.
A window of light in the dark.
Then that's what I'll be.
Did you invite me here to make me jealous?
To humiliate me?
Neither.
But I did think
it was time to stop playing games.
And avoiding the truth.
As ill-advised
as Cheryl's party was tonight,
it confirmed something I've been feeling
for a really long time.
It's sublime, Cheryl.
Thank you, Minerva.
Considering so much of my life
is sheer ugliness,
I'm relieved you think so.
No, Cheryl.
You made me beautiful
because you're beautiful.
No, I'm not.
I'm repulsive.
No. Cheryl, you are...
You're gorgeous.
- Hey.
I went by your house,
but Eric told me you were on duty
the next couple of nights, so...
Serves me right
for starting a fire department.
Archie...
Chad and I are getting a divorce.
He's on his way back to New York,
for good.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I think, in my heart of hearts,
I knew it had to happen.
I was devastated
when I found out you were married.
But that was nothing...
like the pain I felt seeing you unhappy.
More than anything,
I want you to be happy.
Good.
Because I might know a way
that you can help me with that.
Wait, I...
I need to tell you something.
Betty and I...
We didn't hook up
after the key party, but we...
We have hooked up a few times
since we got back to Riverdale.
I wondered about that.
What was it? Just two lost, lonely souls
looking for a connection?
Something like that.
We're just friends, is the truth.
I thought you should know.
The way I see it...
the past is in the past.
I'm only interested in...
what we want.
Now.
In the present.
Hello?
This is a collect call
for Alice Cooper.
- I'll accept the charges.
- Mom, are you there?
- Polly.
- Betty, you have to help me.
I'm at some pay phone
in the middle of nowhere.
- Where are you?
- I don't know. I ran as fast as I could.
Come get me. I'm on the highway.
- The Lonely Highway?
- It looks like it.
I'm gonna hang up,
call me back on my cell.
- Mom and I are about to get in the car.
- -Hurry. They're coming.
Wait. There.
There, Betty!
Polly!