Incoming!
Fire! Fire!
Jackson!
You're gonna be safe down here. I got you.
Hey, look at me.
- You'll be okay.
- Sarge.
Sarge, I can't feel my legs.
Are they there? I can't look.
Retreat!
Sarge, are they there?
Are they?
- Contact, 2 o'clock, 150 meters!
- Eric.
- Contact, 2 o'clock, 130 meters!
- Stand down!
Eric. It's me. Eric, don't shoot!
Okay. Okay. Shh, shh, shh.
You're okay. You're okay.
Nighthawk, can you hear me?
Loud and clear, Base Station.
I'm still a bumper sticker
on this shady-ass truck.
Headed north.
He's approaching the westbound turnoff
at Exit 49.
Too far. Two more miles
and you'll be out of range.
He's pulling over.
I'm gonna park and approach on foot.
Betty, just please, please be careful.
Hey.
Didn't think I'd come across anyone.
Yeah, I'm just taking a break,
stretching my legs.
It gets lonely out here
on the long, dark road.
You want some company?
Even for a little bit?
What, in the woods?
Or maybe back of my truck?
That sounds good.
Do you do this a lot?
Pick up pretty girls on the road?
Yeah, I guess I've had
my fair share of encounters. Yeah.
Uh, before we...
do this, uh...
I wanna make sure that you've got cash.
That's all I needed to hear.
- FBI! Freeze!
- Don't move.
What is this?
FBI. We're taking you in for solicitation.
Okay, this is a mistake.
I am also with the FBI.
No, you're not, Betty.
You quit. Remember?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to catch our killer.
What are you doing, Glen?
Trying to clean up the Lonely Highway.
By entrapping young women?
We should be helping them,
not arresting them.
God, I should have stabbed you harder.
You do realize it's illegal
to impersonate an FBI agent, right?
You shouldn't have that badge or a gun.
Hand them over.
Or should I arrest you?
Wait. Kevin?
Compulsion, thy name is Kevin of Finland.
Does Eric have chronic nightmares?
Yeah. But...
Nothing like last night.
It's like he was living it.
What about you?
Any nightmares since the war?
Yeah. I mean, yeah, at first.
But I haven't had one in months.
I've known soldiers like Eric.
They've crossed the Rubicon
and the only way back is with help.
Wasn't there a recovery place
that Eric was supposed to go to?
Yeah. He tried calling,
and they kept promising him a spot, but...
Still nothing.
Don't give up.
In the meantime,
I'll look into something else.
What are those?
Leads I got on the DL
from a former colleague in New York.
Names of fat cats
with money burning holes in their pockets.
Potential investors.
Branching out from jewelry?
I need to start making money, Reggie.
Real money.
To replace all the funds that Chad lost
in his pathetic Ponzi scheme.
Funds I'm responsible for. The snake...
So I'm getting back
into aggressive investment banking.
Don't you have to be on Wall Street?
Common misconception.
All you need is two things,
this and names.
Which means, time to make it rain.
Good morning, Cheryl.
Can I help you?
No, no, no, sweet Kevin.
The question is, can I help you?
We saw each other in the woods.
I was seeking inspiration
for my next sermon, but what about you?
I thought you gave up cruising
after your latest violent encounter.
I did, for a while.
I see.
Do you know what I believe, Kevin?
I don't think
you were looking for a hookup.
I also think you were looking for meaning.
Peace.
No. I'm pretty sure
I was just looking for a hookup.
Kev-Kev.
I don't know if you heard, but my mother
and I recently started a ministry.
Why don't you come to a service?
You might find the answers
you're looking for.
No offense, Cheryl, but that sounds
like a classic Blossom scam.
Well, I can't speak for Mumzie,
but for me it's no scam.
Understand, my calling is
for a high purpose.
Since I began ministering,
I felt the best I have since...
Since the night
of that misbegotten key party.
What's the harm in trying one service?
Okay. Yeah.
I'll come, just to check it out.
You're lucky it was Glen
and not the Highway Killer.
- You would have been on your own.
- I didn't wanna lose him.
I doubt I'll be spending more time
on the Lonely Highway,
now that Glen's gunning for me.
So maybe we bring the Lonely Highway here,
to Pop's and the Whyte Wyrm.
Go on.
The Highway Killer is most likely
a trucker, right?
Well, what if we offer something
to lure truckers in?
Entertainment?
Smart.
We're not going after truckers, plural.
We're going after one trucker, our killer,
who is targeting young women.
Have you ever seen Coyote Ugly?
Um, please. "Can't Fight the Moonlight"
is one of my karaoke go-tos.
So maybe that's what we need
to tempt our little friend.
Riverdale's very own Coyote Ugly.
And we can wire Pop's and the Wyrm
with closed-circuit cameras.
We can start compiling a database
that not even the FBI has.
Tracking regulars,
running license plates...
Let's do it.
Together.
We'll talk to Fangs.
We wait six hours to see someone
and they tell us
we haven't filled out the right forms.
Sorry, sarge, but that's what happens
every time I go to the VA.
Archie, Eric,
come into the living room.
Fellas, meet our new roommate.
Where'd you get this idea?
I've known many veterans who adopted pets.
It's part of their transition
back to civilian life.
Helps with their anxiety,
adds structure to their day,
gives them a loyal companion.
- Where'd you get him?
- At the shelter downtown.
According to the vet,
they found him near a dumpster.
Did they tell you
what happened to his ears?
No. They weren't sure.
Hey, Arch, didn't you have a dog?
- What was his name?
- Vegas.
- What happened to him?
- When I enlisted,
Mom took him to Chicago with her.
He died while I was overseas.
Aw, damn.
I'm sorry, Arch.
He was my best friend.
Maybe this little pooch will be good
for both of you.
Let me ask you this,
have you ever invested in an IPO?
We have numerous opportunities
in the pipeline
that I'd be happy to walk you through.
Of course, Mr. Mamet.
Thank you for your time.
You win some, you lose some.
Yes, but I'm losing more
than winning, Reggie.
Back in New York,
when I was the She-Wolf of Wall Street,
I had a team of 20.
But now I'm one broker
with no firm to back her up.
Let's double our chances.
Let me work for you.
You can't just start trading.
You have to understand finance,
politics, diplomacy...
Really?
'Cause I've been listening to you all day
and it sounds to me like you just need
to know how to close a sale.
Like I do at my old man's car lot.
I can close, Ronnie.
I'm a closer.
Give me a shot.
Okay.
It's two o'clock now.
If you can turn one lead into a sale
by the time the stock exchange closes,
- I'll cut you in.
- One client? By six o'clock?
The New York Stock Exchange
closes at 4, Reggie.
Clock's ticking.
So, Fangs, we have an idea
that we would love for you to run by Toni.
- Okay.
- If we want to attract the Highway Killer,
we have to give him
something enticing to look at.
So, what do you think about turning
this place into a Coyote Ugly-style bar?
Like the Tyra Banks movie?
Exactly.
Hot ladies dancing on the bar.
Fully clothed, of course.
And free-flowing booze.
It would be the perfect thirst trap.
And who are the hot ladies?
Us.
We are.
I'm trying to get a referral to a doctor.
My name is Sergeant Archie Andrews.
I'm calling on behalf of Eric Jackson
about getting him some treatment.
I've left my number.
If you could give me a call back,
that would great.
Thank you.
How you doing?
Thinking about Vegas?
No. I'm thinking about Bingo.
Who's Bingo?
He was this stray dog
that our platoon adopted.
- What happened to him?
- He didn't make it.
Yeah. We don't like talking about it much.
It's probably why Eric is so happy
about this new dog.
To make up for Bingo.
Yeah.
That makes sense.
I want this for you.
And more importantly,
you should want this for yourself.
You're a smart guy, Bobby.
Think about what this investment
could mean for your family.
I'm talking a down payment on a house,
college tuition for your son or daughter,
vacations you deserve
but haven't been able to afford.
You're in at 100?
Mr. Stone,
I'm telling you, you won't regret this.
Mm-hm. I'll e-mail you the paperwork.
Very good, Reginald.
You're a natural salesman.
Welcome, officially, to Pearls and Posh.
Look, Cheryl, I don't mean to offend you,
but your service wasn't exactly my speed.
To each his own.
But there is a hole inside you
that you're trying to fill.
I think I know what it's about.
Fangs, how you left things with him.
Breaking up with him,
especially the way I did,
is the worst thing I've done.
- Maybe ever.
- Regret.
It haunts you.
I know because it haunts me too.
Go to your man.
Try to make amends. Say you're sorry.
Ask for clemency.
Regardless of how he responds,
you'll feel better having tried.
Kevin.
Hey, this is a surprise.
Hey, Fangs.
I know we haven't talked,
but I have stuff to get off my chest,
- so I hope you'll hear me out.
- For sure.
Right now isn't a good time.
If I don't say it now,
I'm gonna lose my nerve, so just...
- Kev...
- More baguette to the rescue.
- Oh, my God.
- Kevin!
- Moose?
- It's been a while.
This isn't... This isn't what it looks...
You're seeing Moose Mason?
- We just ran into each other.
- Kev, why don't you sit down?
We'll have a glass of wine,
we can talk about this.
Yeah. No, thank you.
I've gotta wake up from this nightmare
in which my ex-boyfriends
are sleeping together.
Kevin.
- Hey, Eric!
- Incoming!
I know you're tired,
but you gotta wait until nightfall,
then I can carry you out of here.
We're gonna get you help,
but you gotta keep your eyes open.
Sarge, is...?
- Is that Bingo?
- Yeah. I'll bring him back.
- Where is he?
- In the middle of no-man's-land.
That's no good.
You can't go out there. You'll get shot.
I can make it if I'm fast.
You can't go out there. No way.
- I can't just ignore him.
- You will die.
You're my only hope of getting out.
I can get Bingo and bring him back,
and I can take you both.
We're in their crosshairs.
We've gotta wait them out.
I have to do it.
I can't leave Bingo out there to die.
Sarge, no! I won't let you!
Eric, what the hell?
Sarge, you gotta help. The dog, he's gone!
- What?
- He's missing. We gotta find him!
- How did he get out?
- It's okay. Calm down. I found him.
- Where?
- Come here, check it out.
- How'd he get in there?
- I guess the door was ajar.
He was looking for a place to hide.
Mr. Preston, it's Reginald Mantle
from Pearls and Posh.
Do I have an exciting proposition for you.
Yes, Mr. Gibbs, we're smaller
than some of the New York firms,
but it means we'll work
that much harder for you.
And just to be clear,
though I want your business,
I don't need your business.
Nolan, there's no judgment here.
If you wanna go
the target-mutual-funds route, I get it.
It's safe. But the truth is,
scared money doesn't make money.
What I'm offering you is a sure thing.
Welcome aboard, Mrs. Artemis.
You will surely be bragging
to your friends at tea time this Saturday.
Speak to you very, very soon.
Okay. Bye-bye.
I just closed my fifth client.
I just closed my third. We're killing it.
We are proving ourselves
to be capable, but...
we need more leads to call.
I'm all tapped out of names.
What's my commission
for all the fish I'm catching?
Industry standard, 5%.
If I get us some fresh leads,
will you bump me to 15%?
If you can really bring in new business:
10%.
Okay, then. But there's one caveat:
The leads are from SoDale.
SoDale? What are you talking about?
The thing about SoDale is,
it doesn't exist.
It's a muddy field with no construction.
Your dad sold his investors on a vision
of something that will never be built.
He's using the money
to fund his palladium search.
Aren't his investors asking questions?
Constantly.
But he's always got an excuse
for why the new houses aren't finished.
So I'm thinking...
What if we go
after my father's investors...
and get them to pull out of SoDale
and invest with us?
Reggie, you're a genius.
Hey. It's okay. Just calm down.
Keep some pressure on it.
What the hell happened?
Eric took the dog for a walk.
They ran into a bigger dog.
Our guy freaked out,
Eric tried to calm him down...
- And he bit my arm!
- That's it. We're done.
- Where are you going?
- I'm calling the shelter.
Archie, please. This is all my fault.
Give me five minutes to clean up Eric
and I'll explain everything.
So how is a rescue dog biting Eric
your fault?
Dog I brought home isn't
an ordinary rescue.
The woman at the shelter told me,
based on his injuries,
he was likely part of a dog-fighting ring.
Are you kidding?
That's happening here in Riverdale?
They started a few years ago,
after everyone began moving away,
leaving their pets behind.
The shelter rescues as many as they can,
but some wound up with the wrong people.
Scumbags who pit dogs against each other
and bet on which ones will win
and which ones will die.
I'll be back.
Mrs. Rawald, you wouldn't have happened
to invest in SoDale LLC?
Uh-huh. And how is that investment doing,
Mr. Barry?
Have you seen any houses in SoDale?
Any blueprints?
Construction's not happening
as quickly as I'd like.
I have it on very good authority
that there will never be a SoDale.
So... might I suggest you withdraw
your funds from SoDale LLC
and invest with us at Pearls and Posh.
You're telling me SoDale's a scam?
Give me a minute.
I'll get Hiram Lodge on the other line.
Chris Barry. Always a pleasure
to hear your voice.
- How's Cindy?
- I'm not happy.
I have a source telling me
that I made a bad investment with you.
SoDale.
Whoa! That's absurd.
SoDale is the finest investment
you could put your money into.
In fact, you should double down.
How does 30% returns
over three years sound?
He's selling me on 30% at three years,
Ms. Posh. Can you match that?
How about an ROI of 35% at three?
I'll throw in a Glamourge Egg as a bonus,
but that's my final offer.
What do you say, Chris?
This is onetime-only, exclusive FOH,
"Friends of Hiram," offer.
Thirty-five percent
and a Glamourge Egg. Okay.
I'm in.
Thank you, Mr. Barry.
You are in good hands at Pearls and Posh.
Sorry, Lodge,
but I'm pulling out of SoDale.
If I don't get my money back, I'll be
calling the State Attorney's office.
Best of luck with your venture.
To you, Ronnie.
The She-Wolf of Wall Street.
So, what happens now?
We take the night off
to help Betty and Tabitha,
and then we keep doing
exactly what we're doing.
Fangs with Moose, you say?
Yeah, I caught them having wine
and cheese.
That's diabolical.
Kevin, you did nothing wrong.
And you brought your sacred truth
to his profane threshold.
That alone is a victory.
Then why do I feel so forsaken?
In godless times like these,
instead of focusing on yourself,
perhaps the only way to know true comfort
is by comforting others.
Tonight, I'm assisting Betty and Tabitha
in a most ingenious ruse
to thwart the evil goings-on
of the Lonely Highway.
Work with us on this, Kevin.
And perhaps in service,
you will find peace and meaning.
Okay, gather round, people.
This is it.
Hopefully, it will be a big night.
We'll be checking everyone's IDs,
aka writing down their names
and driver's license numbers,
regardless of their age.
After my new cameras catch
their faces coming in.
Mom, you'll work the bar,
keeping an eye out for anything sketchy.
As I usually do.
Shouldn't Fangs be here?
Isn't he managing for Toni?
Yeah, but he's helping Archie
with some dog thing tonight,
so Toni asked me to step in.
Veronica, Cheryl, Tabitha,
and I will be performing.
While we keep the truckers busy,
our stealth team of Kevin and Reggie
will be jimmying open their trailers
and looking for anything suspicious.
If you find something, I'll check it out.
Our main goal of the night is recon, okay?
Get names, get licenses.
And, cardinal rule, no one goes off alone
with any truckers, okay?
Are we ready to do this?
I asked around, Archie, and it's true.
The dog-fighting ring in town.
Once a month,
sickos from as far as Montreal
meet to at that address to bet on dogs.
- That's where the ringleader lives.
- When's the next round?
Not for another couple of weeks.
Enough time to loop in Sheriff Keller.
We're not looping in Sheriff Keller.
Or my uncle.
I don't want this scumbag arrested.
- I want him hurt.
- Sarge, our priority is saving the dogs.
Yeah. But that doesn't mean
we can't settle up with this guy too.
- Hey. What's going on?
- I'm an agent with the FBI.
We're investigating illegal contraband
being shipped down from Montreal.
I need you to open up the back.
Okay, no contraband.
But can you explain the blood?
Yeah. I just did a huge meat delivery.
That's cow's blood.
I assume you have documents
to back that up?
Yeah. In my cab.
Get the dogs. I'll go inside.
- Hold on.
- Just do it. This won't take long.
- Those your dogs outside?
- Who are you?
I said, are those your dogs?
Yeah. I train them.
Why? You wanna buy one?
You and me,
we're gonna have a real dog fight.
- You like that? You sicko!
- Stop.
- You like getting beaten?
- Sarge! Sarge, enough!
You can call Sheriff Keller now
or the garbage man, I don't care which.
But if you touch one more dog,
I'm gonna dig your grave myself.
Not a complete success.
But 57 truckers total with their names
and driver's license numbers.
Not a bad start to a list
of possible suspects, partner.
I'll do some background checks on them,
and tomorrow night
we'll do more dancing and recon.
No rest for the weary, huh?
Hey.
Is this where the Wild Foxes perform?
Saw a sign on the highway.
Uh, yeah, but you missed it.
Our last call was an hour ago.
Come back tomorrow.
Shoot. I was looking
for a good time tonight.
What are you doing now?
I was gonna go home, but...
I could be down
for a little fun if you are.
Yeah, hop in.
I know a motel not far from here.
Sounds good.
So are you just passing through town?
Visiting my grandmother.
She's pretty sick.
I'm getting ready to say my goodbyes.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- No. It's all right.
It's a beautiful thing, really,
watching someone pass.
Watching as the light fades
from their eyes.
There's nothing like it.
You mind if I stop to take a leak?
No, sure.
I'll be two minutes, tops.
Tabitha. I got him.
I'm on my way. Don't do anything crazy.
Betty. Are you okay?
Yeah.
I am.
But I need your help with him.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Wild guess...
- You guys went after the dog fighter.
- Yeah.
Sarge went berserk on him.
I wish he wouldn't have done that.
Can't say that I'm surprised.
Not after what happened to Bingo.
What are you talking about?
Bingo. Your platoon dog?
Archie told me how you two were
pinned down in the foxhole...
and you had to sit there and listen
to Bingo howling and dying and...
Frank, Bingo wasn't a dog.
He was a grunt like me.
What do we do now?
We find a out-of-the-way place
to park the truck.
What about the guy? The killer?
I have a place
where we can take him and keep him.
- Shouldn't we hand him over to the FBI?
- Not yet.
If there's a chance
he knows where Polly is...
I want him to give up that information.
At which point, we will hand him over.
Arch, Eric told me the truth about Bingo.
Wanna talk about it?
What's there to talk about?
I've been to war, Archie.
I know the impossible decisions
you have to make.
To hear Eric tell it,
if you had gone back for Bingo,
you and Eric probably wouldn't
have made it either.
You made a choice in the moment
and it was the right choice.
You can't save everyone.
It feels wrong.
Everything feels wrong.
I'm trying to save this town,
but it is so...
corrupt.
Broken, full of awful, despicable people.
I mean, the lowest of the lows.
Dog fighters.
Makes me think
there's nothing worth saving here.
Don't lose sight of what you're doing.
Kevin, I heard you being summoned
to Weatherbee's office.
Were you fired for your cruising ways?
No, Cheryl. Actually, the opposite.
I've just been named Teacher of the Year.
Oh, but that's incredible.
So why the forlorn face?
- Is it Fangs?
- Yeah.
But also it's my entire life.
I love being a teacher,
but it was never supposed
to be my life's calling.
This award is a painful reminder
of all that I haven't accomplished.
I'm supposed to be in New York.
Writing, performing, directing.
Instead, I'm in Riverdale,
still cruising the woods.
Unlucky in love,
being named Teacher of the Year
at a dying high school.
This can't be my life. It can't be.
I think I have an idea
that might not fix all of your problems,
but will replenish your artist's soul.
Well? What do you think?
Not everybody in Riverdale is rotten.
How'd you guys pull this off?
Eric and I called some shelters, told them
we had dogs that needed homes.
Good dogs who maybe need
more attention and rehabilitation
before they can get adopted
'cause of what they've been through.
- Almost gives you hope again, huh?
- Almost.
No, this is good. This is great.
Hey, Sarge. You think it'd be okay
if we call him Bingo?
- Wouldn't be disrespectful, would it?
- No, no. Hey!
We loved Bingo.
I think he'd be honored.
Brothers and sisters, this week,
I learned a simple yet profound truth.
It is in making those around us feel good
that we ourselves may find salvation.
"Comfort. Yes, comfort, my people."
Isaiah, Chapter 40, Verse 1.
As a reminder of that lesson,
today's closing hymn
will be "Everything Is All right"
from the iconic musical
Jesus Christ Superstar.
And singing with me will be our ministry's
new artistic director, Kevin Keller.
Let me start by saying
I'm sorry you had to walk in on that.
We were trying to figure out a way
to tell you without causing a spiral.
- My spiraling days are over.
- Listen.
I know this may be impossible, Kev...
but I'd love for us to be friends.
We are friends, Fangs.
And if you and Moose make
each other happy, I'm happy. Seriously.
We'll be in this together, Jim.
We're both family men. Wife and kids.
I can hear it in your voice
that you want this.
I'm gonna pass you on
to the queen of the shop,
and she's gonna tell you
why you deserve it, okay?
Hold on.
- I think I got him. He just needs a push.
- Say no more.
Mr. Nesper, I hear you're considering
a promising opportunity,
and I just have to say,
this isn't about
what you're putting down right now.
This is about legacy.
How are you talking care
of yourself and your family
for the rest of your life and theirs?
We absolutely can
and we'll do that for you, Mr. Nesper.
And might I add that Pearls and Posh
is honored to be doing business with you?
Bingo!
You there?
Answer me, private! That's an order!
Eric, what's happening?
Why isn't Bingo answering me?
He's dead, sarge.
Bingo is dead.
Hello?
Yeah, this is Sergeant Andrews.
I was calling on behalf of my friend,
Corporal Jackson.
Bingo?
I think I might need help too.