Previously on Riverdale:
If we divorce,
I can testify against you in court.
No one would believe
that the She-Wolf of Wall Street
didn't know about the dirty dealings
going on in her own business.
Archie, I'm staying in New York.
Ronnie, don't do this.
I'm not going to stop looking for Polly.
I will get justice, Mom.
I have a favor to ask. I have
some personal trauma I can't access.
I need someone I trust to watch over me.
You have to get some writing done.
I'll be back in the morning.
- Write.
- Tabitha. Tabitha, don't!
Oh, my God.
Uncle Frank, Kev's dad said
there was a prison break.
Boom.
Some inmates said they were paid
to trash the town, especially this school.
Only Hiram Lodge would be
crazy enough to do that.
Hiram's escapees
trashed everything.
Pulled wires from walls,
smashed circuit breakers,
even broke sinks and toilets.
How long until we can get
this place back in shape, Mr. Andrews?
At least three weeks.
- And that's if I can pull a crew together.
- Count me in, Archie.
Let's get started.
I guess it's back to remote learning.
Ms. Veronica. Welcome back.
Smithers.
Oh! Is that my special delivery?
Oh, ah, yes. It came last night.
Uh, there's something
you should know. Your fath...
Let me get eyes on the opal first.
Oh, Smithers.
My gem contact in Ethiopia did not lie.
This blue opal is even more stunning
than I imagined.
And just in time too.
I've got a buyer coming in
from Montreal, Mr. Sand.
I can use the commission from the sale
to start paying back Chad's investors.
Something happened while you were gone.
Your father's prison was compromised.
What?
The town was flooded
with convicts wreaking havoc and mayhem.
- Hit hardest was Riverdale High.
- Oh, my God.
Archie. Thank God.
I heard about the prison break.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
School's a mess,
but it could have been a lot worse.
How did things go with Chad?
Did he sign the divorce papers?
Uh, not exactly.
Chad threw me a curveball.
I could explain, but for legal reasons,
it's better you don't know the details.
I know. I'm sorry.
I really hate
that I'm dragging you through this.
I appreciate it, but until you
and Chad are officially done...
I think we should keep our distance.
We can be friends, but that's it.
Not until those papers are signed.
I...
suppose that makes sense.
I'm gonna be busy anyway.
I told Tom I'd help him round up any
convicts who are still causing trouble.
Well, only when I feel like it.
Well, you are legally senile.
Good morning, sisters.
What are you so happy about?
Life, Cheryl. Everlasting life.
Whilst in prison,
I started my own ministry.
And now that I am free, I can see plainly
that continuing my good work
is precisely
what this wicked little town needs.
We'll hold two services a day,
right here on the estate.
A ministry.
Shouldn't you be hiding in the walls,
perchance the po-po come a-knocking?
Actually...
due to my active spiritual work,
I was up for early parole.
What we need is money,
not some sham religion created by
and for convicts.
God is on our side, child.
When we start this church,
he will provide.
- Hello?
- Is this Betty?
Yeah, who is this?
It's Tabitha. Tabitha Tate.
Hi.
I know this is out of the blue,
but I can't find Jughead anywhere.
I was supposed to watch him, long story.
Now he's missing. I'm worried about him.
Look, Jughead's been known
to go off-grid for days at a time.
I can stop by Pop's tomorrow
and check in with you if you want.
I appreciate that.
- Thank you, Betty.
- Yeah.
Give me the cash in your register! Now!
No problem.
Please, just don't hurt anyone.
Give me the money!
Jeremiah Peterson,
serving five to ten years
for two counts of armed robbery.
There's about to be three unless
you can help us find your fellow escapees.
Most of them are long gone.
Hightailed it out of Riverdale
after the prison break.
- A few stayed behind.
- How many?
I want a lawyer.
And some more meds.
Maybe after he's had some rest
and some painkillers,
he'll wanna talk to us.
I'll look in on him periodically.
Night.
Isn't it beautiful?
I was tracking this opal down for months.
It finally came in.
It's sublime.
Well, isn't this a small world?
Wait.
You're those psychos
from Thanksgiving seven years ago.
Don't even think about it, darling.
Hands up. Both of you.
Dodger, smash and grab.
We'll take that too.
Hope your insurance is all paid up.
What the hell just happened?
Hey. You should see this.
...to round up the majority
of these criminals.
We believe there's a small group
of escapees still at large
in the town formerly known as Riverdale.
Local philanthropist Hiram Lodge and I
are offering a reward for any information
that may lead to a safe capture
of any and all prisoners.
Wait. So Hiram sets free a bunch of cons.
Now he's offering a reward
for bringing them back?
A PR stunt to paint themselves as heroes.
Where are you going?
We need money to fix this school.
They're offering it.
I'm rounding up criminals and cashing in.
If it isn't my old friend...
- Hello, Archie.
- Hiram.
Governor Dooley.
I saw the press conference.
I'm going after your prisoners.
Do you have a list
of the missing convicts?
Here is some of the names
of the inmates confirmed to be at large.
Thank you.
You'll hear from me.
And keep your checkbook handy.
This is a mess. Blowing up the prison
was never a part of our greater plan.
- As far as you know.
- Cut the crap!
Just give me my cut of the palladium.
I've told you over and over again,
governor,
we didn't find any
beneath the prison, sadly.
And I don't believe you, partner.
But I'll give you 24 hours
to change your tune.
Be careful out there, Donald.
A lot of dangerous folk
still on the loose.
Might wanna watch your back.
Ronnie.
You said you needed my help,
but I'm done doing cleanup work.
Reggie. Thanks to your
and my father's machinations,
that thug Dodger Dickenson
and his crazy mom
ravaged my store.
They got away with half my stock,
not to mention an Ethiopian blue opal,
which you, Reginald,
are going to help me find.
Yeah, no.
Uh, this is not high school, Ronnie.
I work for one Lodge and it's not you.
How did that even happen?
My dad got into money trouble
and turned to your dad for help.
Now I'm working off my old man's debt.
Reggie, it's not too late to switch sides.
Fight with the good guys.
Nah. The bad guys pay better.
But I'll help you find your rock,
for old time's sake.
Thank you, Reggie.
Wow. So Jughead is taking
psychedelics to help him write now.
I guess I'm only sort of surprised,
actually.
I thought if I cuffed him,
he'd be contained until I came back.
But I couldn't stay. Not after...
What?
When he was high, he made a pass at me.
When I rebuffed him, he said...
What did he say?
He said, "Don't be such a Betty.
First sign of fun, you try to kill it."
Okay, um...
I'm sorry that Jughead put you
in this really awful position,
but he shouldn't really be
my problem anymore, or yours,
for that matter.
But, yeah, yeah. I'll help.
Last time I didn't act
on a missing person was my sister.
We'll start at the bunker.
- I wanna see it for myself.
- Thanks.
Hey, what are you giving him?
That's my prisoner.
Darla Dickenson?
Didn't realize I'd made
such an impression on you folks.
Mission accomplished.
In about two minutes,
Jeremiah won't be saying much
of anything to anyone.
Oh. And I hooked us
a little bonus prize too.
Well, he left his phone here.
That's never a good sign.
Okay. Although this will be
potentially cringey,
I think we should read
Jughead's manuscript.
See if there's any clues
about where he may have wandered off to.
We'll each take half.
What am I looking for?
Any conspicuous locations
or people that he mentions.
Anything that might be a lead.
Oh, what do we have here?
Fallen on hard times, friend?
Just trying to keep warm.
Hey, uh, wanna make some money?
No, I'm good.
No, really, take it. I insist.
My mom's building a case
to grant you an early release
because of your heroism
the night of the prison break.
If you help us find these convicts,
it should bolster your chances.
I'll help. Might even know
where some of them are hiding.
I also heard of convicts
squatting in a tuna warehouse
out on the docks.
Great. We'll start there.
- No answer?
- No. Straight to voicemail.
- Thanks for asking.
- Talked to your dad earlier.
He knew we were meeting here.
It's Riverdale. He could be doing
literally anything. Onwards.
- Are we going in armed?
- Yeah. Batons, Tasers and zip ties.
No guns. Minimal bloodshed.
Let's go get them.
All this stuff
about Mothmen and mole people.
Where did Jughead get the shrooms anyways?
His ex Jessica came up
from New York to deliver them.
Maybe he's reached out to her.
Seven years later,
still the same passcode.
Hey, Jones. How was your trip?
Is this Jessica?
Yeah, who the hell is this?
This is Betty Cooper. I'm...
Wait. The Betty?
Oh, my God.
I have so many questions for you.
I'm calling because you sold Jughead
mushrooms and now he's missing.
- Has he reached out to you?
- No.
But don't worry.
Sometimes when he has writer's block,
Jones goes on walkabouts, he calls them.
He's not blocked.
He wrote his book, such as it is.
I thought Diner Girl was supposed
to watch him.
He slipped past her.
Amateur. I'll come up to help you look.
- No, that's really not necessary...
- He owes me 500 bucks.
Text me your address.
Okay. Uh, well, I guess
we'll see you tomorrow.
Maybe she can actually help us.
Also I'm a little curious to meet her.
Efforts are afoot to rebuild Riverdale.
But this town shan't be saved
until its soul is saved.
What say ye?
May our souls be saved!
Amen, I say back to ye!
Now, give yourselves over
to the holy sweetness.
Drink of his sweet water and be saved.
Who exactly is he, Mumzie?
Whose sweet water are they tasting?
The sweetness of this water...
comes from a son
who died for the sins
and the darkness of this world.
Yes.
I speak of my son, Jason.
For years,
I searched to find meaning in his death.
But then, I realized something.
Jason was a sacrifice.
To lay bare the sins
of this accursed place.
And now it is up to us
to shepherd the soul of this township
back into the light.
To that end,
if you have any coins or bills
that you could spare, even a penny
will help to ensure
Riverdale's spiritual future.
Praise be.
I'm gonna drain the vein.
- What the...?
- What the hell?
There are warrants out for your arrest.
And we're taking you in.
You don't have guns.
That was a bad idea.
Drop it. Before I drop you.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
Our old nemeses Dodger
and Darla Dickenson stole my blue opal.
I got one of the cons to spill.
Dodger was here talking up
some fancy rock, but slipped out
before you clowns stormed in.
That's my buyer.
He's getting restless. Okay.
I have to deal with him,
but, Archie, please,
I need you to find Dodger and Darla,
and get my opal back.
All right. Let me get this straight.
You went off to New York,
which I didn't want you to do,
you may have spent the night with your
husband, who didn't sign divorce papers.
- Now you want me to go find a rock?
- I'm sorry
about what happened with me and Chad.
But you're going after the Dickensons
no matter what, right?
Then you can get me my opal.
Fine.
Hey. You should rest.
You're banged up pretty bad.
- You changed my bandages?
- Yes, sir.
You got a fever. Probably an infection.
I gave you aspirin,
but what you need are antibiotics.
Sent a pal of mine out to score you some.
You're shivering.
Here.
Thanks.
Yeah, those guys,
they kicked the tar out of you.
You're lucky you're alive.
I'm lucky you were there.
- What's your name?
- Calvin.
But people call me Doc.
There's this one guy named Doc.
He would stay up all night just to make
sure the junkies didn't mess with me.
And one day, these drunken businessmen
who had heard about
our little shanty town, they found Doc...
and beat the life out of him.
I didn't move. I didn't say anything.
I watched.
What's yours?
Henry.
Well, Henry...
you wanna tell me
how you ended up on Sketch Alley?
I took some shrooms.
I had a bad trip.
I was in and out for a while.
And then I guess I...
wandered here.
I really should go. Thank you very much.
Hey, hey. You're not going anywhere.
Look, my friend will be back soon.
And until then, you sleep.
There you go.
Donald, it's Hiram.
I have some new information regarding
what we were discussing earlier.
If you can meet me ASAP,
I'm at the office.
Satisfied?
Not until I get my share of the palladium.
Or you're dead.
Or both.
Archie said
Jughead has been living in here.
Oh, my God.
Jessica, what do you think?
Our apartment back in New York
was even messier.
What the hell
has he been doing these days?
The maple mushrooms I gave Jones
shouldn't have triggered
a psychotic episode.
- Was he taking anything else?
- Not that I know of.
We should confirm that.
Luckily, I know all about hiding places.
Especially his.
We can search for him and his stashes,
see if there are any other drugs
he might have been sampling.
Where else could he be hiding out?
Or hiding contraband?
Well, it's a long shot, but he did live
under the stairs at Riverdale High once.
- Has a desk there, same as the rest of us.
- That's our next stop.
Well, he is not in the teacher's lounge.
He's not under the stairs.
Pretty sure he's not hiding
in a desk drawer.
Where would he have done most
of his writing, if not here or his crib?
The bunker but we already checked it.
But you don't know
what we're looking for. Take me there.
Okay.
You're shameless, Mumzie.
Swindling those people out of their money
whilst defiling the memory of Jay-Jay.
I am doing no such thing.
I've spent enough time
with corpses to know the truth.
There is no invisible world,
just eternal rot.
We are worm food at best.
- Do you honestly believe that?
- Well...
there was a time when I wanted
to believe in something more.
A time when I thought I was speaking
to Jay-Jay in the beyond.
But you ruined that.
Your gaslighting, your lies,
your deranged Julian doll.
You showed me
that there is nothing eternal.
Just the cruelty of mothers.
Any faith I had went up in flames
when I gave Jason his Viking funeral.
But, Cheryl, there is a realm
beyond this mortal coil
where maple syrup flows in rivers.
Don't you wanna be part
of something larger?
Of course I do.
I just don't think
you're a part of it, Mother.
Daddy, I can't talk right now.
Veronica Lodge.
You don't know me, but my associates
and I have taken your father hostage.
See, he owes me something
and he won't give it over.
So if you wanna see him
or his fellow captives,
Governor Dooley or Sheriff Keller,
alive again,
- you better follow my instructions.
- What do you want?
Palladium.
We dug it out of the ground
for your father and now we want our share.
But he won't tell us where it is.
So I thought maybe
you could get through to him.
We're at the El Royale,
there's three of them...
Daddy?
Do not cooperate with these thugs.
What's palladium?
I don't know.
Daddy?
That was Double D putting a bullet
into Governor Dooley's stomach.
It'll probably take a few hours
for him to bleed out.
The next bullet goes into your father.
So if you wanna save their lives,
find me that palladium!
Wait, Double D?
Is Dodger Dickenson there?
And does he have a blue opal?
He might.
I'll get you the palladium,
but I want my father and the others back.
And my opal.
- Deal.
- I'll be in touch.
What was that about?
Reggie...
...what do you know
about my dad and palladium?
Okay. Now I'm officially worried.
Dad has never been out of touch this long.
Your dad's been
in tough spots before, Kev.
He'll be okay. We're gonna find him.
- Veronica?
- Archie, where are you?
Home. We haven't found Dodger
or his mom yet.
I know where they are.
They're with some other guy named Ted.
Oh, crap.
I know that guy. He's a beast.
They're holed up at the El Royale
and they're keeping my father,
Governor Dooley
and Sheriff Keller hostage.
Wait, what?
They're looking for palladium.
Reggie thinks he knows where it is.
- Can you meet us at Daddy's office?
- We're on our way.
I know where your dad is.
Confirmed.
My father is literally Lex Luthor.
If he's hiding any palladium,
it's in there.
Archie, you still ride
with those tools in your truck?
Yes, I do.
Do you guys wanna give me a hand?
And I will track down a dolly.
Well done, fellas.
Depressing.
I can see why Jones likes this place.
- Damn it. Where is it?
- What are you even looking for?
Jones's manuscript.
Uh, I have it. I took it
when we searched this place earlier.
Can I read it? Is there anything in there
that will help us find Jones?
Not that we could pinpoint.
Okay.
Mmm... New idea.
If this is where he tripped,
should we do the same?
I'm sorry. What?
I have shrooms,
from the same batch I gave Jones.
If we take some,
maybe we could see what he saw,
experience what he experienced.
It'll be like retracing his steps.
Give us a sec?
We've just never tripped before.
- Yeah.
- Just gonna...
We're not gonna do that.
- What is she trying to pull?
- I don't know.
She gave him drugs.
She's trying to get us to take drugs.
She's got multiple agendas.
This was, I think, a really bad idea.
- Let's pivot.
- New new idea.
I wonder if I should go back to New York.
You two have Riverdale covered,
but what if Jughead is on his way
back there to confront his demons?
- That might be a good idea.
- Could be. Good idea.
But it is a long ride back.
Can we grab a bite before I go?
Jones couldn't stop talking about Pop's
when I met him.
Yeah. For sure.
Okay. Come on, ladies. It'll be my treat.
- I didn't ask you for a thing.
- Good point.
- I didn't ask you for anything.
- Doc?
- Did you get the palladium?
- Yes, but there's a catch.
It's locked in a safe.
We have it but not the combination.
- Luckily...
- I have the man who does.
All right. But you make the delivery.
Not your boyfriend. Just you.
Deal. I'll be there in half an hour.
I give you the safe, you give me my opal
and free the hostages.
And Archie tells me you're a military man,
so I know you'll honor your word.
What's the plan, boys?
Once I'm inside,
I can buy us, say, 30 seconds.
Ted knows the El Royale.
- He'll have eyes on all the entrances.
- No, not all.
When I took over, I put in a new roof.
There's a skylight covered with tar paper.
We tear it off and drop in like Batman
with the element of surprise.
He doesn't know you're with us,
Uncle Frank, which gives us an advantage.
They've got my dad. I'm going in too.
- Count me in as well.
- Same.
Good. We'll need the manpower against Ted.
You really didn't have to do that.
I own this diner.
No way. I love splurging on new friends.
It's a lesson I live by.
Help out when you can.
And maybe don't leave people alone
when they're tripping on mushrooms.
I assumed he'd be safe in the handcuffs.
Well, another lesson,
maybe don't give psychedelic shrooms
to someone in a delicate state.
How about don't betray your boyfriend
the way you did?
Getting with his best friend,
that's some Shakespearean-level treachery.
Okay. Yeah.
Clearly, in the stories
Jughead has been telling,
he's cast himself
as the blameless victim here.
But Jughead's not so innocent.
Yeah, no, actually,
he left me this voicemail,
mmm, two years ago.
Betty, where the hell are you?
You said you were gonna come to
my release party, but, what, you bailed?
Of course you bailed.
You've just been blowing me off for years.
Why should I have expected
anything different?
You know, I see you.
I see what I should have seen
seven years ago.
You pretend to be nice,
but you're only looking for weak spots.
And when you find them,
you press on them like a bruise.
Like when you hooked up with Archie?
You know, you found the one person
that would hurt both me and Veronica,
and you just went there.
You're a cold, fake, duplicitous bitch.
And once people read my book,
everyone's gonna see that.
Wow.
- That's darkness.
- Yep.
I was living with Jughead then.
Yeah. Things were good for a while.
But then these writing deadlines started
to get the best of him,
and he started spiraling
into this destructive behavior.
To be fair, so did I.
I'm a writer as well.
We cared about each other.
We just weren't good for each other.
I couldn't be around that energy.
So I got out.
Mmm. Are you guys hot?
I'm feeling hot.
Oh, crap.
I feel bad now, but I'm just gonna say it.
When I got the fries, I sprinkled
some dried mushrooms on them.
- Are you kidding me?
- What?
- They tasted different.
- I'm sorry.
I was gonna chill until you guys started
tripping, then grab the manuscript.
- Is that why you came here?
- Why didn't you ask for it?
Probably PTSD from asking Jughead if
I could read whatever he was working on,
and then him biting my head off.
We should get you guys some place safe.
What is so important about this manuscript
that you would drug us to get it?
It's literal gibberish.
After he used you as fodder
for The Outcasts,
I was afraid
he'd write about our time in New York.
And I really don't want my parents
or my friends reading that.
Go ahead.
He probably won't even remember
writing it.
If he ever turns up.
I'm sure you don't want any more advice,
but just let the trip take you
wherever it may go.
It should be gentle and mellow.
Ride it out together.
Don't fight it. Okay?
Just let the tunes wash over you.
And thanks for understanding.
- Search her.
- Show me the blue opal first.
Okay. Now you can search me.
Isn't it fab?
It's from Lacy's new fall line.
A dozen hidden pockets
for that businesswoman on the go.
Better not be wasting my time.
And that's 30 seconds, you Neanderthal.
I take it, that's worth a lot.
It is.
Tomorrow, I'll hand it over to my buyer,
but tonight, this blue baby is all mine.
Thanks to you and your A-Team.
So when the governor
regains consciousness,
we'll be asking him
to give your uncle a full pardon.
I won't say no to that, Ronnie.
So...
we're still feeling good
about our decision?
To hold off until my divorce is final?
Yeah.
But I am torn.
Well, then...
I better work on making this divorce
happen as fast as humanly possible.
I'll be seeing you soon, Archie.
Thought you might like an update.
Where's the palladium?
That doesn't really matter because...
I'm not sharing.
Not now, not ever.
I've moved heaven and earth to get here.
I've dedicated years of my life
to this cause.
You have no idea.
So as soon as you're healthy enough,
I suggest you go back to that cushy,
little mansion of yours and never return.
Or else.
Are we clear?
Yeah.
Good morning. Feeling better?
- Yeah.
- My friend came by with the antibiotics.
Gave them to you while you were out.
Hey, that guy...
- Did I...?
- Kill him?
Nah. But you knocked him out.
Dragged him to the edge of Sketch Alley
and dumped him on the curb.
Someone will find him.
But you need to get home.
Well, I can't yet.
And why is that?
Something happened to me in New York.
I know it's something horrible,
I just can't remember what.
I keep getting these... delusions.
They're like images or memories, maybe.
And I, uh...
I just know I can't go home
until I... figure it out.
Sounds like you know
where you're going, then.
My name is not... Henry, it's...
- Jughead. I know.
- You knew?
Well, not right away
but I figure you had your reasons.
I'm so sorry,
for everything that happened. I...
- I wish I would have done something.
- You were a kid.
There's nothing you could have done.
Now, you just focus on yourself.
Find your way back
from wherever it is you've been.
Thanks, Doc.
I'll come back and see you.
Oh, my God.
How many days did we sleep through?
A week and a half, it feels like.
Oh, my gosh.
Did I give Jessica Jughead's manuscript?
You did. Yep.
And you played his message.
The message for us.
Oh, God.
It's okay, Betty. It is a...
secret amongst friends.
And, look, I know
we haven't found Jughead, but, um...
what you're doing,
looking for those missing girls?
I wanna help.
I appreciate that, Tabitha.
Speaking of messages...
It's Jughead.
Is he okay? What's he saying?
Oh, God. Where to start?
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I haven't called.
I'm just sorry for everything.
If you blame yourself
about me wandering off, don't.
I was high out of my mind.
I'm fine. I'm safe, more or less.
I'm heading to New York.
There's something I need to confront.
I'm not sure what, but I wouldn't
have gotten this far without you.
When I get back to Riverdale,
maybe we can finish that dance. Okay.