The science fiction writer
Arthur C. Clarke
said this about aliens,
"Two possibilities exist.
Either, we are alone
in the universe
or we're not.
-Both are equally terrifying."
Mom, come on.
It's almost time for the game.
Polly's out there, Mom.
We don't even know if that was
her blood on the phone booth.
She called us
from that booth a half hour
before we got there.
Who else's blood would it be?
We'll find out
when the FBI calls me back
with their analysis.
Maybe you should get back
into your support group
with all of those other moms.
All right. Bring it in.
We lost again.
We totally could've been
practicing for regionals,
instead of wasting
our time here.
I couldn't agree more,
Cassandra.
Could not agree more.
All right, guys,
that was another tough one.
But the Baxter High Ravens
are number two in the league.
You guys fought hard out there.
Keep fighting. We're gonna
break through. All right?
While I do believe
Coach Andrews
is the best motivator
a Gridiron Gang could ask for,
as your de facto team owner,
what can I do
to incentivize you?
How about ten grand
to whichever Bulldog
scores first this season?
All right?
You okay, Derek?
I'll be all right.
It just sucks to lose, Coach.
I'm giving it my all.
I hear you, man.
There was
no better player than you
out on that field today.
Seriously,
what do we do?
Push them more?
I'm already
running them ragged.
Not to mention,
there's zero fan support.
The Bulldogs were supposed
to inspire the town
and Riverdale was supposed
to rally behind the Bulldogs,
but no one even comes
to our games.
In that case,
I'll get the town to back
our Bulldogs again.
You just keep those kids
motivated, Coach.
What about me?
Don't coaches
need motivation too?
Chin up, Andrews.
And the incidents,
they go back decades, Samm.
There's dozens of people
seeing things
they can't explain.
There's even support groups.
Slow down, Jones.
You're writing
about aliens now?
Yeah, but it's
not just about aliens.
It's about personal trauma.
And if I'm right,
it's about a town's
collective trauma.
Could you please just take
the idea to Scribners?
Y-Yeah, I'll let you know
what they say.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Tabitha.
How do you feel about Pop's
hosting a pancake breakfast
so that folks
can mix and mingle
with the new and improved
Riverdale Bulldogs?
Sounds fun.
And if it brings in
warm bodies, then great.
Amazing!
And what if, hypothetically,
Pop's became
the official sponsor
of the Bulldogs?
Let's give it a shot.
I like supporting underdogs.
I will express order
the pancake mix and the syrup.
Oh, no. No.
Don't order the syrup.
I have
a special supplier for that.
I'm sorry, but I cannot donate
my precious maple resource
to help fund that collection
of tatterdemalions
you call
a football team, Archie.
Moreover,
the Vixens can no longer,
in good conscience,
continue cheering for
the bad news Bulldogs.
Cheryl, please.
Just stick around
for one more game
and maybe help get
some more people in the stands.
My Vixens are cheerleaders,
not boosters, Archie.
Fine. I'll do it myself.
Hi, Ms. Bell
Can you turn this on, please?
Attention, everyone.
This is Coach Andrews.
You may not know this,
but a bunch of your classmates
are out there
busting their asses
on the football field
to represent this school
and to represent
each and every one of you.
So why don't you all
show some school spirit
and support your team.
Starting with...
the free pancake breakfast
that Pop's is hosting
tomorrow morning.
Give them your support.
And, hell...
you might even get something
out of it yourselves.
And what about the Vixens?
One more game.
I'll even come out
of retirement
to give the people something
they'd actually like to see.
Namely, moi.
But first,
there's something broken
I need to fix.
Don't forget to turn in
your short story assignments
on the way out, guys.
Thank you.
Good job. Thank you.
Glen.
Did you get the blood results
from the phone booth back?
I did.
The recovered blood
is AB-negative.
The rarest type.
Under one percent
of the population.
And a match for Polly.
So, she... She's really...
I'm so sorry, Betty.
No, you're not.
If you had cared at all
about me or my sister,
you would have done something
to help me.
Betty, look,
I realize you're upset--
Screw you, Glen.
I must admit,
it is a bit disturbing.
Waldo, a kid is held captive
by mole people.
Only to escape
and be abducted by
a family of mothmen
who operate on him
in a spaceship,
in graphic detail.
Doesn't it ring
any alarm bells for you?
But the child survives.
He's found on the side
of the highway.
What do we know about Lerman?
Well, he's a good student,
average grades.
Is there any trouble at home?
He has sustained
a substantial number
of injuries.
A broken arm, a black eye,
was on crutches for a while.
I know what you're thinking,
Mr. Jones,
but I spoke to Lerman
and his parents.
They couldn't be nicer people.
So what?
He's just accident prone?
And then what about this story?
Some kids get hurt a lot.
And, yes...
sometimes a story
is just a story.
Order up.
Behold. 'Tis the nectar
of the gods.
Amazing!
Thank you again.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
We're feeling optimistic
about the rest of the season,
Mrs. Davis.
And your son plays
a huge part in that.
Which is why, Derek,
-I want you to be
captain of the team.
And what's the team gonna do
for my son, Coach Andrews?
Uh, I'm not sure I understand.
Derek's a damn good player.
And football could be
his ticket out of this town.
-He could get a scholarship--
-Mom, chill!
I have to think
of my son's future, Coach.
Not just your team's.
Excuse me.
No, I understand.
So sorry to interrupt.
Coach, we have a situation.
I take it you didn't come
for the hotcakes, Reginald?
No.
I'm here on behalf of
the Greater Rockland County
High School Football League.
The eight other teams
in the conference
and our commissioner saw fit
to send me as a representative.
We're all in agreement.
We'd like for the Bulldogs
to withdraw from the league
like... yesterday.
You guys, uh, suck.
Screw you, Reggie.
Riverdale has a right to play.
Come on, Andrews.
The Bulldogs are
an embarrassment.
They're tainting
the league's prestige.
So, can we tell the league
you're withdrawing?
Like hell.
I want the names
of every member of
this so-called league.
Doesn't it kill you, Coach?
To watch the Bulldogs
lose week after week.
Yeah. Well, it's not
all about winning, Reg.
Keep telling
yourself that, loser.
Loser. Loser. Loser.
Y-You want to talk about it?
A few days ago,
you were getting married
and having a kid,
and now, uh...
Now we're moving you out.
It was my decision, you know.
Maybe you're right, Dad.
Maybe...
I'm not the kind of guy
who deserves a family.
Hold on, now.
You, you don't really believe
that you don't deserve
happiness now, do you?
You know what, Dad,
I actually don't want
to talk about it.
Given how invested you are
in seeing Riverdale High fail
on all fronts,
I find it hard to believe
you're not behind
the league's attempt
to oust the Bulldogs.
All I know about the Bulldogs
is that they're garbage
and that they haven't even
scored this season.
They will against
your precious Stallions.
Oh, please.
We'll be wiping Bulldog blood
off our cleats for weeks.
You seem so sure.
How about a wager?
Ooh. What are the terms?
If your Stallions
keep my Bulldogs
off the scoreboard,
we'll withdraw
from the league, voluntarily.
If, however, we do score,
you'll have to convince
your good friend,
the commissioner,
and his legion of doom,
to stop trying
to muscle out the Bulldogs.
I will take that bet.
Great.
Hey, Lerman.
Could you hang back for a sec?
Story is great.
It's very vivid, it's intense.
I wanted to ask you
what inspired it.
Uh, just a series
of dreams I had.
Really? Recurring?
Yes. Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
Now some experts believe that
stories about aliens
and the like
are really about traumas
that people have experienced
and that these stories
are cries for help.
What? What do you...
What do you mean?
I mean,
is this story real, Lerman?
Any part of it?
Did someone hurt you?
Like what you wrote about
or tie you up,
or keep you locked up?
Mr. Jones...
it's just a story. Okay?
I...
I never should've
written it. I'm sorry.
Sorry. I have to go.
Sweet cousin,
what a surprise.
Any news on your fair sister?
Yeah. As a matter of fact,
that's why I'm here, Cheryl.
When Jason first disappeared,
for a long time,
no one knew where he was
or what had happened to him.
But when you learned
that he had died,
was it helpful
to know the truth?
To say it was soul-crushing
would be an understatement.
So what if you'd never
learned the truth?
If you had had hope
that he might still be alive?
When I learned the truth,
I was able to grieve
for my brother.
From my experience,
it is better to know the truth
and make your peace with it.
Does this mean Polly's...
I don't know what
it's gonna do to my mom.
What's going on?
Why aren't you guys
dressed for practice?
Derek transferred.
He got recruited to play
for Stonewall Prep.
We're doomed.
As much as
I hate Stonewall Prep,
I can't blame Derek.
Enrolling there,
playing for the Stallions.
It's his best shot at college.
And they're a team
that wins games.
The Bulldogs will be, too.
You've only
just re-launched them.
Not to mention,
we're down a player.
The league won't even let us
on the field with ten.
It seems to me
like the Bulldogs
just need a little motivation.
Something to
get them energized.
Luckily...
I just came up
with one of my genius ideas
that will rally the troops
and maybe even
recruit some new ones.
Mom.
We got the blood results back.
Is it Polly's?
No.
No, it was O-positive.
It wasn't a match.
Oh, thank God!
Thank God!
Oh, thank you, Betty.
Hey, you're awake.
Perfect timing.
I ordered a platter
of cold cuts from Pop's.
Would you mind running
to get it?
What's happening?
Oh, I decided
you were right about me
getting back into
the support group.
I'm hosting today.
Would you mind running
to get the cold cuts?
Yeah. No. Of course.
What's the buzz, Waldo?
It was him?
Mr. Jones,
these are the Logans.
Lerman's parents.
Oh, hi.
They've come in to discuss
a conversation you had
with their son.
In what world, Mr. Jones,
do you think
that it's appropriate
to encourage
these wild fantasies
that Lerman is obsessed with?
Death and aliens
and underground monsters?
What's wrong with you?
Well, I'm sorry.
I'd figured
it was my responsibility
as Lerman's teacher.
The story he wrote...
might've been alluding
to some troubles at home.
Then why didn't you come to us?
Instead, you ambush our child?
Mr. and Mrs. Logan,
Mr. Jones' behavior
was wildly inappropriate.
But I can promise you
that it will never
happen again.
Oh, we know it won't,
because we don't want him
teaching our child.
Now, wait.
I didn't reach out to your so--
Not a problem at all.
We'll move Lerman
to another English class.
How dare you break protocol
in such a reckless manner!
I told you, I had already
vetted the Logans.
I know. No. I'm sorry. I...
I felt like something was off.
My instinct was telling me
something strange was going on.
One more misstep...
I mean,
even just a little one...
and you're done at my school.
Kevin. Fangs.
Thank you both for agreeing
to this tete-a-tete.
Toni may never forgive me,
but I will never forgive myself
if I don't try to repair
what my antics
have torn asunder.
Namely, hashtag Kangs.
Your games brought up
deeper issues between
Kevin and I.
-Agreed.
-See? Consensus.
Go on, Fangs.
You've never been all in,
Kevin.
Y-You've always,
always held back.
And I don't know
if that's because of me
or if it's because
you're ashamed of being gay.
I am not ashamed
of being gay.
Dude, you go to the woods,
you hook up
with anonymous strangers.
You don't want to be
in a real relationship
with a real gay guy.
Fangs, don't.
You're not me.
You don't know
my experience, okay?
We were about
to get married, Kevin.
I want to know
everything about you,
the good and the bad.
I think it's too late for that.
-Kevin, please.
I gotta go.
Cheryl, please butt out
of our lives.
What? Are you having a party
and I wasn't invited?
No. Um, it's for
my mom's support group.
How's she doing?
there've been... developments
in Polly's case.
Um, apparently,
the blood they recovered
at the phone booth
is a match for hers.
Which means
most likely that, um...
Oh, God. Betty, I'm so sorry.
And the worst part is,
she disappeared four weeks ago,
which means she has
or had been alive
that entire time,
somewhere along
the Lonely Highway.
So I just didn't do enough.
Hey, I actually met
someone that lives on
the Lonely Highway.
I mean,
he's kind of an eccentric kook,
but he sees a lot of
what goes on out there.
Maybe he might've seen
or heard something
about the missing girls.
If you want,
I can put this tray on ice,
and I can...
take you to go meet him.
-Yeah.
-Yeah?
All right. Bring it in.
What's the point
in practicing, Coach?
We don't even have
enough players anymore.
Bulldogs are a team, Britta.
We play for each other
and for the love of the game.
Yoo-hoo! Got room for one more?
Bulldogs, I wanna introduce you
to a friend of mine
who plays professional football
for a little team
called the New York Goliaths.
-Holy crap!
It's T Dub!
Wow! It's a pleasure
to meet you, bro.
You're one hell of a player.
Oh, man. I appreciate it.
Heard you're one hell
of a coach.
How are you even here?
Ronnie and I go way back.
T Dub was one of
my most loyal clients
when I was selling jewelry
in New York.
Hey. Uh, is it cool
if I say a few words
to the team?
Yeah, please.
Some of you might've seen me
play for the Goliaths,
but my career started off
in a small town
just like Riverdale,
with a coach who pushed me
to be what I could be.
He believed in me.
Just like Coach Andrews
believes in you.
But you gotta be the ones
to make it happen on the field.
You're not underdogs.
You're the damn Bulldogs!
Yeah!
Y'all ready to prove
these haters wrong?
Yeah!
You must be Britta.
Heard you got a cannon.
Come on. Let's see.
This might be the shot
in the arm we needed, Ronnie.
I just wish T Dub
could suit up for us.
We're still short a player.
Oh, Archiekins, not for long.
Behold, a group
of Bulldogs-to-be.
Hey...
-who wants to play football?
We have a problem.
The interest in the Bulldogs
is growing, not waning.
I do not want people
rallying around this team
or that school
or that town.
I want you to target
their weakest link
and knock some heads.
We don't need to go there.
We're still gonna
crush the Bulldogs
on the field
fair and square. Easy.
Your loyalty lies with me.
At Stonewall.
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
break some kid's legs
for no reason.
Yeah.
Consider yourself benched,
Reggie.
I'll be leading Stallions
into battle against
Riverdale High.
So be it.
I'll be standing
with the Bulldogs, then.
What were you doing
out here?
Just working on a book.
So, the old-timer
that owns this place
has been here for decades.
Mr. Dreyfuss, hi.
-Jughead Jones,
you remember me?
-'Course I do.
Great. This is Betty Cooper.
She's a friend of mine,
from the FBI.
-We were hoping that you could
help us with an investigation.
-Come on up.
We're
one hundred percent certain
that my sister made a call
from the payphone
on the Lonely Highway.
But when we got there,
it was destroyed.
Shredded? Like a tin can?
Exactly, yeah.
Have you seen that before?
Back in the summer of '77.
And again in '82.
I know what happened
to your sister.
She's had an encounter.
Yes, right.
But... But with who?
The mothmen.
I'm sorry. The mothmen?
What makes you say that?
The phone booth.
You see,
their ships use
anti-matter fusion reactors
that create
a gravity field that, uh,
that allows them to levitate,
like, like a balloon.
But anything that gets caught
in that stasis,
well, it gets crushed,
like it's made
out of papier-mache.
I knew our friends
were back in town.
I've been pickin' up
their chatter on my radios.
That was a colossal
waste of time.
Look, a lot of people
believe this stuff.
And there is some evidence.
My sister went missing, Jug.
She was taken by someone.
Not some thing.
What are you even saying?
I'm saying that things happen,
especially in Riverdale,
that you and I can't explain.
Sometimes, there isn't
a logical explanation.
-Sometimes,
unexplained phenomenon--
-No, someone is...
kidnapping, torturing,
and murdering women,
that's not a phenomenon.
It's just pure evil.
But I'll be damned if I let it
happen to anyone else.
Can you hurry up?
I need to get back
to Riverdale.
Because I care about you.
You don't live here.
You deserted us.
Okay, being a real sister
doesn't mean coming in
for one day and telling me
how to live my life.
Especially when you don't know anything about it.
My daughter is alive!
-She called--
Betty, you
have to help me.
I don't know,
I ran as fast as I could.
You have to come get me.
Polly, I wanna tell you
that I love you,
and that I'm here for you,
just please, please,
please come home.
Hey, how's it going?
Good, good.
I haven't seen you
in here before.
My name's Shane.
I'm visiting from LA.
Ah. Well...
I guess it's true
what they say about LA guys.
Oh, what's that?
That they're... hot.
And what to they say
about guys from Riverdale?
Why don't you tell me?
-What the hell are you doing?
-Oh.
Uh, I'm sorry.
I must've misread
the situation. I thought--
-You thought I was like you?
-No.
-You thought I wanted you?
You think I came here
to be groped
by your pathetic ass.
No, no--
-What the hell?
-Hey! What are you doing?
Saving your life,
whether you want it
saved or not.
Get the hell out of here.
You're leaving
these girls alone,
and you're never
coming back here again.
Hey, these girls are the ones
looking to trick.
Tell your dirtbag friends
the party's over.
Put a little ice on it.
These bruises will settle down
in a few days.
You keep those cuts clean.
-Thanks, Dad.
-You're a grown man.
And as your father...
I'm terrified for you
right now.
What's going on, son?
I think...
I'm ashamed of myself...
of being gay.
Is this something
that... that I did?
No.
No, Dad. No.
It isn't your fault, okay?
You've... you've always
accepted me.
You've never judged me.
-But, Mom--
-What? What happened?
There was this one time...
we were
back-to-school shopping.
And she made
some offhand comment.
Like, about needing
to buy me...
husky clothes.
I don't know.
Man, I just felt...
like, so ashamed.
So, I, uh...
I told her I was meeting Betty.
And I went to Fox Forest...
to be alone.
I didn't even know
it was a cruising spot.
And there was this
other guy there,
and he was telling me
I was cute...
or whatever.
And it was like...
all the stuff Mom said,
just washed away.
And ever since then,
I... I've been cruising.
It's like I'm hardwired
this way,
or something.
I don't know.
Get out. Now.
You--
-You're not Patty.
-No, I'm her sister.
You can't do this.
You can't arrest me again.
You let me go.
You got nothing on me.
You're right, John.
I'm not gonna arrest you.
But you are coming with me.
Waldo, what's going on?
Jughead, is Lerman with you?
What?
No, definitely not.
I've been steering clear
with him. Why?
His parents just called me.
They think Lerman ran away.
Any idea where he might be?
Oh, God, no.
I haven't talked to him.
Tell the Logans that I'm
calling in some help, okay?
Come on.
Please don't do this.
I told you.
I don't know where Patty is.
What? Why are you doing this?
-You really
have to ask me that?
You are still preying
on these girls.
Exactly the same way
you preyed on Polly.
I have a family.
I had a sister.
No one looked out
for those girls.
No one was protecting them.
I couldn't even protect Polly.
But I can deliver justice.
-Jughead?
-Betty. Hey,
this is an emergency.
One of my student is missing,
and I think
he's on the Lonely Highway.
I'm on the highway.
I'm ten miles north of town.
I'm leaving
from town right now.
I'll meet you halfway.
-Who is it?
-Lerman Logan, he's 14.
I'm on my way.
I'll send someone
to come untie you tomorrow.
If I remember.
Here are
the Stonewall Stallions
versus the Riverdale Bulldogs.
Let's go.
Go. Go.
Lerman. Thank God.
Yeah, he was walking
on the shoulder in a daze.
You okay, bud?
Mr. Jones...
did it happen again?
Thank you
for finding Lerman.
We'd hoped you wouldn't
have to go through this again.
-Again?
-Yeah, Lerman is a sleepwalker.
Has been since he was little.
We thought he grew out of it,
but, uh...
then he started
hurting himself.
He walked into a door.
Another time,
he burned his hand
on the stove.
Even fell out of a window once
and broke his arm.
So, we started locking
his bedroom door at night.
Now, we gave him
the whole basement
to himself.
We just... We made sure
he was safe.
So you were the "Mole People"
who were keeping him locked up.
All we've done is try our best
to protect him.
I remember we were so terrified
after that morning
we found the front door open
and, and...
Lerman was just gone.
That whole week,
we thought we lost my boy.
No, wait. He left
in the middle of the night
and was missing for a week?
Where did he go?
What happened to him?
A good Samaritan
found him wandering
the Lonely Highway...
with no memory
of the prior week.
That's why we were so upset
with you, Mr. Jones.
We thought your questioning
might trigger...
Well, something
like this happening.
God only knows
what draws him to that highway.
I don't think
it's a coincidence, Jug.
Polly and Lerman both end up
on the Lonely Highway? No way.
I agree. But what are
the other connections?
When Polly escaped
and made that phone call,
my mom said,
she described being in
what sounded like
an alien spaceship.
Seriously?
They could've been abducted
by the same person.
Why would they keep Polly
but let Lerman go?
Well, maybe he escaped.
Which is why
we need to find out
what Lerman knows
about that missing week.
Yeah, we're going to have to
exhaust every possible option
no matter how insane
it might seem.
♪ You're the one that
♪ I've been waiting for
♪ Gotta quit this crying
♪ Nobody's gonna heal me
♪ If I don't open the door
♪ Kinda hard to believe
♪ Gotta have faith in me
♪ Freak out, freak out
Freak out, freak out ♪
♪ Look at me
♪ Get down, get down
Get down, get down ♪
♪ Look at me
♪ Freak out, freak out
Freak out, freak out ♪
♪ Look at me now
♪ 'Cause all I ever
Wanted was love ♪
♪ All I ever wanted was love
♪ I want your
Stupid love, love ♪
♪ I don't need a reason
♪ Not sorry
I want your stupid love ♪
♪ I want your
Stupid love, love ♪
♪ We got a stupid love, love
♪ I want your
Stupid love, love ♪
Bring it in.
Come on, bring it in.
Bring it in. Bring it in.
Circle up. Circle up.
Circle up, come on.
Look at me.
Hey, look at me. Don't worry
about the scoreboard.
I don't care what it says.
You guys are playing
with heart.
You're leaving it
all out there.
That is all I could ever
ask from you.
But listen,
this is your moment.
The whole town is behind you.
The people in those stands
are here for you!
Your teammates
I'm here for you!
And we're not gonna give up
on each other.
If you don't give up
on yourself,
then guess what?
You can't lose.
If you don't give up
on yourself,
you cannot lose.
This game is not over.
Keep your head up.
Let's go out there
and make something happen.
Let's make this a night
we'll remember forever.
This game is not over.
Come on, bring it in.
-Britta, on you.
-Bulldogs, on three!
One, two, three!
-Bulldogs!
-Get out there, and make
something happen. Come on!
♪ It's the quiet
In the distance ♪
Let's go, Bulldogs!
♪ The static in the shadows
♪ And the thunder from afar ♪
♪ And it comes
Without warning ♪
♪ It comes without warning
Now.
Left. Hut!
♪ Ooh, you better run
Go, go, go, go!
♪ There's no time
To think it over ♪
To change your mind ♪
♪ You better run
♪ It's the weight
Above the footsteps ♪
♪ And the clouds
Of ash and dust ♪
♪ The will, the faith
-♪ The power
♪ To do what must be done
♪ You better run
♪ Ooh, you better run
♪ There's no time
To think it over ♪
To change your mind ♪
♪ You better run
Archie!
Heck of a game, Coach.
Yeah? What game
were you watching?
Well, the Bulldogs
may not have triumphed
on the scoreboard,
but I'd say we've started
to win over the hearts
and minds of the town.
And thanks
to a little side wager
with my father,
the rest of the league
will no longer demand
that we withdraw.
Ronnie for the win.
I, just, uh...
I just wanted to say,
good game, Coach.
Hey. Thanks, Derek.
You played great out there.
What do you think, Ronnie?
Kid's got wheels, huh?
He sure does.
Just remember. Keep working.
Keep getting better.
I promise I will, Coach.
Just like you taught me.
Waldo, this is becoming
sort of a regular thing
for us?
So it seems.
But I just wanted
to let you know
that Lerman's parents
have pulled him out of school.
They've left Riverdale.
My God. Where'd they go?
They left me a message,
but no forwarding address
or contact information.
I suppose they wanted
a fresh start.
Yeah. Don't we all?
Hey, what's wrong?
Agent Cooper.
Glen, what's going on?
I came to check on you.
Why is my mom upset?
Because you...
You lied to me.
Elizabeth, you made me
feel like she might
still be out there.
That there might still be hope!
You told your mother
that the blood
in the phone booth
wasn't a match
for your sister's?
Mom,
I'm so sorry.
-Don't.
How could you? How dare you!
I can't imagine
what you must be going through,
Mrs. Cooper.
But I want you to know that
I will be personally
taking over this case.
No. I'm working
this case, Glen.
This is my sister!
I'll make sure that this
investigation is handled
thoroughly, by the book.
I'll leave no stone unturned.