BRANDON F.: First to five
points to win.
(ball bouncing)
KIM: Let it bounce.
KOURTNEY: Khloe...
KIM: Aah! Ha! Yes!
KHLOE: When Kim points and
does this, it's too funny.
KIM: What's the score?
BRANDON F.: Four-one...
Well, it's now one-four-one,
your serve.
KHLOE (quietly): What?
KIM: Four-one.
So we're four, you're one.
KHLOE: What the (bleep) are
you counting?
KIM: We have our own method.
KHLOE: Kourtney, be ready.
MALIKA: Come on, Keeks.
KHLOE: You got this, Kourt.
I believe in you, girl.
BRANDON F.: Good.
Come to the line. Come up here.
KIM: Malika, I got it.
KOURTNEY: Khloe.
KHLOE: Go for it.
KOURTNEY: Whoo!
KIM: Get it!
KHLOE: (shrieks) Kourtney!
(indistinct chatter, whooping)
KIM: No, that's no point.
I served. You didn't serve.
KHLOE: Then we would've won
by now. (Kim and Khloe shouting)
MALIKA: Sportsmanship out the
window.
♪ ♪
KIM: Wait, do we take our
shoes off, or it's okay?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, probably.
KRIS: Okay.
(quietly): Hi.
KOURTNEY: So, the tea is from
2,000-year-old trees in China.
(laughs) I might be saying this
wrong. Is that right?
SHIVA: Some are, uh, hundreds
of years and some can be
thousands, yes.
And the tea acts like, sort of
like a medicine, so it sort of
works on you wherever you need
it. And it's-it's a form of
meditation. ♪ ♪
KIM: I'm really into this.
KOURTNEY: When Kendall and I
did it, we were like, "We are in
the best moods," like, "We're
ready to start the day."
KIM: I hope this is what our
trip is about, spiritual
awakening. >> KRIS: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Next week, we're
going on a trip to Bali.
SHIVA: Oh, you are?
Beautiful. Well, that's gonna be
the ultimate place.
KOURTNEY: We have decided to
go to Bali for our family
vacation.
I think we're gonna do a lot of
stuff like this... tea ceremony,
connect with yourself and
breathe and, like, sit in
silence with your thoughts.
KIM: Is Kendall coming?
KOURTNEY: To the trip? No.
KRIS: Kanye'll come?
KIM: He's in Chicago working
on his album, so...
KRIS: Hmm.
I think it'll be fun if Scott
goes.
KOURTNEY: Okay, but that's up
to me.
Do you remember Costa Rica?
KIM: You're gonna (bleep) die.
KHLOE: What?
KIM: Scott flew out a girl.
KHLOE: On our family trip
with the kids?!
KIM: With the kids.
KOURTNEY: I haven't invited.
Scott on the trip, and I feel
hesitant to invite him, because
after the last family trip he
was on, you know, he flew out a
girl on the trip, and... I'm
just not looking to have that
again.
That was the last family trip,
and then I banned him.
SHIVA: Well, Bali will be
beautiful. KOURTNEY: Thank you.
KRIS: Thank you so much.
KOURTNEY: I'm definitely
looking for a drama-free,
spiritual vacation.
KRIS: You don't have any
extra rugs anywhere, do you,
Kourt? >> KOURTNEY: Yeah. Why?
KRIS: I need one for, um...
a room at MJ's.
KOURTNEY: How is she feeling?
KRIS: The test was
inconclusive.
We're gonna have another scan
done on Monday.
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: We'll see where to go
then.
KOURTNEY: Is it cancer?
KRIS: We don't know.
My mom hasn't been feeling very
well lately, and has been
diagnosed with pneumonia and has
an underlying mass under the
pneumonia, and they really can't
quite figure out what it is.
This is why I wanted her up here
to Calabasas, so I can pop in
and see her and make sure she's
okay.
Like, yesterday she had such a
lack of energy...
KOURTNEY: Mm-hmm.
KRIS: That she said she
could barely brush her hair.
It's just...
heartbreaking, you know? ♪ ♪
SCOTT: Look at this bad boy.
I'm feeling this whole item.
KRIS: Kourtney gave me
something like this that lights
up, and she puts on her face...
SCOTT: Oh, that white one?
Yeah, the kids are scared of it.
KRIS: Oh.
Speaking of Kourtney...
SCOTT: You bring Kourtney up
quite a bit, you know.
KRIS: I do?
SCOTT: Yeah, I'm just trying
to shop here.
KRIS: This is cute.
SCOTT: That's cute for Poosh.
KRIS: It is cute for Poosh.
Have you guys talked about going
on the family vacation together?
SCOTT: No, you know how she
is; She tries to hide that sort
of thing from me as if there's
things that are exciting, she
doesn't always love to include
me. KRIS: We're going around the
world.
It takes 24 hours to get to
where we're going.
And that's a huge big trip to go
on without their dad.
SCOTT: Yeah. I agree.
Obviously, the kids, I think,
assume that I would be going.
They don't really know.
KRIS: Right.
SCOTT: So I don't want to,
like, break it to them and say
I'm not going and then I am.
KRIS: Yeah.
SCOTT: And I also don't want
to put her in a weird position.
KRIS: Yeah.
SCOTT: But to me, we're both
mature enough at this point,
we're able to be around each
other, there's no reason that
we can spend time together at
home but not travel.
KRIS: Right.
Bali is been on my bucket list
for the longest time, and
everybody who's been to Bali
has just raved about it.
I'm really hoping that Scott can
come on the trip, because
there's nothing better than the
entire family getting together
and being on a family vacation.
Who do you feel comfortable
enough to talk to about this?
SCOTT: Probably Kim.
KRIS: Who might have a
really good perspective on...
SCOTT: Kim. KRIS: How Kourtney's
feeling? Okay.
So why don't we ask Kim what her
suggestion is. Right?
Oh. My people.
SCOTT: Uh-oh. Is there
anything you don't have here?
KRIS: I don't have any of the
new stuff.
SCOTT: Oh-ho-ho, poor you!
KRIS: This is cute.
SCOTT: Wow.
SALESWOMAN: And then you
just slip it... there you go.
SCOTT: That's insane.
KRIS: It's a muff.
SCOTT: You look like you're
gonna kill somebody.
KRIS: I love this.
SCOTT: What is that?
KRIS: And it hides your
stomach at the same time.
SALESWOMAN: Exactly.
SCOTT: This just makes me
think of a big old horse having
sex with this thing. KRIS: What?
(laughs): Oh, stop it!
(horse neighs)
♪ ♪
PHOTOGRAPHER: Wow. Yes.
Good. So gorgeous.
KIM: I like them... like,
strawberry in my teeth.
WOMAN: You like that?
(photographer laughs)
PHOTOGRAPHER: Move the chin
down a little bit. Yeah.
KIM: So, I'm working.
A friend of mine texted me and
was like, "Oh, you're moving to
Chicago?" and I was like, "No,
Kanye's just spending time
there."
Then someone else texted to me
with the link.
KANYE (on video): So, the
first thing on my mind that I
have to tell you is I got to
let y'all know that I'm moving
back to Chicago.
I'm never leaving again.
(crowd cheering)
LARSA (on phone): It's all
over the Internet.
KIM: Oh, my God.
That is so insane that he didn't
tell me.
I know Kanye really loves being
in Chicago, but I had no idea he
wants to move there, until I
hear about it on social media.
I'm a little bit annoyed.
We have to talk about this.
TRACY (on phone): Are you
guys having a full-blown photo
shoot? >> KIM: Yeah.
I'm on set right now.
TRACY: Oh, sorry, I didn't
mean to kill your vibe.
KIM: I have to get there in
person and see face-to-face
what's really going on.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, don't press any of that.
Hey. North?
I'm literally trying the best
that I can to be there for
everyone, and sometimes I'm just
like, "Oh, my..."
Like, I just need a minute.
KRIS: How are you feeling, Mom?
MJ: Talk to the doctor?
KRIS: Yes, I did.
He said that he should have a
result by Tuesday.
Not knowing what's going on with
MJ is incredibly upsetting.
♪ ♪
KANYE: Social media is fun,
to put up stuff and share with
people.
KIM: The thing that set me
off was, okay, that just should
have been a conversation before
I see on the Internet you're
moving to Chicago. I find out...
KANYE: No, no, I told you
that before.
We had that conversation.
KIM: Not a serious
conversation.
KANYE: It was a con... Any
conversation I have is serious.
I don't joke. I don't play.
KIM: You said we were gonna
move into your mom's house, with
all of our kids, in a
one-bedroom, and I thought, "Oh",
we'll stay there for, like, two
weeks, and we can do that and
live in the house," and so I go,
"Oh, okay," and...
KANYE: I'm sure I'll have
more than one home in Chicago.
We'll have more than one home
in Chicago.
KIM: Well, I didn't know that.
I didn't think that was serious.
I get that Kanye's really
excited about Chicago.
He just needs a change of scene.
I totally respect that.
But I can't really imagine
moving to Chicago.
I-I did not think that that was
serious.
KANYE: You don't be taking me
seriously...
KIM: So, my bad for not
taking you seriously.
KANYE: We're moving to.
Chicago. That's the vibe, babe.
It feels good.
KIM: I think I'm gonna kind
of ride it out and see it
through, 'cause, you know, with
him, I just always want to make
sure that this is what he wants
to do, then we can make a real
informed decision.
We're gonna miss our flight.
KANYE: What you mean y'all
gonna miss y'all flight?
It's private.
KIM: They said we couldn't
leave past a certain time 'cause
they have another flight.
(Kanye laughing)
♪ ♪
SCOTT: Aw, cute.
KIM: So cute, right?
SCOTT: Those look very artsy.
KIM: It's me laying down in a
bathtub. >> KRIS: I love this!
I want this... I need this in
black and white.
KIM: Ew!
SCOTT: That's, like, PG-13.
KRIS: At least you don't have
the handcuffs on.
KHLOE: Hi, everyone. KRIS: Hey!
SCOTT: All right, mates,
let's hit the table.
KOURTNEY: Hey, guys! Hey!
SCOTT: Hey, Reign.
KOURTNEY: I'm supposed to do
Iris again today.
KHLOE: Who's Iris?
KOURTNEY: The acupuncture,
but it's Reiki.
She, like, burps...
KIM: What is Reiki?
KOURTNEY: She burps the whole
time. >> KIM: She burps on you?!
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
SCOTT: I guess she rubs you
down and is like...
(imitates loud burp)
KOURTNEY: And the first time
I did it, I couldn't stop
laughing.
COREY: She's calling, saying,
"I'm getting the poison out of
you"?
KOURTNEY: Yeah. I'm just
asking, do you think it's, like,
opening yourself up for, like,
bad spirits to enter you?
SCOTT: (laughs) And you start
to feel like this could be real
and you take it in and then
maybe you believe it.
KIM: Kourtney apparently does.
KOURTNEY: Mom, you should do it.
KRIS: No. No. (Laughter)
KOURTNEY: Wait, Mom, you
can't come with us Saturday
night?
KHLOE: What's Saturday night?
KOURTNEY: Sound of Music.
MASON: I'm not going, I'm not
going. >> KOURTNEY: Why?
KIM: You think Mason would
like the Sound of Music
sing-along?
MASON: I want to go to one of.
Ye's concerts.
SCOTT: Well, they're gonna
all be in Chicago now.
MASON: They are?
KIM: I don't know.
He is thinking of moving to.
Chicago.
MASON: You can't move to.
Your whole family's here.
KIM: Well, you tell him.
SCOTT: That's what we're
telling him.
KIM: That is the place that
he grew up, so I can't, you
know...
MASON: Then the whole family
would have to come to... all the
way there for, like, two hours.
KIM: I know. Well, he keeps
saying, "Well, Khloe does it to
Cleveland."
SCOTT: Not 'cause she really
wants to.
KIM: But...
SCOTT: Because of basketball.
KHLOE: Yeah.
KIM: So, he thinks we're
going to give up... this...
SCOTT: You're not serious.
He actually thinks the whole
family can live there?
KIM: Well, no, I think he is
serious.
I mean, Khloe, you've been in
that situation before, moving to.
Cleveland, packing everything
up.
KHLOE: Dallas.
I've done, I've done the moves a
couple times.
KIM: Oh, yeah. Yeah.
KHLOE: The hardest part about
uprooting everything, I mean,
you still have your family.
Your roots are right here.
KIM: Yeah. All of the cousins
won't be together.
KHLOE: I mean, obviously, you
literally can do anything, so
I'm not worried about you.
But, I mean, it's a lot.
♪ ♪
(engine revs)
KIM: What are we buying today?
SCOTT: So, this is, like, the
new 620.
It's dope.
I mean, pretty dope car.
KIM: Yeah.
SCOTT: And then Ferraris.
KIM: I think I like a Ferrari.
SCOTT: Kylie just bought one
of these for your mom.
I don't know if you knew that.
KIM: Oh, really?
SCOTT: As a surprise, so
don't tell her.
KIM: Oh, that's nice.
She'll love that.
After talking to my mom, I came
to Scott's to talk to him about
my brilliant plan to get him
invited on the family trip.
I definitely see Kourtney's
hesitation, but I really do feel
like he's in a different place
now.
And I think we should at least
give it a try.
So, I'm going to New York.
I know it's your hometown.
We're gonna go to SNL.
So I thought this could be,
like, an easy segue and have you
come and then you invite.
Kourtney and be like, "Oh, Kim
mentioned New York."
SCOTT: Ah.
KIM: And it'll go great.
And then we'll be like, "Oh, my
God, wasn't that so much fun?"
Oh, the trip can work out
perfectly."
SCOTT: I'm down.
KIM: I think it would be so
perfect to have a little test
trip to see if everything runs
smoothly.
It'll be the perfect setup for
our family trip.
KOURTNEY (on phone): Hello?
SCOTT: Hey. >> KOURTNEY: Hi.
SCOTT: So, I wanted to ask.
KOURTNEY: Yes.
SCOTT: I'm gonna... Kim wanted
me to go to New York with her
this weekend, and I was thinking
I would probably take Mason to
do, like, a little boys' trip.
But then I was thinking... kind
of feel like it would be nice if
we all went.
KOURTNEY: I mean...
SCOTT: It's quick, too.
And Kanye's doing SNL, so we'll
go to that.
KOURTNEY: Okay.
SCOTT: Yeah, it would be
easy.
We would leave Friday morning,
come back Sunday night.
KOURTNEY: 'Kay. Thank you.
SCOTT: I'll talk to you later.
KOURTNEY: Okay, bye.
KIM: That's so crazy.
(chuckles) >> SCOTT: Yeah.
♪ ♪
I'm, uh, proud of you for being
on time.
KOURTNEY: I was here before Kim.
KIM: Mase, guess what we're
gonna do tomorrow night.
MASON: What?
KIM: Tell me if you want to
come. You don't have to though.
SCOTT: You don't have to.
You might not be interested.
MASON: What is it?
KIM: Kanye and Lil Pump are
gonna perform their song.
MASON: Yeah, I want to go!
KIM: You do? >> MASON: Yeah.
KIM: It's at midnight!
MASON: Oh, I'll still go.
SCOTT: So, what are you
thinking for tonight?
Should we make plans with
everybody?
KOURTNEY: Simon has his, um,
exhibit for his show, A. Human.
So I told Simon I would go to
that.
It closes at 9:00, and this
weekend's the last weekend.
SCOTT: Okay, fun.
So you have your stuff planned.
I guess, um, Mase, we'll go out
to dinner.
And then, late night at the
house, we're having a pizza
party.
KOURTNEY: And then I'm gonna
meet you guys for the pizza
party.
SCOTT: Ooh, the pizza party's
really what it's all about.
Come to me, my jungle boy.
(Reign squeals)
♪ ♪
PHOTOGRAPHER: Beautiful.
Almost cheek to cheek.
MAKEUP ARTIST: I just need to
step in for one second.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Yeah.
DIRECTOR: All right, sound is
speeding.
Quiet all around, please.
ASSISTANT: 101, take one.
Copy, mark.
INTERVIEWER: Khloe, when was
the first time you met Malika?
KHLOE: Actually, my best
friend was a guy and happened to
be Malika's boyfriend.
And he actually loved to keep us
separated, because I'm sure he
knew that we would hit it off
and be best friends.
MALIKA: And that's why he's
no longer in the picture.
KHLOE: (laughs) I would say I
was like, 15, 16 years old, and
we've been inseparable ever
since. Hi, Mom!
KRIS: Hello! KHLOE: Hi, Mom!
KRIS: Hi, guys!
KHLOE: We're just doing our
last Boomerang.
KRIS: Really? Okay.
MALIKA: Are you so excited?
KHLOE: Oh, you're in it?
We can put makeup on Kris.
MAKEUP ARTIST: Yeah, put
makeup on her.
KHLOE: Sit in the middle.
KRIS: Okay. PHOTOGRAPHER: Love.
KHLOE: Why have a mom if you
can't whore her out?
KRIS: Yeah, that's right.
(laughter)
That's what I do best.
MALIKA: Where are my shoes?
KHLOE: Malika, your shoes are
here, if you want them.
MALIKA: Oh, great. Thanks. 'Kay.
(phone rings)
KRIS: Oh. Hey, Mom.
MJ: How are you? KRIS: I'm good.
I'm here with Khloe.
KHLOE: Hi, MJ!
MJ: Hi, Khloe. KHLOE: Hi, MJ!
KRIS: How are you feeling, Mom?
MJ: I'm okay. I made it through.
KRIS: Good girl.
MJ: Talk to the doctor?
KRIS: Yes, I did.
He said that he should have a
result by Tuesday. >> MJ: Okay.
KRIS: MJ had a biopsy on her
lung to try and figure out
what's going on.
MJ: You don't have to come
down Saturday, you know.
My house is a mess and all that.
KRIS: I don't care about your
house, Mom.
I don't care.
I'm not gonna have any makeup
on.
Just gonna come in my sweat suit
and hang out.
MJ: All right. I love you.
KRIS: I love you, too.
Bye. See you Saturday.
MJ: Bye.
KRIS: Not knowing what's
going on with MJ is incredibly
upsetting.
DIRECTOR: Okay, everybody
settle.
KRIS: At this point, I'm
really hoping that I can go to.
Bali, but I can't imagine being
on the other side of the world
and having her need me for one
reason or another.
DIRECTOR: All right, we're
ready to go.
KIM: When are you gonna know
about Bali?
KOURTNEY: I was kind of
waiting to see how this weekend
was.
SCOTT: Is anybody hungry for
real food? All right.
KOURTNEY: Or do we want to
just go back, chill...
SCOTT: Do we want to leave?
Whatever.
KRIS: How was the show?
I haven't seen it.
KIM: SNL?
KRIS: Did he do a rant at the
end?
KIM: At the end, yes, but the
credits were rolling.
I don't know if they'll invite
us back ever. (Chuckles)
♪ ♪
KIM: Northie, do you want to
go get some ice cream and French
fries? >> NORTH: No!
KIM: Listen, we're not gonna
cry.
Come on.
Why don't you go downstairs and
get some food, go get...
NORTH: I don't want to get
some food!
KIM: Well, I'm gonna lose my
mind with this attitude. ♪ ♪
(gasps) Don't go in there.
Don't go in there.
Daddy's recording.
The kids and I have not seen.
Kanye since we were in Chicago.
So our first stop is gonna be to
the studio.
Even though Kanye has Saturday.
Night Live, Kanye goes nonstop.
So he's working on his new album
here in New York.
That's what he likes to do.
And so I'm trying to be, like,
super supportive of all of that.
KANYE: What y'all think
about Nicki on "New Body"?
PRODUCER: I think she, I
think she'd be dope.
KANYE: Yeah, okay.
Send it to her, then.
PRODUCER: Okay.
KANYE: Wait a second.
Kim, you want to send it to her?
KIM: Whatever you want.
KANYE: She asked you.
KIM: She did ask me, "Can."
Kanye send me new music?"
You know, the way Kanye works is
probably a little bit different.
He brings, like, so many
different people from all
different kinds of music, and
just his, like, specialty is
just pulling out the magic from
each person. >> NICKI: Hi, Kim!
KIM: How are you?
NICKI: I missed you.
KANYE: I missed you, too.
NICKI: And thanks for
thinking of me to call.
KANYE: It's like this is
gonna be fire.
NICKI: I'm gonna say some
real-ass (bleep) that bitches
need to hear, too, and that they
want to say and be feeling like
they can't say.
KANYE: That's all we do.
NICKI: (laughs) Okay, let me
start working on this, 'cause
I'm really excited.
And, Kanye, thank you so much.
And, Kim, thank you, my darling!
KIM: Oh, my God, of course. Bye.
NICKI: Thank you. All right.
KIM: Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, don't press any of that.
Hey, North. What did I say?
You can't press the buttons in
this room.
Babe, I think I should take her,
'cause she's getting really
antsy, and I feel like you've
got to focus.
KANYE: Okay. KIM: Bye, guys.
I have some work to do, and I
have to give the kids dinner and
get them back to the hotel.
Guess who's going in Dylan's
candy shop.
If you're a good boy, you can
go. Yeah. Oh, this face?
You're trying to get me with
this face?
Let me see this face.
You know, I'm thinking of.
Chicago, uprooting all the kids.
And I'm literally trying the
best that I can to be there for
everyone, and sometimes I'm just
like, "Oh, my..."
Like, I just need a minute, you
know? You have so much going on.
But then I just try to, like,
roll with it.
Okay, sit in.
I got to buckle you.
NORTH: Why are there lots of
people every day taking pictures
of us? >> KIM: Well, to get very
technical, my name is Kim
Kardashian.
NORTH: No.
KIM: And Daddy is Kanye West.
And Daddy is a singer...
performer... artiste.
Mommy...
has so many talents, I can't
even begin to name them. ♪ ♪
SCOTT: All right, boys and
girls.
How does it feel, first day in
New York?
CHARLI: Feels good.
SCOTT: You have a beard.
Look, I got Abraham Lincoln.
CHRIS: Reign-aham Lincoln.
I love it. REIGN: Taste it, Dad.
(Scott gulps loudly)
SCOTT: It's good.
KIM: Sorry I'm so late, guys.
SCOTT: Oh, this is some
outfit for dinner. >> KIM: Hi.
CHRIS: Hey.
SCOTT: Where are you going?
KIM: Where am I going?
CHARLI: Hi.
KIM: To see you. Greek salad.
Yes, yes, yes to all of this.
SCOTT: So what happened with
the kids?
KIM: My kids are... passed
out. >> SCOTT: Ugh, I know the
feeling. I'm tired myself.
Feels like 2:00 in the morning.
I'm excited to get back to the
room, watch movies with the
kids.
KIM: Scott's turned into,
like, the family man.
It's pretty crazy.
CHRIS: He has.
Did a total 180.
SCOTT: I was young when I
first had the kids.
You know what I mean?
Now I appreciate it and like it
way more.
They're like my best friends.
I'd rather hang out with them
than anybody else.
Think I want to go hang out with
my friends... other than Chris?
"How are you?
Oh, what have you been up to?
You look so good."
"Yeah, I get it. Thanks.
Let's go."
KIM: Having dinner with Scott
and seeing his idea of what,
like, New York is versus, like,
before...
Even, like, a year ago when were
at Fashion Week, he was going
out and not showing up, and it's
so good to see what a different
person Scott is.
SCOTT: We're all gonna get up
early, but I think tonight, we
might have, like, a little pizza
party back at the room.
KIM: I mean, I know that.
Kourtney's not even seeing this
and, like, witnessing how, you
know, amazing Scott's being.
He's just having a good night
with all of his kids and being
such a good dad.
SCOTT: What's the plan tomorrow?
KIM: I don't know.
CHRIS: Saturday Night Live.
I didn't know it ends at 1:00.
SCOTT: Oh, yeah.
So, yesterday, he kept writing
me.
He goes, "So, what night is
Kanye performing on Saturday."
Night Live?"
I go, "Saturday night."
And he goes, "Right, so what
night?"
I go, "SNL."
He goes, "I know what SNL is.
Now what day?"
I go, "Saturday... Night...
Live."
He's like, "I get it, but what
day?"
So then I said, "On Sunday, we
should watch Monday Night
Football."
♪ ♪
KIM: Hey, what are you doing?
KOURTNEY: I'm in the car with.
Mase and Scott. >> SCOTT: Hey.
KOURTNEY: We're on our way
to SNL.
KIM: Okay, cool.
Oh, my God, the studio was crazy
today. >> SCOTT: Oh, my God.
I can imagine. Is he excited?
KIM: I think so. SCOTT: Yeah.
KIM: I think performing's,
like, really easy for him.
SCOTT: Right, it's like
second nature?
KIM: Yeah, so, it's like he
doesn't get nervous.
KOURTNEY: All right, we'll
see you guys.
KIM: Okay, cool. Bye.
I have to be honest.
Inside, I'm kind of freaking out
a little bit, because live TV...
You never know what could
happen.
KOURTNEY: I didn't see his
last SNL.
Were you there? >> SCOTT: Mm-mm.
KOURTNEY: So I'm excited.
SCOTT: I've never been to SNL
ever.
KOURTNEY: I've never been to.
SNL, either.
SCOTT: It's a pretty
legendary show.
KIM: I made a comment to him.
Like, "Oh, so, you guys, it's"
"online that you're staying at
the same hotel," or something
like that. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: And he was like, "No,
no, no, I don't want to, like",
play that game.
We're just really co-parenting,
"and we're, like... I'm not even,
like, focused on that."
SCOTT: If it's a family trip
and everybody's going, of course
I don't want to miss out on
those times.
KOURTNEY: My only hesitation
is just, like, I don't want to,
like, give mixed messages by,
like, all going on a trip
together.
SCOTT: Mixed messages with
what?
♪ ♪
WOMAN: (whoops) SNL!
KIM: I guess they cut it off.
KOURTNEY: Oh, the speech?
KIM: At the end.
That's what I'm seeing here.
KOURTNEY: I'm sure they're
gonna air it at some point.
KIM: I'm sure they're gonna
air it, yeah, on the...
KANYE: What's online? KIM: Yeah.
KANYE: Well, they don't have
to, they don't have to air it
online. KOURTNEY: I was, like...
Mason and I were, like,
cheering, like, going crazy.
KIM: Yeah, I was, too.
SCOTT: SNL was, um, a little
different, but it was cool to
bring my kids there, and it was
fun to hang around, and Mase got
to see a lot of people.
Overall, it was exciting.
It was just, you know, all
happening quick.
KIM: I was listening.
I was trying to listen.
KANYE: And here?
KOURTNEY: Well, I think Kim
gets nervous, 'cause she's like,
"I don't know what's going to
happen right now."
KIM: I always get nervous
like you're my child.
Like-like, if North performs
and she drops the mic and she
doesn't talk, when it's, like,
your loved one, you sit and
you're just like...
I know that Kanye is always
gonna be Kanye, and I'm never
trying to change that.
I mean, that's who I fell in
love with, and I'm not trying to
change who he is.
North, come here.
Let's leave them alone.
Northie, stop. Guys...
North, get out of the window.
NORTH: There's a whole crowd
of people waving at us!
KIM: I know.
Get out of the window.
KOURTNEY: Reign's friendly.
They were like, "We like your"
balloon, Reign."
And Reign was like, "It's a
sword."
KIM: Penelope told her that
they're famous.
KOURTNEY: Yeah, but don't you
think they need to know that a
little?
KIM: Yeah. Maybe not them.
Maybe, like, Mom and Dad, so...
Maybe not those words.
Maybe more like "well-known."
I don't know.
I just never refer to myself as
that.
KOURTNEY: Well, I don't think
I said that, you know.
KIM: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: I think they heard
it from other people at school.
Ooh. Feel this.
KIM: That's cool.
How's, um, everything going,
like, with Scott and everything?
KOURTNEY: It's fine.
KIM: It's good?
Are you guys, like, getting
along?
KOURTNEY: Yeah, no, we always
get along.
I just, um, I feel like he can
easily, like... forget about...
boundaries, so, like, I just
like to do my thing a little.
KIM: Yeah.
I think he knows that.
I made a comment to him.
Like, "Oh, so, you guys, it's"
"online that you're staying at
the same hotel," or something
like that. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: And he was like, "No,
no, no, I don't want to, like",
play that game."
Like, he was like, "We're just
really co-parenting, and we're
like... I'm not even, like,
focused on that."
KOURTNEY: Oh, really?
I mean, I'm really happy that
Kim is saying that Scott's
really focused on the kids, but
it does make me nervous to think
about the dynamic of our
relationship changing again.
The fact that we're hanging
out, if it was when I was in a
relationship, I wouldn't even
think twice about it, but I
think just because I'm somewhat
newly single, like, it's just a
weird feeling. >> KIM: So, wait.
When are you gonna know about
Bali?
Have you made a decision yet?
KOURTNEY: No.
I was kind of waiting
to see how this weekend was.
KIM: Yeah?
After being in New York and how
hectic it is, like, I'm like, I
can't wait to go away and just,
like... (hums) KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KIM: Like... I can't wait.
Just honestly, with the fact
that I have... another baby
coming...
KOURTNEY: Mm.
KIM: My stress level is,
like, on another... just my
anxiety level.
Maybe all we just need is a
little bit of tea in Bali and a
ride on an elephant, and we will
have a...
KOURTNEY: No, I think we all
need all the help we can get.
KIM: Seriously. ♪ ♪
(siren wailing)
REIGN: Ooh, wow. Wow.
KOURTNEY: Look, it's a candy
store.
Do you want a candy necklace,
Mase? >> MASON: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Come here, look.
REIGN: I want some of
that, too. >> SCOTT: Look.
You got to get that.
KOURTNEY: Do you want a
little butterfly, Reigny?
REIGN: Yeah.
SCOTT: Wait. I love these.
KOURTNEY: What is that?
SCOTT: This is a splattering
hot dog.
You know, New York is so, so
good.
Being able to be together with
our kids, running around, doing
different things...
KOURTNEY: This is yours.
SCOTT: How cool is this?
I couldn't be happier that I'm
on this trip.
Is anybody hungry for real food?
See, we can get a snack now if
we want, if we don't...
All right.
KOURTNEY: Or do we want to
just go back, chill...
SCOTT: Do we want to leave?
Whatever.
We can go back to the hotel.
We could chill.
I wish I could say that Kourtney
could see we are a family and
traveling together still works.
Let's go.
But at this point, I don't know
what she's thinking about the
trip to Bali.
Okay, shall we?
KOURTNEY: Okay, so I'm taking.
Reigny and anybody else that
wants to come in my car.
Thank you. >> SCOTT: Come on, P.
KRIS: You really need to pay
him a little more attention.
KIM: Mom, I have a million kids.
I have a million jobs.
I don't have any much more to
give. I was thinking about...
you being in Chicago.
KANYE: You know, when I went
to Chicago, I felt like I was
home.
There was a lot of things that I
missed.
KIM: Yeah.
It's not gonna benefit us if
we're, you know, that separated
all the time.
KRIS: Something's just
pulling me to stay here with MJ.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KRIS: I would be taking off,
feeling like I was making the
worst decision.
♪ ♪
KOURTNEY: Wow, Reigny, look
at all these airplanes!
SCOTT: Reign, I used to come
here when I was a little kid
with my mom. You fly one?
REIGN: I like to fly.
SCOTT: Okay. I'd like to keep
it moving, people.
There's a lot to cover.
KOURTNEY: To be honest, I was
worried about Scott in New York,
which is usually, like, very
distracting to him.
SCOTT: Reign, do you
understand this used to be a
real working battleship?
KOURTNEY: But it's really
nice to see Scott in full Dad
mode...
SCOTT: Look at this thing, P.
KOURTNEY: Hanging out
together as a family.
SCOTT: Yeah, they're real.
KOURTNEY: And I feel like
he's really focused upon this
family trip.
SCOTT: How cool is that?
I got to trade my cars in.
KOURTNEY: So, do you have a
boyfriend? >> CHARLI: No.
SCOTT: Whoa! I leave for
one second, and this is...
Wow, you hit her hard.
KOURTNEY: I know.
SCOTT: Do you like anybody?
CHARLI: No.
SCOTT: Okay. Good.
Kourt probably has someone she
can introduce you to, though.
KOURTNEY: What?
SCOTT: So, anyway, guys,
you'll notice this plane here.
♪ ♪
SCOTT: I don't think these
are gonna fit.
KOURTNEY: Is that...
What is that?
SCOTT: Mason's toiletries.
KOURTNEY: No, but what's the
big thing? >> SCOTT: This?
KOURTNEY: Oh, his dirty clothes.
SCOTT: I'll just leave it
out, 'cause he might shower
before we go to the plane.
KOURTNEY: So...
How do you think the trip was?
SCOTT: I had fun.
I feel like we haven't been to
New York together in forev...
Well, we haven't really gone
anywhere...
KOURTNEY: Yeah, since...
SCOTT: Together in a long
time. >> KOURTNEY: Costa Rica?
SCOTT: No. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
Everyone's been asking me about
the family trip.
SCOTT: Mm.
KOURTNEY: Obviously, I said,
after Costa Rica, that you
weren't ever coming on a family
trip again. >> SCOTT: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: I think that's when
I put the kibosh on the family
trips. >> SCOTT: Right.
Yeah. I mean, I don't think I
was in the best place, but I
feel like you and I also weren't
in the best place.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
SCOTT: You were, you know,
living your life the way you
should be, and I just wasn't
ready to handle it, and...
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
SCOTT: I don't know. I feel
like the biggest thing that you
and I have always talked about,
that you wanted from me, if
there was anything, was just to
see me consistent with you and
my family.
And, you know, it's been over a
year of consistency, and I feel
like we're good, and our
parenting's been better, and the
kids are better.
We've always said that we were
gonna try to be family.
Obviously, it didn't work out
perfect, but this is as close as
we can get. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
My past with Scott has always
been complicated, and I just,
you know, I feel like this New
York trip has really, like, made
me feel excited.
I mean, it's really nice to see
how much Scott has grown and
how much, like, he's invested in
really being a great dad to the
kids.
I like to all be able to go on
trips together.
So I think it's fine if you
want to come to Bali.
SCOTT: Yeah. I mean, if it's
a family trip and everybody's
going, of course I don't want to
miss out on those times.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
SCOTT: But I also want you to
feel comfortable.
KOURTNEY: My only hesitation
is just, like, I don't want to,
like, give mixed messages by,
like, all going on a trip
together.
SCOTT: Mixed messages with what?
KOURTNEY: Like, with you or
anything.
SCOTT: You're giving me a
mixed message?
I'm in a full relationship.
KOURTNEY: I know that.
But I'm just saying, I don't
ever want to...
SCOTT: Oh.
KOURTNEY: You to think I'm
giving a mixed message.
SCOTT: You barely give a
regular message.
KOURTNEY: (laughs) Okay.
♪ ♪
KRIS: Hello. >> KIM: Hey.
KRIS: Look what I have here.
KIM: What is that?
KRIS: This is Khloe's MTV Award.
KIM: Oh, cute.
KRIS: Look how great...
It's so heavy.
Isn't it great? Thank you.
KIM: (gasps) Whoa.
KRIS: Oh, my God.
KIM: Sorry. That is so heavy.
Wait. Try.
KRIS: Hey. >> KIM: Hi.
KRIS: Here's your MTV Award.
Best reality show.
KHLOE: This is all so much
pressure.
KRIS: Who would you like to
thank?
KHLOE: My Lord and savior.
And Kimberly for (bleep) on
camera.
KRIS: I don't get any credit
ever. ♪ ♪
KHLOE: What a beautiful table
setting, if I do say so myself.
KRIS: Hey, sweetheart.
I missed you.
How was New York?
KIM: It was good. It was fun.
It was hectic.
KHLOE: How was you and the.
Lord? >> KOURTNEY: Good.
KHLOE: I heard there might be
some news about the family trip?
KOURTNEY: No, I said he could
go.
KIM: You what?
KOURTNEY: Could go.
KIM: He could?
My brilliant plan worked out
perfectly.
Scott is coming to Bali, and I'm
so excited. >> KHLOE: Okay.
I'm happy that Kourtney has come
around and she's decided to let
him come.
I have so much more fun when he
is around.
It just adds a different dynamic
to the group, and as much as I
love my sisters and everything,
I-I miss Scott.
Sounds like a good trip.
We've made major progress here.
SCOTT: I love it.
KRIS: How was the show?
I haven't seen it.
KIM: SNL? >> KRIS: Yeah.
KIM: North, Penelope and
Mason had so much fun.
North was dancing up a storm.
KHLOE: I saw videos, so cute.
KRIS: North, you could host
next time.
KIM: I don't know if they'll
invite us back ever. (Laughs)
KRIS: Did he do a rant at the
end?
KIM: At the end, yes, but
the credits were rolling.
Look, I can't control it.
KRIS: I just feel like...
to keep him calm, you really
need to pay him a little more
attention. >> KHLOE: Oh, Mom.
What is wrong with you?
KIM: Mom.
I have a million kids.
I have a million jobs.
This is all I've got. KRIS: Kim.
SCOTT: I feel like you guys
are not supportive enough of.
Kim. KRIS: There's nobody more
supportive of Kim than me, but
I...
SCOTT: No, but all of you are
like, "Why don't you do this?"
Why don't you do that?"
Do you guys think that she could
do more?
He's already moving to Chicago.
KIM: I'm really happy that
Chicago is such a good place for.
Kanye. It's where he grew up.
He has so many memories there.
There's a lot he wants to do
there, but I definitely feel
like I'm being pulled in a
million directions.
The kids are in school, and we
have another baby on the way, so
moving to Chicago would have to
be, like, a long conversation.
And, honestly, it might be my
breaking point.
KRIS: Well, I think he just
is expecting a lot more than
you're giving.
KIM: I-I don't have any much
more to give.
♪ ♪
KRIS: Hey, Kourt.
KOURTNEY: Hey, Mom.
KRIS: What are you doing?
Ooh. Bootay.
KOURTNEY: I have to try on
my bikinis to pack.
This is the bikini and cover-up
that I like.
KRIS: Oh, is that Chanel?
KOURTNEY: Yeah. It's vintage.
KRIS: It's gorgeous.
KOURTNEY: You look nice.
KRIS: Thank you.
KOURTNEY: You're not coming
to the movie tonight, right?
KRIS: No. I'm taking MJ to
the doctor. Oh, life.
I woke up in the middle of the
night.
I didn't feel great.
I just think there's just a lot
going on.
I've been really stressed out
because of my mom.
I just feel something tugging at
my heart, like, not to go on the
trip.
Like, something's just pulling
me to stay here with MJ.
I would be taking off feeling
like I was making the worst
decision.
I feel, like, terrible FOMO,
but, you know, I can't really
leave and have every single one
of you gone and nobody really
here.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KRIS: The results of MJ's
biopsy are saying it's a
terrible, intense infection,
which is still very serious.
I could never leave her now.
And because of that, I've
decided not to go to Bali with
my family, and stay home and
spend time with MJ, and be here
in case she needs me.
And I just want to make sure
she's okay. >> KOURTNEY: Yeah.
KRIS: But I'm glad Scott's
going.
KOURTNEY: Me, too.
KRIS: I'm really glad he's
going.
And it makes me feel less guilty
about not going, to be honest.
KOURTNEY: Yeah.
I'm going to pack one bathing
suit, though, for each day.
KRIS: Yeah, I would just take
things like that, and then
maybe, like, an option of, like,
a little bike short or
something under it.
'Cause I feel like the trip is
gonna be...
KOURTNEY: No, we're doing
more, like, soul searching...
KRIS: Yeah.
KOURTNEY: Than, like, tanning.
KRIS: Well, if you find your
soul, text me.
KOURTNEY: Yeah. ♪ ♪
KIM: Wakey, wakey.
Eggs and bakey.
(Kanye grunts)
How annoying would that be if I
woke you up like that? (Laughs)
KANYE: Mm-hmm.
KIM: I'm sorry to wake you
up; I just have to leave, so I
wanted to catch you before, so
we could talk face-to-face.
But... I was thinking about you
being in Chicago and the kids'
schedules and everything, and I
feel like they're in school now.
I don't want to, like, uproot
them from all of their friends
and their routine and their
cousins and everything.
And I just think that it would
be amazing to have a second
place in Chicago.
And if you need to spend more
time out there, that's
totally fine.
But I think it would be really
hard just to take the kids and
leave and permanently move to
Chicago.
KANYE: You know, when I went
to Chicago, I felt like I was
home.
There was a lot of things that
I missed...
um, just not being there for a
long, long, long time.
KIM: Yeah. I get that.
KANYE: Yeah. Like, you know,
it's funny, 'cause you said...
I said, "I'm never going home,"
but what is home though exactly?
You know?
I have literally a song called.
"Coming Home."
It is not about, uh, a house in.
Hidden Hills.
KIM: Calabasas. Yeah.
(Kanye laughs)
Well, so what do you want to do?
Do you want to live in Chicago
and I'll live here?
And we'll FaceTime?
I mean, I'm willing to split it.
I'm just saying, during the
school year, it's gonna be
really hard.
I do think it's really important
to definitely support my
husband, but our whole life is
in California.
I met him when he lived in
California.
It's not like I met him and he
lived in Chicago and moved to.
California for us.
KANYE: I feel connected.
I feel inspired. Um...
KIM: When you go there.
KANYE: Yeah. When we're there.
KIM: Maybe we should get a
place in Chicago that we can go
back and forth to, but it's not
gonna benefit us if we're, you
know, that separated all the
time.
Okay, so we're in agreement.
We're not moving our family to.
Chicago full-time?
KANYE: Yeah, we're not gonna
move full-time, but we will...
KIM: Spend more time there.
KANYE: Spend time because
that's my home, too.
Like, when I'm in Chicago,
they're like, "Ye!"
It's Kanye! Ye! Look."
They're like, literally, like,
"Yay." Like, my name is, like,
K-A-N-Y-A-Y.
Like, "Yay! Kan-yay!"
And, you know, when I'm in L.A.,
they're like, "Oh, it's Ye."
KIM: No, they're like, "Kim!
(whoops) Kim! Oh, my God!"
It's Kim Kardashian!"
KANYE: Yeah.
KIM: On the next episode...
It's so high!
(women screaming)
(elephant trumpets)
Bali is so green and beautiful.
KHLOE: Oh!
Yeah, it's pretty epic.
You are so (bleep) up your own
ass(bleep).
I don't even have to (bleep) be
here. >> KOURTNEY: I just really
wanted this to be, like, a
positive trip between us.
I just think that kind of an
outburst isn't normal.
KHLOE: My feelings were hurt.
SCOTT: Both of you hurt each
other's feelings.
KHLOE: I'm gonna slap her in
her (bleep) mouth.
Captioning sponsored by.
BUNIM-MURRAY PRODUCTIONS