Keeping
Up with the Kardashians...
It just sucks it has
to be so public.
I'm not just a TV show.
Like, this is my life.
You'll put me down
just to make yourself not look
- lame.
- Moving to Chicago might
- be my breaking point.
- My family was ruined!
Here's to Jordyn and Kylie!
Tristan might love me,
whatever that means; He has no
respect for me whatsoever.
How many people have
- you been in love with?
- One.
I didn't think that I
was gonna have happiness again.
Liar!
We just can't seem to
catch a break.
You called me and said
that you were the watchdog.
I just hope that
there's a light at the end of
this tunnel, but I don't see it
right now.
- Yeah!
- We're having a baby.
True is the best thing
- that's happened to me. Ever.
- It's difficult.
Nothing is private.
Everyone feels like they have
the right to talk about you,
even though they have absolutely
- no idea what's going on.
- Sometimes the world
forgets just to be kind and that
we're all going through
something.
Maybe just be a little
more understanding, 'cause
it sucks.
You ready?
Yeah.
So, if you want to,
like, look up.
This is my first
time doing this.
I'm not actually attempting to
do good, I just...
Like, part of the reason why I
even thought about or considered
doing this, um... this
recording, like, what do you
call, what do you call... it's
an interview?
- Interview.
- This interview is.
The The...
- Why?
- It starts off with the
interviews.
The superheroes are giving
The wife got a big butt, and I
just see our life becoming The
until we can finally fly.
What?
Scott, how was it
seeing the Palm Springs house?
- Yeah. Tell us.
- There's, like, a golf
course down there that you can
run the sprinklers.
Me and KiKi, and your mom...
- Yeah.
- They used to turn on
the sprinklers in Palm Springs
'cause it was so hot, and we
would run through them all.
My mom bought a family vacation
home in Palm Springs, and I
think that is so cool.
Our entire childhood we had a
vacation house there.
We would drive up every weekend,
and we have so many memories in.
Palm Springs, so I think it's
awesome that all the kids get to
- have the same kind of memories.
- Come here.
Yeah.
We have an announcement to make.
My God. What?
We're having a baby.
- Hey!
- No!
Another one!
- We're having a boy.
- I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations, you guys.
- My God!
- Are you excited for
- your fourth kid?
- Yeah. I'm pleased.
I stopped using the word
"excited."
I'm very happy.
- Yeah.
- I feel like the energy
is gonna be really balanced out.
Saint happens to be one of my
- favorite human beings.
- I don't think it's
good when, like, parents be
like, "This is my favorite"
- "child."
- I think it changes.
I mean, it's reality.
I was my mom's favorite for a
- good decade, and now it's Kylie.
- I don't think you
- should play favorites with kids.
- Well, they would never
- know that, I'm just saying.
- Yeah, they just
- watch this, be like, ""
- But, you guys, it's
really top secret.
We don't want anyone to know
- until it happens.
- We're getting a new
- baby?
- Yeah.
North! Kiki's getting...
- You're getting another baby!
- I know.
She said, "I know."
My God.
You have to show True
the movie with the two dogs that
eats the spaghetti together.
Lady and the Tramp?
Yes! They have a French accent.
You know spaghetti is
more Italian.
They're Italian,
the dogs are Italian.
But they're not.
It's been a few months.
Me and Tristan are great, and I
am loving being a mommy.
It's bittersweet; I love seeing
every milestone with her, but I
feel like she grows... like, in
one week she's a completely
- different baby.
- That's all you're
- eating?
- Yeah, I'm so
- anxious, I just can't eat.
- Why are you anxious?
- Anxious about what?
- Life.
But what are you anxious about?
Yeah, but give us the reason.
I'm just anxious at
all times. I don't know.
My God, who just says that?
And then I saw
Scott 'cause I go, "I've been"
been crying all morning," and
then Scott was like, "You should
be celebrating that that guy's
out of your life."
- Hear, hear.
- I got out of a
relationship, and have been
feeling a lot of anxiety.
When I'm in a relationship,
there's, like, this sense of
security, and when I'm single,
it's like, I just don't like the
unknown, and I really don't do
well with change.
I've been trying doing Reiki to
get rid of some of the bad
energy, but nothing's really
helping.
Northie, this is Chicago.
- This is where Daddy grew up.
- I like the air.
You like the air?
Kanye's in Chicago working on
his new album, just working on
so many projects out there, like
tech stuff, architecture, his
whole Yeezy office is out
- there.
- Ha ha.
- Who's this pretty girl?
- I am bringing North so
that she can see where her dad
grew up, and he can show us
- around.
- Just so you know,
we're good at 4:30 at the Regal
if you want.
Yeah, so, we're, um,
re-refurbishing the Regal, which
is a Chicago landmark.
It's like our Apollo and it's on
79th Street, which is the
street I grew up on.
- That's so cool.
- So we can go by the.
Regal, that'd be fire, and then
we can go by my mom's house.
- Yeah.
But you know who we gotta get to
let us in?
Kanye decided to start
an organization after his mother
passed away called "Donda's
House" that would really help
the youth in Chicago.
He had his friend, Rhymefest,
that he's known for a long time,
head that foundation.
And when Kanye was going through
that tough financial time, he
was in debt, and he didn't have
the means to really take care of
it anymore, Rhymefest wanted to
take full responsibility of it,
and then all of a sudden...
Rhymefest, you know, was
publicly tweeting that Kanye
does nothing for Donda's House.
It's still your house.
He can leave the key.
We don't need to see his face.
You don't want me to see him.
Well, we got love, babe.
I'm letting you know.
I... You got love.
I-I don't have all the love.
My problem that I had with.
Rhymefest is that he was using
your mom to talk you and
that's where I drew the line.
He was saying, "You have failed."
Donda's House."
Your mother's name.
He didn't respect it, so
I was being protective.
I tweeted.
But you know why he
did it, though?
- Why?
- I had an assistant
that was rude to Rhymefest.
We were connecting.
- No.
- No, let me finish what
I'm saying.
Because we were connecting and
bonding, and he came to the
studio with me, then this person
that worked with me was
extremely rude to him...
Come on. Come on.
One of my sister's assistants...
- Yeah.
- Was rude to me.
I don't say anything.
I don't feel a way.
I don't start tweeting.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I don't start going
crazy about my sister.
If Rhymefest is your boy that
you grew up with and knows your
mom...
I'm not saying his
reaction was called for.
Then I would call and be
like, "What the is wrong"
with your assistant?
She was so rude to me."
I would just never start
tweeting, "You won't give me"
money for da da da da da."
That is some serious...
disturbed.
For real, you can walk up, you
can say hi.
I'm gonna zoom in and write some
- foul on, over his Face.
- See, that's some...
- On Snapchat.
- That's not what we're
- gonna do.
- That's what I'm gonna
do.
- Hello?!
- I'm so excited!
This house is crazy.
Everyone clap.
I don't have time for this.
- It's too much.
- I just want to know,
what's your rationale in being
cool with him?
- He's not gonna bully me.
- Bullying?
- Ain't nobody bullying me.
- I'm not saying he is.
Yeah. I get what you're saying.
We're painting fake abs.
- Trying to keep up with you.
- That's awesome.
- I gotta go, babe.
- Love you, bye.
Wow. Nice. Very nice, Khloe.
Am I making them big
enough for you?
I need to sell a sports bra
here, people.
Hey. What are you doing?
Just a Good American
photo shoot.
Just got out of the shower.
- I'm going to do a call with GQ.
- Fabulous, darling.
Wait, so can you tell me what's
going on with Palm Springs?
Kim can't come
'cause she's in Chicago.
- So there's like 14 of us.
- Isn't this like a
really, like, bougie
neighborhood?
- Yeah.
- I was gonna say,
"Can we TP people's houses?" but
we might get kicked of the
- community.
- Yeah, Mom will kill
- us.
- The Kardashians are
- here!
- We should do.
- Connect Four.
- Now you're just
getting a little too wild.
Connect Four. Whoa.
Since Kourtney's dealing with
anxiety, we all figured why
don't we have a fun, really
light girls weekend?
Let's go to Palm Springs, have
fun and check out the new digs
that Kris Jenner got.
I want Kourtney to enjoy being
single and focus on her.
No kids, no responsibilities,
- just let her hair down.
- Tomorrow will be
fun. Have a good shoot.
Toodle-oo.
- Hello.
- Hi, there.
I wanted to come, mwah, see you.
Why do you have these little
coasters everywhere?
- 'Cause I want to.
- Lot of stuff on this
- table, lot of little stuff.
- Don't worry about it.
MJ's been living in
Calabasas for a while now, and
it's really great.
I can pop in and see her on my
way in, on my way out, of
anything I do, make sure she's
okay and that makes me feel
really good.
I do have one thing for
you, though.
This is the other part of our
genealogy.
- Okay.
- So this is the Wyatt part
of the family, you know, like
Grandma's mother.
And Walter Wyatt, which
- was Grandma's...
- Wait, hold on.
Cute boots.
So, are we through with this?
All right, Mom, I love you.
I'm going over to Kourtney's.
You're always in a big hurry..
I love you. Mwah.
I love you very much.
- I love you.
- Mwah.
You be good.
Kourtney, I hope
you know that these are what
real friends do.
They go on a trip with you when
- you're single.
- Thanks.
No one else in this
car is single, so we're doing
this for you.
This is a support system.
Well, you know what, guys?
I appreciate you enjoying my
singleness with me.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much for being
single.
- Yes, thank you.
- And thank you, Mom,
- for the house in Palm Springs.
- Yes.
Hello?! Hi!
- I'm so excited!
- I knew my mom bought a
gorgeous house in Palm Springs,
I don't think I imagined just
- how spectacular a house.
- I don't think you
- can call it a "house."
- It is breathtaking.
I'm really excited that all you
guys are here because Kourtney,
I think, really needs to, like,
get away, it's her trip, and
she's been super, like, anxious
lately, but I think she's now
single, and even though it's
not, like, some wild vacation, I
just think it's fun that we're
all doing a girls trip.
- Girl-guys trip.
- You can live,
there's life after that
relationship.
I just like that
she's, like, getting out and
about. It's fun.
My... Kourtney? My God!
That's that single body.
There's the breakup body!
Mommy, this should be for you.
Thank you. Hey, hey, now.
What does she want?
My gosh.
Look at those huge lollipops.
- Are we gonna go see your house?
- Yeah.
I need to get the keys and all
that, everything.
You should be able to
walk right in there without his
permission. It's your home.
- He's not gonna bully me.
- He's not gonna bully
me, either. What you mean?
- Why you say it like that?
- 'Cause I'm saying, like,
he's not gonna be nice and
we all got love, I get it all,
- but I don't...
- Nah, but you said
bullying.
Ain't nobody bullying me.
I'm not saying he is.
He's acting like, he's not gonna
like, talk, keep talking
to me on Twitter.
- Like, he's not gonna...
- Yeah.
I get what you're saying.
I just want to know
what's your rationale in being
- cool with him?
- I'm not rational.
- I'm spiritual.
- Okay, but do you
- understand that, like...
- Spirit is love.
That's so hard to, like...
- Yeah.
You know I'm about forgiveness.
You know, I'm on that Buddha
you know?
Well, I think that, you
know, we definitely...
I see where you're coming from
and I want to be as good a
- person as you are, but...
- You want to be mad at
somebody.
You just want to be mad at
- anybody.
- No, I don't, I just get
really protective and I'm like,
"No."
And then you just go forgive
them.
How many times is this gonna
happen with you two?
Forgive people forever.
They... with love, they will
grow.
So wack.
We literally
broke up the day before.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I know Kourtney's
going through something, but
let's focus on what's happening
- now.
- This sucks.
- Rhymefest is coming.
- Yeah, I don't like
- negativity.
- Yeah.
I can't get the door, will you
get it? It's your friend.
Yo.
I'm letting you open the
door like a gentleman.
Get me some points on
I've always felt a special bond
with MJ over the years.
She's so quick in her wit, like,
I just feel like we get each
other.
So, I found this really, really
cute little tea place.
I felt like it would be the
perfect little date for her and.
I. This is unbelievable, this
- little spot.
- The decor is so cute.
I can't believe this
even exists.
I think we should come
back and get really dressed up.
I do, too.
We could wear the fancy cos...
- 'Cause you have award clothes.
- Yeah, I would have to
- wear a tux or a suit.
- Do you still have your...
- Of course I do.
- Plaid pants and...
- I've got it all.
- Then cool.
We should get really
decked out and come.
We should. I have a great hat.
Yeah, okay.
So, have you adapted fully?
From living in San Diego to.
Calabasas?
When Kris started moving all my
stuff, I had pneumonia, so I was
kind of at a... She scooped in.
She knows when to get you.
It's like if they took
your house and said, "We're"
gonna make this better, Scott,
just stand by."
And they moved
everything to a new house...
But I was already happy.
Yeah. But you know what I really
resent?
She'd say, "Let's go to the"
"mall," and she's like this the
whole time.
So I resent that.
I thought, "Why are we going to"
- "lunch?"
- What's the point?
- Yeah.
- MJ moved all the way
to Calabasas to be around
everybody, but everybody's so
busy, she probably feels like
she's being swept under the
carpet and not really getting
a lot of time with people.
- I get where she's coming from.
- You eat cereal?
- No.
- Why?
We'll, like, have
scrambled eggs or something...
I love scrambled eggs.
- Not more than that.
- Yeah.
I remember the only
thing my dad could cook was
- scrambled eggs.
- That's so cute.
That was the only
thing I ever remember...
Well, then you should learn it.
I kind of have someone
who does it.
Well... I believe in
doing things yourself.
All right, I'll learn
how to do scrambled eggs this
week. Can you teach me?
- Yeah.
- All right, so, let's
do it. This week, you
- teach me how to do scramble...
- I'll show you how to
- whisk them.
- All you got to do is
- crack it open and...
- Right?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- I love your outfit!
- Thank you!
Thank you.
Even though it's been kind of a
- rocky day...
- What's good, man?
Respect, respect. Respect.
- Love. Love.
- I know that Kanye's
been really excited about this
theater he wants to renovate.
- That's it. Got it.
- Cool.
So I'm excited to go see it
with him.
This is my favorite part.
Shine a light up in here, you
can see the jewels that are on
- the ceiling.
- Ooh, there's jewels on
- Largest flying
carpet, yeah.
All of these murals depict
scenes from King Arthur.
And that's actually Avalon
'cause this was built as the
Avalon Theater in 1927.
Transitioned into the new Regal
Theater in 1997.
- Mom, when are we...
- Wait, let's listen, he's
- telling us about what it means.
- What if we changed it
changed it back to the Avalon?
I love that name.
So, dig this, I'm
changing it to the Avalon Regal.
Theater because it spells "art."
- Art. Incredible.
- Can you dig it?
- >> KANYE and JERALD: Yeah.
- This is a really cool
theater where a lot of artists
would perform in Chicago.
I opened up for Jay-Z
at the Regal Theater.
That's so cool.
It's really beautiful to be able
to give back to the community
- that helped make me who I am.
- It's fire, right?
If you guys can, like,
redo this, it'll be really cool
- for the whole city.
- Yeah.
Hi, Mama.
How are you? Baby True.
I love you, Mama.
Have fun on your walk with your
cousins.
Mwah, mwah, mwah. Bye, boo.
My God, are you so obsessed?
- I'm so obsessed.
- We literally broke
- up the day before.
- Right.
And the next day,
that's how you're gonna go act?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Like, I don't have
time for this.
And it just was too much.
- And I was like...
- Too much.
That was another
too much and then it just was so
- many too muches.
- This sucks.
What the?
I know Kourtney's upset, but I
wish she would be in the moment
more and realize that she
doesn't need to be in a
relationship to be happy.
Let's focus on what's happening
now.
Kourtney!
Let me tell you, get your fat
ass over here.
My God! What?
We need a blow-
- dryer!
- What do I do?
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Just eating dinner.
Is North having fun?
Yeah, she's having...
She always has, like, so much
fun when it's just us.
She, like, loves it, you know?
- Yeah.
- You know, tomorrow
morning we're gonna go see the
house that Kanye grew up in.
- That's cool.
- Yeah, it's cool, but he
bought it in the foundation name
and then gave the foundation to
his friend Rhymefest, that I
cussed out on Twitter.
- Dear.
- And I'm just, like, so
annoyed because he just, like,
lets all of his, like, friends
back in that, like, always
publicly talk about him
and it's like, I've just never,
I've just never dealt with close
people like that.
Those are like his brothers, you
- know?
- Yeah.
But the fact that you're back
there and you're trying to
figure it out, I think it's
amazing that you support him and
you want to show your daughter
his world.
Well, that's why, that's
what I do on a daily is to
protect him, and then I get
stuck in this, like, circle
because I'm like, "I got to take
care of the kids, I got to",
like, work."
I have, like, so much to do that
I can't, like, babysit him
and figure out, like, who's
him over today and who
he's gonna forgive.
Like, I just don't have the
energy for it.
- It's, it's a lot.
- Yeah.
- It's so draining.
- I know.
I mean, you can have all
the love in the world and want
to wish everyone well, but it is
so frustrating to me to just see
him not care and let people,
like, walk all over him.
- So, I don't know what to do.
- Forgiveness is an
amazing thing.
- Yeah.
- I'll figure it out.
Okay, well, I'll be here.
All right, I love you. Bye.
All right, I love you, too. Bye.
You guys, someone save me!
Everyone drove up here
all for Kourtney and so we are
gonna just have a ball.
You won't even talk to me.
You go, "Mom, this is business."
I thought, "Couldn't I have
20 minutes alone with her?"
But I don't.
I don't know your stove.
- Same.
- Just like any stove?
- All right.
- I have to say yes,
but...
I really don't know
how to make much.
I thought it was literally the
nicest, cutest thing that MJ
actually wanted to take her time
and teach me how to cook some
- things.
- Crack us four eggs in
- there.
- I've seen this done,
but I...
- There. You did it.
- I'm done.
- Here, put this here.
- I knew I had talent.
Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow.
Here, like this. Get under it.
Wow!
Why haven't you learned this?
I'll tell you the
exact reason, I'm a man.
- I'm not sitting in the kitchen.
- That's, that's very
- sexist.
- Listen, I do a lot for
women and people and humanity.
You turned off the stove, right?
No.
Beautiful. I'm an egg maker.
- Hello.
- Hi. Where are you?
- I'm at Scott's.
- Wait a second, I have
- to look at something.
- She calls just to...
- You called me. Hello?
- Hi, just a second.
No, no, no, no.
You can't do that.
- Hello?
- She's not even
- listening.
- She's not even on the
- phone.
- I can totally
understand now what MJ's talking
about.
This is crazy.
I mean, it's her mom.
- Go forth, my dear.
- I don't know what's
happening over there, but I feel
like you don't want to hang
- out with me.
- Well...
You're literally
always on your phone.
Nice, Scott. Okay.
Do you want go with us to
- our favorite hangout?
- What?
- What's your hangout, Mom?
- The Cottage Tea Room.
That's so cute.
I would love to come with you.
Be sure to dress up, though.
She better start
getting ready now.
You better call your
makeup people right now.
My God. All right, you guys.
- Well, I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- I don't think there's
any way Kris is gonna be able to
sit through a whole tea without
using her phone.
I can't wait to see how
long it takes.
- Should we bet on that?
- Two minutes.
I'm going five.
You're going two?
Yeah. Two.
You guys, you're
- not ready for this.
- Hold on.
- A boom box?
- Okay, let's set it up.
Let's start singing and our
voices will get them to come in.
The fact that there's a
karaoke machine, it's, of
course, Kris Jenner style.
My mom is the queen of drunk
karaoke.
Coming in hot!
Coming in hot, people!
What's going on?
I heard the karaoke.
I mean, I know
Kourtney's going through
something.
You guys, someone save me!
I'm forcing Kourtney
to have fun right now, so she
sees that she can be single and
it's okay.
- Just have a ball.
- Odis!
Odis!
- We're doing karaoke.
- Ooh, can we do.
- "CoCo"?
- Can we do "CoCo"?
- Word.
- A thousand bitches
have never sang your song for
you, watch!
I'm in love with the
coco, coco...
There's a mic on the floor.
I'm in love with the
coco, coco...
- Hey!
- I got it for the low,
low Cause I'm in love with the
- coco, coco...
- I'm stealing your
- hit!
- I'm in love with the
coco
- I got it for the low, low...
- Say what?
I'm in love with the coco.
Hey, hey!
Help me.
- Cheers, guys.
- Cheers.
I needed that.
Thanks for coming, you guys.
- Yeah.
- May you stay single
long enough for us to do this
at least one more time.
Very well, guys.
Northie, look at the water.
I just saw a dolphin jump.
- You did?
- Yeah.
The one, like, sentiment
that I really want to get
across... like, I hope you know
when I talk about your friends,
you don't have anyone else
around to protect you.
So, I feel like I have to double
watch everything,
so when I... it comes from a
different perspective.
I'm not, like, being a hater,
- I'm, like... like you think I am.
- Nah, I didn't... I-I
never... I never thought you were
a hater.
I thought you were doing what
you felt, and I think that it
shows that you care.
And I... and I appreciate
- you for having that perspective.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- My favorite thing about.
Kanye is that he is a completely
free thinker.
Yeah, that's beautiful.
I wanted you to be like, "Man,
you know, his is bomb,"
no.
No, um, I think it's
just good that he hears
me out and we're having this
conversation.
I think it's gonna shape the way
that he deals with his friends,
but I know that Kanye is always
gonna be Kanye and I'm never
trying to change that.
I mean, that's who I fell in
- love with.
- Who's your favorite
husband?
You.
Next time Rhymefest is in L.A.,
I'd love to sit down with him
and talk face-to-face.
Yeah. Yeah, here we are.
Pull up right here, stop, stop,
stop.
- This right here.
- Where are we going,
- Daddy?
- This one right here.
Look at the hearts, North.
So there used to be
ch... cherries on this tree,
or grapes.
I remember being back here when
the Reebok Pumps and the
Nike Pumps came out, explaining
to my friends how the pump
technology work.
I ain't have no idea, I would
just be like, "Yo, and see",
"when you pump it, then you drive
fast," you know, how, like,
kids, like...
"Or you run extra fast when you
- "pump it up."
- It's so special that.
North gets to see that life that
Kanye lived that really made
- him who he is.
- I love you, Northie.
That was really cool to see.
Wait, can someone take a pic of
me with them?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
How cool is this?
Thought we was friends.
You can't make
positive by doing negative.
Kanye is from a village.
Our dear brother turned his back
on the village.
This is the life, Kourt.
So good. My... it's so hot, I'm
dying.
What? A bee? Ooh.
- My God.
- Move.
My God.
I swear to God, was
- that not the biggest bee?
- No, it legit was about
- to attack you.
- Was that a huge
- bumblebee?
- Yeah. I've never seen
- you move that fast.
- It was literally
- trying to kill me.
- You are hilarious, I
- swear.
- My God.
Those are, like, the bees that
you die from, right?
- I don't know.
- The bees you die from?
There are some,
they... aren't they called killer
- bees?
- I don't know if
that means they're gonna kill
you.
I feel so much better, I've been
feeling so anxious.
- Yeah.
- But now I feel... I
feel like I needed this trip to
get away.
I love that we have this house
now.
I am the kind of
person... I feel like I'm usually
better when I'm in a
relationship, but I feel good.
It's almost like...
It's an anxiety, but it's also,
like, an excitement.
It's not necessarily...
- Like, the new chapter?
- At some moments,
it's...
I feel like, you know, I-I've
feel like I've gone through
already, like, the sad and
- the... like, I feel good.
- Yeah.
I feel happy, I
feel like this is where I'm
meant to be.
I don't have regrets.
- Yeah.
- I feel like I gave
it my 100%.
I'm feeling much
better and, you know, as scary
as this might be, I'm really
ready.
It's kind of like, God has a
plan and just trusting.
This is the first time I've
really been single in a long
time, so I'm just going to
embrace it and really enjoy the
time to myself and focusing on
my kids and myself.
I'm excited for the future.
I mean, I feel like,
from the looks of everything,
the breakup blues are nowhere
in sight.
- What breakup blues?
- It worked!
What a trip, guys.
- That was...
- So fun.
- That was so fun.
Hello.
We're here with a vengeance.
- How are you?
- Welcome back.
- You're looking dapper today.
- Yeah.
- You told us to dress up.
- My goodness, the style.
- Thank you.
- Got you the best table.
- Very excited.
- This is so great.
- Do you love it?
- I love it.
Where does everybody
want to sit?
Let's get this party started.
MJ, you look marvelous.
- Well, thank you, darling.
- Wow.
- Thank you so much.
- See, this is what we
- should be doing with our time.
- Enjoying each other.
- Yeah.
- I'm so glad you could
just settle down and spend some
time with us, and we agreed that
we're all gonna put our phones
in a pile and not touch them.
- Got it.
- So remember which is
- yours.
- The one that rings.
Who knew this is what
you and MJ have been up to all
this time?
I have to dress it up for her.
You do.
I take you out and you're in
sweats and a hoodie, but for MJ,
you pull out all the stops.
- Yes, all the stops.
- Yeah.
I'm a little jealous
that you guys hang out together.
- I'm not gonna lie.
- Well, you're always
invited, you're just always too
busy.
We can't take you
anywhere, that's why.
She does bring up a good point.
We were worried you were gonna
do business.
I'm not trying to say
poor me, but... poor me.
Yeah, I'll say it for you.
I think MJ's just excited to
have some quality time with you.
- Absolutely.
- And I think, you know,
she hasn't really vocalized it
enough, but I think she felt
like you kind of moved her life
to be closer, and then she kind
- of feels like...
- While I had pneumonia.
You don't even have time...
- Aw, Mom.
- When you're here
for her and she sometimes
doesn't understand why did I
just move my whole life if
you're not gonna spend the time
that you thought you were gonna
be able to spend with her?
I can't, I can't talk to you.
You go, "Mom, this is business."
And you won't even talk to me,
and I thought, "Good, I have
20 minutes alone with her," but
- I don't.
- I didn't realize that.
MJ feels like I don't pay
attention to her.
- That's like time-shaming.
- Time-shaming.
You guys heard of
time-sharing? Time-shaming.
It makes me really,
really sad that she...
- Aw.
- Thinks I don't give
- her enough attention.
- Yeah. I think you try.
I have to try harder. I get it.
I know you do.
Kimberly.
I'm in your house, ready to go.
Hi. How are you?
Okay. Okay, so I...
- So I, so I like one.
- Okay.
A lot.
You already... You know the ones
- you like?
- Yeah.
This one, I feel like I got to
smell.
I feel like it has potential.
What we found online is
that this ML, this looks
obviously better, like, on your
counter.
And I feel like it's
even cuter for people to take
pics like this, like...
- Yeah. That's...
- And it'll actually fit.
This one, like, is more of a
joke, you know?
Cute. Let's just go
with the small one.
Wait, I want to show you
something.
- Ooh!
- There's the strong
- heartbeat right there.
- Isn't that crazy?
Wow. That is so exciting.
I'm low-key freaking out.
- Why?
- I didn't think it was
gonna, like, happen.
I thought, like, "It
probably won't even take, so,
like, who cares?"
You know? We'll try it.
And now that it is, the two
little ones are gonna be a year
apart.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah, I'm not gonna tell
any of my friends.
I'm gonna tell your friends
'cause your friends are the ones
that keep it quiet, so I'm not
gonna... if I have to tell
anyone, I'm gonna call your
- friends.
- Yeah, of course.
Do you know who I think
our informant is?
North.
What do you mean?
She tells everybody?
She appar... A mom at
school texts me and goes,
"Congrats, I heard you're having
a baby brother," and I go,
"What?"
And I go, "That," and she
goes, "Yeah, North is going
around saying she finally has a"
baby brother so Saint won't
bother her anymore."
- Stop.
- "And I was like,"
that's just her dream. Hahaha."
And, like, she's the one
- this whole time.
- Stop. That is crazy.
- What're you gonna do?
- I mean, nothing.
- I mean, I-I killed it.
- I'm just kidding.
- I'm just...
- No, but I killed the
rumor.
Do you have some
scissors?
And I need a cube of butter and
- your rolling pin.
- I got it, I'm your
sous chef. Here you go, madame.
Hi, MJ!
- Hi.
- Hi, Mom.
Look at you in your Burberry.
We're making cheesecake.
- Beautiful, beautiful.
- This brings back a lot of
memories. Does it?
- Yeah.
- You're so cute, MJ.
I feel like you like it when we
spend time together.
- I do love it.
- Sometimes I'm running
around and I'm trying to figure
out, like, running here, running
there, working, filming, and you
forget that I...
- You are busy.
- Well, I don't mean to
- be, like, I want to give you...
- Well, I think you mean to
- be.
- I think one-on-one time
and being present in the moment
is really important.
- Very important.
- I love being present.
What is this stool you
have in your kitchen?
- Is it good on your knees?
- This is how I go if I
need to go from, like, pot to
pot.
- I need that.
- Ta!
I never want my mom to
think I'm not paying attention
to her because if my kids did
that to me, I would be
devastated.
I just want to make sure she
knows I'm pulled in so many
different directions and I'm
just doing the best I can and I
never want her to feel anything
but loved. La, la, la, la...
- My sandal.
- La, la, la, la.
La, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Not even... Whoa!
You know, I'm really
happy that Rhymefest is coming.
I'm like, definitely in a more
calm place then I was when we
were in Chicago, where I feel
like, "I'm gonna slap this... I'm"
gonna punch him in the face."
Like, I'm just way more Zen now.
Yeah, I just want him
to know that we're talking about
this, so it's not just another
public thing that just...
brings it up again in, like,
a negative way, 'cause I don't
like negativity.
Yeah. I can't get the door.
Will you get it?
It's your friend.
Yo.
- What's good, bro?
- What up?
- Good. Chillin'.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Hey, hey.
- How are you?
- Good, good, good.
Good to see you.
You want me to sit right
- here?
- Yeah, wherever.
Um... when we came to Chicago,
I was really angry, so I just
think we should have a
conversation about it, so that
all of our sides are out there
and it's just really fair.
I agree. Heal-Healing.
- It's for healing. Yeah, yeah.
- So, from my perspective,
I grew up with all the same
friends being my same best
friends from when I was in
preschool.
Not one of my friends has ever
spoken out about me.
He can't really say no to
people.
If they ask him financial
questions, if they ask him for
any kind of help and, sometimes,
I think it's, like, to a fault
where he'll hurt himself and
then he won't have something
- financially and he's struggling.
- Well, I-I-I just
want to, I-I want to, um, make
it clear, um...
Nah, it wasn't about money.
It's, it is deeper than that
- because-because we are friends.
- Okay.
Kanye wanted me to
help work on the album, and I
said, "Yeah, I'll help work,"
and he said, "Well, what do you
want?"
And it wasn't about money.
It was like, "Yo, I want you to
tweet out what we're doing about."
Donda's House."
And I kept telling you, "Kanye,
I need you to do this.
Come on, we got to do that, do
this."
Kanye is from a village and-and
the village was feeling like our
dear brother...
You know what I'm saying?
Turned his back on the village.
And so, I struck out.
It's-it's 'cause me and you have
- been talking about peace.
- You can't make
positive by doing negative.
You could've said, "Hey, can I"
call you?
I want to just talk to you
"directly before I say something,
you know."
I just think if Kanye
said, like, "I can't deal with."
"Donda's House right now," to me,
that means in all capacities.
Yeah, but that was
after he said he would.
But even if I said I would...
That's what I didn't know.
I was going through some.
Yeah, but it was all negative.
Yeah, the I
was going through, that's why
it's called going through some
'cause it's negative.
What you talking about?
You guys can go through
all the in the world.
You guys have been friends for
decades, but I wish that you
guys could have that in private
because so much is public.
This is where I
will take accountability.
I could've reacted better.
There's no good excuse.
And I wish that I wasn't
tweeting.
I think there's
hurt on both sides and strikes
on both sides, like, "How can I
get him to see me or hear me?"
Like, we... I thought we was
friends, but-but-but what you're
saying, and I get it, there's a
better way to handle these
- things.
- Totally.
I bought you a gift.
- My God.
- So I'm into
- crystals.
- So am I.
It's a Herkimer diamond.
- My God.
- And it's for, it's
for good feeling, for
manifestations, whatever it is
you're trying to get, whatever
journey you're going on.
Thank you. I love that.
That's so nice of you.
Thank you.
It's good that we all have,
like, calm, understanding
conversation.
- That's really nice of you.
- Because you love
him, I love you.
Like, you know, and families go
- through things.
- Totally.
I just think that everyone
should communicate to each other
and not on social media, and I
think you just get so much more
- done if you have a conversation.
- We are love.
- Love.
- That's really cool.
He is thinking of moving to
Chicago.
Your whole family's here.
Uprooting the kids...
I'm freaking out.
- You're not serious.
- No, I think he is
serious.
I'm literally trying the best
that I can to be there for
everyone...
Hey, hey, hey, don't press any
of that.
And sometimes I'm just, like,
my... like, I just need a
minute.
I don't have any much more to
- give.
- If it's a family trip,
of course I don't want to miss
out on those time.
I don't want to,
like, give mixed messages.
Mixed messages of what?
Captioning sponsored by