[opening theme music playing]
[female singer]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray ♪
♪ And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[music ends]
[whimsical music playing]
[Ridley] Fly like an eagle.
So, what's this big surprise?
Serengeti adventure?
A new hat?
[gasps] The museum's
getting an ice cream exhibit!
Oh. The stamp machine. Cool.
This isn't just like any stamp machine.
Here. Now that you're
officially in training,
it's time that you had your very own
Museum Passport.
Just like your mom and I did.
As you train, you'll earn stamps.
[whispers] Special stamps.
Once you've filled the entire passport,
you'll get one of these.
[Mama] It's called the Compass Eye.
It has magic in it.
I want one! I want one now!
[chuckles] I know.
But you'll have to wait.
Every full-fledged protector
of the museum needs one.
It's what makes this happen.
[mystical twinkling]
[Ridley] Seriously? That never gets old!
So, are you sure I can't just get
my own compass-thingy now?
Not until your passport is full
and you're truly ready.
For now, just be patient and work hard.
Be patient and work hard. Got it.
Houston, we have a passport.
Dude, it's just like the one your mom got
when she was your age.
It's so cool. Don't you think, Dudley?
Dudley?
Earth to Dudley. Come in, Dudley!
Hello? Dudley? What are you looking at?
Oh, hey! When'd you guys get here?
I was just dreaming about--
I mean, checking out the eagle exhibit.
They have the coolest exhibit.
It's always been my dream
to fly with the big birds.
Why don't you?
Because I'm a flightless bird.
I just flap my wings for effect.
I mean, why don't you
go hang out in the eagle exhibit?
Wait, really? [splutters]
Could I transfer to the eagle exhibit?
Don't see why not.
My job is to help everyone in the museum.
If that's your dream,
I'm gonna make it come true. Come on!
[chuckles]
Knock knock! Anybody nesting?
Hey! You must be that Ridley Jones kid
that has all the exhibits squawking!
Nice to meet ya.
I am! And this is Dudley.
Hey there. We met at the bird exhibits
potluck last year, um, remember?
Oh yeah! Well, good to see ya again.
-I'm Flo, and this pile of feathers is--
-Pierce Featherton the Third.
I come from a long, important line
of museum eagles.
-Quit posing, ya big goof!
-My bird!
Hey, I didn't mean
to ruffle your feathers.
[laughing]
You see what I did there?
We actually stopped by
because Dudley here,
who's the coolest
and chillest bird I know, by the way,
was wondering
if he could move in with you.
[spluttering] Uh…
But the eagle exhibit is for eagles!
It is sacred ground.
In all my years
perched atop this Styrofoam log--
Oh, don't be such a stickler, Pierce.
We'd love to have ya.
Welcome home, kid!
[gasps]
Opening time!
Now, let's see. The Nile leak is corked,
the music exhibit is tuned,
Dudley's in the eagle exhibit. Wait, what?
That's not good. [gasps] Mr. Peabody!
Ridley, we've got a dodo-sized problem.
I need you to get Dudley out of
the eagle exhibit before anyone sees.
Wait, what? Why?
I'll explain later. For now, I'll distract
Mr. Peabody while you handle Dudley.
I'm on it!
[mama] Mr. Peabody!
Everything is perfectly…
The visitors are gone.
Grandma's locking up.
And Dudley's back in his exhibit?
Yep! Just checked.
But, Mom, why can't Dudley
be in the eagle exhibit?
He really likes it there.
Well, as protectors of the museum,
we have to make sure everything is true
to the best of our knowledge.
Facts matter. Museums teach kids
the truth about the world,
so we can't let any exhibits
be empty or incorrect.
-Make sense?
-Mm-hmm.
You can count on me
to keep everything straight.
Thanks for understanding, Dudley.
Sure. I understand.
[sighs]
I'm alone because I'm the last of my kind.
Last dodo bird standing.
Umph. Sitting.
Oh, I wish I didn't have to stay here
all by myself.
♪ When you're one of a kind ♪
♪ Life can get lonesome ♪
♪ One of a kind ♪
♪ You're all on your ownsome ♪
♪ Oh, how it stinks ♪
♪ That the brink of extinction's a grind ♪
♪ When you're one of a kind ♪
♪ One of a kind ♪
♪ Never together ♪
♪ With birds of a feather ♪
♪ You may have heard ♪
♪ It's absurd how a bird is maligned ♪
♪ When you're one of a kind ♪
♪ It's such an emotional load
Oh ♪
♪ When the rest of your kind ♪
♪ Goes the way of the dodo! ♪
♪ I'm one of a kind ♪
♪ Lost and unfriended ♪
♪ One of a kind ♪
♪ My species has ended! ♪
♪ I can attest you get stressed ♪
♪ Empty nests put a bird in a bind ♪
♪ And even your feathers feel blue ♪
♪ Just like you
When you're one of a kind ♪
[song ends]
Hey, Dudley? Just wanted to check in
to see how you were doing and-- [gasps]
No, no, no. That just won't do.
Raise your wings higher.
-Now flap! Flap, I say!
-Uh, Dudley?
Can I talk to you for a minute?
No can do!
I'm up flying like an eagle, and--
I guess I could take a quick break.
[Ridley] You have to stay in your exhibit,
remember?
Do I really have to?
Yes. Mom says that no exhibit
can be empty or wrong.
Every part of the museum
has to be as true as we can make it.
Facts matter.
Facts matter, huh?
[laughter]
Okay, I did some research on the Internet,
and it turns out dodos can be anywhere.
Look at these.
Dodo birds in space,
dodo birds cuddling with kittens, and--
Aha!
A dodo bird flying next to an eagle.
And it's on the Internet,
so it must be real.
Do you wanna tell him, or should I?
Um, the thing is, you can't believe
everything you read on the Internet.
Those aren't real.
Sorry, Dudely.
Even the one of a dodo bird driving a car?
[inhales sharply]
Yeah, right, that doesn't make sense.
[chuckles] Dodos don't drive.
[shivering] I am a genius!
With this disguise,
I'll blend in with the penguins.
-Dudley?
-[yelps]
The jig is up.
[strains, grunts]
Your exhibit can't be empty, remember?
Oh. Right.
As you can see,
this exhibit is rotunda-adjacent,
just steps from the trendy music exhibit,
boasts views of the Jones Tree House,
and comes fully furnished. Mmm?
Well, it's gotten pretty crowded
in the lemur exhibit.
And I'm tired of sharing a branch
with all our brothers and sisters.
You sure it's cool if we move in here?
Sure, I'm sure. As long as an exhibit
isn't empty, we're fine.
If you need me,
I'll be in the eagle exhibit.
I didn't think it was okay
to switch exhibits.
I didn't either, but you heard the bird.
And I've always wanted
to move to the Serengeti.
Wait. But if you move in there,
where will those animals go?
Huh?
What? Where are you all going? [gasps]
[intriguing music playing]
Uh-oh.
Hey, what gives?
The knight took over my bison exhibit!
And now she's the one who looks tough!
Doesn't she always look tough?
What do ya think
caused this whole hullabaloo, Ridley?
I don't know for sure,
but I have a pretty good guess.
[Dudley laughing]
Don't worry.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
You guys get everyone
back to the right exhibit.
[Peaches] Fly home, butterflies! Fly home!
Don't you miss your usual spot, milady?
Sorry for the chaos.
I thought I was following the rules… ish.
I wish I could let you move
where you want,
but everyone in the museum
has to stay where they belong.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Great.
[sighs] But I feel like over there
with the eagles is where I belong.
[sighs] There.
Now I can keep an eye out until morning
and make sure everyone stays
where they're supposed to.
[eagles laughing]
[intriguing music playing]
Uh-oh. If I go this way,
Ridley'll definitely see me.
Aha.
[grunts] Just a little bit further,
and I'll be right above the eagle exhibit.
[laughs] Yippee-ki--
[grunts]
[rattling]
[gasps] Oh no, I fell asleep,
and… [gasps] …it's morning already?
-The museum's gonna open any minute!
-[Dudley] Help!
Somebody help, I'm stuck!
Don't worry, Dudley. I'm coming!
[panting]
Ridley! Boy, aren't you a sight
for sore bird eyes?
What happened?
I was trying to get into the eagle exhibit
without getting caught.
I'm sorry for sneaking off.
Dudley, why do you wanna be
with the eagles so badly?
[sighs]
I'm one of a kind, y'know?
And it gets lonely
being the last of the dodo birds.
Just once, I wanted to be
a part of a family.
-[Fred] Ridley, we're ready to go!
-Hmm? Who said that?
Your family.
We're all here for ya, D-man!
We must free you so you can attend
your next flying lesson!
Ridley, let us know when to start pullin'!
[Ridley] Okay, now!
[all] Heave-ho! Heave!
Wait! Stop! It's Lonny.
[whistling]
[Lonny singsong] Doo-doo-doo-doo.
[Peaches] Okay, back at it!
[all] Heave-ho!
Heave-ho!
[all screaming, grunting]
Great job, team! Be right down!
Dudley, are you okay?
Okay? I'm great!
I have the world's bravest friends.
You all risked hoof and claw to save me.
Well, yeah!
Duh, Dudley!
-You're part of our herd.
-Our copilot.
Our family.
You're one of a kind, Dudley,
but you're not alone.
♪ So you're one of a kind ♪
♪ There's only one of you ♪
♪ One of a kind ♪
♪ But that's why we love you ♪
♪ Who could replace that sweet face? ♪
♪ Not a trace of a doubt in my mind ♪
♪ That you're one of a kind ♪
[sniffles] Thanks, everyone.
And you're right. I do have a family.
All of you.
And while you might be back
staying in your own exhibit from now on,
you can hang out with us at night.
Really? You mean it?
Of course!
[grunts] Ooh! Uh! Oh!
Yes, of course! [chuckles]
You are an honorary eagle, after all.
[exclaims]
[boy] Huh.
-[boy 2] Who's this guy?
-A dodo?
So he's one of a kind? Cool!
Everything in the museum is in the right
place, and Dudley's in his exhibit.
I'm so proud of you. You've earned this.
-[mystical twinkling]
-[gasps]
[epic music playing]
I did it! My first stamp! Wow.
Looks like everything ended up
where it was supposed to be.
[music fades]
[Ridley] My dinner with Ismat.
It's a tight game.
Kickballers on first and third.
Ismat at the plate.
As queen, I'm totally comfortable
being the decider.
And I declare that we shall win!
[all chanting] Ismat! Ismat! Ismat!
[trumpet sounds]
Oh. Uh… [chuckles]
That's me! Gotta go!
Wait, what about the game?
Yeah, one trumpet means dinner.
Gotta get home.
Huh. You know, it's weird.
I've seen everyone else's exhibits,
but I've never been to yours.
Really? What? Yeah, so see ya!
Wait, as long as the game's over,
why don't we walk you home?
That's so nice,
but, um, I'm actually getting picked up.
Oh! Hi, guys.
Here's my ride. Thanks though!
Did I say "picked up"?
I meant walking home.
Yep, walking. Bye!
Was it me, or was Ismat
acting kind of weird right now?
And has anyone else
actually been to her place?
Let's start a new game!
-I'm up next.
-Play ball!
Wait. Don't you guys think
we should check on Ismat?
Nope.
Come on. We're her friends.
Something was clearly bothering her.
We should find out what it is.
[begrudgingly] Okay.
Oh, there she is!
[sighs]
Wow! Looks like the princess
is treated like a princess.
I thought she was a queen.
Ugh, same difference.
I think she's good.
So can we get back to playing?
Just because she's being totally pampered
doesn't mean something isn't wrong.
Even though it looks so, so right.
Ismat, wait up!
Ridley? Dante, Dudley, Peaches, and Fred?
Your Highness.
Got a little carried away?
"Carried away"? Oh. [chuckles]
This? [laughs]
Whoa! Uh…
I… I wasn't being carried.
That's not what this is.
So, what are you guys doing
in this neck of the museum?
-Looking for you.
-[doors opening]
Ismat! There you are!
Ready for a royal feast?
Dude. Am I? I am hungry!
Hey, Hungry, nice to meet you.
Kidding! Kidding! Mummy-dad joke.
Wait…
You're Ismat's friends!
Hiya, hi, hi!
We're the dads.
I'm Aten. This is Kosy.
It's really nice to finally meet you.
Ismat's told us all about you.
Nice to meet you too!
She's told us nothing about you.
Well, then,
you all just have to stay for dinner.
We'll get extra place settings
from the basement.
[Ismat] Wait! Dads!
Ismat, you weren't trying to hide
that you have two dads, were you?
'Cause that seems awesome to me.
What? No!
Having two dads is the best.
I get to hear twice the dad jokes!
Then why haven't you invited us over?
If your part of the exhibit is small
or kinda cramped, that's cool!
I promise to watch the tail.
That's definitely not it.
You'll see what I mean.
[all] Whoa!
[Dudley] Ay, chihuahua!
Okay, definitely not small or cramped.
My tail can have its own wing.
My wings can have their own tail!
That… that doesn't make any sense.
But still, this place is ginormous.
You live here?
Yeah, but only this room,
and the next room,
and the 33 rooms after that.
But… but that's it. [chuckles nervously]
Just a simple royal life.
Whoa!
Uh, I guess it's time to sit down to eat!
Can you believe this place?
It might be bigger and more impressive
than I am.
It's out of this world!
And I've been out of this world!
Good evening, ladies and gentle-mummies.
Before we eat,
we present to you our queen.
Queen Ismat Chione Jomana
Edrice Khepri the Great…est.
[trumpet sounds]
But you can just call me "Ismat."
It's not really a big deal.
Now, let us begin
the first of our nightly "big deals."
The royal mummy pampering!
Uh… [chuckles nervously]
Dudes. I've seen a lot of wild stuff
in my 65 million years,
but this is way over the top.
Can I get another fan over here?
One for each wing?
[sighs]
Talk about five-pyramid treatment.
I don't know.
Ismat doesn't look too happy about it.
[mouthful] Ooh, I know it looks like
I get treated like a queen…
Well, I mean, I do. I am.
But it's not as fancy as it seems.
Oh, good,
'cause, uh, it seems ridiculously fancy.
Next you're gonna tell us
there are dancing peacocks.
No! [chuckles]
I actually, um… The thing is…
And now for the most important part of
our nightly tradition.
"Nightly"? You get treated this way
every night?
Presenting the queen's crown!
Bowing. Bowing.
Not looking in your eyes. Bowing.
Wait! [splutters] No! Dads!
The thing is… Enough! That's enough!
Dinner is over!
-[all gasp]
-Sweetie!
I'm not your sweetie!
[all gasp]
I mean, I am. I love you, Dads, kiss-kiss,
but right now, I'm the queen!
And by royal decree,
I'm canceling dinner!
[all gasp]
[melancholy music playing]
[Ridley] Ismat, what's going on?
You can tell us. We're your friends.
But also your subjects, so please,
no "off with his head"-ing.
I like my head.
She can't really do that.
-Can you?
-I can.
-[gasps]
-But I wouldn't.
[sighs] The truth is,
I never invited you over
because I'm kind of embarrassed
of all of this whoop-de-do!
Every night, our dinner has
all of these grand traditions,
and I get pampered
from head-wrap to toe-wrap!
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I like a little pampering.
I'm a queen, after all,
but not every night.
I don't think I'd mind it at all!
I could rock a throne and a scepter.
I like hanging out with you guys
because you treat me like a normal kid.
Even when my queenly side
comes out in front of you.
Of course!
You'll always just be Ismat to us.
I know. But my dads get carried away.
And they treat me more like a royal
than a daughter.
I kinda miss just being a kid. Their kid.
[Peaches] Bringin' these arms in
for a landing.
Thanks, everyone.
You should tell your dads
what you just told us.
I'm sure they'd wanna know.
You're right.
I need to tell them that I don't wanna
wear this crown every night.
Wait, the crown, where did it go?
Crown down! Crown down!
Nothing in here except, uh…
[chewing] …delicious leftovers. [gulps]
Oh no. My dads are gonna be crushed
when they find out I lost the crown!
I already hurt them when I yelled at them.
I gotta make this better! What do we do?
Don't worry, Ismat. We'll find it.
We just need to keep an eye out.
Or should I say eyes in the sky?
[chitters]
All right, y'all. Got my peepers on peeps
from every wing in the museum.
I'll find out where that crown is.
Wait, is it--
What in NASA is goin' on over there?
False alarm! Give me a sec.
There we go!
Ridley, one of the mummy subjects
must've accidentally cleared the crown
with the dinner dishes!
Okay, we'll head that way.
I'll stay in case my dads come back.
Good luck! Make your queen--
I mean, your friend proud!
You got it!
Okay, head to the right up ahead,
then to the left!
There it is!
Hurry!
We got the box now.
[Ridley] That's a lot of boxes.
So, the crown is now in this giant room,
in one of these boxes,
which all look the same?
Time to start unboxing. And fast.
Hey, trying to nap here!
Sorry!
Don't see it in--
Whoa!
Wipeout! Comin', little buddy!
Wait, Dante!
Whoa! Look out!
Ah! Box tidal wave!
Whoa! [grunts]
Dudley, you found it!
[muffled] Ha! It wasn't easy.
You know what they say.
Heavy is the head that wears the crown.
[laughing]
Oh, Dudley!
[muffled] No, I'm serious.
This is really heavy. Help!
Ridley, everyone, thank you.
I don't know what I would've done
if the crown was lost forever.
Dad, Dad, I'm sorry
for hurting your feelings by royal decree.
And for not being honest with you.
Well, you were a little "royal,"
so apology accepted.
But what's been goin' on with you, kiddo?
Well, it's kinda embarrassing having
you treat me like a queen all the time.
I didn't want my friends to see.
And sometimes I just miss having you be
my dads instead of my subjects.
[mid-tempo music playing]
♪ I must admit
I love the banquets and the bowing ♪
♪ And OM-Ra
This crown feels perfect on my head ♪
♪ But there are days when even with
The sweet subservient kowtowing ♪
♪ I'd like to be a normal kid instead ♪
♪ Sometimes I long to be
An ordinary family ♪
♪ Just my two dads and me ♪
♪ I love the way my subjects
Dote upon their leader ♪
♪ And all this fanning
Well, I'm totally a fan ♪
♪ You wouldn't think a queen could tire
Of her own personal grape-feeder ♪
♪ But every now and then
I guess she can ♪
♪ Sometimes there's something
I would rather be than royalty ♪
♪ Just my two dads and me ♪
Is that okay
to have a night not fit for a queen?
-Are you kidding me? Of course!
-What a relief!
Huh? You're not upset?
Not at all!
You know you can tell us anything.
And it's pretty tiring
sticking to strict traditions every night.
You know how much polish it takes
to keep a crown shiny?
Plus, we're not exactly
a traditional family,
which is pretty mummerific.
Thanks for inviting us
for dinner again, Ismat!
Yeah, it's good to be back.
I could really use some pampering
right about now. Loyal subjects? Hello?
[chuckles] Dudley!
My dads and I gave everyone the night off
so we could have a quiet dinner with you.
What? But then who'll feed me grapes? Me?
Hey, Dante,
you can use your tail to feed me.
No problem, little dude!
Okay, a little lower… a little lower…
[gulps, sighs]
A bird could get used to this.
[all laughing]
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]