[opening theme music playing]
[female singer]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray ♪
♪ And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[music ends]
[Ridley] The taming of the tail.
Hey, Grandma!
Oh, Ridley, your vine work
is really coming along.
Yeah, I think I'm getting the swing of it.
So, what's in the crate?
Whoa!
Look at all these vases.
From every corner of the world.
Ooh, careful with the swinging, dear.
The pottery is very breakable.
Don't worry, Grandma, I'm always care--
Whoa!
Well… [chuckles] …almost always.
What's it all for anyway?
Our new world pottery exhibit!
I'm building a space for it,
then I'll load the pieces inside.
I could really use an extra pair of hands
to get everything ready. Wanna help?
Really? Me? Yes! I accept!
I'll do it! Thank you, Grandma.
I'm so happy
I could swing on a vine, and--
But I won't.
[chuckles] I know, too many breakables.
-[rattling]
-Oops! Can't take this thing anywhere.
Except I have to
because it's attached to me.
-Hey, everybody!
-Hiya, sunshine!
Ooh!
Are you redecorating the tree house?
I love a good makeover.
Nope! These are
for the new world pottery exhibit
that I, Ridley Jones,
am helping Grandma set up.
Wait a stegosecond.
We can help with the pottery too!
-I love new exhibits.
-Cool!
Let's make it an official
Eyes of the Museum mission!
Come on, team. Eyes on three! One, two…
Sorry. Ralph here's pretty excitable.
You know how tails are.
I'm not so sure it's a good idea
to have Dante help tonight.
This pottery is one-of-a-kind
and very, very, very fragile.
It really needs to be handled with care.
And Dante, well…
Come here, Ralphie!
[chuckles] Come here! Oops!
Yeah, he does have a knack
for knocking things over.
As a protector of the museum,
I need to do what's best for the pottery.
Spoken like a true Jones woman.
You know, I think I'll help Grandma
by myself.
This is a Jones family job!
We can't leave you alone!
We're the Eyes of the Museum.
All for one dudette
and one dudette for all!
Watch out!
That tail is bananas!
Whoa! Board wipeout!
Psst! Eyes, huddle up.
I think you-know-who
needs to tame his tail
before he can go near any of the pottery.
"You-know-who?" I don't know who.
Is it me? [gasps] It's me, isn't it?
No, it's Dante!
Oh. I should've known that.
But Dante's part of the team.
Yep. Which is why we're gonna help him.
We can show him how to move carefully
around fragile stuff.
Bisonic idea! Let's go tell him.
Wait! Saying the training is only for him
might hurt his feelings.
True. As the very last dodo,
I know how it feels to be singled out.
[drill whirring]
Time to whip this new exhibit space
into shape!
Oh, cool, power tools!
Uh, Dante, wait! We can't go in there yet.
Not until we have a team training session.
[laughs] A training session?
You pullin' my scales?
What kind of training do we need
to move a couple vases around?
Uh, oops! [chuckles]
We need someone who knows
how to handle having a big tail.
And I know who has the biggest tail
in the whole museum!
Mrs. Sanchez knows all about hanging
around priceless artifacts!
She can show us how to not,
you know, knock stuff over.
Indeed I can.
Now, find your flow.
Be one with your tail.
And try an "om"…
[all] Ooh.
What if you don't have a tail?
Then just go with the flow.
I'm in the flow zone.
-[drill whirring]
-[screams]
Now I'm in the no-flow zone!
Dante, it's just Grandma's drill!
[Dante screaming]
I'm spinning out!
[grunts] I don't think this is the pose
we were going for.
Is all of this really necessary, princess?
It's "queen." And yes.
As a royal and fashionista,
I'm the perfect mummy
to teach Dante poses and poise.
We need to move around the pottery
with respect. That's poise.
And given the choice,
you should always do it in style!
That's poses.
Aw. None of that happens
when I clap in my exhibit.
Balance these scrolls on your head,
and let's try,
"Follow the Ancient Egyptian Leader!"
Chin up. Shoulders back.
And strut. And turn.
And strut. And turn!
Gimme your best mummy-smize!
[grunts] Ah!
I'm getting mummy-wrapped up! [grunts]
[chuckles]
I don't think poses
were a step in the right direction.
You all know me
as a rough and tough beast…
-The cutest rough and tough beast!
-I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
But I'm also a bit of a twinkle toes.
Or hooves!
Being light on my hooves helps me
not break things when I'm stompin' around.
How can we be light on our hooves
if we don't have hooves?
By doing my patented,
secret bisonic dance moves!
Line up here and follow my groove.
[dance music playing]
[singsong] Hoof it to the left,
cha-cha-cha!
Hoof it to the right!
Now spin and roar! Cha-cha-cha!
[all] Roar! Cha-cha-cha!
Wait! My tail's
cha-cha-cha-ing the wrong way!
[strains, grunts]
Sorry, I guess the bisonic dance class
isn't for beginners.
Houston, it's time
for some basic training. Over!
Astronauts might be famous
for being shot through the sky
at hundreds of miles an hour,
but we also perfected our controlled,
low-gravity walk.
I mean, what could be better
for being around super breakable things?
Not moving at all.
That's what I always do
in dangerous situations.
[laughs] Nothing!
[Dante] Woo-hoo!
Yeah!
Dante, no!
[exclaims] Sorry, everyone!
It was my tail!
[Ridley] Oh no!
[crashing, thudding]
It's headed for the pottery!
Dante, gimme your board!
-[sighs]
-[Dante] Whoa! This place is a mess!
[Ridley] Oh no.
-I'll clean up over by the pottery.
-[all] No!
Uh, what we mean is, we'll clean it up.
You just, uh, have a seat.
Away from the pottery.
Oh! Um, okay, I guess.
I mean, it's kinda far from the action,
but if it's what you want…
[clank]
Wait. The museum is a mess
because I made it a mess.
Dude, I think I'm the problem!
No wonder my friends don't want me around.
How can I protect the museum
when all I do is break it?
Looks like it's just you and me
from here on out, Ralph.
[emotional music playing]
♪ I guess it's clear
Don't need to fuss ♪
♪ They're better off
They don't need us ♪
♪ We're always in the way
On a Jurassic scale ♪
♪ So now it's down to me and you ♪
♪ And nothing can part this party of two ♪
♪ We'll find a safer place
For you to flop and flail ♪
♪ 'Cause from now on
It's just me and my tail ♪
♪ So I will go where no one else
Can ever find me! ♪
♪ Because I know
That you will always be behind me! ♪
♪ We're quite attached
Joined at the hip ♪
♪ A tale of true appendage-ship ♪
♪ And, dude, there's just no way
That I will ever bail ♪
♪ Yeah, from now on
It's just me and my tail ♪
I love you, little dude!
[song ends]
How's the sitting still thing
working out, Dante? Eh, Dante?
Huh? That's his team bandana.
Dante never takes it off
on our adventures.
Why would he do that?
Oh, maybe he thinks he's not part
of our adventures anymore?
I need to find him.
-I need to make this right.
-[drilling]
Sorry about the noise, Rids!
Setting up this exhibit needs
a surprising amount of jackhammering.
[drilling]
Does anyone else think that sounds like a…
[Fred gasps] Stampede!
I bet the herd got spooked
by Grandma's jackhammer.
We need to keep the pottery
from getting pulverized!
Protect the pottery!
[gasps] Wait, that sounds like Ridley.
I should go make sure she's okay!
Though I bet I'd just make things worse.
No. Tail or no tail, my friends need me!
I think the pottery's
about to go to pieces!
And so am I!
[Dante] Not if I can help it!
-Dante!
-You came back!
'Scuse me! Sorry, dudes!
-Okay, go take cover. It's tail time!
-[Dudley whimpers]
Be one with my tail!
Chin up, shoulders back, mummy-smize!
And roar, cha-cha-cha!
And freeze!
Oh! He froze and did nothing!
That's my move.
And it worked!
-[Ridley] You did it!
-Aces!
-[Dudley] Nice freezing!
-Aw.
I was happy to help.
Even if I can't be part
of the team anymore.
Wait. There's something
I need to tell you.
Those training sessions
were just for you to tame your tail.
But we only did it
because you're our friend.
We wanted to make sure
you were part of the team.
Even with my troublemaking tail?
We all have something about ourselves
we're working on.
Like, I'm still figuring out
how to be a protector of the museum.
I might actually be too big and too tough.
Or I'm too cute and too adorable.
And my legs turn to mush every time
I'm too high in the sky.
The point is,
these things shouldn't keep us apart.
We're stronger together.
All for one dudette
and one dudette for all, right?
That's right. Bring it in, big guy.
Sorry for not telling you
the truth, Dante.
We'll all be honest from now on.
It's what good museum protectors
and friends do.
That sounds cretaceous.
[strains] This one is on loan
from my own personal collection.
I was using it to store my clean socks.
Very nice, dear.
I've got the perfect spot
at the top of the exhibit.
Hmm. But I have no idea
how to get it up there.
Whoa! [grunts]
[all grunt]
Tail nail!
The pottery exhibit is finished!
Which means you officially earned a stamp
for helping me build it.
Passport, please, Miss Ridley Jones.
Couldn't have done it without you.
[mystical twinkling]
And I couldn't have done it
without my friends.
[chuckles] Or their tails.
[all laughing]
[Ridley] Tunnel vision.
[whimsical music playing]
Hey, Mama! Hi, Mr. Peabody!
-Hi, Rids!
-Yikes! It's kind of a mess in here.
[strains, grunts]
[yelps, grunts]
What in blazes is this thing?
That's the Golden Hammer of Mambrino.
[strains, yelps, grunts]
Careful! It… it's heavy.
So, why is everything on the floor?
[sighs] Museum inventory. We have to check
every single artifact in the museum
to make sure nothing is lost
or in the wrong place.
Every item, all of it.
From this unnecessarily heavy hammer
to the smallest fossil.
I need to know how valuable…
I mean educational… this museum is.
I explained to Mr. Peabody
that inventory
is a big job to do all in one night.
And I explained, I want the museum
accounted for by morning,
or I'll hire someone who can.
Ugh! It's gonna take me all night
just to check off the things I can find.
Wow! Wait.
There are things you can't find?
This meteorite from the space wing
and this old bicycle.
Also, something Grandma
and I have never been able to find.
The baseball that was hit
for the first-ever home run.
Finding all of these by morning
is going to be almost impossible.
Not if I help.
And don't forget about us!
Yes! Great timing, team.
We have an epic
Eyes of the Museum mission tonight.
Operation Help Mama
find the stuff on her really long list.
-Yeah!
-Ready for launch!
Let's do this!
Okay, but where do we start?
How about with the princess's crown?
It's "queen,"
and hooves off the most royal of bling!
Why don't we look for the missing stuff,
Mama?
Then you can focus on everything else.
Ridley, great idea.
Okay, over the years,
the protectors of the museum
scribbled down notes about the artifacts.
These maps show where the bicycle,
meteorite, and baseball were
before they disappeared.
Thanks for your help, Eyes.
We'll protect the museum together.
-Juras-sick!
-Bisonic choice!
I think we should use the buddy system
to find this stuff.
Dante, you go with Peaches…
-Juras-sick!
-Well, hot dog!
-Dudley, you're with me.
-I'm your wingman!
And that leaves team Fred and Ismat.
-[Fred] I'll lead!
-[Ismat] Follow me!
Uh, Fred? As someone
who was literally born to be a leader,
I should hold the map.
[grunts]
Sorry to break it to you, princess,
but as the roughest, toughest,
and bravest bison in the herd,
I should have it.
It's the buddy system, remember?
So, buddy up on the map too!
All right, Eyes of the Museum team,
let's move out!
-Woo-hoo!
-Yippee!
-Make way for the bi--
-[both strain, grunt]
You mean "queen"?
[groans]
According to the map,
the baseball's up somewhere high.
And what's one of the highest places
in the rotunda?
Well, hello there!
Hi, Mrs. S!
Have you seen a baseball
around here lately?
Her royalness thinks it might be up here.
I'm sure it isn't,
but mind if we have a look?
Be my guest!
But I should warn you,
my tail is very, very…
[laughing]
-[Ismat] My wraps!
-[Fred] My horns!
…ticklish!
Strike out on the baseball being up here!
Now hand over that map.
I have a better idea.
[Ismat] The spaceship? I dunno.
Wouldn't Peaches know
if there was a baseball on her roof?
Maybe it's inside the ship.
-Hmm. Does this open the trunk?
-Wait, don't touch that!
Ah! That's the liftoff button!
Turn it off! Turn it off!
[male voice] Four, three, two,
one, liftoff-- Never mind.
-[sighs]
-Told you not to touch that!
Well, it was worth a try!
Not a try that launches us into space!
Hey, I heard a noise. And a blast.
And some yelling. Everything okay?
The buddy system isn't working
because we're not buddies.
On that, we agree! Can we just work alone?
Alone? Why?
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Just look at us
I think you'll see ♪
♪ We're opposite
As two friends could be ♪
♪ I like to roam through grassy plains ♪
♪ While I like desert-y, dry terrains ♪
♪ I'm so refined ♪
♪ I'm tough and strong ♪
♪ We're too different to get along ♪
♪ The strangest pair you've ever seen ♪
♪ She's a princess ♪
♪ I'm a queen! ♪
♪ My pharaoh friends have been interred ♪
♪ I'd rather run with my favorite herd! ♪
♪ We can't duet ♪
♪ Need our own song ♪
♪ We're way too different to get along ♪
♪ There's no debate ♪
♪ We're just not meant to collaborate ♪
♪ I'm always right ♪
♪ I'm never wrong ♪
♪ We're way too different to get along ♪
♪ We'll never get along ♪
[song ends]
You two are different.
The most different friends
I've ever met, actually.
Doesn't mean you can't work together
to find the baseball, right?
I've gotta catch up with Dudley,
but please try. For Mama and me?
[both groan]
-[Fred] Okay.
-If it's for you and your mom.
Hey, wait a mummy.
The point on my pyramid
is usually facing up.
You've been holding the map upside down!
No, you have!
-[gasps] The baseball isn't up above.
-It's down below!
According to the map,
there's a hidden door in the trunk.
-Right…
-Here!
Bisonic!
Mummazing!
I can't believe this was in the
lost-and-found the whole time!
Gimme some feathers, Dudley.
Right back at ya.
[chuckles] You're the best buddy
a dodo could ask for.
One down, two to go.
We can do this.
[Ismat] That's a lotta hallways,
and I can't tell
which one leads to the baseball.
But if I had to guess…
Time to follow my bison sense!
It's never wrong.
Let's go…
-This way!
-That way! Oh! The map!
You ripped it!
Nice job, princess!
Way to go, buffalo!
I'm a bison. There's a difference.
And labels matter.
This isn't working!
We gave the buddy system a shot,
but it's time for this bison
to hoof it solo.
Well, same here!
I'm a mummy leader, not a mummy follower.
Gotta be careful.
If these halls are like the ones
in my pyramids,
they're full of booby traps.
Ah! Booby trap! Or just really strong AC.
Either way-- [screams]
Can't believe I'm gonna say this,
but I could use a tough,
stampeding bison right about now!
Whoa!
I can't see a foot in front of my fuzz.
Oh, I wish Ismat were here
with her glowing beetle night-light.
Moo!
[suspenseful music playing]
What? What'd you see?
Spiders? Zombies? Spider zombies?
Worse! A dead end!
[sighs] Here. You take the map.
And the lead. For good.
Seriously?
Yeah. We're getting nowhere like this.
Plus, who knows hallways
better than a queen?
My exhibit does have 50 of them.
Thanks, Fred. Let's find that baseball.
Okay, this says the ball was last seen
in the storage room, here!
Ta-da!
Huh? Empty.
And the only thing in here is that lever.
Oops!
The baseball!
Grab it!
[rattle]
[both scream]
-[bell ringing]
-Someone order a radical old-timey bike?
It was in the Amazon River exhibit.
Go figure. Dino-monkey buddy bump!
[both grunt]
Amazing job, team!
But we're still missing the baseball.
And two buddies.
I wonder where Fred and Ismat are?
[both groaning]
The trash chute? Really?
Being stuck in the trash
is the perfect end
to our mission together.
Oh! [grunts]
This could not get any worse.
-[whirring]
-Uh…
Looks like things can get worse!
So, don't even think of trying to give me
a comforting hug right now.
Same! I don't need any reassurance
from a brave friend.
[Fred, Ismat scream]
Uh, do y'all hear that?
[gasps] The tree house
has a secret trap door?
That is so cool!
[Ismat] I might as well tell you,
I've admired your bisonic dance moves!
[Fred] And I know
that you're actually a queen!
[gasps] That's Ismat and Fred!
Are you sure?
It's them. Sounds like they need help.
Because of the panic in their voices?
Or that they're being nice to each other?
Either way, we should go save them.
-[whirring]
-I think our stampede ends here.
[snorts, sobs]
I'm glad I shared it with you.
It's been a royal honor to be your friend.
-[thud]
-[gasps] Ridley? [whimpers]
-We weren't hugging!
-Um, okay?
You can jam that board between the walls
and climb out of the trash chute,
but only if you work together.
[Fred grunts]
[both grunt]
Up you go, my queen.
-Oh, and take this for safekeeping.
-Thanks, Fred.
[Ismat grunts]
[both straining]
[both grunt]
Woo-hoo!
Ah!
[grunts]
-Fred!
-We'll get you out of there, Fred!
Okay, everybody, link arms. And feathers.
[tense music playing]
[grunts] I can't reach you, Fred!
Ismat!
[pants] Unless… Grab my crown!
But what about
"keep your hooves off the bling"?
As your queen and your friend,
I command you to grab it!
Now pull!
[grunts]
[all grunt]
-Epic save!
-Close call!
We did it!
So you found the meteorite
and the bicycle.
But where's the baseball?
You mean this baseball?
Oh!
Well, I'll be a space monkey's uncle.
[laughs]
That means--
The museum inventory is complete.
Well, I guess it is all here.
Now I'll know if anything goes missing.
Yes I will! Yes I will!
Nothing gets past me.
[chuckles, exclaims, grunts]
[all laughing]
I meant to do that.
[groans]
I didn't mean to do that. [groans]
Thank you, Eyes. I never would've
found everything without your help.
Passport, please, Miss Ridley Jones.
You've earned an inventory stamp!
Thanks, Mama! That was a close one.
Sorry, Ridley.
Even though we were buddied up,
I kept trying to do everything myself.
Me too.
Turns out, when we actually work together,
we make a good team.
Told ya!
The two of you together is a home run.
-Sure thing!
-Of course!
Ismat… [chuckles] …you know that
mushy stuff I said in the trash chute?
Yeah, it's okay.
I know you didn't mean any of it.
Mm, that's the thing, I kinda did.
Really? I meant what I said too.
Being an odd couple has its perks.
I still can't believe
you let me touch your crown!
Hey, that was a one-time-only event!
Hooves off the bling!
[both laughing]
[Fred snorts]
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]