[opening theme music playing]
[female singer]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray ♪
♪ And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[music ends]
-[whimsical music playing]
-[Ridley] Unfit for a queen.
[Dudley] So yummy.
Really glad we got to have this hard,
warm, ice-cream-wannabe brick.
It is ice cream. It's just freeze-dried.
You can't have your ice cream cone
dripping while you're in outer space!
Thank you, science.
-Thanks for dinner, Peaches.
-We should probably get home.
We're adding a new Sphinx fountain
to the courtyard.
It's twice as tall as me and lights up.
Don't forget the laser show!
That sounds amazing! Can we see it?
Oh, I don't know.
Should I play hard to get?
No! I totally want you to see it.
This fountain's truly
my crowning achievement! Yay me!
He installed it himself.
So, we'll see if it works.
Hey, hey, hey.
We mummies once built the pyramids.
I think I can handle a little home decor.
Ta-da!
[Ismat] Oh no! My dress'll be ruined!
[Dante] Surf's up!
-Run!
-Ah!
[Peaches muffled chattering]
[blowing, grunting]
Oopsie. I was saying there's good news.
This old eyesore-- I mean, fountain--
did not cause the leak!
I can't figure out
where all the water's coming from.
And there's a lot of it.
What about our house?
And all of our beautiful things?
I'm afraid it's all underwater.
Oh, Ismat, I'm so sorry.
Dads, are we gonna be okay?
We are because we have
everything we need right here.
Okay, I'm goin' back underwater
to investigate,
but I'll need someone strong as an ox
to come with me!
I'm both strong and like an ox.
We're gonna get wet.
Maybe someone else should go.
Nothing ruins a perfectly styled pair
of fake horns like water.
How about Dante?
Oh yeah! Scaly skin for the win!
How's your doggie paddle?
I mean, dino paddle?
I was at the tricera-top of my swim class!
[Peaches] All right!
-Juras-sick!
-Yippee!
Well, that was one wild night.
I'm exhausted. Ready for bed, everyone?
There's just one little
princess and the pea-sized problem.
Our exhibit is flooded, remember?
Oh, right.
You guys definitely can't go home.
Your wraps will unravel
if they get too wet.
-Yikes!
-Not a cute look.
Yeah, I don't need to see that.
Don't worry!
I'll find you someplace to sleep tonight.
Oh! I have lots of space in my exhibit
on account of being alone all of the time.
I think I see
where you're going with this, Dudley.
Aten, Kosy, you two can bunk
with Dudley in the dodo exhibit.
And Ismat, why don't we have a sleepover?
Sleepover? I want in!
Hope you don't snore, princess!
Queens never snore!
They just breathe loudly in their sleep.
Sounds like snoring to me.
Kind sirs and lady, I heard about
the incident with your royal bedchambers.
Why don't you take
my chain mail sleeping set?
I think you'll find them most comfortable.
Whoa!
Thank you.
Aw, thank you.
Now I can clean one tooth at a time.
And I can sing you all a lullaby.
[bellowing]
Thanks, Mrs. Sanchez.
See, Ismat? We're all here for you.
Thanks, everyone! You're the best!
[sighs] I almost forgot that I can't sleep
at home in my own room.
Here's our beddy-bye bunk.
I think that maybe we'll need something
a little bit roomier?
Of course. I totally understand.
Give me just a second.
[clanking]
[grunts]
[inhales, blows]
Sorry, um…
I lost the power cord in the Serengeti.
[inhales, blows]
Ridley, don't forget to put away
your rope and binoculars.
We don't want a repeat of last week.
Some people sleepwalk, I sleep-adventure.
Peaches to Mama! Come in, Mama!
I think I found
where the water's coming from.
There's a leak
in the Amazon River exhibit next door!
[Dante] Dude,
there are piranhas everywhere!
[grandma] Ouch! Ooh! Ah!
We are not on the menu!
I'm sure they're fine,
but I'm gonna go check.
Because, you know, piranhas.
Whew! Guess it's time to hit the hay.
Oh, sorry. Did you… [gulps] …need this?
[laughs] No, I meant it's bedtime.
I'm just gonna get the light, and--
Wait! I'm, uh, having a hard time getting
comfortable with a commoner pillow.
At home, mine was Egyptian cotton.
[grunting]
There you go, princess.
Ridley, the light, please?
Uh, wait!
[splutters] It's more than just my pillow.
It's the whole room!
I demand that we rearrange the furniture!
Also, it'll be super fun.
[both grunting]
A little to the left.
-[both grunting]
-Now a little to the right.
Now left.
We've rearranged the furniture five times.
This place is fixed up.
And then some.
Yeah, I think it's time to sleep.
Wait! It's not really a sleepover
until you play games, right?
[Ismat] Ooh, Ridley, your turn!
-Left foot blue.
-[Ridley snoring]
Ridley?
Whoa! Wha--
You win, princess! Bedtime!
Wait! Um…
[gobbling]
[mouth full]
Your queen demands a royal refill!
Is it just me, or is Ismat being
even more demanding than usual?
Oh, she's really outprincessing
herself tonight.
Need anything else?
We're all set!
No, thank you!
Are you sure? Some water? A fan?
Or maybe telling a bedtime story
to your favorite extinct bird
will help you fall asleep?
Okay, one story.
Once upon a time,
there was a very handsome mummy…
[sighs]
[Ridley sighs]
No, wait!
[Fred] Okay, that's it!
I didn't complain when you forced us
to make royal friendship bracelets
or when you made us style
each other's hair
because that was… [chuckles] …awesome,
but this has got to stop!
Just tell us what's really wrong
so we can finally go to sleep!
Yeah, it's obvious something
is bothering you, but you can tell us.
We love you no matter what.
She's right. We do.
Okay. You're right. I'm just gonna say it!
I'm afraid of the dark.
Why didn't you just tell us that?
I'm a queen!
Queens aren't supposed to have fears.
They're supposed to be brave leaders.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ A queen should rule the Nile ♪
♪ With a fearless sense of style ♪
♪ She ought to be immune
To such inconsequential frights ♪
♪ A queen should not routinely
Feel anxious and un-queenly ♪
♪ Any time somebody goes
And turns out all the lights ♪
♪ A queen should be audacious ♪
♪ If slightly ostentatious ♪
♪ She shouldn't be so royally afraid ♪
♪ A queen should run her nation ♪
♪ Without fear or trepidation ♪
♪ That's the way a leader
Makes her legendary mark ♪
♪ Intrepid and empowered
She shouldn't be a coward ♪
♪ A scaredy-Sphinx
Afraid of something silly like the dark ♪
♪ Adventurous and daring ♪
♪ As bold as what she's wearing ♪
♪ Why am I so royally afraid? ♪
♪ A queen should not be royally afraid ♪
[song ends]
Ismat, admitting you're afraid
is one of the bravest things you can do.
Telling us you're afraid of the dark
was really tough of you.
And I would know! I'm the toughest.
Look, telling everyone
what you're afraid of…
Well, that just makes you human.
A really old mummified human,
but you get what I mean.
It'll make you a better leader.
Thanks, Ridley. Thanks, Fred.
Hey. Now that we know
what you're afraid of,
we can really be there for you.
What makes you feel
less scared of the dark?
Well, the only way I can sleep at night
is with my glowing beetle night-light.
Of course, it's nice when
my royal subjects rock me to sleep too.
Sounds like we need to go on an adventure!
[Ridley whispers] Dudley! Psst!
-Are you awake?
-[whispers] No!
[Ridley] Then how are you whispering?
Yeah. You're right. [chuckles]
We need your help!
All right, team,
we're here on a rescue mission.
Ismat left something important
in her exhibit,
and we have to get it back.
Peaches, what's the status on the leak?
That's a 10-4.
Your mama and your grandmama
went into the Amazon River exhibit
to see if they could fix the leak
on that side.
[grandma] Not today-tor, gator! Get back!
Sounds like they have it under control.
Okay, everybody, follow my lead.
Oh, and watch out
for the Amazonian piranhas.
Okay, we gotta jump.
Ready? One, two, three, jump!
[all grunt]
[water splashing]
Everyone look out for
a night-light in the shape of a beetle.
Uh, you mean like that thing?
[gasps] And there it is!
Nice work!
I'll have to hop to it.
Peaches, can you keep an eye out
for any dangers up ahead?
-[Peaches] Roger that.
-[grunts]
Tangly vines, twelve o'clock!
[Ridley grunts]
Oh, look out, electric eels dead ahead!
[grunting]
Glad I forgot to put away my rope.
[grunting, straining]
-Got it!
-[Dudley] Ah! Piranhas!
-[gasps] Oh no!
-[Dudley] Hey!
[all gasp]
I don't think I'm gonna make it in time.
-Oh man.
-Ah! Scared. Really scared.
But now that I said it, I can face it
because saying I'm scared is being brave.
Hey, piranhas! Over here!
[action music playing]
-Whoa! Tubular!
-Way to go!
[Dudley] I saw my whole life
flash before my eyes.
Ridley, everyone,
thank you so much for helping me tonight.
We should be thanking you.
You saved our hides back there.
It's like Ridley told me.
It's okay to admit that I'm scared.
And as soon as I did,
I felt a whole lot braver.
Plus, I wanted to be a good leader.
And friend.
-You're the bravest queen I know!
-You're all right, princess.
-Proud of you, dude!
-[Peaches] So brave!
[snoring]
Fred, you're adorable.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Ridley, for traversing the waters
of the Amazon and helping your friends,
a new stamp!
Woo-hoo! I've got so many now!
And great news! We finally fixed the leak!
Turns out it was caused by a poor anaconda
who just needed glasses.
Luckily, we have the same prescription.
Aten, Kosy, Ismat. You can go home.
You guys are leaving already?
But I just made us dodo-donuts.
Oh, and they smell delicious.
Yum! Dudley, you're welcome to stay
at our place anytime.
Especially if you make these.
Really? You mean it?
Astronomical news!
I was able to save
a few of your things from the water.
[gasps] This is the only treasure I need.
-Oh, Ismie.
-Aw, I love you guys.
[Ridley] Peaches, we have a problem.
And we're clear.
All the visitors have left the building.
Which maybe means another stamp?
[chuckles]
Thanks for all your help today, Ridley.
Good work.
[mystical twinkling]
[yawns] I can't wait to get
in the tree house and take a load off.
Why not go now?
I mean, I can finish closing up by myself.
Are you sure you're ready?
[chuckles] Seriously? So ready.
I have things to learn,
but if you're teaching me
to run the museum,
this has to be on the list.
True. And with your mom out of town,
I could use all the help I can get.
I'd say you're ready.
Thank you, Grandma!
I promise to make sure everything,
and everyone, is safe and sound.
Let me know if you need anything.
There is one thing I need.
That's it! Your Compass Eye.
Now, I'm good to go.
-[keys jingle]
-[lock clicks]
-Hey, gang!
-Ridley!
-Hi!
-Wow!
Those are some sweet new wheels, sunshine!
Thanks!
Now that I'm a protector in training,
Mama decided to get me
my very own museum cruiser.
I am ready for some adventure!
-[rattling]
-Dude, what was that?
Maybe the penguins
got in the snow cone machine again?
Shh. Let's go find out.
-Keys?
-I got it, I got it!
[gasps] It's Mr. Peabody and Lonny!
Museum Mayday!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
No time to get to your exhibits.
Just freeze, and… and try to blend in.
[Mr. Peabody] I told you someone was here.
Aha! Oh.
Ridley. It's just you.
Uh, Mr. Peabody? Lonny?
What are you guys doing here so late?
I've noticed peculiar activity
in the museum!
I think there may be some
funny business going on here at night.
What? No! I haven't seen anything funny.
So, I had Lonny here install
an electronic security system.
If something's going on in this museum
at night, I'll know about it.
Ta-da!
It all runs off of this thingamajig.
Mostly. I think?
Anyway, from the alarm to the lights,
to the doors, nothing gets past me.
If the alarm goes off… [sinister laugh]
…I'll be back.
So nothing will get past me either.
[chuckles] Especially tonight.
Okay, off to do my security rounds.
She's gone. For now, at least.
A security system? In the museum?
That's bad! Royally bad.
We won't be able to move around anymore!
When will I practice flying?
I'm getting really good
at visualizing myself flying.
-What about my skate tricks?
-Or my big gruff beast roars?
[roars]
Life in the museum as we know it
is going to change forever!
I am not gonna let that happen.
As protector of this museum,
I'll keep our home free. I promise.
But how?
I don't know yet.
Peaches, see what you can find out
about Lonny's security system.
Copy that.
I'm your eyes in the sky.
Let's see what Lonny's been up to.
-[typing]
-Weird. I don't see any extra security.
Then again, Lonny's never been
very good at her job.
Hmm. I'm forgetting something.
Oh yeah! I forgot to turn it on.
-[laughs, makes beeping sounds]
-[tablet beeps]
[lasers whirring, beeping]
-[gasps] Lasers?
-Whoa!
-Watch out!
Uh, Peaches?
We have a problem.
I think Lonny's better at her job
than we thought!
Yep. I can't believe it,
but Lonny's system looks foolproof!
Hang tight until I can turn it off.
[gasps] It works!
I can't believe it works!
-[alarm blaring]
-[screams]
Why'd you have to work?
-Alarm off! Off!
-[alarm continues]
Aw, come on! Just this once,
let me get something right!
Peaches? Lonny's headed your way.
[whimpers] But I still haven't figured out
this darn security system!
[Ridley] She's almost to the room!
-Get out now!
-[door rattling]
Why is this door locked?
Is someone in there?
Alarm, turn off!
Pretty please with pickles on top?
Oh boy.
I sure am up pretty high right now.
[gulps]
Come on!
-Oh, I give up! [gasps]
-[computer chimes]
Security system deactivated?
The lasers!
-They're off!
-Yes!
I'm saved!
Peaches, the lasers are off,
and everything is back to normal!
Why did it have to be heights?
Ooh! I can't look anymore!
-It's too scary!
-[crackling]
[alarm sounding]
I don't think
this is what "back to normal" looks like.
[exclaims]
[Ridley] Peaches, we have a new problem.
Or, make that lots of new problems.
What happened?
[splutters] I was hidin' in the ceiling
and had a little banana blunder.
-This is nothin' I can't take care of!
-[beep]
-You sure? You sound scared.
-[alarm blaring]
Me? Scared?
[nervous chuckle] Of course not!
Remember who you're talkin' to.
Oh no!
With the stairs to the tree house out,
Grandma's trapped there.
It's up to us to get everyone into their
exhibits before Peabody gets back.
With Lonny walking around
and the museum going bananas,
how exactly are we supposed to do that?
I guess it'll be an adventure!
This way, mummies! You're almost home!
-[Dante] Yeah!
-[Dudley whimpers]
That's all well and good for them,
but is the Egyptian wing usually so foggy?
It's really making my hair horns
frizz out.
No, it's more of a dry heat.
Peaches, we've got fog
blocking our way out of here.
I got eyes on the fog, but not on you.
Hold, please.
All right, I got eyes back on you.
Everyone take two steps forward.
Now take three steps to the left.
Dante, your other left.
Oh. [chuckles]
Thanks, Peaches.
Now take one giant leap for monkeykind!
-Woo-hoo!
-[Dante] Sweet!
-Yeah!
-Thank you, Peaches!
Hey, butterflies, don't panic.
Your exhibit is just around that corner.
-Thanks!
-We're saved!
-Okay, now we need to get back to--
-[lasers beeping]
Uh-oh! More lasers!
-Run!
-[Ismat] Whoa! [grunts]
Ismat!
Keep going!
This might be a wrap for me!
[grunting]
Don't worry, Ismat.
We'll find a way to get you out.
But who's got the moves
to get through those lasers?
Yeah, not me. Or Ralph.
He's a terrible dancer. Oops!
But I'm not.
I got moo-ves!
[grunts, imitates dance music]
May I have this dance, princess?
It's "queen." But, yes, thank you, please!
[imitates dance music]
What can I say?
These hooves were made for dancin'!
You know you're the most
cute-cute-cuteity-cute bison ever, right?
[groans]
Yes. But I don't wanna be cute.
I wanna be a big gruff beast!
Peaches, is there any way
to get the museum back under control?
[Peaches] All the sensors are overloadin'!
At this point, all I can think to do
is shut off the electricity.
It looks like the power control box is…
[nervously] …way up there. [whimpers]
You need to blast off to reach it.
Oh no! The door is closing!
And Peabody's back!
I better rocket back to my exhibit.
Peaches over and out!
[Ridley] Hurry!
[grunts]
Whew!
Well, looks like none of us
are gettin' back to our exhibits.
What else could go wrong?
[all gasp, scream]
-[whimpers]
-[Ismat] This is not a good look.
We can't let Mr. Peabody see us like this.
Wait! That's the power control box, right?
We can turn off the electricity from here!
-Dude, that is a whole lotta wires.
-[electrical crackling]
-[thud]
-[all screaming]
[all gasp]
Peaches will know which one to cut.
Right, Peaches?
What's wrong?
[splutters] It might not be the best time
to tell you this…
[whimpers] …but I'm scared of heights.
But you're an astronaut.
Who's been strapped to a rocket.
That took you hundreds of miles
above the Earth!
By choice! How could you do that
if you're scared of heights?
I close my eyes during takeoff?
[yelps] Bad floor buffer, bad!
[buffer whirring]
Lonny! Let me in!
Wait. Is that why you sounded scared
when you were up in the ceiling earlier?
Why didn't you just tell us?
It's just that I've done a lot of
out-of-this-world things in my time,
and I've never let my crew down until now.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Maybe I don't have
the right stuff after all.
Everyone has fears, Peaches.
I'm scared I'll never find
my magical compass.
I'm terrified of missing
Cairo Fashion Week.
And I'm scared
Ralph's gonna move out one day.
I'm scared
I might not be scared of anything.
And I'm scared of everything.
Thanks, everyone.
But I still don't think I can move
a single astronaut muscle,
let alone cut the power.
Yes, you can.
For once, I'll be your eyes in the sky.
Look at me,
and I'll be your mission control.
♪ Your heart is pounding ♪
♪ You feel it race ♪
♪ But you're the primate ♪
-♪ Who braved the depths of outer space ♪
-♪ Outer space! ♪
♪ The task is daunting ♪
♪ But don't you scoff ♪
♪ Fire up your thrusters
You're blasting off ♪
♪ Rise above! ♪
♪ Face your fear! ♪
♪ As you soar across the sky
Your fears will disappear ♪
♪ Rise above ♪
♪ The odds are scary
The stakes are high ♪
♪ But you're the mammal ♪
-♪ Who somehow found a way to fly ♪
-♪ Flying chimp! ♪
♪ The clock is ticking ♪
-♪ We can't get caught ♪
-♪ Tick-tick-tock ♪
♪ We need our favorite monkey astronaut ♪
♪ Rise above! ♪
♪ Just believe! ♪
♪ Face your fear and there is nothing
That you can't achieve ♪
♪ Rise above ♪
♪ Rise above! ♪
[song ends]
Rise above, face my fear.
For you guys, I can do it!
Eh… [exclaims]
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
Aha! Gotcha! [splutters]
Wait. So…
-All this was a--
-[sighs] False alarm.
You know, Mr. P,
I'm more of a daytime security guard.
I think we should leave overnight security
to the Joneses.
Nobody knows the museum
better than they do.
Hmm. I suppose you're right.
For now, I can't prove
anything strange is going on, so…
[yawns]
I'm going home.
Need a lift?
Thank you, sir. Especially since
the floor buffer ate my car keys.
Yes! We did it!
The museum will stay a safe, open space
for all of us who call it home.
-Splendid!
-Roger that!
Mummazing!
Thank you for piloting me
through my fears, Ridley.
I couldn't have done it
without you as my wing-girl.
Anytime.
Fears are always easier to face
with a friend.
You're the wind beneath our wings,
Peaches!
[all laugh]
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]