[opening theme music playing]
[female singer]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray ♪
♪ And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[music ends]
[Ridley] A knight's tale.
[gasps] She's coming! Everyone get ready!
I'm so excited, I can barely stand it!
Me, too, Pedro.
On my count.
One, two, three!
[all] Surprise!
-[yelps] En garde, you beasts!
-[chuckles]
Oh.
Hello. Ha. My apologies.
I thought you were an ambush
of villainous roadside thieves.
Nope. Just us. We wanted to wish you luck
on your big day!
Big day?
[clears throat] What big day?
Fred found this
in the gift shop trash can!
Oh, uh… Hmm.
I have not the foggiest idea
what that could be.
It's an invitation to the annual
Round Table Tournament of Heroes!
And it's addressed to you, Ida!
[splutters] Are you sure it says my name?
Mayhaps it's for another Ida?
Yep, there's your name right there.
"Ida of the First Floor,
Guardian of the Rotunda,
Grand Master of the Gift Shop,
and Tamer of Lonny's Floor Buffer."
That is pretty specific.
We know it's been your dream
since you were a little knightling
to take home the first-place trophy
at the tournament.
And now,
you finally have the chance to do it!
Um, I must tell you all something.
That you're one of the greatest heroes
in my kingdom?
I mean, the museum?
[chuckles] Girl, we already know.
No, that's not exactly--
Let's hear it for Ida, a true hero!
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Three cheers for Ida
She's completed every quest ♪
♪ Who needs King Arthur
When you've got the very best? ♪
♪ She rescued Dudley
From the sticky spider web display ♪
♪ And slew the dragon
Of the second floor cafe ♪
[all]
♪ You're a hero, Ida, you're a hero ♪
♪ You're a hero, Ida, you're a hero ♪
♪ Through the rotunda
They recount her every deed ♪
♪ A knight so brave
She doesn't need a noble steed ♪
♪ She rid the lobby
Of each evildoer, rogue, and knave ♪
♪ And saved the cavemen
Who got lost in their own cave ♪
♪ Anyone could do those things, I feel ♪
♪ Trust me, it's no big deal ♪
♪ You're a very big deal ♪
[all]
♪ You're a hero, Ida, you're a hero ♪
Hey, hero! Catch me!
-Oh!
-[crashing]
-[gasps]
-[groaning]
Yep. Even a graceful, but tough,
bison like me
has to crash a few times
before landing a big move. [chuckles]
I'm sorry for letting you down, Fred.
I'm sorry for letting all of you down,
actually.
I was the one
who threw away the invitation.
Because… I'm no hero.
What? Of course you are!
It's not just my armor that's rusty.
It's me.
It's been so long
since I've done anything heroic,
I don't even know if I still have
what it takes to be a hero.
That is why
I'm not entering the tournament.
I must accept that my hero days
are behind me.
Today,
I am officially retiring from knighthood.
-[gasps]
-[Dudley] No!
-[Dante] Dude!
-[Ridley] Retiring?
My favorite knight is retired?
But she doesn't even have tires.
She's not retiring. Not if I can help it.
We can't let Ida forget about her
lifelong dream of winning the tournament.
I like the way you think, sunshine.
What's the mission?
Well, heroes always come to the rescue,
right?
We just need to create
some dangerous situations
so Ida can save the day!
Then she'll realize she's still a hero.
-[horses whinnying]
-[Pa screaming]
The horses won't stop!
We're gonna go right off
of that there cliff!
[both] Help!
[Ma] Somebody help!
Help!
To the rescue!
Woo-hoo! [grunts]
-[Ida grunts]
-Whoa! That was so cool!
[Ridley] It totally was!
Ida, you saved the settlers, Ma and Pa.
Howdy! Thanks to yer bravery, Ma and I
can continue on our journey west…
of the rotunda.
We hear there's some purdy nice exhibits
out that way.
Now all we gotta worry about is crossin'
that puddle by the water fountain.
And bandits.
[spits] But I can handle those.
So, ready to enter that tournament?
The tournament? Oh no!
All I did was save one little family.
Hey! Size don't matter.
Even a small rescue
is still an important rescue.
Even a squire could've done that.
Goodbye, tiny wagon-folk.
Stay safe on your quest.
Hmm. If we're gonna help Ida
get her groove back,
we're gonna need a bigger rescue.
Slip, slip, knit. And there you go!
[sighs] Zounds.
[panting] Ida! We need
your mad knightly skills, lady-dude!
There's a meteor storm in the Space Wing!
It's gonna destroy the space shuttle!
And a mummy's tied to the train tracks!
Oh, wait.
That was our first fake rescue idea.
I mean, Peaches is inside the shuttle!
Say no more. We must away!
Uh, hello? Are we still doing the whole
"tied to the train tracks" thing?
Queen Ismat?
[Ida] Oh!
Thank Saturn you're here, Ida!
I dunno how much longer my ship
can withstand this real meteor storm!
Heeya! Ho! Ha! Hee! Yah!
-[grunting]
-Ha!
And we're out.
Great job, team!
I'd say our hero
definitely hit a home run.
[blows]
You did it, Ida!
-That's amazing!
-Juras-sick!
You saved me and my shuttle.
That makes you one of the greatest heroes
in the galaxy.
Oh, oh, 'tis nothing.
Anyone with basic dragon-slaying training
can defend like that.
I don't know anyone else
who could do what you just did.
You've clearly never met Lancelot.
Oh! Look at the time.
Better hurry if I'm going to make it
to water aerobics
in the marine biology exhibit.
Fare thee well, friends!
Ugh! We're so close to helping Ida
believe she's a hero again.
I can feel it.
We just need to stage
one more super big rescue.
One that's really scary!
And astronomically dangerous!
Why do I have a feeling
I'm not gonna like this plan?
Oh! [gulps]
This is why.
Thanks for letting us borrow this rope,
Mrs. S.
No problemo.
Just make sure to return it
when you're done.
That rope gives me lower tail support.
Rope is secure! You good, Dudley?
Of course. I'm just a flightless bird
hanging helplessly over a volcano.
[laughs] Why wouldn't I be good?
Don't worry.
Dante'll pull you back to safety
if our plan doesn't work.
-Yeah, I got ya, dude! Oops!
-[Dudley screams]
[laughs]
No harm, no foul!
Or harm to fowl. Get it?
Because you're a bird!
[laughs] Yeah, never mind.
Places, everyone.
Let's get this hero show on the road.
Knight takes queen.
And robot. Huzzah!
Ida! We need your help!
Dudley was visiting Mrs. Sanchez,
and he fell into the volcano!
And it's gonna erupt any minute!
Ah. Help! I'm a dodo in distress.
-[lava burbling]
-[whimpers]
But seriously, somebody help!
It's getting really hot over here!
[action music playing]
[panting, grunts]
Thank you, your knightness.
I was about to be a deep-fried dodo.
Now that was heroic.
-You're darn tootin'!
-For sure!
Huh. I guess it was pretty heroic.
Can you sign this, pwease?
[giggles]
[clears throat] Hear ye, hear ye.
I have an announcement!
I, Ida of the First Floor,
have decided to compete in the
Round Table Tournament of Heroes!
-Hooray!
-Sweet!
Go, girl!
I must gather my things,
then depart for the competition!
[Ridley] You both did great.
Ida actually believed you were in trouble.
Yeah, we were purdy good.
Now, uh, about our payment…
Oh, right. Here you go.
[chomps] Yee-haw!
We're rich!
Anytime you need us
to fake like we need savin'…
[chuckles] …just give us a holler.
[melancholy music playing]
Ida? Oh no!
I think she might've overheard us.
Well, that ain't good.
She prolly don't feel like a hero no more.
But… [clears throat]
…we're still gonna be keepin' this penny!
Ida, wait! Let me explain.
It's all right, Ridley.
What you all did for me tonight was noble.
But I know it was not real.
I'm no hero, after all.
But you are! We all know that.
We just wanted you to believe it too.
Oopsies. Guess we forgot
to return this. [chuckles, gasps]
Oh no! My ropes!
Look out below! Oh!
[Dudley] We're about to be
whale tail pancakes!
Run for your lives!
[all screaming]
My picture!
Ouchie.
Oh no! Pedro!
You don't need to fake any more disasters
for me, Ridley.
Uh, that's not a fake disaster! It's real!
We need to save Pedro!
[gasps] Hang on, wee penguin!
[grunting]
Catch, Lady Jones!
Gotcha!
[grunts]
[epic music playing]
[Ida grunts]
Whoa!
[Dudley] She did it!
[Dante] Go, Ida!
You saved me! My hero!
That was incredible!
Do you really think I'm a hero?
Even though the other times weren't real?
Of course we do!
Sure, the situations
may not have been real,
but your actions were.
Yeah! You never think twice about riding
into danger to save someone.
Exactly.
It doesn't matter if your armor is rusty.
What makes a true hero
is what's beneath the armor.
Your heart.
And you, Ida, have the heart of a hero.
Thank you, Ridley.
Thank you, everyone.
For helping me remember
what it really means to be a hero.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a tournament to enter!
-Yes!
-[Dante] Crush it!
[Dudley] Be safe!
Just remember, trophy or no trophy,
you're still a hero to us.
Wow, so the trophy is an actual table.
Didn't see that coming.
It's the coolest twophy I ever saw!
Thank you, wee Pedro.
You may come over anytime
and help me polish it.
Three cheers for our friend, Ida.
A true hero.
[all] Huzzah! Huzzah! Huzzah!
Hey, hero! Catch me!
[all chanting] Ida! Ida! Ida!
-[whimsical music playing]
-[Ridley] Dudley's inferno.
[panting, whimpering]
-Hiya, Dudley!
-Greetings, our feathery friend.
Pierce! Shh! Use your inside squawk
so Lonny doesn't catch me
getting cozy in here. Huh? [laughs]
Buddies and birdseed,
all a lonely dodo needs.
Wanna watch the big show with me?
-[gulps]
-A big show?
What big show?
-[rumbling]
-Whoa!
That big show!
Dante's volcano! It's working again!
Woo-hoo!
The volcano's fixed and back in business.
Turned out there were
some dinosaur-sized socks jammed inside.
-Rids, will you lower the lift back down?
-On it!
Bravo, Joneses!
Everything's back to normal. [gasps]
Make that almost back to normal.
I have no idea how this dodo
keeps getting misplaced every night.
[Lonny laughs]
There ya go, little fella.
Back where you belong.
Lonny to Mr. Peabody. Hello?
If Lonny weren't around,
I wouldn't be stuck
in this lonely exhibit.
I'd have the keys to my freedom.
[gasps] Keys!
-Mr. P? You there?
-[beeps]
Hey! You're not my radio.
You're my ticket scanner!
Lonny to Mr. Peabody.
The Joneses fixed the volcano!
-Lonny!
-[yelps] Wow. That was fast.
Hurry up and lock the front doors
so I can go home.
[grunts]
Um, I'll walk you out.
Hmm. Uh…
Well, looking, looking… So many pockets!
Everything okay, Lonny?
Yeah, it's just--
I can't lock up because I've lost my keys
for the hundredth time!
Lonny, how can I make money off of--
I mean… [clears throat]
…safeguard this museum
if you can't even lock the front door?
Everyone makes mistakes, Mr. Peabody.
That's why I'm giving Lonny here
one last chance.
Find your keys before I get back,
or I'll have your badge
and your ticket scanner!
Because you'll be fired!
Fired?
This museum is the one place
I feel like I belong.
I know the feeling, Lonny.
My keys could be anywhere,
which means I have to search everywhere.
Ugh! I wish I was as good at
looking for things as I am at losin' 'em.
Bad news, everyone.
[Dudley] Great news, everyone!
-We have to find Lonny's keys!
-I took Lonny's keys!
[splutters] Wait. You have them?
Yep! Lonny's always putting me back
in my exhibit.
My lonesome, little exhibit.
But I'm a social bird, you know?
So how does taking Lonny's keys
change that?
Because if Lonny gets fired,
then the museum won't have
a security guard anymore.
I'm a genius!
But Lonny's part of the museum.
Even if she's not the best security guard
in the world.
She never even noticed
the banana stash I keep in her office.
We need to get Lonny's keys back to her
so she doesn't get fired.
It's the right thing to do.
Where'd you stash them, Dud-man?
[sighs] Follow me.
I hid them under my nest.
-Um, are you sure?
-The keys, they're gone!
Yay! [chuckles] I mean, boo!
It's up to us to find them, and fast.
Eyes, are you in?
I'm in!
-Totally in!
-Ten-four!
But just think.
Without Lonny,
you could leave your tiny dodo exhibit
and take flying lessons with the eagles
whenever you wanted.
Only you do that.
Okay, fine. I'll help.
But I won't try that hard.
Peaches, can you go to the security room
and check the monitors?
Maybe we can figure out
where the keys are.
Mission accepted!
[chittering]
-[Ma] Yee-haw!
-[Pa] Whoo-wee!
What a haul!
-We're rich!
-[Pa laughs]
Ridley, I've got eyes on Lonny's keys!
Round up the posse
for an old-fashioned wagon chase!
Ma! Pa!
-[Ismat] Stop!
-[Dante] Wait up!
Looks like
we got some bandits on our tail.
-[exclaims] Head for that there cave!
-[Dante] Got 'em!
[Dante grunts] Wipeout!
-[beep]
-Peaches, we've hit a dead end.
The vent exits around the corner!
[Fred] Cut 'em off at the pass!
[Pa] Yee-haw!
-Hold your horses!
-Whoa!
Ma? Pa?
I'm afraid those keys belong to Lonny.
-Land's sake!
-We had no idea!
[Ma] Lonny's good people.
She keeps kids from trying
to take us home in their pockets.
Really? That's awful nice of her.
A lot nicer than always being carried back
to the dodo exhibit.
[Pa] Here ya go.
What's left of 'em, that is.
Left of them?
According to this list Ma and Pa gave us,
they traded keys with two exhibits.
-I think.
-Who's first on that little list?
Whoa! Watch the hair horns.
The Lemurson kids.
Hey, kids, we need that key!
[laughter]
-Up here!
-Nope!
Finders lemurs!
You heard the kid. Finders lemurs.
Well, we tried. Let's pack it in, folks.
We just need to play with them.
Lemursons! Go long. Really long!
[grunts]
-Going super long!
-Epic moves!
Yes! One key down, one more to go.
Oh, Pierce, you old softie!
Thank you for the beautiful necklace.
Well, I do know how much
you love shiny things.
Happy exhibit-versary.
-Um, excuse me--
-Ridley!
Did you see
what this bag of feathers got me?
Oh, best roommate ever!
That's why I'm here.
The key belongs to Lonny.
We need to give it back to her,
or she'll get sent out to pasture.
Though it is a good look.
Very fashion-forward, Flo.
Hon, don't I know it!
But I'm happy to part with the key
if it means helping Lonny keep her job.
I wholeheartedly agree.
She always wipes chocolatey
kid fingerprints off our exhibit.
Huh. I didn't know she did that.
Maybe Lonny isn't so bad after all.
Phew! And now we have all the keys.
Keys? Here, key-key-keys!
-Everyone hide!
-[all gasp]
[grunts]
Lonny! Great news!
We-- Uh, I found your keys!
What? I can't believe it!
Yay! Back door, side door, trap door…
Did I say "yay"? Aw, I meant "boo."
What is it?
The key to the front door isn't here.
It must still be missing.
And it's the most important key by far.
Oh, how did you end up in here again?
Ugh, if I don't find that last key
before Mr. Peabody gets back,
I'll be like the east wing of the museum.
History.
Don't worry. I'll keep looking.
Thanks, Ridley, but let's face it,
this might be my last night here.
[emotional music playing]
♪ Goodbye to the house in the treetops ♪
♪ Farewell to that really big squid ♪
♪ Oh, I'll never forget you ♪
♪ Or how I would pet you ♪
♪ Just don't tell my boss that I did ♪
♪ Goodbye to the fabulous gift shop ♪
♪ Adieu to the creep-tastic bugs ♪
♪ I'll soon be alone
Where there's no ancient stoneware ♪
♪ So long to you dusty old jugs ♪
♪ How sad when a legacy ends! ♪
♪ Farewell, my inanimate
Very best friends! ♪
♪ Oh, goodbye to the last little dodo ♪
♪ My pal I so often dream of ♪
♪ I'll say adios to my friends
I'm so close to ♪
♪ The eagles who soar up above ♪
♪ Goodbye to this place that I love ♪
[music ends]
[sobs] Lonny does love the museum.
So, so much.
I can't let her go.
We gotta find Lonny's last key!
Glad you're finally on board.
[Peaches] Ridley,
I've good news and bad news.
The good, I found the last key.
[Ridley] Great job!
Wait, what's the bad news?
I went back into security cam footage.
Turns out, Lonny accidentally
dropped a key into Dante's volcano!
-[gasps] Oh no!
-[Fred] Whoa!
As someone who's dropped lots of things
in there, mainly socks,
getting stuff out can be gnarly.
Especially now that it's back to
"snortin' fire," as us bisons like to say.
[Peaches] Hot bananas with peanut butter!
Mr. Peabody
just pulled into the parking lot!
We are royally in trouble.
Everyone, back to your exhibits.
I'll grab some gear
and get the key out of the volcano.
[panting]
Hopefully, in time.
[sniffles] Goodbye, museum.
[gasps] Dudley!
Time for this dodo to swan dive!
[Dudley screams]
There are a lot of stinky socks down here.
Don't you worry, little lady.
We've got an iron grip on your birdy here.
[gasps] Oh no. It's about to erupt!
Dudley, get outta there!
[Dudley] Ma, Pa! Do your thing!
-[Ma] Yee-haw!
-[Pa] Giddyup, horsies!
Woo-hoo! Oh no!
[grunts, sighs]
Dudley, are you okay?
I am now!
Ta-da!
The final key.
-[Mr. Peabody] Lonny? Let me in!
-[gasps]
Mr. Peabody's here.
And so is the next eruption!
Grab my hand!
-[both grunt]
-[Dudley screaming]
All right, Lonny.
Show me your keys.
Or I'll show you the door.
Actually, Mr. P…
[gasps]
Here you go!
All of 'em! Right here.
Yay! Ha ha!
I… I can't believe it.
Frankly, neither can I, sir.
So, Lonny can keep her job. Right?
For now, until the next time
she loses her keys.
Ooh-hoo! Whooptie-whooptie-doo!
-All right!
-Bisonic!
Nice work helping Lonny.
Passport, please, sweetie.
Mm-hmm.
For lending a hand
to a fellow museum lover…
[mystical twinkling]
…you've earned a stamp.
I couldn't have found
all Lonny's keys without you, Dudley.
This stamp's for both of us.
But I gotta ask.
What made you decide to help Lonny?
As the last of my kind,
I might've mentioned it before,
I know how lonely it can be
until you find a place where you belong.
And Lonny belongs with us here
in the museum.
-[door opens]
-[all gasp]
[all panting]
[whimpers]
I will never know
how this dodo gets around.
[chuckles] He is really one of a kind.
You both are.
I think I found a new best friend.
[sighs]
We might both be one of a kind,
but we're definitely birds of a feather.
[giggles]
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]