[opening theme music playing]
[female singer]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray ♪
♪ And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[music ends]
-[whimsical music playing]
-[girl] Ready or not, here I come.
Bye-bye. Thank you for coming.
Mama, I noticed the Phoenix Ruby.
It's gone!
[both] Shh!
[clears throat]
Anything wrong?
What? Like, something-missing-wrong?
No! Mr. Peabody,
everything is perfectly perfect.
[Mr. Peabody] Hmm.
Ever since he bought the museum,
he's been looking
for a reason to fire you.
But, if you weren't running the museum,
we'd have to--
Move. I know. Don't worry, Ridley.
I'll find the necklace.
I can help. It'll be an adventure!
Oh, sweetheart, Dante hates it
when you hang on his tail.
Who is Dante?
Ha! Did I say Dante?
That's weird. [chuckles]
And I can't think why I said that.
-[door opens]
-Hello? Who's there?
Just me. Lonny.
Security Guard of the Month,
42 months running!
Um, Lonny, you're the museum's
only security guard.
True. I got a couple stragglers for you,
Ms. Jones.
Sorry, we love it here.
It's always hard to get them to leave.
You're that kid who lives here, right?
In the museum?
Yep. I know it seems cool,
but it can also be kinda boring.
You're not allowed to do anything…
[girl 2] I'm a dinosaur! Chomp! Chomp!
All I know is, it'd be way more fun
if the dinosaurs really could talk.
You live in a treehouse
inside a Children's Museum,
and you don't have enough fun?
[laughs] Okay, okay.
[grunts]
She's a natural.
The answer is no.
She's not old enough. She's not ready.
She's as ready as she needs to be.
A journey doesn't start at the end.
[emotional music playing]
[soft rattling]
-Mama, I heard something.
-[murmurs]
[Mama] Hmm-Mm.
Whoa.
[mystical twinkling]
I'm ready. I know I am.
[uplifting music playing]
♪ There's a sense that I get
As I walk through these halls ♪
♪ A feeling the relics
That hang on the walls ♪
♪ Whisper, "Destiny calls" ♪
♪ Like these silent exhibits
Are somehow a part ♪
♪ Of some new adventure
That's waiting to start! ♪
♪ I know in my heart I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready to find what is waiting in store ♪
♪ Yes, I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready to do something more ♪
♪ And although it sounds crazy
I can't shake the feeling somehow ♪
♪ Every last exhibition says
"Ridley, your moment is now" ♪
♪ My moment is now! ♪
♪ Now that I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready to find what is waiting for me ♪
♪ Yes, I'm ready ♪
♪ No matter what it might be ♪
♪ Ready for Mom to finally see ♪
♪ See that I'm ready ♪
♪ Ready for my destiny ♪
♪ I'm ready! ♪
[rattling]
-[intriguing music playing]
-[fan motor whirring]
[whirring stops]
-[mystical twinkling]
-Huh?
[gasps]
Whoa.
[voice] Who turned off the fan?
[uneasy] I did.
[voice] How can I fake-fly without it?
That fan is the wind beneath my wings.
Sorry, I was looking
for a missing necklace and--
Wait, "fake-fly"? Who are you?
[voice] I think the far more important
question is, who are you?
[both screaming]
-Why are we yelling?
-I don't know!
No, no, no, wait. Yes, I do.
Because you're a museum dodo bird
who's supposed to be extinct!
Well, you don't have
to get personal about it!
[sadly] You have no idea how lonely it is
to have an exhibit all to yourself.
And forget being extinct. You're talking!
You're not supposed to be talking!
-[voice 2] Dudley!
-Ah!
[voice 2] You up?
[Ridley] No way! Dinos can talk!
Of course we can talk.
-Whoa! Watch the tail! Sorry.
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
My tail is always trying
to sneak up on me.
Sweet to finally meet you. I'm Dante.
And that's Ralph. Say hi, Ralph.
I'm Ridley. [chuckles] And I'm talking
to a dinosaur. And his tail.
-Ha! You know it.
-[lemurs chittering]
Whoa! Watch out! Lemurs comin' through.
Thanks, mate. I'm takin' the little ones
for a field trip to the Space Wing.
-Come on, keep it moving.
-[gasping]
Ismat, looks who's here!
OMEgypt! Ridley?
Warning. I might be mummy royalty,
but I'm still a hugger!
[straining] Yes, you are!
Mummy hugs. Cool.
[sighs] Wait, I've seen you
in the mummy exhibit.
But you've changed.
New outfit!
The clothes I have to wear during the day
are so last dynasty.
[muffled] Heya, I'm Peaches.
First monkey
to slip on a banana peel in space.
-Huh?
-[Dante] Psst.
Houston, we have a problem
hearing you.
Sorry. Always forgettin'
I have this thing on.
Heya, I'm Peaches.
First monkey
to slip on a banana peel in space!
Wow!
So you finally got called up
to lead the herd.
She did say she was ready.
You heard me?
Of course.
You're a lot like your mummy, you know.
You know my mummy-- I mean, my mom?
Of course we know your mom.
She's kinda in charge of this place.
I know. But I didn't know--
-About us?
-Yeah.
You must feel like you landed
on a strange, new planet.
It's kinda mind-blowing!
[imitates explosion]
Dudley! Your fan ruined my fur!
Sorry, Fred.
It just makes me feel like
a glorious winged eagle
-soaring through the clouds.
-[wind gusts]
Dodo birds can't fly.
[yelps] Not with that attitude they can't.
Is Fred a she? Or a he?
I don't know. They're just a Fred.
Cool.
Come on. We'll give you a tour.
[yelps] Wait up!
I can't actually fly. Uh, yet!
Hang ten, Mrs. Sanchez!
I've been hanging for more like
a solid twelve
hours, that is.
I have such a cramp in my tail!
The butterflies love to surf the tail.
This place is incredible!
Well, your mama and grandmama
have always taken
galactically great care of us.
My mom's in trouble.
The Phoenix Ruby is gone.
If she doesn't find it before the morning,
she could lose her job.
I wanna help,
but she doesn't think I'm ready.
Sometimes you have to tell people
who you really are on the inside.
I just wish I could do more to--
Wait, what's that?
[Ridley gasps]
The necklace! I can help my mom.
Careful! Caribou get real jumpy
when you go into their exhibit.
You know what would be really bad?
A stampede!
[screams] Stampede!
It's like they read my mind!
See? If I can think it, I can be it!
I am an eagle. I am an eagle!
-[Ridley] Whoa!
-[gasps]
Dude, that was cretaceously close.
[caribou] Stampede!
Wait. There's no back wall?
Not at night.
-[adventurous music playing]
-Are they going away or getting closer?
-Oh! Oh! Closer!
-[Peaches] Brace for impact.
[caribou] Stampede!
[panting]
-Are you sure you're ready?
-[all] Huh?
Oh, helmet. Forgot.
Ridley, are you sure you're ready?
Stampedes are serious business.
We wouldn't want you to go
the way of the dodo bird
because we went extinct! You know?
Uh, I feel your pain, dude.
[caribou] Stampede!
-I'm ready.
-I was hopin' you'd say that.
You're cleared for takeoff.
Show 'em what you're made of,
but do it in style!
Now you're runway-ready!
[caribou] Stampede!
[Ridley] Whoa!
[grunts]
[gasps, grunts]
Ah!
[caribou] Stampede!
[grunts]
[yelps]
Whoa! Whoa!
-Oh, I can't watch!
-I can't stop watching.
[grunts]
That's one giant leap for girlkind!
[twinkling]
[grunts]
Hi! I'm Ridley. Nice to meet you.
Would love to chat, but gotta mosey.
[grunts]
Stampede. Stampede.
-Hi!
-[screams]
I mean, hi. I mean, what are you doing?
Trying to get that necklace back.
-[gasps] What necklace?
-The one on your horns.
[gasps] There's a necklace on my horns?
Get it off! Get it off!
If you could just stop stampeding,
I could grab it.
The thing about a stampede is
you can't stop.
Stampede!
Ridley's in a hoof load of trouble.
-We gotta help her.
-Do we?
A good queen always protects her friends.
Who's with us?
[groans]
We gotta orbit those caribou
back into their exhibit.
That way, they won't destroy anything
else.
Stampede!
Stampede! Stampede!
Whoa!
[piano notes playing]
[caribou panting]
[Ridley gasps]
[Ridley] Whoa!
[caribou] Stampede! Stampede! Stampede!
[adventurous music playing]
I know this is shocking,
but it's time to power down!
[hooves rumbling]
The pottery exhibit
is closed to stampedes today!
Uh, please fasten your seat belts,
put your tray tables upright,
and thank you for flying
with Dodo Airlines!
[tires screech]
The eagle has landed!
Ridley! We gotta get 'em back
into the exhibit.
I don't have the necklace yet.
Now or never!
Well, in that case, now!
Bisonic choice!
[grunts]
[sighs]
Did you complete your mission?
Yep.
-Juras-sick.
-That was royal.
I have to get it to my mom.
Mom! Mom!
[shushes]
[chattering]
I'm afraid the necklace is
magnificent!
I guess everything is in order this time.
But I'll be back.
I'm watching you, Joneses!
Thank you for coming, Mr. Peabody.
I'll walk you out.
I told you I was ready.
[chuckles] But how did you get this?
[gasps]
-You met--
-Mm-hmm.
So, I have a lot of explaining to do.
And so do you.
[chuckles] About that…
I know this doesn't look great,
but, um, I am ready to run this place.
I don't think so.
But maybe you're ready
for me to start teaching you.
-Yes!
-Oh, Juras-sick!
You made your mummy proud!
As someone wise once told me,
you don't start a journey at the end.
There's so much to explain.
But I think we should
jump right into lesson number one.
Yes? What is it?
-Cleaning up.
-[laughs]
Cool. I can do that.
And your new ground crew can help.
-[Ismat] Mummazing!
-[Dante] Mesozoic!
[Ridley] Some like it hot.
[Lonny over PA] Attention, guests.
The museum is now closing.
-Unless you're planning on moving in…
-I don't wanna go.
Thanks for coming! Exit's this way.
See you soon!
Bye!
Phew! That's the last of the guests.
Coast is clear.
Everyone can come out now, right?
[laughs] Someone's antsy tonight.
-[mystical twinkling]
-I can't help it.
Now that I know the truth
about the museum,
all I can think about
is going on adventures!
[gasps] Adventures?
So you're sure you're ready
to start your training?
-Yep.
-You're sure you're sure?
The surest! I was born ready!
Well, that's true.
-[both] Okay.
-Yes!
The women of our family
have always taken care of the museum.
Our job is and always has been
to take care of the artifacts
who make their home here
and preserve them.
Mm-hmm. Yep. Got it.
And learn from these cultures and history,
recent and ancient.
Uh-huh. I know!
It's also our job to return artifacts
whenever we can find their home
or their people…
Oh my gosh. Are we still talking?
Mama, Grandma,
the Jones family history is super cool,
but when I found out that the museum,
you know, comes to life at night,
I thought I'd be going on adventures!
Traipsing through jungles,
rushing through temples, eating bugs…
Okay, maybe not that last one.
[sighs] Ridley, most of the job
isn't about adventures.
It's about keeping the peace.
This is part of training. [sighs]
But you can go into the museum
and meet everyone.
Now that's more like it!
Bye, Mama! Bye, Grandma!
Hey there! Oh, how's it going?
Mrs. Sanchez, did you do something new
with your tail?
You noticed! Thank you, dear!
-Bison's greetings to ya!
-Ridley!
[grunts] Be careful of your queen!
Ismat, you're not our queen.
What's on your flight plan this evenin'?
I started my museum training.
But it was a little less exciting
than I thought it'd be.
-I was hoping for some adventures.
-[grunts, gasps]
You know, I don't remember
your mama startin' adventures
until she was pretty far
into her training.
Even a big, wild animal like me
started small.
Moo! [coughs]
I know I have what it takes
to protect the museum.
-Excuse me.
-Huh?
Can I get some help?
Oh! Why, yes, you can.
Goin' on an adventure.
You lucky duck.
-I mean, you lucky penguin.
-[mystical twinkling]
See? Totally ready to help.
Pedro! Pedro, where are you?
Have you seen Pedro? Have you?
Please, he can't be out of the cold
for very long. Pedro?
-[whimpers]
-Dudley? Everything okay?
No, it's a disaster! Pedro is missing.
He's just a little flightless bird
thrust out into the world all on his own.
Something I know all about,
and it is not good!
Who's Pedro?
Is he one of my loyal subjects?
I don't know.
But if he's part of this museum,
he's my responsibility.
I'm gonna need a description.
He's little. Yay high.
Black and white. And he waddles like this.
Doopdadoopeedoo.
Uh, you're describing a penguin.
He's a penguin.
A penguin?
[gasps] I know where he is.
Whoa! Ridley, where you rollin' off to?
To the Serengeti!
I have to go rescue Pedro.
Though I probably need to pack
some supplies first.
"Supplies," eh?
We know where you can get supplies
fit for a queen.
[gasps]
Whoa!
It's an adventurer's dream!
How did you know about this?
Are you kidding?
These are the bodacious secret supplies
of your mom and grandma!
-[rattling]
-[chuckles]
Well, you know,
luckily, it's pretty sturdy stuff.
Mom and Grandma, huh?
[uplifting music playing]
-[Dante] Whoa!
-[Fred] Nice!
[Ismat] I like it!
I think I'm ready to go.
But you're not goin' alone, dudette.
We're coming with ya.
-You are?
-[Fred] Duh!
You're gonna need
a big ol' bison bodyguard.
Me. I mean me.
Oh! Right!
And you'll need a royal escort
to tell you what to do in a nice way.
Uh-uh. No way.
The Serengeti is hot and dangerous,
and dodos sunburn easily,
and I don't have my flip-flops
for the sand.
You can always stay here.
Alone.
Alone? Never mind. I guess I'm coming.
Not like I'm the last of my kind
or anything.
Thanks, everybody.
-[button clicks]
-[gasps] Wait.
[adventurous music playing]
If we're gonna adventure together,
that would make us a team.
A team! Cretaceously cool!
I am so proud to be a part of the… the…
What are we called again?
We don't have a name yet.
We can be…
[gasps] "The Eyes of the Museum"!
Because it's our job to watch over
every artifact, every diorama.
And every friend.
-Copy that!
-Cool!
"Eyes" on three! One, two…
[all] Eyes!
[uplifting music playing]
♪ Take a look at these hallowed halls ♪
♪ See this marvelous collection ♪
♪ Can't you hear
All these priceless treasures ♪
♪ Cry out for protection? ♪
♪ All the way from the ends of the Earth ♪
♪ History and stunning beauty ♪
♪ We cannot forget our sacred duty ♪
♪ We must look out
For each ancient artifact ♪
♪ So we will not rest
Until the case is cracked ♪
♪ We are the Eyes of the Museum ♪
♪ We're the Eyes of the Museum ♪
♪ Time to act ♪
♪ Little Pedro is on his own ♪
♪ All alone in the Serengeti ♪
♪ Never fear
The Eyes are always ready ♪
♪ Oh, no matter what the odds
We must prevail ♪
♪ Pedro's missing?
Well, we're quickly on the trail ♪
[all] ♪ We are the Eyes of the Museum ♪
♪ We're the Eyes of the Museum ♪
♪ We're the Eyes of the Museum
We won't fail ♪
[song ends]
-[elephant trumpeting]
-[Ridley] Whoa.
When the Serengeti comes to life,
it really comes to life.
[Peaches] Don't worry. I got your back.
Do you hear that?
Or is it my inner fear talking to me?
This thing working?
Oops! Forgot to put this on. Hi, Peaches.
Mission control here.
While y'all are in the field,
I can keep an eye on things back here
in the museum.
All kinds of things and--
What in the name of Saturn?
Some of it you just can't unsee.
Anyway, I'm your eyes in the sky.
Call when you need me.
-Over!
-Over and out!
Now, where were we?
Talking about how scary the Serengeti is.
And how there's no shame in turning tail
and heading home.
Come on, everyone!
[chuckles] After you, Dudleys first.
No? After me?
Dudley, we have to go in.
Even if we're scared,
it's our job to keep everyone
from the museum safe.
Besides, I put Pedro
in this dangerous place. Literally.
I have to get him back.
Sleigh tracks! Pedro must be this way.
Come on. We're hot on his trail.
-Um, Ridley?
-[Ismat] Elephant!
Get behind me! My patented
"Stampede Staredown" will scare it off!
Scare it? Are you nuts?
You're way too adorable!
I am not adorable.
I'm the biggest and toughest of beasts!
Everyone dive!
[screaming, grunting]
That was too close!
This place is a lot more dangerous
than I expected.
I really hope Pedro's okay.
[birds squawking]
Ugh! I feel like I'm being mummified.
Huh? What's that, everybody?
You say you wanna turn back?
[deep voice] "Yeah, Dudley!
Let's go and get some delicious birdseed!"
[chuckles]
Come on. We have to keep going.
If we're hot, just think of how badly
a penguin like little Pedro is feeling.
[gasps] Oh no! The tracks end here.
[Pedro] Hello?
Pedro?
[Pedro] Help!
[Ridley gasps] Pedro!
[rocks rumbling]
I'm scared.
[Ridley] I know, but don't worry,
we're gonna get you home!
Okay.
-[rocks rumbling]
-[gasps] Uh-oh.
-[tense music playing]
-[grunts]
Yikes! That is not good.
Sorry. It's rumbly and tumbly,
and I got stuck.
You sure did.
Looks like you're the only thing
keeping the rocks from coming down.
[sighs] I shouldn't have come.
I just wanted to go
on an adventure like you.
You have nothing to be sorry for.
But I do. This was my fault.
But I'm gonna get you out of here, okay?
Okay.
Hmm. We gotta find
something that's your same weight.
Then we can switch you out
without causing the rocks to move.
-[beep]
-Peaches,
can you look up the average weight
of a baby penguin?
You got it, Ridley.
Hmm. It's 200 pounds.
Uh, wait, that's a baby elephant.
-Hold, please!
-[beep]
[easy-listening music playing]
Here we go.
Great. Thanks.
[gasps] I know what to do.
Can you guys start
passing me up some sand?
Hope I get this right.
We'll only have one shot at it.
[pensive music playing]
[groaning]
No rockslide. Phew!
-Yes!
-Go, Ridley!
Nice!
Oops. Total tail-fail.
-[Dudley gasps] Rockslide!
-[Ridley] Everyone, run! Go!
-[yelps, grunts]
-[Ridley] Dudley!
I told you, dodos don't do deserts!
Don't worry, buddy. I've got you.
[grunts]
[Dudley] I was so close
to becoming permanently extinct!
[grunts]
Pedro, are you okay?
That was awesome!
But can we go home now?
[chuckles] Definitely.
[sighs] I can't believe we got out okay!
Ridley, your quick thinking
was a crowning achievement.
Not to mention how I helped
Ridley and Pedro swing away at the end.
We'll let him have that one.
I'm just glad we're all out of danger!
Pedro! Oh, my little pingüino!
I was so worried.
Thank you for finding my son.
Of course.
And, Pedro, I don't think either of us
is ready for dangerous adventures yet.
We might need to learn
some stuff before we are.
Mama, Grandma, before you get mad…
We're just glad you're safe.
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you.
We almost got run over by an elephant,
smushed by rocks, and dried up by the sun!
Which is probably why
you wanted me to learn about the museum.
How about we get back to that training?
[Mama] So, you have to keep the elephants
away from the ancient pottery.
And the models of ancient ships
out of the bathrooms.
They're desperate for water,
and they do clog the toilets
no matter what they tell you.
[Ridley laughs]
And the penguins out of the desert.
Got it.
[chuckles] You done for today?
Nope. Let's dive into gemstones.
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]