[opening theme music playing]
[female singer]
♪ In a place full of mystery ♪
♪ Where the past comes alive ♪
♪ There's a hero of history ♪
♪ Who is ready to thrive! ♪
♪ She is saving our future ♪
♪ By protecting our past ♪
♪ She's a hero
Whose moment's arriving at last! ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Daring and bold and courageous ♪
♪ Guards the museum with pride ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Her sense of adventure's contagious ♪
♪ With dinos and dodos
And astronaut chimps by her side ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
♪ Wearing her trademark fedora ♪
♪ No challenge can get in her way ♪
♪ She won't ever give in to her fear ♪
♪ She shines when adventure is near ♪
♪ Swinging into the fray
And then saving the day ♪
♪ Ridley Jones! ♪
[music ends]
[Ridley] Ridley's babysitter club.
Woo-hoo! [laughs]
[grunts]
Ridley!
-[Ismat] Hi!
-Hey!
How was everyone's day?
Was it good? Great? Spectacular?
Can't wait, gotta show you.
Look what my mom gave me!
Whoa! She's letting you borrow
the Compass Eye? Awesome!
You know what they say,
magical compasses
are a girl's best friend.
They do say that, right?
Your mom is supposed to have
her compass at all times!
Not tonight.
Mama's going to her archaeology school's
20-year reunion,
so she's putting me in charge of it
while she's gone!
Whoa! That's a monster wave
of responsibility, dude.
I know!
Watching over the museum
without your mom's help.
And while your grandma's out of town.
[chuckles]
You sure you can do this?
Of course!
[mystical twinkling]
See? Didn't need any help to do that.
Hey, Mama!
Lookin' snazzy for your school reunion!
Thanks, sweetie. But I like to think
I always look snazzy.
Ha! Uh, has anyone seen Peaches?
She's joining me tonight
as the guest of honor.
Guest of honor? Lucky!
Yep! My archeology friends
begged me to bring her.
They think she's one of the most lifelike
displays they've ever seen.
[vehicle approaching]
Reportin' for guest of honor duty!
Great. We gotta dash. Unless…
Ridley, you sure you're okay
watching over the museum tonight?
I've got everything
totally under control here, Mama.
Okay, but call if you need me.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
You should go! You don't wanna be late!
Oh, and Peaches, remember,
you can't talk or move once we get there.
Roger that! I'll be as silent as Saturn.
Uh, bye, Mama! Bye, Peaches! Have fun!
Okay, Ridley, you're in charge now.
-Come on. Keep it moving.
-Oh, look, it's the Lemursons.
Heya! Cool flowers!
-Thank you!
-They're for our mommy.
They're her favorite color!
Aw! That's so sweet! What's the occasion?
-It's me and my wife's anniversary!
-An anniversary?
Tell me every romantic moment
you have planned!
Don't leave out a thing!
-[chuckles]
-What?
Big, tough bison
can be hopeless romantics!
It doesn't make me adorable!
No one has to make you adorable, Fred.
You just are.
We don't have any plans, actually.
Nothing planned for your anniversary?
This is not okay!
We can't really go anywhere.
-We gotta stay home with these rascals.
-[giggles]
What if we watch your kids?
-Say what now?
-Yeah!
We'll babysit tonight
so you and your wife can celebrate!
That's a hoof-tastic idea!
Crikey! Are you sure, Ridley?
You bet! We're here to help!
Oh, thanks, mates!
Well, now I just gotta figure out
where to take the missus. Hmm.
Ooh! The gift shop, maybe?
I could buy her a new bobblyhead.
Oh, let your pal Fred handle this.
I'll set up a date so big, so romantic,
that it'll make your wife fall
head-over-hooves for you all over again.
[Ismat] The cutest.
-It is pretty cute.
-Cute, cute!
I'm not being cute!
Would a cute bison
plan a once-in-a-lifetime date
for the lemurs' anniversary?
Don't answer that!
Ooh! I'm gonna tell my wife
the crackin' good news!
Great!
We'll stay here and watch…
[baby talk] …your little angels.
I don't like the idea of doing this
while your mom's gone.
Do you even know the first thing
about lemur-sitting?
It's my job to help anyone in the museum
who needs it.
Plus, we've trekked through the Serengeti
and survived piranha-infested waters.
Babysitting's gonna be a breeze.
Whoa! You two clean up real nice.
Thank you.
Harold picked all the bugs out of my fur.
Then you're ready for the très romantique
evening I've got planned for ya!
[romantic music playing]
This knight in shining armor
will guide you
to your night of shining amour.
That means love.
Tonight, you'll dine in the Paris exhibit,
where love is always on the menu.
Paris? [gasps] I've always wanted to go!
Ooh-hoo. I hear they make
the tastiest gourmet tree bark!
[kissing]
Be good for your babysitters.
And no sap before bedtime.
You won't be able to sleep.
-We will!
-Yes, Mommy!
[baby talk] Aren't they just the cutest,
sweetest things you've ever seen?
[giggles]
[screaming]
They're not the cutest, sweetest things
I've ever seen!
Tickle monster's gonna get you!
[Dudley] I don't wanna be tickled!
Hey, hands off the horns!
Do you know how much time and fur spray
it takes to style these?
[Ismat] I'm creating a new law
that orders you
to keep your messy fingers
away from my new wraps!
Think happy thoughts.
Think happy thoughts-- Oof! Whoa!
-[giggling]
-[screaming, grunts]
-Ha!
-[grunts]
-[adventure music playing]
-[giggles] Here comes tickle monster!
-[Ismat] Whoa!
-[gasps]
My horns!
[sighs, gasps]
-[lemur babies] Woo-hoo!
-[elephant trumpets]
[Fred] Those lemurs are out of control!
Look what they did to my fur!
That hairdo is so not you.
There! Much better.
So what do we do, Ridley?
Uh…
You know who'd know exactly what to do?
[pants] Your mom. We should call her.
No. I told her
I could handle everything here.
We can do this.
But how?
Those little lemurs are royal pains!
I know. Who knew they'd be so difficult?
They're just teeny-tiny babies, after all!
Wait a minute. That's it!
They're babies.
And what do babies need a lot of?
Reassurance?
Fashion advice!
No, they need a lot of sleep.
So we just have to figure out
how to get them to sleep.
"Addie the Adventurer leaps off the cliff,
escaping the dangerous rockslide."
"She parachutes down
and lands into a pit of snakes!"
-Snakes!
-Scawwy!
[screams]
Hmm, maybe that was too adventurous
for a bedtime story?
If you want something done right,
let a queen do it.
[chewing]
Oh no, Ismat.
What did you give them?
In my family, we have a saying
when someone is being fussy.
"Let them eat cake!"
Uh-oh. This is not good.
See? It totally works!
Oh. Well, if I had a dodo family,
we'd also have a saying.
"When baby lemurs eat a lot of sugar,
run for your lives!"
[lemurs exclaiming]
Watch and learn, princess.
A good stampede wears out
even the biggest, strongest bisons
like me. [pants]
These little lemurs
will be snoozin' in no time.
[lemurs exclaiming]
I've never… [panting] …stampeded
this long in my life.
[all sigh]
Stampede! Stampede! Stampede!
[Dudley] Can we admit defeat now?
I could go to the hall of flags
and get a white one to wave.
No, I can do this.
Ridley, I think
it's time to call your mom.
But I wanted to show her I could handle
a whole night in the museum by myself.
Without her help.
Asking for help isn't a sign of weakness.
It's the sign of a good leader.
Yeah! Even dinosaurs need help sometimes.
You always help everyone, Ridley.
Which is why you're going to be
a great protector of the museum.
But you're allowed to ask for help too.
You're right. I do need help.
Time to call Mama.
-Ridley!
-[both gasp]
[Peaches] Houston,
we have a gigantic mess!
I'm sorry, Mama.
I thought I could handle babysitting
the lemurs while you were gone.
[sighs] Don't worry, sweetheart.
We can fix this.
First things first,
we need to track the lemurs down.
And I know you can handle that.
Yeah! Okay. Gather up, team.
We have some little lemurs to find.
[lemur giggles]
You got this, Dudster?
Oh yeah, I do.
Here comes the tickle monster!
[Ismat] Time to wrap it up, little lemur.
Woo-hoo! Now that's how you babysit!
All right, Mama, we got 'em all!
Now how do we put them to sleep?
Remember how I used to put you to sleep
when you were little?
Uh-huh.
You used to sing me the Museum Lullaby.
Wait, that's it?
We need to sing the lemurs to sleep?
But I'm not sure
I remember the words to the song.
But we do.
Wait, you guys know the lullaby?
Ha ha. I wasn't the only one
who'd sing you to sleep.
We all used to sing
to cutity-cute baby Ridley.
Just follow our lead.
♪ Close your eyes, my precious dear ♪
♪ Listen close and you will hear ♪
♪ This place has its own melody ♪
♪ Mysterious and deep ♪
♪ Every statue sings a song ♪
♪ While the pharaohs hum along ♪
[both] ♪ Listen close and everything ♪
♪ Will sing you off to sleep ♪
[all]
♪ All day long you've run and twirled ♪
♪ With the wonders of the world ♪
♪ Time for counting giant whales ♪
♪ And dino tails and sheep ♪
♪ Go to sleep ♪
♪ Hmm-hmm-hmm ♪
We did it!
[whispers] I mean, we did it!
Thanks, everyone.
You're always there to help me.
Even when I don't admit I need it.
Sorry I made such a mess of everything,
Mama.
You did a much better job than I did
my first time babysitting.
But if you were having trouble,
why didn't you call sooner?
I didn't wanna make you miss your reunion.
You were so excited.
Nothing in the world is more important
than helping
my favorite little adventurer.
Thanks. But to be honest,
I also wanted to prove
that I could take care of the museum
all by myself.
I don't think I'm ready yet.
I need a lot more help before I get there.
Can I see your passport?
[mystical twinkling]
[Ridley] A stamp? What's that for?
For asking for help.
It's one of the most important lessons
a protector of the museum can learn.
Thanks, Mama.
[romantic music playing]
[sighing] Oh!
What a wonderful evening.
The lights, the glamour…
And how about that food?
I've never had
a French bark-guette before! Yum!
Oh! They look so peaceful
when they're asleep.
We can't thank Ridley enough
for helping us have
such a cracking anniversary.
[chuckles] You'll have to thank
your babysitters tomorrow.
Tonight, I think they need their rest.
[all snoring]
[both] Aw!
-[whimsical music playing]
-[Ridley] Riddle me this.
You guys ready?
-Born ready!
-I think so!
Me too!
Okay, then.
Operation "Sanchez Smile" is a go!
Cue flossers!
[yelping, grunts]
Now cue brushers!
[chuckles] Okay, I never thought
I'd have to help a whale floss and brush.
That's museum protector training for ya.
You look like a million barnacles,
Mrs. Sanchez!
Thank you for the krill-free smile, dears!
So what's the next stamp
you're aimin' for, sunshine?
-[whirring]
-[gasps]
Hold that thought.
I'd know the sound
of grandma's forklift anywhere.
And grandma's forklift means…
[all] New exhibit!
Hey there, team.
Here to take a peek
at our newest addition?
Ooh! What is it? What is it?
[dramatic music playing]
-[Ismat] OMEgypt!
-[Peaches] Wow!
But seriously, what is it?
It's a Sphinx!
An ancient, powerful statue
that holds a very valuable secret.
And an even more valuable treasure.
-You see--
-[Mr. Peabody] Dr. Jones!
-Whoa! It's Mr. P!
-Scatter, dudes!
[tense music playing]
Uh, Mr. Peabody,
what are you still doing here?
I had to come see our newest exhibit,
The Sphinx's Treasure.
People will be lining up around the block
to see its… its…
[clears throat]
Wait, uh, where's the treasure?
The Sphinx guards the treasure
inside her vault, Mr. Peabody.
That's kinda her whole sitch.
Then let's open this up
and see what we bought.
Well, the thing is,
no one's been able to open it. Ever.
But the mystery's half the fun!
The fun is having the treasure on display,
so people can pay to see it.
Either you get that vault open by morning,
or I am returning the Sphinx!
He wants to send the Sphinx away?
But she gives the Egyptian wing
such a glamorous touch.
I'll handle Mr. Peabody.
Think you can tackle getting the treasure?
You bet. The Eyes of the Museum are on it!
"Eyes" on three!
One, two…
[straining, grunting]
It was worth a try.
Maybe we can just ask her
to open the door?
I don't know.
Sphinxes are usually very tight-lipped.
This one might not even come to life.
Hello? Hello!
-Boo!
-[all scream]
Ah, that was so worth the wait!
You should've seen your faces!
You were all like, "Blahaha!"
[screams] Not again.
Oops! Sorry, cutie-bird-tootie.
Just havin' a little fun.
Good one, stone lady!
This "stone lady" goes by Thoebe
because that's my name!
Welcome to the museum, Thoebe.
Come on. We'll show you around.
So over there is Ida the Knight.
She's super brave and friendly.
That's the music exhibit,
and this is my tree house!
-I think you're gonna love it here.
-If I get to stay.
I heard that kinda rude guy talking.
He wants to have me sent away, again.
What do you mean, "again"?
I've been in museums all over the world.
But people get so mad
when they can't open my vault.
Ooh!
Must be some treasure in there.
What is it?
Oh, I can't say.
That's one of the… [loudly]
…Rules of the Sphinx!
-[whimpers]
-Oops! [chuckles]
Sorry, that happens sometimes.
Sphinx habit.
It's fun seeing the world.
But just once, I wanna stay in one place
so I have time to make friends.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ Life's not always easy
When you're born a sphinx ♪
♪ If you want the truth
In fact, it kinda stinks ♪
♪ Got a little secret
And I guard it well ♪
♪ But I really want to tell ♪
♪ Only way to see the treasure
That I guard ♪
♪ Is to solve a riddle
That's, like, super hard ♪
♪ Wish someone would solve it
But they never do ♪
♪ And I can't give them a clue ♪
♪ It's the Riddle of the Sphinx ♪
♪ Though it's sorta cool
To roam from town to town ♪
♪ All I wanna do
Is just to settle down ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll never really
Find a friend, you see ♪
♪ Till someone solves the mystery ♪
♪ Can't help you and it stinks ♪
♪ It's the Riddle of the Sphinx
Ooh! ♪
♪ Just a little Riddle of the Sphinx ♪
[music ends]
So you're saying the only way
to open your vault is…
If you solve my riddle.
And it's a really good one,
if I do say so.
Why don't you just tell us the answer?
Then it won't be a secret anymore.
Love it, love the energy, love the spirit.
But I can't just tell you!
You have to figure it out!
Just one of the rules!
Then that's exactly what we'll do.
A riddle is just like a puzzle,
and we can do that.
Really? You'll try?
We'll have your vault open by morning,
or my last name isn't Jones!
-Of course!
-Yeah!
Oh! You've truly touched
this stone heart of mine!
But I'm warning you, it's tough.
And so am I! Let's hear it!
[clears throat]
I stand by myself, but am never alone.
I have many feet, but I move as one.
I walk on the ground,
but have eyes in the sky.
I will never unravel, so don't even try.
I'm as strong as a rock,
but I have heart to spare.
I have many mouths,
but it's one voice they share.
What am I?
-Ooh! Ooh! I know!
-Then flap on up, my feathery friend!
"I stand by myself, but am never alone."
That's me! [chuckles]
I stand by myself in my exhibit,
but I always have my friends,
so I'm never alone.
The answer must be a dodo!
[imitates buzzer]
Thanks for playing, but wrongo!
-[rumbling]
-What did I do? What did I do?
[all whimpering]
Fred, urn! Dante, pottery!
[grunting]
[whimpers] What was that?
Sorry, that was me.
Every time you guess wrong,
you have to face a challenge.
I hate seeing you stress out like that,
but those are the…
[loudly] …Rules of the Sphinx!
This is gonna be harder than I thought.
I knew it! It's too hard!
I know! What if I told you
that the first letter of the answer is--
Ow! I know, I know. No hints.
-[both grunt]
-Watch out, princess!
Don't worry.
This riddle's tough,
but if we put our heads together,
I know we can figure it out.
I've got it!
"I have many feet, but I move as one."
Easy-peasy-Tricerasqueezy!
[chuckles] The answer to your riddle is
a skateboard!
-Sorry.
-[rumbling]
Wait, I meant a skateboard-ing dinosaur.
A skateboarding dog?
[whimpers] A skateboarding waffle?
Maybe just run?
[action music playing]
[grunting]
Dino down!
[chuckles] My bad, dudes. Who's next?
"I walk on the ground,
but have eyes in the sky."
I'll be licked
if that's not a space monkey like me!
Whoa!
Mayday! Mayday!
[screams] Whoa! Whoa!
"Strong as a rock"?
[gasps] Nothing's stronger than a bison!
Oh! Look at you!
You're the strongest cutie I've ever seen.
But also no. Watch your step.
[screams]
Okay, being big and tough doesn't help
when the ground's so crumbly.
Don't worry,
because I'm great at worrying!
Hoof it to the tiles I point to.
This tile looks sturdy. [whimpers]
Now left. Left. Right. Right!
Wait, no, stop!
I'm trying not to fall here, Dudley!
I meant "right" like "correct" on that.
-Now left and straight!
-[rumbling]
-[screams]
-Didn't mean straight into me! [grunts]
"I will never unravel"?
That's a perfectly-poised mummy royal
for sure!
[rumbling]
Ah! This queen may "never unravel,"
but her bandages are dry-clean only!
I'm on it!
[water burbling]
I don't mean to get y'all's goose,
but it's almost morning.
Oh, you're so close! In a sense.
In another truer sense,
you're still right where you started.
Can you give us any hint?
I mean, if Mr. Peabody comes back
and the vault isn't open,
you'll have to leave.
I don't wanna go!
I finally made friends. Good friends.
Oh! Who are they? Wonder if I know 'em.
It's you, Dudley.
-All of you.
-Oh.
Okay, I'm really not supposed to help.
You know, the rules.
But you guys are so great.
I'll just say, you're all wrong,
but you're all right.
Uh, is that even possible?
I don't know.
But I do know the only way Thoebe stays
is if we get this open,
so we are not giving up.
Thanks, Ridley, but I'll be okily-dokily.
It's been so nice knowing you all,
even just for a night.
Hey, you can't give up either!
You're our friend now,
and friends stick together.
That's right!
Like when Peaches saved her highness,
and all of us, from that flood.
Or how Dudley
helped me get across that pit.
When the Eyes of the Museum work together,
we can do anything.
Including solving this riddle.
"Eyes" on three.
One, two…
[all] Eyes!
Wait. "I have many mouths,
but it's one voice they share."
That's it! I know the answer!
"I stand by myself, but am never alone."
"I have many feet, but I move as one."
"I walk on the ground,
but have eyes in the sky."
"I will never unravel, so don't even try."
"I'm as strong as a rock,
and I have heart to spare."
"I have many mouths,
but it's one voice they share."
"What am I?"
We were all wrong, but we were all right.
Because the answer is "us"! A team!
[dramatic music playing]
[rumbling]
[laughs] You are a team!
Because only a team could solve my riddle!
-All right, dudes!
-We did it!
OMEgypt!
Thoebe, I can't believe
you weren't going to tell us
about this glorious treasure!
I couldn't say because I didn't know.
My vault's never been opened before!
[sobs] I'll tell you what's not a secret.
How happy I am!
Thank you for not givin' up on me!
Hey, what are friends for?
[Grandma] Don't worry, Mr. Peabody,
we'll get the treasure opened eventually.
Mr. P's coming! Hide!
[Dudley] See you later!
[coins clanking]
If the vault isn't open by now,
this Sphinx has a one-way ticket
back across the pond!
-Looks like no shipping necessary.
-Huh?
-[chuckles]
-You opened the treasure?
-I want to see it now.
-Oh, wait!
So much g… g… g… gold.
It's beautiful!
Well done, Joneseses.
I think I'll keep this exhibit
for a long time.
I agree.
So, let's talk marketing.
Did you hear that, Thoebe?
You're here to stay!
Yay!
-Bisonic!
-Stellar!
You all are the best!
The gold is great, but the real treasure's
having friends like you.
[Dante chuckles] Bring it in, team.
-Love you, dudes!
-[Fred] We love you, Thoebe.
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]