NARRATOR:
Previously on The Shield.
Yesterday, Measure 16
on the city ballot failed,
which means we'll have to make do
with the lack of manpower
here in the Barn and
on the street.
Hold this out long enough,
some people feel compelled
to take the gum.
It's a sign they'll crack
under pressure.
Gum?
No, thanks.
Here you go.
Sure, thanks.
KAVANAUGH:
You know the IAD has been looking
into Detective Mackey
and the Strike Team he ran
under your command.
We've got Lemansky.
He lifted a brick of tar
off the El Salvadorans.
We've been waiting for it to spin
into something.
So you still got nothing
on Mackey?
KAVANAUGH:
We got a CI next to him.
When he jumps dirty, we'll know.
Vic and his guys are tight.
Lemansky, he's a soldier.
So you're gonna need
something to drive a wedge
between him and Mac.
Terry was working with Justice
to bring down Mac.
And I think Vic had him killed.
We killed a cop.
Get over it.
Don't bring it up again.
Curtis Lemansky. I need you
to come with us.
Why is it that the guy with
the conscience always has
to get caught holding the bag?
What do you want?
We want the guy that put it into motion.
Who do you think
I want, Curtis?
VIC:
Still no Lem?
SHANE:
Left a second message.
Probably knee-deep in a booty call.
RONNIE:
Hope he's getting the cop discount.
SHANE:
I hear yours
charges by the minute.
I get mine for free.
VIC: Must be seeing a charity worker.
I was just about to call
you again. Vic, it's nice of you
to finally show up.
VIC:
Better be a damn good reason
for you blowing up my cell phone.
Who dimed you that crack mule
last year?
It's payback time, man.
Come look at this.
Man, look at my windshields.
VIC:
We don't monitor lemon laws.
SHANE: Good thing they're sold as is.
Look, don't waste my time again.
Next time you call me,
it better be something real.
Shit, the name Vic Mackey used
to have some juice around here.
Up to no good,
looking to run and hide
from Vic Mackey?
Oh, no, he'd find you
and you'd get yours.
Now assholes like him lean
on honest people
because they know cops like you
can't do dick anymore.
Who's leaning?
Wetback.
Street name Doomsday.
Squeezing every shop
on the block for insurance.
Is that real enough
for you?
How long has it been going on?
Couple of months.
Man, I've come in today,
man. I missed one payment.
One payment.
And look at my windshields now.
Man, my son's right.
He's right.
It's every man
for himself from now on.
Shit, I should have paid
that prick off.
You're scared.
It's understandable.
You made a serious mistake
and you don't see
a way out of this.
I didn't commit any crime.
I'm a goddamn cop.
Gotta start with denial
till you get your head
around all this.
It's cool. I understand, really.
We got time here.
I've never seen
those drugs before.
Come on, man. It was taken
from your vehicle
with a search warrant.
I got the seizure on videotape.
You know I can walk
out of here right now.
Well, if you do, I'm gonna have
to arrest you,
take you downtown,
make it official.
I'm trying to save you
the embarrassment here.
I got nothing
to be embarrassed about.
We've both been through
enough of these
so I can be straight
with you, yeah?
Sure.
Every guilty suspect that
you've ever interviewed
started with denial, right?
So did the innocent ones.
[KNOCKING]
VIC:
Ah, you must be Doomsday.
Who are you?
I'm Armageddon.
Say hello to the hounds of hell.
Ruff.
You've been squeezing some
of the local business owners.
Consider us the Better Business
Bureau shutting your ass down.
I didn't invite you in.
You got some paper
or something?
It's an unofficial visit.
Letting you know
the cops are still on
the job in Farmington.
Yeah, and we're putting
the word out
one asshole at a time.
Get your toy-cop ass
out of here.
Are you getting my message,
or you need your ears cleaned?
[DOOMSDAY CHUCKLES]
SHANE:
What are you laughing at?
The only words I wanna
hear out of your mouth
are, "Si, señor."
Suck my dick, señor.
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTING]
SHANE:
Hey!
No warrant.
It's your call.
Hey. Over here.
SHANE:
Get up.
VIC: Come on. Hands up.
That'll give you plenty
of time to think about
your new career direction.
We'll return this
to its rightful owners.
You gotta take a piss,
be sure and give us a call.
[GROWLS]
I need to get back to my team.
Eat something.
We're gonna
be here for a while.
The only thing outside
that door for you
is a prison cell.
And I haven't been able
to tell you how I'm gonna
keep you out of it yet.
You know, I read your package,
and I met with
one of your old partners.
And he said that...
He said you made a lot
of great arrests.
You started off
an upright guy.
What happened to you?
How'd you go from riding
with cops to hunting them?
Tio Osmond.
Diagur Leyva.
Connie Reisler.
They were all Strike Team Cls.
So what?
Any of the people you
work with make it out alive?
Look, they chose the life.
They chose to cooperate
with the police.
And now they're dead.
Better them than us.
Or did you forget that
from the academy?
Angie Stubbs.
She was 15 when
she helped you before
she was murdered.
She choose the life too?
No.
She was a good kid.
Bet she was.
What do you think
should happen to, uh?
To someone who kills
a kid like that?
To someone who kills a cop
or a grandma?
Life in prison? Death penalty?
The needle's too good
for someone like that.
Finally. We agree
on something here.
Detective Terry Crowley.
Remember him?
Two and a half years ago,
he was on your Strike Team.
He was undercover
when he was killed.
Part of a federal investigation
into your team.
You know what,
I've seen a lot of things
that make me think
that you're a good guy.
I just cannot figure out
how you could be involved
with this murder.
What are you talking about?
Terry was killed by
a drug dealer. I was there.
I know you were there.
But we both know that
is not the way it went down.
Could you be more full of shit
right now?
Terry was killed
in the line of duty.
The one thing I know for sure
is that by the end of the day,
you are either gonna be helping me
with the truth
or you are going
to be behind bars.
[###]
SHANE:
What's up, big mama?
You ready to announce Papa yet?
No, but you'll be
the last to know.
Listen, guys, Lem's running late.
What, he called in?
No, a friend did. Said
his car broke down. He'll
be in as soon as he can.
VIC:
Okay, thanks.
Guess honey was nothing
to write home about.
Got multiple homicides
on Dozier. Billings gave this to you.
His gang?
You tell us.
Two black males, a black female.
You're no one till somebody kills you.
Not in this corner
of paradise.
These kids aren't
flying colours.
Any forced entry?
Back door's busted in.
Victims had cash and credit cards.
Whoever it was didn't get much.
Whoever it was got
exactly what they came for.
[WOMAN SOBBING]
RONNIE:
She called it in.
Came over to study with her friends,
saw the bodies through the window.
VIC:
Street's gang-neutral.
Plus, this was a beating,
not a shooting. Strictly personal.
Any crack houses
in this neighbourhood?
VIC:
None that register.
All right, let's find out
who these kids were
and what they were into.
Bodies are still warm.
Let's crack it before they cool.
Shop owner found him on the
pavement. He didn't recognize him.
Strong odour of alcohol.
Any bars nearby?
No. A couple of auto body shops,
a church up the street.
I checked the wallet.
Lives 10 blocks from here.
Good. You're starting
to get an instinct for
the right things to look for.
He didn't walk here on his own.
Not in that condition.
Check the houses on this
side of the alley and look
around for some teeth.
Guillermo Solis.
Alcohol-induced coma.
EMT says it's 50-50.
Where have you been?
I'm here now.
Since when does a misdemeanour
drunk in public need two detectives?
I don't think this guy
got plastered and fell over.
He had broken teeth, facial cuts.
I'm calling it an assault.
Any sign of robbery?
Didn't take his money. I'm
thinking he was dumped here.
So he got drunk, he passed out.
They drug him here,
let somebody else deal with it.
It's not the most neighbourly thing,
but we've seen worse
and we didn't call it assault.
Eh... Maybe.
VIC:
Hang on a second.
I saw you look out.
Now open up. Now.
Always look out your window?
There's cops. I was curious.
Curious enough to see
something that happened
earlier across the street?
We're gonna keep talking.
It's only gonna take your neighbours
about 30 seconds to figure
you do know something.
So you might as well tell me
so I can get off your porch.
[DOGS BARKING]
Quiet.
I came home to let my dogs out
and I saw somebody
leaving that house.
What did he look like?
Got something?
I'm not leaving till I find out.
Look, the guy was scary.
He looked right at me
and I went cold.
He looked like evil, okay?
Go now.
I'm gonna take you in
and put you with a sketch artist.
You said you'd leave me alone.
A lot of people wanna know
what evil looks like.
KAVANAUGH:
Councilman. Hey, hey.
I picked up Lemansky last night.
Where is he?
Back at the motel.
Feel him out before
I make a move, you know.
What about the rest of the team?
You were right about Lemansky.
And this Terry murder?
It is a soft spot.
But with me,
it was still theoretical.
I mean, I'm trying to get inside it
and I will get inside it.
But I need you to add
that personal element to it.
The department brought you in
to close this and you come
running back to me?
I can just see where
this is going, and I'm not
above asking for help.
Besides, I thought Crowley
was your friend.
He was.
You suspected Mackey all along,
and you just let him go.
I pursued it as far as I could.
Yeah, well, here's another chance.
Mackey's out the door
in four months.
Forced retirement.
Out the door?
Fifteen-year pension.
That ain't a bad reward
for killing a cop, is it?
Sorry. Please, sorry.
We could never prove it.
But you know it.
And now we got someone
that can prove it.
Hold on a second.
Witness give you something?
You gotta see this.
Sure looks a lot like
the Salvadoran we
leaned on today. Doomsday?
Could be it. It's hard to tell.
Besides, he's tied up.
Is that Doomsday?
We put this out yet?
Yeah, went out on
the wire a few minutes
ago. Gets worse.
IDs came back
on the victims
at the house.
Community college geeks.
No history of trouble.
One of the males' last names
was Hughes.
As in Hughes Used Cars?
It was his kid.
Big D said he didn't pay
last week, remember?
So Doomsday sent a message.
We don't know that yet.
It was a couple of busted windshields.
Why'd we push so hard?
Because there's still
some goddamn laws in Farmington,
no matter what the voters reject.
Plus he came at me.
He was in my face.
That the suspect in the triple murder?
Yeah.
Do we know him?
Could be a Salvadoran lowlife
who lives in the neighbourhood.
We're trying to get a 20 on him now.
You think it's another racial incident?
I'll let you know.
BILLINGS: Great.
Grab some extra unis
if you need them.
Yeah, if we can find one.
So we cause a triple murder
before breakfast,
start a race war before dinner.
That's a pretty good day.
Get the word out to the Aztecs
and Zulus that this wasn't retribution.
Some beef about
business, that's all.
You with me?
Yeah.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO]
He chewed through
that goddamn thing?
Holy shit.
We gotta find this guy.
You got a minute?
Sure, come in.
I need a line on a Salvadoran,
calls himself Doomsday.
You heard of him?
No. Know where he lives?
Temple Colter area.
You got friends down there?
I'll have to spread
a little love around.
I need to pull this guy
off the street now.
Now, this is one of
those times you can earn
yourself some real money.
That's too much, Vic.
All I need is
a couple dubs for my girls.
Keep what you save.
Ten times that amount
if we can get him in custody.
Everything copasetic?
DUTCH: Yeah.
That's what I like to hear.
All the emperor needs
is a toga and a violin
while Farmington burns.
They offered you that job first.
You turned it down.
It would have been yours
but you screwed it up.
Mrs. Solis.
Thanks for coming in.
How's your husband?
At the hospital
they said the machines
are keeping him alive.
But his brain...
Sorry.
We just need
your signature here
and you can take
his personal effects.
Did you see your husband
last night?
I took him to church for his meeting.
CLAUDETTE: Is it a 12-step program?
They didn't work for Guillermo.
He just kept on drinking.
DUTCH:
What sort of meeting was this?
Señor Romero has them
drink until the alcohol
cures the sickness.
Aversion therapy.
You weren't concerned
when he didn't come home?
Señor Romero lets them
sleep at the church
if they're in, you know,
bad shape.
Who's Señor Romero again?
SOLIS:
Our minister.
Señor Romero?
Yes.
DUTCH:
We need to talk to you
about Guillermo Solis.
Is there a problem?
He's in a coma.
He may not live.
Too much drink.
Lord bless his soul.
We understand you
were treating him
for substance abuse
at the church last night.
I don't treat people.
I don't have a license for that.
He attends our prayer group.
Where you feed booze
to alcoholics?
That's fascinating.
Everything they drink,
they drink of
their own free will.
We fight the sickness
with sickness.
This aversion therapy,
it really works for some people?
It's how I conquered
my issues with alcohol.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have
my business and my church.
My ex-wife was a drunk.
Do you think if I'd hauled her
off to happy hour every night,
I could've saved the marriage?
I wouldn't wanna speculate.
CLAUDETTE:
Who else was there last night?
Hector Santiago.
He works at the church.
And he's going through the therapy.
Just the three of you?
Well, the group gets smaller
as more of us are healed.
Well, uh,
keep up the good work.
Sure.
Told you I had a feeling.
Preachers need to stick to preaching.
Want me to ask Romero
if he's got that
in your size?
ASHER:
Your witness was worried
about her dogs.
She made me promise
to come check on them.
Living room.
Guess Doomsday
ain't a member of PETA.
What do we know about Doomsday?
RONNIE: He's from North Carolina.
Did a stint for agg assault
in Atascadero, got out
six months ago.
Took a guy's eye out
with a fork for stealing
his food in junior high.
Keep pressing the local
sets. Guys like this
make friends all over.
SHANE:
It's a good thing you pulled Irma in.
Where are the heads?
Nowhere. Checked
the whole place.
He took
the goddamn dogs' heads.
RONNIE:
What's he gonna do?
Put them on a pike?
We gotta find this freak.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Councilman.
You two know
each other already.
Curtis.
What are you doing here?
KAVANAUGH:
You've got a big decision
to make, not a lot of time.
So I thought you should
get as much information
as possible.
ACEVEDA:
It's time for you to step
into the sunlight, Lem.
LEM:
Look, I didn't do anything wrong.
You're not my captain anymore.
You took some heroin,
you got caught.
Now, we're not just talking
about your career here, Lem.
The city referendum showed all of us
what the public thinks of cops.
The department's fighting
to change that perception
so somebody has to pay a price.
And right now, that's you.
Well, you know what?
I'll take my chances
with the truth in court.
Everything that Lieutenant Kavanaugh
told you about Terry was true.
Terry didn't have a grudge
against Vic going in,
but it only took him
two weeks to find out
that Vic was a dirty cop.
I have his original notes
detailing his suspicions.
He was your teammate,
he was a threat,
so he had to die.
No. Never!
You didn't know, did you?
Vic never told you.
All this time, I thought
the four of you
were in it together,
but you really didn't know.
This changes everything.
You're saying you didn't
know about it until right now.
It was the other guys.
I didn't say that. I didn't say that.
But you didn't know.
I mean, I respect a guy
being loyal, but now
you're protecting a guy
for something that you don't
have any stake in.
Something that you
told me the death penalty
was too good for.
This is a damn witch hunt
right now.
You cannot be a cop
and be a part of it with him.
You gotta choose.
Vic did not kill Terry.
So prove it.
Wear a wire.
Ask him as a friend.
See what he's got to say.
Look, you wanna railroad
an innocent guy,
go ahead and do it.
Do it, but I do not
have to help.
So you'd rather take on prison
than someone
who took out one of your own?
That is a tough choice...
but I understand.
SOLIS:
Guillermo was a jealous man.
The drinking only made it worse.
You give him reason
to be jealous?
Why are you asking me
those questions?
Those are nice shoes.
You get those from Romero?
Saw a pair like them.
They were a gift from El Señor.
How long have you been
sleeping with Romero?
I have never done that.
But he's made advances,
hasn't he?
I'm a married woman.
He made me feel good.
But I told El Señor
I would not betray my vows.
You mean "till death do us part"?
You know what? Know what?
I need a decision.
What happened
to having some time?
Can't believe you need any.
Look, Vic is your friend
and you're loyal,
but you also gotta be loyal
to your badge.
Gotta be loyal to yourself.
To an innocent brother cop.
It's decision time.
You tell me. Do I parade you
into Police One
or do I call a technician
and wire you up?
ACEVEDA:
You know, Lem,
if Vic is innocent like you say,
you'd be helping him out.
If I do...
what do I get out of it?
SHANE: Doomsday's here?
VIC: According to Emolia's friend.
That's not exactly laying low.
All right, let's go.
VIC: On the ground now!
SHANE: Let's go! Let's go right now!
On the ground!
VIC: Get down on the ground!
You son of a bitch.
You do need your ears cleaned.
Where'd you put
the dogs' heads?
What are you talking about?
Right.
Where does Mackey like to put these?
On the chest.
Make a case on Mackey,
the others, you walk away free.
Here you go.
There's one more thing.
If you lie to me,
try to screw me,
or you just don't live up
to the deal
I will push for maximum
for distribution of heroin.
Just know that's the truth.
Did you get all that?
TECH:
Perfect. Mike's working great.
KAVANAUGH:
Let's go.
Hey, hey. Where you going?
I've gotta run an errand. Sorry.
I'll be back in about an hour.
Can it wait? I'm trying to close.
Sorry.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'll hurry back.
Well, I'll start. Jump in
when you get back.
DUTCH:
Tox report came back.
He was practically embalmed.
No way he had enough
motor function to swallow,
much less hold the bottle.
It even amazes me
sometimes how much
these chronic alcoholics
can put away.
DUTCH: You, uh,
screwing any other sheep
in your flock, Reverend?
Or you just like giving shoes
to all the pretty wives?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
And in my faith,
I am called Apostle, not Reverend.
How did Guillermo's
front teeth get broken?
He must have fallen down.
You shoved a bottle in his mouth.
Celia Solis said she
wouldn't sleep with you
while her husband was alive,
so you tried to kill him,
but only his brain died.
No, the devil did that to him.
Alcohol was his demon.
Santiago said Guillermo
had the shakes.
You notice anything like that?
I left them both asleep
in the sanctuary.
I went to my office.
I wrote this week's sermon.
When I returned,
Guillermo wasn't in the church.
I figured he had sobered up
enough to walk home.
And Santiago was too out of it
to say otherwise.
You've got all
your bases covered.
I'll put my hand on the Bible.
Not as much fun
as putting your hand
on another man's wife.
VIC:
Get in there, you sick prick.
Glad you could join us.
Hey.
Smells ripe, buddy. Hope you put
a little boom in her womb.
I had to stop by my friend's
on the way back from Chino.
Car broke down so I waited
a half day for a mechanic.
Good thing
you didn't call back.
I ain't about to haul my ass
out there to pick
you up. Oh, yeah.
DANNY:
Hey, Vic. Downtown called.
They wanna see any records
that you have on Terry Crowley.
VIC: They say why?
No, just want anything you got.
Probably just wanna close out the file.
Yeah.
All right, I gotta pull a couple of
old boxes, but I'll see what I can do.
You missed the first half.
We're still in the game.
I just picked up a suspect
in a triple murder.
Put me in, coach.
It's not him.
VIC:
Oh, for chrissakes. Don't do this.
I said it's not him.
This man killed three
innocent people today.
That's not my fault.
What about the next person
he kills? That will be.
He already killed my dogs.
SHANE:
Well, you think just because
you're not ID'ing him,
he's not gonna try
to kill you too?
You're protecting a killer.
Makes you no better than he is.
IRMA:
Sorry.
For the record,
I saw someone, but not him.
What happened to your hands?
Looks like you got
into one hell of a dogfight.
Scratched them up
someplace.
Senior Hughes refuses to pay you
protection, Junior winds up dead.
Niggers die every day.
Save that grin for the lineup
before I smack it off your face.
Need a witness for a lineup.
Ruff, ruff.
I'm holding you on suspicion
of vandalism. Cruelty to animals.
That means we're about
eight minutes into
a 12-hour conversation.
Wanna see how cruel I can be
to animals like you?
A lot can happen in 12 hours.
Problem for you
is we don't scare like girls.
And our bite's as good
as our bark, asshole.
JULIEN:
We gain entry and do what?
TINA:
Separate the parties,
look for visual signs of injury.
You taking the son?
JULIEN: Yeah, you get the father.
Control the scene.
Use force if necessary.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO]
Over there.
[PEOPLE YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
JULIEN:
Hey. Come here, come here.
AARON: Did she take it?
JULIEN: Calm down.
Calm down.
[YELLING]
TED: He's on the drugs again.
AARON:
She steals my shit,
and you let her get away!
TINA:
Sir.
Sir, I just need you to step outside.
[GRUNTS]
Shit.
JULIEN:
Hey, that's enough!
Tina! That's enough!
TINA:
Thanks.
He wouldn't listen.
It's your job to make him listen.
I was trying...
Trying gets you killed.
You failed to get the father
out of the room, then you
used excessive force.
You said to use force if necessary.
Controlled hits.
Behind his knees...
That's exactly what I was doing.
No force would have
been necessary, none,
if you had followed
proper procedure.
That's gonna need stitches.
KAVANAUGH:
Corrine, hi.
CORRINE:
Hi, Jon. Um,
you picking up your son?
Yeah, my ex was supposed to.
She bailed out at the last
second, so I skipped out
of work and came here.
I'm sorry.
It's par for the course.
Hey, guys.
You know what? Why don't
you guys go play over by
the swings for a little bit?
Watch your sister for me, okay?
So is it a bad divorce, or?
Yeah.
She's with this other guy now.
I got primary custody,
she's supposed to be
paying child support.
She's this big-time
money manager.
I haven't seen a cent, though,
in like three months.
You're kidding? I mean,
she doesn't even help out at all?
I'm just running a little late
on the tuition here.
And you? You're paying
for your children all by yourself?
Oh, no. Uh, Vic helps out.
But the occupational therapists,
and the evaluations, and...
Yeah. Um...
You know, Vic always comes up
with whatever extra cash
I need for the kids, so...
He sounds like a great guy.
Well, let's not make him
a saint quite yet.
Yeah? What's his bad side?
Just trying to compare him
to my ex's bad side because...
Okay. Well, he's hard-headed.
Uh... He likes to get his way.
And job comes first.
Same here.
But he loves his kids.
What's your boy's name again?
Andrew. Andy.
Uh, is he?
No, he's, uh...
He's doing some
extra work with one
of his teachers right now.
Maybe, uh, you could
bring Andy around for
a play date some time?
That would be a huge, huge help.
Billings keeps asking what we got.
We got nothing.
We got no prints,
no weapons...
No goddamn witness.
Why don't we just cut this guy loose
and continue this conversation
on the street.
VIC:
What kind of conversation?
Well, Irma's the only thing
we had. She ain't
sticking her neck out ever.
We could turn him on
to Special Cases.
Let them run with it.
Pass the buck?
And have the street still think
that we're stuck behind desks
with our tail between our legs?
They got the resources,
the manpower...
Every minute he walks
around free, we're
a bigger joke.
We're gonna handle
this guy so people know
that we got him.
Hey, what about the guy
that we met on
the Mexi sting last year?
VIC: What about him?
Hold on. Look, I gotta take off, man.
Where you going?
My stomach's bugging me.
Do you mind if I pick it
back up tomorrow?
VIC: Sure, you gonna be all right?
Yeah.
It's just my medicine. I'm back on it.
I left it at home.
VIC: All right, I'll see you tomorrow.
Take care.
He gonna get paid for today?
Keep going.
VIC:
It's a great country.
Respecting the human rights
of a bloodthirsty piece of shit
like yourself.
I just might have to sue your ass.
I got a feeling your life
just took a turn for the worse.
Or it could just be
wishful thinking.
[DOOR BUZZES]
You go back to filling out
your paperwork.
Stay the hell off my street.
DANNY:
Well, I told you to lose the earrings.
Figured it was no big deal
but I should've listened to you.
Protocol's there for a reason.
Well, it won't happen again.
You know what?
Do yourself a favour.
Don't turn being a cop and a girl
into a juggling act.
MAN:
Yeah. All right, see you later.
You were Julien's
training officer, right?
I mean, he's a good guy and all,
he reads the Bible, but...
But maybe he has a problem
working with women.
We have the same plumbing,
but that doesn't mean I'm gonna
dish with you about your TO.
I didn't mean it like that.
You wanna succeed around here?
Do yourself a favour.
Just listen up
and do like you're told.
CLAUDETTE:
What did I miss?
DUTCH:
Uh, everything.
I lasered the PowerPoints
on the Romero thing for the DA.
They weren't biting.
You called the DA?
Yeah. I just said I lasered them.
DUTCH: What did you tell them?
BILLINGS: What Claudette told me.
On my way out, he asked me
where we were. I filled him in.
Well, we're still investigating.
The guy is guilty.
BILLINGS:
Look, your hunches
notwithstanding,
my strong sense is
they're not gonna find
the arena sexy enough.
DUTCH:
Sexy enough?
Hey, I'm just passing along
what your partner told me
and what I found out.
You got a beef with her,
you figure it out instead
of walking on me
with your anger shoes.
Anger shoes?
SHANE:
That's him.
RONNIE:
Hello, asshole.
Against the wall.
Come on.
RONNIE:
Somebody called
for a police escort.
Must've been you.
Always happy to help out
a citizen in need.
Let's go.
You sure you want in?
Yeah.
SHANE: We can do this without you.
VIC: Where's the fun in that?
We're a team.
Okay.
DOOMSDAY:
What are you guys talking about?
Want in on what?
CLAUDETTE:
Now, take everything
that's a name-brand
trademark violation.
MAN: You got it.
DUTCH: Take him into custody.
CLAUDETTE:
Is it worth taking
another run at the DA?
Romero skates
on attempted murder.
At least he won't be selling
knockoff shoes anymore.
Well, you get lemons,
you make lemonade.
Where is this hey-man-it's-all-good
whatever bullshit coming from
all of a sudden?
CLAUDETTE: Excuse me?
Catch the mediocrity flu
Billings has been passing around?
This guy tried to kill somebody.
He's getting off on a Class B felony
while you took a half-day
of personal time.
I was out of the Barn
for an hour and a half today, max.
Come on. You're coming in late,
when you're here,
your head's not in the game.
I'm sorry the case didn't make.
It was never a slam dunk.
Hey, Julien.
"Officer Hanlon used
unnecessary and excessive force
in subduing the second suspect."
You really want that
on her record?
That's what happened.
DANNY:
Look, Billings hasn't seen this yet.
Why don't you sleep on it?
Especially since she was
coming to the aid
of a fellow officer.
Department is still liable
for her actions against
an unarmed citizen.
She's 5'4".
Excessive for you,
excessive for her are
probably two different things.
It's my call. Night.
Hey, have you requested
extra baton training for her?
No.
Maybe you should think
about your responsibilities
as a training officer.
I also have a responsibility
to wash her out if
she can't handle it.
I could have washed you out
a couple of times.
I'd like to think
that I made the right decision.
Where are the dogs' heads?
They're in the freezer.
I was gonna make them into soup.
Make that bitch
who saw me drink it.
Where are we going?
Over there.
[DOOMSDAY GRUNTING]
RONNIE:
Come here, come here.
SHANE:
Let's go. Let's go. Get in the car.
VIC:
Amigo.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
VIC:
Para tú.
Guy spends a weekend a month
at a whorehouse in TJ.
Likes his Mexican pussy.
Just keep him away
from the chihuahuas.
RONNIE:
But he should have left this at home.
[TONIO SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Possession of a weapon
in my country
is a very serious crime.
DOOMSDAY:
You can't do this shit.
You can't do this shit!
I'm a citizen!
SHANE: Yeah?
Phones work in those
Mexi jails. Maybe they'll let you
call the State Department.
VIC: Government types
aren't too helpful
getting murder suspects
out of foreign prisons.
Mexico makes our gun laws
look like parking violations.
Good luck.
VIC: See you in 20 years, asshole.
I know you hate
passing the buck.
What are you gonna do?
[ALARM HONKS]
Hey.
Hey, man.
Something's bothering me.
We need to talk.
VIC [OVER RADIO]:
Sure, what's going on?
LEM: Look, I...
I was reading through those
Terry files that Danny ask ed for.
Why? It's ancient history.
Well, he died on
our watch. Something
always seemed weird,
and now people are asking
for these files.
Where's this coming from?
LEM:
What happened that night?
VIC:
You were there.
You know what happened.
You're not telling me everything.
Of course I am.
No, no, you're not.
He was my friend.
I'm your friend.
Tell me.
What the hell you think you're doing?
Don't you lie to me. Don't lie to me.
What are you doing? Stop.
[STATIC CRACKLES OVER RADIO]
Where's the sound?
TECH: I don't know.
I need the sound.
I'm working, I'm working.
Hey.
IAD has me wired, all right?
What?
I just disconnected it.
IAD has me wired, okay?
They're watching us
right now.
They busted me with
some heroin, they're talking
prison if I don't do this.
What else?
I've been protecting you all day.
They're gunning for all of us.
Some IAD player and Aceveda.
Okay, I gotta make a decision,
and I gotta make it quick.
Why is it even a question?
Because I think you're lying to me.
I'm not.
Then you look me in the eye
and you tell me
the truth about Terry.
Okay, if I don't
believe you, I'm gonna start
looking out for myself.
Don't listen to them.
Don't buy into their bull...
Tell me the truth.
We're a team.
Yeah, that Terry was a part of once.
KAVANAUGH:
Come on, come on.
Now tell me.
How can you even ask me that?
They told me Terry was working
with the feds to bring us down.
Now answer me, okay?
You look me in the eye.
You tell me the truth.
I mean, if we're really a team, man,
tell me the truth already.
Oh, my God.
We're in on this together, all right?
I need to go. I need to go.
Everything's fine.
We're fi... Everything's fine.
Where you going?
We gotta talk. Don't.
I need to go, man.
Where is the sound?
It's gotta be his mike.
Lem.
Lem!
[###]