NARRATOR:
Previously on The Shield.
ACEVEDA: We're talking
about making a case that puts
Mackey behind bars for a long time
and I want you to help me prove it.
Okay.
[###]
Detective Terry Crowley
was pronounced dead
at 2: 13 this morning.
No!
We killed a cop.
Get over it
and don't bring it up again.
Stay on Mackey, all of his guys.
You sure?
I wish I wasn't.
Your captain's been relieved
of duty. We need someone
to cover in an interim capacity.
What was that about?
He asked me to be the
company yes-man jellyfish.
Told him to shove it.
Where's your stash?
PITARRIO: It's in there, man.
If we find the dead girl's body,
you get this back.
Those drugs were never
logged into evidence.
Wally called in
one of my colleagues.
We were able to ID Lemansky
from her description.
Searched his vehicle while he was
sleeping, procured the heroine,
and replaced it with
a nonnarcotic substance.
Vic likes me and my boy.
He wants to take care of us.
We can use that.
I thought you were Vic's CI.
Whoever's got the money.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING
AND SHOUTING]
WOMAN 1:
Stop it!
WOMAN 2:
Stop it. Stop it!
[DISPATCHER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING
AND SHOUTING]
Stop, police!
SHANE: Police!
LEM:
All right, let's split them up.
Hey, hey.
SHANE:
Come on, Joe.
Let's go, in the other room.
Get out.
LEM: Get out.
SHANE: Get in the other room.
VIC: Get him out of here.
Get in the other room right now.
Get out of here. Get out!
Ronnie, you all right?
Yeah.
SHANE:
Everybody, just be quiet.
Who hit me?
Jesus Christ?
Come on, man, turn around.
Let me see hands.
Anything?
SHANE:
Nothing. No blood on the Mexis.
LEM: Blacks are clean too.
Shit.
Go to the ER,
get that looked at.
Get a waggon.
Haul in the grieving families.
Tell the captain I said to send it.
All right.
Bullshit uni calls.
Better get used to it.
Sir.
You see who
domed my guy?
Black kid. Got, like, a blond afro.
I see him hanging out in front
of Kwiky's Liquor on my way home.
What the hell's going on here?
It's, like, the second black and
Latino brawl I've had this week.
Where do you live?
Culver City.
Hell, you better learn how
to coordinate your colours
there, Westside.
Last week, some black guy went
hit-and-run on a Mexican kid.
Crushed his skull.
We couldn't generate
any cooperative witnesses.
Cholos took it on themselves.
Hunted the driver and beat him
to death.
Black hood jumped in
and killed two Mexicans.
Went sideways ever since.
I didn't know.
Yeah. Thanks.
PARAMEDIC: She's got
three punctures in her back.
TINA:
Who found her?
A junior. Zellie Praza. She's pretty
devastated. She's in my office.
Do you have any
metal detectors here?
Some of them
don't work very well.
TINA:
Any other witnesses?
Well, there's 1500
students in the school.
I would think so.
Thanks.
Good questions. Nice work.
PRINCIPAL:
Officer, would you like to see Zellie?
Uh, the detectives will. Keep her
in your office until they get there.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Tina? Tina. Hey.
T... Tina!
What?
You're contaminating
the crime scene.
Oh, shit.
All right, guys, come on.
The captain's gonna address
the troops in the briefing room.
Let's head in.
This should be educational.
Hey. Hey, come on.
I'm hormonal and I expedite
your pay cheques,
so let's move it.
What's going on?
Captain's calling a pep talk.
SHANE: Yeah, because when
I think pep, I think Billings.
BILLINGS:
Okay.
Thanks for joining me.
Bet you lunch he says
"and so forth" at least twice.
As you probably know,
yesterday, Measure 16
on the city ballot failed.
So it looks like those temporary
budget cuts are now permanent.
That'll be 17 percent
across the board.
[CROWD MURMURING]
Which means...
Which means we'll have to make due
with the lack of manpower
here in the Barn and on
the street and so forth.
Um...
Now, the chief wants you to know
this is by no means a reflection
of the fine job that
you're all doing for our city.
Of course not.
BILLINGS:
Listen, uh, starting next week, we're
gonna be going to single-unit patrols.
I know. Which means if you have
more than six months on the street,
you're gonna be flying solo.
And speaking of flying solo
at six months,
Officer Sofer might be mum
on who the daddy is,
but she'll gladly spill the beans
on your new assignments.
[CHUCKLES]
[DANNY CLEARS THROAT]
Okay. Um, that's all I have.
You guys keep up
the good work, all right?
Hey, cheap bastards don't wanna
cough up a half a cent of sales tax,
screw them.
Next time somebody bitches
P.D. didn't show up,
tell them that could have
bought two cops, on time.
So let's keep showing up.
Everything else
will even itself out.
That's right.
Everything always evens out.
And so forth.
Don't hate me
because I'm always right.
We need to talk
to the rest of Zellie's class.
Well, the juniors are at lunch.
The entire class?
We'll be here all day.
[STUDENTS SCREAMING
AND SHOUTING]
JULIEN:
Hey, hey, hey.
TINA:
Get down. Get down.
Come on, move it.
TINA:
Get down. I said, move. Move!
GIRL 1:
I'm out of here!
[GUNSHOTS]
JULIEN:
Gun!
[STUDENTS SCREAMING]
Come on. Get them out!
JULIEN: Tina.
Julien.
JULIEN:
Tina.
GIRL 2:
Oh, my God.
[###]
We got a full-blown riot
at Wellman-Chase High School.
Shots have been fired.
Officers need help.
Tactical alert. All we got.
Get them there now.
Have FD and EMS
stage two blocks out.
Tell them it's chaos on arrival.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
LEM: Stay down.
SHANE: Stay down.
Let go of me. Let go.
SHANE:
Hey, kid, get off him. Back off!
Get off. Get off him.
[GIRLS SCREAMING]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Shit. Go on, get out of here.
Get the hell out of here.
Let me borrow that.
Give it to me.
All right, fire it up!
[SIRENS WAILING]
JESSE:
Vic, Wilshire East came through.
Set up a mobile field force.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Come on. Get up, punk.
This was your solution?
Turn the goddamn fire hose
on my kid?
What was I supposed to do, open fire?
Never stopped you all before.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm David Aceveda,
your councilman.
I can assure you that
it was the safest option
to protect all these kids.
Right.
PARAMEDIC: Let's get a gurney
over here. Have to bag him.
Get the lab rats to lift those
prints. May be our knifer.
It's not.
Paramedics?
JULIEN: Officer Hanlon.
She got a little bit too close
to the crime scene.
I've already
discussed it with her.
You went into the bathroom?
It's my fault. I should have...
Preserving the scene
is Training Officer 101.
That's how murderers go free...
Murderers go free.
I'm really sorry, detectives.
It won't happen again.
It's okay.
Let's go.
It was a rookie mistake.
She's way too young for you.
DUTCH:
I am mature and distinguished.
A lot of young women
appreciate that.
You really ought to cut back
on the porn.
MAN:
Please move back.
DUTCH:
This shooting related to our stabbing
or was this for extra credit?
CLAUDETTE:
Either way, he's not graduating.
You okay?
I'm fine.
I can grab those
paramedics.
I said, I'm fine. Let's give that to Vic
and we'll stick with the stabbing.
Okay.
DANNY:
Parents wanna take their kids home.
Nothing would
make me happier.
Unfortunately, all those shitheads
are suspects and witnesses.
They wanna talk to a captain.
And I want more hair.
All right, you handle it.
It's good mothering practise.
Vic, what do you got?
Armed and dangerous, Taser.
He was in the cafeteria
when the kid got shot.
All right. Listen.
Anything you can do to quiet
this shitstorm, get it off my plate,
it's got my blessing.
[DOOR CLOSES]
You a member of
the Varsity Taser Club, Weston?
Eleven of your classmates
are in Mission Cross,
some critical, one dead.
And this... puts you at the top
of the most-likely-to-be-tried-
as-an-adult list.
Knife and gun did the damage.
That don't mean shit.
Shit.
SHANE: That's persuasion by proxy.
I didn't hurt nobody.
Yeah? What do you use this for?
Toasting Pop-Tarts?
Protection, man.
Shit's crazy going on.
What shit?
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
Goddamn, that shit ain't right.
All right, all right, all right.
It's a kill clock.
Some Mexican's gotta kill
a couple brothers by tonight.
Why?
I don't know the whys,
man, just the what.
Who's the Mexican?
If I knew that, I wouldn't
be carrying the zapper.
That's for being a wiseass.
Claudette, I might know
what your stabbing's about.
Guy in 1 thinks there's
a kill clock ticking.
Kill clock?
Yeah, gangs use it to set
a time limit on an initiation
or a retaliation.
He heard some Mexican's
gonna try to kill two blacks.
Just randomly?
You think it's legit?
It doesn't matter.
If it stirs up enough fear, it's real.
Would explain why
our witness isn't talking.
Yeah.
VIC: All right, keep at her.
I'm gonna tap into a CI of mine.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, that girl that was stabbed,
Caroline Tylin,
she just died in surgery. Sorry.
Hey, how you feeling?
How do I look?
Great.
Yeah?
Pretty much how I feel.
Thanks for asking.
Bad news, Zellie.
DUTCH: We know about
the black-brown retaliation.
And right now you're the closest
brown to our dead black girl.
She died?
CLAUDETTE:
Which means you were involved
or you know who did it.
DUTCH:
By not talking, you're interfering
with an investigation,
and that's a crime.
All right, I saw him
running out as I came in.
And then I saw her by the sink,
all bloody and shit.
Who was it?
Lorenzo Lavedra.
This kill clock's gotta fall gangland.
Vic and I should follow up on this.
Okay, we'll take over
the cafeteria shooting.
I'll tell the captain
we traded cases.
Why confuse him?
That it?
MAN:
For now. You'll hear from me soon.
Something else?
No.
[KNOCKING]
Excuse me.
You're here early.
Come in, please. Come on.
Come on. Have a seat.
I've only got a few minutes.
How can I help you,
Lieutenant Kavanaugh?
You know that IAD has been
looking into Detective Mackey
and the Strike Team he ran
while under your command.
Captain Rawlings began
that investigation.
I was aware of it.
That investigation still ongoing?
Yes, it is.
Well, what have you got?
What have I got?
We've got Lemansky.
He lifted a brick of tar
off the El Salvadorans.
We've been waiting for it
to spin into something more.
Which means you've got
nothing on Mackey.
His day job's
keeping him busy.
He hasn't had the freedom
to navigate much game.
But we've got a CI
next to him and when
he jumps dirty, we'll know.
Until then, I was hoping that you
might be able to help us out.
You've got my letter,
and I've got nothing else to add.
Mackey's your problem now,
not mine.
No, perception
is your problem.
I'm going after Mackey and his team.
Now, you can get on board
and be proactive,
or you can sit back
and spectate.
Just like you did when he was
running dirty on your watch.
Hey, I did everything I could
to rein him in.
Don't sit there
and threaten me with bad PR.
You're right.
I was out of line.
Hey, I'm sorry.
Please, come on. Sit down.
Mackey's jacket is like
a 20-page cautionary tale.
This is a lawsuit
waiting to happen.
I just wanna get him off
the street before he does
any more damage, that's it.
P.D. is looking for a poster boy
for corruption.
They crucify one of their own,
the public will trust the rest.
And next time,
that ballot measure, it passes.
Hm?
When you were captain,
Mackey and Vendrell were
interrogated
about the shooting death
of a Detective Terry Crowley.
From the notes, it's very clear
that you thought Mackey was
involved.
And your comrades
ruled it line of duty.
I was hoping you might be able
to shed some light on the specifics.
Though rumour has it that the feds
might have been involved with that.
Is that true?
What's my end?
Your suspicion. It's your letter.
We say you got the ball rolling.
You followed it through
even after you left the job.
Now, that's the man
that I would want to be mayor.
I would vote for that man.
Vic and his guys are tight.
And Lemansky, he's a soldier.
He'll follow
Mackey anywhere.
But he's also the one
with a conscience.
So you're gonna
need something
to drive a wedge
between him and Mackey.
I need that wedge, councilman.
I need that wedge.
If I give you this, I'm done.
I don't want that guy's stink
on me anymore.
My word.
Terry was working with Justice
to bring down Mackey
and I think Vic
had him killed.
What kind of proof?
Detective Crowley's deal
with Justice.
That's good.
Can I get the intel
by the end of the day?
Sure.
No, thank you.
Come on, this is a fresh pack.
It's Juicy Fruit.
I said, no. Thank you.
You hold this out long enough
some people feel compelled
to take the gum.
It's a sign they'll crack
under pressure.
I know.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, listen...
Oh, there he is.
Hey, Sebastio,
how you doing?
Look how big you got.
Ooh. Oh, oh.
Wait a minute.
How did that get in there, huh?
You want that?
You want anything?
No. Here on business.
Got a kill clock ticking.
Mexican-on-black. These things
usually start on the inside,
so check with your
prison contacts, okay?
Okay.
Good.
Your CI renewal papers
hit my desk.
You need me to sign them?
Look, I know it pays the rent,
but CI work is a roll of the dice.
We've had a good six months,
but you should get out
before you get hurt.
I need that money, Vic.
What else am I gonna do?
Anything else.
I'll help you
find something.
You're worried about us.
I just want this to end
on good terms.
Now, tell me
you'll think about it.
Okay. I'll think about it.
Good. And if you hear anything
about this kill clock...
I'll let you know.
Good.
Was the riot
gang-related?
Well, we're still putting
the pieces together,
trying to get a clear
picture and so forth.
Well, what the hell
started it?
We don't have a motive yet,
but we have a suspect.
Good. I need a minute.
Shut the door.
This about me
hosing down those kids?
Rather have them pissed off
and wet, than dead and dry.
Huh, what?
You breaking up with me, Roy?
Got a call from Pensions.
Chief's having them
put through your papers.
They want you out
when you hit your 15.
You're putting me
on the beach?
This referendum failing,
cutbacks are hitting hard.
Anybody near their 20 or carrying
a risky jacket is getting the push.
At least you'll get
a piece of your pension.
There aren't enough cops as it is.
It's not personal. It's policy.
If it's not personal,
then why am I getting the news
hand-delivered to me
by the chief's inner circle?
Figure I owed you
a face-to-face.
It's bullshit and you know it.
It's some suit making
a judgement call.
Can't you put in a good word,
turn it my way?
I'm not Gilroy.
It's a different time.
Play this smart, Vic.
Don't give them a reason
to pull your pension.
SHANE:
Hey, AC.
Hey.
Uh, kid who did the stabbing,
Lorenzo Lavedra, 17.
A couple misdemeanours,
nothing violent. No gang ties.
His pops, however, is, uh...
He's doing a dime in Chino.
Assault.
Good.
What's up?
Jesus Christ.
These are retirement papers.
VIC:
Yeah.
Well, am I missing something?
Department's cutting
its liabilities.
Phillips wants me out
by the time I hit my 15th year.
That... That's like in
four months. That's crazy.
Um...
What are we gonna do?
I'll walk out the front door
on my own
before I'll let someone
push me out the back.
[LEM AND RONNIE CHATTERING]
This is between you and me.
Not a word.
[RONNIE CHUCKLING]
That's right.
Hey. How's the head?
RONNIE: Intact.
Man, nothing can hurt that cabeza.
Is it sore?
Yeah, okay.
Okay, okay.
LEM: Let's see it.
I want that asshole
who clubbed me.
VIC:
Oh, we'll get him.
'Hood needs a little reminder.
You hurt us, we hurt you worse.
We'll make sure
that measure passes.
We got a clock to
kill first, guys. Let's go.
[KNOCKING]
We're looking for Lorenzo.
Haven't seen him since this morning.
Has he been home all day today?
Don't know, just got here.
Was picking up Cisco
from soccer.
[MOTOR WHIRRING]
Hey, that's our guy!
Stay here.
[TYRES SCREECH]
SHANE:
Whoa, whoa! He went down.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Asshole's trying to finish
the kill clock.
Can't let him get out of browntown.
RONNIE: I got it.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
Get out of there
or I'll shoot.
SHANE: You okay?
Hey, give me your keys. Right now.
LORENZO:
Get out.
Ah! Damn it.
Get out of the car!
Hey, get out of the car!
Hands on your head right now!
Don't move or you're dead!
Let me see your hands!
SHANE: Let's go, let's go!
Come here.
Let's see your hands, buddy.
Stop struggling.
Got him?
Yeah, I got him.
What are you doing?
Why are you arresting him?
He ran a stop sign.
Where's Cisco?
He's downstairs.
The black guy. The guy
with the Bible. Is he dead?
No, he lost a lot of blood,
but he'll live to see Armageddon.
CALIDA:
My son was scared,
he panicked.
He sees what white cops do
to Mexican kids.
Oh, really? He panic when
he stabbed Caroline Tylin today?
Got a witness, saw him
fleeing from the bathroom.
No. Tell him you didn't do it, Renzi.
What time is it, Mama?
You got some place you gotta be?
I don't feel so good.
VIC: I wouldn't feel too good either
if I just slaughtered an innocent girl.
I'm guessing you didn't download
the death photo with your ringtones.
CALIDA:
Oh, Jesus.
Lorenzo.
VIC: Christ.
Take him to the bathroom,
please.
Hey, Officer Hanlon,
got a little job for you.
Anything you need, detective.
Clean him up.
Get him to the john.
Okay.
I'm Mexican. Why am I gonna
be offing up some other homes?
DUTCH: Maybe you had
a beef with him.
Maybe it was so crazy in
the cafeteria you got caught up
in the rush, fired off some shots.
I didn't do that.
DUTCH: Sure, you did.
No, I didn't.
CLAUDETTE: Then who was it?
I don't know.
Because you shot him.
Why do you keep saying that?
Because the truth rolls
comfortably off my tongue.
Heard you were bragging
about the new gun you bought.
Telling kids
you pack it for protection.
Man, that was just me talking.
I didn't even bring it to school.
DUTCH: You snuck it past
the lame metal detectors,
you pulled it out during the riot
and you shot him in the back.
Man, it wasn't me.
DUTCH: Fine. Call juvie.
Let him spend a few weeks
in lockup, get a taste of his future.
Maybe a little truth will
seem like a good idea then.
It's Every-Day.
What's every day,
that you shoot somebody?
Evan Dayne.
Call him Every-Day.
Bangs with the Hope Hill Set.
He can't know it was me
that said anything.
MAN 1: Whoa, whoa, hey.
MAN 2: Hey, get off, man.
[LORENZO GRUNTING]
[LORENZO CHOKING]
VIC:
Dutch!
CALIDA: Stop it, you're killing him!
Dutch! That's it, it's over. That's it.
DUTCH: Are you okay?
Fine. I'm fine.
[DUTCH PANTING]
Shit.
Goddamn it,
this is a new suit.
Have a wonderful day. Bye.
Bye, guys. Love you.
Bye.
KAVANAUGH:
Hey.
Jon. I'm new here.
At the school.
Corrine. Which one's yours?
He's inside already.
Orientation.
Gum?
Oh, no thanks.
Come on, it's a fresh pack.
Here you go.
Sure, thanks.
That's your boy?
Yeah, yeah. And our daughter.
Two. Wow, that must be tough.
And I'm struggling
with just one autistic child.
It's the challenges
of single parenthood.
Yeah. Yeah, doing it alone is hard.
You too?
Yeah.
The daddy's not in the picture?
Uh, he does what he can.
My ex, she doesn't even
acknowledge our child.
I'm sorry.
Sometimes I wonder
why I even married her.
You ever feel like that?
I'll see you around.
Could I call you sometime?
Sorry, it's just that they told me
that I should try to get to know
some of the other parents...
and I'm out of my depth.
I could talk to you or I could talk
to your husband. Either one, if...
You know, whatever you...
Okay, last name's Mackey.
And you can call me
about the kids or the school.
My husband's not
gonna be much help.
Thanks.
Thank you.
SHANE:
Hi.
Hey, Julien. You gotta give me
the scoop on Danny's baby.
What do you mean?
The father.
The pool's up to 1100 bucks.
Of course, there's a,
you know, broker's fee for
any insider trading, but...
She won't say. Why don't
you guys just leave her alone?
Oh, come on, man.
Help a brother out.
TINA: Who would you take?
I always take Shane in these things.
Not me, brother. I'm married.
That means no sticking, just licking.
Charming.
Besides, I like my women tiny.
So your dick fits better?
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Easy. Easy.
TINA:
Put me down for 20
on the sperm bank.
I gotta get this organised.
Tina, 20, turkey baster.
CALIDA:
You okay, mijo?
See you later, darling.
SHANE:
I got it.
Turn around.
Are you on drugs?
I didn't raise an animal.
You hear me?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Who set the kill clock?
Don't you touch him!
LEM: Vic. Vic.
The little kid who got
run over last week was
a nephew of a Los Mag capo.
Doing 20 in Chino. Los Mags
are reaching out to settle the beef.
SHANE: Chino's where
Lorenzo's pop is stretching.
'Hood's been under the microscope.
Maybe the Mags used a proxy.
Make sure no blood
blows back in their direction.
I got a few juvie graduates
in Chino. I'll find out what
pop's story is. Come on.
Shane, give me a minute.
Yeah.
Where's Sebastio?
My mom's watching him.
Here.
It's okay, I'm on the clock.
I know how much gas costs.
Come on.
More and more.
Thanks.
Any thoughts about
hanging this up?
Still thinking.
A Los Mag captain set
the kill clock from Chino.
Same cellblock where
your father got caught
helping the black brethren
distribute smokes.
Pissed off the inked vatos.
SHANE:
That asshole can't even
play by the rules in prison.
My guess is Lorenzo Senior
offered you up as a junior assassin.
Settle both scores.
CALIDA: Is that true?
Does that bastard have
something to do with this?
Answer me.
Mommy can't help you.
You grow a dick. Tell the truth.
It's about justice.
Thought I could help the cause.
It's Mexi-pride.
Jesus, mother of God.
I didn't wanna hurt no one.
Dad started crying.
Said if I didn't kill
two dark by 10 tonight
Los Mags were gonna waste him.
It was him you were
on the phone with last night?
I gotta finish it or he dies.
Why? Why would you
do this for him?
Not for him. I hate him.
But if I don't do it, it falls on Cisco.
He was on the other line.
Dad told him too.
He gave us the combination
for the guns.
Guns? There's more than one?
CALIDA:
Oh, no.
Cisco still thinks my dad's
like a real dad. He'll do it.
He'll throw it all away
for that asshole.
VIC: Paula. Where's the kid
that was sitting in that chair?
CALIDA: Cisco!
What kid?
Shit.
RONNIE:
Description of the shooter
sounds like our lost brother.
Go.
Hey.
Whoa, whoa.
What happened here?
Little spic came in, shot him cold.
I mean, Tommy never
saw it coming.
He's gone.
Which way did he go?
BARBER: Out the back.
Come on, Shane.
You know, that crazy kid stopped
to take a goddamn Polaroid.
I stuck him with my best pair though.
LEM: Stuck him with your scissors?
[SIREN WAILS]
LEM:
Shit, they're here.
Let's go. Go, go, go.
Hey.
VIC:
Yeah.
Easy.
Hey.
Cisco? Put the gun down, kid!
Put it down right now
or I'll shoot!
I gotta get this picture to my dad.
Hold it.
All right.
We'll talk about the picture
after you put the gun down.
You'll take it to him?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll take it to him myself.
That's it. Where we can see it.
Good boy. Go.
All right,
give me the camera.
Give it here.
CISCO: This really hurts.
No! Shit.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right, hold on it.
Put pressure on it.
Go get those paramedics!
Goddamn it.
Oh, Christ Almighty, here we go.
Got it?
Watch out. Go, go, go.
All right.
Hurry up, Ronnie!
CLAUDETTE:
What happened in the cafeteria, Evan?
Look, I heard those
shots and hit the floor
like everybody else.
Anyone else see that?
Don't know. We all ran for the door.
DUTCH:
We got three people who saw
you pull the trigger, Every-Day.
Well, then you got three liars.
Three against one.
Those aren't very good odds for you.
I'm used to it.
We're gonna need
a little more than bad attitude
to be convinced
of your innocence.
You best tell pale boy here
to get out of my goddamn face.
Look, I ain't been playing
trouble for a while now.
Y'all can ask around.
We did. That's how
we got the statements.
From who?
Some chilli-shitters?
They're killing us niggas.
You don't think they wanna
put another one away?
That sounds like motive to me.
Lazy-ass cop.
Hey, I bust my ass on this job.
Well, your busted ass suck at it.
Hey, book him for murder.
This is wrong, man.
I ain't kill nobody, man.
Come on. It's been a long, shitty day.
CLAUDETTE:
Every day.
EMT says
he's gonna make it.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Yeah, I wouldn't be too thankful.
He just killed an innocent man.
I wanted to kill their
father a dozen times
and I never did
for their sake.
Los Mags should slit
his throat from ear to ear.
PARAMEDIC:
Ma'am.
She's right, you know.
That prick should die.
He will.
Just not today.
Look, this isn't the way
I wanted to do it,
but at least it'll end
this round of blood.
Talk to your guy in Chino.
Find out where those pictures go.
You got two hours to get them there.
LEM: All right.
VIC: Stop the clock.
I'll get it done.
Got a call from
a teacher at Wellman.
He just realised his gun was stolen
out of a locked desk drawer.
Evan Dayne in any of his classes?
Homeroom and science.
Now we know where Every-Day
got his weapon.
Whatever happened to rapping
a kid's knuckles with a ruler?
Uh, good job. Thanks.
It's, uh... It's Vic's kid.
I got 50 bucks in the pool.
That's funny,
because I got 50 on you.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I tried calling.
No one answered.
Something wrong?
I thought maybe I'd try to catch
them before they went to bed.
Say good night.
It's not your usual night.
I know.
Vic, you can't just show up.
I mean, they have a schedule.
Mine's always changing.
You want me to ever see
them or not?
These aren't my rules.
It's the custody agreement.
Oh, Jesus.
Is that blood?
Shit, I thought I got it all.
Twelve-year-old.
It's been a shit day. I just
wanted to kiss them good night.
Wash it off before you see them.
Hey.
Daddy.
My baby.
Heard you already have
a suspect in custody on
that cafeteria shooting.
Most cases are solved
within the first 24 hours.
After that, the odds of solving them
decrease exponentially.
I'm gonna learn
a lot from you, aren't I?
Could be.
Have a good night, detective.
You too.
Relax.
What?
Gun-residue test came back
on Evan Dayne. Negative.
We're sure
about this guy?
He knows when
to wash his hands.
So do I.
We're looking
for a brother.
Blond afro, tall,
hands might be cut up.
Ain't seen nobody like that.
Yeah, we know he hangs here.
And we know
this shop's been hit
nine times last year.
RONNIE:
Twice last month.
And it took you guys three hours
to show up last time I called.
Well, next time...
you call us. We're your new 911.
We'll make sure that people
don't mess with your shop.
We steer that kind of business
someplace else.
Talking straight about
keeping my place safe?
I got a badge, don't I?
Darius McBride. D-Mac.
Came in this morning.
Bought some Band-Aids and beer.
Lives over in Belmont Green.
VIC: Consider your
protection clock running.
Hey.
Anybody,
any colour, hits this store,
I will beat them half-dead
and plant enough shit on them
to send them away for a 10 stretch.
Spread the word.
Screw.
Guys like the girly girls.
Who says you gotta look
like Janet Reno, right?
You replaced your breastplate
with lipstick and tampons?
Well, a place to put
your shit, you know?
Yeah, well,
that's a reprimand,
as well as probably
getting you killed.
Lose those hoop earrings
before someone rips your ears off.
Did I do something
to piss you off?
You know what, you have a job,
sweetheart, all right?
Take it seriously.
You're a cop, not a Kelly Girl.
Okay, look.
I appreciate you
being straight with me.
It's just hard to catch a break
with these guys.
Treat you like you don't belong.
Yeah, I know.
They talk a blue streak
about equality, but the truth is
the shitheads just think
we're a bunch of little girls
playing cops.
So we have to prove them wrong.
Yeah, we do.
Thanks. It's good
to have some backup.
Here you go.
JULIEN:
You still here?
I thought you were supposed
to be more 9 to 5.
Thanks. Tell that to Billings.
You pretty much
run the place.
Yeah, I'd rather be running
the streets with you.
Hell of a lot easier.
Don't be so sure.
I got my work cut out for me.
Tina, she ain't no Danny Sofer.
Well, who is?
Anyway, I wouldn't
write her off too soon.
She's raw,
but she's got potential.
Yeah. Guess I made a few
mistakes out there myself.
DANNY:
Yeah, you still do.
You're supposed to have
your DFARs on my desk
before the end of the shift.
I'll get Tina right on it.
See? I did train you right.
Yep.
[COLDPLAY'S "TIL KINGDOM COME"
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[KNOCKING]
Damn it.
Curtis Lemansky.
Yeah.
What's up?
Jon Kavanaugh, IAD.
I need you
to come with us.
What about?
Get dressed. Guys?
Please.
I'll get dressed. Leave me alone.
Walter.
Yeah.
[COLDPLAY'S
"TIL KINGDOM COME" PLAYING]
Bye.
Hey.
SHANE:
Come here.
Enough.
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
KAVANAUGH:
About six months ago,
we found this kilo of pure heroin
in the glove compartment of your car.
We seized the drugs,
documented it on camera
and replaced it with dummy tar.
But...
you never logged it
into evidence.
So you've been watching me
for six months?
I don't want you to
spin a story. Really.
I just want you to think
about what this means.
Felony theft under
colour of authority.
Intent to distribute.
You're a smart guy.
You've been on the other side
of this table a long time.
You know how that will play out.
Does that seem fair to you? Hm?
Look, if you were arresting me,
we'd be at Police 1,
and you'd be parading me
past OIG.
What do you want?
I want us both to do
the right thing, Curtis.
Really?
Why is it that the guy
with the conscience
always has to get caught
holding the bag?
And we never really
want that guy, do we?
We want the guy that
put him in the motion.
The one who is
really dangerous.
Who do you
think I want, Curtis?
Come on, man. Come on.
Who do you think I want?
[###]