NARRATOR:
Previously on The Shield.
It's Terry Crowley, one of my guys
killed by a drug dealer
couple years ago.
That is one version.
If you could, uh, have your clients
walk me through the house
where Terry Crowley was killed,
that would be great.
VIC:
Hey!
KAVANAUGH:
Terry was working for Justice,
investigating allegations
of a relationship between
drug dealers and your clients.
Officer Danielle Sofer
who works here
is filing paperwork
relating to a sexual relationship
with Vic over the last couple of years.
Officer Sofer is now pregnant.
KAVANAUGH:
Need to know everything you know
about these men.
The price is simple: I help you
put away these fine young men,
you make sure you put them away
right here.
So you can kill them, huh?
I made a life for myself.
Have you been missing me?
Ex-wife.
Ask me to come back again.
You're gonna remanded
to psychiatric care.
I am your goddamn wife.
VIC:
At least we found his weak spot.
SADIE: Come on, Jon.
Shit. Go.
SADIE: Don't leave me!
Hey!
You're under arrest for possession
of heroin with intent to distribute.
I need you to tell me
everything that you know,
about Mackey and the Strike Team.
No deal.
You got your deal.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
GU ARD:
Okay, Mills, Brown,
move up to the day room.
INMATE:
What you looking at, you punk ass?
[DOOR BANGS]
GU ARD:
Fernandez, Wilson.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INMATE LAUGHING]
[INMATES CHATTERING LOUDLY]
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
[DOOR OPENS, KEYS JINGLING]
DEPUTY:
Ten minutes.
[DOOR BANGS]
How's it going?
I'm all right.
What's... What's going on?
We got a plan?
Yeah, get you the hell out of here.
Did Mara back off putting up
her and Shane's house as collateral?
We're still working on bail.
Right.
But Kavanaugh had the IRS
freeze our assets, all of us.
So I'm stuck.
There's no way you're coming up
with $100,000.
I've already filed a motion
to have your bail reduced.
Okay. How long you think
I need to hold out for?
You listen to me.
Twenty-four hours, you're out of here.
Tomorrow night,
you sleep in your own bed.
You just gotta stay good for 24.
All right.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[RADIO CHIRPS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER POLICE RADIO]
Take the back.
MAN:
Don't move. Stay still. Don't move...
[MEN GRUNTING,
TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
TINA: Police. Drop your weapon.
It's okay. Don't shoot.
Drop your weapon!
Don't shoot! I'm a cop!
Goddamn it, drop your weapon now!
[MEN GRUNTING]
Stop. Stop right there.
[BUMPS, CAR ALARM BLARING]
Get on your knees. Get on your knees.
Nice work.
Get on your knees.
Rookie, right?
JULIEN: Tina.
Man, tell your partner not to shoot.
He's undercover.
I didn't know.
He didn't identify himself.
His right arm,
it's the colour of the day.
Which makes you
ditz of the month, honey.
Terry went down here?
Uh, yeah, about where the chair is.
Uh, Two-Time came out blasting.
Terry went down.
We fired back.
Ballistics gave Vic the kill shot.
Well, I must've been a close second.
Off my game, I guess.
Were you off your game
when Angie Stubbs got murdered?
Your bullet got the kill shot
on that one.
Gun wasn't in my hand.
Right, Angie's death
got pinned on Antwon Mitchell...
Nothing got pinned. He killed her.
Right. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Uh...
You just watched.
Mitchell ever give you any money?
Put you on his payroll?
He was undercover.
It's all documented.
Not all of it.
The drug payoffs.
The One-Niner pimps
you were shaking down.
Not the nights and days
that you spent being
Antwon Mitchell's bought bitch.
You think that
I don't know about that?
We are here to talk
about Terry Crowley.
BECCA:
Otherwise, we'll be going.
Sure.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
MAN: All right.
Stay right here.
Just relax, asshole.
I'm just copping a squat, all right?
KAVANAUGH:
Detective Mackey.
Come on up.
KAVANAUGH:
According to you,
Terry entered the room
before it was cleared.
I failed to clear the bathroom.
I looked, I thought it was clear,
but Two-Time must have
been behind the wall.
There were noises, uh, movements
from the other side of the house.
Shane and I started that way.
I moved on before I should have.
I'm gonna have to live with that.
Soon as I turned around,
about two seconds,
heard the shot, Terry fell.
We returned fire.
Now, we can run this
six more times,
Two-Time's always
gonna have the gun.
Terry's always gonna be dead.
DREW:
Right.
You got some kind of a problem?
I thought you'd remember Drew
from Terry's funeral, but no matter.
Drew Crowley, Vic Mackey.
Doesn't remember because he never
looked at me or my family that day.
Formerly Officer Drew Crowley,
San Diego.
Left the force
after his brother was murdered.
Mothers, you know.
DREW:
I just wanted to see your face
here where my brother died.
Of all the underhanded bullshit...
I want to know the truth.
What happened?
DREW:
Tell the truth, son of a bitch!
Get him out, right now!
KAVANAUGH: Hey. No, no.
If you killed him, God will know.
My brother was a good man.
I'm sorry what happened to him.
It went down just like I said.
BECCA:
Come on, Vic. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
If you're lying,
God will have your soul
and I will give it to him personally.
[###]
All our stories matched up.
Now he'll give up this bullshit case.
Move on to shit we actually did.
Bullshit. This was rubbing our faces
in the Intel he's already uncovered.
Like what?
He knew all about the pimps
me and Army were bleeding.
VIC: Where the hell did he get that?
I don't know, Antwon maybe?
No. He'd never give up anything
for nothing.
With his stretch for double capital,
there's nothing to give him.
RONNIE: Army?
SHANE: No.
SHANE: Halpern?
Maybe Rawling.
No. She didn't know
these kind of details.
Could be some One-Niner.
Could be Lem.
Stop that shit.
I'm not saying it was Lem.
I'm just... I thought
we were just listing possibilities.
VIC:
Well, don't.
We gotta stay focussed
on getting Lem out of there.
This is the last night
he spends in County.
Well, we got about 700 in cash
and three frozen bank accounts.
VIC: That's it?
Yeah. Lem's kin is trailer park trash.
Couldn't spare the money.
Big Powerball this weekend.
So we gotta find 100 grand
on the street.
Just lying around?
With Kavanaugh watching us?
He's fixated on the past,
not the present.
RONNIE:
You're wrong.
We'll end up keeping Lem company.
We're not leaving him in there.
I promised him.
Yeah.
JULIEN:
Construction worker called it in.
Whoa, talk about a dump job.
Okay, uh, maybe the murder
occurs around here,
probably in the heat of the moment.
Killer panics, sees this as the best
possible way to dispose of a body.
Hopes it gets carted away
before it's discovered.
What do you think?
Sounds good to me.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER POLICE RADIO]
Partner coming back anytime soon?
Couple of weeks.
Let's go.
[KNOCKING]
[EXHALES]
Hey, kids ready? I might
have to drop them back off early.
My money's been frozen.
What?
Checking, savings, debit cards.
I can't even buy groceries.
Shit, I'm sorry. I just need some time...
I can't.
I can't be around you,
and neither can the kids.
It's not me, it's the lawyer.
I was the one who told you
to hire the asshole, remember?
To protect you.
In order to do that I have to create a
pattern of distancing myself from you.
Listen, it's only temporary,
until you sort these legal matters out.
Hey, sweetheart. Hi.
[WHISPERS]
You should go. Please.
Mom's been crying all morning.
At least let me give you some cash...
No, Vic. Vic, I can't. I'm sorry.
Look, we're gonna sort this all out.
We'Il... We'll figure
something else out, okay?
If you need me, I'll be at work.
Hey, captain?
Captain, this is Detective Hoffman.
He had an incident
with Officer Hanlon last night.
You got an office where I can bitch,
in private?
I like hanging with my cops.
We can talk here.
Tina failed to identify Hoffman
as undercover officer.
HOFFMAN:
First, she nearly blew my head off,
then she allowed the perp to escape.
He was clearly wearing
the colour of the day.
Julien put a report on your desk
this morning.
We'll take all necessary steps
to ensure this doesn't happen again.
You know, I live with lowlifes
smelling like piss and shit
so guys like you
don't have to get your suits dirty.
I get enough guns to my head
without Barbie adding to the action.
You expect me to fire her?
Look, I've tried with Tina, sir.
So has Julien.
She doesn't get it, she never will.
Till it's too late.
Look, she's a woman, Latina besides.
There's like three hoops
to jump through to can her.
Well, you know what,
she's gonna land herself
or someone else in a body bag.
Look, your girl saw this colour,
not the colour on my arm.
You handle it any way you like.
Being captain's about tough choices.
I'll take care of it.
VIC: Hey, man.
Hey, how you doing, Vic?
Any asshole sightings today?
Uh, not yet.
Guess even rats have to sleep.
Heh.
Isn't it your day off?
Uh... My kids got sick. Uh...
Wanted to see if you had anything
juicy I could sink my teeth into.
Uh... There's, um,
some new chicken pot pies
in the Quick-Mealer.
What about that loan shark
over on Clinton?
Newman and his team
still set up on him?
Well, he cut a deal. We got two to six.
Shit.
Vic, there's a girl
waiting to meet you
or one of your guys.
All right, give me a second.
What about that dealer on The Decks?
Uh... What's-his-name, Felonious T?
No. Intel says he's hanging up
his dealer hat.
Been busy making a documentary
of the streets or some shit. Heh.
Can't wait to see that.
Yeah.
You looking for me?
You Mackey? Antwon Mitchell
needs a sit-down with you.
That dickhead sent you?
Gave me a message.
Stand up and put your hands
against the wall.
Psh. Go to hell.
Your incarcerated old man
wants to fly a kite? Let her rip.
Told me to ask you
what you're willing to put on the table.
For what?
To keep your boy, Curtis, alive.
Stop playing games
or you're gonna get matching
his and hers cells.
Your cop buddy's
headed for Lompoc.
Gonna be in the same cell block
with Antwon real soon.
Horseshit.
Ask the other cop, the big brother.
He made the deal with Antwon.
Kavanaugh?
Even a douchebag like Kavanaugh
wouldn't jump into bed
with Antwon Mitchell.
God knows what kind of diseases
you'd get.
Ask him, but do it quick.
Antwon don't like waiting.
Said make sure you know
offer of protection
ain't out there for long.
You tell Antwon I'll put a bullet
in that fat head of his myself
before I'll let him kill another cop.
Tell him yourself.
Sounds like it's a matter of time
before you follow your boy inside.
Get the hell out of here.
Get your hands off.
You just giving Antwon more reason
to make it worse on your boy.
[CHUCKLES]
Open it.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
CLAUDETTE: What do you got?
Nothing. Huh?
Your face is red.
[CHUCKLES]
You're back.
And what a pleasure it is.
Your doc said another two weeks.
I can recuperate better at my desk
than I can in my bed.
What are we working?
Your knee?
Knee, ankle, the whole shebang.
I fell pretty hard.
What do we got?
Uh... Dump job.
Artemis Cooke, 43, black male.
Shot in the face,
stuffed in a dumpster.
And no next of kin?
Uh... Mother. I've got her upstairs.
Come on, pick up the pace.
Artemis was always hard-working.
All sorts of jobs.
Where was he working now?
Ambulance company.
Drove body organs to Canada.
Company paid him
to paint his van up.
Very professional.
Uh..."Body organs"?
You know, they take them
just before you die,
give them to people
who need them.
You mean donor organs?
I guess they have a big need up north.
You can ask his buddy, DeKnight.
He helps him load up sometimes.
Your attempts to drive
a wedge between me and my guys
include planning a murder?
Just looking for my salad.
Somebody took it.
Why don't you just find out
who did it,
send him to prison
to be killed by Antwon Mitchell.
What's that make you,
serving Lem up to some cop killer?
Just like you served Terry up?
Terry was a snake, just like you.
Oh. So you did know that Terry
was working for Justice...
You told me about it yourself.
I'm done with crying about
him getting killed by Two-Time,
no matter how many weepy relatives
you bring by.
[SIGHS]
Had a conversation
with Antwon Mitchell.
Very illuminating, especially
as it relates to Shane Vendrell.
Is your neck a little sore?
Excuse me?
From the noose tightening?
You send Lem to Lompoc,
it's you that's the real murderer.
The four of you come completely
clean, I will let you pick the prison.
No deal?
Well, I guess you're not as concerned
for his safety as you claim.
Anyway, there's nothing on paper
as to where Lemansky will end up,
but I'm sure
I'll have a recommendation
when the time comes.
That being said,
any correctional facility
is dangerous for a cop.
Best thing to do is play by the rules
and stay out of jail.
Streets can be real dangerous too.
Are we levelling threats, detective?
Just making random observations.
Same as you.
Here's another one:
You're bluffing, trying to split us up.
You're Mr. Straight-Arrow, right?
Couldn't even cut your poor,
sick-in-the-head, defenceless ex-wife
a break from the rules, could you?
You don't have the stomach
to serve Lem up to Antwon.
I didn't used to.
Excuse me.
MAN:
I worked with Artemis at the plant.
That donor thing was something
he got on his own.
Don't know much about it.
Seems weird.
Usually organs
have to be transplanted
within hours.
It takes a hell of a lot longer
to drive to Canada.
Wouldn't you think they'd fly them?
Maybe it's low-priority organs,
like fingers or tongues.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here.
Artemis was not running
fingers and tongues,
back and forth
to Vancouver, was he?
Whatever he was running
got him shot in the face.
Shit, he's dead?
Found him in a dumpster
like common trash.
[SIGHS]
He was running some cush,
some sort of super-weed.
You get near this shit, the contact
high'd knock you out for a week.
He made 8 grand a run.
CLAUDETTE:
That makes him invaluable.
He have any beefs with anyone?
Hell, no. Everybody loved Art.
He drove that van into L.A.
full of the good tree.
It was like Santa Claus
was coming to town.
Uh, we got a guy upstairs,
needs a ride home.
No problem. She okay?
DUTCH:
Says she's 100 percent.
I'm not going to argue the point.
When I get my six weeks,
I'm gonna forget this place exists.
DUTCH:
Yeah.
Hi there.
Oh, let me guess. You're here
to give me shit about something.
Ooh... What? No. I, uh...
These... These have been
floating around.
I thought you should know.
Jesus Christ.
The door was locked. How'd they...?
I barely glanced.
Just... Just enough to identify you.
Apparently some asshole
put a camera in the locker room.
So every jerk-off in the Barn's
been staring at my tits?
Hey, you can't let their
high-school mentality get to you.
They'll get their kicks,
then move on to somebody else.
Shit.
I think I'm gonna get fired.
I screwed up at a call last night,
that's why I'm stuck in here.
We all make mistakes.
Even I've been known
to make one or two. Occasionally.
I wore those brown panties two days
ago, the red ones the day before.
That's something to go on.
I'm gonna find out who took these.
I'm gonna see
that every picture's destroyed.
Okay.
Thanks for being such a gentleman.
We're not all Neanderthals.
[CHUCKLES]
I should probably keep those,
stick them in a drawer. For evidence.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, we don't have anything planned.
I'm resigning my position
as a reserve officer.
So now you no longer
can compel my cooperation
by threatening to take my badge.
It's all yours.
That's not necessary.
You should also know that
as vice-chair of the Police Committee,
I'm launching an investigation
into your investigation.
Really?
Yeah.
And why after tens of thousands
of dollars, you have nothing more now
than you had seven months ago.
I got Lemansky in custody...
Yeah. On seven-month-old charges.
I got 65,000 unaccounted-for dollars,
courtesy of Mackey's wife.
I got Mackey's assets frozen,
along with every member
of the Strike Team.
And I've got Antwon Mitchell talking.
You're getting Mackey panicked,
hoping he'll overplay his hand.
Something I hope
you could help me with.
Nicely done, by the way,
stomping in here like that.
That was good. I like that.
You're trying to get Mackey
running to me?
What, the enemy of my enemy
is my friend?
Well, forget it. It won't happen.
He and his boys,
they were in business
with Antwon Mitchell.
These guys, they're desperate.
They're gonna need
a friend in a high place, like you.
All right,
I'll hold off on my investigation.
For now.
Walk out angry.
Mackey's watching.
Vic, you got a sec?
Barely.
You ever hear of, uh,
a Canadian super-pot?
What, you looking to buy
a dime bag?
Dump job this morning was driving
vans of the stuff down
from Vancouver.
You know any locals
plugged into that route?
Probably. You...
You guys have the van?
Still looking, uh... Might be a robbery.
l-I'm just looking for a few names.
[DOOR SLAMS]
Well, seeing as, uh,
you and Claudette's Wonder Twin
powers aren't fully activated yet,
I'Il... I'll do you a favour,
pick up the slack on this one.
Okay. Thanks.
All right, uh,
let me shake the One-Niner tree.
See if any
five-pointed leaves fall out.
That prick cut a deal
with Antwon Mitchell.
Wants to send Lem to Lompoc
if he gets a conviction.
What?
That's why Kavanaugh knows
so much about you and Antwon.
He's hoping the threat'll
get Lem talking.
That's not exactly
playing by the rules.
Means we don't, either.
If he puts Lem in with Mitchell...
I know.
Yo, coz.
Shit. Let's go.
This five-0 is Hitler.
You miss us?
Not especially.
Hear Antwon's cutting deals
over in Lompoc,
shoring up the power structure.
If it don't involve the street,
it don't involve me.
Maybe you're part
of Antwon's restructuring.
Nice try,
but me and the big guy's tight.
You really expect me to believe
he's letting you call
the shots out here?
Well, he can't do it.
Somebody's got to, right?
Antwon know you're recruiting
out of middle school?
Lots of the old guard hung it up after
Antwon left. This is the new regime.
Any of your students running chronic
down from Canada?
Let's take a ride.
What, shooting me wasn't enough?
Tell me what we wanna know
or we're gonna be back
in your life again full-time.
All right.
Dude with a fancy French name,
runs most of the bud to the crews.
Best shit in years.
What's Frenchie's name?
Dijon.
Get back to class.
VIC:
Porkchop's stuck on street duty.
Knows where the pot comes from
but Antwon's cut him out
of the inner circle,
the decision-making.
You thinking regime change?
Well, something to keep an eye on.
Dude, sweet pictures.
What pictures?
It's okay. I'm cool.
You think, uh, Tina's panties
are regulation?
Just wish we could've
seen her badge.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Hey, between you and me,
how'd you pull it off?
Shit, I'm no perv.
Found them on Billings' desk.
Anyone make copies?
[WATER RUNNING]
What do you think?
Anyway, thanks for sharing them
with me.
Way you stare at that chick,
would've been cruel not to.
[TOILET FLUSHING]
You had the IRS freeze my money.
I'm sorry, that isn't...
Sorry?
You did it.
Yes.
I did everything that you asked.
l... I told you about the money.
Now I can't feed my children.
You told me about $65,000.
Now I'm hearing there may be more.
A lot more.
Please. You think I would default
on my children's tuitions
if there was more?
I hate that this is hurting you.
But I'm building walls around Vic.
To stop him from slithering away.
And you?
You're one of those walls.
I'm not a wall, I'm a mother.
And... And I'm disconnecting Vic
from my life and from the kids.
So leave me out of this.
Are you aware that I arrested
Curtis Lemansky two days ago?
He's in County,
waiting for Vic and his friends
to bail him out.
If they don't have the money,
they can't do it.
And every minute
that Lem spends inside,
I'm just a minute closer
to getting at the truth.
That has nothing to do with me.
My advice is to go to Vic yourself,
ask him to confess.
You want your life back,
ask him, not me.
What did I do to deserve this?
You married the wrong man, Corrine.
Now, I'm not doing this
because that cowboy called me out.
JULIEN: Of course not.
I got two of my finest officers
telling me that Tina's got to go.
Look, every day that she is out there,
she's putting people at risk.
She's just so damn popular.
I can call her PBA rep.
Okay. Get him down here ASAP.
Julien,
I want a full report of her conduct.
You're going on the record.
Got it.
Thanks, guys.
What's up?
Shit, where'd you get these?
They're circulating.
They were on my desk.
Is nothing sacred?
You're asking me?
Come here.
I put a nanny cam in the locker room.
People have been ripping off
the vending machines.
I was just trying to catch
whoever's doing it.
You could've put a camera
in the hallway. Over the machines.
Well, not where it could be hidden.
And I think whoever's stealing
this grub is stashing it
in their locker.
I pulled these photos and some others
so that they wouldn't
get into the wrong hands.
You know this only happened
because I don't have
a goddamned private office anymore.
Do you have any idea
what kind of storm you're looking at
when she finds out
you're behind these photos?
She saw them?
You told her?
She had a right to know.
I just promised to wash her out.
[SIGHS]
You think he's gonna
take care of that baby?
He's not.
I've no idea what you're talking about.
You think he's gonna be a father?
Who the father is
is not your business.
Really? It's not my business
that my kids are gonna get
a new brother or sister?
I'm at work right now, okay?
This isn't the place.
Right. Come find me later.
You managed to find someone
to screw at work.
Why not talk about it here too?
I'm walking away from you right now
because you're obviously
not being rational.
Really? Were you being rational
when you slept with a married man?
He made that vow, not me.
Which makes him a cheat.
That makes you a whore
and the baby you're both having
a bastard.
[DOOR SLAMS]
You Dijon?
I ain't do nothing
if that's what you mean.
Nice threads.
We hear you got
the best BC bud in Farmington.
Hey. What?
White guys can't get the good stuff?
RONNIE:
Or you only sell to bangers?
That's discrimination.
I got nothing, look around.
Okay.
VIC:
You took a hit today.
SHANE:
We're offering you a chance
to get it back.
Whoa. Run that by me again.
Your Canadian organ express
got taken down.
VIC:
Your driver got killed,
supply ripped off.
We can get it back for you,
for a finder's fee.
Why?
Don't worry about that.
Hundred grand, no questions asked.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Only a matter of time
before the detectives
on the murder case
follow the phone records back to you
and your monthly pot runs.
But you work with us, we see to it
that the trail ends with Artemis.
And I keep the rest?
It's a hell of a lot better than nothing,
isn't it?
All right.
Only thing is, it wasn't my shipment
that got jacked, it was my cash.
Artemis was on his way
up to Canada.
How much did you lose?
A quarter of a million. Get it back.
I'll cut you the 100 gees then.
Uh-uh. Don't trust you.
We'll take our fee up front.
You crazy? I'm out of pocket on this.
Everything I got
was invested in that run.
Jesus Christ, man.
This is just a waste of time.
VIC:
No, it's not.
A deal's a deal.
Put together a list of every customer,
anybody who would have known
about Artemis' run.
Dirty yourself up. We need you
to play the ignorant friend
for some colleagues of ours.
VIC:
Yo, Asher.
Upstairs. America's favourite couple
wants to have a little chat with him.
ASHER:
Sure thing.
VIC:
I'm telling you, my Intel's good.
Artemis was flying solo.
His buddy's got some details
about his criminal dealings.
Well, let's see
what's up between these two.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
I'll be right up.
Lem?
I finally got some phone time, man.
So, uh, what's going on?
Am I getting out of here today?
l-I'm working on it. Hang on.
[DIALS]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
VIC: Hey, it's Vic.
I'm gonna put you on with Lem.
Hold on.
You guys both on?
I'm here.
LEM: Yeah.
VIC: All right, Lem,
you're talking
to your lawyer Becca Doyle,
in case there are other ears
on this call.
Whoa, you can't use me as cover
for anything illegal.
What I'm about to tell Lem,
you need to hear too.
What is it?
VIC: All right, the good news first.
We've got a lead on some bail for you.
LEM: How?
Calling in a few favours.
All right. Look, man,
I know you got my back.
LEM:
What's the bad news?
Kavanaugh has been sitting down
with Antwon Mitchell.
He made some sort of deal
to send you to Lompoc
in case there's a conviction.
No goddamn way.
BECCA: That's insane.
He doesn't make those calls.
It's never gonna get that far.
We'll gonna get you out of there,
then we'll get you out
from under this prick.
Do you know this?
Kavanaugh said those words?
He'd never admit it but it's real.
All it means is Kavanaugh knows
he's got jack shit on us
and he's getting desperate.
All right, I hear you. I hear you.
Vic, you coming or not?
VIC: Yeah, hang on.
All right. Listen, I gotta go. Stay safe.
Yeah.
VIC: Okay.
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
BILLINGS:
Dutchman.
Uh, I'm in the middle of something.
I got it, Dutchboy.
You know I was on the up and up
taking those photos.
Tell the chief.
If Tina makes a stink about this,
maybe she'll get a huge pile of cash,
but her career will be kaput.
You know how these things wash out.
Uh, I don't know
what you expect me to do.
I have a plan.
This thing goes away,
everybody wins.
Including you.
No, thanks.
You can either be a hero
in Tina's eyes,
or you can watch her,
and her red bra and panties
march out that Barn door forever.
He's full of it.
He probably is a member
of the ring but why kill your driver?
I really don't think he was involved.
If this guy's funding Artemis' run,
he'll never cooperate.
He'll recover the money himself.
Or Artemis is working solo.
Your Intel hasn't been
what it used to be.
Fine. I'll see what else
I can squeeze out of him.
What did I miss?
What the hell
did you bring him into this for?
I thought we could use a little muscle.
Yeah. Brains over brawn, Dutch.
How many times I gotta tell you that?
Move it, asshole.
Don't need to keep selling it so hard,
do you?
Your list of customers
got us nowhere.
The only thing those bangers want
more than ass and cash
is some of your top-grade
Canadian bud.
They know a good thing
when they smoke it.
If I don't find
who knocked over your van,
you'll be hanging up
a "Closed" sign.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Who else besides your customers
knows about the runs?
Just my wife
and my dumb-ass stepson.
How old is he?
He's 20.
What's his name?
Jaden Reid.
He drove the route for me
a couple of times until I noticed
the load kept coming back light.
Punk don't know
the meaning of "high enough."
Where is he now?
Well, who knows.
He gonna send his momma
to an early grave.
Does your wife know where
Jaden is?
She got no clue.
You never know.
Blood is thicker than bong water.
Kid's name is Jaden Reid.
Think he's our shooter.
Let's pay Jaden a little visit.
First we gotta find him.
Kid's a burnout.
Now he's got enough cash
to keep him stoned for a long time.
Enough cash for us to spring Lem.
So where do we start?
Our unis found the abandoned van
in a parking lot in Silver Lake.
Lots of blood, no cash.
If I had a bag full of money,
I wouldn't wanna walk too far with it.
Check out the local weed dealers.
He had the cash, he'd want to score.
SHANE:
What about Claudette?
We're a step ahead of her
and she seems two steps slow.
Let's find this kid before
she figures out anything else.
SHANE:
Okay.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Yeah.
Got it.
Got a hit on the fingerprints
in the van. Belongs to a Jaden Reid.
Address?
Last known, his mother's.
Tasha Reynolds.
VIC: What's up?
Got a suspect. Jaden Reid.
According to the file,
he's your friend Dijon's stepson.
Nice work.
Gonna check out an address.
Why... Why don't we let
some unis pick him up?
They can join us.
VIC: Dutch is right.
Uh, why don't you let me and my guys
handle sweep-up duty.
You can join us too if you want.
CLAUDETTE:
Mrs. Reynolds, when was the last time
you saw Jaden?
Couple months.
Look, he's a good kid.
There's no way he'd be involved
in anything like this.
Dutch, uh, why don't you have
Dijon show you
where Jaden stays when he's here.
Sure. Um, lead the way.
Mrs. Reynolds, I know you're worried
about your son
but he could be in trouble,
and not just from us.
He wouldn't kill no one.
Then help us find him
so we can clear this mess up
and keep Jaden from being hurt.
He has a girl. I don't like her.
She lives by that old theatre
on Sunset.
CLAUDETTE:
Got an address?
2409 Cole Street,
by the Vista Theatre.
Jaden's there.
Uh, 2409 Cole. Yeah, we got it.
How far out are you?
Uh, traffic, 15 minutes maybe. Why?
Because Dutch and Claudette
are on the way over there too.
Just get inside the house, find
the money, and get out of there fast.
Well, how far are they?
VIC: Same as you.
Jesus. What if they catch us?
We've only got the day off,
remember?
Just get there. I'll make it work.
Okay, park it, let's go.
Yeah, where?
Claudette knows this truck.
Check around back.
Come on, man. Move.
Locked, man.
I'll get the front.
Two minutes. That's it.
Then we're gone.
No arguments here.
Goddamn it.
Let's forget it, we're out of here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, shit.
What?
[DOOR CREAKS]
Shit, is he dead?
SHANE:
No. No, it's just a damn good buzz.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
SHANE [WHISPERS]:
He's sleeping on the money.
[SIGHS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Oh, shit.
Grab it. Grab it.
[GRUNTS]
RONNIE:
Let's go. Go.
Hey, you take him. I'll clear the back.
Clear.
DUTCH:
Looks like we got our shooter.
Come on, buddy, wake up.
Party's over.
Somebody took my money.
VIC:
You won't need any
where you're going.
J ADEN:
He cut me out.
He didn't have to do that.
There you go.
I didn't want to hurt nobody.
You shot him in the face three times.
VIC:
We should probably wait
until he sobers up.
Can't use anything he says
right now anyway.
J ADEN:
All that money was his.
All that bud, his.
I don't know why you ain't after him.
CLAUDETTE: Artemis?
You killed him and took the money
belonging to Artemis?
Artemis?
I was driving for Dijon.
It was his shit.
He fired me.
I'm his stepson.
What kind of shit is that?
You really dialled the wrong number
on your street Intel.
Still don't have
any evidence against Dijon,
and his hazy memory
ain't gonna get you far either.
Jaden said somebody broke in
to his girlfriend's apartment,
took the money.
What's our next move?
It's my day off.
I helped you catch the killer.
Finding the money's your problem.
SHANE:
Hey, Smitty.
Haven't seen you guys in a while.
It's been nice.
Yeah, well,
it's about to get a lot nicer.
Like to make a hundred grand?
[CHUCKLES]
Pass.
Hear us out.
The shit I've done
for you guys for peanuts,
I don't even want to know
what a hundred grand looks like.
Looks a lot easier than you think.
Lem's in jail.
You're gonna put up
a hundred gees for his bail.
You expect me to give you 100K?
We're gonna give it to you.
And when Lem shows up in court,
you're gonna keep it.
And the catch is?
IAD's gonna ask you about it.
Might wanna look at your books.
Your business
is profitable lately, right?
Very.
How'd those leads
we gave you last year work out?
SMITTY: Great.
Could always use a few more.
How many jobs does it take you
to clear a hundred grand?
[CHUCKLES]
Why you guys always coming to me
with this shit?
Because you're
the last honest guy we know.
VIC:
Hey.
Found someone willing to post bail.
My old friend came through.
Kavanaugh will be looking into
that old friend.
Nothing to find. He likes Lem.
l... I'll see if I can wake up a clerk,
get things fast tracked.
Thanks.
What? What is it?
I'm stuck here.
I don't wanna convince you all
to turn on Lem.
And I don't want to convince him
to turn on you but,
that's what a good lawyer would be
advising all of you to do right now.
[SIGHS]
I don't want to see
any of you going to prison.
Well, that's nice to know.
Right now, I think I'd make
a better friend than a lawyer.
Lem...
Lem needs you right now.
And we sure can't afford
to hire someone else.
If you have to make a choice,
you go with Lem.
And advise him to hurt you?
If you can make a deal that has me
switching places with Lem,
then you do it.
Just me.
None of my guys.
I want to see you
get your second chance.
I already have.
BILLINGS:
On behalf of the entire department,
I'd like to apologise
for the wrong done to you.
Captain learned about the photos
earlier this afternoon, came to me.
Did you find the dickwad, or what?
Unfortunately, no.
The identity of the culprit's a mystery.
Great. So where does that leave me?
Uh, during the course
of our conversation,
I mentioned to the captain
that I've seen you have
some really great instincts.
He agreed that
you have a lot of potential.
BILLINGS:
And potential needs to be nourished.
I've asked special permission
to take you under my wing.
Show you the detective ropes
in your spare time.
Unless these photos
have you too upset to focus
on career advancement?
[WHISPERS]
I see.
[NORMAL VOICE]
So I keep my mouth shut,
I climb the ladder.
Dutch is just offering an opportunity.
Did you get rid of the rest of them?
Every last one.
I look forward
to working with you, detective.
Thanks, captain.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Prisoner all clear for release.
[BUZZER SOUNDS IN DISTANCE]
Hey. Told you we'd get you out.
SHANE:
Hey.
Looks like your hymen's still intact.
You have to get your own
pussy tonight, though, buddy. Aah!
Where's Vic at, man?
He's, uh...
He had some place he's got to be.
He'll meet us later.
SHANE:
Come on, man, let's go grab a beer.
Smitty's buying.
SMITTY: I am?
SHANE: Yes.
SMITTY:
One round.
SHANE:
You're riding with me.
What are you doing here?
Kavanaugh.
He's out of control.
He's unbalanced.
He's breaking the rules,
he's threatening Lem's life.
Hey. IAD is your problem, not mine.
Look on your face walking out
of his office today says otherwise.
He's got screws in you too, yeah?
Hell, yeah.
I'm an element
in Kavanaugh's investigation.
Price I pay
for having been your boss.
But I'm hardly in the same category
as you and your guys.
Really?
You think if Kavanaugh's successful
I'm gonna go down quietly?
[CHUCKLES]
I will scorch the earth
covering this whole department,
starting with you.
I can tie you to every bullshit thing
he's accusing me of and then some.
Your stink will smell up
every voting booth in this city.
On the other hand,
you want that little nameplate on
your desk to read "Mayor" someday?
We work together.
Make sure that you, me, my team,
are the last men standing
long enough
to go our separate ways.
What's your plan?
[###]