NARRATOR:
Previously on The Shield.
CLAUDETTE:
Kleavon Gardner, questioned on
four separate homicides.
Kleavon is not a killer.
I'm his sister. Believe me, I'd know it.
We're releasing your brother.
DUTCH:
Deep down, you know we're right.
There's something wrong with him,
you just don't wanna see it.
Now that you know,
things will add up.
About six months ago, we found
this kilo of pure heroin in the
glove compartment your car.
But you never logged it
into evidence.
Lem got picked up by IAD.
Got him wearing a wire.
Kavanaugh might be planning
to formally arrest you.
That happens, we'll be
ready to bail you out.
You hired a lawyer?
You need to shift perception,
make Internal Affairs look like
they're hurting good guys.
I got Mackey making a deal with
the Russians. Hot prescription drugs.
Here's our good faith.
Yes.
COP: Do it.
OFFICERS:
Freeze!
[ALL SHOUTING]
What the hell is going on?
The IAD just shit all over our sting.
What's this?
I don't know where you got
your intel, but it's wrong.
He ran the whole operation
by me this afternoon.
I guess IAD will spin any kind of
fiction to stain good cops bad.
[TRUCK BEEPING]
MAN:
Coming. Looks good, yeah.
All right.
Gonna be tight.
Is there another way in?
BILLINGS:
No, this is it.
MOVER:
All right. Come on, down here, guys.
BILLINGS:
Oh! Watch it.
Delicate machinery, people.
MOVER: Oh, hang on.
BILLINGS: Careful, guys.
Watch the turn. Watch the turn.
Coming through. Heads up.
DETECTIVE 1:
Heads up?
DETECTIVE 2:
I'll grab it for evidentiary.
BILLINGS:
Watch your back, Dutch boy.
You gotta be kidding me.
BILLINGS:
No. Hey, guys, just be careful
on the landing, all right?
I don't want you to
scratch the leather.
Ah? After our big
pharmaceutical bust,
the brass put through some
of my purchase orders
they've been sitting on.
Well, now you'll be
sitting in style.
DUTCH:
Anything for us?
[THUD]
BILLINGS:
Careful. Come on.
I give that couch two weeks
before we're moving it down here.
I'm not wired.
You're what?
Look. I'm not wired.
I don't get this guy.
What did Kavanaugh say?
I can't find him.
I went by the motel. It's empty.
I called his cell, offices, no answer.
Why hasn't he arrested you?
Maybe he never had a solid case.
VIC:
You think he's packing it in?
What, pull the plug on
the investigation?
Until we're sure,
we act like it's still on.
But I like the feeling I'm getting.
[KNOCKS]
Vic, I hate to start your morning
with this, but multiple gang homicide.
Beautiful. Better than
a strong cup of coffee.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Set tripping?
JULIEN: Drive-by.
Male victim's affiliated Bop Street
judging by the ink.
It's what happens when
you cross enemy lines.
SHANE:
That turf's been gang-neutral since
Antwon's crew slithered out of Dodge.
Any witnesses?
Yeah. Friends of the deceased.
And about as helpful.
VIC:
Yo.
You two see anything?
Yeah, brothers having courage.
My boys went down wet
like real G's.
Do you know who did this?
KASPER: Some hater.
They almost capped me and Moni too.
Beyond that I couldn't say.
Did you get a look at the car?
We didn't see nothing.
VIC:
Well, you better start
searching your memory
or you're gonna get a good look
at the inside of our car
on the way to the station.
So me and my breezie almost
catch hollow points and po-po
got his foot up my ass?
Ain't that some toy
white-cop bullshit.
Better check your colour, honky.
BILLINGS: Chair over here, all right?
MOVER: Yeah, all right.
You getting rid of that chair?
You know, the stuffing in this one
is shot. My ass dies a daily death.
Yeah, well, sorry.
It's headed back to surplus.
Well, you can send this one back.
Inventory's expecting that one.
Well, well, well.
Pretty ballsy showing
your face around here.
I get to officially notify you that
Internal Affairs is investigating
all four members of your
former Strike Team.
Well, you got burned trying
to make that case already.
Why don't you move on?
Since all the Strike Team's files,
all your files on them are here,
I'm gonna be setting up shop
in the Barn until my
investigation's complete.
You're kidding me, right?
[KAVANAUGH LAUGHING]
Most of the time,
just not this time.
Ahem. And where exactly do you
think you're gonna drop anchor?
Well, I need some privacy,
and I don't wanna restrict any
of these officers from using
the interrogation rooms.
So the easiest thing for me
to do is to use your office.
Excuse me, lieutenant. Are you
forgetting that I'm captain here?
KAVANAUGH:
Acting captain.
And that entitles you to a workspace
and a phone. Not a private office.
But I understand the last captain
did very well right here on
the killing floor.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Scott?
Hey.
Put that stuff...
Put it over there till
I can work this shit out.
I didn't see nothing.
I don't know nothing.
I got nothing to say except thank
the Most High my man's okay.
Your man? He's a kid and you're not.
How's that work?
He laces me with nice shit
and got a big dick. It's all good.
RONNIE:
You're a deep one.
See, what I'm having a
hard time understanding is...
Aside from the ghetto-speak.
Is why some evildoers
lit up on your peace posse
for no good reason?
It's the Curse of the Fu Manchu?
Arrogant little prick for
only being 19, Preston.
That's my government name.
The homeys call me Kasper.
The famous Kasper?
Been making quite a name
for yourself these last
few months moving rock.
You must have me confused
with some other cat.
I hear you been working
with the rival sets.
Black, brown, One-Niners,
Spookstreet.
You're an equal-opportunity
dope dealer.
Don't know about that.
But see, when you white
in Farmington, you don't fit in,
so you gotta make
friends everywhere.
It'd make it a whole lot
easier on us if we just put
our heads together on this.
Yeah, it would be. But see,
I ain't no cheese-eating rodent.
VIC:
Looks like you been gnawing
on something nasty to me.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Yeah.
BILLINGS: Vic?
We got issues here.
What the hell
are you doing?
KAVANAUGH:
I know this will come
as a big surprise to you,
but you and your team
are the subject of an
IAD investigation,
which I am heading up.
You already lost face in front of
the brass, blowing our Russian bust.
How's this play helping you?
I appreciate your concern,
but let me worry about that.
Don't expect any cooperation
from those folks down there.
They're a home crowd.
I wouldn't do anything
to wanna upset them.
Last thing I wanna do
is rock the boat.
[###]
Ahh.
Man, if he'd arrest me already,
at least then he'd have to
lay out what he's got.
[KNOCKS]
Goddamn it.
VIC:
Oh, come in.
Hey.
BECCA: Hey.
Lem, Ronnie, you
remember Becca Doyle
from the Crawford case.
Yeah, hey.
VIC: Well, she's representing us now.
Protecting us legally against
this nut job upstairs.
You lawyered up?
SHANE:
She's helping out all of us.
For just such an occasion.
You're taken care of.
Well, your boy Kavanaugh's
quite the loose cannon.
Even his IAD buddies are
surprised by this move.
He's made it personal, which
helps me make the case that
you're being unfairly targeted.
[DOOR OPENS]
Oh. This looks like
attorney-client privilege.
Yes, it is.
Ms. Doyle, is it?
Yes.
Jon Kavanaugh.
I'm representing all four
of these detectives.
Make sure your communications
with them go through me.
Oh, be my pleasure.
Looking forward to working
with you. You just let me know
when you're ready, okay?
All right.
Okay.
All right. We gotta concentrate
on doing our jobs.
Let her worry about whatever
bullshit charges he's trumping up.
The last thing we want
is him getting at you
through some side door.
Throws you off your game, he comes
at you on competency issues
or some mistake you
make on the street.
Well, we got some dead kids
to account for.
Kasper and his squeeze gave us zip.
What's the next move?
All right, the dead bangers
are Bop Street.
It could be their own set
whacked them for breaking ranks,
working with white folks.
That's a tree worth shaking.
LEM: All right.
Appreciate what you're doing.
Yeah, thanks.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[CALYPSO KNOCKS]
Step off, ho. You got
nothing to trade.
I been flossing
and pussy tossing.
PAPERBO Y:
Hand it over.
Oh, shit, get out the back!
Whoo!
[COUGHING]
LEM:
Police.
[GRUNTING]
On the ground.
VIC:
Couple of your crew
caught dirt naps today.
I'm thinking you Bop Street boys
are policing yourselves.
You're tripping, man.
Then why were they
rolling with Kasper?
We all right with Kasper, mostly.
As in you wanted him
and his crew mostly dead,
or you beefing with
some other set?
I don't know.
This guy's rank and file.
RONNIE:
Look what I found.
We been letting Bop Street run game
as long as you kept it low-key.
Truce is over.
You tell Gunsmoke I'm gonna
shut down a Bop Street
rock house every two hours
until I get that shooter.
SHANE:
Your clique, rival set,
doesn't matter.
We want a name.
Nice touch. Crack vials.
That's old school.
A name by the end of today
or Bop Street can start
filing for Chapter 11.
DUTCH:
Uh, no. Thank you.
Well, what do you know.
Robbery-Homicide.
Seems they're sniffing around the
Dutch man, wanna set up an interview.
That's impressive,
elite of the elite.
Well, it's not a total surprise.
We've closed some big ones,
the whole business with
the DA's behind us.
I guess we got some buzz.
You, anyway.
Hey, isn't that, uh?
CLAUDETTE:
Fatima Gardner.
It's Kleavon's sister.
Yeah.
You all were pretty sure Kleavon
killed that girl back when.
Lana Gregory. Her and several others,
we just weren't able to prove it.
I've been doing what you said,
watching and listening.
And I found this while
I was cleaning his room.
It's Kleavon's.
DUTCH:
That's a lot of blood.
We'II, uh... We'll check this for DNA.
FATIMA:
I don't know if he's
noticed it's missing.
He hasn't mentioned cutting
himself or an accident.
If there's nothing to it, he never
has to know you were here.
I don't know how to
look at him anymore.
My own brother.
Just go home, keep doing what
you're doing. Don't be nervous.
Don't give him any
reason to think twice.
FATIMA:
You know, she says
not to seem nervous.
How am I supposed to do that?
I just don't know
if I can take this.
If we searched your brother's
room for evidence...
It's your house, you have every
legal right to let us inside.
Kleavon been, uh,
keeping odd hours?
Being secretive?
FATIMA:
Nothing out of the ordinary,
except the shirt.
His room's this way.
All the furniture's mine.
Only thing he brought
was, uh, the mirror.
Kleavon do anything else
with his time besides work?
Reads a little. Watches TV.
Like everyone else.
Dear Lord.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FATIMA GASPS]
Fatima?
[FATIMA GASPING]
FATIMA:
Hey. Changing the sheets.
I thought you were at the track.
Aw, bum day. They only
needed me an hour.
Here, let me help, then
make me a grilled cheese.
I got it. It's okay.
It's all right, it's already done.
You all right?
Course.
Come on, I'll make you some lunch.
KLEAVON:
Can you believe all that time
and effort just to get across town
then they send me
home after an hour?
[FATIMA CHUCKLES]
FATIMA: You want some pickles?
Sure.
FATIMA:
Okay.
What about that...? That other
job you were looking into?
Oh, manager told me to
call back next week.
FATIMA:
Oh, baby, something will turn up.
KLEAVON:
Yeah. You going to
Barbara's house tonight?
Just curious. Hey, you know,
we need some paper towels.
Where the hell's our door?
The other one too.
That son of a bitch.
Thought you might like
a little fresh air.
Let a little sunshine in.
Pretty cheap stunt.
I assume you guys have got
nothing to hide, right?
Anyway, with all the
confusion last week,
I never did get a chance to
congratulate you on that bust.
Nice work, even if it was
a little unorthodox.
[KAVANAUGH CHUCKLES]
But back to business.
I need to see you in my office.
Not without my lawyer.
Becca Doyle, huh? Good call.
Let me know when she gets here.
Vendrell, you got a sec?
Or do you, uh, need a lawyer too?
No, I'm good.
VIC: Shane.
I'll answer whatever
questions you got.
I see you just bought
a new house.
L.A. real estate's bananas.
You doing a little moonlighting,
security work on the side?
Mara's a realtor.
Between our two salaries,
we make do.
Reason I'm here is I wanna
nail shut the Terry Crowley file.
I see that.
That happened over two
years ago. IAD cleared us.
Or didn't you hear the squeaks
in your rat hole?
Wonder if you'd mind taking
a look at a transcript
of your interview after
the, uh, shooting.
See if it jars anything new loose.
I've been looking at
your jacket. Wow.
Pretty effective cop.
Gotten yourself into a couple of
sketchy situations along the way.
Black mark or two.
You were on your own
for a while last year.
Vice. What made you come
back to the Strike Team?
I would think that you
would wanna make a name
for yourself flying solo.
Like you dribbling shit all over us
to make a name for yourself?
All the same,
living in Mackey's shadow
all the time?
You don't feel that he was trying
to get you back into the fold
so that he could get
a leash on you, do you?
What's here is how
it went down.
So there was just you, Vic,
Terry and Two-Time in that room?
Just me and Vic.
No Lemansky, no Gardocki?
It was true then, it's true now.
Thanks so much for your help.
I'm gonna need you
to sign a document
confirming that you know that we are
reopening the Terry Crowley case
and you are under investigation.
Blow me.
CLAUDETTE:
I've talked to every
precinct in the city.
No recent bodies matching
Kleavon's m.o.
You gonna do something with that?
Just got off the phone
with Robbery-Homicide.
Turns out they didn't
just find me.
A "veteran detective"
recommended they
review my file?
I'm gonna check
Missing Persons again.
Are you trying to get rid of me?
I thought Robbery-Homicide
was your dream job.
I didn't need your help.
There is buzz.
Hey, you guys have a Fatima Gardner
sign in to see you this morning?
Yeah.
Her brother just
reported her missing.
Yeah?
Captain left a few things up here.
He asked me to get them.
Sure. Anything you need.
I pulled this off
the wall downstairs.
Pretty demeaning,
don't you think?
Doesn't really bother me.
Just boys being boys.
A lot of money on Vic
being your baby's daddy.
Everybody's got an opinion.
Heard a lot of rumours
about the two of you.
Are you saying that
they aren't true?
Look, I'm sure you
won't blame me
when I don't discuss stupid gossip
about my personal life with IAD.
Sexual relationships between
department personnel
need to be divulged
in a timely manner
according to the
employee handbook.
Failure to do so can
result in suspensions,
even demotions.
You just got a pay bump
recently, didn't you?
Come on, there's no relationship
between me and Vic.
Should I make this official?
Because I can do that,
widen my investigation.
[DANNY SIGHS]
Vic and I had a thing, okay?
It's in the past.
When was that?
Eight or nine months ago?
You wanna get a court order
to draw blood, go right ahead.
But this is none of
your business.
You still have to disclose
your relationship with Mackey.
Fill out the forms today
and I'll overlook the tardiness.
Hey, Vic. Checked out our next
Bop Street target on Hoover.
Doors and windows are fortified.
All right, have Ronnie get a
doorknocker. Flash-bangs too.
All right, man.
VIC: Hey. Hang on.
OFFICER: Over there.
Gunsmoke. We were just about
to pay a visit to another one
of your crack palaces.
Look, man, I don't know
who capped my peoples,
but I tell you straight up, it
wasn't no Bop Street niggers.
After Hoover we're gonna stop by
your Temple Street smoke house.
That'll bring your one-day loss
to what, 12 K?
You know what it does
to my street cred even
walking into this pig farm?
Oink when you got
something we can use.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
Come here.
Tell him.
I'm chilling at homegirl's
around the way,
hear shots, see these
two vatos drive off.
What did they look like?
Vatos.
You know, shaved heads,
white tees.
Guy driving had "L.A."
tattooed all up in here.
But I didn't get a look
at the dude shooting.
LEM: What kind of car?
Old, I don't know.
[SCOFFS]
But they was riding on
gold-anodised hundred-spoke D's.
I know my wheels.
So we straight now?
VIC: Not yet.
How's a punk-ass wigger
like Kasper get respect from
a crew hard as Bop Street?
Thought he was a poser
myself for a minute.
White boy got business skills.
Splits fifty-fifty off top,
so folks are getting paid.
Come with these names
for the product:
Pink Yo, Yellow Fever.
Same old shit, only
different coloured caps.
You're moving Kasper's
product out of the place we
took down this morning?
GUNSMOKE:
Look, man, fiends want
what Kasper's selling.
Can't argue with
the free market.
Looking forward to
that truce again, fellas.
DANNY: Hey, Vic, you gotta sec?
I'll get on those rims.
What's up?
Uh, that guy from IAD got all over
me about department policy,
disclosure of personal
relationships on the job.
None of his business.
Yeah, well, he's pushing me
really hard. Okay?
I can't take a suspension
or a pay cut right now.
I gotta notify Billings.
I just wanted you to know.
When was the last time
you saw your sister?
Lunchtime. She was gonna run out
for some soda, never came back.
Your family drinks a lot of soda.
I seem to remember you
were out for soda when
Lana Gregory was killed.
CLAUDETTE:
It's only a few hours, grown woman.
Bit premature to call the police.
I know my sister. She say
she be back, she be back.
Mind if we look around?
Wouldn't have called you if I did.
CLAUDETTE:
I'll take her room, you take his.
Fatima's room's clean. Back door's
unlocked. What do you have?
It's what I don't have.
Kleavon's death kit. Latex gloves,
knife, duct tape. It's gone.
I was... I was here earlier.
What?
It was spur of the moment.
Fatima gave her consent.
You searched a murder suspect's
house without backup?
What if Kleavon showed up?
I hid in the closet. He didn't see me.
I slipped out the back door.
If you're wrong, and he
confronted her after you left...
I shouldn't have come alone, but
I wasn't sure you were up to it.
Stress is a trigger, I saw you
were hurting this morning.
I am fine.
OFFICER: Got a neighbour
says he saw a prowler exiting
the backyard this morning,
wearing what he called
"a hundred-dollar suit."
I'll deal with the neighbour
if you think I'm up to it.
Take Kleavon to the Barn,
get a statement.
I paid over $300 for this suit.
KAVANAUGH:
Hey.
BECCA:
Who's this?
It's Terry Crowley. He was
one of my guys, killed by a
drug dealer couple years ago.
That is one version.
Terry was working for Justice,
investigating allegations
of a relationship between
drug dealers and your clients.
BECCA:
You have a different version?
Detective Mackey, either acting alone
or with other members of his team,
killed Detective Crowley or
put him in a position to be killed.
Just like that Russian I was gonna
murder before you blew our sting?
Any evidence or are you all attitude?
In due course.
These theatrics why
you wanted to see us?
I'm sure the three of us
have better things to do.
Yes.
I'm officially informing you
you are under investigation
for the death of Terry Crowley,
and other allegations of corruption.
You have a right to
a PBA rep, to a lawyer.
I see you already got one,
and a good one.
Please, could you get him to initial
here and here, his signature there?
BECCA:
We'll cooperate fully so you can stop
wasting everyone's time, lieutenant.
I suppose you want a statement?
Actually, if you could, uh,
have your clients walk me
through the house
where Terry Crowley was killed,
that would be great.
I'll arrange it soon.
Oh, and take down these photos
or I'll file for harassment.
Becca.
Thought the headline in this case
was David against Goliath.
Or did this murder charge
slip your mind?
I can't talk about
this right now.
[WHISPERS]
This is a big goddamn deal.
It's all a lie. I'm sorry.
I'll call you later.
What the hell's going on?
He told them to bring me in.
Can you take the kids?
You don't have to
talk to him, remember?
I just wanna get this over with.
He can't compel
your cooperation.
If you feel uncomfortable
at any time, you just leave.
Okay.
Corrine. Thanks for coming.
The children, they can wait inside.
I can take care of my own kids.
Okay.
This way. Upstairs. Hey, guys.
Dad, what the hell's going on?
Don't talk like that.
He's a cop, right?
Did Mom do something wrong?
No, never.
Come on.
BILLINGS: Vic.
I, uh, caught a 187 times two.
Need you to get on it.
What's 187 mean?
It means Dad's gonna
find you guys a ride.
Come on, kids. Let's go.
You need anything?
Can I get you something?
Coffee or water?
Just ask your questions.
You've told me that it's really
difficult to make both the tuitions.
Yet Vic seems to be able to come up
with the money all the time.
How do you think
he does that?
Overtime.
Yeah, I've checked those paystubs.
He always has been a good
provider, wouldn't you say?
I guess that might change
now that you have to split the pie
four ways instead of three, huh?
I don't understand.
Oh, maybe you're not aware,
Officer Danielle Sofer,
who works here,
is filing paperwork admitting
to a sexual relationship
with Vic over the last
couple of years.
When did you get divorced?
Last year.
Right.
Officer Sofer is now pregnant.
Is this another imaginary child
like Andy?
I mean, what kind of a man
says he has an autistic child
to a woman who has two
of her own? How sick is that?
You know, I didn't
really like doing that.
I'm sorry, I just needed to know
what kind of woman you are.
Corrine...
Really, I mean,
this is not about me.
This is about Vic.
It's about you, it's about the kids,
it's about this new baby,
how we got to this place, and
where we're gonna go from here.
Please.
Have a seat?
VIC:
"L.A." California.
Same calibre as the Bop Street hit.
LEM: Yup.
It's gotta be the shooter
from this morning.
Payback's a bitch.
Yeah, and karma's a whore.
Amado Alvaro. His place.
No sign of forced entry.
What about ass-boy over there?
STAMOS: No ID yet.
Neighbour called 911, saw
Alvaro's car driving away
a little while after she
heard the gunshots.
Hooptie? Gold rims?
Yeah, '69 Olds Cutlass. Why?
Run Alvaro's registration,
put an APB out on the car.
Got it.
Squad, let me get a run
on a '69 Olds Cutlass.
OFFICER [ON RADIO]:
Vehicle should be rolling up to you
right now, detective. You see it?
VIC:
We got it. Nice work, Larry.
Say hello to whoever
killed L.A. and ass-boy.
Who's the Chinaman?
VIC:
I don't know, but we're
gonna find out.
[TYRES SCREECHING]
[HORN HONKING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, you guys, hey!
LEM:
Stop!
Go.
[GRUNTING]
Stop.
SHANE: Hey.
Halt.
Hold it.
Hey, stop, dumb-ass.
It's a barbed-wire fence.
LEM:
What the hell's he doing?
[YELLS]
[KANG GRUNTING]
I didn't do nothing.
Except a double homicide.
That's crazy.
Amado's my main man.
Funny how you know exactly
the murders we're talking about.
We got you fleeing the scene
of a murder in the victim's car.
You take one last look
at the outside world.
Where'd you put
the murder weapon?
They were dead when
I got there, I swear.
All right, search the car.
KANG:
He was into me for 10 grand.
Some white guy named Kasper
was coming by to drop off money.
[KANG PANTING]
VIC:
Amado was meeting Kasper?
I wasn't supposed to know.
Kasper was coming by to
pay him for some work he did.
When I saw bodies, I bounced.
We've gotta take
another run at Kasper.
Remember Terry Crowley?
CORRINE:
Sure, he was on Vic's team.
Do you remember any change in Vic's
behaviour leading up to Terry's death?
No, but he was pretty torn up
afterwards. We all were.
I'm sure it was, uh, terrible.
Terry was working for Justice,
investigating your ex-husband's
team for corruption.
Planting evidence, extortion,
kickbacks, laundry list of things.
When Vic made Terry
as working for the feds,
we believe that he and
Shane Vendrell murdered him.
Vic's a lot of things,
but he's no killer.
Vic is a survivor.
He'll do whatever it takes
to protect himself,
his team and his family.
Are you really trying to tell me
that after 12 years of marriage,
you don't think that that man
is capable of pulling
the trigger on someone
who's trying to take away
everything from him? Everything?
[CRYING]
You need to stop this, okay?
Don't cry.
I don't wanna see you
shed one single tear.
Because tears imply
that you didn't know.
And don't you sit here and tell me
that you didn't know, Mrs. Mackey.
Twelve years you shared his bed.
You knew.
He paid your mortgage,
he paid your bills, and now he's
paying for private schools.
You always knew what
he was capable of,
just like you knew about
the other women.
Don't you sit here and cry
and tell me that he's a good man.
Because we both know that's bullshit.
You left him because you knew.
And yet you protect him.
You protect him and you lie.
You lie to me.
No.
Don't you dare sit here
shedding tears.
You can only do that if
you've earned that right,
if it was all a surprise.
But it's not a surprise to the
woman who knew him better
than anyone else on this earth.
Is it?
[JULIEN KNOCKS]
JULIEN: Police. Open up.
MAN: I can't!
Help me.
Please, help me.
Please.
JULIEN:
Sir, what's the problem?
Something's got me... My dick...
Please, just... Please help.
All right, sir, just relax,
I'm gonna try to...
No! No! No! Oh, God.
Shit.
Oh, please.
Please, hurry up.
You're caught in a rat trap.
Call the paramedics.
Get it off me, please.
One-Tango-Bravo
requesting paramedics
for male Hispanic, mid-30s...
[SCREAMING]
TINA: Lacerations on his groin.
TRUJILLO: Oh, God.
Sir, it's okay.
Paramedics are on the way.
Oh, damn.
Ouch.
Meanwhile, this IAD guy's
got my nuts in a waffle iron.
You say this happened
at a glory hole?
Yeah, it's pretty sick, huh?
Yeah. Guy's lucky his
schlong wasn't cut off.
Well, I figure the perp only
let it snap halfway, otherwise
it would've... no question.
Anyway, we're re-interviewing
the victim as soon as he
gets back from hospital.
Price tag. Check out the
hardware store that sold it.
It's one of 20 in the same
transaction two days ago.
That's why my TO thought
you'd wanna put detectives on it.
Well, I can't spare any, so why
don't you guys run with it.
It's right up Julien's alley.
It's the kind of case he can
really sink his teeth into.
You and Fatima had a fight.
She was nagging you too much,
invading your privacy...
Lady, I came to you. Now y'all
wanna pull me in here about
this thing, you're wasting time.
My sister's missing.
And we're trying to find her.
Then why ain't you talking
to that neighbour about the
man he saw at my place?
We're following up on that.
CLAUDETTE:
We want to help you find your sister.
You have to start answering questions.
You gonna cooperate or not?
Anything for her.
DUTCH:
Give us a minute.
Anyone else, I'd say he's
genuinely concerned about her.
Given that he's a homicidal
sociopath, who knows?
When we get this guy, I wanna
administer the needle myself.
Wow. He's really under your skin.
I wish I could get under his.
Okay, maybe we hit Kleavon with the
bloody shirt, the missing death kit.
We get him rattled.
We've already exposed
Fatima enough. I don't
want to blow her cover.
She could still be
out there alive.
You know, he could've realised
that the bloody shirt was missing
figured out Fatima turned on him
even if he didn't see me.
Great. Now that we've
covered your ass, you
help me figure out what to do.
SHANE:
Four o'clock this afternoon,
where were you?
Four o'clock this afternoon?
I was at Moni's crib,
hitting skins and smoking endo.
Don't believe me, ask the girl.
You know an Amado Alvaro?
KASPER: No.
Shot and killed in his home
along with a buddy.
Pretty messy.
Rest in peace.
Matches the description of
someone we're looking for in
the attack on you and your peeps.
Well, like the book says,
"No hand raised against me
shall prosper."
The other DB is Adair Zeborio.
Vegas P.D. was looking at him
on a murder-for-hire case.
Didn't make.
Professional hit.
He didn't get the whole job done,
wigger got the last word.
This punk? Unlikely.
Hey, Gilligan's still half-baked on
chronic. Let's keep him yapping,
see where it gets us.
All right.
Am I done here?
SHANE: No, you're not done here.
Not until you tell us what you
were doing at Amado Alvaro's
apartment today.
You all are bugging.
I was at my homegirl's.
And how am I gonna try and kill
somebody I never even heard of?
And how long before you
piss off the wrong Mandingo
and he wastes your pasty
wigger ass as reparations?
Man, the streets got nothing but
love for Kasper as long as I'm
putting money in their pockets.
Ha. One bad month and you'll
be dangling from a balcony
just like Vanilla Ice.
Another great white wannabe.
Next thing you know, we're gonna be
hearing about some shitty rap album
you're gonna wanna put out.
Why you tripping on
this black-white shit?
Colour ain't a thing.
Oh, come on, man. This is
just us glacier monkeys.
We both know white is right
and black is wack.
Which is why you're rolling
with the pretty white lady.
You might talk like a brother,
but you hang with your own.
Not that the sisters would
show you love anyway.
Man, I get more black ass than
a bus bench in Compton, you heard?
[VIC CHUCKLES]
Hard for me to imagine you
holding it down with some
Nubian mattress-monster.
Well, then you need to ask somebody,
one-time. Taneisha's my go-to girl.
She let me tear her phat ass and
sugar walls up any time I want.
White ho's only around
because she swallows nut
and I can take her home
to Mom's without any drama.
Word.
LL Douchebag's
starting to piss me off.
Yeah, well, he gave us enough
to put his alibi to the taste test.
Pick up the girlfriend.
I'm gonna stick around.
You must've seen something.
The assailant had to walk right
past you to leave that bathroom.
I really didn't get a look at him.
Get a booking slip going.
I need you to stand,
hands behind your back.
TRUJILLO: What?
Stand, hands behind your back.
You're arresting me?
Public indecency, lewd conduct.
I'm not the one who did anything.
You think maybe I've
suffered enough?
I have a wife and daughters.
If they find out... Jesus.
Look, I don't normally
do this sort of thing.
Just once or twice, to work stuff out.
JULIEN: In the cage.
Please, don't do this.
It'll ruin my marriage.
Come on, sir, come on.
I don't have to say
anything to you.
We were married and I'm protected
under spousal privilege.
He told you to say that, didn't he?
Because it protects him.
You know you can waive that right
any time you want to, right?
Which is why he probably
didn't even tell you to get
an attorney, did he?
You knew he's got his own lawyer?
Maybe you saw her downstairs.
She's real pretty, dark-haired.
[SCOFFS]
Such a good provider.
And yet he's covering his ass,
he's covering guys' ass,
and he leaves you
just hanging out there.
You know why?
Because he doesn't want you
listening to anybody else but him.
Your lawyer would, uh, be
looking after your interests.
And that doesn't help him.
That hurts him, in fact, so...
Your lawyer would advise you
to cooperate, tell me the truth.
Tell me what I wanna know.
But you're here all alone.
You wanna know what I see?
I mean, just looking at you?
I see a mother of three going away
for obstructing justice,
protecting a man she
knows is a criminal.
What are your two
autistic children gonna do
when you're, like, locked away
and you're serving your sentence?
What are they gonna do?
How are they gonna be in foster care?
Stop it! Stop!
Well, tell me what I wanna know.
I'm just asking you to tell me what...
Tell me what I want to know.
Vic is not going to take care of
those kids when you're gone.
Vic gave me some cash
in a bag a little while ago.
That's it. I don't know anything else.
There's nothing else.
Well, how much?
Sixty-five thousand.
Where'd it come from?
I didn't ask. I never asked.
Where is it?
I spent most of it on
tuition and on therapists.
There's... There's only...
There's only about $5000 left.
I need that money.
I need that money back.
Now. Now you can cry.
SHANE:
You might wanna rethink this alibi
you're handing Kasper.
Because we can put him in
the crib where Amado Alvaro
got his brains splashed.
That's the guy who shot at you
and killed your friends.
If you're lying to cover
for your man-boy toy,
we can get you on conspiracy
to commit murder.
SHANE:
Just like pulling the trigger yourself.
You'll be old and in the way
by the time you see the sky again.
I got nothing to say,
period, point-blank.
Kasper's got plenty
to say about you.
KASPER [ON TAPE]:
I get more black ass than a
bus bench in Compton, you heard?
[VIC CHUCKLES ON TAPE]
Hard for me to imagine you
holding it down with some
Nubian mattress-monster.
KASPER:
Well, then you better ask somebody,
one-time. Taneisha's my go-to girl.
She lets me tear her phat ass and
sugar walls up any time I want.
White ho's only around
because she swallows nut...
You all right?
Don't talk to me.
What happened?
Not now. Just let me go.
Corrine...
SHANE: Vic.
Corrine, I'll call you.
Hey, Vic, Moni gave up
our friendly ghost.
What's wrong?
Hey, come on, man. Let's go.
VIC:
You know the thing
about women?
And it doesn't really matter
what colour they are.
When they get pissed off, watch out.
Moni just threw your pink
ass cheeks to the kerb.
VIC:
You had the smarts,
the business model.
SHANE:
The stripper girlfriend.
What you didn't have
was the street cred.
Not really. Not like
some hard-ass brother.
You're only a true baller when
somebody wants you dead.
If the bullets miss you, makes you
immortal to the street, right?
So you hired Alvaro and Zeborio
to shoot up your friends.
Make you look like the target.
Market yourself as some bad-ass dude
instead of a punk-ass white boy.
You been smoking crack.
SHANE:
Your girl, Moni, just gave us the
key to her locker at the Cheetah,
where she stashed the TEC-9
you did the two hitmen with.
Shooter out of the way, you don't
have to pay for the hit, right?
The businessman in you
saw a way to save a buck,
instead it's gonna cost you three
to five dimes in the state pen.
Bitches ain't shit.
Your sister's a church-going woman.
You grow up that way?
Jesus is my saviour,
that's what you mean?
That's what I love
about the church.
No matter how bad
you are, how often,
forgiveness is always there.
All you gotta do is come clean.
What's that got to do
with finding her?
I don't know. Maybe she
started looking at you funny
after you murdered Lana.
Maybe she wanted to ask you
about it, but she was too scared.
Then one day it all came out.
But you couldn't have that.
So you had her killed and
reported her missing so you could
make yourself look innocent.
No! I didn't kill my sister.
That's my blood.
They're all somebody's
blood, Kleavon.
Didn't stop you then, why
would it stop you this time?
Don't talk to me like that!
I'll talk to you
any way I goddamn please.
You can't arrest me and
you're not helping me.
I'll find her myself.
I'd be willing to make these charges
go away on two conditions.
TRUJILLO:
Anything you want.
You never do this type of thing again.
My word.
And you help us ID
the guy who did this.
Ha. Then I'll be involved
in a court case.
I know how this works.
My brother's a lawyer.
Either way, it's all public.
I'll keep your name out of this.
But I cannot get this guy
and his 19 other rat traps
off the street without your help.
The bridge of his nose is right,
but his cheekbones are higher.
Hey. You decided to
cut him some slack?
Lesser of two evils,
gets the kook off the streets.
You think we're looking
for a vigilante?
Don't know.
Julien, you and I got off
to a rough start
but I feel like things are
starting to make more sense.
Good.
Look, man, I grew up with
my gay uncle living with us,
so it's no big deal to me, but I saw
what he had to go through.
I honestly just didn't
get your situation.
I'm not sure what you're trying to say.
All I'm saying is that I understand.
And it's between you and
your wife anyway, so I'm cool.
You're cool? With what?
That I'm the TO that should've
washed you out weeks ago?
You don't understand anything.
I know why you recommended
me for Robbery-Homicide.
There's no need to thank me.
You're getting sicker and you
can't bear for me to see it.
A woman may be dead because
you wanted to protect me.
I shouldn't have done the search
without you. I'm sorry.
I do not let my illness
get in the way of my job.
You do. That's dangerous.
I'm not leaving you.
Detectives? You wanted to be notified
of any black female dump jobs.
Late 40s. Probably strangled.
That's not Kleavon's m.o.
That's his sister.
Uni says it looks like rape.
To his own sister?
[SIRENS BEEPING]
OFFICER:
Just showed up on scene.
It's not Fatima.
DUTCH:
Who is it?
Look at this.
He chopped her hair off.
Yeah. Not with scissors.
Probably a knife?
You recognise the haircut?
Looks like I got under
Kleavon's skin after all.
Hey, thanks for swinging by.
I wanted to finish this in person.
Me too. If you didn't before,
now you can see how
out of control Kavanaugh is.
I need to decide if I
wanna represent you.
Any of you.
First you're a sacrificial lamb
to appease angry voters
after that referendum...
We're the good guys in this.
Only not that good.
Because then you tell me Aceveda
had you doing dirty work for him
and is setting you up
to take the fall.
Today I find out this is about
capital murder on a cop.
Becca, it's a put-up job.
Right now,
I have no clue about who
the hell you really are.
How can I help you with that?
I actually had a kernel of faith
that you could take the guy down.
Now it just seems like
you've lost your senses.
You're under investigation,
councilman.
For what?
Your connection with Mackey.
I don't understand how you could
be so gung ho to get this guy
and yet be in his pocket
at the same time.
Something I gotta look at.
What, you still think that I helped Vic
set you up with that Russian sting?
Man, he got to you.
Playing us against each other.
You may as well fold up
your tent and go home.
One thing I know for sure,
when you sat in this office,
you could've put an end to him,
but you didn't. Now it's my turn.
You seriously think this little
display of yours is gonna work?
I need you to initial here, here,
and I'd really like
your signature here.
You're sill a reserve cop, right?
I do have authority over you.
You walk out that door,
I'm gonna take your badge
and I'm gonna tell every
reporter in town why.
Then you may as well add
insubordination to your list
of bullshit allegations.
You want any paperwork signed,
you send it to my office, I'll have
the city attorney take a look at it.
Fine.
I'm chairman of the
Police Committee.
This is a fight you don't want.
I didn't want any of it.
But I'm here and I'm staying.
Corrine, call me.
Kavanaugh's upstairs with Aceveda.
What the hell's going on?
It's almost 8 and he's still at it.
What do we do, just
leave for the night?
[###]