[FAUCET SPUTTERS]
[CLANGING]
Kavanaugh was here all morning?
Yeah.
He said he wanted to ask me,
um, a few questions to wrap
up his case, but...
Did he try to touch you?
Why would you ask that?
What...? What did he say?
Well, he was desperate and kind of
Ionely and I felt bad for him.
And then, out of nowhere,
he said he was coming after you
and that he wanted to make sure
me and the kids would be okay if...
If something happened to me?
This is about Lem. He didn't show
up at court to turn himself in.
Where is he?
Nobody knows. He's a fugitive.
Kavanaugh probably figures
I had something to do with it.
No, I didn't.
He's just pissed because
his case against Lem tanked.
He's making it personal.
He wants to hurt me through you.
Please, don't let him in
this house again, all right?
Bye.
Be careful.
Always.
Where's Lemansky?
I don't know.
You screwed him once,
and now you've done it again,
putting him on the run.
SHANE:
Didn't they kick your ass
out of the Barn?
You aid and abet him,
you communicate with him
in any way without reporting it,
you'll be put in prison alongside him.
We had nothing to do with this.
My office will have
eyes on all of you
every second of every day
until Lemansky's caught.
Thank you for bringing me
back into your life.
[###]
All right, where are we
with those errands?
I spoke to our Federale buddy
who took Doomsday off our hands.
He's gonna meet Lem in T.J.,
get him to a safe house in Ensenada.
Well, that's wall-to-wall wetbacks,
surfer boy will be a little obvious.
He'll be on the move.
Taco-cop's got a brother.
He owns a goat ranch in the
mountains north of San Ignacio.
It's a really good place to get lost.
How much?
It's 2 grand and a call on our
services to be determined later.
I can't wait.
What about living expenses?
Got a line of wire transfers
to Guatemala.
VIC:
How secure?
Enough to keep it off Immigration's
radar. Used to pay coyotes mostly.
He's gonna need cash.
It's gonna be his only leverage.
Let me work on that.
Now all we need is a way
to get him across the border.
[SIREN WAILING]
We were working something else.
Not anymore. You've got history
with these grenade-tossers.
Any victims?
Just a half-dozen Crown Vics.
You've tangled with some well-armed
Salvadorans before, right?
The guy who imports the
grenades is named Guardo.
We hit him hard, and his
weapons stash, but he got away.
Looks like he didn't go far.
GALLAGHER:
Agent Gallagher, DEA.
Captain Wyms,
Farmington Division.
This is our lot. We've been running
an op on the El Salvadorans
out of the travel agency.
Someone wants to
move up to first class.
Detective Mackey and his team
busted some of that gang a week ago.
Swept up a bunch of grenades,
MP5s, few top-level lieutenants.
And let their playmaker, Guardo,
slip out from under your nose.
We're here to assist.
Great. Start directing traffic.
Look, a grenade goes off on my turf,
you get help whether you like it or not.
Don't step on our toes,
we'll stay off yours.
What an asshole.
Well, Rawling did burn them.
So now's our chance to make it up.
Track down whatever you can find,
run everything by me.
And, Vic, that renegade shit's
not gonna fly on my watch.
But you already knew that.
Looks like a new sheriff
just limped into town.
Yeah, well, she's smart.
She keeps tabs on us from her end,
DEA keeps an eye on us
from the other.
I don't give a shit about either.
We'll follow up on this,
but finding Lem safe passage
to Mexico is still priority one.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHILD CRYING]
Hey, hello?
Hey, open the door.
Open the door now.
[CHILD CRYING]
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
Where's your mommy?
GIRL: She's gone.
She's gone. Hey, buddy,
what's your name?
What's your name? What's his name?
Wendell.
Wendell, do you want me
to wash that out for you?
Shh. It's okay.
It's gonna be all right, bud.
It's all right. It's gonna be okay.
It's just a little cut.
There we go. It's all right.
MAN:
What the hell's going on
in here, guys?
Look, it's okay. It's all right.
Lisa.
It's okay, I'm a cop.
GEORGE:
Lisa, there's a gun. Call the police.
Come here, come here.
GEORGE: Lisa, are you calling?
Hold this tight. Hold it tight
till someone gets here, okay?
Okay, buddy.
GEORGE:
That's the guy.
LISA:
He had a gun?
That's the third Mexican that gave up
that it's payback for busting Osorio.
Which means it can't
possibly be true.
Souljahs have been fed their
cover story, but what's the truth?
Hey. I think Kavanaugh
found Lem's trailer.
What?
Sheriff's Department got called to
the trailer park on a disturbance.
Cliff says Kavanaugh's
on his way there now.
VIC:
Your pal say anything about Lem?
No. Radio blackout.
But something's popping.
If Kavanaugh's poking around,
man, what else could it be?
VIC:
Look, we'd have heard
something if they arrested him.
Maybe. Maybe not.
Who knows with Kavanaugh?
Maybe they found him and he was...
There's no way he'd
eat his gun. No way.
Well, we told him not to
contact us at any cost.
We're in no-man's land.
Best-case scenario, he's on the run
with Kavanaugh on his ass.
Look, man.
Lem knows the score.
He's gonna meet us tonight
and get supplies, which means
we gotta pull our shit together and
get his ticket out of here by then.
Truth is, this could be goodbye.
Come on.
VIC:
What's this?
Your former CI says she's
got information on the
demolished DEA cars.
VIC:
Well, give her to the feds.
We don't want her.
I tried. She'll only talk to you.
Kavanaugh cut me loose, Vic.
I'm not working for him no more.
Now that you've stabbed one of
my guys with an indictment?
It's... It's real good intel.
It's not my dime. Your call.
Give us a minute.
I know she's the one Kavanaugh
had testify against Lem.
It's all bullshit.
She as inside as she says?
See what the story is.
Make sure she sticks around
the Barn, where I can see her.
Blowing up those DEA cars
wasn't retaliation.
Nothing we don't know.
EMOLIA:
Guardo's play for drug
protection's paid off.
Colombians have a huge shipment
coming up from Mexico.
Hired him and
his crew to guard it.
The feds feel like they were making
a dent in the Salvadoran drug game,
meanwhile, something else is
going on underneath their noses.
Yeah, Guardo's a crazy shithead.
Any excuse to blow something up.
When and where?
Tonight. Going through
a grocery-import guy.
Aldo Melchor.
The importer, he Salvadoran?
Mexican.
Need a place and a time.
That's... That's all I got.
That's real good
information though.
Yeah, if it's true, and not just
another chance for you to help
Kavanaugh to nail us again.
No, I never wanted to
help Kavanaugh. l...
Right, now, who's
the source of your intel?
You never needed to know that before.
I trusted you before.
Fine.
I wanna get paid up front, then.
I need money to get out of L.A.,
take Sebastio, head up to Seattle,
be with my sister.
SHANE:
I'm so happy you got a little plan.
What about Lem?
He gonna head up to Seattle,
live with your sister too?
Oh, that's right, he can't,
because he's gonna be in prison.
I'm sorry.
Vic took care of you.
He fed you and your kid
for months.
And you were sticking us
the whole goddamn time.
EMOLIA:
No. You see this?
I slept with this scumbag, Ignacio,
to get this info for you, okay?
But then two of his buddies joined in.
Ripped me up pretty bad.
If you
made different choices
from the beginning,
none of us would be
ripped up right now.
Becca?
Come on, make it look
like we're on a date.
I can't do anything to
help you escape the police.
All right, make it look like
a lovers' quarrel, then.
Look, the only advice I can give you
legally is to turn yourself in now.
That's exactly what I wanna do.
Then we're in the wrong side of town.
Look, I need assurances.
You're not exactly in a position to...
Look, I need to do my time
someplace where the One-Niners
and Antwon Mitchell can't get to me.
All right?
Federal prison, back East.
The feds aren't calling this.
And going fugitive means
the original deal's gone.
Then I'll plead to new federal charges.
I'll tell them all the shit that I did.
You can't just serve them
your head on a platter either.
Kavanaugh's not gonna stop
till he's carving me up.
Tell them that I ripped off
an Armenian money-
laundering operation,
stole cash that was part of a
federal sting. I'll plead to that.
You did this by yourself?
Yeah.
Listen to me. They're going to
insist on Vic and the others.
I got nothing to say about them.
Then why are you running?
I'm not running. I'm giving myself up.
All right? I'm ending it.
You want a new deal,
they'll want new information.
I'm giving them new
information on myself.
You are not hearing me.
There will be no deal until
you give them more than you.
Curtis, please. Listen to me.
You have got to think
about yourself one time.
It's your only option.
Now, Vic told me that you guys
sometimes would spread around
some drug money
to keep peace on the streets.
I can spin that...
Listen to me. This Armenian thing
was armed robbery. People got killed.
And they weren't the only ones.
You think it was all just
palming off some drug money
to keep the streets quiet?
I can't tell the truth about the
others because they'll throw us
away for the rest of our lives.
Open your goddamn eyes
to who we are.
People got killed?
Look, this is all
attorney-client privilege.
Detective Terry Crowley...
You've heard enough.
Just get me my deal.
Do my time back East.
Then I'll turn myself in.
I'll call you in a few hours.
Aldo Melchor.
Hey, let me see your hands.
Easy, easy.
SHANE: It's a knife.
To cut my chorizo.
It's okay if I have my lunch?
As long as it's finger food.
What can I do for you, officers?
Well, rumour has it you import more
than just chorizo from down south.
Everything in this store is legal.
Really?
You won't mind if we stick around,
monitor your import-export.
I close at 7.
VIC: Not tonight.
You're gonna stay open until
that shipment of coke arrives.
We're just gonna hang out, provide
a little after-hours security.
Salvadorans realise
you snitched on them,
they're gonna grind you
into chorizo,
sell you by the quarter-pound
like the rest of the sausage
you got down there.
Is there something I can do for you?
Tell us what time the shipment comes.
We'll keep you out of it.
Bust the Salvadorans after they leave,
keep your pipeline up and running.
What else?
Obviously you can import.
Your exporting skills
better be just as good.
I've stayed in business 15 years.
We got a little package
we wanna overnight to Mexico.
How big is it?
About 6'2".
VIC [WHISPERING]:
Hey, yo.
You wanna tell me what the hell
Becca's doing up there?
SHANE [WHISPERING]:
Talking to Kavanaugh and Aceveda.
You think of any scenario
where that's a good thing?
Curtis Lemansky is prepared
to turn himself in.
If you talked to him, you have an
obligation to tell us where he is.
I know my obligations.
I don't know where he is.
Curtis knows where the Barn is
if he wants to turn himself in.
He couldn't hand himself over to you,
for reasons that involve his safety.
Any cop who's incarcerated
faces those risks.
He knew that. He made his choice
when he broke the law.
All we're asking for is protection.
At least until I have a chance to
investigate his claims against
Lieutenant Kavanaugh.
And after that?
He'll accept the previous deal.
As long as we can reasonably
guarantee his safety.
He can't have the same deal.
He ran away from that deal.
And if the council signs off,
they're gonna want more.
My client is willing to
plead to new charges.
But he wants his choice
of federal prisons.
What's he have to say
about his friends?
BECCA: Nothing.
KAVANAUGH: Not good enough.
I have to run this up
a few ladders, so, uh,
give me till the end of the day.
Look, I'll find him first.
Then we can dictate the terms.
I need bodies, though.
I want two surveillance teams
on Mackey and his guys
in case they try to help
Lemansky escape.
You burned your bridges
with the chief.
I need my people on the street.
Becca?
Becca, what happened with Lem?
Is he all right?
Privileged information.
Tell me he's okay.
Well, at least tell me what's wrong.
Wait.
Don't touch me.
Haven't you done
enough damage yet?
Becca, come on. Come on.
Let's go somewhere and talk.
Talk about armed robbery
of an Armenian money-
laundering operation?
Talk about murdering
Terry Crowley?
I told you.
Yes, you did.
And now I know the truth.
I let you touch me.
It makes me sick.
Becca, I don't know
what Lem told you...
No more explanations.
It's all bullshit.
You know, I was worried
about what I'd do
if I had to choose between being
Curtis' lawyer or your friend.
Not anymore.
BILLINGS:
Did you see the guy
who attacked you?
No, he just came up from behind me
and started hitting me, and I was
trying to cover my face.
This area can get pretty rough,
even in daylight.
What were you doing here,
besides prettying up the place?
Thanks. Um...
I'm a volunteer tutor at the
community centre on the corner.
I'm just trying to help
some kids, you know?
We're gonna have you come in,
look at some pictures.
But why? I told you
I didn't see him, so...
Maybe you saw more than you think.
Is that really necessary?
Excuse us for a minute.
Send her home. If she remembers
anything, she can call us.
Yeah, why don't you
figure out another way to
get her phone number?
Because I'm bringing her in.
I was acting captain, remember?
I'm making the call.
Hey, it's Curtis.
BECCA [ON PHONE]: Hi.
Look, I'm kind of in a hurry.
What's going on?
They're in a holding pattern.
They said they'd tak e your
offer under advisement,
but gave no indication when
or what the answer might be.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, look, I need you
to get a message to Vic.
That would be breaking the law.
Shit.
All right, forget it. Forget it.
It's gonna be worse
if they catch you.
Now that I've told them
what you want, they know
there's more shit to uncover.
Kavanaugh will show no mercy.
I know.
There is one other option though.
What?
Witness protection.
And you tell them everything.
The entire truth.
Imagine, you'd be free of
the lies, the running.
People pay a price
for what they did.
I can't. I can't.
Curtis, you're the one with
a heart, now use your head.
This isn't about my goddamn heart.
I'm just trying to
help you here, Curtis.
No, you're trying
to get me to turn
on my family.
Please, just get me my deal.
He held out as long as he could.
He's still holding.
He didn't wanna run in the first place.
He'd run before he would rat.
How do they know
about the money train?
Educated guess.
There's always been plenty of
suspicion, just never any proof.
Unless Lem gave it to them.
VIC: We know Lem.
Look, if he had a change of heart,
he would have tipped us.
Or he wouldn't if his deal
meant us going down.
Look, I'm not saying that it happened.
I'm just saying, are we willing to bet
our freedom that it didn't?
I'm not gonna believe it until
I see it with my own eyes.
Lem's not contacting us
to protect us.
We're gonna meet him
tonight at midnight
and he's gonna travel
tonight. That's it.
Okay.
On whose nickel? Man, this spic cop
doesn't take American Express.
I know.
It's already taken care of.
Look, I told Mara that
Lem was in trouble.
She felt very strongly that
we needed to help him.
So we pulled a little cash
out of the house.
I mean, it's not a lot, but...
Hey, 5 grand ought to keep him in
burritos and beer long enough, man.
All right. Go get this cashed.
Keep half of it for tonight,
put the rest on the wire.
Lem must have said something
to Becca about Terry too.
All that gives Kavanaugh
is a little more suspicion.
Doesn't mean we're gonna
catch a case, let alone a needle.
Lem starts talking,
it puts teeth in an
otherwise empty rumour.
These people,
every time they look at us,
they're gonna see two cop killers.
Now, that's on me.
Terry was a decision
that we both made.
I forced it on you.
Now you're in Kavanaugh's
cross hairs. That's on me.
Lem's gonna have to hide under
a rock for the rest of his life.
That's on me too. I know that.
And skewering yourself
is helping Lem how?
How's it gonna help any of us?
You made a call, and that call
was to protect the team.
Now, that couldn't have
gone down any other way.
It's done. It's done.
Now, is he still on our side
against Kavanaugh?
I'm gonna find out.
VIC:
You.
What the hell was that powwow
upstairs about?
Call me later.
I'm running out of later.
Now, are you and me still
allies against Kavanaugh,
or do I pull out my flamethrower
and start that scorched-earth plan
that I talked to you about?
Becca's being a good lawyer.
Lem wants to turn himself in if
he can get his original deal back.
But Kavanaugh
won't sign off on it.
He's gonna file new charges
for him running.
I thought Kavanaugh
was out of the picture.
He was until Lem didn't show.
And now the chief's believing
that Kavanaugh was right.
He's giving him back all his power.
What about Lem?
You let him twist in the wind?
Claudette's gonna call the DA.
But she's waiting as long as
she can to give Kavanaugh
a chance to find Lem.
And that's all I know.
You gotta throw a
wrench in the works.
You know, you wanted an inside guy
for intel, and you got one.
You need help aiding and abetting
a fugitive? Find someone else.
Witness says you
attacked Tori Burke.
Also says you two had an argument
first. What was that about?
You just, uh, think you can go around
beating women on the street?
Okay, your thing is just knocking the
shit out of random, total strangers.
Works for me, Gilbos.
So l... So I picked up a hooker.
I'm not the only guy who's
had to bust out of a slump.
Doesn't mean I deserve to
get rolled and robbed.
Say again?
She set me up.
Soon as I got my clothes off
and my dick hard,
these two black guys ran in,
started smashing me up,
took everything.
So I gave her a little payback.
Arrest her ass, not mine.
BILLINGS:
We talked to people at
the community centre.
You volunteer there at least
three days a week?
Yeah, I read to disadvantaged kids.
Are you a prostitute, Tori?
Maybe in your fantasy
I'm a prostitute.
All right. You know what? Um...
If I'm gonna be insulted on top of
assaulted, I think I'd like to leave.
Okay. We need to ask you
a few more questions.
You're a suspect in a separate
assault and robbery.
I'd like to see my legal counsel.
VIC:
All right, they're moving
the blow into the van.
Still no sign of Guardo?
They'll lead us to him.
RONNIE:
Okay. Gracias.
Hey, wire transfer went through.
Meet-and-greet in T.J.'s confirmed.
Now we just need to
get Lem on board.
Okay, good. Almost home.
They're on the move.
Hey, come on.
Pairing me up with Billings?
You know a guy like that's
gonna throw me off my game.
You'll adjust.
I'm filing for a transfer.
Dutch.
No, I'm serious.
Things haven't been
the same between us,
even before you got captain.
There is no reason why we can't
work this out in a new way.
DUTCH: The only reason I was
hanging around here was
because we were partners.
And that's gone.
I'd just like to move on.
Okay, I'll prepare the paperwork.
BILLINGS: Okay, check this out.
Tori has an M.B.A. from UCLA.
Worked as an account manager
at a brokerage firm until she
was fired six months ago.
PAULA:
Excuse me, captain.
This guy is here for Tori Burke.
I'm her legal counsel.
What are your credentials,
Mr. Wallis, Esquire?
What I have is a client, and I
need to see her immediately.
Now, do I get to see her now,
or do I file for a dismissal?
She's in 2. Show him up.
PAULA: Yes, ma'am.
I'll check him out.
RONNIE:
Gallagher's DEA bozos are
tied up on a sting in Compton.
They're a little short on cars.
Maybe in a few hours.
We can't wait that long.
We gotta meet Lem.
What about backups from the Barn?
There's a manhunt on Curson.
Byz Lats shot a grocery clerk
and there's no units to spare.
We gotta go in.
There are six of them at least.
We don't know how
many more inside.
And Lem's gonna be waiting on us.
Who's coming?
[LATIN MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO]
VIC: Get down! Down on the ground!
SHANE: Get on the ground!
Don't move! Get down on your knees!
Hands on your head!
I got rabbits!
VIC: Let them run.
Get up! Let's go.
VIC: You all right?
RONNIE: Yeah.
On the ground.
On the ground right now.
VIC:
Search it.
SHANE:
Christ.
How many grenades
do these guys got?
Claudette's so hot for these guys,
she can book them herself.
We gotta go get Lem.
Bomb Squad's on a crank call at
some Westside abortion clinic.
They'll pick up the grenades later.
I told you to call in every move.
You were outnumbered three to one.
They were getting ready to bolt.
Split up in two vans.
We had no choice.
GALLAGHER:
Sorry we missed all the action.
Good work.
Just wish we were able
to nail Guardo.
He's been staying off
the front lines these days,
probably feeling the heat
from you guys.
Two busts in as many weeks?
He's feeling your heat.
And I've seen what they do
when they get pissed.
Better watch your Crown Vics.
You should be warning him, not me.
Thanks.
Glad you caught the guys.
Actually, we didn't nail Guardo.
I'll see if I can find something out.
You find another tip,
find another buyer.
Please don't be this way.
I'm sorry I made that deal,
helped Kavanaugh.
You should go.
I did it for Sebastio.
You'd do the same thing for
your kids too, I know you would.
Hey, take your rat money,
your retarded rat-baby kid
and get on the first bus...
Don't you say that about my boy!
What, you gonna let him talk
about Sebastio that way?
[EMOLIA GASPS]
I showed you mercy once
and it ruined my friend's life.
Not gonna happen again.
Get out.
The Police Committee is
willing to consider a deal,
but like I thought, they insist
on adding more time.
How much?
ACEVEDA: Maximum of 10 years,
with parole in four if he turns
himself in immediately.
What about the safety issue?
He'll be held in protective custody
until it's all sorted out.
But there's no guarantee of location
unless you can prove your claims.
What about the others?
No condition about him
giving us something on them?
ACEVEDA:
We wanna put this behind us.
Now, if he's caught before
he comes in, all bets are off.
What's going on, man?
What was that?
It wasn't my choice.
It's what the Police
Committee wanted.
If we don't find Lemansky
before he comes in or he
gets out of the country,
we're gonna lose our
last chance at nailing Vic
before this case seals off.
What do you want me to do, Jon?
He trusts you now, right?
When it comes to me?
Maybe.
I want you to scare them.
I want you to make
Vic lead us to him.
How?
The way to get him is we
gotta catch him in the act.
With Lemansky AWOL, Vic knows
he's got eyes and ears all over him.
He's not gonna do
anything stupid.
Unless he thinks he's got
one last mess to clean up.
What mess?
There was a detective I spoke to here.
He suspects that the Strike Team
robbed an Armenian money train.
Wagenbach.
Yeah, but he doesn't
know it was Dutch.
You gotta make him believe
that Lemansky gave it up
for witness protection.
It'll put him in motion.
We follow, we catch them trying
to help Lemansky escape.
And nail them for
harbouring a fugitive.
It won't be the amount of time that
they deserve, but it'll be enough time
to make them lose their badges
and get them off the street.
Catching them in the act,
that's gonna gives us leverage.
Lemansky, he may have held
his tongue, but the other ones,
they might not be as strong.
Lemansky's talking.
That's bullshit.
Is the Armenian
money train bullshit?
Because that's what he gave
them. He's coming clean.
There's nothing to come clean about.
That explains where your 65,000
unaccounted-for dollars comes from.
Look, he's tired, he's scared
and he wants his freedom.
And he doesn't wanna die at
the hands of Antwon Mitchell.
The DA said he's gotta give them
something on the team.
I guess he's agreed.
Lem would never agree to that.
DA gave him no choice.
He has to give you guys up.
And now all this bullshit
could blow back on me.
Now, you gotta get a
message to your boy and
tell him to shut the hell up.
Can you do that? Hm?
If you can speak to him, can you
convince him to keep his mouth shut?
Yes.
Do it, for chrissake.
I don't know where he is.
You know, Kavanaugh
is out of control,
but with Lemansky unaccounted for,
he's got the chief's ear.
And now the DA's smelling
blood, all of ours.
I shouldn't be telling you any
of this, but you threatened me.
So now I've told you
everything I know.
Now it's time to clean this up.
You guys just see
pimp and hooker.
That's not who we are.
Yeah. Says the hooker
letting pimp daddy drag her
into the shit with him.
TORl:
No, actually he dragged me out.
He dragged me out of
the steaming shit piles
of a superficial,
empty everything.
And then he hosed me off,
and he held me, and he
made me whole.
I had nothing. I was nothing
before I met him.
According to your sister,
you had a pretty nice condo.
You equate a roof over
your head to love?
What exactly does equal love?
Do you see the wrinkles on my face?
Do you see them?
Yes.
Well, Spank doesn't.
I understand you not wanting to
be away from your, uh, boyfriend.
But what do you think's gonna
happen when you go to jail?
Because we both know that your
man's just gonna set his sights
on the next piece of Century City
ass that comes his way.
Shut your mouth!
Shut your goddamn mouth!
Who do you think you are?
You don't know us!
Get her off me, Dutch. Get her off me.
How dare you?
No, no. Now, let's just sit down.
You don't know me.
DUTCH: Sit down. Let's sit down.
Let go of me.
The girl just gave you up.
Says it was all your idea and you're
the one who beat up the john.
[CHUCKLING]
I know that didn't happen.
Ooh! She put the claws
in you, right?
Shouldn't let no woman
do you like that.
Someone like Tori.
Smart, educated, good job.
How do you turn out a girl like that?
Any punk can get some
crack ho to go down on dick.
But how do I get a little pink toe
from Westwood to do what I say,
whenever I say?
Every chick's got
a hole in her heart
and it's connected to
the one between her legs.
I just figure out how to fill it.
And then I feed it to her.
And I keep feeding it to her,
until it's overflowing.
Until she can't live without it.
And then I take it away.
That makes me God.
Tori was easy.
Her fiancé left her last year
for some young blood bitch.
I just kept telling old girl
she was still the prom queen,
like back in the day.
And that white faggot dude,
he didn't have eyes to see.
Sooner or later, all bitches break.
Every goddamn one.
That's if you got game.
And that's why she's your whore?
If you born a woman,
I can make you my ho.
Which is why she's saying I had
nothing to do with no illegal shit.
Now that y'all got some
pimpology, no charge,
my black ass is out of here, right?
Anyone here believe
Lem cut a deal?
Maybe he felt like he had no choice.
He's out there in the wind alone.
Becca's probably pushing it.
He has no idea about this
ranch in San Ignacio,
or the money we're gonna
be funnelling to him.
Becca told you he took a deal?
No, Aceveda.
RONNIE: Aceveda?
He's got a stake in this too.
Not like we do.
Man, he could be full of shit.
The truth is, we can't know
what's inside Lem's head
until we see him face to face.
RONNIE:
We need an exit strategy.
How are gonna get out of this?
We don't need an exit strategy.
We need to fill Lem in,
on the cash, the ranch,
the lines of communication.
He's right. You know, Lem,
he's been in the dark
as much as we've been.
And if Lem is talking,
it's because he believes
that Antwon has marked him
as a dead man behind bars.
Now, once he knows what
we've pulled together for him,
he'll go along.
He will.
We go to the spot.
If he doesn't show,
assume he made the deal.
RONNIE:
And then what?
SHANE:
If he does show,
then we'll take his temperature,
make sure he's still solidly on board.
He'll be on board.
Lem trusts us.
He trusts us.
And I still trust Lem.
I do.
COP 1: Need to do the paperwork?
COP 2: Yeah.
Where's Vendrell?
KYLE:
Shit, they're taking different cars.
I'll take Mackey.
You take Gardocki.
All right.
KAVANAUGH:
Kyle, keep your distance.
Okay.
Ronnie, I got a tail.
I'm trying to lose him.
You sure?
He's pretty far back, but he's there.
Watch your back, man.
Looks like I got one too.
Call Shane.
Give him a heads-up.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yeah.
Vic and I both have tails.
Shit. I'm looking.
We gotta lose them without
looking lik e we're trying to
lose them. Tak e your time.
We can't lead Kavanaugh to Lem.
SHANE:
I don't see anyone on me yet.
Vic says whoever loses
his tail first gets to Lem,
moves him someplace safe
until we can all regroup.
SHANE: All right, I got it.
[TRUCK APPROACHING]
SHANE: Hey.
Jesus, man. I'm glad it's you.
SHANE: Hey, man. Hey.
What's up?
Look, man, we gotta get out of here.
What's going on?
Kavanaugh's got a tail on
Vic and Ronnie. Could have
an eye up in the sky.
Follow me. That, uh... The old
body shop that closed down.
The one on Mission, okay?
All right, man.
Never thought it'd come to this.
Hasn't come to anything yet.
What now?
I'll go back and get Vic and Ronnie.
We got a way for you
to get to Mexico.
What, like Gilroy?
No, man. The man died alone.
I'm not going that route.
Look, you're not a miserable drunk.
It's gonna be different.
No, it won't.
It won't.
Look, I'm not going.
No more running.
So you'll spend the rest of
your life looking over your
shoulder for Antwon Mitchell?
I mean, you in Mexico's the only
thing that keeps us all safe, man.
Especially you.
How the hell am I gonna
live in Mexico? Tell me.
We got it all figured out.
How?
San Ignacio.
What the hell is that,
some shit hole?
No, man, it's a ranch.
Up in the mountains. We got a
Federale that's gonna get you there.
It's beautiful, man.
It's gonna be peaceful.
We got money parked
in an account for you.
It's all set up.
Mara and I even kicked in
5 grand for you.
I don't want that.
It's just a start.
We'll keep skimming off the street.
Man, we'll keep you hooked up.
I can't. I can't. I can't do that.
It's all in play.
Trust me, man, it's gonna work.
It's gonna work.
There's a way for me
to take the hit solo.
No, there's not, man.
There is.
Kavanaugh? Aceveda? The DA?
There's no other deal to make.
They're gonna make you give us up.
Maybe not now.
Maybe a year from now.
But, man, you got one chance
to get out of here.
Take it, man. Take that
chance right now. Take it.
I got it figured out.
I mean, why did you even
come back here tonight if you
weren't planning on leaving?
Dude, I came to see you guys.
Don't do this, man.
Look, where's Vic?
I wanna talk to Vic.
He'll call when he loses his tail.
We can't let Kavanaugh
catch us with you, man.
[SIGHS]
Mara's pregnant again.
LEM:
No shit?
Yeah, yeah, almost, uh...
Almost three months.
I wasn't supposed to say anything
to anybody until next week, but, uh...
Hey, congratulations. Hey.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's another mouth to feed.
Mara's gonna be laid up near
the end, so I'm gonna have to...
I have to step it up, you know?
Man, I hope I get to
see the little guy.
Or girl.
Little girl, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, a little girl.
Hey, I'm gonna be all right.
Shane.
Yeah?
I'm gonna be all right.
It's all about family, right?
[SIRENS WAILING
IN THE DISTANCE]
[SIRENS FADE]
Look, what if Vic and Ronnie
can't shake the tail?
Maybe they doubled back to the Barn.
I'II, uh... I'll go check it out, all right?
Move your car.
Get it out of sight.
Did you get enough to eat today?
No, man, I'm hungry.
I bought you some food.
Thanks.
[LEM CHUCKLES]
Thanks, man.
Ha-ha. My favourite, buddy.
Shane? Shane!
[SHANE COUGHS]
[SOBS]
I'm sorry.
Shane...
I'm sorry, buddy.
I'm so sorry, buddy.
[SHANE SOBBING]
Lem.
Lem, I'm sorry!
But I had to, right?
But you know I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, man.
Buddy.
Oh, God!
Hey.
I, uh... I had a tail.
Took me a while to shake it.
VIC: Yeah.
SHANE:
Lem hasn't shown, huh?
He's late,
but he'll be here.
Hey. It's your lucky day.
Cab driver can't ID you,
she won't testify against you.
Only thing to testify about is
my love for that girl right there.
I'm getting you out
of here soon, baby.
Yeah, get yourself out of here.
Take him out, will you?
COP: Let's go.
Dutch, I spoke to your
ex-partner, the new captain.
She says she trusts your instincts,
so she wants me to increase
the number of hours I trail you.
I just wanted to say thank you
for putting in a good word.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Hey. Um...
You know why you're gonna be
such a great detective someday?
Because most people don't realise
how damn smart you are.
They just see the surface.
They can't get past your looks
to see what you're really about.
I know, right?
But you're not nearly as
smart as you need to be.
The help I'm offering doesn't
come along every day.
And if I'm gonna spend my
valuable time focusing it on you,
well, you better make it
worth my while.
Sure. Definitely. Of course.
TINA: What's going on?
DUTCH: I don't know.
COP:
Officer down.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Your transfer's denied.
I need my best detective on this.
DUTCH:
Grenades.
The thing this morning.
The El Salvadorans.
The leader's missing.
His name is Guardo. Start there.
[SOBBING]
Oh, my God.
TINA [SOBBING]:
[TINA MUMBLING AND SOBBING]
DUTCH:
Vic. Vic, you can't touch anything.
KAVANAUGH:
You happy?
Are you happy now,
Detective Mackey?
[VIC YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
TINA:
Stop it! Stop!
Break them up.
COP 1:
Come on.
Lieutenant.
That's enough, come on.
Come on.
COP 2: Come on, lieutenant.
COP 1: Let him go.
COP 2: Break it up. Come on. Let's go.
[VIC YELLING]
SHANE:
Get off of him. Move.
Get off. We got him.
COP 1: Come on.
COP 3: It's over. It's over.
SHANE: It's all right.
[VIC YELLING]
COP 2:
Lieutenant, let's go.
Breathe. Calm down.
Calm down.
Okay. Okay.
We're gonna find out who did this
and we're gonna kill him.
[###]