[dramatic music echoing]
[owl hooting]
[Jonathan] I'm sorry. I'm having trouble
understanding any of this.
I mean, what exactly is going on
in Hawkins? What's doing these killings?
-That's what we're trying to ascertain.
-Where is El, like, right now?
-For her safety, it's best you don't know.
-This is insane! This is insane!
So this training to get El's powers back,
how long is it gonna take?
-Could take weeks, could take months.
-Months?
Until then, agents Harmon and Wallace
will stay with you.
We're not in danger.
Our friends live in Hawkins.
My family lives in Hawkins.
I'll work to contain the situation
until Eleven is ready.
In the meantime, it is of vital importance
you do not speak to anyone about this.
[scoffs] No. No way.
-I know this is difficult to understand.
-It's not difficult. This is impossible.
There are factions within our government
who are working directly against Eleven,
who are, in fact,
searching for her as we speak.
We can't risk contact.
If they learned about any of this,
it will jeopardize Eleven.
And if Eleven is jeopardized,
so are your friends.
And so is your family.
[scoffs] So, what? We're just supposed
to trust that you're the good guys?
Whoever you are?
We're friends of Owens.
[dramatic music continues]
Eleven trusted us.
Now we're asking the same from you.
For you.
[Jonathan sighs]
[Will sighs heavily]
[door slams]
[dramatic music continues]
[tires screech]
[dramatic music builds]
[Max] It was here.
Right here.
A grandfather clock?
-[clock chiming]
-[audio distortion]
It was so real.
[clock ticking, chiming]
[Max] And then,
when I got closer, suddenly I just…
-[Dustin] Max, come on.
-[Steve] Max?
…I woke up.
[eerie audio distortion]
[panting]
[Dustin] It was like
she was in a trance or something.
Exactly what Eddie said
happened to Chrissy.
That's not even the bad part.
Fred and Chrissy,
they both came to Miss Kelley for help.
Uh, they both were having headaches,
bad headaches
that wouldn't go away. And then…
then the nightmares.
Trouble sleeping.
They'd wake up in a cold sweat.
Then they started seeing things.
[unsettling rustling]
[screaming echoes]
Bad things.
From their pasts.
[moans]
These visions, they just…
they kept on getting worse and worse,
until eventually…
everything ended.
[police radio chatter]
[police sirens ringing]
Vecna's curse.
Chrissy's headache started a week ago.
Fred's, six days ago.
I've been having them for five days.
I don't know how long I have.
All I know is that,
for Fred and Chrissy,
they both died less than 24 hours
after their first vision.
And I just saw that goddamn clock, so…
[Max breathes shakily]
…looks like I'm gonna die tomorrow.
[distant clang]
Stay here.
[lamp clattering]
[uneasy music playing]
[distant clattering]
[footsteps approaching rapidly]
[all yelling]
-It's me!
-Lucas?
-It's me.
-Jesus, what's wrong with you?
-I'm sorry.
-I could've taken you out with this lamp!
[panting] Sorry, guys. Sorry.
I was… I was biking for eight miles.
[grunts, pants]
[panting] Give me a second. Shit.
-We've got a code red.
-What?
[intense music playing]
Dustin.
I've been with Jason, Patrick, and Andy,
and they've gone totally off the rails.
They're trying to capture Eddie,
and they think you know where he is.
You're in terrible danger.
All right. Yeah, that definitely sucks,
but we've got bigger problems
than Jason now.
[clock chiming]
[clock ticking and chiming]
[intense music builds to climax]
[opening theme music playing]
[inquisitive synth music playing]
[doorbell rings]
-[Mrs. Sinclair] Would you get the door?
-I'm busy!
[Mrs. Sinclair] I said get the door.
This is unbelievable.
Hey there. Is, uh, is Lucas home?
Negative.
You know where he is? [chuckles]
Uh, we're just…
We were supposed to go out and--
Go out? I see he's taken
a step down from Max.
-[door slams]
-[menacing music playing]
[chuckles] I'm sorry.
Uh, well, you're the little sister
who plays Dungeons & Dragons, huh?
What's it to you?
Do you know Dustin Henderson?
Know him? I've bled with him.
Chances are,
he's with your cheater boyfriend.
Oh, if and when you do find Lucas,
please tell him I've been
covering for his ass for two days now.
Each day of covering
costs ten bucks, with a DPR.
That's a daily percentage rate of 7.9%.
Another week of this
and he's buying me a goddamn Nintendo,
with Duck Hunt.
Where the hell's Sinclair?
That's what we're about to find out.
We've been tricked, boys.
[tires screech]
[Steve grumbles]
Okay, be honest. Uh…
You guys understand any of this?
-No.
-Pretty straightforward.
Oh, straightforward, really?
What's confusing to you?
So far, everyone Vecna
has cursed has died,
except for this old Victor Creel dude
Nancy found.
He's the only known survivor.
If anyone knows
how to beat this curse, it's him.
That's assuming he was cursed,
which we don't even know.
How can Vecna have existed in the '50s?
It doesn't make sense.
Far as we know,
Eleven didn't create the Upside Down.
She opened a gate to it.
The Upside Down has probably been around
for thousands of years. Millions.
I wouldn't be surprised
if it predated the dinosaurs.
-Dinosaurs? What are we--
-[Lucas] Okay.
But if a gate didn't exist in the '50s,
how did Vecna get through?
-How's he getting through now?
-[Lucas] And why now?
And why then? Just pops out in the '50s,
kills one family,
and he's like, "I'm good."
And poof, he just disappears. Just… gone?
Only to return 30 years later
and start killing random teens?
No, I don't buy it.
[exhales, sighs]
Straightforward, my ass.
Honestly, Henderson, a little humility
now and then, it wouldn't hurt you.
Sorry.
[delicate, intense music playing]
Any idea what she's writing?
[Dustin] Did she sleep?
I mean,
would you?
[door opens]
[footsteps descending stairs]
Okay, so…
-[Robin sighs]
-…we have a plan.
[music continues]
[Robin] Thanks to Nancy's minions,
we are now rock-star psychology students
at the University of Notre Dame.
-I'm now Ruth.
-And I'm Rose.
Ruth?
Nice GPA.
[Nancy] Thanks.
So we called Pennhurst Asylum,
told them we'd like to speak with Creel
for a thesis we're co-writing
on paranoid schizophrenics--
To which they said no.
But we landed
a three o'clock with the director.
Now all we have to do is charm him
and convince him to let us talk to Victor.
Then maybe we can rid Max of this curse.
[Steve] About that.
We've been doing
our Victor Creel homework, and, uh…
[sighs] …we got some questions.
Lots of questions.
So do we.
Hopefully, Victor has the answers.
Wait… Wait… Wait a second. Uh…
Where's mine?
[dramatic music builds, halts]
Nancy, you're outta your mind
if you think I'm babysitting again.
First, they're not babies anymore.
And Max is in real danger.
-She needs people around her.
-I know. But why me?
Oh my God, you have a Tom Cruise poster.
You have a Tom Cruise poster.
That's old.
-It's just…
-[Robin laughs]
-Can you please not touch anything?
-I can't do anything here, Nance.
Maybe I can be helpful
with this asylum director dude.
I don't know.
I could turn on my… my charm.
-Not the charm we need.
-Ouch.
No, I just… [sighs]
I did a little digging last night,
and it turns out this Dr. Hatch
is a distinguished fellow
of the American Psychiatric Association
and a Harvard visiting scholar, okay?
This is a lifelong student of the world.
If we're gonna win him over,
we're gonna have to convince him
we are too.
That, like him…
-[music box playing]
-…we are true academic scholars.
[whispers] Holy shit.
There's a little ballerina in here.
Academic scholar? She's giving you
an academic scholar vibe? Yeah.
-No, but…
-[Robyn sighs]
…she will.
Oh, please, tell me you're joking.
[truck horn blares]
[Joyce] It's busy. It's still busy.
Did I do something wrong?
It says dial one, then the number, which--
-You can check on your kids later.
-I don't understand why it's still busy.
Joyce, there are certain things
one can be late to in life.
A dentist's appointment.
A one-year-old's birthday party,
because who cares?
Little idiot's not gonna remember it.
But for what is essentially
a ransom exchange,
for that, for that,
I think you very much need to be
on time.
I'm sorry. I'm very tense.
Clearly.
[grandiose Russian music playing]
[music continues over speakers]
[dog barking]
[Antonov] Head west, through forest.
You will see a church with a gray roof.
Wait inside. Yuri will meet you there.
So you heard from her?
Yeah, they arrived last night.
They're meeting Yuri soon.
If all goes well,
by tomorrow night you're home,
eating Enzo's with your sexy woman.
She's not my woman.
Of course not.
She saves your life because of friendship.
[guard speaks in Russian]
[Antonov] Look, American,
do not put too much hope into this dream.
I have thought long about this,
and I give you odds of success
fifty to one.
[tense music playing]
You don't even seem nervous, American.
I'm impressed.
You're a cool cat.
Like Steve McQueen. The Cooler King. Yeah?
-[chuckles]
-Let's hope not.
Of course not,
because Cooler King went back to cooler.
So, you must be better than McQueen today.
I change mind.
Now I give you odds
a hundred to one.
Our nosy friend again.
Where do you want it?
Just not my face.
Of course not.
Must be pretty for your woman.
She's not my woman. [grunts]
[Antonov speaking in Russian]
-[Antonov speaking in Russian]
-[dogs barking]
[Antonov speaking in Russian]
[tense music continues]
[music crescendos]
[announcer in English] Amazing you can get
this many people and have it this quiet.
Keep in mind that…
Where are you going?
[scoffs] I'm just getting something
to drink.
Is that allowed or…
How does this house arrest work?
You're not under arrest.
Right.
No, no, you're… you're here to protect us.
And watch TV, apparently.
[mid-tempo synth music playing]
[sighs]
[music swells]
[indistinct chatter from TV]
[applause from TV]
[sighs] I… I mean, I don't think
they've thought this through.
If this goes on for a month, or months,
and people can't get a hold of us,
they're gonna totally freak out.
Meanwhile, my mom's
probably having a panic attack.
And what about Hawkins?
That lady's supposed
to keep it "contained."
Like you can contain any of this
without El. I mean…
Yeah.
[sighs]
If you keep staring at that,
it's not gonna change. You know?
-Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
-[paper crumples]
-[Will sighs]
-[emotional synth music playing]
Before the cops came,
me and El, we… we had a bad fight.
We never fight.
I mean, we fought before,
but just, like,
silly fights, stupid fights.
But, I don't know,
this one just felt more adult.
Like, it… it just felt more real.
Like, a fight you can't come back from.
Maybe I should've said something,
and if I would've said that thing,
then maybe she'd want me there with her,
wherever she is.
No. Look, Mike,
you're gonna see her again,
and whatever you didn't say,
you can say it to her then.
Okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
She's gonna be okay.
She's not in Hawkins.
That's what we should be worrying about.
You don't trust Owens?
No. I don't know.
I mean,
he's been good to us and good to El,
but he wasn't able to protect me.
That was you guys who saved me.
That was you guys.
[sighs] Looks like
it's gonna be up to us again.
It always is, isn't it?
[laughs]
[Jonathan] Which is why
we can't stay here.
[determined synth music playing]
Listen,
let's assume these friends of Owens
are telling the truth.
We can't call Hawkins
without alerting the military,
putting El in danger.
Fine. Then we'll just go to them.
-Go to Hawkins?
-How?
What are you worried about?
Ponch and Jon out there?
They're half-asleep now watching golf.
No, Jonathan. I mean,
we don't have a car or money.
Then we'll hail ourselves a ride.
A cheap one.
[music pulses]
[indistinct TV commentary]
Excuse me, sir?
[sighs]
What?
We're hungry.
I could eat.
[surfer rock music playing]
[bell rings]
[phone ringing]
Surf's up. Surfer Boy Pizza,
this is Argyle speaking.
We make everything fresh here
at Surfer Boy except for our pineapple,
which comes from a can.
But I still highly recommend slapping
some juicy pineapple on your pie.
Oh, fruit on your pizza's gnarly, you say?
Well, I say try before you deny. [laughs]
Hello?
[surfer rock fades]
[sighs]
-I know you guys are staring at me.
-What, sorry?
-You said you needed something?
-Just hanging out.
How you think your eyes
boring into the back of my head
is protecting me from Vecna, I don't know.
-You can look at me now.
-Thank you. Sorry.
-Sorry.
[Max sighs]
For you.
And, um, you.
Oh, and, um,
give these to Mike, El, and Will.
If you can ever get a hold of them again.
What are you doing? No, don't.
That's not for now. Don't open it now.
Don't… Okay.
[letters rustling]
I'm sorry. What is this?
It's, um…
it's a fail-safe.
For after.
-[distressing music playing]
-If things don't work out.
Wait, whoa.
Max, things are gonna work out.
No!
No, I don't need you to reassure me
and tell me it's all gonna work out.
People have been telling me that
my entire life and it's almost never true.
It's never true.
I mean, of course this asshole curses me.
Should've seen that one coming.
[distressing music continues]
[inhales deeply]
If we go to East Hawkins,
will this reach Pennhurst?
-Of course. Yeah.
-Why are we talking about East Hawkins?
[distressing music intensifies]
No. No. No!
Max, Max. Seriously.
Seriously, I'm not joking.
I'm not driving you anywhere.
If you think I'm going to spend
what is likely the last day of my life
in the armpit
that is Mike Wheeler's basement,
you're out of your mind.
Either take me where I need to go
or tie me down,
which is technically
kidnapping of a minor.
And if I live to see another day, Steve,
I swear to God, I will prosecute.
[determined music playing]
Open the door.
Uh, no.
I know a good lawyer.
[scoffs]
Henderson, that super walkie of yours
better reach Pennhurst.
-[clock chimes]
-[engine turns over]
[sinister music playing]
[chiming continues]
[sinister music swells]
[eerie music playing]
[Robin grunting]
I can't breathe in this thing,
and I'm itchy. I'm itching all over.
It's not all about comfort.
Okay? We're academics.
Who are evidently coming
straight from Easter brunch.
Also, this bra that you gave me
is really pinching my boobs.
Okay. Could you just let me
do the talking? If that's even possible?
It's not only possible, it's inevitable.
Because shortly,
I'll be dead from strangulation.
3.9 GPAs.
Both of you.
Impressive.
And this is a recommendation
from Professor Brantley.
Yeah, I know Larry. Quite well, actually.
Eh, you know what they say.
"Those who can't do, teach."
[Robin, Hatch chuckling]
Uh, yes, yes,
that's actually why we're here.
I mean, we can only
learn so much in a classroom.
Mmm.
And I'm sympathetic
to your struggle, truly.
But there is a protocol
to visiting a patient like Victor.
You put in a request
and then undergo a screening process,
at which point
the board will make a decision.
I can see you're disappointed.
[Hatch inhales]
But I'm more than happy
to give you a tour.
Perhaps you can even speak
to some patients in our low-security wing.
And we'd… we would love that.
It's just that, um… [clicks tongue]
…our thesis is due next month.
And you're out of time.
Whose fault is that?
Ours. Absolutely.
And I do apologize--
Don't apologize, Ruth. Screw that.
The fact is, we did put in a request
months ago and were denied.
And then we reapplied
and were denied again.
And coming here was
our last-ditch effort to save our thesis.
And I really…
I can't breathe in this thing.
Well, Rose, maybe you'd like
to go outside and get some air.
-Maybe I should, Ruth.
-Mm-hmm.
Because I'm starting to think
this whole thing is a colossal mistake.
I'm breaking out in a rash.
My boobs hurt.
And I'll tell you the truth, Anthony.
May I call you Anthony?
These aren't my clothes.
I borrowed them
because I wanted you to take us seriously.
Because nobody takes girls seriously
in this field. They just don't.
We don't look the part or whatever.
But can I tell you a story?
-[inspirational music playing]
-1978, I was at summer camp.
And my counselor Drew
told me and everyone in Cabin C
the true story
of the Victor Creel Massacre.
And little Petey McHew…
You know Petey, right, Ruth?
Of… Of course.
Yeah. Little Petey McHew
started sobbing right there on the spot.
Full-on hyperventilating.
The other campers
couldn't sleep for weeks.
I couldn't either,
but not 'cause I was scared.
Because I was obsessed with the question,
"What would drive a human being
to commit such unimaginable acts?"
Other kids wanted to be astronauts,
basketball players, rock stars.
But I wanted to be you.
I wanted to be you.
So, forgive me if I'll now
try anything in my power,
including wearing this ridiculous outfit,
if I might get to speak to the man
that ignited my passion
and learn a little more
about how his twisted, but let's face it,
totally fascinating mind works.
So, yes, we don't
have the official paperwork,
but don't tell me
that cry-baby Petey McHew
wouldn't have gotten
an audience with Victor in moments
if he'd asked politely,
because you and I both know that he would.
[music trails]
[Robin] So… ten minutes with Victor.
That's all I ask.
I'm back in 30.
-[secretary] Mm-hmm.
-[dramatic music swells]
If things go sideways, I should mention
I'm now a black belt in karate.
Hello?
[Joyce] Hello?
[tense music playing]
[Murray] Hello?
-Hello--
-[welding sparks crackle]
[tense music swells]
Who are you?
I… Uh… We're looking for Yuri.
Why do you need to see Yuri?
It's actually, uh--
It's a private matter. Is Yuri here?
I'm sorry.
I don't know how to tell you this,
but you're a day late.
-What?
-You see damage to this hull?
Yuri was on sightseeing trip
to see polar bears.
And then bears got into plane
and pull him out of cockpit and kill Yuri.
-No.
-Yeah.
And he loved bears.
They broke his heart.
Or rather punctured it
with their bear claws.
[grunts, imitates bears snarling]
[tense music stops]
[laughs]
-[Joyce grunts]
-I got you. I got you good.
[laughs]
I'm Yuri. I'm Yuri.
-Oh.
-[chuckles] Oh.
-Uh, you… you must be Joycey?
-Just Joyce.
-And you are?
-Murray.
-Murray?
-Yeah.
Yuri. Yuri, Murray, Yuri, Murray.
[laughs] We rhyme.
Yeah. I hear it. [Murray laughs weakly]
[Yuri chortling]
[mysterious music playing]
Forty thousand American dollars,
as promised.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
I love the smell of cash in morning.
-[chuckles]
-Right.
I hope you do not mind if I count.
You two seem very nice,
very trustworthy people.
But so did my brother
before he stole my wife!
[wheezing laughter]
[Joyce and Murray laugh nervously]
Poor bird, you're freezing.
Please, have some coffee. Still hot.
This could be a while [chortles]
[clang]
[in Russian] Why are you staring at me?
Huh? I am asking you!
Move, bastard!
-[handle snaps]
-[grunts, pants]
[hammers clanging]
[exhales heavily]
Crazy American.
[foreboding music playing]
[chains rattling]
Hey! Get back! Get back!
Get back!
Broken…
Cannot work.
Stay there.
[Hopper mutters indistinctly]
[dramatic music playing]
[Hopper whistles]
-[guard grunts]
-[clattering]
[prisoner grunts]
Where is the American?!
[tense music building]
[indistinct yelling in Russian]
[clattering]
[breathing heavily]
[restrained grunt]
[bone crunching]
Watch your back, American...
[grunting in pain]
[panting]
[strained grunt]
Where do you think you're going, American?
Stand.
Stand up!
Hands.
Hands!
-[chains rattling]
-[guard grunting]
-[Hopper grunts]
-[guard groans]
[both grunting, struggling]
[yelling]
[guard choking]
[guard cursing in Russian]
[both grunting]
[weapons clattering]
[yelling]
[gunfire]
[music swells ominously]
[guards, prisoners yelling]
[guard] Tool shed!
It came from the tool shed!
Open up!
Open the door!
Keep pushing! Hurry!
[guards clamoring]
[guards yelling indistinctly]
RUN!
[tense music builds]
-[explosion gushes]
-[ominous music swells]
There!
[engine revs]
We can't let him get to the tree line!
[gunfire]
[tense music subsides]
[cheering]
[in English] A hundred to one.
Son of a bitch.
["Hard Feelings" by Al Kerbey
playing on radio]
♪ You talk a lot, but you don't say much
In the things you do ♪
♪ You're always right ♪
♪ In all our fights ♪
♪ Because no one else can shut you down ♪
♪ Or turn you around
You should see yourself ♪
-This better be fast, Mayfield.
-Twenty seconds.
That thing's got batteries in it, right?
I'm not even answering that question.
-Yes, it has batteries.
-Yeah, I got it.
[dog barking in distance]
[breathes shakily]
[poignant music playing]
Mom.
Hey, sweetie. I thought
you were with your friends today.
Yeah, I… I was. I am.
Shouldn't you be at work?
Oh, Mr. Bradley let me off early.
So I'm just catching up on some chores.
Um, I… I left some letters inside.
For you and… and Granny and Uncle Jack.
And Dad.
If you can find him.
Letters? I… I don't understand.
Uh,
I just… um…
With all the murders and everything, I…
I know it's stupid,
but I just started to think,
"What if something happens to me?"
Max, baby,
nothing is going to happen to you.
I know. But if… if it did, I just…
There's so many things that I want to say,
that I need to say. And…
-Promise you'll give the letters out?
-Max, you're scaring me.
-I'm not trying to scare you.
-Is something going on?
-No.
-[shakily] Is it, baby?
No. No, you're right.
I'm sure I'll be fine. I'm being silly.
Max. Oh, sweetie.
[Max's mother] Shh.
It's okay.
-Nothing is going to happen, baby.
-[Max sniffles]
I promise.
-[distant rumbling]
-[sinister vocalizing]
Nothing you don't deserve.
[sky rumbling]
[sinister music playing]
[ominous bell tolling]
Mom, let go of me.
Mom? Let go.
[Vecna] Maxine.
You think some letters
are going to make things right?
You've broken everything.
[echoing] Billy!
[Vecna] Your time
is almost at an end.
Let go!
[chimes]
[grunts]
[panting]
[sinister music fades]
Hey, that was longer than 20 seconds.
Hey, whoa, whoa. You all right?
I'm fine. Just drive.
-[Dustin] Did something happen?
-Can we please just go?
These are our gardens.
Beautiful, aren't they?
We allow them two hours
of outside time a day.
[Robin] Can't they just escape?
[Hatch] They could.
But the vast majority choose to be here.
They like it here.
[delicate classical music playing]
This is one of our more popular areas.
The listening room.
We found that music has
a particularly calming effect
on the broken mind.
The right song,
particularly one which holds
some personal meaning,
can prove a salient stimulus.
But there are those who are
beyond a cure.
[door slam echoes]
Uh, Dr. Hatch, do you think
it might be possible for us
to speak to Victor alone?
Alone?
I… I think that we would just love
the challenge of speaking with Victor
without the safety net
of an expert such as yourself.
Then we could really rub it in
Professor Bradley's face.
Professor Bradley? I don't believe
I know a Professor Bradley.
Brantley.
She… she meant to say Brantley.
Didn't I say Brantley? What did I say?
Sorry, silly me.
Words, letters. [chuckles]
Guess I'm just nervous. I mean, excited.
So excited to speak with Victor.
Preferably, as she said, alone?
[ominous music playing]
Yes.
Why not?
You've caught me in a rebellious mood.
[both chuckle]
And there's something rather urgent
I need to check on anyway, so…
Sure.
Keep a close eye on them.
-Thank you so much, Dr. Hatch.
-Thank you.
[Robin sighs]
-[key rattling]
-[door opening]
[door grinds open]
[patients clamoring]
Do not startle him.
Do not touch him.
Do not pass him anything.
Stand five feet away from the bars
at all times.
[patient] Get away.
Is that clear?
-Yes, sir.
[bars clanging]
Victor.
Today's your lucky day!
You got visitors.
Real pretty ones.
[scratching]
Must be in one of his moods.
Have fun.
[foreboding music playing]
[guttural growling, snarling]
[Nancy] Victor?
My name is Nancy.
Nancy Wheeler.
And this is…
Robin Buckley.
[Nancy] Um, we have some questions.
I don't talk to reporters.
Hatch knows that.
We're not reporters.
We're here because… we believe you.
And because
we need your help.
Whatever killed your family,
we think it's back.
[nails scraping]
[chilling musical sting]
["Pass the Dutchie"
by Musical Youth playing]
♪ Pass the Dutchie
'Pon the left-hand side ♪
♪ It a go bun ♪
♪ Give me the music
Make me jump and prance ♪
♪ It a go dung ♪
♪ Give me the music ♪
-You're packed already?
-Yeah, I mean, I never really unpacked.
[clicks tongue] Thanks, by the way.
For what?
For knocking some sense into me.
I was being a total self-pitying idiot.
Oh, I didn't say it.
You didn't have to. [chuckles]
[emotional, tender music playing]
Hey, also, about the last few days--
You don't have to say anything.
I… I was being a total jerk to El.
I deserved it.
No.
No, no, no. You didn't deserve anything.
Listen, the truth is, the last year
has been weird, you know?
And I mean, you know,
Max and Lucas and Dustin,
they're… they're great.
They're great. It's just…
It's Hawkins.
It's not the same without you.
And I feel like maybe
I was worrying too much about El,
and I don't know,
maybe I feel I lost you or something.
Does that make sense?
I have no idea what's gonna happen next.
But, whatever it is,
I… I think we should work together.
I think it'll be easier
if we're… we're a team.
Friends.
Best friends.
Cool.
[vehicle approaching]
[tires screeching]
-That was fast.
-Thirty minutes or less.
-All right. You guys ready?
-[Will, Mike] Yeah.
[doorbell rings]
Pizza time. I got it.
[TV playing faintly]
[doorbell rings persistently]
Yeah, I'm coming.
Hold your horses. Jesus Christ.
Hello there.
-[silenced gunshot]
-[thud]
-What the hell was that?
-[Will] Shit.
Stay here!
[gunshots]
[rapid gunfire]
[Harmon] Go in the den!
-What's going on?
-Get back!
-Shit!
-Listen, we gotta go right now!
-[Mike] Shit! Shit!
-[Jonathan] Go! Run!
Move! Move!
[gunfire]
-[boys panting]
-[glass shatters]
[Mike] Shit!
-Follow me.
-[Mike] Okay.
[dramatic music pulsing]
[Mike] What the hell is going on?!
-[gunshots continue]
-[boys yelling]
Just stay there.
Get down!
[boys yelling]
I shoot, you run!
♪ Pass the Dutchie
'Pon the left-hand side… ♪
Byers, man, having a party
and not inviting me, man?
That's not cool.
That is so not cool, man.
-Whoa!
-Stop the car!
[Argyle] The hell is going on?
[Harmon yelps]
-Go, go, go!
-Whoa, is that real blood, man?
-[all] Drive!
-Okay. All right.
But… Oh my God.
Why is that guy holding a gun?
-Drive!
-Okay!
♪ Pass the Dutchie
'Pon the left-hand side ♪
♪ It a go bun ♪
♪ Give me the music
Make me jump and prance ♪
[song ends abruptly]
[Yuri muttering]
Forty thousand.
Wow, all there.
Okay, now your turn.
Go get Hopper.
I will.
But first, I will call Enzo.
If your friend is dead,
I could save myself trouble and fuel.
[wheezing laughter]
I'm kidding. I'm sure he's not dead.
But still, I should check.
[tense music playing]
I don't like him.
[Hopper panting]
[intense, dramatic music playing]
[wind whistling]
[music pulses]
[grunts]
[panting]
[hinges creak]
[door squeaks]
[mysterious synth music playing]
[wood snaps, clatters]
[grunts]
[bright, hopeful music playing]
[inhales deeply]
[stifled laugh]
[emotional gasp]
[hopeful synth music continues]
[grunts]
[panting]
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
[speaks Russian]
[in Russian] Antonov, phone for you.
You realize we just had an escape?
They say it's urgent.
[speaks in Russian]
Hello?
Enzo. It is Yuri.
Why are you calling me here? Are you mad?
I know. I am very sorry. I just felt
you should know that there has been...
...a slight change in plans.
What? What has happened?
[distant yelling]
[ominous music playing]
I just got off the phone
with your warden.
A very productive call.
It turns out, escaped prisoners
are worth quite a bit of money.
[guard yells in Russian]
[yelling]
So Yuri thinks, why not keep
the forty grand and make extra money?
That wasn't the deal.
[chuckles] But it is
a better deal for Yuri, yes?
And you know what is worth
even more than escaped prisoner?
Corrupt guards.
What have you done?!
[yelling]
And worth most of all...
Americans...
...wanted by the KGB.
[audio distortion]
[guards yelling]
[shattering echoes]
[guard yelling]
[dramatic music swells]
[handcuffs locking]
[sounds of struggle over phone]
Goodbye, Enzo.
[Yuri whistling]
[gasps]
[in English] I'm sorry, poor bird.
Did I make your coffee too strong?
[Yuri laughing]
[distorted] Don't worry.
[echoing] You will be reunited
with your American boyfriend very soon.
Very soon.
[dramatic music swells]
[music fades]
Turn here.
Here?
-[Lucas] Max?
-Lucas, please, just wait in the car.
-Max, just wait. Max, please.
-Lucas, just wait--
Just listen to me. Just, please.
I know something happened there
with your mother.
[emotional music playing]
Was it Vecna?
I told you, I'm fine.
Okay?
I mean, as fine as someone who's hurtling
towards a gruesome death can be.
Max…
you know you can talk to me.
Right?
Yeah, I know that.
Okay, then why do you
keep pushing me away?
Okay, look,
I don't need a letter.
I don't want a letter.
Just talk to me.
To your friends.
We're right here.
I'm right here.
Okay?
I'm here.
Wait in the car. This won't be long.
[Nancy] When he attacks,
our friend described it as a trance.
Like a waking nightmare.
That's why we think
he's coming for her next.
Does any of this, anything we've told you,
sound like what happened to your family?
[Victor breathes shakily]
Victor.
-I know this is hard--
-You don't know anything!
[ominous chord swells]
You're right.
We don't know. That's why we're here.
To learn, to understand.
We need to know
how you survived that night.
[disbelieving laugh] Survived?
Is that what you call this?
Did I survive?
[groans] No, I assure you,
I am still very much in hell.
[sinister music
overlaid with jaunty big band music]
[jaunty big band music playing]
[Victor] I had been back from the war
some 14 years.
Her great-uncle had died,
leaving us a small fortune.
Enough to buy a new home,
a new life.
-What'd I tell ya?
-Wow.
This is amazing.
It looks like a fairy tale.
A dream.
Alice, no running.
-It's so big!
-[mother giggles]
[sighs] This is nice.
Yeah.
-It was a magnificent home.
-Yeah.
Alice said it looked like
it was from a fairy tale.
Alice.
Was this your daughter?
Mmm. Yeah.
But Henry, my…
my boy,
he was a sensitive child…
[electricity buzzes]
…and I could see
he felt something was wrong.
We had one month of peace in that house.
[echoing] And then it began.
[Alice gasps]
[unsettling music playing]
[Victor] Dead animals,
mutilated, tortured,
began to appear near our home.
Rabbits, squirrels, chickens, even dogs.
The police chief
blamed the attacks on a wildcat.
This… [disbelieving laugh]
…this was no wildcat.
This was an evil.
And evil neither animal nor human.
This was
a spawn of Satan.
A demon.
And it was even closer than I realized.
[dramatic music playing]
[pipes rumbling]
[spiders chittering]
[shrieks]
Victor!
[Victor]
My family began to have encounters
conjured by this demon.
Nightmares.
Waking, living nightmares.
[dramatic music continues]
This demon, it seemed
to take pleasure in tormenting us.
Even poor, innocent Alice.
[shrieks]
[mother] Alice!
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay. Come here.
It wasn't long before I began
to have encounters of my own.
[baby crying]
-[chilling note playing]
-[baby wailing]
-[flames roaring]
-[wailing continues]
I suppose
all evil
must have a home.
And though I had not
a rational explanation for it, I…
I could sense this demon,
always close.
[chilling music playing]
I became convinced it was hiding,
nesting,
somewhere within the shadows of our home.
It had cursed our town.
It had cursed our home.
It had cursed us.
[chilling music fades away]
["Dream A Little Dream Of Me"
by Ella Fitzgerald playing]
♪ Stars shining bright above you ♪
-♪ Night breezes seem to whisper ♪
-[radio squawks]
[reporter] Time, weather, and--
[staticky signals overlapping]
[ominous musical flourish]
[signals overlapping]
-[rumbling]
-♪ Dream a little dream of… ♪
[screams]
It took Virginia first.
-[bones cracking]
-♪ Just hold me tight ♪
-♪ And tell me you'll miss me ♪
-[shrieking]
I tried to get the children out,
to save them.
[grunting]
Come on!
[panting]
[garbled audio distortion]
[man, faintly] Creel.
Creel! What the hell happened here?
[Victor] But I was back to France,
back in the war.
It… it was a memory.
I had thought German soldiers were inside.
I ordered its shelling.
[indistinct shouting]
[baby wailing]
I was wrong.
[baby continues wailing]
[murmurs, pants]
This demon,
it was taunting me.
And I was sure it would take me,
-just as he'd taken my Virginia.
-[Alice screaming]
But then…
-I heard…
-["Dream A Little Dream Of Me" playing]
…another voice.
♪ Stars shining bright above you ♪
At first, I believed it was an angel.
And I… I followed her,
only to find myself…
-[music swells]
-[distorted] …in a nightmare far worse.
[unsettling music playing]
While I was away,
the demon took my children.
[clock ticking]
Henry slipped into a coma
shortly after that.
A week later, he died.
I tried to join them.
I tried.
[unsettling music builds]
-[wet squelch]
-[scream echoes]
Hatch stopped the bleeding.
He wouldn't let me join them.
[whimpers]
The angel you followed,
who was she?
[hums "Dream a Little Dream of Me"]
[continues humming]
Victor?
[tense music builds]
Victor.
-[door opens]
-Is he everything you hoped he would be?
I just had a very interesting conversation
with Professor Brantley.
Perhaps we should discuss in my office
while we wait for the police.
[tense music builds to climax]
"Dear Billy, I don't know
if you can even hear this."
"Two years ago, I would have said,
'That's ridiculous, impossible.'"
"But that was before I found out about
alternate dimensions and monsters,
so… I'm just going to stop assuming
that I know anything."
"So much has happened since you left."
[emotional music playing]
"Your dad was
a total mess."
"He and my mom
started getting into fights."
"Bad fights."
"I don't think he could stand
being here without you."
"So he left."
"And he didn't leave Mom much."
"She's taken an extra job, and we moved
to that lovely trailer park off Kerley."
"Basically,
ever since you left,
everything's been…
a total disaster."
"And the worst part is,
I can't tell anyone why you're gone."
"I can't tell them
that you saved El's life."
"That you saved my life."
"I play that moment back
in my head all the time."
"And sometimes I imagine myself
running to you,
pulling you away."
"I imagine that if I had,
that you would still be here."
[sniffs]
"And everything would be… [sobs]
…everything would be right again."
"I imagine that we…
that we could've become friends."
"Good friends, like…
like a real brother and sister."
"And I know that's stupid."
"You hated me."
"I hated you."
[emotional music continues]
"But I thought that maybe…
maybe we could try again."
"But that's not what happened."
"I just…
I stood there
and I watched."
"For a while, I tried to be happy."
"Normal."
"But I…
I think that maybe
a part of me died that day too."
"And I haven't told anyone this."
"I… I just can't."
"But I had to tell you."
"Before it's too late."
"If you can even hear this."
"I really hope that you can."
[sighs]
"I'm sorry."
"I'm so, so sorry, Billy."
"Love, your shitty little sister,
Max."
[eerie rumbling]
[clock chimes]
-[eerie laughter]
-[unsettling music playing]
[man] Max.
All right, it's been long enough.
-Steve, just give her some time.
-I have, all right?
I'm calling it.
She wants to get a lawyer, she can.
[tense music playing]
Max.
Time to giddy up, yeah?
Max?
-Max. Max.
-[dramatic music swells]
Max!
[man] Max.
I've been waiting
to hear those words, Max.
[gulps]
Waiting so very long.
[audio distortion]
Wake up!
Hey! [Steve claps]
Max, wake up!
Max! Wake up!
-Oh, something's wrong.
-Max!
Guys!
[chilling music playing]
Come on, wake up!
But it wasn't the full truth, was it, Max?
[Max breathing shakily]
You know, I think there's a part of you,
buried somewhere deep,
that wanted me to die that day.
That was maybe even relieved.
Happy.
Billy, no, that's not true.
That's why you stood there, isn't it, Max?
It's okay. You can admit it now.
No more lies.
-No more hiding.
-Billy, that's not true, I swear.
-I swear it's not true.
-That is why you feel such guilt.
-No. [sobs]
-Why you hide from your friends.
-Why you hide from the world.
-No. No.
And why, late at night,
you have sometimes wished to follow me.
-[clock chiming]
-Follow me into death.
-That is why I am here, Max.
-No.
-To end your suffering, once and for all.
[grunts]
[audio distortion]
It is time, Max.
Time for you
to join me.
[breathing heavily]
[sinister music playing]
Max, you gotta get outta there!
Can you hear me?
-Max!
-You gotta get outta there!
Call Nancy and Robin!
Go get 'em! Call Nancy and Robin! Go!
-[Lucas] Please, Max!
-Shit!
Shit, shit, shit! Shit, shit, shit!
Nancy? Robin? Do you copy?
This is a code red. Do you copy?
Shit. Robin!
You're not listening.
Our friend is in danger.
Do you really expect me
to believe anything you have to say?
It's the truth.
You are free
to tell your sob story to the police.
-Move along.
-Don't touch me!
["Clair de Lune"
by Claude Debussy playing]
Victor said the night of the attack,
everything went on in the house,
but he made specific mention of music.
He said music was playing.
["Dream A Little Dream Of Me"
playing, warps]
And then, when we asked him
about the angel, he started to hum.
[humming "Dream A Little Dream Of Me"]
♪ Say nighty-night and kiss me
Hold me tight… ♪
-"Dream a Little Dream of Me."
-Ella Fitzgerald.
-The voice of an angel.
-Yeah.
Hatch said that music can reach
parts of the brain that words can't.
So maybe that's the key, a lifeline.
-A lifeline back to reality.
-It's worth a shot.
[dramatic music playing]
-I think we can beat him.
-What?
To the car.
Okay. I'm warning you right now,
I have terrible coordination.
Took me six months longer to walk
than all the other babies.
-Just follow my lead.
-No, my God!
[guard] Hey! Get back here!
Cinderella, you dropped your shoe!
[guard] Stop right there!
[tense music playing]
-[inmate cackles]
-Go!
[Robin] Oh my God!
[Max panting]
[owl hooting]
[distressing music playing]
[Vecna] You cannot hide from me, Maxine.
[Robin yelping]
-[intense chase music playing]
-[guard] Let's go!
[guard] Stop! Get out of there!
-Ah!
-[guard] Hey!
-Go, go, go, go, go!
-Stop! Get out of the car.
-[engine revs]
-Get out of the car.
[tires screech]
Holy shit! Holy shit! Holy shit!
You really are a weird runner.
[Dustin] Robin, where the hell are you?
This is a code red. I repeat, a code red!
Dustin, it's Robin. We copy.
Holy shit. Finally!
Please, please tell me you guys
have this figured out.
[dramatic music playing]
[Max's gasps echoing]
Lucas!
Dustin!
Lucas, please, help! Dustin!
[menacing synth music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[creature chittering]
[wet squelch]
[menacing music intensifies]
[distant, indistinct screaming]
Max, get outta there!
-Can you hear--
-Guys!
-What is this?
-What's her favorite song?
-Why?
-Robin said if she listens…
It's too much to explain now.
What's her favorite song?
[thunder clapping]
[clock chiming]
[Vecna] What are you doing in here, Max?
-[wet popping]
-[clock chiming]
[spiders chittering]
[Vecna] Come back to me.
[shrill audio distortion]
[menacing music intensifies]
How do you like them, Max?
Would you like to join them?
[grunts]
[gasps]
Shit!
No! [screaming]
No!
[creature screeching]
[choking]
[whimpers]
[growling]
-Which one is it?
-Okay, okay!
Lucas, which one is it?
What's her favorite song?
[choking]
[Max whimpering]
-Which one?
-It's right here! Got it!
-Give it to me.
-Go, go, go!
-Okay, headphones!
-Now!
["Running Up That Hill"
by Kate Bush playing]
[grunting]
[Dustin] Max!
[Dustin] Max, wake up!
[Steve] Max! Wake up!
[Lucas] Max, we're right here!
-[Dustin] Come on, Max.
-They can't help you, Max.
There's a reason
you hide from them.
♪ Thunder in our hearts ♪
[Steve] Max!
You
belong here,
with me.
[coughs]
You're not really here.
Oh, but I am, Max.
I am.
♪ It's you and me, won't be unhappy ♪
♪ And if I only could
I'd make a deal with God ♪
♪ And I'd get him to swap our places… ♪
[friends shout] Max!
♪ I'd be running up that road
Be running up that hill ♪
♪ Be running up that building… ♪
[friends shouting] Max!
[Lucas] I don't want a letter.
We're right here.
I'm right here.
[music swells emotionally]
♪ Come on, darling ♪
♪ Let me steal this moment from you now ♪
♪ Come on, baby, come on, darling ♪
♪ Come on, angel ♪
♪ Come on, come on, darling ♪
♪ Let's exchange the experience… ♪
[friends] Max!
[high-five echoes]
[Vecna grunts]
[emotional bridge builds]
[powerful drum line builds]
♪ And if I only could
I'd make a deal with God ♪
♪ And I'd get him to swap our places… ♪
[friends crying out] Max!
♪ I'd be running up that road ♪
♪ Be running up that hill ♪
♪ No problems ♪
♪ Say, if I only could ♪
♪ I'd make a deal with God ♪
♪ And I'd get him to swap our places… ♪
[friends, desperately] Max!
♪ Be running up that road… ♪
♪ Be running up that hill ♪
[Max gasps]
[song fades]
[friends] Max! Max!
[overlapping shouting] Max! Max!
Max! Oh my God.
-It's okay.
-[Max hyperventilating]
It's okay.
I thought we lost you.
-I'm still… I'm still here.
-Oh shit.
[Max] I'm still here.
[emotional instrumental cover
of "Running Up That Hill" playing]
[emotional cover continues]
[music fades]