[thunder booming]
[creatures chittering]
[Steve struggling, exclaiming]
[creature whimpers]
Hey there.
-Quick! Hold it, Robin!
-I got it.
-Get it!
-[Eddie] Kill it! Kill it!
-[Nancy grunts]
-[creatures baying]
[Eddie] Shit!
Yeah! Come on!
Nancy! [Robin grunts]
Come on! Please!
[Eddie] Nancy, behind you! Watch out!
-[Nancy yelps]
-[Robin] Oh my God, Nance!
[Nancy] Robin, get it off me!
Got it, got it, got it!
God damn it! Shit!
[Robin] Let go!
[Steve] Come here!
-[Eddie] No!
-[Robin] Get it!
-[Robin] Nancy!
-[Nancy] Go to hell!
-[creature shrieks]
-[Robin grunts]
[Eddie] Come on, come on, come on,
you son of a bitch!
I said come on! Let's go!
[Eddie grunts]
[Steve grunting]
[Steve panting]
[thunder booms]
[spits]
-[Nancy] Steve!
-Jesus Christ.
Jesus H. Christ!
[oar clatters]
[Nancy] Are you okay?
-[gasps]
-Well, they took about a pound of flesh.
But other than that,
yeah, never better.
Uh, do you guys think
these bats have, like, rabies?
-What?
-It's just that rabies are, like,
my number one greatest fear.
And I think we should
get you to a doctor soon
because once symptoms set in,
it's too late. You're already dead.
[creatures chittering]
[gasps]
All right. There's not that many.
We can take 'em.
Right?
[swarm chittering]
You were saying?
[menacing industrial synth music playing]
The woods. Come on.
Great.
More running.
[menacing industrial synth continues]
[music swells, fades away]
[synth intro music playing]
[Wallace panting]
How'd you sleep, Mr. Wallace?
[wheezing for breath]
Have you
reconsidered your position?
-Where's the girl?
-[breathing shakily]
Perhaps you need more time to think.
[suspenseful music playing]
[soldier] Let's go.
No, wait, wait. Please. Wait!
Please.
Just don't kill her.
Promise me you won't kill her.
[suspenseful music builds]
[music fades away]
[faint audio distortions]
[audio distortions intensify]
[gasping]
We're running out of time here, Martin.
Hawkins is running out of time.
I understand the stakes quite well.
Sometimes I wonder if you really do.
Or maybe you've just done all this
'cause you missed
your daddy-daughter time.
I've given you everything you asked for.
I've compromised my principles.
I've risked my life, my family's life.
All because you assured me
this would work,
that this was the only way.
But I don't see
any progress out there, Martin.
You know what I see?
I see a frightened,
traumatized little girl.
Good for us.
-[door opens]
-[tense music playing]
[door closes]
[Brenner] The truth is,
you're regressing, Eleven.
You're going backwards.
Eleven, look at me.
Look at me.
I know you're frightened.
You're terribly frightened
by what you've seen.
But it's this very fear
that's now holding you back.
If you want Nina to succeed,
you cannot hide from the truth,
no matter how frightening it may be.
I saw what I did.
I am a monster.
You speak of monsters,
superheroes.
That's the stuff of myth and fairy tales.
Reality, truth, is rarely so simple.
People are not so easily defined.
Only by facing all of ourselves,
the good and the bad,
can we become whole.
What if I don't wanna become whole?
Then that is a choice.
Your choice.
The door is always open.
This place
is not a prison.
This is.
You chose to trust me once.
I'm asking you to trust me again.
Journey with me into the past
one last time.
Stop hiding, Eleven.
[mysterious music playing]
[gears clanking]
[machinery whirring]
[mysterious music continuing]
[Ten, Brenner laugh]
[high-pitched distortion]
What have you done?
[mysterious synth music playing]
[machinery whirring]
How much time did you skip?
You wanted progress.
I'm giving it to you.
[screaming]
[Powell] What exactly
were you all doing at the lake?
[Dustin] Uh…
-It's comp--
-We were… We were just going for a walk.
[Callahan] A walk?
At 9:00 p.m.?
[squeakily] To the lake.
We were gonna
take a little swim.
Little night swim.
[Mrs. Henderson] Dusty.
Someone was just murdered there.
Yeah, we… we didn't realize that
until we got there.
That's why we didn't swim.
And Nancy,
was she with you at this night swim?
-No.
-Yes. Uh…
We're not sure.
[Dustin] She was there.
Then she left.
-It's all a little confusing.
-That's when you guys came.
Right. Then they dared me
to say what I said.
Oh, yeah.
-About the killer.
-[laughing]
You're lucky you didn't get shot.
Have you had any contact with Eddie?
That psycho… freak killer?
God, no.
-Nope. Absolutely not.
-No. We haven't heard from him.
-We barely know the guy.
-Who?
Oh, that's a bunch of bull.
-[both] Erica!
-I mean, you realize they're lying.
The whole couch is on fire.
-[both] Erica.
-Just the facts.
Are you lying to these policemen, Dusty?
-[high-pitched] No.
-Lying to cops is a crime, son.
-I'm not lying.
-The fire is consuming us.
Threaten them with a little jail time.
Maybe that'll loosen their lips.
-Okay--
-You wanna send our kids to jail?
-We need to take this seriously.
-He didn't mean it like that.
[overlapping arguments]
-Shut up!
-Oh my God.
[yelling] Shut up!
-Jesus.
-Shh.
We're gonna try a more civilized approach.
One at a time.
You first.
-Wait, what? Why me?
-Follow me.
I'm not even in Hellfire.
Do I need to cuff you?
Up.
Chop-chop.
Let's go.
[mysterious music playing]
[creatures chittering]
Oh… okay.
-That was close.
-Yeah.
[Eddie] Too close.
Oh, sh… shit.
Steve?
-Jesus.
-I'm fine. I'm fine.
No, no, no.
You're not. You're losing blood.
Come on, sit. All right?
[grunts]
[Nancy] All right.
-[music pulses ominously]
-Oh…
[Steve grunting]
Okay.
So the good news is I'm pretty sure
wooziness is not a symptom of rabies.
But if you start having hallucinations
or muscle spasms
or you start feeling aggressive,
like you wanna punch me, let me know.
-Robin.
-Yeah?
I kinda wanna punch you.
[laughs] Sense of humor's still intact.
That's a good sign.
Yeah.
-Okay.
-[Steve grunts]
Okay.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Just do it.
[wet squelch]
[stifled groan]
Sorry.
It's okay.
-[grunts]
-Too tight?
-No, that's good.
-All right.
[grunting, panting]
Okay.
Thanks.
Yeah.
[thunder rumbling]
[Eddie] So, uh,
this place is like Hawkins,
but with monsters and nasty shit?
Pretty much.
Wait, watch out for the vines.
It's all a hive mind.
It's all a what?
All the creepy crawlies around here.
They're, like, one or something.
Step on a vine, you're stepping on a bat,
you're stepping on Vecna.
Shit.
But everything from our world
is still here, right? Except people?
As far as I understand it, yeah.
So, theoretically,
we could go to the police station
and steal guns and grenades
and whatever we need
to blow up those bat things
that are guarding the gate.
I highly doubt
the Hawkins PD has grenades, Robin.
But guns, yeah, sure.
Well, we don't have to go
all the way downtown for guns.
I have guns in my bedroom.
You,
Nancy Wheeler,
have guns, plural,
in your bedroom?
Full of surprises, isn't she?
A Russian Makarov and a revolver.
Yeah, you almost shot me with that one.
You almost deserved it.
For your modesty, dude.
[loud rumbling]
[Robin] Oh my god!
[all panting]
[creature baying in distance]
[creatures snarling]
So guns seem like
a pretty good idea to me.
Yeah, me too.
So what are we waiting for?
[ominous music playing]
[dark, industrial synth music playing]
[music trails off]
You know,
what we are to attempt is quite mad.
Even by your standards, American.
Yeah?
You got odds for us this time?
[scoffs]
I think…
a thousand to one?
[chuckles]
Even if we somehow kill this beast,
we still must escape.
We fail there,
I don't think they will be so kind
as to throw us back in a cell.
They will shoot us on sight.
We'd die as monster slayers.
You'll be a legend.
But still a traitor. You forgot traitor.
Monster slayer trumps traitor.
I bet Mikhail
will be proud of his pops, at least.
Mikhail?
-Mmm.
-No.
I can't do nothing right
with him anymore, it seems.
He will say,
"Papa, I bet that bald American
did most of the monster slaying."
He's that age, huh?
-Yeah, he is that age.
-[Hopper chuckles]
It is same for you, American?
With your new daughter?
The last time I was with El, she wanted
just about nothing to do with me.
I was just in her way, really.
I think back to the way I was with my dad
at that age. I was the same way.
The exact same way.
[emotional music playing]
I think it must be hardwired into us
to reject our fathers.
So we can grow and move on.
Become something of our own.
I hope that's what she's doing.
Coming into her own.
But still--
You worry.
To worry for our sons and daughters,
that is natural, isn't it?
Yeah.
But nothing about what El
has had to deal with is natural.
[jarring musical stinger]
That beast,
that monster in there,
it's a part of something
that wants to hurt El. To kill her.
I don't understand.
To be honest, neither do I.
All I know is that thing…
that thing shouldn't be here.
It shouldn't be alive.
Because it is,
it means it still isn't over.
I thought I was put here
to pay for what I've done.
But I might've been put here
for some other reason.
Maybe I…
maybe I can still help El.
Even if it's the last thing I do.
You almost sound religious, American.
Religious? I don't know about that.
But maybe I should
give that prayer thing a try.
'Cause if we wanna get out of here,
get back to El and Mikhail,
you and me…
we're gonna need a miracle.
[Demogorgon chittering]
-[horn honks]
-[brakes creak]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Can I help you, comrade?
My name is Yuri Ismaylov.
[in English] Hello.
[laughs]
[in Russian] The warden is expecting me.
I have a very special delivery for him.
A rare import from America.
[laughs wheezily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Yuri speaking, muffled]
[in English] Okay, okay. I'm okay.
[gasps, chuckles]
[buzzing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[mysterious music playing]
[Brenner] Try your best not to blink.
Any more headaches?
Nausea this morning?
How about your memory?
Can you remember what happened now?
Perhaps someone else
can help fill in the gaps.
Yes?
[tense music playing]
[Brenner] Good morning, children.
[children] Good morning, Papa.
[Brenner] Today's lesson
is going to be about rules.
Ah, for some of you,
this may seem redundant.
For others,
it appears a refresher is required.
Eleven, please step forward.
Last night, your sister Eleven
suffered a concussion
during her alone time in the rainbow room.
Now, she claims to not have
a memory of what happened.
But injuries of this nature
don't simply happen.
Someone did this.
Someone in this room.
Now,
who's going to tell me what happened?
[uneasy music playing]
[Two] She must've… fallen.
Fallen?
You've seen her, Papa.
She's clumsy.
Stupid.
[bullies snickering]
Eleven, you may step back.
Number Two, please step forward.
[Brenner] Collar him.
[whoosh echoing]
[collar clinks]
[collar clasps shut]
Thank you.
You think because
you demonstrate some talent
that you're somehow immune
to the rules, is that it?
No, Papa.
That the rules don't apply to you
in the same way
that they apply
to your brothers and sisters?
No, Papa.
Then why did you attack Eleven?
-Did she tell you that?
-Are you asking the questions or am I?
Did you attack Eleven?
If she told you that,
then… then she's lying.
-[Two pants]
-[remote clicks, beeps]
Papa, please, you have to believe me.
Papa, please.
She's lying--
-[electricity crackling]
-[pained groaning]
[intense synth music playing]
Now,
shall we try again?
[remote clicking]
What happened?
It was an accident.
-[electricity crackling]
-[pained groaning]
[remote thrums]
[Two's wail echoing]
[thunder booms]
[Robin] Couldn't we have tried a road,
or something just slightly less creepy?
[Nancy] I think we're getting close.
We're almost out of here. Don't worry.
[Steve] Eddie.
Eddie. Hey, man. Uh…
Listen, I just, uh…
I just want to say thanks.
For saving my ass back there.
Shit. You saved your own ass, man.
I mean, that was a real Ozzy move
you pulled back there.
Ozzy?
When you took a bite out of that bat.
Ozzy Osbourne?
Black Sabbath?
-He bit a bat's head off onstage.
-I don't--
-You know? Doesn't matter.
-No.
It's very metal, what you did.
That's all I'm saying.
Thanks.
Henderson told me you were a badass.
Insisted on the matter, in fact.
-Henderson said that?
-Oh yeah. Shit.
Kid worships you, dude.
Like, you have no idea.
It's kinda annoying, to be honest.
I don't even know why I care
what that little shrimp thinks,
but, uh, guess I got
a little jealous, Steve.
I guess I couldn't accept the fact
that Steve Harrington
was actually
a good dude.
Rich parents, popular, chicks love him.
Not a douche?
No way, man. No way. That, like,
flies in the face
of all the laws in the universe
and my own personal Munson doctrine.
Still super jealous as hell, by the way.
Which is why I would never have
jumped in that lake to save your ass.
Not under any, uh… normal circumstances.
[branch snaps]
[growling in distance]
Nope.
Outside of D&D, I am no hero.
I see danger and I just turn heel and run.
Or at least that's what
I've learned about myself this week.
-Give yourself a break, man.
-See?
The only reason I came in here
was 'cause those ladies
came in straight after you.
Now, I was too ashamed
to be the one who stayed behind.
But Wheeler right there,
she didn't waste a second.
Not one second.
She just dove right in.
Now, I don't know what happened
between you two,
but if I were you,
I would get her back.
'Cause that
was as unambiguous a sign of true love
as these cynical eyes have ever seen.
[subdued, emotional music plays]
-[loud rumbling]
-Goddamn it!
Here we go again.
Second on my list
of least favorite things, earthquakes.
Seriously, I'm unsteady enough as it is.
Nancy!
Where are you going?
[tense industrial synth music playing]
Nancy!
[thunder booming]
Come on.
[Dustin] Steve, do you copy?
Nancy? Robin?
This is Dustin. Where are you?
We've been collared by the law.
I repeat, we've been collared by the law.
Do you copy?
[radio squawks]
Shit!
[flushes]
-Should we get lawyers?
-[Powell] We're not ready for that.
As far as we know,
nobody did anything wrong.
[Mrs. Henderson]
But what if they did do something wrong?
-Anything?
-Nothing.
-You don't think they went through…
-Through Watergate?
Without us? Without a plan?
Without weapons?
They wouldn't be that stupid.
Yeah.
They must just be laying low
'cause the law got us.
[Erica] "The law"?
What is this, Gunsmoke?
The Stupid and the Ugly?
Should I round up the posse?
-Saddle the horses?
-Erica.
Please, just go away.
Here's the deal.
Either you tell me what's happening
or I tell Dustin
what I found under your bed.
Please, no.
Spill your guts, cowpuncher.
-What'd she find?
-Nothing.
Is it gross?
-Scale of one to ten.
-A hundred.
A hundred?
The serial killer is a dark wizard
from the Upside Down.
And we've been looking for him,
but he's in the Upside Down,
which we can't reach.
At least we thought we couldn't,
until we found a gate at Lover's Lake.
That was the reason why we were there,
but these stupid cops grabbed us.
And if you tell anyone about this,
that's including Mom
and Dad
and Tina…
[Erica slurping juice]
…especially Tina,
I…
will smother you
in your sleep.
Do you understand?
Hmm…
Erica?
Do
you
copy?
The smothering in my sleep part,
but not much else.
Why would they open up a gate
at Lover's Lake?
-What?
-The commies.
-The commies didn't.
-Then who did?
-Nobody.
-So it just opened up for fun?
Erica, you have no idea
what you're talking about.
No, she doesn't,
yet she raises an essential question.
How did Watergate open up?
Only two gates have opened,
so far as we know.
One by El, one by the commies.
But it's not the commies
or El this time, so it…
[eerie music playing]
Holy shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
"Wait, wait, wait," what?
There's one thing we've never understood.
Which is why Vecna's killing people.
What's his motive?
Killing teens?
It always just seemed too random.
Too prosaic.
On top of that, how does
the Mind Flayer figure into all this?
Maybe this is it.
This is the answer.
What is the answer?
You sure you just want water?
-We have Coke, Sprite, Dr. Pepper.
-Coke works. Thank you.
Okay, just hear me out.
How did El open the Mothergate?
She contacted the Demogorgon.
With psychic contact. Just like…
-Vecna when he casts his spells.
-Exactly.
So, what if, with each kill,
he's not simply killing them,
he's making a powerful
psychic connection with his victims?
A connection powerful enough
to rip a hole in the fabric
of time and space.
He's opening more gates.
Bingo.
Copy. We're still at the Wheeler house.
[police radio chatter]
-Why would he be opening gates?
-To take over the world.
Who do we know
that wants to take over the world?
The Mind Flayer.
So if the Demogorgon
was just his foot soldier,
Vecna's his five-star general.
A five-star general
with the power to open gates.
-Holy shit.
Holy shit. That was incomprehensible.
You lost me at "Mothergate."
Please be kind. Rewind.
[Dustin] Okay, so remember the gate?
[Erica] Oh, no. I blocked that out.
[Dustin speaking indistinctly]
[Erica] So what was that giant laser?
[buzzing, rattling]
Might be time to get a maid, Wheeler.
Come on. I don't want to stay here
longer than we have to.
[eerie, mysterious music playing]
[Dustin speaking indistinctly and faintly]
Those aren't guns.
These heels are pointy,
but I was hoping for a deadly projectile.
-I don't understand.
-Maybe you left them somewhere else.
There's a six-year-old in the house.
I know where I keep my guns.
And also, I threw these away years ago.
[mysterious music playing]
Jesus. How many did you make?
You said you wanted to help.
I get that grades are important,
but perhaps studying can wait
till we get out?
These are from sophomore chemistry.
And this… this wallpaper,
this is old wallpaper.
And this mirror, this went to a yard sale.
And you…
you're not supposed to be here.
No, I gave you to Cousin Joanna
two years ago.
[mysterious music continues]
What is it?
Nancy? You're freaking me out.
I think the reason
that my guns aren't here
is because they don't exist yet.
They don't… exist?
This diary should be full of entries.
It's not.
The last entry is November 6, 1983.
The day Will went missing.
The day the gate opened.
We're in the past.
[eerie stinger]
[Steve] Dustin! Dustin!
Dustin!
Can you hear me? Dustin!
Du-- Hello? Hel… Hello?
-Maybe he really does have rabies.
-Hello! Hello?
What are you doing?
Hello!
He's here. Henderson.
That little shit, he's here. He's like…
He's in the walls or something.
Just listen.
Dustin.
Dustin! Dustin!
Dustin! Dustin! Can you hear me?
[Dustin] That brings us
to the question you first raised.
How and why
is there a gate at Lover's Lake?
Let's analyze.
What do Eleven and Vecna have in common?
Dustin!
-Dustin?
-Dustin!
All right, either this kid can't hear us
or he's being a total douchebag.
-Will found a way.
-What?
Will.
He found a way
to speak to Joyce through the lights.
-[Steve] Lights?
-Yeah.
-The switch. Try the switch.
-Okay.
[Dustin continuing, faintly]
[Nancy] It's not working.
Guys?
You seeing this?
[energy thrumming]
[Dustin speaking faintly]
[mysterious, ethereal music playing]
[Dustin] …to open a tear
in time and space,
just like the Mothergate.
Whoa.
[ethereal music continues]
[Dustin] …are these like the Mothergate…
But a gate nonetheless.
[Steve exhales]
It…
tickles.
It kinda feels good.
Does anyone know Morse code?
[Robin, Steve] No.
Wait, does SOS count?
Is that…
is that good?
So our working theory is that Vecna
makes remote contact from his attic.
We don't know why.
We assume he can do it from anywhere.
[energy thrumming rhythmically]
-Are you even listening to me?
-I'm listening.
It's just…
You said you followed Vecna
through lights, right?
Yeah, why?
Because I think he's here.
[ethereal music builds]
It's working.
"S."
"O."
Hey, uh,
remember when I said
they wouldn't be stupid enough
to go through Watergate?
Yeah?
I overestimated them.
[wind rushing]
[Murray] Warden,
beautiful prison you got here.
How about this? Huh? [laughs]
How about that? Huh?
Huh?
-[Joyce groans]
-That's what I thought, yeah.
Warden. [chuckles]
So nice to meet you.
Uh, I'm Yuri, of course,
but allow me to introduce you to my very--
Shit.
-[muffled] Murray!
-I'm sorry.
What?
Can you please
stop playing with that thing?
I am not playing. I am practicing.
Will you please stop trying
to talk to me and stay in character?
Remember, you are frightened,
scared, confused.
-Yes, I am frightened, scared, and--
-Okay. All right. Yes. Good.
[in Russian] Yuri Ismaylov.
[laughing]
At last, we meet.
Comrade Major.
This is the Bauman spy?
[Yuri struggling, muffled]
He looks different.
Uglier in person, I know.
He also shaved his beard
to disguise himself.
Tricky bastard.
[in English] Silence, American scum!
Enough from you. Enough!
[Yuri moaning]
[laughs wheezily]
[in Russian] Now this one…
This one I would recognize
a continent away.
She was more beautiful
in her uniform, but still,
quite striking, isn't she?
Yes, very pleasing to the eyes, comrade.
But not so pleasing to the ears,
I am afraid.
[in English] Where is he?
What have you done with Hopper,
you vile commie pig?
[in Russian] As I said,
unpleasant.
But, I must say,
I, too, am curious.
The other American.
What did you do with him?
I don't know why,
but I imagine him on a rack,
in the cold, stretched thin,
birds pecking his eyeballs.
Am I... close?
I have heard stories of Yuri Ismaylov,
the Peanut Butter Smuggler.
And you…
you are not the Yuri I have heard of.
I am…
I am not?
No.
[menacing music plays]
The Yuri I was told of had a screw loose.
And you…
have many screws loose!
-[laughs]
-[menacing music stops]
[intense, dramatic music plays]
[Murray whoops]
I hope we have not missed the show.
On the contrary, just in time.
[Yuri speaking, muffled]
[guard yelling in Russian]
This key here will give you access
to that weapons locker.
Choose any weapon you like.
[dramatic music intensifies]
Work together or alone.
What… what is happening?
They are being told the rules.
Rules for what?
I could tell you...
but that would spoil the fun,
now, wouldn't it?
[Murray chuckles]
You wait for the buzzer.
You wait.
You move before the buzzer...
you will be shot.
Is that understood?
[prisoners] Yes.
I'd wish you luck
but it won't help you.
[in English] Let us hope your prayers
have been heard, American.
[Demogorgon snarling]
[Demogorgon pounding on door]
[Joyce whimpering]
[snarling continues]
[chip clattering]
[indistinct chatter]
[unnerving music playing]
[chilling audio distortion]
[balls rattling]
-[balls clang]
-[chips clatter]
You open for something
a little more challenging?
Try not to show any emotion
as I speak, okay?
Just keep playing the game
if you understand.
Two is still in the infirmary recovering.
He's being watched now,
but once he is released,
he and the others
are going to attempt to kill you.
Right here,
in this room.
And Papa
will allow it to happen.
In fact, he wants it to happen.
He's been planning it for some time now.
[Eleven breathing shakily]
Stay calm.
Focus on the game.
There's a reason why Two and the others
were able to escape their room last night.
Why the security cameras were turned off.
Why Papa punished Two today.
They don't even realize it,
but he is moving them
like pieces on this board here.
Driving them
to do exactly what he wants,
which is…
[music intensifies]
Why?
You frighten him.
He knows you are more powerful
than the others.
And he also knows he can't control you.
That's all he wants.
Control.
I saw all this happening.
That's why I wanted to help you,
but I only made things worse.
Helping me…
made Papa hurt you.
-[electricity crackling]
-[orderly grunting]
[sighs]
And it is why you must escape.
Today.
But they are watching us.
Closely.
If you want to make it out of here alive,
you must do exactly as I say.
Do you understand?
Why do you still help?
Because I believe in you.
It is time you are free from this hell.
[music intensifies]
[TV playing faintly]
[cereal jingle playing on TV]
Hey!
[mysterious synth music plays]
-I'm sorry!
-Sorry, sorry, sorry.
For your understanding.
[Steve] Come on. Come on.
-Okay, that's it. Go, go, go.
-Yeah, okay.
Okay, you guys seeing this?
[Dustin, faintly] …seeing this?
[mysterious, ethereal music playing]
[energy hums]
-Holy shit!
-[Dustin laughs]
[Dustin's laughter echoing]
We're not moving it,
but we're gonna unplug it. Stand by.
Yank it.
Okay, try it now.
-Try it now.
-Okay.
Um… Uh…
[music swells]
[Dustin laughing]
"H."
[Dustin] "Hi"!
-Hi!
-Hey! Hi.
That worked!
[Eddie] Yes! Yes!
Hi!
Okay. Um…
[Robin chuckles]
Um…
[energy thrumming]
[all] "S… T…"
"U…"
-"Stu…"
-Stupid? Stupid?
"…C… K."
-"Stuck."
-Stuck.
-[Steve] Yes.
-We are.
-They're stuck in the Upside Down.
-Okay.
Uh, you can't get back through Watergate?
-What the hell's Watergate?
-'Cause it's in water and it's a gate.
-Oh.
-That's cute.
-Right.
-Um, no. It's…
[Lucas] That a six?
-"G"?
-No, "G."
-Yeah.
-[all] "U… A… R."
"Guar"?
Guar…
[Dustin echoing]
Guar… Guar…
-[Erica] "Guard…"
-[Dustin] "Guarded."
-[Lucas] "Guarded"?
-Okay. Uh, Watergate's guarded.
Perfect. Yes. Yes. Yes.
We think we have a theory
that can help with that.
-Yes.
-Genius child.
We think Watergate isn't the only gate.
That there's a gate at every murder site.
[Dustin] …murder site.
Does anybody understand
what he's talking about?
-No.
-No idea.
Okay. Seriously?
How many times do I have to be
right on the money before you trust me?
Jesus Christ.
This kid's gotta get his ego in check.
It's his tone. Right?
-I know.
-Okay.
So… So how far is your trailer?
Seven miles.
Nancy?
Uh, I know your house here is, like,
weirdly, creepily frozen in time and shit,
but haven't you always had bikes?
[ethereal music stops]
[police radio chatter]
[Mrs. Wheeler] So, anything?
-Nope. She's sticking to her story.
-["Running Up That Hill" plays]
They went to the lake for a night swim.
Nancy showed up at some point…
-[Powell continues indistinctly]
-[mouthing]
[mouthing] Come on!
[Powell] …same thing she said
here on the couch.
Pretty much all she told us.
She stuck to her guns.
Honestly, shouldn't have
gone with her first.
She was, like,
kinda mean.
[Powell] We'll find your daughter,
Mrs. Wheeler.
Don't worry.
One of these little brats is gonna squeal.
I just know it.
Where are they?
Upstairs.
Moping.
Oh little pigs.
[rapping lightly]
Let Officer Callahan in.
[mysterious music playing]
-[dog barking]
-[clattering outside window]
-[Lucas] Let's go.
-[Max] Careful.
[Callahan] Hey!
-Excuse me! No, get back here!
-[kids whispering]
[Dustin] Let's go! Let's go!
-I guess it's just a minor misdemeanor.
-[Callahan] Hey! No!
No!
-[Mrs. Wheeler grunts]
-[parents panting]
-Lucas!
-[Mrs. Henderson] Dusty!
Dusty!
[Mrs. Sinclair] Lucas, Erica!
Get back here!
[Mrs. Henderson] Dusty!
[sinister music playing]
[creatures chittering]
[shrieking]
[music fades away]
[chip clattering]
[tops whirring]
[energy thrumming]
[door opens]
[Eleven panting]
[Brenner] That's your favorite, isn't it?
How are you feeling today?
[Ten] Okay.
[Brenner] Are you up for
some more lessons?
Good.
[sinister music playing]
I feel dizzy.
Dizzy?
Yes.
And the light.
The light is hurting my head.
[toys clattering]
[sighs]
[foreboding music playing]
[medical monitor beeping]
[door opens]
Sorry to bother you.
-Everything all right?
-Not sure.
She says she's still dizzy.
Lights are hurting her.
Hurting who?
[suspenseful music playing]
[steam hissing]
[whispers] Quiet.
Follow me.
[orderly grunts]
Now,
it's going to be a bit scary in here,
but this,
this will lead you out
beyond the lab fence to the woods.
But you're too big.
[mysterious music playing]
I'm not going with you, Eleven.
I meant what I said
when I called this place a prison.
And everyone here is a prisoner,
not just you.
Not just your brothers and sisters,
but the guards, too, the nurses.
Me.
[uneasy stinger]
Here.
Can you feel it?
Your papa calls it Soteria.
It weakens me. It tracks me.
Even if there were another way out,
he will find me.
And if he finds me, he will find you.
What if I make it go away?
You helped me.
I help you.
[hopeful music playing]
[Demogorgon bellowing]
[pounding on door]
[Demogorgon continues bellowing]
[in Russian] Stay calm.
Stay close.
Stick to the plan.
[ominous synth music playing]
[Joyce whimpering]
[alarm blaring]
American!
I enjoy this part...
When they still believe there is hope.
[alarm continues wailing]
[alarm blares]
[gears clanking]
Whatever comes out of there...
hold your ground.
HOLD YOUR GROUND!
[Hopper panting]
What is the American doing?
I don't know.
Find out!
[tense music playing]
[Joyce grunts]
[guttural snarling]
You move so much as an inch,
I'll kill you.
What?
[lighter clinks]
[in English] Oh, come on!
[in Russian] What is this?
Some kind of sick joke?
It's no joke. As I said…
[in English]
…the Americans are very tricky.
[Hopper] Come on. Come on. Come on.
Tell me that's not out of fluid.
Come on! Come on!
If you wanna live,
then whatever sick, twisted game this is,
you're gonna stop it
and you're gonna free our friend.
Then I'm afraid
you're going to have to kill me.
Because your friend is already dead.
Come on!
Come on! Oh, come on!
[music swells, fades away]
[feral snarling]
[prisoners yelling]
-[prisoner screaming]
-[bones crunching]
[roaring]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STAY TOGETHER YOU FOOLS!
Order your men to shoot. To kill it!
If I give that order,
I will be shot tomorrow and die a traitor.
You want to kill me, do it!
[Murray laughs]
[muffled yelling]
[in English] Come on! Come on! Come on!
Ah! Ah!
[yells]
Get back! Get back!
Get the hell back!
[prisoner yells]
[bones crunching]
[in Russian] I'll kill him! I'LL KILL HIM!
TOSS YOUR GUN! OVER TO ME!
[intense industrial synth music playing]
You, open all the doors below.
You understand?
OPEN THE DOORS.
You open all the doors,
that monster will get loose in this prison
and we are all dead.
I will pull this trigger! OPEN THE DOORS!
[Demogorgon snarling]
[metal creaking, groaning]
They would need a battering ram
to open that door.
Let the monster feed.
[prisoner grunts, screams]
[Demogorgon feeding wetly]
[Murray] You think I'm playing?
You think I won't do it?
OPEN THE DOOR!
If I open those doors,
I condemn not just myself,
but all of my comrades to death.
In good conscience, I cannot.
I will not.
[in English] I gotta hand it
to you commies. You're committed.
[Murray grunting]
[prisoner screaming]
[Hopper] Stay back!
Back! Back! Get back!
Get away!
-Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
-[console buzzing]
-What are you doing?
-No idea. There's a lot of buttons.
I can't see.
I need my glasses. Gimme a second.
Come here. No.
Give me. Mine!
[Hopper grunts]
[snarling]
Running out of time here!
I'm trying!
No, no, no. Joyce, we have no idea
what these buttons do.
You can't just press away like that.
[device powering down]
Get back!
Back! Get back!
[Murray] Joyce, just relax.
Come on!
-[alarm blares]
-[gears whir]
American!
That did it! That did it!
Close it, Joyce.
-Close it!
-[Joyce gasps]
[Demogorgon chittering]
[snarling]
-[panting]
-[Demogorgon snarling]
[alarm blaring faintly]
For a second,
I thought we had your miracle.
But out of one prison into another.
[alarm blares]
[gate opening]
[gears whirring]
[tender, emotional music playing]
[creatures chittering in distance]
[ominous music playing]
[Eddie] Right here.
That's gotta be a Guinness World Record.
Most miles traveled interdimensionally.
Just inhaled a bunch of that crap.
[coughs] It's stuck in my throat.
[eldritch thrumming]
Goddamn.
[Eddie] This is where Chrissy died.
Like, right where she died.
[fissure writhing wetly]
I think there's something in there.
What the hell is that?
[all yelp]
[mysterious music playing]
No way.
[music swells, fades away]
[Dustin laughing]
Hi there.
-Hi.
[Dustin laughing]
[triumphant music plays]
Holy shit, this is trippy.
Bada-bada-boom!
Remember, you can't hurt me
more than they already have.
[exhales]
[eerie music playing]
[eerie audio distortions]
-[flesh rips]
-[grunts]
[Soteria clatters]
[tense music plays]
[orderly] Huh.
[unsettling chord]
Who knew something so small
could cause so much trouble?
Thank you.
[guard] There they are!
-Stop!
-[orderly] Run.
[guard] Freeze!
[dramatic music playing]
[guard] Stop!
[guard] Lock it down! Lock it down!
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
[electricity sparking]
Against the wall.
Both of you. Now.
No.
You don't have to be
afraid of them, Eleven.
Not anymore.
[sinister music playing]
Take 'em.
[dramatic music playing]
[guard yells]
[yells, grunts]
[bones snapping]
Come.
Wait here. Don't move.
-I'm going to find us a way out.
-Wait.
How did you--
Like I said,
we're alike,
you and I.
[discomforting stinger]
[eerie, delicate music playing]
[Eleven exhales]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Those stains are, uh…
-I dunno what those stains are.
-[Robin] Mmm.
Not quite sure how these physics work.
But, uh…
here goes nothing.
[eldritch gurgling]
-[ethereal music plays]
-There we go.
And if my theory is correct…
-Huh. Abracadabra.
-Holy shit.
All right, pull on it! See if it holds!
[grunting]
[Dustin laughing]
This is the craziest shit
I've ever seen in my life.
And I've seen some crazy shit.
Guess I'm the guinea pig.
[grunting]
Let's clear the landing pad.
Oh my God!
Oh, thank God.
That was fun.
All right, guess I'll go.
All right.
Easy, easy.
That
was fun.
Shit.
[Steve chuckles]
See you on the other side.
On the other side.
[Nancy grunting]
Nice.
[ethereal music continues]
[distressing music plays]
[yelling]
[grunting, groaning]
[grunting, panting]
Nancy.
Hey! Hey!
Stay with me. Nancy! Hey!
Nancy, wake up.
-Wake up! Nancy!
-Vecna.
[ominous music playing]
[jarring stinger]
[gasps]
[Vecna] Do you remember
what you did, Nancy?
-[snarls]
-[screams]
[Vecna] Or have you already forgotten?
[Barb panicking]
[Vecna] When I kill someone…
[Barb's scream echoing]
[Vecna] …I never forget.
Nancy!
[sinister music playing]
[sinister music swells]
[music trails off]
-[alarm wailing]
-[gasps]
[sinister music plays]
[garbled radio static]
[garbled radio chatter]
[staticky screaming over radio]
[screaming continues]
[lights buzzing erratically]
[jarring stinger]
[distant screaming]
[guttural snarl]
[Eleven panting]
[shrill scream]
[sobs]
[Eleven sobs]
[sinister music continues]
[screaming echoes]
[music stops abruptly]
[panting]
[jarring stinger]
[straining]
[music intensifies]
[Two struggling]
[eldritch power thrumming]
-[bones snap]
-[thud]
[gasps]
[intense music fades away]
-[Eleven panting]
-[One seething]
[One sniffs]
[One grunts]
I asked you to wait.
[Eleven yelling]
[Eleven whimpering]
Why do you cry for them, Eleven?
After everything they did to you?
Hmm?
You think you need them, but you don't.
You don't.
Oh, but I know you're just scared.
I was scared once too.
I know
what it's like
to be different.
To be alone
in this world.
[thunder booming]
[clock ticking]
[distant wailing]
[clock chimes]
[Vecna] I see
you've been looking for me, Nancy.
You were so close.
So close to the truth.
How was old, blind, dumb Victor?
Did he miss me?
I've been meaning to check back in,
but I've been busy.
[horrifying stinger]
So very busy.
[sinister organ music playing]
-What'd I tell ya?
-Wow.
This is amazing.
It looks like a fairy tale.
A dream.
-[Virginia] Alice, no running.
-It's so big!
This is nice.
Yeah.
-[Victor] Yeah.
-[One] Like you,
I didn't fit in with the other children.
Something was wrong with me.
All the teachers
and the doctors said I was…
"Broken,"
they said.
My parents
thought a change of scenery,
a fresh start in Hawkins,
might just cure me.
It was absurd.
As if the world
would be any different here.
[solemn choir singing]
[One] But then…
to my surprise, our new home provided
a discovery.
And a newfound sense of purpose.
I found a nest of black widows
living inside a vent.
Most people fear spiders.
They detest them.
And yet,
I found them endlessly fascinating.
More than that,
I found a great comfort in them.
[whoosh]
A kinship.
Like me,
they are solitary creatures.
And deeply misunderstood.
They
are gods of our world.
The most important of all predators.
They immobilize and feed on the weak,
bringing balance and order
to an unstable ecosystem.
But the human world
was disrupting this harmony.
You see,
humans
are a unique type of pest,
multiplying
and poisoning our world,
all while enforcing
a structure of their own.
A deeply unnatural structure.
Where others saw order,
I saw a straitjacket.
[clock ticking]
A cruel, oppressive world
dictated by made-up rules.
Seconds, minutes,
hours, days, weeks, months,
years, decades.
Each life a faded, lesser copy
of the one before.
Wake up, eat, work, sleep,
reproduce, and die.
Everyone
is just
waiting.
Waiting
for it all to be over.
All while performing
in a silly, terrible play,
day after day.
[ticking]
I could not do that.
I could not close off my mind
and join in the madness.
I could not pretend.
And I realized
I didn't have to.
[ticks]
[distorted chiming]
[unsettling audio distortion]
[whirring]
I could make my own rules.
I could restore balance to a broken world.
A predator…
but for good.
[shrill shriek]
[panicked chittering]
[rabbit struggling]
As I practiced, I realized
I could do more than I possibly imagined.
I could reach into others,
into their minds,
their memories.
[bones cracking]
[rabbit shrieking]
I became an explorer.
I saw my parents as they truly were.
To the world,
they presented themselves
as good, normal people.
But like everything else in this world,
it was all a lie.
A terrible lie.
They had done things, Eleven.
Such awful things.
[dramatic organ music continues]
[baby wailing]
I showed them who they really were.
I held up a mirror.
My naive father believed
it was a demon
cursing them for their sins.
But my mother somehow knew.
Knew it was I
who was holding up that mirror,
-and she despised me for it.
-["Dream a Little Dream" playing faintly]
-She called a doctor, an expert.
-[static garbling signal]
She wanted him to lock me away, to fix me,
even though it wasn't I who was broken.
It was them.
And so she left me with no choice.
No choice but to act.
To break free.
[energy thrumming]
[dramatic music playing]
[Virginia screams]
[bones cracking]
With each life I took, I grew stronger.
More powerful.
They were becoming a part of me.
But I was still a child.
[electricity buzzing]
And I did not yet know my limits.
And it nearly killed me.
He was arrested, blamed for the death
of my sister and mother,
just as I had planned.
But I was far from free.
I woke up from my coma only to find myself
placed in the care of a doctor,
the very doctor I had hoped to escape.
Dr. Martin Brenner.
[monitor beeping]
Papa.
But the truth…
the truth is he did not
just want to study me.
He wanted more.
He wanted to control.
When Papa finally realized
he could not control me,
he tried to recreate me.
[tattoo needle buzzing]
He began a program.
And soon,
others were born.
You were born.
And I am so glad you were, Eleven.
So very glad.
They're not gone, Eleven.
They're still with me.
[mysterious music playing]
In here.
You tricked me.
Tricked you?
No, I saved you.
You are a prisoner here,
just like me.
To your papa, you are nothing more
than an animal, a monster,
a lab rat to be tamed.
But the truth, Eleven,
the truth is just the opposite.
You are better than they are.
[emotional aria playing]
Superior.
That is why you frighten him.
If you come with me,
for the first time in your life,
you will be free.
Imagine what we could do together.
We could reshape the world,
remake it however we see fit.
Join me.
[aria swells]
No.
[music stops abruptly]
-[Eleven grunts]
-[One grunts]
[One pants]
[intense music playing]
[lights buzzing]
[Eleven struggling]
[One growling]
[slippers squeaking]
[high-pitched ringing]
[grunts]
He had found his strength
in a memory from his past.
Something that made him sad.
[powerful music building]
But also angry.
[bullies grunting]
Do you have a memory like that?
No! No! Jane!
[Eleven yelps]
[thud]
[whimpering]
[sinister snarling]
[Eleven screams]
No! No!
[energy thrumming]
[Eleven screams]
It wasn't supposed to end like this.
[bones cracking]
[Eleven struggling]
[wails]
[wail echoes]
[distorted whooshing]
[medical monitor beeping]
[baby crying]
Jane.
I love you.
[crying continues]
[gasps]
[audio distortions intensify]
[Terry] Jane.
[Eleven screams]
[epic music plays]
[electricity crackling]
[monitor beeping wildly]
It's happening.
[One struggling]
[epic music continues]
[high-pitched ringing]
[ringing intensifies]
-[Eleven yells]
-[One screams]
[screaming]
[wailing]
[music fades away]
[panting]
[ominous pulsing]
[wet writhing]
[thunder booms]
[One yelling]
[yelling]
[dramatic music playing]
[yells]
[yelling]
[ragged panting]
[dramatic music builds]
[music fades away]
[suspenseful outro music plays]