Do-doo-doo-do-do
Billy Dilley, we're subterranean
Billy Dilley, you're such a brainy kid
Billy Dilley, it's fascinating how
Billy Dilley, it's complicated now
Billy Dilley, situation critical
Billy Dilley, I hope it's fixable
Billy Dilley
Oh oh-oh-oh-oh ooooh
BILLY: Spending the day with you,
my precious gem,
has crystallized my feelings for you.
You're flawless and radiant in every way.
A guy could spend the rest of his life
with a rock formation like you.
In fact... Aha!
Just the thing I need
to finish my zuber duber.
The power source.
Beautiful and powerful.
I like that in a rock.
Let's get you home.
- (THUDS)
- Hi, Anaximander. Did you miss me?
I missed you, too.
MALE VOICE: We now return
to Attack of the Cheese Zombies.
Brie!
JANET: Jimmy, the cheddar zombies
are at the front door.
JIMMY: I know, Janet,
and they're about to break through.
- ZOMBIE: Brie!
- (BOTH GASP)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
- Guys.
- Hi, Billy.
Get a load of this beautiful rock.
That rock pillar forest has a bounty
of natural resources.
Sorry. For a second there,
I thought you said rock pillar forest.
- I did.
- Of course you did...
- Really?
- Don't you know
the rock pillar forest is cursed?
- Cursed?
- You can't take rocks from there.
Why ever not?
Because the rock pillar people
will turn you into a beast!
- (ROARS)
- Pfft. A beast.
Where did you hear such nonsense?
From an old orangutanasaur,
while we were having a sandwich.
She told me the legend that,
300 years ago, a curious orangutanasaur
snuck into the rock pillar forest,
stole a rock from the rock people.
The rock folk took their revenge
on the orangutanasaurs
by transforming them
into horrible beasts! (GASPS)
But, Marsha, the orangutanasaurs
are beasts.
How do you think they got that way?
Oh, Marsha, I stopped believing
in silly tall tales
way back in seventh grade.
That was, like, a whole year ago.
(CHUCKLES)
You don't understand, Billy.
This curse is serious.
First, you'll feel insatiable hunger.
Then, you'll notice your senses
are heightened
and overwhelming.
Finally, your big, beautiful brain
will shrivel into a primitive shadow
of what it used to be.
If you keep the rock,
you'll turn into a beast!
Pfft. I thought you were
beyond that kind of hocus-pocus.
Me, I'm a man of cold, hard facts.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Behold my latest accomplishment.
The zuber duber.
- Now to take it on its first test run.
- (MARSHA PANTING)
Billy, stop! It's not worth it!
I don't want to lose my second-best friend
in all of Subterranea Tania.
Wait, second? Who's the first?
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- MARSHA: Let me introduce her.
- Her?
- This is Dame Footsworth. Hiya.
- Pleased to meet...
- Return the rock,
or you'll become a beast!
Please, Billy!
I don't wanna have to walk you
twice a day. (SOBS)
(BILLY SIGHS)
All right. I'll put this perfect,
beautiful,
scientifically impossibly well-shaped rock
back for you, Marsha.
Really? I'm so relieved!
And now that that's settled,
I'm gonna get some more popcorn.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
It feels like we've just met,
and it's already...
(SNIFFLES) ...goodbye.
(SOBS)
Not yet. (SOBS)
Just one brief moment in the zuber duber
before we say goodbye.
No one has to know.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(TRIANGLE CHIMES)
ZUBER DUBER: Initiating departure mode.
Departure mode... Uh-oh.
(WHIRRING, CRASHING)
- Uh...
- (ZUBER DUBER TOOTS)
Uh...
You put the rock back already...
(SCREAMS)
I can explain.
I just couldn't bring myself
to return the rock...
Billy, how could you?
Hurry, Billy. We must find the zuber
and return the rock
to the rock pillar forest
before your transformation
into a beast is complete.
But, Marsha,
I really think you're overreacting.
- (SCREAMS) Look.
- BILLY: The zuber duber trail.
- (STOMACH GROWLS)
- Billy, was that you?
- (GROWLING CONTINUES)
- Yep, it's just my stomach growling.
I'm so famished, I could eat a horse.
- Or a hot dog.
- A horse? (GASPS)
The transformation has begun!
(SHUDDERS)
No, no, it was just a figure of speech.
I skipped my second breakfast earlier,
- and my appetite is...
- Insatiable! Oh, Billy!
We've got to find the zuber duber
before it's too late!
Insatiable? Oh, that, Marsha,
always overreacting.
Or is she? Whoa!
Keep your eyes peeled.
(SNORTING, SNEEZING)
(BLOWS NOSE) Allergies.
There must be petunias nearby.
- Hmm. A petunia!
- My sense of smell is very accurate.
- What color do you think it is?
- I don't know. Blue?
Almost spot on.
Heightened senses, they're the second part
of the transformation.
I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
Or is it?
Come on. We've gotta find that zuber
and get that rock back to its home.
Don't worry, we'll get it... Home?
Marsha, that's it!
The zuber homing beacon.
It emits a sound that only the zuber duber
responds to.
It'll follow the signal
back to its source.
- Oh, you mean like a dog whistle?
- Something like that.
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
- (EAGLE SQUAWKS)
- Uh... uh... Oops.
- (GROWLING)
- Sorry. Wrong homing beacon.
- (SIGHS)
(BEEPING)
Oh, as you can see, Marsha,
I haven't become primitive in the least,
proving that curse of yours
is a bunch of... What?
(STUTTERS) Wh... what's that on my cheek?
The curse!
- (SHRIEKS)
- Billy, what is it?
Marsha, I think I'm a beast!
Look at it, Marsha. Gaze upon the horror.
- I don't see anything.
- Hold on. How about now?
A hair! Oh, my gosh!
You have become a beast!
Let's get the rock
back to the rock people.
Maybe they can still remove the curse.
- (HORN HONKING)
- It's too late for me, Marsha.
I can feel the beast inside me.
Growing too strong!
The itchy skin tells me
my pelt is growing,
forcing me to rip off my human clothing!
I wonder if I'll be a brindle.
Or maybe a blue point.
Run, Marsha! Get away from me
while you still can!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
- (PANTS)
- Uh, what's going on?
- Billy's a beast. He's turned...
- (BANGING ON DOOR)
...we have to keep him out!
That's impossible.
I'm sure it's just a misunderstan...
- (GROWLING)
- Do something!
What's he doing now?
ZEKE: Oh, no.
He's going for the house key.
- (GROWLING)
- Never mind.
MARSHA: Well, I'm not taking any chances.
Good thinking.
Well, I'm gonna hit the men's room.
(SCRAPING)
(PANTING) Phew!
(THUDDING, CLINKING)
(GRUNTING) Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Are you okay in there?
- ZEKE: (GROANS) Get out!
Well, don't forget to flush.
- Flush. That's it. (GRUNTS) Gotta flush.
- (TOILET FLUSHES)
(BILLY SCREAMING)
(SIGHS, GRUNTS)
(BOTH GROAN)
While you were in there, I secured
every door, window, dumbwaiter...
- porthole, vent, and WiFi router.
- (BEEPS)
That's great, but what about that big hole
in the ceiling?
- (GROWLING)
- (BOTH SCREAMING)
(BURBLES)
(ZEKE SCREAMS, GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- (SCREAMS)
- (SHRIEKING)
- (SCREAMING)
- Whoa. Nice broom work, Marsha.
- Thanks.
Guess we better take that rock back,
and reverse the curse
before Billy wakes up.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- Whew! Think we finally shook him.
- (SIGHS) What a relief.
(BOTH PANTING)
Oh, mighty rock person.
We return your rock.
Oh, please turn Billy back into a human.
Hmm. What's that?
(BILLY PANTING)
- The curse for stealing a rock.
- Curse? What curse?
- (PAINTING CONTINUES)
- What?
- I don't put curses on people.
- (SHRIEKING)
Eh. What? Did you say there isn't a curse?
Are you kidding me?
I'm a rock person, not a magician.
But what about when I was overcome
with insatiable hunger?
You probably missed your second breakfast.
It always makes my tummy rumble.
- Then how did I know about the petunias?
- I always know when petunias are around.
- They give me terrible hay fever.
- Then how do you explain the hair?
It's a hair!
I'm a rock person, and I have hair.
Mostly on my back. See.
- Ooh.
- (RETCHES)
So if I'm not a beast, then I was right!
There isn't such a thing as a curse.
(GROANS)
(RUMBLING)
Actually, what I said was,
I don't put curses on people.
But they do.
(GROWLING)
(SIZZLING)
Hey, Marsha, sure you don't want in
on these hash browns?
Oh, no, thanks, Zeke,
but Billy looks like he could use
a second helping.
(SLURPING, PANTS)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHISTLING)
Feeling good, feeling right...
- (SHRIEKS)
- (ZARTRAN GROANS)
Young lad. I was in a battle.
(GASPS) A great, epic... (GROANS)
- Gee, mister.
- The name's Zartran.
Gee, Zartran.
Maybe we should get you back to my place
- where my friends and I could...
- I can't put you and your friends...
(SCREAMING) ...out. If you insist.
(GRUNTING) Okay, come on.
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
- Guys! This is Zartran.
- Greetings.
I don't want to be a bother,
but these arrows seem to be lodged
in a few vital organs.
- Oh, you poor thing!
- Uh...
Quick, find the first-aid kit.
- Or second-aid kit.
- In the kitchen.
Nice place. (HUMMING)
Oh, real nice.
MALE VOICE: Why don't you come clean
and tell me who stole the family jewels.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
- (GIGGLES)
(GRUNTS, SIGHS) Yep. Score.
Zartran, we couldn't find the... (SHRIEKS)
- What happened to all your arrows?
- Oh, the arrows.
I pulled them out, one by one, by myself.
- Wow!
How'd you get shot?
There I was, in the land of Cotyledon,
volunteering in the soup kitchen,
as I am one to do,
when suddenly, my arch nemesis,
- the Gumbrump, appeared in line.
- (TEETH CHATTERING)
He drank everybody's soup! (SLURPS)
(ALL SHUDDERING)
So I chased him outside.
But he ambushed me,
and pulled my ponytail scrunchy clean off
with all seven of his arms. (GROANS)
(GASPING)
Then I made him carry
seven heavy suitcases
up the stairs of insanity!
- That must've finished him off.
- Not even close. (GRUNTS)
And then he threw his soup at me. (GROANS)
So I punched him in his big, dumb eye!
(GROANS)
Then he ran away. The end.
- Holy guacamole!
- Whoa! Amazing!
And that's when you got shot
with the arrows?
Oh, uh... Uh... Oh, no.
My legs. Giving out. (GROANS)
Must be post-battle stress disorder.
It's overpowering! (GRUNTS, SNORING)
We should let him stay here for a while
until he recovers.
- You're right, Zeke.
- (SNORING CONTINUES)
(GIGGLES)
(YAWNS)
- (GASPS)
- (GROANS) Stay away from me, ground sloth.
Oh, hi, Zartran. Sorry to trip you
with my body.
Oh, that's perfectly fine.
But now that you mention it...
I am a little hungry.
Ta-da! I hope you like your eggs
sunny side up.
(CHOMPING)
Zartran, last night as I was sleeping
on that hard floor right there,
- I kept dreaming about your epic battle.
- (CHOMPING CONTINUES)
- Please tell us again.
- Yeah. Tell us every barbaric detail!
- Tell us, tell us.
- BOTH: Tell us, tell us.
- (GULPS)
- Yes, like I said,
I was battling that Gumbrump,
but he's got three arms, and he's...
- BILLY: Oh. Oh, wait.
I thought you said seven arms.
Well, he has seven now.
He can grow three more arms
any time he wants.
But three more only makes six.
(MUMBLES) Oh!
Oh, the seventh one, he stole
from the poor saps in the soup line!
So that's how he carried
the seven suitcases.
- Wow!
- Whew!
There's still one thing
I don't understand.
- I can't believe this kid!
- (DOOR UNLOCKS)
- 'Sup, guys?
- Zeke! Zeke! Tell me, what is that object?
You mean my hacky bag?
(CHUCKLES) Yes!
You must regale me with the tale
of how you achieved such mastery
over this hacky bag of yours.
Sure thing, Zar-dog.
It was me, Trevor, and Chris,
and we were totally bored one day, so...
This affords me the perfect opportunity
to shift the focus.
- Ah.
- So where exactly
do these stairs of insanity lead?
Off me, creature!
Billy, Zartran wants to hear
about the bag master.
Sorry, Zeke.
Oh, please, Zeke, start again.
I've got all the time in the world.
- (SLURPS)
- Hey, Zartran buddy...
(SPITS) You certainly are
a persistent little fellow, aren't you?
The reason you are confused
is that I left out the part
where I body slammed
the Gumbrump so hard that it ripped open
a hole in the space-time continuum,
which we tunneled through,
head... (MUNCHING) ...over heels...
for a thousand eternities!
- Wow.
- Whoa.
We arm wrestled each other for supremacy
until the landscape was decimated,
leaving nothing but sand. The end.
So now, O curious one,
have I answered all of your questions?
- Every single question was answered.
- Whew!
And every single answer
raised several more questions.
What do you want?
A full-scale reenactment or something?
- Reenactment! Reenactment!
- Uh... W... wait, I...
- ALL: Reenactment! Reenactment!
- Hold that thought.
- Reenactment! Reenactment!
- ALL: Reenactment! Reenactment!
- ZARTRAN: A full-scale reenactment?
How in the loincloth am I gonna do that?
Ah, forget it. I'll just leave.
I mean, who needs things like...
fuzzy toilet seat cover?
No. It's just too much to give up.
Who's ready for a full-scale reenactment?
(CHUCKLES)
- All right!
- (BOTH CHEERING)
(CHUCKLES)
The first thing we'll need is soup.
From the soup kitchen?
Let's go get it, you guys!
Now for a little Plan B!
(GROANS, GIGGLES)
Hello. Goodbye! (CHUCKLES)
Whoo-hoo. Yah! (GIGGLES)
(BURBLES)
(YAWNS) Aha, here we are.
(GROANING)
- ZEKE: Marsha, grab the soup!
- MARSHA: I have the soup.
Hey, Zartran soup's... Oh!
- Just look at this place.
- And look at Zartran.
- Zartran!
- Huh? Oh.
What happened, Zartran?
The Gumbrump was just here. (COUGHS)
- (ZARTRAN GASPS)
- Here?
And we partook in another epic battle.
A real battle.
Aw, man, I can't believe we missed Zartran
in a real battle.
Good news, my friends.
The Gumbrump is coming back.
But the bad news is
that it's far too dangerous
for you to stay here.
So, for your own safety,
you'll have to find a new place to live.
- (BOTH GASP)
- What's that?
Gather a few prized possessions,
and leave before it is too late.
I shall protect this place
to the best of my ability.
It is the least I can do...
Oh, and, Zeke,
- better leave me the keys, son.
- Good call. Thanks, Zartran. Be safe, bro.
Woo! (LAUGHS) I win!
It's mine, all mine.
- (WHOOPING)
- Wow. Zartran sounds real upset
- about us having to leave.
- He's not only brave, he's sensitive.
- He's the perfect man!
- Oh, no, Marsha. You've been shot.
With Cupid's arrow.
Looks more like you were shot
by the Gumbrump to me.
What? Eww!
That's the last time I go clothes shopping
in the dumpster.
Wait.
- "Property of Zartran."
- He's a total phony.
And he took advantage of our hospitality,
just so he could steal our house!
We've got to figure out a way
to get it back from him.
I feel so violated.
Wait a second. What's this?
- What is it, Billy?
- What do you see?
Guys, I think I have a plan.
(GROWLING)
Pardon me, sir,
but you wouldn't happen to be
- the Gumbrump, would you?
- Who want to know?
See, I told you this was the guy
Zartran beat up.
- What?
- Oh, yeah. He said he beat you
like a big, soft crying drum.
Where is this liar?
He's right down there.
In that house.
Stand to side.
Gumbrump have important business
with rotten little liar man!
- (ZARTRAN SCREAMING)
- Could've used the door.
- (ZARTRAN GRUNTING)
- (GUMBRUMP GRUNTING)
Well, at least we finally
get front-row seats to an epic battle.
Now it time to finish you
once and for all.
That's an entertaining story, but...
you're gonna have to catch me first.
Gumbrump get you!
Doodly doozers, guys!
We got our house back!
- (SHRIEKS) Who goes there?
- (GROWLS)
(WHIMPERS) Oh, hey, Francis. Have a seat.
Oh, thanks, Zart, old buddy.
Sorry for going so hard on you earlier,
partner, but they were watching.
- I had to make it look good.
- Eh, no hard feelings.
Plan A kinda went south,
so we had to improvise.
- Did you at least get some food?
- Only the mother lode.
Tonight, we feast like kings!
(BELCHES)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I said
You've got the wrong number
For the right guy
I'll do the job for you
Just pay the price
Run, run, run away
Baby, stick to the plan!
Whoo whoo!
Run, run, run away
Catch me if you can