Doo doo-doo-doo doo
Billy Dilley, we're subterranean
Billy Dilley, you're such a brainy kid
Billy Dilley, it's fascinating how
Billy Dilley, it's complicated now
Billy Dilley, situation critical
Billy Dilley, I hope it's fixable
Billy Dilley
Oh oh-oh-oh-oh ooooh
(GLASS BREAKING, PUNCHES LANDING)
(GRUNTING, GROANING)
Can't you chuckleheads read?
No con artists allowed!
Con artists? Huh.
That doesn't necessarily mean us.
RHINO: Ahem.
Beat it!
Ya chuckleheads!
(TURTLES WHINNY)
- (COUGHS)
- (COUGHS, SIGHS)
- Well, guess it's boiled shoes again.
- Dibs on the insole.
(MUNCHES, GAGS) Bleah! Bleah!
Oh, Francis. I'm tired of living
on under-seasoned footwear.
We can't even scam ourselves
a piece of pie!
They even had pecan.
What we need is a big score!
- Size thirteens!
- No. I mean big big.
So big, we could have
all the pecan pie we could eat!
It's my favorite.
Gee, it's not like an opportunity like
that is gonna just hit you in the face.
What the... Old lady offering reward
for the return
of long-lost nephew, Willie?
"If you return him safely to me,
a great treasure awaits you.
"Love, Aunt Agnes." This is it!
All we have to do is pose
as this long-lost nephew!
Well, how hard can that be?
Hmm. If only we knew someone
who resembled this nephew.
BILLY: Oh, leaves!
I can see you from my windowsill.
- Green is the color of your chlorophyll
- Billy Dilley!
- What?
- It is I, your glorious friend...
- Zartran.
- Hi, Zartran!
I've come to you because someone
needs your help.
- My help?
- There is an old lady named Aunt Agnes
- who is very, very sad.
- Sad?
But you, Billy Dilley, you could make her
happy once more.
- I can?
- All you have to do
is pretend to be
her long-lost nephew, Willie.
- Will you help, Billy?
- I willie will, Zartran!
(CHUCKLING) Okay, Willie.
Ringest thou bell.
Huh? Uh, yeah. That's me.
(RECORDING OF DOORBELL PLAYS)
- Hello.
- Good afternoon, Ma'am.
I am Zartran,
and I have come to reunite you with...
- your long-lost nephew Willie!
- Hi, Aunt, uh, uh...
- Agnes.
- Oh, yeah. Hi, Aunt Agnes.
Willie! My, how you've grown.
Really, really grown.
Why, just last week you looked like this.
Uh... (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY) Yes, well,
there's a perfectly good explanation
for...
I've been working on a donut farm.
- You have?
- (LAUGHING) Well!
Aren't you just delicious!
Aha! Billy, I believe I see a donut
on the lawn that needs harvesting.
I'm all over it, Zartran!
So, since said nephew
has been returned safe and sound,
I believe you have a little
sumthin-sumthin for me?
Of course! Aunt Agnes
will be right back
with Mr. Zartran's treasure.
Treasure! That's exactly why we're here!
To treat you to a day of fun and games
- that you'll treasure forever!
- We are?
A day of fun and games?
Well, aren't you boys
a couple of sweet peaches!
Come on in! Let's get this party started!
Bah-bah-boop-boop-boo-boo. (GIGGLES)
Remember the games
we used to play, Willie?
(LAUGHS) What was that one
you liked so much?
- Ring around the...
- Rosie?
Rosie? No!
The song we used to sing went,
- Ring around the...
- Eh...
- AGNES: Ring around the...
- Hat rack?
Ring around the...
- Tea cozy?
- Ring around the...
- Creepy doll face toilet roll cover?
- What's gotten into you, Willie?
Are you even my long-lost nephew?
- Uh, uh...
- Let's try this, one more time!
Ring around the...
Uh, uh, Barbarian?
Oh! You remembered!
BOTH: Ring around the Barbarian
BOTH: Loin cloths are very in.
BILLY: Bashes! Clashes!
We all fall down!
ZARTRAN: (MUFFLED) Well... (LAUGHS)
...I'd say Aunt Agnes
has had enough excitement for one day.
We don't want to put
any undue strain on her.
The only strain on Aunt Agnes
is from smiling
from having such a good... (SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
- It's working, Zartran!
- (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY, SIGHS)
- What do you want to play next, Agnes?
- Please make it stop.
How about...
Paint the Barbarian.
Paint the Barbarian?
Well, why didn't you say so?
- (SWORD RINGS)
- This physique was made to be painted!
(SPITS)
Say "Adorable Pink Bunny Man!"
(GROWLING, ROARING)
(ROARING, SCREECHING) Eh?
- (ROARING)
- (SCREAMS)
- Oh, no!
- (ROARS)
Boy, he sure was hungry.
Zartran, guess what I made?
It's a list of even more games
we can play to make Aunt Agnes happy.
Spin the barbarian, pin the tail
on the barbarian, roll the barbarian...
Enough! Egads!
Oh, yeah. We bandaged your wounds
with doilies.
(GRUNTS, GROWLS) That does it!
Under seasoned footwear
is sounding pretty good
right about... (GASPS, SNIFFS)
- Wait. Is that...
- Fresh pecan pie.
Fresh pecan pie?
With a flaky, buttery crust! (MUNCHING)
Oh! Ah, tastes just like love.
(SOBS) You're like the nana,
I never had.
This calls for more pie.
Nana? I have something I need to tell you.
- We have been conning you.
- What was that, dearie?
I dressed my friend up like your nephew,
Willie, so we could trick you
out of your treasure.
But a beautiful creature like you
doesn't deserve any of that! (SOBBING)
No one has ever said
anything like that to me before.
- Oh, from the heart?
- No! Into a tape recorder!
ZARTRAN: We have been conning you.
Nana? Your con artist career has come
to a close,
Gregory P. Zartran.
This is Special Agent Aunt Agnes
in the fly trap requesting backup.
- You mean, you're...
- That's right! I'm The Fuzz!
- The Fuzz!
- Hey, I got more pie... (GASPS)
Not now, Billy.
- Aunt Agnes has some baking to do!
- (ZARTRAN WHIMPERS)
- Aunt Agnes?
- Billy, help me!
(WHIMPERS, GASPS)
Zartran!
Wha... Now why'd you go and do that, boy?
(SCREAMING)
- Billy! What have you done?
- She was going to hurt the barbarian.
Not that. You ruined the pecan pie!
- Why? Why!
- (SIREN BLARING)
- Huh?
- POLICE OFFICER: Criminals!
We have you surrounded!
- It's The Fuzz!
- The Fuzz!
- Tell 'em we're gonna get 'em.
- We are gonna get you!
Come out! Oh, cool... (LAUGHS)
...Thanks, guys.
Uh, he did it. All him!
It was totally him! His idea!
He conned her! It was all him! Not me.
Um, is this true, son?
If protecting my fair-weather friend
from a sap-happy old bat is a crime,
then call me a criminal!
(PLAYING THE BLUES ON HARMONICA)
- Hey, keep it down over there.
- They got you too?
Yeah, but not before I got...
the treasure!
Aunt Agnes's treasure!
(GASPS, HOOTS)
Open it, Francis! Open it!
A decorative photo album?
BOTH: A decorative photo album!
Memories are the greatest treasure of all!
Excusez-moi.
Look! There's you as a bunny.
- And there's you being velocirapted.
- (CRYING) Those were special times.
- All right, chuckleheads.
- Lunchtime!
OFFICER 2: Today we are offering
boiled shoe.
Oh, boy! Size thirteen!
You know, memories like these
will last a lifetime.
(SLURPING) You said it, Willie.
BOTH: It's Billy.
(LAUGHING)
(CRANK SQUEAKING)
Gotcha.
Huh? Yowzers! My berries are missing!
Aha! Footprints.
That can only mean one thing,
someone with feet stole my berries.
I'll get to the bottom of this
if it's the last thing I...
Eh, my berry? There you are.
- Hey!
- (PANTING)
Gimme back that... (GASPS)
- (GASPS)
- All right, hand it over.
Bleah.
Ah! Okay. Uh, you can have half.
(BOTH MUNCH)
You're a Troggie! I've encountered
the grownups of your species,
but never a little guy like you!
- My name is Billy.
- (GROANS)
- Yucky!
- Nice to meet you, Yucky.
Um... (CHUCKLES) ...whoo!
Oh! Uh, I guess you've never seen
a human before. (CHUCKLES)
(GROANS) Uh.
Ooh! Ooh! Yucky!
- Wow! A wart.
- Hey, eh?
Fascinating.
- (TWANGING)
- Oh! No way!
That's what I'm talkin' about!
- Do you mind if I try?
- Um, Yucky.
- (TWANGING)
- (CHUCKLES) Just one more!
- (MAMA YUCKY GROWLS)
- Goawah. Yucky.
You have to go already?
But... But... Nice meeting you
and spending time with you!
You too, Yucky!
That's it, it's over. I'm never gonna see
anything that fun again.
I've peaked at age 12.
- (SLURPS)
- You are so right, Anaximander.
I've got way cooler stuff
than that little old wart.
Uh-huh. Here we go. An old piece of bread
with an entire civilization
of mold living on it.
(SNEEZES)
Or how about this thing? It's a...
A... I don't actually know
what this thing is.
Oh, who am I kidding?
I have to have that wart if I'm ever
gonna be truly happy again!
I mean, Yucky probably
doesn't even realize what he has.
A wart like that has special needs.
It requires love and attention.
More love, more attention,
back to love again, and then attention,
and then still more love,
and some more attention,
a little more love, and more attention,
and love and some attention,
- and love, and attention...
- (SIGHS)
it needs love, it needs attention.
I'm just gonna have to take it!
But taking it would be bad.
Well, what if I just borrow it?
And then I can return it... eventually.
That kind of sounds like stealing.
Or does it?
I'm just gonna have to do what's right,
for me and for Yucky.
But mostly for me.
(SNORING)
- (BILLY PANTING)
- (OBJECTS CLANKING)
(CLANKING CONTINUES)
(SNORING)
Ah. Bingo.
(CLANKING)
Wakey-wakey, little wart. (GIGGLES)
Sleepy-sleep, Yucky sleep.
Sleep, sleep, sleep.
There you go, that's good.
(DEVICE WHINES)
(BEEPING)
(GIGGLES)
Whee!
(LAUGHS)
(BILLY ROARING, GROWLING)
(PLAYS VIOLIN)
(SOBS) It's so beautiful!
- Hey, Zeke!
- Uh-huh?
You notice anything different
about, uh, Billy?
- There's a bump on your arm?
- No, no, no, no. It's a wart.
Look. Look. Watch. Watch. Look.
Look. Watch. Look.
Are you looking? Are you looking?
(GIGGLES) You wanna see it again?
Only if it means not looking at it,
talking about it or acknowledging it
- in any way.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hold that thought, Zeke. Hello... Oh, no.
Yucky!
- (WHIMPERING)
- Who's at the door, Billy?
Mm, eh. (GASPS)
- (SLURPS)
- Well, hello.
- Look, Billy. It's a little Troggie.
- Why, so it is.
- Yucky.
- He says his special wart is missing?
Don't get all goopsie-whoopsie.
We'll find something else
to replace your missing wart.
Billy, are we still talking about
your new wart?
- Yucky?
- Billy's got a new wart? I wanna see!
(CHUCKLES) Hey, now! Let's not go and say
something that I'm gonna regret.
(SLURPS)
- (SCREAMS)
- Billy!
- Yucky!
- Uh-huh.
- (SCREAMS)
- Billy!
- Yucky!
- Uh-huh.
Everybody just take a breath.
- Yu... Yu... Yu...
- Now, Yucky, isn't it true that your wart
- had two hairs?
- Yuck, yuck.
Well, as you can plainly see,
my wart has...
(PANTS, GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
- ...one hair.
- (FANFARE)
(SOBS)
No need for tears, Yucky. You'll find
your wart. You probably just dropped it
- somewhere, right?
- (SOBS) Yucky?
It could be anywhere.
You coulda dropped it in a, uh,
- uh...
- (STOMACH RUMBLES, BURPS)
BILLY: ...uh, oh, um...
(FIZZLES)
Oh, yeah! You coulda dropped it
in a volcano for all we know, right?
- Yu-ucky?
- You just gotta get back out there
and keep lookin'.
- Yucky.
- Well, now that that's solved... (YAWNS)
- ...off to bed for me. See ya.
- Bed?
- Yeah, Zeke. It's 2:30 in the afternoon.
- Yucky.
Man, hiding the truth
from your friends is hard work.
(CHUCKLES) But it sure is worth it!
(HOOTS, SNORES)
- Yucky...
- (YUCKY PANTS)
BILLY: Heck, you coulda dropped it
in a volcano for all we know.
Yucky!
- (SCREAMING)
- (BILLY SCREAMS)
This picture is terrifying! But also....
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES) He's in trouble!
Terrible, terrible danger!
- Who?
- Yucky! I gotta save him!
- Why?
- Because I sent him to his doom!
What?
Yucky!
I'm too late! (WHIMPERS)
Oh, Yucky!
What have I done, and why?
This silly little wart... (WHIMPERS)
Oh. (GIGGLES)
- (TWANGS)
- No!
Without Yucky in my life,
I don't want the wart anymore!
(BAWLS)
- (DEVICE BEEPING)
- (BELL DINGS)
Goodbye, wart! Goodbye, Yucky!
(BAWLS)
(CONTINUES BAWLING)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
- (BILLY SCREAMING)
BOTH: Huh? (GRUNTING)
- (YUCKY SOBBING)
- Yucky?
(GASPS) Yucky!
You're not a smoldering pile of dusty ash!
(SOBS)
Ah, yeah. Your wart.
I am so sorry, Yucky. I borrowed...
No, I stole your wart in cold blood,
and then threw it into a volcano.
- Yu-ucky?
- I'm a horrible friend!
Horrible! Horrible! Horrible friend!
- Horrible!
- Ah... Yucky.
No, no, just a few more.
Horrible! Horrible!
Horrible! Horrible! Horrible!
Horrible friend!
Yuh-yuh-yuck-yuck-yuck-yuck!
(TWANGS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
- (TWANGS)
- (LAUGHING)
Yuck!... (CHUCKLES) ...Yucky!
Whoa! Back it up! This one's mine!
- Yucky!
- No, no, no! You can come over
- and flick it and stretch it any time!
- YUCKY: Yucky!
BILLY: The wart stays on
my head, ya understand?
YUCKY: (CHUCKLES) Yucky!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I said you've got the wrong number
For the right guy
I'll do a good job for you
Just pay the price
Run, run, run away
- Baby, stick to the plan
- Whoo, Whoo!
Run, run, run away, catch me if you can