SARAH [VOICE-OVER]:
There are those who believe...
...that a child in the womb
shares his mother's dreams.
Her love for him,
her hopes for his future.
Is it told to him in pictures
while he sleeps inside her?
Is that why he reaches for her in that
first moment and cries for her touch?
But what if you've known since he was
inside you what his life held for him.
That he would be hunted, that his fate
was tied to the fate of millions...
...that every moment of your life
would be spent keeping him alive?
Would he understand
why you were so hard?
Why you held on so tight?
Would he still reach for you...
...if the only dream you've ever shared
with him was a nightmare?
Would he know my love
runs through him like blood?
John, now.
Now.
- The cops make you at the diner?
- I don't know. Maybe.
Yes, definitely.
COP 1 [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Sarah Connor, John Connor.
Drop what you're carrying.
Put your hands on your head
and kneel on the ground.
Now!
[JOHN GRUNTS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[ENGINE TURNS OVER AND STARTS]
[RADIO CHATTER]
Do me a favor, will you?
Fix it.
COP 2:
Ohhhh!
[COP 2 GRUNTING]
[COP 2 MOANING]
[SIREN WAILING]
COP 1:
Drop your weapon!
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[SARAH GRUNTS]
Move. Move.
Get down.
You run! Run!
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
John!
John. John.
John.
No.
Do it!
Do it, kill me.
Nothing matters anymore.
Kill me!
You're right.
Nothing matters anymore.
Only the boy.
The future's ours.
And it begins now.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Hey.
Did you scream or something?
Scream? No.
[SIGHS]
Go back to sleep.
No, I can't. I've got early shift.
Are you all right?
I'm good.
- Yeah?
- I'm great.
Well, you damn well better be.
You know the guy down at the store
told me any woman would be lucky...
...to have this ring.
He doesn't know the giver like I do.
You wanna know a secret?
I don't know. I don't like secrets.
No? Ha, ha, this is a good one.
- Really? Oh.
- Yeah.
All right.
John picked it out.
Yeah, well, sort of.
I'd been looking and looking and
I kind of started freaking myself out...
...with the whole color and cut
and clarity...
So you turned the job over
to a 15-year-old boy?
You think I'm a jackass, don't you?
Thinking I love you.
Always remember that.
Early shift.
- Better get going.
- Right.
Early shift. Uh-huh.
Bye.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Mom, how many times have I told you
it's freaky when you do that?
I'm sorry.
Mmm.
What's going on?
We can't stay here, John.
What?
It's not safe.
Not safe from who?
No one knows us.
No one asks questions.
It's been almost two years.
School starts in, like, three weeks.
- We need to go.
- No, you need to go.
You're scared. He gave you a ring
and now you freak out.
- I know you like him.
- So do you, Mom.
So do you.
You love him, I know you do.
Listen to me,
the cops will never find us, we're safe.
Don't you think that, John.
Don't you ever think that. Look at me.
No one is ever safe.
Half an hour.
One bag...
...plus the guns.
I'll make pancakes.
SARAH [VOICE-OVER]:
Every family has rules...
...and we had ours.
Keep your head down.
Keep your eyes up.
Resist the urge to be seen
as important or special.
Know your exits.
COP: I mean, she's not
exactly missing, right?
- The way you explain it.
- Right.
The way I explained it,
she's not missing, she left.
- Happens more than you think.
- You don't know her.
I could say the same to you,
Mr. Dixon.
DIXON:
FBI?
Been together long?
Six months, maybe.
Bit of a whirlwind.
Ha, ha, ha. You have no idea
the whirlwind.
Tell me, does the Skynet
defense system mean anything to you?
No.
How about this guy?
Miles Dyson. No.
Never seen him before.
That's because he's dead.
Your fiancée freshly escaped from the
Pescadero Mental Hospital...
...blew him apart two years ago.
Leveled a four-story research lab
along with him.
But since there's no lethal injection
for the destruction of property...
...let's just stick with the murder of one
of our brightest computer scientists...
...and a dedicated family man.
That's... It's just not...
Why would she do that, huh?
Well, you know, Mr. Dixon.
It's the robots.
The ones from the future.
The ones Skynet sent to kill her son?
Which makes total sense, because in
the future, John's not only her son but...
What does it say here?
"The leader of the resistance
fighting artificially intelligent machines...
...determined to annihilate
the human race."
Did he strike you that way?
Leader of a scrappy band of rebels?
Luke Skywalker type?
He's just a kid.
He's a great kid.
He was like a son to me.
I came down here for help.
You can't really be asking me this.
No, I'm not.
This is just my patter, Mr. Dixon.
This is me impressing upon you that I'm
not here because you lost your fiancée.
Love of your life and all around
good-time girl.
I'm here because my boss,
the United States...
...thinks Sarah Connor is a deluded,
dangerous, Grade A whack-a-mole...
...who killed a man because she believes
in the future he'll invent a computer...
...that declares war on the world.
So let's begin with her name.
I understand it's not Connor.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
MAN 1: I couldn't go, so I saved it all
till the last minute.
MAN 2: How'd it turn out?
MAN 1: Ah, I think all right.
You'll be responsible
for three chapters a week.
You have a quiz each Friday.
You'll be allowed one makeup test
with a parent's note.
- If you're late for class without a note...
- What's your name?
- John.
- Cameron.
...Cleaning beakers.
And no talking while I'm talking.
[STUDENTS CHUCKLING]
John?
- Hey.
- I haven't seen you around here before.
- Did you just move here?
- Yeah, I did.
- Ha, ha. Sucks for you.
- Ha.
My dad sells tractors.
- What about yours?
- Insurance.
Really? What kind?
- The boring kind.
- Ha, ha, ha.
Those are the kind of tractors
my dad sells.
What about your mom?
My mom stays home.
You know, I've really gotta get
to the next class, so...
So maybe I'll see you later?
Sure, yeah.
Okay, well, bye.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
[CROWS CAWING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON HEADPHONES]
[ROCK MUSIC STOPS]
This is a hick town, Mom.
We've been in worse places.
A lot worse.
Well, my clothes are all wrong.
I need, like, some different shirts.
You know, here everyone wears boots?
Like cowboy boots.
I hate cowboy boots.
See what I can do.
Their computer's like from the frigging
'50s or something.
- Their computers? I thought we agreed.
- No, they switched my class.
- Last thing I need is you caught hacking.
- I'm not hacking. God, I know the rules.
They're, like, written on the inside
of my eyeballs, all right?
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
Hey.
You meet any pretty girls?
[JOHN SCOFFS]
No. I'm telling you, it's a hick town.
Come on.
Agent Ellison.
Welcome to New Mexico.
The sheriff's detached me to hustle
you around on your business here.
Whatever that is, he wouldn't say.
He doesn't know.
MAN [OVER PA]:... between Nutrition
and Second Period today.
Come and show your support.
Show some pep.
I lied to you yesterday.
My dad doesn't sell insurance.
He's dead.
He was a soldier.
He was killed on a mission.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, it's all right.
My mom was pregnant with me when
it happened. I never even knew him.
So it's all right.
My mom, she... She's...
She's kind of uptight.
Actually, no. She's really uptight.
She likes me to come home
after school...
...and hang out with her and that
kind of thing, you know?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I'm all she's got.
Thank you for explaining.
It'll be our secret.
[BELL RINGING]
Mr. Ferguson is ill today.
My name is Cromartie.
Is that your only name, like Madonna?
Madonna? Why? No.
[STUDENTS LAUGHING]
Let's take attendance, then.
- Marie Booeye?
- Here.
- Donald Chase.
- Franklin Lane.
- Here.
- Cynthia Nolan.
- Wayne Parker.
- Here.
Cameron Phillips.
Cameron?
Here.
Reese.
Do we have a John Reese?
[JOHN CLEARS THROAT]
Excellent.
[STUDENTS YELLING AND SCREAMING]
[TERMINATOR'S LEG WHIRRING]
Class dismissed.
WOMAN [ON TV]: Witnesses are
reporting gunfire just minutes ago...
...at Crestview High School
in Red Valley. Police are...
[GRUNTS]
Ahhh.
Come with me if you wanna live.
[GRUNTS]
- Sarah Connor.
- Where is he?
What have you done with him?
You don't know.
You don't know?
Killing yourself is the best strategy.
If you're alive,
I can use you against him.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[SARAH GAGGING]
[IN SARAH'S VOICE] John?
- Mom, Mom.
I tried to call you.
JOHN [ON PHONE]:
I've been trying to call you.
Listen to me, okay?
They're back. It's back.
John, slow down. Where are you?
JOHN: I'm going to the house.
- I'll be right there.
- Mom.
I love you, John. Stay right there.
Let's go.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES]
[DOG BARKING]
[GAGGING]
[IN SARAH'S VOICE]
John?
John.
Are you okay?
JOHN: Mom?
John?
John! No!
John!
[SARAH EXHALES SHARPLY]
CAMERON [IN JOHN'S VOICE]:
Neat trick. You like?
[SARAH GRUNTING]
Next time you do
what you're trained to do. You run.
Go. Ugh.
[ENGINE REWING]
[BANGING]
[JOHN GRUNTS]
Did you stop him?
One hundred twenty seconds
and the system reboots.
- I was sent here to protect John.
- Not now. Not yet.
You might want to put
those back in the holster.
Oh.
We should be good here
two more hours.
Hit the border at lunchtime.
What year are you from?
2027.
How long have you
been looking for us?
Seventy-three days.
And the war?
The Skynet missile defense system
goes online April 19th, 2011.
Declares war on mankind and triggers
a nuclear apocalypse two days later.
And Miles Dyson?
Someone else builds Skynet.
Who?
- We don't know.
- You don't know who builds...
...the computer that
blows up the world?
I wasn't sent here for that.
No. You were sent here to keep
my son from being assassinated.
Your fiancé went to the police.
You should've changed your alias.
Go to hell.
They'd have found you anyway.
They always do.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[CHATTERING ON RADIO]
There's Kevlar in that chair.
APB's statewide, but it's been...
Nineteen hours.
What the hell happened here?
Twenty-two witnesses, Deputy Ridge.
Twenty-two of your good town folk.
That's a whole football team.
Guess what 19 of them saw?
A shooter
with some kind of robot leg.
[SIGHS]
Hey.
Why is this happening again?
I don't know.
You stopped it.
I guess I didn't.
But you can.
You changed the future,
you didn't change it enough.
So you can do it again.
- I don't know, John.
- I can't keep running. I can't.
I'm not who they think I am.
Some messiah.
You don't know that.
I know.
I can't lead an army.
Maybe that's you but it'll never be me,
so you've gotta stop it.
Please.
Mom.
All right.
All right, what?
SARAH:
I'll stop it.
[BEEPING]
We're not going across the border.
Where are we going?
To find Skynet.
Chip?
Back at school...
...you apologized for lying to me.
So I should apologize for lying to you.
It's all right, I get it.
You needed to get close to me.
It's just the way you're...
...programmed.
Like some hot girl is really gonna try and
make friends with the new weird kid.
If I'd thought about it...
...I would have known something
was messed up, you know?
In the future, you have many friends.
What model are you?
Are you new? You seem...
...different.
I am.
Let's go.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Mom, pizza's here.
Mom, the pizza.
Mom?
- You.
- We need to talk about Miles, Tarissa.
Danny, go to your room. Right now.
- How dare you come here?
- I know what they told you.
- But it didn't happen that way.
- Get the hell out of here.
- Now.
- It didn't happen that way.
I can't let you do that.
TARISSA: Let go!
- Listen to me.
I didn't kill Miles.
[TARISSA INHALES SHARPLY]
All right? I didn't do it.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I would never.
Miles was a hero.
Then why are you here?
CAMERON:
We're back.
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
TARISSA: You told me
there'd be no more machines.
[TARISSA SIGHS]
Look, it's happening again.
Everything we fought to stop.
Miles' work at Cyberdyne
is the only link we have.
Is there anyone, anywhere
who's shown an interest in his work?
Anyone he could have told,
someone he forgot?
There's nobody. It's all gone.
You destroyed it all.
You and Miles destroyed...
[INHALES SHARPLY]
You destroyed everything.
[FOOTSTEPS]
We have to go.
Now.
[DOGS BARKING]
Help me.
Help my son.
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[ENGINE REWING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Mom! Mom!
[BEEPING]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Oh, God.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BANGING]
Bandages. Rubbing alcohol.
- Mom, you need a doctor.
- Go!
We'll find cover out back.
First aid kit on the floor.
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Get it done before he gets back.
I'll get some ice.
It'll numb you, slow the blood loss.
Needle and thread
slow the blood loss.
Do it now.
[SARAH EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CLOTHES RIPPING]
We can't keep running.
I'll lose my boy.
He'll leave me.
- What time is it?
- 7:52.
How's the arm?
Better.
CAMERON: Good.
- We need to go.
- Where?
I'll show you.
Do you have, like, an account here?
Safety deposit box.
When did you open that?
1963.
[CHATTERING]
Everybody on the floor.
Please.
[ALL CHATTERING LOUDLY]
Keys to the safety deposit boxes.
[GUN COCKS]
Get inside. Keys.
Lock us in
and then get away from the door.
I'll know if you don't.
You said you had a safety
deposit box.
I do.
Open these boxes.
Put everything you find on the table.
Carefully.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Hey, James. You gotta see this.
The alarm tripped seven minutes ago.
Camera autodumps a digital copy
to the L.A.P.D. servers.
Don't you know them?
Less and less all the time.
Is that from the future?
You can't bring anything through
when you come.
Not weapons, not clothing...
...nothing.
You send someone back to build it.
What is it?
Hope.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
Is that the police?
- No. Get away from the door.
- Why?
That's why.
That better be what I think it is.
CAMERON: One of our best engineers.
Took him eight months
to scavenge the parts.
When the isotope solution turns red,
you fire.
Isotope?
What, is this nuclear?
No, not really.
[CRASHING]
I don't get why you locked it.
- We didn't have to get trapped.
- You're not trapped.
What is that?
Engineer got a job building the vault.
So we'd always have a way
back home.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
[BANGING]
- What have you done?
- You wanna find Skynet?
You wanna stop Skynet?
- This is the way.
- You don't know who builds it.
No. But we know where
and we know when.
We can go kill it before it's born.
You can stop running,
stay in one place, fight.
[BANGING AND CRASHING]
[BANGING]
Mom, we gotta go, now.
Mom!
Do it!
[SARAH GRUNTS]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
- Where are we?
- Same where. Different when.
MAN 1:
Man, check this out.
MAN 2: Oh, yeah.
MAN 3: Oh, yeah.
MAN 4:
It'll be a good day, baby.
I got something for you.
[MEN GRUNTING]
So, this is where it all starts?
This is where Skynet begins?
Somewhere in there.
And nobody knows we're here?
You're safe.
- No one is ever safe.
Come on.
SARAH [VOICE-OVER]: It is said
that the death of any one person...
...is the death of an entire world.
Certainly for parents...
...the death of a child
is no less than a holocaust.
In the case of my son,
these words are literally true.
MAN [ON TV]:
And finally tonight...
...amateur video
of what we can only assume...
...is a college prank gone wrong...
...as three streakers caused chaos
trying to cross the 105 Freeway.
Honey, did you hear me? We're late.
Yeah, I heard you.
SARAH [VOICE-OVER]: And even though
we've traveled through time...
...bent the rules of nature...
...they will keep coming for him...
...keep trying to kill him.
But until that day...
...it's gonna be one hell of a dogfight.