SARAH: In the future, my son will lead
mankind in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system
programmed to destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
I haven't seen you around here before.
- Did you just move here?
- Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
- Sucks for you.
- Heh.
We can't stay here, John.
JOHN:
No one knows us. We're safe.
Don't you think that, John.
No one is ever safe.
DIXON:
FBI?
ELLISON: Your fiancée killed a man
because she believes that in the future...
...he'll invent a computer system
that declares war on the world.
TEACHER: Cameron Phillips?
- Here.
Do we have a John Reese?
Excellent.
[STUDENTS YELLING]
Come with me if you wanna live.
I'm not who they think I am.
You changed the future,
you just didn't change it enough.
So you can do it again.
You wanna stop Skynet? This is the way.
Mom, we gotta go now!
Do it!
SARAH: Where are we?
CAMERON: Same where.
Different when.
[HONKING]
SARAH:
A wise man once said, "Know thyself."
Easier said than done.
I've had nine aliases, 23 jobs,
spoken four languages...
...and spent three years in a mental hospital
for speaking the truth.
At least when I was there
I could use my real name.
Through it all, I've always known
who I am and why I'm here.
Protect my son.
Prepare him for the future.
But lately it's gotten harder to control.
Even as I try to help John
find firm ground in this new world...
...the battlefield shifts beneath our feet.
Maybe it's all catching up to me.
Maybe if you spend your life
hiding who you are...
...you might finally end up
fooling yourself.
Hey, how's it going?
All right. Ahem.
You bought me the wrong
needle-nose pliers though.
I did? You said red handles.
Oh. Heh.
I'm sorry. I, uh...
I guess I'm still...
- Heh, I don't know.
- I've been calling it time lag.
- What?
- It's like jet lag, but for time travel. Heh.
Time-lagged. Yeah, sounds about right.
You know what would help
with time lag? Some fresh air.
- John.
- I've been cooped up here for three days.
I know.
You don't know,
because you keep going outside.
Yeah, so will you, when we get new ID's.
- So let's get them already.
- We will.
Can you be patient, please?
It's not just a name.
It's a legend, a life, a whole new you.
- We go through this every time.
- This is different.
[FOOTSTEPS]
New IDs today? It's been three days.
I want my new name.
I want that whole new me.
Can't you track down Enrique?
All right, I'll track down Enrique.
Old friend. Ten years ago,
he was the best fake-paper guy around.
John sent back better ones.
You cannot walk into the living room
after three days...
Three days. And now, after three days...
...now you tell me
there are other people here?
Resistance fighters.
Resistance fighters. Humans.
Sent back from the future by John.
What, are they manning some kind of
apocalyptic paramilitary convenience store...
...filled with fake ID's
and guns and money?
[PHONE RINGS]
- Yes.
- You done yelling at her, yet?
I'm not yelling.
JOHN: Right.
Mom, there's no turkey.
SARAH: Turkey. It's in there, John.
- No.
Just move the food around,
and the turkey will reveal itself to you.
Mom. I already looked. There's no...
Oh, yeah. There it is. Thanks.
And stay inside. No ID means...
Yeah, I know what no ID means.
[ENGINE STARTS]
SARAH:
How many guys are we meeting?
CAMERON:
Four.
These Resistance fighters,
they know you?
They've seen me before.
SARAH:
I've seen that before.
Kyle Reese had one.
Skynet work camp.
Prisoner.
[MAN GRUNTS]
[MAN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Off.
[ENGINE REVS]
Please remain calm.
Oh, my God.
You told me we'd be safe.
Safe!
Was that safe?
Three days, and we're at war.
Why jump at all?
Why not stay in the past?
I'd have seven more years to get ready.
To get him ready.
No, you wouldn't have.
Why not?
Because you died.
Two years ago.
December 4th, 2005.
You died.
So, what I'm getting is
these things, they're here.
All over, I guess.
And they, some of them, all of them,
are programmed with specific missions.
The one at the safe house
was sent there for those fighters.
Skynet doesn't know you're here.
There's no directive to hunt you.
So wait. If I was to walk right by one...
They'll walk right by you.
They don't know what you look like.
That's really awesome.
And what if they found out who he was?
Would they all know what to do then?
- They do.
- Awesome.
So school registration is at 3 tomorrow.
Do you think we can have all this
sorted out by then?
Can't you just be happy being yourself
for a little longer?
Just sit still.
It's not so bad being a Connor.
That's easy for you to say.
Is it?
[CHILD CRYING NEARBY]
- You all put back together, Tin Man?
- Tin Man?
You ready to go?
Thank you for explaining.
You. Stay here. Still, like a statue.
- Enrique?
- Statue.
I've been a statue for the last three days.
We'll be back.
[SIGHS]
I did paramilitary training
with Enrique outside of Oaxaca.
He taught John to shoot rifles.
So, what you said before,
is that why we're really here?
Did John...? The future John, did he send
you back to help me jump over my death?
- Is everything else a lie?
- No.
He sent us here to fight.
But you're the best fighter he knows.
- I'm sure that's not...
- The best.
So if I'm such a great fighter,
how was I killed?
Cancer.
We're here.
Hey, it's John. I'm not here right now.
You know what to do.
Hey, sorry, I missed you,
but leave a message and I'll call you back.
Probably.
You've reached the future leader
of mankind.
It may take me a little while to get back
to you, but leave a message anyway.
818-555-0147. Leave a message.
Statue.
Screw it.
ENRIQUE:
I'm not surprised.
I know I look surprised
when I saw you in that first moment.
Heh, but I am not surprised.
Do you know this woman well?
It's rhetorical. if you don't, you don't.
But if you do, and you're anything like her,
you'll lie and say you don't.
But, if you do, then I know that you,
like me, are not surprised.
And John, he's a man now.
He's grown up.
He misses you.
I need three sets of papers.
I can pay. Not a lot, but some.
Why not?
I'm finished with that life.
What?
Are you familiar with Ricardo Lopez?
The boxer from Cuernavaca.
He is very famous in my country.
His nickname is El Finito.
- Finisher.
- Yes.
He fought 52 fights:
51 victories, one draw.
And no losses. Zero.
I don't understand.
I wanted to be El Finito.
To retire undefeated.
I lived my wild life.
I fought the wars I wanted to,
and a few I did not.
But I lived every day free.
Not one day behind bars,
nor in the hands of the enemy.
So now, I am finished.
El finito.
SARAH:
Happy for you.
Sorry for me, but happy for you.
Eh.
Don't give up so easy.
I did not say I can't help.
My nephew, Carlos, has, uh...
...how we say,
taken over the family business.
His operation is very good...
...but he is not a believer.
Few believers left, I think.
You are a very quiet girl.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[CROWD CHATTERING]
GIRL:
Who's Charlie Dixon?
You shouldn't surf with the demo.
People get in your business.
Clear your history too?
- My history?
- Your history.
What you've been looking at.
Snoopy people, dude.
Snoopy people all over.
- Got a special on those.
- Uh, no. Maybe later. Thanks.
[PURRING]
[HISSES]
[DOG BARKING]
[MAN GAGS THEN DOG WHIMPERS]
Carlos?
Enrique sent us.
[CROWD CHEERING ON TELEVISION]
[BARKING AND GROWLING]
CARLOS:
What the hell?
Quiet their crazy asses down!
Wait at the car.
[YELLING IN SPANISH]
Something about your friend
I should know?
- Cat person.
- Heh.
- Want a soda or something?
- I'm good.
We got the old-fashioned soda machine.
The little bottles.
It's a collectible now.
José.
Soda, por favor.
[RAP MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
My uncle, he's very good
at keeping secrets.
When I was young I'd see him at barbecues,
I'd try to get him to tell me his secrets.
- How did that work out for you?
- Not so good.
Except one day...
...about eight years ago.
I find him in the kitchen,
bottle of Patrón and the Times.
You know who's picture's
on the front page?
[MIMICS GUN CLICKING]
Only time I ever seen my uncle cry.
He's a good man.
CARLOS:
Not for me to say.
But he's my uncle.
And you're as close as I'm gonna get
to one of his secrets.
- So I'm gonna give you what you need.
- Thank you.
- Twenty thousand.
- Heh.
What? I don't have that.
CARLOS:
Twenty thousand.
That's a family discount
in these hard times.
Especially for someone
who's been dead eight years.
That's extortion.
War on terrorism makes this
the front lines, lady.
Some rag-head gets fake papers here,
we're all going to Guantánamo.
9/11 doubled prices overnight.
9/11, what's that?
[SCOFFS]
[CHATTERING OVER POLICE RADIO]
Hey, baby girl.
What'd I tell you about hanging around?
Who's your new friend here?
Is she someone I need to know?
The longer you stand around, the more
I think she's someone I need to know.
- You got a name?
- Mm, no.
Mm.
This your car?
No.
It's definitely not my car.
I know about everyone in this neighborhood,
and you are not one of those everyone.
So now you got me wondering
not just who you are that you won't say...
...but why you're here,
and that you won't say.
It's not uncommon in these neighborhoods
for a gang dealing in drugs...
...to store their drugs inside
of a stolen car.
That way, no drugs
can be found on their property...
...or on any property belonging to them.
But they also like to leave a lookout.
Sometimes a pretty girl
to watch their stash.
Now, you don't mind
if I call this license plate in, do you?
SARAH:
Jenny. Damn it. Jennifer!
How many times have I told you?
Stop seeing that little punk ass.
I swear to God. Is he meeting you here?
OFFICER: Ma'am?
- Is he meeting you here?
- Ma'am.
- You know this girl?
- Yes, I know this girl.
Do I have any choice but to know you,
you spoiled little bitch?
Do you do domestic complaints, officer?
Can I make a domestic complaint
against my spoiled little stepdaughter...
...for making me wanna beat
my own brains in?
It's her real mother's fault.
Can I tell you what she lets her do?
- Is this your car?
- Why would I drive that piece of crap?
Because I will send you back
to private school.
The one with the uniforms.
They will dress you like a flannel sock.
Maybe you can have this conversation
somewhere else. At home perhaps?
Out of gang territory.
- Gang territory?
- Mm.
Of course, thank you, officer.
Come on.
It's 13 miles to walk home.
We need another car.
Were you gonna kill that cop?
Don't answer that. Don't wanna know.
We need rules.
Are you supposed to take orders
or something like that?
I do. From John.
From John.
So if I told John to forbid you...
- Not this John.
- Aren't they the same?
- Not yet.
SARAH:
I cannot imagine the apocalypse.
No matter what Kyle Reese told me...
...or others who have come back.
I cannot imagine three billion dead.
But I can imagine 3000.
I can imagine planes hitting buildings,
and I can imagine fire.
If I would've witnessed it,
if I would've been here...
...I'm sure I would've thought
the end was near.
I'm sure I would've thought...
...we have failed.
[DOOR OPENS]
John?
Johnny?
Is it really you?
It is you.
I...
I saw a picture of your mother on a
television, and I could barely believe my...
I can't believe this.
Don't come any closer.
Stop.
You came to my house.
- You married?
- Yeah, I am.
She's a nurse at the hospital
where I work.
That's nice. That's good.
Johnny, what happened?
Stop.
Johnny, it's... It's okay.
Please, stop.
No, no, no, Johnny. It's me, Johnny.
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
I'm sorry.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Hey.
How'd it go with Enrique?
El Finito is a true believer,
but he is finished with the life.
- Heh, what?
- We need 20 grand. It's a long story.
- That taking you a while?
- Yeah, it's taking me a while.
I gotta, you know, strip wires...
John has a high level of stress.
Genetics are a bitch.
I did a brief analysis.
Surface skin temperature high...
...salinity high, pulse abnormal.
It's because the kid snuck out
while we were gone.
Won't look me in the eye,
his shoes are wet with grass.
Don't need to be a Tin Man
to figure that one out, just a mom.
- Where did he go?
- Worry about that later.
We just need to make sure
he doesn't do it again.
I didn't know that was something
you could do, the skin trick.
I should know about your skills,
or whatever.
Like, can you analyze blood?
- Can you scan someone?
- You mean computed axial tomography?
- CAT scans?
- Yeah.
That. Can you do that?
No.
Get your shoes on.
Do you want your new name or what?
JOHN:
You sure there's money here?
Money, guns, anything they valued.
It would be hidden.
It's always hidden.
Yeah, well, whatever they had,
let's hope the cops didn't get to it first.
Let's hope our metal friend didn't find it.
Our metal friend was only here to kill
that fourth fighter when he came home.
Nice to know we spoiled that.
It'll find him.
That's ridiculous.
People do like small animals.
Yeah, but... I don't know.
How do I explain this?
Some badass soldier is not gonna have
a kitty poster on the wall.
Mom.
Do what you do, girlie.
What?
They rigged it.
What did she say, 120 seconds
before the system reboots?
We gotta get in there.
We can't come back.
- We'll find the money some other way.
- Whatever's in there, I want it now.
Numbers. What...? What are the numbers?
What could the numbers be?
Damn. Fingerprints.
- How'd you...?
- It's a date.
Judgment Day.
[DOG BARKING]
What are those?
- Why are diamonds a girl's best friend?
- What?
Why are diamonds a girl's best friend?
Where'd you get that?
- John gave it to me.
- He did, did he?
That was sweet of him.
We have a whole bag of them,
do you want one?
They're a girl's best friend.
Not this girl.
I know what the Tin Man is.
He needed a heart.
The Wonderful Wizard of Oz,
written by L. Frank Baum in 1900.
- First published in...
- I know all about The Wizard of Oz.
When John was little, I, uh...
You read it to him over and over again,
in Spanish.
He never told you, but it was one
of his favorite things that you did.
He used to talk about it a lot.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]:
Okay, shoppers, $49.98...
...for this DVD/CD player with remote.
Hey! Who...?
Who the hell are you? Huh?
What are you doing here, man?
This is my house, man.
Chet?
What's with the trespassing
and the visor?
Chet?
You're not Chet.
[SHOUTS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
They're exactly like you asked.
These ain't just forgeries.
This is full service.
You're in the system and everything.
Collect welfare with them, if you want.
We might have to.
Didn't take you long to round that up,
so I'm feeling the price is right.
Maybe you could've gone
another 10 G's.
Uncle Enrique would be proud.
So I miss the next family barbecue.
[CARLOS SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Charlie?
You okay?
You've been a little...
...you know, out of it, all night.
No, I'm good. I'm fine, I just...
I had a rough call.
It was a guy on meth.
- God, babe. Want me to take a look at that?
- No, no, I'm good. I'm good.
- Sure?
- Yeah.
Love you.
Yeah, I love you too.
SARAH:
Carlos was right.
Twenty thousand dollars
wasn't that much money.
A new identity, a new life, a chance.
You can't put a price on that.
But unlike John, I was never eager
for that new life to begin.
I liked having no name.
No story.
It was the only time I got to be me.
Unfortunately, sometimes
you have to pay for that.
And the price was getting higher
every day.
[GUN COCKS]
Sarah.
You can either drink it or dump it.
I say drink it.
Anything I should know?
- Excuse me?
- Anything I should know?
Anything you forgot to tell me?
Neglected? Lied about?
- First and last chance.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Please...
- ...put the gun down and explain...
- El finito.
El finito, yes, what about it?
Not a day behind bars,
lived a life of freedom.
- Yes.
- That's not what Carlos said.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
My nephew, he's a thief and a liar.
- I told you, noth...
- He was speaking Spanish to his crew.
He referred to you as a rata.
It's slang for snitch, isn't it?
- You must have heard him wrong.
- Rata, rat.
Denunciante, informer.
Certain words I know and don't forget.
Are you selling people out?
Are you selling me out, Enrique?
Okay.
I was in Lompoc, many years ago,
on a federal gun charge.
- You said you never...
- Three weeks.
Only three weeks.
- And you made a deal? You talked?
- No.
I gave information on my cellmate.
He had kidnapped a child, and put her
in his trunk, and drove her from Oregon.
He told me it...
He told me where he dumped her.
And...
They dropped my charge, yes.
But that was all.
That was all I gave.
And, yes, I lied to you.
But where I grew up,
where we grew up...
...a man doesn't... You know...
[GUNSHOTS]
El hablador, it's another one.
It means the same thing.
Why would you do this?
Did you hear what he said?
We don't know. We don't know.
He was possibly lying.
Possibly?
You just executed him on possibly?
He had a family.
Why would you do this?
Because you wouldn't.
How do you know what I would
and would not do?
You don't know me. You don't know me.
And you don't know my son.
Not John.
Not my John.
You don't know what I would
and wouldn't do.
I don't even know what I would
I wake up this morning, and you tell me...
I don't know anything anymore.
I don't even remember what my name is.
Sarah Connor.
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
CAMERON:
So where are you from?
Lawrence, Kansas, actually.
It's a pretty good-sized city. About 80,000.
Go to Kansas City often?
Well, Lawrence is about 50 miles east
of Kansas City.
Twenty-five miles west.
I knew that.
What about your father?
JOHN: Hmm?
- Your father.
Did you leave him behind
in Lawrence, Kansas?
Your father's dead.
He was a police officer.
He died apprehending a criminal.
- He's a hero.
- Yeah, I know that.
My dad's always a hero.
And he's always dead.
Did you go out late last night?
No, why?
Motion detectors.
I thought I heard a beep.
Probably her.
She just walks and walks.
Look, if you wanna hold me out
another few days...
- ...until I get these stories straight...
- You're going to school.
But...
SARAH: At least I'll know where you are.
And who you're with.
Mom.
What?
Never mind.
ENRIQUE [ON ANSWERING MACHINE]:
Good evening, agent.
Perhaps you think I was retired, yes?
That I did not have my ear to the street?
If you return my call, I believe
I may have something of interest to you.
Muy expensivo, but of great interest.
El Finito will not disappoint.
WOMAN [OVER SPEAKERS]:
Attention all students.
Class schedules will be available
in the hall at 3:30.
SARAH:
Know thyself.
John once told me it's inscribed
on the front of the Temple of Apollo.
The entire quote is:
"Know thyself, and thou shall know all the
mysteries of the gods and of the universe."
It's quite a mouthful.
My version is this:
"Know thyself,
because what else is there to know?"
People hide secrets.
Time is a lie.
The material world
can disappear in an instant.
It has and it will again.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
The doctor will see you
in a few minutes, Ms. Baum.
SARAH:
Our identities change.
Our names, the way we look,
how we act and speak.
We're shape-shifters.
There is no control, no constant.
No shelter but the love of family
and the body God gave us.
And we can only hope that
that will always be enough.