SARAH: In the future, my son will
lead mankind in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created...
...to change our future...
...to change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
ANNOUNCER: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
CAMERON: Cromartie came through.
He knows we're here.
It's just a head.
CAMERON:
We're programmed to repair ourselves.
To blend in.
He will rebuild
and continue his mission to hunt and kill.
I know what his mission is.
SARAH:
We got a problem.
- Andy Goode rebuilt his chess computer.
- The Turk.
DEREK: Somebody killed him
and took the machine.
I was paid money for it, $20,000.
- Who bought The Turk?
- That's all I have.
These things, they're here.
They're programmed with specific missions.
CAMERON: The one at the safe house
was sent for those Resistance fighters.
SARAH: Humans sent back
from the future by John.
Everything needs to be destroyed,
every last bolt.
Even a single unaccounted-for piece
could hasten the arrival of Judgment Day.
- You get it done.
- I swear.
I need the list of new students who've
enrolled in the school since the fall of 2007.
Males, Caucasian, ages 15 to 18.
You boys are in here at least twice a month
waving your Patriot Act around.
Let me guess. Drugs?
Look me in the eye and tell me
you've never smoked a little marijuana.
I've never smoked a little marijuana.
[SCOFFS]
Okay. Let's see your paperwork.
Court order
or a signed national-security letter.
- I don't have my paperwork.
- Sorry.
The district will not release
personal information on students...
...without written authorization from the...
[CHOKING]
[BONES CRACK]
Thank you for your cooperation.
SARAH:
All of us wear masks.
They can be worn out of love and the desire
to remain close to those around us...
...to spare them from the complicated
reality of our frayed psyches.
Mom...
...food's done.
Smells done.
SARAH:
We trade honesty for companionship.
Mom, come on, it's gonna get burned.
SARAH:
And in the process...
...never truly know
the hearts closest to us.
Mr. Sarkissian, I'm calling again about
the computer, the one called "The Turk."
Can you please call me back,
818-555-0189.
JOHN:
Mom.
The roast should have been removed from
the stove 18 minutes and 27 seconds ago.
It's fine.
SARAH:
All right...
...not exactly fine.
Where did you get this?
- Her room.
- Why were you in my room?
You told me you destroyed everything.
She lied.
The chip contains visual records
of the T-Triple-8.
Where it's been, who it's interacted with.
It carries important information.
It's a brain, the only truly irreplaceable
part of the machine and she kept it.
Next, she's gonna tell us
that's gonna help us find The Turk.
- It won't help us find The Turk.
- What are you saying?
What I'm saying is what I've been saying.
"She can't be trusted."
No matter how she acts on the outside,
we have no idea what's going on in there.
Well, I could say that about you.
Who showed you to my safe house?
She did.
Who else knew about it? Nobody.
Where are my men?
In the morgue.
I didn't give the Triple-8
the safe-house location.
Prove it.
Have you ever hacked one of those?
- Have you ever read what's on it?
- No.
But you have.
So how often do you lie?
When the mission requires it.
Do you lie to me?
Sometimes.
About important things?
Yes.
Important things.
KENDO:
All right, bro.
This is what I'm talking about.
You can't get these goods
unless you got family in Korea.
Dual-core processor, brand-new system bus,
overclocked memory.
They're using it for the effects
in the new "Star Command."
Oh.
- What's the video throughput?
- One-point-four terabytes per second.
Mâs macho, brother.
I'm gonna need two.
Cool.
Am I making a mistake
with this chip thing?
Do I wanna see what's on it?
Tell me now.
I'd rather tell you after.
[JOHN SIGHS]
Look, since you have no clue
how to read this...
...would you mind
making a 7-Eleven run or something?
Pick up some burritos, chocolate milk.
It would mean a lot to me.
[LAUGHS]
How much power are you giving the chip?
Uh...
- We're running at 2.5 volts.
- My CPU requires a minimum of 6.2...
...and a maximum of 8.7 continuous voltage
in order to function properly.
That much use would burn out
any processor I've ever seen.
Access to visual memory will require
less power than higher-level functions.
Higher-level functions?
Decision-making, strategic mission analysis.
We don't wanna activate those functions.
So crank the juice but not too much.
Yes.
Crank the juice.
[LAUGHS]
Wow, what a mess.
How the hell
do you keep your brain organized?
- Not like yours.
- No kidding.
No! Please, don't!
Vick, God, you poor thing,
you're up again?
I told you, just take one of my pills.
Fine, babe, come back to bed.
I can't sleep with you standing there
like a statue.
Was that thing...
...married?
The T-Triple-8 is
an advanced-model infiltrator.
I don't think she knows.
I mean, is that possible?
She would not be the first human
fooled by a machine.
I know I've been working a lot
and I know it's been hard for you...
...hanging around at home
since your car accident...
I thought we'd made progress.
Just talk to me, sweetie.
Don't keep it inside, please.
Please.
SARAH: At least now we have
an address to go to.
That chip is really creepy.
We've seen some creepy things.
He's protecting her.
Why? And why like that?
Because they're twisted. That's why.
I'll be in the jeep.
She didn't do it.
She didn't give up the safe house.
- She's not like that other one.
- I hope not.
Have fun at school.
It's Pizza Day.
I read the newsletter.
Isn't Pizza Day tomorrow?
Yeah.
Well, she hasn't been here for a while.
I wonder what she thinks
happened to her husband.
Are you kidding?
She's dead.
You don't know that.
He wasn't holding her captive.
Wasn't intimidating her.
They lived here together.
Think you'd know?
I know I'd know.
Computer's gone.
Triple-8 probably junked it
to cover his tracks.
Barbara Chamberlain,
city manager, Los Angeles.
A city manager? That's infrastructure.
No wonder Skynet's interested.
You think this woman
has anything to do with The Turk?
I think if Skynet's interested,
we're interested.
Do you not wanna work on this?
Because I do.
I want us to be happy.
I've made a decision.
We're gonna figure out what we want.
Together.
I'm quitting my job, I'm...
I'm coming home.
VICK:
That's not a good idea, babe.
MORRIS:
See it?
I got it crowd surfing during Björk's
secret show at the Echo last October.
Man, it was the best five seconds
of my life, I swear to God.
But I got dropped on a chair.
I consider it my first tattoo.
That's tight.
Hey, Cheri.
Uh, I was thinking we could use study hall
to get ready for the Chem test.
Yeah, sure. That'd be great.
- I hear we used to be Midwest neighbors.
- What?
You know, I'm from Lawrence in Kansas
and I heard you were from Wichita.
- We're practically cousins, geographically.
- Who told you I was from Wichita?
- I don't remember.
- I'm not.
- Whoever said it, heard wrong.
- Okay.
- I'll see you in study hall?
- Yeah.
Okay.
BOY 1: He's got the height, but, dude...
BOY 2: Yeah, but he's got no game, dude.
- Good job.
- Thanks, coach.
I need to speak to Eric Carlson.
- He in some sort of trouble?
- No, no trouble. Where is he?
He just got out of gym class.
Give him five to finish showering.
Eric Carlson?
COACH: Hey!
- Eric Carlson?
- Mm-mm.
Eric Carlson?
What seems to be the problem, sir?
COACH:
Hey. Are you for real, buddy?
You think I can't get you fired
for that little peep show?
Coach!
BOY 3: Did you see that?
BOY 4: Yeah?
I just finished going through
the first set of files you grabbed.
Only understood a third of what I read.
You've been doing that
for 20 minutes now.
With my toothbrush.
I got you your own.
And now it's mine.
JOHN:
Mom?
Mom.
So I figured out that they don't store
memories the way we do.
They store them by categories.
Like "mission" or "location" or whatever.
- How'd you figure that out?
- Remember those robot symbols?
I still don't know how to read them,
but the same one kept popping up...
...every time a clip of Barbara
was playing.
You should look at this.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
He gained her trust.
Made her think he was human...
...and killed her.
It's what they do.
John, get the flashlights.
We're gonna find her.
Finding Barbara's body
should not be a mission priority.
You're right,
but we're gonna do it anyway.
We're here.
You see anything?
No.
I don't understand your need to find her.
She's dead.
That's because
you don't value human life.
But she's not life.
She's just a body, bones and meat.
Is that bad to say?
[JOHN SIGHS]
JOHN:
So do we do this a lot...
...in the future, sneak around in the dark?
We do this a lot.
I was kind of hoping
we wouldn't find her.
[WHISTLES]
That's not Barbara.
Who the hell's Jessica Peck?
A threat to Skynet.
Well, how did she get in there to meet
with the city council without us knowing?
I can't be everywhere, I can't.
I'm working from home because I just
have some family stuff I need to deal with.
I have to go.
Jessica Peck's trying to shut down
my program again.
Jessica Peck was a lobbyist...
- ...being paid to oppose ARTIE.
- Who's Artie?
Automated Realtime Traffic
Information Exchange.
It was one of Barbara's Chamberlain's
pet projects.
I think it's one of Skynet's pet projects.
So this is about traffic lights?
JOHN: Exactly.
It's a fiber-optic network linking every
intersection to a data center in city hall.
Cameras, microphones, sensors.
Right now it's only a pilot program
but it could grow statewide.
Traffic?
CAMERON: It's not about traffic,
it's about information.
Eyes and ears everywhere.
A system that can watch you,
track you everywhere you go.
If The Turk is destined
to become Skynet's brain...
...this software
could be its nervous system.
Like a body waiting for its head.
And we don't have either one.
I guess when they say,
"You can't fight city hall," they mean it.
Well, whoever said that
didn't have as much plastique as we do.
- We can't blow up city hall.
- It's really not that hard.
If we destroy the program,
they'll just rebuild it.
But if we plant a virus and crash it,
maybe they'll think it's a bust.
- It's already a controversial program.
- Can you make the virus?
Sure, but city hall's computers
aren't accessible from the outside.
Just make me the virus. I'll get it inside.
SARAH:
Getting through security won't be easy.
Once we're inside,
there'll be more guards.
Cameras.
- Hi, can I get you anything?
- Just an iced tea, thanks.
A beer.
WAITRESS: Okay.
Thank you.
I used to be her.
Huh?
The waitress. I used to work in a diner.
I can't see that at all.
I had this regular, Tracy.
She had two beautiful kids.
She left her husband, moved her kids
to L.A. to get them into show business.
I'd bring her eggs every day.
And I'd hear what she said to them...
...that they had bad skin
or crooked teeth.
One lie after another.
I swear, sometimes I understand
why they drop bombs on us.
MAN:
Excuse me, ma'am.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER RADIOS]
Don't worry about it.
We're not going in the front door.
These buildings are all connected
by underground tunnels...
...that were built during the Cold War.
I did a project on them in the ninth grade,
my last year of school.
Here you go.
DEREK: Thanks.
You're welcome.
And how do you know
they're still functional?
I lived there. Kyle and I.
After they dropped the bombs on us.
Cameron?
Cameron Baum?
Yes?
Happy Pizza Day.
Thank you. I had two slices.
Do I look fat?
Um, still good.
So I had a little issue last week...
...with a banned substance
in the student parking lot.
And now,
as a condition of my rehabilitation...
...I hand these out to people.
There's a cop in the principal's office.
He wants to talk to your brother.
Is he hiding?
Does he have stuff in his locker?
Wait, he's not a narc, is he?
I'll make sure John gets this.
Hectic.
I need you.
You wanted to see me?
- John Baum?
- Yes, sir.
Thank you for your time.
Cameron.
What are you doing?
Never mind.
Okay, I have no clue
what happened to you in Kansas...
...but your sister's a genius
and I've got nerves of steel.
Huh?
We got that cop off your back and, ha,
I've never felt more alive.
- What cop?
- Oh...
I don't think I can do it. I can't finish.
VICK:
But you've almost completed it.
But if I do, I just...
I feel like it's become a monster,
you know?
It's become a horrible thing between us.
And ever since I started working on it...
...you've been so...
I don't mean to blame you.
VICK:
Finish it.
You scared me. How long you been there?
A little while.
That was effective.
What he did.
When he touched her lips.
Effective?
I could see that she liked that.
What are you doing?
No.
When you say things like that,
what are you doing?
Just making conversation.
Since when do you
just make conversation?
I don't know.
It just seems like something I should do.
Was having Morris impersonate me
with that cop...
...also something you thought
you should do?
- No matter what happened to him?
- Yes.
But it wasn't a cop.
It was Cromartie.
What?
He's going school to school
looking for you.
Trying to match your face.
He's moved on, though.
He won't go back there.
I wouldn't.
The only way that I'm reassured by that...
...is if I remember...
...that in the core of your chip...
...you're just like him.
Oh, God, she'll move us so fast.
You cannot tell her, okay?
Promise me.
Hey. Do I smell nail polish?
What are you guys talking about?
Just making conversation.
- Hey.
- Come on!
Come on!
Sayles was always, uh...
[DEREK SIGHS]
I loved him,
but he was an idiot sometimes.
- He was careless.
- You were following Barbara Chamberlain.
No, I wasn't.
I didn't know he was.
There were a lot of leads,
we spent a lot of time on our own.
I didn't know.
Mom, what are you doing?
Mom?
Mom, talk to me. What are you doing?
Barbara's name is in here somewhere.
On some list, in some file.
She's buried in here.
Why do we always find out about people
when it's too late, when they're dead?
Do all these people have to die
so that we can win? Is that it?
Who else are you talking about?
Are you talking about Andy Goode?
Is the virus ready?
City hall is closed.
I'll leave in half an hour.
I didn't know Sayles was tracking her.
You gotta believe me.
I don't have to believe anything.
In fact, I don't.
- You sure you know where you're going?
- Well, I should.
This is where I lost Kyle to the machines
when we were kids.
We need to keep moving this way.
There's an elevator shaft.
There shouldn't be a wall here.
In the future, there's no wall here.
Meaning...?
Meaning, we need to blow it up.
SARAH:
That's gonna draw attention.
We're on a fault line.
They'll think it was a tremor.
Data Center's on B4.
All right, let's go.
It's working.
- What's going on? Are we good?
- Something's wrong.
- The system's blocking the virus.
- We can still blow the place.
[ALARM WAILING]
COP 1: Get the gates.
COP 2: There!
Quick, men, stop them!
COP 1:
Over here.
Hold it.
Stop.
COP 1:
Which way did they go?
[INDISTINCT YELLING]
COP 2:
Far corridor.
COP 1: Stop, right there!
COP 2: Hold it!
Get them past here.
COP 1:
There, there.
Freeze! Down on the ground now.
COP 2: Better do what he says, huh?
COP 1: Hands behind your back.
[GRUNTING]
SARAH:
Reese.
Let's go.
CAMERON:
What's the matter?
I get in, I get to a certain point,
and it kicks me out.
It's like a part of Vick's memory
just turns off.
I've even cranked up the juice.
And there goes the power supply.
[MODEM DIALING]
That's weird.
My phone is dialing
for an Internet connection.
What the hell?
Vick's reactivating.
Is he trying to get online?
Did it happen? Did he get out?
Did he call someone or something?
No.
CAMERON: We should be very careful
with Vick's chip.
[DOOR OPENS]
Yeah, that's the understatement
of the century.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- How did it go?
- Didn't work.
- We should just blow it.
- Can't go back there.
What are you gonna do,
take an ax to every traffic light in town?
No.
We only need to take down one.
Two centimeters left.
One centimeter down.
Cut a semicircle
with a diameter of 12 centimeters.
- Is it okay if I'm off by a little bit?
- Yes.
Cut a bigger circle to compensate.
How exactly is this gonna work?
Her neural network is the most
sophisticated learning computer on Earth.
If we get her chip into the ARTIE system,
it can take over the whole thing.
Just like Vick did with my laptop.
- She can kill it.
- You can get in through a traffic light?
Yes.
- Are you sure?
- No.
Start the incision.
CAMERON:
Push harder.
Down to my endoskeleton.
Sarah.
Once she's in the city's mainframe,
what's to say she'll come back out?
You know, maybe it's not The Turk
that created Skynet.
Maybe it's her.
Maybe this was her plan all along.
She's a machine.
She doesn't have a soul and she never will.
You don't have to trust her.
You can trust me.
Good.
Set the pliers over the shielded tab
on the end of the chip...
...a half turn counterclockwise
and pull it out.
It's okay, John.
It's not the first time we've done this.
We have to get this
into the CPU interface.
I'll take him to the traffic light.
- Okay she's in.
- How long?
Fifteen seconds.
Twenty.
For what it's worth, I believe you.
I don't think you knew
your guy was watching Barbara.
Thanks.
Okay, it's done.
Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
Derek, don't.
I want you to hear this
in no uncertain terms:
Someday, one of these things
is gonna kill you.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
It's not gonna be this one.
[CAR TIRE SQUEALING]
[POWERS UP]
What was it like?
What did you see in there?
I saw everything.
[SHOWER RUNNING]
Sarkissian returned my call.
He'll meet about selling The Turk.
He's still got it? When's the meeting?
Tomorrow morning.
Meaning this news could have waited?
You killed Andy Goode.
There was no one to protect him
and you killed him.
You lie to me again, I'll kill you.
SARAH: So much danger in this world
is hidden behind masks.
We tell our children stories
of good and evil...
...while knowing it's not that simple.
Do you realize that in 36 hours,
we'll be waking up in Tahiti?
I can't believe you bought us tickets.
True evil doesn't give us time to fight...
...or to be afraid.
[CHOKING]
SARAH: We keep our heads down,
never bothering to look behind the masks.
And in doing so...
...we resign ourselves to terrible fates
we can never see coming.