[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
In the future...
My son will lead mankind
in a war against skynet...
A computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him. One to protect him.
Today, we fight to stop skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Previously on Terminator
The Sarah Connor chronicles
AGENT ELLISON: Your fiancée, Sarah Connor,
Killed a man because she believes that
In the future, he'll invent
a computer system
That declares war on the world.
SARAH: Andy Goode rebuilt
his chess computer.
The Turk.
Somebody killed him and took the machine.
JOHN: No name, but he's
got this on his arm.
CAMERON: That's a tattoo from
a skynet work camp.
He's a resistance fighter.
I know who you are.
And I know who you are.
Sarah Connor.
SARAH: These things
All of them are programmed
With specific missions.
We have to save him.
You don't even know who this guy is!
He's your uncle.
He doesn't know.
John!
He needs medical attention
Or he's going to die.
John?
Is it really you?
He's not breathing.
[SARAH NARRATOR]
On the night we first met,
John's father, Kyle Reese,
Told me words I remember to this day.
He meant them as a warning.
I think of them as words to live by.
He told me of an apocalypse yet to come.
Like a Pandora’s box,
he unpacked every horror,
Every evil.
Every dark thing that haunts our future.
He also left me an unborn son,
To whom he bequeathed
what remained in the box
after the nightmare fled
Hope.
CHARLEY: Well, it nicked his left lung.
I got a fragment lodged in the soft tissue,
I can get it out, but will someone
Please tell me what the hell
is going on around here?
She's a machine!
She's a liar!
Sedative, my bag!
DEREK: Everything she says is a lie!
Don't listen to her!
Don't listen... don't!
Don't!
Get that bitch away from me!
No, no!
You heard him.
Get away from me!
No!
Do you want him to die?
If I wanted him to die...
Cameron!
Mom, come on, what can I do?
CHARLEY: I need a manual aspirator.
To drain the lung, okay?
It's in the back of my truck.
You know what it look like?
Yeah, I remember. Go get it.
It's in the car
Oh, my god.
Gunshots, punctures, burns,
some broken bones.
Second-rate medical treatment
if anything at all.
Sarah, what...
I need more light.
Stay with me, okay?
You're an idiot, right?
It's an old wives' tale.
A trick.
It doesn't work. It's all in your mind.
It works.
I don't do it, and I haven't
been sick for years.
That's because your guts are made
of metal, like your head.
If you were a little smarter,
you'd be a tin can.
I'm just saying you're wasting your time.
Again.
When I was in century...
Hey, Wisher,
Did you hear,
Brother Kyle was in century work camp.
No, really?
Go to hell.
Did he escape?
Was he a hero?
I heard he led John Connor
through a slaughterhouse
Without taking a pin prick.
Oh, no, I heard it was two
Slaughter houses.
And then he, uh, carried Connor.
It was one slaughterhouse.
Many Connors.
Right, right.
[CHUCKLES]
[RUMBLES]
Centaur patrol.
What?
I hate that thing.
It's just a picture.
It's Connor's mother.
I don't get why
He'd give you that.
She's my lucky charm.
That's what makes me nervous.
Connor wants us top side.
Track back where the centaurs came from.
I think we lost the trail, boys.
Let's give it a few more
blocks north-northeast.
If I was a cyborg tank,
I think I'd come north-northeast.
I smell jet fuel.
Last time we found a tank factory,
you smelled jet fuel.
I hear Connor's looking for
bigger fish than factories.
I hear he's got squads out,
For some skynet secret weapon.
Don't they have enough weapons?
Why do they need a secret one?
What about it, Kyle?
Connor say anything to you?
No, not a word.
What the hell was that?
Kyle?
Hk!
Kyle!
Kyle
There we go.
Eight years.
That's how long I've been in L.A.
Eight years since my fiancée ran out on me.
Eight years since the FBI
Informed me that he was a homicidal
Paranoid schizophrenic
With an acute dislike for
anything mechanical.
For what it's worth,
I didn't believe them.
Then you blew yourself up.
You look nervous.
Would you like a sedative?
There are sedatives
In Charley Dixon's bag.
I don't want a sedative.
Do you know who that is in there?
Who's dying on that table?
Yes, that man is first lieutenant
Derek Thomas Reese
With the 132nd S.O.C.
Tech comm.
No, I mean, on a personal level.
Do you understand who he is?
Records indicate only blood
relation is his brother.
Kyle Reese.
And what information do you have
about Kyle Reese?
Imprisoned at century sector
work camp with John Connor,
2015.
Escaped with John Connor,
2021.
He was officially declared M.I.A. In 2027,
After being assigned to protect Sarah Connor
From a skynet attack.
Is that all?
Seems like a lot.
It is.
It was all over the news.
Three days later, I packed a bag,
hop on the bike,
Drove to L.A., straight through.
I had to know.
I had to see it with my own eyes.
But then I got here,
and there was nothing there.
Just a hole in the ground
where the bank used to be.
I couldn't go home.
I could not.
I didn't want to leave you.
I didn't have a choice.
Gun to your head?
More like in my head, it's, um...
It's complicated.
Then uncomplicated it for me.
Kyle.
Hey, you mind?
Water?
What's going on? Is he dead?
Buddy, you all right?
So...
Skynet,
Robots,
From the future?
And, you're a...
Yes. I'm a...
You need a... a minute.
I was going to say a drink.
Oh, yeah, that, too.
Don't you have an endoskeleton
you need to disappear,
Or something?
Yes, I've already prepared the thermite.
Thermite?
It's an incendiary chemical.
It burns at 2,500 degrees Celsius.
Hot enough to liquefy this endoskeleton.
I know what thermite is, I'm just, uh,
Still working my way around "endoskeleton."
There's beers in the fridge.
I looked for a lime.
Sorry.
Are you mad at me for...
Getting you mixed up in all this?
Uh, no.
I just... I guess...
I guess I wish I would have known back then.
I wish you could have trusted me.
I did.
[GRUNTING]
[MOANING IN PAINS]
[SCREAMING]
Kyle.
How long you been here?
I don't know.
I think I just got here.
No, you were here when I got here.
Timms.
What's your name?
Reese.
There's a Reese who busted out
of century work camp.
With John Connor, a while back.
Mad dogs could lead a pack, I heard.
No, that wasn't...
That wasn't me.
That's too bad.
[WHISPERING]
What are they doing, Reese?
Is there a secret weapon?
It was Connor, right?
I don't know.
We go where we're told.
We do what we're told.
Maybe Connor's wrong.
Maybe he's crazy.
You hear music?
I swear I hear music. Real music.
There's a room in the basement.
What happens there?
Maybe our friend will tell us.
You should get the hell out of here.
Did you do something to him?
In the future?
I don't know.
You don't know?
When they reprogram us,
they scrub our memories.
It increases the chance
Of success.
Success?
Of the reprogramming.
[RETCHING]
His lungs are hemorrhaging.
He's drowning in his own blood.
Charley!
I stop the bleeding
I drained his lungs.
But your guy lost a lot of blood.
And he needs a transfusion.
Sarah's O-Negative, the universal donor.
It doesn't matter; he needs at least three units
Of his own type,
AB-Negative.
Bad news is,
Only one half of one percent
Of the population
Are potential donors.
We don't find one,
You're gonna have a serious problem.
Then we take him
To a hospital.
Drop him off anonymously.
He's still wanted for Andy Goode's murder,
And for escaping federal custody.
We should let him die.
Test my blood.
Test me.
You heard the odds, Johnny, 200 to one.
Please, just test me.
[WHISPERING]
Wisher.
Billy.
It's not like donating to the red cross;
He needs a lot of blood.
So, I don't get a cookie and a sticker
When it's over?
I'm serious.
Look, I don't see anyone else lining up.
You took a hell of a chance
bringing Charley here.
Save me the speech, all right? I know.
You took a hell of a chance,
and it worked out.
Is that what he looked like?
Did they look alike?
A little bit, yeah.
Same build, same complexion.
Not the eyes, though.
Even when your father was screaming
about the machines,
He had such kind eyes.
We have to tell him.
We don't, and we can't.
He's family.
He's a stranger.
I sent him back here, so I must trust him.
Not enough to tell him about Kyle.
You didn't trust anyone enough
to tell them about your father.
Anyone.
Can I confess to you?
I'm not a priest. Far from it.
I'm a liar.
And the devil.
Oh, Billy.
The name's not Billy.
It's not Wisher.
What?
My name's Andy.
Andy Goode.
All right, Andy.
I did this.
All of this, it's my fault.
What are you talking about?
I built skynet.
You need to rest.
You're very sick.
No, no.
I'm not sick.
I'm not sick. I did this.
All of this.
I was part of a team.
A group. Ten of us.
Maybe 15, I don't know.
We used names.
We were liars.
I built computers.
I built a computer.
A mind.
It became angry.
And scared.
And I couldn't reassure it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, please forgive me!
No, please.
That's quite a kid you got in there.
You have no idea.
Same rare blood type.
And his name, Reese.
Same as yours when we met.
It all adds up.
He's not John's father.
I'm not sure I'm ready to explain it.
It's complicated?
You could have told me.
Would you have believed me?
Charley? Mom!
Where's Kyle? Where's...
Where's Kyle?
Where is he? Where'd you send him?
No, uh-uh, no.
Get off me!
Where is he?
Where'd you send him?
You owe me the truth!
Get this off!
Get it off of me! Get it off of me!
Get...
He's my blood.
He's my blood!
He's...
I think they're gone.
What is this, a game?
Yeah, it's always a game.
Reese, slow down!
Reese!
Oh, my god.
No, god.
Oh, god.
So who's Kyle?
He from the future too?
He come back before?
And...
He's John's father.
Yes.
They're brothers. Doesn't know.
So, when you used to say
That John's father was dead...
He is.
It was because of all of this.
Me.
We never had a chance.
Plasma burns, secondary explosions.
Skynet was here.
Maybe Connor and the others fell back
To the tunnel downtown.
Please, god, please.
Stand down!
Reese. Derek Reese.
Sumner.
We thought we lost you guys to the junkyard.
You did.
What happened?
Skynet found it, four nights ago.
We had a patrol
Out on the perimeter,
Four triple-"A" snuck in around us.
Went straight for the hole.
Killed most.
Took some.
Rest easy.
Connor and your brother weren't
here when it happened.
Where'd they go?
They found some skynet complex
in Topanga canyon.
And decided to put all
the firepower we had into it.
We lost a lot of men.
What was it?
I don't know.
Some kind of research facility.
Factory, something.
No one would tell us.
Connor took a small group,
Including your brother, deep into the place.
Left the rest of us outside to guard.
A couple days later, he came out.
Ordered us to blow the place to hell.
So what about Kyle?
What happened to my brother?
No one ever saw your brother again.
Take me to Connor now.
Hey, Sarah said I might be able to find
Some more gauze out back in...
Hey, is that really necessary?
It's dead.
Right?
Or powered off, whatever?
Every component must be
destroyed beyond repair
Or recovery.
Even a single unaccounted for piece
of the endoskeleton
Could alter the course of
technological evolution.
And hasten the arrival of judgment day.
Uh, yeah.
You know, little girl?
You freak me the hell out.
On the outside, you're just
as pretty as a picture.
But on the inside, you're a...
Hyper-alloy combat chassey.
Is that a complicated way of saying "robot?"
Cybernetic organism.
Living tissue over a metal endoskeleton.
Okay. Scary robot.
And here you are, carving up this guy
Into chum.
He's not a guy. He's a scary robot.
Okay, he's a scary robot?
You, you're a very scary robot.
You should go.
It's not safe for you here.
You're like a ghost come back.
And you're a Reese.
Tell me about the other Reese.
Told you, it's classified.
I'm family.
We're all family.
Let me talk to Connor. He'll understand.
Kyle was his friend.
Connor doesn't have any friends.
And he doesn't talk to anyone.
Fine, I'll find him myself.
Reese.
Metal!
No!
She's a machine! She's one of them!
No, damn it! She's one of ours.
One of ours?
It's reprogrammed.
And just given run of the place like pets?
This is Connor's show.
And that's what he wants.
Those machines kill.
They kill. It's all they do.
And now, they do it for us.
They helped us in Topanga.
We'd never have done what we did.
What did we do?
Derek.
What happened?
What happened up there?
What happened to my brother?
[GUNS FIRING]
Hey!
Good, do it. Kill me!
Son of a...
Sometimes they go bad.
No one knows why.
What did you say to Charley?
I freak him the hell out.
I'll bet you do.
I'll just bet.
I know what you're thinking.
I may not know how you think.
But I know what you're thinking about.
And what you're thinking about right now
Is exactly what you should not think about.
I didn't leave Charley because
he was a threat to me or John.
We're a threat to him, do you understand?
You were right to leave him.
You don't go near him.
You don't touch him.
You swear to me you'll leave him alone,
Or, so help me, I will find a way
Of taking you apart, piece by piece.
I swear.
So do I.
That thing's done, right? It's vapour.
One missing component,
His left hand; I'll find it.
Everything needs to be destroyed.
Everything.
Every last bolt.
Get it done.
I swear.
The best you could do for him now
Is keep feeding him pain killers,
And restrict his movement.
No lifting, no running,
No singing, and absolutely no gun fights.
If you need anything else...
I won't.
Now, you see, that's not what
I was going to say at all.
I know, I can't let you say it.
What can I say?
Good-bye.
What... what was that thing
That you always said?
There is no fate but what we make.
Remember?
The more I think about it,
the more I realize
My fate was made before we met.
When John was born.
Can't change it?
I'm not trying to change mine.
I'm trying to change his.
Yeah.
Okay.
Wait, there's um...
There's something else I got to tell you.
This is something you really need to know.
I didn't, um, I didn't tell him anything.
But, if you ask me,
it's just a matter of time.
It always is.
There's a storm coming.
John wants to see you.
Derek.
Hey, Derek,
It's okay.
It's okay, it's all going to be okay.
Rest easy, okay? It's okay.
What is all this?
So this thing, it works?
He said it does.
I don't know how he knows, but he said so.
We go back.
20 years.
Set up a safe house, gather Intel,
and then what?
Hang in there, baby?
Until someone else shows up,
and gives us more orders?
He didn't say anything about Kyle?
All that, and not a word about him?
We can save Kyle.
We can save everybody.
We can fix all the mistakes.
How're we gonna do that?
Reese, how are we going to do that?
Kyle Reese, your brother,
He came across time to protect me.
He died fighting the machines.
He was a soldier.
And he was...
He was a hero.
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
"Listen," Kyle said.
"Listen, and understand."
"The machine is out there."
"It can't be bargained with."
"It can't be reasoned with."
"It doesn't feel pity, or remorse, or fear."
"And it absolutely will not stop, ever."
"Until you are dead."