[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
In the future,
My son will lead mankind
in a war against Skynet...
a computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time...
some to kill him,
one to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created,
To change our future,
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Previously on Terminator
The Sarah Connor chronicles
CAMERON:
Cromartie came through.
He knows we're here.
It's just a head.
CAMERON:  We're programmed
to repair ourselves.
And to blend in.
He will rebuild and continue
his mission to hunt and kill.
I know what his mission is.
SARAH:
We've got a problem.
Andy Goode rebuilt
his chess computer.
The Turk.
DEREK:  Somebody killed him
and took the machine.
I was paid money for it, $20,000.
Who bought the Turk?
That's all I have.
SARAH:  These things, all of them, are
programmed with specific missions.
CAMERON:
The one at the safe house
Was sent there for the
resistance fighters.
Humans sent back from
the future by John.
SARAH:  Everything needs to be
destroyed. Every last bolt.
CAMERON:  Even a single,
unaccounted for piece
could hasten the
arrival of judgment day.
Get it done.
No sweat.
I need a list of new students (INDISTINCT)
who have enrolled since the fall of 2007.
Males, Caucasian,
Ages 15 to 18.
You boys are in here
at least twice a month,
waving your patriot act around.
Let me guess - Drugs?
Look me in the eye and tell me
you've never smoked
a little marijuana.
I've never smoked
Hmm.
Okay, let's see your paperwork.
Court order or a signed
national security letter.
I don't have my paperwork.
Sorry, the district
will not release
personal information on students
without written authorization from the--
Thank you for your cooperation.
[NARRATOR]
All of us wear masks.
They can be worn out of love
And the desire to remain
close to those around us,
to spare them from
the complicated reality
of our frayed psyches.
Mom, food's done.
It smells done.
We trade honesty for companionship.
Mom, come on.
It's gonna get burned.
And in the process,
never truly know the
hearts closest to us.
Mr. Sarkissian, I'm calling again
about the computer, the
one called "the Turk."
Will you please call me back?
818-555-0189.
Mom.
The roast should have
been removed from the stove
18 minutes and 27 second ago.
And it's fine.
All right.
Not exactly fine.
Where'd you get this?
Her room.
Why were you in my room?
You told me you
destroyed everything.
She lied.
The chip contains visual
records of the T888,
where it's been, who
it's interacted with.
It carries important information.
It's a brain.
It's the only truly irreplaceable
part and she kept it.
Next she's gonna tell us
that somehow that's gonna
help us find the Turk.
It won't help us find the Turk.
What are you saying?
What I'm saying is what
I've been saying, John.
She can't be trusted.
No matter how she
acts on the outside,
We have no idea what's
going on in there.
Well, I could say that about you.
Who showed you to my safe house?
She did.
- Who else knew about it?
- Nobody.
Where are my men?
In the morgue.
I didn't give the triple-Eight
the safe house location.
Prove it.
Have you ever hacked one of those?
Have you ever read what's on it?
No.
But you have.
So how often do you lie?
When the mission requires it.
Do you lie to me?
Sometimes.
About important things?
Yes.
Important things.
MAN:
All right, bro.
This is what I'm talking about.
You can't get these kind of goods
unless you got family in Korea.
Dual-core processor,
brand-new system bus,
overclocked memory.
They're using it for the effects
in the new Dark Man series.
JOHN:
Wow.
What's the video throughput?
1.4 terabytes per second.
Mas Macho, brother.
I'm gonna need two.
Cool.
Am I making a mistake
with this chip thing?
Do I wanna see what's on it?
Tell me "no."
I'd rather tell you after.
Flick those bastards off the jeep.
Look, since you obviously
have no clue
How to read this garbage,
would you mind making a
7-11 run or something?
Pick up some burritos,
chocolate milk.
It'd mean a lot to me.
How much power are
you giving the chip?
Uh...
we are running at 2.5 volts.
My CPU requires a minimum of 6.2
and a maximum of 8.7
continuous voltage
in order to function properly.
Well, that much use would burn out
any processor I've ever seen.
Access to visual memory
will require less power
than higher level functions.
Higher level functions.
Decision making.
Strategic mission analysis.
We don't wanna activate
those functions.
So crank the juice
but not too much?
Yes.
Crank the juice.
Wow.
What a mess.
How the hell do you keep
your brain organized?
Not like yours.
No kidding.
Vick, god, you poor thing.
(INDISTINCT)
I told you, just take one of my pills.
Fine, babe, come back to bed.
I can't sleep with you
standing there like a statue.
Was that thing...
married?
The T-888
is an advanced model infiltrator.
JOHN:
Yeah, but I don't think she knows.
I mean, is that possible?
She would not be the first
human fooled by a machine.
I know I've been working a lot.
And I know it's been hard for you,
hanging around at home
since your car accident.
I thought we'd made progress.
Just talk to me, sweetie.
Don't keep it inside. Please.
Please.
SARAH:  At least now we have
an address to go to.
That chip is really creepy.
We've seen some creepy things.
He's protecting her.
Why?
And why like that?
Because they're twisted. That's why.
I'll be in the jeep.
[DOOR CLOSING]
She didn't do it.
She didn't give up the safe house.
She's not like that other one.
I hope not.
[EXHALE]
Have fun at school.
It's pizza day.
I read the newsletter.
[DOOR OPEN/CLOSING]
Isn't pizza day tomorrow?
Yeah.
She hasn't been here for a while.
I wonder what she thinks
happened to her husband.
Are you kidding?
She's dead.
We don't know that.
He wasn't holding her captive.
He wasn't intimidating her.
They lived here together.
You think you'd know?
I know I'd know.
Computer's gone.
Triple-Eight probably jumped
it to cover his tracks.
"Barbara Chamberlain,
city manager, Los Angeles."
City manager, that's infrastructure.
No wonder Skynet's interested.
You think this woman has
anything to do with the Turk?
Well, I think if Skynet's
interested, we're interested.
Do you not wanna work on this?
Because I do.
I want us to be happy.
I've made a decision-
We're gonna figure
out what we want.
Together.
I'm quitting my job. I'm--
I'm coming home.
That's not a good idea, babe.
See it?
I got it crowd surfing.
During bjork's secret show
at the Echo last October.
Man, it was the best five seconds of my life,
I swear to god.
But I got dropped on a chair.
I consider it my first tattoo.
That's tight.
Hey, Sherry.
Uh, I was thinking
maybe we could use
study hall to get ready
for the chem test tomorrow.
Yeah. Sure.
That'd be great.
So I hear we used to
be Midwest neighbours.
What?
You know, I'm from
Lawrence in Kansas.
And I overheard you
were from Wichita.
So we're practically
cousins geographically-
Who told you I was from Wichita?
I don't remember.
I'm not.
Whoever said it heard wrong.
Okay.
See you in study hall?
Yeah.
Great.
Way to go, Johnson.
I need to speak to Eric Carlson.
He in some sort of trouble?
No, no trouble. Where is he?
He just got outta gym class.
Give him five to finish showering.
Eric Carlson?
Hey!
What seems to be the problem, sir?
COACH:
Are you for real, buddy?
You think I can't get you fired
for that little peep show?
Coach!
I just finished going through
the first set of files you grabbed.
Only understood a third of what I read.
You've been doing that
for 20 minutes now.
With my toothbrush.
I got you your own.
And now it's mine.
Mom... Mom!
So I figured out that they don't
store memories the way we do.
They store them by categories.
Like, mission or location or whatever.
How did you figure that out?
Remember those weird robot symbols?
I still don't know how to read them.
But the exact same one kept popping up
every time a clip of Barbara was playing.
You should look at this.
[EXCLAIMS]
Stop. Please.
He gained her trust.
Made her think he was human.
Then killed her.
That's what they do.
John, get the flashlights.
We're gonna find her.
Finding Barbara's body
should not be a mission priority.
You're right.
But we're gonna do it anyway.
We're here.
You see anything?
No.
I don't understand your need to find her.
She's dead.
That's because you
don't value human life.
But she's not alive.
She's just a body.
Bones and meat.
Was that bad to say?
JOHN:
So do we do this a lot in the future,
sneak around in the dark?
DEREK:
We do this a lot.
I was kinda hoping
we wouldn't find her.
[DEREK'S WHISTLE]
That's not Barbara.
Who the hell's Jessica Peck?
A threat to Skynet.
Well, how did she get in there
to meet with the city
council without us knowing?
I can't be everywhere. I can't.
I'm working from home
because I just have
some family stuff I need to deal with.
I have to go.
Jessica Peck's trying to
shut down my program again.
[SCREAMING]
Jessica Peck was a lobbyist
being paid to oppose Artie.
Who's Artie?
Automated Real time Traffic
Information Exchange.
It was one of Barbara Chamberlain's
pet projects.
I think it's one of Skynet's pet projects.
So this is about traffic lights?
Exactly.
It's a fibre optic network
linking every street intersection
to a data centre in city hall.
Camera's, microphones, sensors.
Right now it's only a pilot program,
but it could grow state-wide.
Traffic.
CAMERON:
It's not about traffic.
It's about information.
Eyes and ears everywhere.
A system that can watch you,
track you everywhere you go.
If the Turk is destined
to become Skynet's brain,
this software could be its nervous system.
Like a body waiting for its head.
And we don't have either one.
Well, I guess when they say,
"you can't fight city hall"
They really mean it.
Yeah, well, whoever said that
doesn't have as much
plastic as we doing.
We can't blow up city hall.
It's really not that hard.
If we destroy the program,
they'll just rebuild it.
But if we plant a virus and crash it,
maybe they'll think it's a bust.
It's already a controversial program.
Can you make the virus?
Sure, but city hall's computers
aren't accessible from the outside.
Just make me the virus.
I'll get it inside.
SARAH:
Getting through security won't be easy.
Once we're inside,
there'll be more guards,
cameras.
WAITRESS:
What can I get for you?
Just an iced tea, thanks.
Uh, a beer?
Thank you.
I used to be her.
Huh?
The waitress. I used to work in a dinner.
I can't see that at all.
I had this regular, Tracy.
She had two beautiful kids.
She left her husband,
moved her kids to L.A.
To get 'em into show business.
I'd bring her eggs every day
and I'd hear what she said to them.
That they had bad
skin or crooked teeth.
One lie after another.
I swear sometimes I understand
why they drop bombs on us.
[INDISTINCT RADIO DISPATCHER]
Don't worry about it.
We're not going in the front door.
These buildings are all connected
by a series of underground tunnels
that were built during the cold war.
I did a project on 'em in the ninth grade.
My last year at school.
And how do you know
they're still functional?
I lived there,
Kyle and I.
After they dropped the bombs on us.
[INDISTINCT PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Cameron.
Cameron Baum.
Yes.
Uh, happy pizza day.
Thank you. I had two slices.
Do I look fat?
Um, still good.
So I had a little issue last week
with a banned substance
in the student parking lot.
And now, as a condition
of my rehabilitation,
I hand these out to people.
There's a cop in the
principal's office.
He wants to talk to your brother.
Uh...
Is he hiding?
Does he have stuff in his locker?
Wait, he's not a narc is he?
I'll make sure John gets this.
[CHUCKLES]
[INDISTINCT PEOPLE CHATTERING]
I need you.
You wanted to see me?
John Baum?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your time.
Cameron.
What are you doing?
Never mind.
Okay.
I have no clue what
happened to you in Kansas.
But your sister's a genius,
And I've got nerves of steel.
Huh?
We got that cop off your back,
and I've never felt more alive.
What cop?
Oh...
I don't think I can do it.
I can't finish.
But you've almost completed it.
But if I do, I just--
I feel like it's become
a monster, you know?
It's become a horrible
thing between us.
And ever since I started working on it,
you've been so--
I don't mean to blame you.
Finish it.
You scared the hell outta me.
How long you been sitting there?
A little while.
That was effective.
What he did,
when he touched her lips.
Effective?
I could see that she liked that.
What are you doing?
No.
When you say things like that,
what are you doing?
Just making conversation.
Since when do you
just make conversation?
I don't know.
I just seems like something I should do.
And was having Morris impersonate
me with that cop
also something you
thought you should do,
no matter what happened to him?
Yes.
But it wasn't a cop.
It was Cromartie.
What?
W- What?
He's going to school looking for you.
Trying to match your face.
He's moved on though.
He won't go back there.
I wouldn't.
The only way that I'm reassured by that
is if I remember
that in the core of your chip
you're just like him.
Oh, god. She'll move us so fast.
You cannot tell her, okay?
Promise me.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Hey.
Do I smell nail polish?
What are you guys talking about?
Just making conversation.
[DEREK'S SNIFFING]
Sayles was always, uh-
[EXHALE]
I loved him, but he was
an idiot sometimes.
He was careless.
You were following
Barbara Chamberlain.
I wasn't.
I didn't know he was.
There were a lot of leads, you know.
We spent a lot of time on our own.
I didn't know.
Mom, what are you doing?
Mom.
Mom, talk to me.
What are you doing?
Barbara's name is
in here somewhere.
On some list in some file.
She's buried in here.
Why do we always find
out about these people
when it's too late,
when they're dead?
Do all these people have to die
so that we can win?
Is that it?
Who else are you talking about?
Are you talking about Andy Goode?
Is the virus ready?
City hall's closed.
I leave in half an hour.
DEREK:  I didn't know Sayles
was tracking her.
You gotta believe me.
SARAH:
I don't have to believe anything.
In fact, I don't.
Are you sure you know
where you're going?
DEREK:
Well, I should.
This is where I lost Kyle
to the machines when we were kids.
[SIGHS]
We need to keep moving this way.
There's an elevator shaft.
There shouldn't be a wall here.
In the future, there's no wall here.
Meaning?
Meaning we need to blow it up.
That's gonna draw attention.
We're on a fault line.
They'll think it was a tremor.
Data centre’s on B-4.
All right, let's go.
It's working.
What's going on?
Are we good?
Something's wrong.
The system's blocking the virus.
We can still blow the place.
[ALARM SOUNDING]
Hold it.
Get them past here.
Freeze!
Down on the ground. Now!
[GRUNTING]
Reese.
Let's go.
CAMERON:
What's the matter?
I get in, I get to a certain point,
and it kicks me out.
It's like a part of Vick's
memory just turns off.
I've even cranked up the juice.
Oh.
And there goes the power supply.
[DIALLING CONNECTION]
That's weird.
My phone is dialling
for an internet connection.
What the hell?
Vick's reactivating.
He's trying to get online?
Did it happen? Did he get out?
Did he call someone or something?
No.
We should be very careful
with Vick's chip.
Yeah, that's the understatement
of the century.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Well, how did it go?
It didn't work. We
should just blow it.
We can't go back there.
What are you gonna do, take an axe
to every traffic light in town?
No.
We only need to take down one.
Two centimetres left.
One centimetre down.
Cut a semicircle with a
diameter of 12 centimetres.
Is it okay if I'm off by a little bit?
Yes.
Cut a bigger circle to compensate.
How exactly is this gonna work?
Her neural network is the most
sophisticated learning computer on earth.
If we can get her chip
into the A.R.T.I.E. System,
it can take over the whole thing.
Just like Vick did with my laptop.
She can kill it.
You can get in through a traffic light?
Yes.
Are you sure?
No.
Start the incision.
Push harder, down
to my endoskeleton.
Sarah.
Once she's in the city's mainframe,
What's to say she'll come back out?
You know, maybe-
Maybe it's not the Turk
that created Skynet.
Maybe it's her.
Maybe this was her plan all along.
She's a machine.
She doesn't have a
soul and she never will.
You don't have to trust her.
You can trust me.
[EXHALE]
Good.
Set the pliers over the shielded tab
On the end of the chip.
A half turn counter-clockwise
and pull it out.
It's okay, John.
It's not the first time we've done this.
I have to get this into the CPU interface.
I'll take him to the traffic light.
Okay, she's in.
How long?
15 seconds.
20.
For what it's worth,
I believe you.
I don't think you knew your
guy was watching Barbara.
Thanks.
Okay, it's done.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Derek, don't.
I want you to hear this
in no uncertain terms.
Someday one of these
things is gonna kill you.
It's not gonna be this one.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[HORN HONKING]
[TRAFFIC NOISE]
What was it like?
What'd you see in there?
I saw everything.
Sarkissian returned my call.
He'll meet about selling the Turk.
He's still got it?
When's the meeting?
Tomorrow morning.
Meaning this news could have waited?
You killed Andy Goode.
There was no one there to protect him,
and you killed him.
You lie to me again, I'll kill you.
[SARAH]
So much danger in this world
is hidden behind masks.
We tell our children
stories of good and evil,
while knowing it's not that simple.
Do you realize that in 36 hours
we'll be waking up in Tahiti?
I can't believe you bought us tickets.
True evil doesn't give us time to fight.
Or to be afraid.
We keep our heads down,
never bothering to
look behind the masks.
And in doing so,
we resign ourselves to terrible fates
we can never see coming.
ææàãðü×öä»×é×÷æ·»¶ó­¾óèë
-==Http://www.Ragbear.Com==- edited by rogard
2nd Edited for the hearing impaired by Shocker