[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
In the future, my son will lead man
kind in a war against Skynet...
A computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time...
Some to kill him,
one to protect him.
Today, we fight to stop
Skynet from ever being created,
to change our future,
to change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
<font
color="#4096d1">-==http://subland.5286.cn==-
color="#4096d1">sync:ÏºÃ×, edited by rogard,
2nd edited for the hearing impaired by Shocker.
Previously, on Terminator:
the Sarah Connor chronicles...
SARAH:
I need three sets of papers.
20,000 - that's a family
discount in these hard times.
Especially for someone
who's been dead eight years.
AGENT ELLISON:  Your fiancé killed a man
because she believes that
in the future he'll invent a computer
system that declares war on the world.
Skynet robots from the future.
And you're one of them.
CAMERON:
Yes. I'm that.
These things, all of them are
programmed with specific missions.
DEREK:
Don't let that thing touch me.
SARAH:
We have to stop you bleeding!
DEREK:
Get away from me!
You don't even know who this guy is!
He's your uncle.
He doesn't know.
My Turk could defeat every human player
that has ever lived and probably ever will live.
You talk about it like it's human.
Well, you never know.
What about the Turk?
I was paid money for it.
That's all I have.
Sarkissian returned my call.
He'll meet about selling the Turk.
[NARRATOR]  When John was little, he used to
sleep with his hand under my chin.
At night, I lay awake watching him.
Calm, peaceful, happy.
I wanted to freeze time and let
my son live in that moment forever.
But you can't freeze time.
You can't protect your children
from the future that awaits them.
Batting's hard, Derek.
You're doing great, Kyle.
Just remember how I showed you.
Stay on top of the ball.
Moment there...
And then...
Yes!
Finally!
It's gone.
[RUMBLES/EXPLOSION]
Fireworks!
(INDISTINCT)
He's a very hot-headed man.
- I learned Armenian.
- Armenian.
The guy we're meeting with,
his name's Sarkissian.
That's Armenian.
Well, we're not here to charm him.
We're here to get the
Turk and get out, simple.
He said we should
meet him at table 19.
Excuse me, I think we have
some business to take care of.
Oh, of course. Sorry.
Table 19.
It's right there.
Keep the change.
DEREK:
Remind me again.
Why--why are the boys out
here and the girls in there?
Because one of the boys
is still wanted for murder,
and one of the girls is...
harder than nuclear nails.
And the other one's a Cyborg.
[CHUCKLES]
You wanna know why we're really here?
Why?
Moore's law.
The guy who founded Intel
said that every two years,
the number of transistors
on a computer chip doubles.
30 years ago, it was an observation.
Now it's a law.
Tech industry spent billions
doubling chip power.
And?
And that's how we can go
from a chess computer
to the apocalypse in just four years.
I learned that a lot can
happen in four years.
A lot can happen in four seconds.
One minute, I'm in the yard with
my brother, playing baseball,
and the next, we look up,
and the sky's on fire.
Judgment Day.
What'd you do?
The only thing to do:
Took Kyle and went underground.
What was he like?
He was just a kid when it happened.
Eight years old.
I was 15.
How do you tell an eight-year-old
machines have taken over the world?
How do you?
You don't.
Maybe he's at another table.
[COMPUTER BLEEPING]
Nice doing business with you.
We don't have $500,000.
Not yet.
[DOORBELL CHIMES]
[SIGHS]
Mr. Dixon
It's been a long time since we
spoke. So, what, eight years?
Mm, I see you're a man of faith.
Oh, no, my wife's a catholic.
It's her mother's.
Do you know the story on
the rapture, Mr. Dixon?
Like I said, my wife.
Hmm.
"And I heard, as it were,
the noise of thunder.
and I heard the voice of the
fourth beast say, 'come and see'.
and I looked.
and behold, a pale horse.
and his name that
sat on him was death.
And hell followed with him."
The book of revelation.
What is this?
I've seen some things, Mr. Dixon.
I've seen some things with my own
eyes, and heard 'em with my own ears.
I've beheld.
And upon my beholding,
I've come to the conclusion,
while new to me,
might be old hat for you.
What the hell are you talkin' about?
Sarah Connor's alive.
And I think you know where she is.
You're crazy.
If Sarah is alive, and I believe she is,
we are working in the realm where
much, perhaps anything, is possible.
Robots...
Soldiers from the future, Skynet.
If...
...Sarah were alive, I'm sure
she'd like to hear you say that.
Come on, tell me what you know.
I'm gonna tell you...
What I told the other guy.
I don't know anything.
The other guy?
The other agent you guys sent here.
Kester.
Kester?
Ooh!
Can I help you with something...
Bro?
That is a nice sword.
Hey...
You don't touch that.
Family heirloom?
None of your business.
You're right.
But this is my business.
Shh, shh, shh.
Do you know this woman?
I never seen her before in my life.
Well, I'll help you out.
Her name's Sarah Connor.
I know that, because I read her FBI file.
I told you.
I don't know her.
Well, that's...
Very interesting.
Because your uncle Enrique knew her.
He knew her pretty well, in fact.
And you know what?
He's in that file too.
As one of the last known
associates and an FBI informant...
You know what I think?
I think she went to him
looking for identification.
And I think he sent her to you.
And I think, after she got what she
wanted, she went back to Enrique.
And I think she killed him.
And now I have something she wants.
So where is she?
"Los Ninos Heroes."
They were the six military cadets
that died defending Chapultepec castle.
[CHUCKLES]
Bright boys.
[GROANING]
Now, my friend...
how brave a boy are you?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I'll handle this.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
Go home.
Agent Ellison came into my house.
And you turn around and come to mine?
I know, it's okay.
This is gonna be hard
for you to imagine, but...
I think he's ready to believe you.
Believe me?
Charlie, this isn't about believing me.
If he believes you, he can protect you.
Do you remember what you saw here?
What we destroyed?
Who destroyed it?
The FBI can't protect us.
You can't protect us.
If one of them follows
you here, not the FBI...
One of them...
He'll have killed us.
So take your wife.
Get as far away from here as you can.
Forget me.
Forget John, Just go!
CAMERON:
Bright yellow tint.
Grade M.
´Slightly included. Shallow cut.
DEREK:  You can't just give a briefcase
full of money to a guy like that
and expect he's just
gonna and over the Turk.
Actually, I can.
Well, those are from the safe house I
set up, so, technically, they're mine.
Well, I'm guessing you stole them, so
technically, they're evidence in a felony.
What are we up to?
Current estimated value, $246,000.
You don't even have enough.
We'll negotiate.
DEREK:  We don't even know what
this guy looks like.
SARAH:  We know what the Turk looks like.
DEREK:  I love these places.
SARAH:  Food courts?
DEREK:  First day after me and
the guys jumped through,
we went to the Century City mall
and we spent the whole day there.
We all puked.
You know, the funny thing, in the future,
that place is a concentration camp.
Is that it?
Where is he?
Son of a bitch stood us up again.
We have to go.
We came here for the Turk.
We can't get it if we're in prison.
MAN:  Sarah Connor.
So nice to finally meet you.
You know, a woman...
She calls my cell phone.
She says she's interesting in buying this...
Very special computer.
Now, what do you do?
You just turn around and you just sell it?
Or, maybe...
You're very beautiful.
For a dead woman.
Just let us pay you for the computer,
and you'll never hear from us again.
If I was gonna sell you the
Turk, you'd have had it by now.
So this is my counter offer.
The money you was gonna
pay me for the Turk,
you take that number and
you multiply it by four.
$2 million?
You're a fugitive, Ms. Connor.
Might make that a small price for freedom.
Here's my counter offer.
You tell us where the
Turk is, we keep our money,
and I bury you in the back yard.
[CHUCKLES]
Will you listen to me?
If I don't walk out of here in ten minutes,
my people are instructed to call the FBI
and tell them everything I know.
Your people?
Yeah.
My people.
Same people who are watching your son.
He's on a field trip, isn't he?
With his class?
Science museum, I believe.
Your people have no idea
what they're walking into.
Derek.
How long do we have to get the money?
You got 24 hours.
Follow him.
You haven't spoken for 28 minutes.
Well, it's nothing.
All right.
My birthday's tomorrow.
Okay?
I know that mom totally forgot.
Birthday?
Hey, you don't know what a birthday is?
It's the day you were born.
Pretty memorable for a mother, right?
But it was 16 years ago.
No, a birthday's like a holiday.
Like once a year, every year,
people just kind of...
celebrate you, I guess.
And you get presents
and you eat cake and...
It's fun.
It's supposed to be.
Last year, mom got me a flak jacket.
That's a tight present.
No. It's not.
Whatever...
Look, I don't know why I care.
I've been driving since I was 12, and,
technically, this is my 24th birthday.
It's just I...
time-travelled over eight of them.
Do I have a birthday?
I don't know.
Were you born?
I was built.
Well, then, maybe you have like a build day.
Hey, Cameron, listen to this.
Hey, what do you have on there, man?
Hatful of hollow, man.
Just downloaded it this morning.
JOHN:
Dude, you gotta be kidding me.
Cameron.
Stay with the group, please.
Sorry.
Hey, Cameron.
There you are.
Your brother's been looking for you.
Oh, wow.
Is this your car?
No, it belongs to the guy I
killed and stuffed in the trunk.
Hey!
Where you been?
Mom says we gotta get home right now.
What's up with the car?
Cameron stuffed a dead guy in the trunk.
He was following us.
[CHUCKLES]
Your sister's dark, bro.
You're gonna love the Smiths.
JOHN:
Yeah, she's, uh, she's really Goth.
CAMERON:
Get in.
Wait, Cameron.
Hey, um...
There's something I...
kind of need to ask you.
Um, you think maybe you might
wanna go to the prom with me?
- Just say yes!
- Yes!
Hey, Karen.
Can you run a name for me?
I thought you knew everybody around here.
Who you looking for?
Guy's name is Kester.
He's an agent.
Uh, it doesn't ring a bell.
Give me a sec.
There we go.
This the guy?
We've been so swamped lately, it's all
I can do to keep this place organized.
What file did you need?
File number 100-655371.
The Sarah Connor case.
Looks like it's checked out, my friend.
To agent Ellison.
James Ellison?
One and only.
Thank you for your time.
Oh, hold the elevator.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
He was a threat to us.
Did he say anything?
A name, a location?
He said very little.
And then he was quiet.
I lost Sarkissian at the Cahuenga pass.
Damn it!
We have to find him.
We have to get out of this house.
No, we're not moving.
- He knows where we live, John.
- I don't care.
We're not running, not today.
This house has a bull's-eye
painued on the front door.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[CONTINUED RINGS]
Do your thing.
[IMITATION MAN VOICE]
Hello?
Are you still watching those kids?
I got my eye on them right now.
I think they have someone following me.
No more games.
Bring them back here.
Here?
Where's here?
Okay, so he's expecting this
guy to show up there any minute.
And when he doesn't, the first
place he's gonna come is here.
Mom...
We can't stay here, John.
Not while he's out there.
It's too risky.
I'm sorry.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Wait here.
Where is he?
Who?
Uhh!
He.
Need I repeat?
John, go check the office.
See if he stashed the Turk in there.
Can you get through the door?
Yes.
But the wall would be much faster.
Hi,
What are you doing here?
Waiting for my daddy to finish work.
Okay, listen.
I need you to stay in this
room with the door closed, okay?
Even if you hear loud noises or you
get scared, you need to stay in here.
Can you do that for me?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Okay.
[SIGHS]
Let him go.
Not my kid.
Not mine either.
Are you okay?
[WHISPERING]
John...
Let's go back inside.
Hi...
Is that your daddy out there in the alley?
No.
My daddy went to the café.
You know how to get
back there from here?
You go find your daddy.
Don't look back,
just go.
JOHN:
Sarkissian's hard drive.
Do I need to kill you now?
[COCKS GUN]
Kester.
Yeah, that's what he likes to call himself
when he's out trick-or-treating
in his FBI costume.
George Lazlo's a better
actor than we thought.
That's not Lazlo.
James, are we looking
at the same picture here?
This is your guy.
It's Lazlo.
The blood doesn't match.
[CHUCKLES]
Come on, what are you saying?
That this guy somehow killed six people
and then found a plastic surgeon who
made him look identical to George Lazlo?
And then what?
Killed Lazlo, stole his
identity, and then...
put himself in the FBI database
as this guy Kester?
To what end?
What's the goal here?
Who is he?
What is he?
Yeah.
What is he, that...
stands across from a man after killing
two other men within 36 hours...
and when asked of his involvement,
cannot only lie, but lie well?
And not only lie well,
but not blink or twitch
or perform one simple human
reaction to the situation.
So, yes...
I think it's fair to ask:
what is he?
You know as well as I
some men are monsters.
Yeah.
Monsters.
Let's go get him.
Mom...
Sorry.
Look, he double-encrypted the drive.
I've unlocked a lot of it, but
there's still a lot left to go through.
How much?
That's about 1,000 useful files.
Each one takes about five minutes to decrypt.
And I'm on number 37.
You do the math.
Let me know when you have something.
How are you holding up?
I'm all right.
So it's your birthday.
Yeah, how'd you know?
You kidding?
I celebrated your 30th with you.
How was that?
You got drunk as a skunk.
Come on.
I'll buy you a beer.
I'm 16.
All right, I'll buy you an ice cream cone.
Come on.
It's your birthday.
When there are things to celebrate,
they should be celebrated.
Let's go.
Your mom has never
killed anyone, has she?
You know, she's got murder in her eyes
all the time, but her heart's pure.
It's a good thing, you know.
Keep a-- keep a pure heart.
[DEREK'S EXHALE]
It's beautiful here, isn't it?
You know, you stay long enough,
you start fooling yourself
into thinking that this is...
How it's always gonna be.
And you remember what this place'll
look like when it's on fire, and...
you realize you'll do whatever it takes
to keep from watching it burn again.
Is that...
you?
And the younger one, is that...
Kyle.
Throws pretty good for a five-year-old, huh?
Your father always had a nice arm.
How'd you know?
Every time I look at you, I see him.
Besides, your mom's his type.
Happy Birthday
[ RADIO DISPATCHER ]
FBI raid in North Hollywood.
Suspect considered armed
and extremely dangerous.
May be posing as an FBI agent.
Last name Kester.
[SIREN WAILING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[GUN FIRING]
[CONTINUED GUN FIRING]
[SCREAMING]
[SIREN WAILING]
[NARRATOR]  In 'Lord of the Flies', a group of
boys slaughter a pig in the jungle.
They torture it and place its head
on a sharpened stake as an offering
to the beast that hovers,
god-like, above the island.
[SIREN WAILING]
Black blood drips down the pig's teeth.
And the boys run away.
Later, when one of the boys is alone, he weeps.
But not for the pig.
The boy weeps for the end of innocence
and the darkness of men's hearts.
Have you seen Derek?
No.
He's, uh, still at the park, I think.
And what were you two doing?
Nothing.
Uh, we just went to get an ice cream.
Here.
Check these out.
Looks like you weren't the
only one looking for the Turk.
Who's this?
I'm not sure.
But he came in after Dimitri and before you.
Enough time for sarkissian
to sell him the Turk.
It's not much to go on,
but it's something.
Why don't you take a break?
No, no, it's all right.
I can keep going.
How are we supposed to
celebrate your birthday
if you're sitting in
front of a computer?
You actually thought
I forgot your birthday?
It's just we have much
more important things to
think about than my stupid birthday.
Your birthday is important.
No, it's not important.
Finding the Turk, stopping Skynet,
judgment day-- that's important, that's...
That's our life.
It's our mission.
This is our life.
If we stop caring about that, then we're lost.
Well, when you put it like that...
I sent Cameron to get a cake.
What do you want for dinner?
Well, not to insult your cooking or anything,
but do you mind if we went out?
Yeah, we can do that.
All right, let me shut this down.
What? What's the matter?
The guy that Derek killed...
in the alley.
Sarkissian.
I don't think that was Sarkissian.
[ALARM SOUNDING]
subtitle edited by rogard,
2nd edited for the hearing impaired by Shocker.