SARAH: In the future my son will
lead mankind in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created...
...to change our future...
...to change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
ANNOUNCER: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
SARAH:
I need three sets of papers.
Twenty-thousand.
That's a discount in these hard times.
Especially for someone
who's been dead eight years.
ELLISON: Your fiancée killed a man
because she believed in the future...
...he'll invent a computer system
that declares war on the world.
Skynet...
...robots from the future.
And you're a...
CAMERON: Yes, I'm a...
SARAH: These things, all of them,
are programmed with specific missions.
[GROANING]
Don't let that touch me.
- We have to stop you bleeding.
- Get it away.
- You don't even know who this guy is.
- He's your uncle. He doesn't know.
My Turk could defeat
every human player that has ever lived...
...and probably ever will live.
SARAH: You talk about it like it's human.
- Well, you never know.
- Who bought The Turk?
- I was paid money for it.
That's... That's all I have.
Sarkissian returned my call.
He'll meet about selling The Turk.
SARAH:
When John was little, he used to sleep...
- ...with his hand under my chin.
- Come on.
At night I'd lay awake watching him.
Calm, peaceful, happy.
I wanted to freeze time...
...and let my son
live in that moment forever.
But you can't freeze time.
You can't protect your children
from the future that awaits them.
- Batting's hard, Derek.
- You're doing great, Kyle...
...just remember how I showed you.
Stay on top of the ball.
The moment's there...
...and then...
- Yes!
- Yes. Finally.
...it's gone.
[EXPLOSION IN SKY]
Fireworks.
Cool.
[CAMERON SPEAKING IN ARMENIAN]
He's a very hotheaded man.
- I learned Armenian.
- Armenian.
The guy we're meeting with,
his name's Sarkissian.
- That's Armenian.
- Well, we're not here to charm him...
...we're here to get The Turk
and get out. Simple.
He said we should meet him at Table 19.
Excuse me,
I think we have business to take care of.
Oh. Of course. Sorry. Table 19?
- It's right there.
- Keep the change.
Remind me again,
why are the boys out here...
...and the girls in there?
Because one of the boys
is still wanted for murder...
...and one of the girls
is harder than nuclear nails.
And the other one's a cyborg.
[LAUGHS]
- You wanna know why we're really here?
- Why?
- Moore's Law.
- Hmm?
Moore's Law.
The guy who founded Intel said...
...that every two years the number
of transistors on a computer chip doubles.
Thirty years ago it was an observation,
now it's a law.
Tech industry spend billions
doubling chip power.
And?
And that's how we can go
from a chess computer...
...to the apocalypse in just four years.
I learned that a lot can happen...
...in four years.
[DEREK SCOFFS]
A lot can happen in four seconds.
One minute I'm in the yard
with my brother playing baseball...
...the next,
we look up and the sky's on fire.
Judgment Day.
What did you do?
Only thing to do.
Took Kyle, went underground.
What was he like?
He was just a kid when it happened.
Eight years old. I was 15.
[CHUCKLES]
How do you tell an 8-year-old
machines have taken over the world?
How do you?
You don't.
Maybe he's at another table.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
- Nice doing business with you.
- We don't have 500,000 dollars.
Not yet.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
[SIGHS]
Mr. Dixon.
What's it been, eight years?
Mm. I see you're a man of faith.
Oh. No, my wife's a Catholic.
It's her mother's.
Do you know the story
on the rapture, Mr. Dixon?
Like I said. My wife.
Hmm.
And I heard as it were,
the noise of thunder.
And I heard the voice
of the fourth beast say:
"Come and see."
And I looked.
And behold, a pale horse.
And his name that sat on him was Death.
And hell followed with him.
The Book of Revelation.
What is this?
[SIGHS]
I've seen some things, Mr. Dixon.
I've seen some things with my own eyes
and heard them with my own ears.
I've beheld.
And upon my beholding,
I've come to the conclusion...
...while new to me...
...might be old hat for you.
What the hell are you talking about?
Sarah Connor is alive.
And I think you know where she is.
You're crazy.
[CHUCKLES]
If Sarah is alive, and I believe she is...
...we are working in a realm where much,
perhaps anything, is possible.
Robots...
...soldiers from the future...
...Skynet.
If...
...Sarah were alive...
...I'm sure she'd like to hear you say that.
Come on, tell me what you know.
I'm gonna tell you...
...what I told the other guy.
I don't know anything.
- The other guy?
- Yeah.
The other agent that you guys sent here.
Kester.
[MEN LAUGHING]
MAN 1: Watch... You see him?
MAN 2: Where'd you get this at, homey?
[GUN COCKS]
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
I don't know, homey.
Can I help you with something, bro?
- That is a nice sword.
- Hey.
- You don't touch that.
- Family heirloom?
None of your business.
SARKISSIAN: You're right.
- But this is my business.
- Shh, shh, shh.
Do you know this woman?
Never seen her before in my life.
SARKISSIAN:
Well, I'll help you out.
Her name's Sarah Connor.
- I know that because I read her FBI file.
- I told you...
...I don't know her.
SARKISSIAN:
Well, that's very interesting.
Because your uncle Enrique knew her.
He knew her pretty well, in fact.
And you know what?
He's in that file too.
As one of her last known associates...
...and an FBI informant.
You know what I think?
I think she went to him
looking for identification.
And I think he sent her to you.
And I think after she got
what she wanted...
...she went back to Enrique.
And I think she killed him.
And now I have something she wants.
So where is she?
"Los Niños Héroes."
They were the six military cadets
that died defending Chapultepec Castle.
[LAUGHING]
[WHISPERS IN SPANISH]
Brave boys.
[GRUNTS]
Now, my friend...
...how brave a boy are you?
[BANGING ON DOOR]
I'll handle this.
- What are you doing here? Go home.
- I need to talk to you.
Agent Ellison came into my house.
- And you turn around and come to mine?
- I know. It's okay.
This is gonna be hard for you to imagine,
but I think he's ready to believe you.
Believe me?
Charlie, this isn't about believing me.
- If he believes you, he can protect you.
- Do you remember what you saw here?
What we destroyed? Who destroyed it?
The FBI can't protect us,
you can't protect us.
If one of them follows you here...
Not the FBI.
...One of them...
...you'll have killed us.
So take your wife,
get as far away from here as you can.
Forget me, forget John, just go.
CAMERON:
Faint-yellow tint.
Grade M.
Slightly included, shallow cut.
You can't just give a briefcase full of money
and expect he's gonna hand over The Turk.
Actually, I can.
Well, those are from the safe house I set up
so technically, they're mine.
Well, I'm guessing you stole them.
So technically,
they're evidence in a felony.
What are we up to?
Current estimated value: 246,000.
You don't even have enough.
We'll negotiate.
DEREK: We don't even know
what this guy looks like.
SARAH:
We know what The Turk looks like.
DEREK:
I love these places.
Food courts?
Day after me and the guys jumped,
we went to the Century City Mall...
...we spent the whole day there.
We all puked.
And the funny thing, in the future?
The place is a concentration camp.
Is that it?
Where is he?
The son of a bitch stood us up again?
We have to go.
- We came here for The Turk.
- Can't get it if we're in prison.
SARKISSIAN:
Sarah Connor.
So nice to finally meet you.
You know, a woman...
...she calls my cell phone...
...she says she's interested in buying
this very special computer.
Now, what do you do?
Just turn around or you just sell it?
Or maybe...
You're very beautiful...
...for a dead woman.
Just let us pay you for the computer
and you'll never hear from us again.
If I was gonna sell you The Turk...
...you'd have had it by now.
So this is my counteroffer.
The money you was gonna pay me
for The Turk...
...you take that number
and you multiply it by four.
Two million dollars?
SARKISSIAN:
You're a fugitive, Ms. Connor.
Might make that
a small price for freedom.
[GUN COCKS]
Here's my counteroffer.
You tell us where The Turk is,
we keep our money...
...and I bury you in the backyard.
Ha, ha. Will you listen to me?
If I don't walk out of here
in 10 minutes...
...my people are instructed
to call the FBI...
...and tell them everything I know.
- Your people?
- Yeah.
My people.
Same people who are watching your son.
He's on a field trip, isn't he?
With his class?
Science museum, I believe.
Your people have no idea
what they're walking into.
Derek.
How long do we have to get the money?
You got 24 hours.
[DOOR OPENS]
Follow him.
You haven't spoken for 28 minutes.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, it's nothing.
All right.
My birthday's tomorrow.
Okay?
I know that Mom totally forgot.
- Birthday?
- Yeah. You don't know what a birthday is?
It's the day you were born.
Pretty memorable for a mother, right?
But it was 16 years ago.
No, a birthday's like a holiday.
Like, once a year, every year...
...people just kind of celebrate you,
I guess.
And you get presents
and you eat cake and...
...it's fun.
Ha. It's supposed to be.
Last year, Mom got me a flak jacket.
That's a tight present.
No.
It's not.
Whatever, look, I...
I don't know why I care.
I've been driving since I was 12
and technically, this is my 24th birthday.
It's just I time-traveled
over eight of them.
Do I have a birthday?
I don't know.
Were you born?
I was built.
Well, then maybe you have, like,
a built day.
Hey, Cameron. Listen to this.
Hey, what do you have in there, man?
MORRIS:
Hatful of Hollow, man.
Just downloaded it this morning.
JOHN: Dude, you gotta be kidding me,
I love The Smiths.
MORRIS:
Yeah, here.
JOHN:
I don't have that album.
Cameron.
Stay with the group, please.
Sorry.
Hey, Cameron.
There you are.
Your brother's been looking for you.
Oh, wow.
Is this your car?
No. It belongs to the guy I killed
and stuffed in the trunk.
Hey.
Where you been?
Mom says we gotta get home right now.
- What's up with the car?
- Cameron stuffed a dead guy in the trunk.
He was following us.
[LAUGHS]
Your sister's dark, bro.
You're gonna love The Smiths.
JOHN: Yeah, she's, uh...
- She's really goth.
- Get in.
Wait, Cameron. Hey, um...
There's something
I kind of need to ask you.
Um, you think maybe you might wanna
go to the prom with me?
- Just say yes.
- Yes.
[CHUCKLES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Yes. Yes. Ha-ha-ha!
Hey, Karen.
Can you run a name for me?
I thought you knew
everybody around here.
- Who you looking for?
- Guy's name is Kester. He's an agent.
Oh, doesn't ring a bell, give me a sec.
Here we go.
This the guy?
[SIGHS]
We've been swamped lately,
it's all I can do to keep this place organized.
What file did you need?
File number 100-655371.
The Sarah Connor case.
CLERK:
Looks like it's checked out, my friend.
To Agent Ellison.
- James Ellison?
- One and only.
Thank you for your time.
ELLISON:
Oh, hold the elevator.
He was a threat to us.
Did he say anything? A name? A location?
He said very little.
And then he was quiet.
[SCOFFS]
I lost Sarkissian at the Cahuenga Pass.
Damn it.
- We have to find him.
- We have to get out of this house.
- No. We're not moving.
- He knows where we live.
We're not running. Not today.
This house has a bull's-eye
painted on the front door.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Do your thing.
[AS MAN] Hello.
SARKISSIAN: Still watching those kids?
I got my eye on them right now.
Well, I think they had someone follow me.
No more games, bring them back here.
[LINE GOES DEAD]
"Here"? Where's "here"?
Okay, so he's expecting this guy
to show up there any minute.
And when he doesn't,
the first place he's gonna come is here.
Mom.
We can't stay here, John.
Not while he's out there.
It's too risky.
I'm sorry.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[GUNS COCK]
Wait here.
- Where is he?
- Who?
- Unh!
- He. Need I repeat?
[BEEPING]
John, go check the office,
see if he stashed The Turk in there.
Can you get through the door?
Yes.
But the wall would be much faster.
Hi. What are you doing here?
Waiting for my daddy to finish work.
Okay, listen.
I need you to stay in this room
with the door closed, okay?
Even if you hear loud noises
or you get scared...
...you need to stay in here.
Can you do that for me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Okay.
Let him go.
Not my kid.
Not mine, either.
[SOBBING]
Shh, shh, shh.
You okay?
Yeah. You okay?
[GIRL SCREAMS]
John.
[PANTING]
Let's go inside.
Let's go in.
Hey.
Is that your daddy out there in the alley?
No.
My daddy works in the café.
Do you know how to get back there
from here?
You go find your daddy.
Don't look back, just go.
JOHN:
Unh. Sarkissian's hard drive.
Come on.
Do I need to kill you now?
Kester.
That's what he likes to call himself when
he's out trick-or-treating in his FBI costume.
George Laszlo's
a better actor than we thought.
That's not Laszlo.
James, are we looking at the same
picture here? This is your guy.
It's Laszlo.
The blood doesn't match.
[CHUCKLES]
Come on. What are you saying?
This guy somehow killed six people...
...and then found a plastic surgeon who
made him look identical to George Laszlo?
And then what?
Killed Laszlo, stole his identity...
...and then put himself in the FBI database
as this guy, Kester?
To what end? What's the goal here?
Who is he?
What is he?
"What" is he?
Yeah.
What is he?
What is he
that stands across from a man...
...after killing two other men
within 36 hours?
And when asked of his involvement...
...cannot only lie, but lie well.
And not only lie well...
...but not blink or twitch...
...or perform one simple human reaction
to the situation.
So yes.
I think it's fair to ask, what is he?
You know as well as I.
Some men are monsters.
Yeah.
Monsters.
Let's go get him.
Yeah.
[SNIFFS]
- Mom.
- Sorry.
Look, he double-encrypted the drive.
I've unlocked a lot of it
but there's still a lot left to go through.
How much?
About a thousand useful files,
each takes about five minutes to decrypt...
...and I'm on number 37.
You do the math.
SARAH:
Let me know when you have something.
How you holding up?
I'm all right.
[DEREK SIGHS]
So it's your birthday.
How... How'd you know?
You kidding?
I celebrated your 30th with you.
[CHUCKLES]
How was that?
You got drunk as a skunk.
[LAUGHS]
Come on, I'll buy you a beer.
I'm 16.
All right, I'll buy you an ice-cream cone.
Come on, it's your birthday.
When there are things to celebrate,
they should be celebrated.
Let's go.
Your mom has never killed anyone,
has she?
[DEREK CHUCKLES]
You know, she's got murder in her eyes
all the time, but her heart's pure.
It's a good thing, you know.
Keep a... Keep a pure heart.
[DEREK SIGHS]
It's beautiful here, isn't it?
When you stay long enough you start
fooling yourself into thinking that this is...
...how it's always gonna be.
Then you remember what this place
will look like when it's on fire and...
...you realize you'll do whatever it takes
to keep from watching it burn again.
JOHN:
Is that you?
- And the younger one. Is that...?
- Kyle.
Throws pretty good for a 5-year old, huh?
Your father always had a nice arm.
- How'd you know?
- Every time I look at you, I see him.
Besides, your mom's his type.
Happy birthday.
WOMAN [ON RADIO]: All fire and EMT
personnel advised to standby.
FBI raid in North Hollywood.
Suspect considered armed
and extremely dangerous.
May be posing as an FBI agent.
Last name, Kester.
[SIREN WAILING]
AGENT:
Move, move, move! Go, go, go!
[EXPLOSION]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
AGENT:
Fall back!
Fall back, now!
[MAN YELLING]
AGENT:
Shoot!
Shoot him!
[GASPS]
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
SARAH:
In Lord of the Flies, a group of boys...
...slaughter a pig in the jungle.
They torture it and place its head
on a sharpened stake...
...as an offering to the beast
that hovers God-like over the island.
The black blood drips down
the pig's teeth...
...and the boys run away.
Later, when one of the boys is alone,
he weeps.
But not for the pig.
The boy weeps for the end of innocence
and the darkness of men's hearts.
Have you seen Derek?
No.
He's, uh, still at the park, I think.
What were you two doing?
Nothing. Uh, just went to get an ice cream.
Here.
Check these out.
Looks like you weren't the only one
looking for The Turk.
- Who's this?
- I'm not sure.
But he came in after Dmitri
and before you.
Enough time for Sarkissian
to sell him The Turk.
It's not much to go on,
but it's something.
- Why don't you take a break?
- No, it's all right. I can keep going.
How are we supposed to celebrate your
birthday if you're in front of a computer?
You actually thought
I forgot your birthday?
We have much more important things
to think about than my stupid birthday.
Your birthday's important.
No, it's... It's not important.
Finding The Turk, stopping Skynet,
Judgment Day, that's important.
That's...
That's our life.
It's our mission.
This is our life.
If we stop caring about that,
then we're lost.
When you put it like that...
I sent Cameron to get a cake.
[LAUGHS]
What do you want for dinner?
Well, not to insult your cooking or anything,
but do you mind if we went out?
We can do that.
All right, let me... Let me shut this down.
What? What's the matter?
The guy that Derek killed in the alley.
Sarkissian.
I don't think that was Sarkissian.
[CAR ALARM RINGING, DOG BARKING]