SARAH:
In the future...
...my son will lead mankind
in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time.
Some to kill him. One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created...
...to change our future,
to change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
CAMERON: Cromartie's here.
- Are you forgetting that I blew his head off?
He came through. He knows we're here.
He's just a head.
CAMERON:
We're programmed to repair ourselves.
We're programmed to blend in.
SARAH: There are other people here.
CAMERON: Resistance fighters.
SARAH: Humans sent back from the future
by John who have money and guns.
JOHN:
Jumper outside the gym.
That's my new friend.
The crying one from the bathroom.
- We gotta help her now.
- No.
SARAH:
I need you to look at these photographs.
Tell me if you recognize anybody.
TARISSA: The young one.
His name is Andrew Goode.
He was an intern
at Cyberdyne one summer.
Do you wanna have dinner
with me tonight?
My Turk plays chess at a level that could
defeat every human player ever lived...
...and probably ever will live.
SARAH: You talk about it like it's human.
Well, you never know.
CAMERON:
Andy Goode must be killed.
SARAH: Of all of the training
my son received...
...in the jungles of Central America...
...nothing prepared him better
for combat...
...than the game of chess.
It taught him almost everything
he needed to know about war.
That to win, you must be patient...
...bold...
...calculating...
...and most of all...
...willing to sacrifice.
[PHONE RINGING]
Andy.
I haven't heard from you in a while.
MAN: Sorry I've been out of touch,
but after the fire at my house...
...how can I explain?
It was kind of a blessing.
- Can you meet me?
- Where are you?
A hotel in Pasadena.
I'm checking into a tournament.
- A tournament?
- Yeah, you know, chess.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Charlie Dixon.
Agent Kester, FBI.
I need to ask you a few questions.
- What's this about?
- Sarah Connor.
Yeah, come in.
You're really good at math.
Yes.
You wanna do mine?
SARAH:
We got a problem.
Andy Goode
rebuilt his chess computer.
The Turk. But you napalmed it.
Apparently
he's spent every minute since then...
...in a coffee shop in Van Nuys
rewriting the code from memory.
Good code is like a good song.
It's gotta come out.
Yeah, well, this song
might blow up the world.
You should have killed him
when you had the chance.
I'm surprised it's taken you this long
to bring that up.
I'm busy doing John's homework.
Andy entered it into a tournament.
- Computer vs. human?
- Computer vs. computer.
JOHN:
It's the new thing.
These programs are too smart
and powerful to play people.
It gets better
the more we talk about it.
You're going to school.
You and Tin Miss
can meet met there later.
- You don't know anything about chess.
- I know a bit about Andy.
Besides, you can't be absent.
Absent gets you on their radar.
Okay. I get it. I'll go.
Can I have some money for lunch?
[CHATTERING]
MAN:
Is this the most recent one?
WOMAN:
It's the new edition, it just came out.
ANDY:
Isn't this awesome?
God, I love robots.
Come here.
SARAH: So is this one better or worse?
ANDY: Well, it's different, really.
More adaptable, but less predictable.
Not as powerful, for now,
but it's quicker on its feet.
It has a hunger for learning,
but sometimes the lessons it learns...
Sounds more human.
Well, if you want an analogy...
...I'd say that Turk I
had grown into a brooding teenager...
...and Turk II
is still more of a precocious child.
[DMITRI SPEAKING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Speaking of brooding and precocious,
this is my partner Dmitri Shipkov.
I built the Turk
but Dmitri taught it to play chess.
She'll never sleep with you.
We should plug that in.
Yup. Don't listen to him.
He's just worked up
about the military contract.
We have a deal, we split the money.
- What military contract?
- Oh, the one the winner gets.
Why don't you people get your story
straight? Is she dead or isn't she?
Sarah Connor survived the explosion
in the bank vault, and so did her son.
Yeah, that was eight years ago.
You guys just figured that out?
[PHONE BUZZING]
- Yes.
- Yes? "Yes," what?
Yes, we just figured that out.
MICHELLE:
Babe, who was that at the door? Oh.
Good morning, ma'am.
- He's from the FBI.
- I'm asking a few questions.
- Charlie, is something wrong?
- No.
- I'm looking for the Connors.
- Sarah Connor? Your ex?
- I'm looking for them here.
- Here?
Mr. Dixon wanted to marry
Sarah Connor before you.
She's alive.
Maybe he's hiding her here.
What? I already told you, no.
No. Okay?
Look, with all due respect,
Agent Kester...
...the woman that I knew,
Sarah Reese...
...she blew herself up at a bank
eight years ago.
I never knew
and I do not know Sarah Connor.
If you see or hear anything, call me.
Any time. I never sleep.
Just a reminder:
Grief counseling will be available
in my office throughout the week.
- What are they doing?
- Writing notes, for Jordan.
She's dead.
- Yeah, I remember watching her fall.
- Me too.
How will she get the notes?
- She won't.
- But you said...
Sometimes things happen
and they're so bad...
...that people don't know how to deal
with their sadness.
So they write it in a note.
But I thought people cried
when they were sad.
Sometimes it's not enough.
Are you gonna...?
I didn't really know her.
I didn't either.
I like the note part.
[BELL RINGS]
MAN:
Thirty-eight. Come on.
Pass to me the 50 mm...
WOMAN: Okay, so, three-quarter inch,
open-ended.
[IN SPANISH]
MORRIS:
Nice accent, white boy.
I have no idea what's with those guys.
They're always messing with me.
Hey, man, I have no idea.
- I'm Morris.
- John.
Hey, I saw you talking to Cheri Westin
this morning.
Maybe no one told you because
you're new. She's damaged goods.
She's my chem partner.
Do you know her or something?
No one knows her. Something went
down at the last school she was in...
...but no one knows what it is.
Her dad's got her locked down tight.
That's a pretty boring rumor.
- It's truth.
- Not much of it.
I'm just looking out for you, bro.
Yeah, you and everyone else.
WOMAN: An extremely close match
between the American...
...and Japanese computers
here in the finals.
The Americans,
lead by programmer Andrew Goode...
...have a slight positional advantage.
[MAN SPEAKING
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
The Japanese seize control of the center
with bishop to C5.
MAN: The construction's not consistent,
you know.
[BARKING]
Do you know
how many grand masters are here?
How's Andy doing?
Well, that depends on
what your plans are for Andy.
On the one hand,
he's in the final round.
On the other hand,
winner gets a military contract.
Military? Are you serious?
What do we do?
Cheer very hard for the Japanese.
Or Cameron will kill him.
WOMAN: An unorthodox move
by the Japanese...
...leaving their queen hanging
on B6 square.
The American computer
calculating a response.
What just happened?
That bishop on C5 totally hammered him.
Black's in total zugzwang.
- Translation.
- The Japanese just lost their queen.
- They're in big trouble.
- Andy's gonna win.
So that was quite a speech earlier.
With the agent.
That wasn't a speech. It was just...
It's just what it was.
What it was, was a lie.
- What?
- A lie.
You have a tell.
- A what? A tell?
- You have a tell.
When you lie.
Do you know why you love me, Charlie?
I'm gonna tell you why you love me.
It's because I'm not that girl.
I'm not that jealous girl.
I'm not that insecure girl.
- I'm not that petty girl.
- Of course not.
Yeah, so just don't make me
into that girl by lying to me.
If that woman is alive,
if you've seen her...
This is important.
I saw John.
What?
- Where?
- Here. In our house.
MICHELLE:
In our house?
In our house? What did he want?
I don't know.
I think he just wanted to see me.
What are you gonna do about it?
I don't know.
They're fugitives, Charlie.
They're dangerous people.
Sarah's not dangerous.
Oh, well, maybe not
the Sarah you knew, Sarah Reese.
But Sarah Connor killed a man.
- We don't know that.
- Well, what do we know?
What do you know?
Ugh.
WOMAN: The Japanese desperately
hoping for counter play...
...after the disastrous loss
of their queen.
Victory appears imminent
for the Americans.
Andy Goode's Turk seized control
of the match in the middle game...
...and now appears just moves away
from winning.
Rook to C2.
Checkmate.
A shocking turn of events.
The Japanese team has won
the tournament and the military contract.
It's over.
- Andy lost.
- But the other team?
Didn't lose their queen.
They sacrificed it.
Just like Byrne-Fischer all over again.
Byrne-Fischer, 1956?
- Never mind. The point is...
- The Turk fell for a trap?
It's like it just choked.
So now what?
Go after them now?
No, their names weren't
in the safe house. Andy's was.
What computational error
let them put the bishop on E6 to...?
I can't help it if it's stupid.
Nobody's gonna want
Andy's program now.
- That thing's kind of crazy.
- He could still be a threat.
- It could still become Skynet.
- Could also become Pong.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
Maybe I'll just sit Andy down
and tell him everything.
Andy.
[GRUNTING]
Who are you?
[SIRENS WAILING]
Put your hands above your head.
MAN 1:
Do it now. Turn. Turn.
Spread them.
MAN 2: Put your hands behind your back.
Open.
I'm so sorry, Andy.
What's this?
You should write Andy a note.
If you can't cry.
Doesn't bother you that he's dead,
does it?
The world is safer without him.
That was way too easy.
L.A.P.D. firewalls really blow.
Show me what you found.
Okay. Look. No name.
But he's got this tattoo on his arm.
He's one of them.
That's a tattoo
from a Skynet work camp.
He's a resistance fighter.
From the future,
like the three guys in the safe house?
- He was the fourth.
- Then you know him, in the future.
So do you.
He's one of your best soldiers.
They've been watching Andy Goode.
Doing surveillance. Same as us.
Well, not exactly the same.
He actually killed the guy.
That was not his mission.
You sent him here to wait for us.
Well, then I guess he changed his mind.
A lot.
I have to talk to him.
Talk to him, how? He's in lockdown.
MAN:
Freeze!
[GUN COCKS]
What are you doing?
- Math.
- I already did your homework.
I know,
but I still have to take the test.
I need to know this stuff.
Then why did you ask me to do it?
Because maybe it's kind of hard
to concentrate on geometry...
...when people keep dying around you.
You have no idea what I'm talking about,
do you?
You're grieving.
Grieving?
How do you know what grieving is?
I read all the notes.
Cameron Baum?
Mr. Harris wants to see you.
I know this is difficult
for you to talk about.
So I'm gonna need you to be strong.
Okay?
- Can you do that for me?
- Yes, I can be strong.
People say you were the last person
to speak with Jordan before she died.
- Is that true?
- I don't know.
Are you asking me if people say
I was the last person to talk to Jordan?
Or are you asking me
if I was the last one to talk to her?
- I guess I'm asking if you were.
- I don't know.
What did she say
when you did talk to her?
I mean, was it something upsetting
for you to hear?
She said:
"You saw it, right? Right?
You saw it? It's so freaking big
and right out there."
She was talking about the graffiti?
It's freaking big.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
- And no.
- No?
No, it wasn't upsetting
for me to hear it.
Did Jordan mention any names?
Any specific people
that she was upset with?
- Her parents.
- Anyone else?
- The hall monitors.
You ask that question a lot.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
I don't think I told you anything.
Oh, okay.
Can I go now?
I'm done with grief counseling
and I feel much better.
Yeah. Please, go.
Yo, John Doe. You've got a visitor.
MAN:
Those hurt?
Sometimes they crank those tight
before they bring you in here.
That way you might ask me
to loosen them up...
...and I'm able to accommodate you
in that.
It's a trick they do.
It gives us a connection.
But we already got a connection.
Your prints are everywhere.
Oven, light switch, toilet, safe.
Wasn't us who found it.
But somebody did.
After police thought
they cleared the scene...
...somebody came back
and emptied the safe right quick.
Didn't force it either.
They knew the combination.
So we've got you running from
the scene of Andrew Goode's murder.
And we've got you living at,
and disappearing from...
...and most likely returning to,
the scene of these three murders.
All of which
would be a prosecutorial bounty.
But I've also got forensic evidence
linking this...
...to this.
And this.
Feeling connected yet?
What is it?
Hm?
The forensic evidence
linking all these people. What is it?
Blood.
Not my blood?
No, not your blood.
And technically, not even blood.
Some kind of synthetic.
Come on, man, help me out.
Tell me something I don't know.
We're all gonna die.
Yeah. I want him
out of local custody today.
He has more to say, and I want him
on federal turf when he says it.
SARAH:
Yes, this is Cameron's mother.
HARRIS: Mrs. Baum, you're aware of the
recent tragedy we've had here at school?
- Jordan somebody.
- Cowan.
When I spoke to Cameron about it,
she seemed strangely unaffected.
I'm sure you're doing all you can
as a parent.
It's been overwhelming for all of us.
First with the tornado
and then the move.
Tornado?
I'm sorry, she didn't mention that.
That might explain what I think might be
classic post traumatic stress.
You're gonna have to speak up.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[DIAL TONE HUMS]
You shouldn't be here.
- I know who you are.
- And I know who you are.
Who else but Sarah Connor would have
burned down that poor kid's house?
It was you, wasn't it,
on Andy's porch that night?
You've been watching.
You wanted to kill him, the poor kid.
And you did.
I didn't do it.
All I wanted was the Turk.
Somebody else killed him
and took the machine.
- What?
- He was dead when I got there.
He was dead and the Turk was gone,
and I hoped you'd done it.
- You thought I killed him?
- But you're here.
And the Turk is out there.
So we both failed.
You gotta get out of here.
If you haven't figured it out,
I have a T-triple-8 on my ass.
Now, if you found me, it will too.
- We should get you out.
- Go.
Find the partner of the Russian.
He's gotta be neck deep in this.
- You're dead in here.
- Go.
Please.
I won't be the bastard who brings
metal down on the Connors, so go.
You're prettier than your picture.
Picture?
Yeah, it's actually how I clocked you.
- My brother carried your snap for luck.
- Who's your brother?
What does it matter? You don't know
the Reese boys and you never will.
- Reese boys?
- Derek Reese.
Brother's Kyle.
SARAH: When John sent Kyle Reese
back to protect me...
...we had two days together.
He told me about the future...
...about the apocalypse...
...and the terror
of a world run by machines.
Kyle Reese saved my life.
He gave me a son.
He never told me
that he had a brother.
we would have family...
...that, in our grief, we are not alone.
Cheri.
- Cheri.
- Walk away.
John, please.
Lock and key, bro. Lock and key.
- Mom's here.
- Whoa.
Hi, I'm Morris.
You're brother's new best friend.
- Cameron.
- Nice grip.
Watch yourself.
I'm just looking out for you.
- Field trip.
- I call shotgun.
I call 9 mm.
What's the ETA on my prisoner?
All right.
[DEREK WINCES]
- Drop it. Now. Run.
- Easy, easy.
You stay close.
Take the jeep and follow us.
- Metal bitch.
- She's on our side.
Triple-8. Lose him.
SARAH: Let's go.
- Where's Cameron?
Leave her. Let's go.
SARAH: Let's go.
Stay back.
SARAH:
Get down.
[GUNSHOT]
[GROANS]
Bring me the toolbox.
Switchblade.
Pliers.
[POWERING DOWN]
Do something, we have to help.
DEREK: Don't let that thing touch me.
- We have to stop you bleeding.
- Get away.
Please don't move,
you're increasing your blood loss.
- I can't fix it.
- You took a bullet out of me.
He has internal damage. He needs
medical attention or he's gonna die.
- A stun gun. Are you nuts?
- He needs a doctor.
So you're just gonna go kidnap one?
There's an ER a mile away.
It's almost dark.
- Mom, this is crazy, even for you.
- We have to save him.
- What happens when you get caught?
- We have to.
- You don't even know who this guy is.
- He's your uncle.
He doesn't know.
He's your father's brother.
His name's Derek Reese.
John.
Two females.
Approximately 5'6", 120 pounds...
...overpower you and your partner...
...ambush your secure vehicle
and kidnap my prisoner.
Is that an accurate summation of
what happened out here today, officer?
Yeah.
Five-six.
SARAH: if there is a flaw in chess
as a game of war, it is this:
Unlike war,
the rules of chess are constant.
The pieces unchangeable.
You will never win the heart of a rook
or the mind of a knight.
They are deaf to your arguments,
and so be it.
[DEREK BREATHING HEAVILY]
The goal of a chess game
is total annihilation.
But in war,
even as the blood beats in your ears...
...and you race after your enemy,
there is the hope...
...that saner minds than yours will
stop you before you reach your target.
In war, unlike chess,
rules can be changed.
Truces can be called.
The greatest of enemies
can become the best of friends.
Derek?
He's not breathing.
Reese. Reese.
In war, there is hope.