[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
In the future,
my son will lead mankind
in a war against Skynet,
a computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time...
some to kill him...
one to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Season 1 Episode 3
The Turk (v. 1.08)
http://Projet-SG.net
Transcript : Sadgeezer.com
Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
- Where are we?
- Same where.
Different when.
- I want my new name, my all-new me.
- I'll track down Enrique.
I need three sets of papers.
My nephew has taken over the business.
- You're in the system.
- Uncle Enrique will be proud.
He referred to you
as a rata... a snitch.
- Why would you do this?
- Because you wouldn't.
- Why not stay in the past?
- You died.
Two years ago... Cancer.
- I've seen that before.
- Skynet work camp. Resistance fighters.
- You sure there's money here?
- Anything they valued,
money, guns... it'll be hidden.
You told me we'd be safe.
Skynet doesn't know you're here.
There's no directive to hunt you.
What if they found it,
but they don't know what to do?
Who the hell are you, man?
They do.
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
When I was in the mental hospital,
I became obsessed with science.
Not all science, actually.
And not really science at all.
Scientists...
and then only nuclear scientists.
The ones who invented the bomb.
Oppenheimer, Heisenberg,
Fermi, and Teller.
Pioneers, geniuses all.
I read every book I could.
I wanted to understand
why couldn't they stop,
these fathers of our destruction?
And why wouldn't anybody stop them?
And if I had the chance, would I?
Morning.
You look like hell.
Up late.
Newsper clippings...
surveillance photos, bank records.
Pamphlets from every
high-tech company in the state.
I even thought I saw the deeds
to city hall somewhere.
Those resistance guys weren't
sent back here to be our support crew.
They're a Skynet hunting party.
Really? Are you sure?
Most of this is still a puzzle to me,
but there is one list I understand.
Employee list, Cyberdyne Systems.
Seems they thought
it was a good place to start.
And it is.
She's not gonna be happy to see you.
She never is.
- Want me to come along?
- No. You have your own job to do.
A big one.
You're getting pretty good at that.
Thank you.
Still, it's not exactly
brain surgery or anything.
Be pretty funny if you were some sort of
advanced cybernetic intelligence,
yet stumped by a stick of eyeliner.
No, it's not brain surgery.
It would have to be a lot sharper.
Much better.
When you wear clothes...
much better.
Six ways in. Six ways out.
The front opens to the street here.
Security's minimal.
Two armed guards in the morning.
Four in the afternoon.
And if anything goes wrong,
there's a parking lot here.
Mom, it's high school, okay?
Not supermax.
We can handle it.
Don't you kiss me.
Or anyone else.
Okay, now blend in.
Blend in.
Yeah, I mean don't seem like a freak.
You know what I mean, right?
Freak.
Weirdo. Kook. Oddball. Crackpot.
Strange duck. Queer potato.
Nut.
I've been reading the dictionary.
- I don't sleep.
- That's what I'm talking about.
You do that, you sound like a freak.
Don't walk around
acting like my bodyguard.
You're supposed to be my sister.
You won't fool anyone.
I fooled you.
[SIGHS]
What's that all about?
Appears to be a reimagining
of a trompe l'oeil fresco.
I don't sleep.
GUARDS: Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling,
take it off and put it in the basket.
Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling
in the basket.
In the basket, people. Come on.
The line keeps moving. Let's go.
Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling.
In the basket.
Please, keep the line moving.
Cell phones, caps, rings, and bling.
In the basket, please.
Let's go. Come on. Thank you.
Cell phones, caps, rings...
[ALARM SIREN]
Again with you, missy.
Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling
in the basket.
Hold that. Come through.
[ALARM SIREN]
Excuse me. This is my sister.
- Extra credit for you.
- She's got a metal plate in her head.
Really. It's a big one.
[SOUND WAILING]
I fell.
Hard.
All right, let's go.
Cell phones, caps.
I thought you were dead.
Well, I'm not.
Lucky you.
- You look...
- Different?
The same.
Well, I can't explain.
I wouldn't want you to.
Is John...
He's good.
What about that machine?
She's still around.
Not that one.
- The other.
- No.
Do you mind?
You brought it.
Danny's not here?
It's ten years, right?
He's at school.
He hasn't come in a long time.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What do you want, Sarah?
You never die,
and you always want something.
I need you to look at these photographs,
tell me if you recognize anybody.
I know it's been a long time, but...
No.
Nobody. Sorry.
Cause one of them may be involved
with Skynet right now.
They might not even know it.
Sorry to bother you.
I'll leave you alone.
The fourth photo.
The young one.
His name is Andrew Goode.
Andy.
He was an intern
at Cyberdyne one summer.
Miles liked him.
Is he going to die too?
Is that what happens now, he dies?
I don't know.
I hope not.
Well, if he does,
just make sure it matters.
Make sure it's not in vain.
No one dies in vain.
WOMAN: Agent Ellison.
They told me you were coming.
But I told them the last time
you worked a crime scene,
Hoover was cross-dressing at Quantico.
Ballistics.
I can already tell you mine are bigger.
Same gun that killed your boys here
killed one of my CIs.
Enrique Salzia.
What's the connection?
He made fake paper.
Your guys had fake paper.
I hope you're not selling the terrorist
cell theory, 'cause I'm not buying it.
- Why not?
- Well, look at the print report.
KLID, NCIC, CDP, Interpol.
There's nothing here.
These guys were drug dealers,
small-time.
Definitely not worth
you putting your tie on
and breaking open your Thomas guide.
Oh, yeah.
You see this every day.
You didn't find that curious?
Why would anyone wire a safe
directly into the power?
Why's the sky blue, Ellison?
Don't overthink it.
The guys were druggies.
They're not rocket scientists,
not terrorists.
Your guy sold my guys paper.
My guys whacked your guy
to cover their tracks.
Go back to your office.
Your desk misses you.
Right.
Good one.
Somebody came back here
for whatever was in that safe.
They're out there.
And I'm gonna find them.
Hey, buddy.
Hey!
Can't go in there!
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Enjoy.
Have a good day.
Can I help you?
No.
Andy.
Just looking.
You just kept looking over
like you needed something.
That's the phone.
Seriously, if I was gonna
be alone on a desert island
with only a phone for a companion,
that would absolutely be the phone.
Is that something you would do?
[CHUCKLES]
May I?
Got a four-meg camera.
Texting... true texting too.
Not that SMS cartoon bubble junk.
3G data access.
10 Gigs free music.
6 hours of talk time and
36 standby on your battery.
What happens if I press
these numbers here?
'Scuse me?
These numbers, one through nine.
If I press seven of them, will someone
talk to me through the ear part up here?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll take three.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Hi.
Are you calling me?
I was just following up
to make sure phones are okay.
I just left the store.
I know.
Okay. Do you wanna have
dinner with me tonight?
No.
Well, you answered too quickly.
Hear me out.
Just give me one minute.
- 30 seconds?
- Talk fast.
Okay, well, first let me
clear up the whole
desert island and a cell phone thing.
Seems kind of strange if you picture it.
I wasn't.
Right, of course. Why would you?
It's an asinine sales pitch.
There's nowhere to plug in the phone.
It would be worth less than
a rock when the battery died.
- Couldn't use it to open a coconut.
- This is you selling yourself?
Selling myself? Oh, I don't know.
There's something immoral
about the whole selling process.
And yet, that's your job.
Part-time.
And I'm not very good at it.
So I'm actually less immoral
than the average...
anyway.
[SIGHS]
Where was I?
You're right.
About what?
I answered too quick.
Mr. Baum.
- Yes.
- Take your seat, please.
- Hi.
Okay, paper and pencil out.
Time for a pop quiz.
Here.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR LOUD]
I said come on in.
I'm transferring in.
Okay. Any open seat.
What part about don't act like a freak
didn't you understand?
Sit down.
- So...
- So?
Like I said on the phone,
your sweet uncle Enrique
lived a colorful life.
One we have not yet painted in full.
You grow apart.
Every day's a new adventure.
Who can keep up?
I got an uncle who's like a father.
I also got one who's like a stranger.
- How 'bout you two?
- More like an a aunt.
Chatty, chatty.
All right.
So you're not too close.
But he did call you three times
the day he was murdered.
What'd you chat about?
Well, those lakers.
Really? What about 'em?
Kobe. He's the bomb.
I always thought he was a ball hog.
He's all alone, man.
He's got no one elsewho can shoot.
Is that you, Carlos?
Now that your uncle's dead?
You all alone?
Yeah...
all these boys can shoot.
[CHUCKLES]
I didn't kill my uncle.
No.
And you're too smart to know
nothing about who did.
I'll be in touch.
No, I know. The guy's 18 months
ahead of the germans.
Yeah, well, I would
if I had that kinda grant money.
No, I'm not saying
the guy's a complete idiot.
But it's not exactly
avant-garde science, is it?
Why don't they give the money
to the people on the cutting edge?
But they never do. They never...
[FOOTSTEPS]
[GASP]
[GRUNTING]
Hey.
How was school?
I have a metal plate in my head.
She's gonna need a note.
I meant you, not her.
- Yeah, fine.
- You're not gonna give me anything?
We went, we learned.
I didn't get killed.
She didn't kill anybody.
It was a pretty good first day, I think.
- What about you, did you go?
- I did.
And was she surprised
to see you weren't dead?
More like disappointed.
She ID'd one of the safe house photos.
- Intern at Cyberdyne.
- Really? So what does he do now,
build rocket guidance
systems or something?
Cell phone salesman.
Shut up.
And not a very good one.
These need to be cleaned.
Okay, so about the cell phone guy.
I-I'm having dinner with him tonight.
Dinner?
What do you mean, like a date?
- Not a date.
- Are you going to kill him?
Kill him?
I don't know the first thing about him.
He interned at Cyberdyne
when he was in college.
His photo is in a pile of photos.
Nobody dies till I say so.
Tell her.
People die all the time.
They won't wait for her.
I fooled you again.
[SIGHS]
Who are you?
How did you find me?
What--what do you want?
Are you a veteran?
Is that what this is about?
Do you speak?
Read that.
How did you...
No, no, no. That's not possible.
That's an epidermal growth rate.
That's just not sustainable.
Keratinocyte and...
at that rate, you couldn't
possibly maintain
cell regulation or differentiation.
It's impossible.
Possible.
Woo was wrong.
Thomason was wrong.
Parker and Lang were
almost right and still...
completely wrong. I was...
I wasn't even close.
Can you do it?
Well,
[HE STUTTERING]
I'd have to go to my lab.
There's a whole mix of...
growth rates, TGF Beta,
PDGF, EGF.
I'd need...
You know, this is a lot of equipment.
Oh, and blood. We'd need...
at least 20 units.
Preferably with tissues comprised of...
I brought my own.
Can you do it?
Yes.
Yes, I can.
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
In 1943,
the german physicist Werner Heisenberg
delivered a physics lecture
to a packed hall in Zurich.
One of the audience members
was Moe Berg,
an ex-professional baseball player
working as a spy for the O.S.S.
Berg's task was to listen to
the lecture and determine
whether Heisenberg and the Germans
were close to perfecting
the atomic bomb.
If Berg discovered
that this was the case,
he was to wait for
heisenberg outside the hall
and shoot the scientist in the head.
He had never killed anyone before.
So what's your deal, Andy?
I can't imagine you majored
in cell phone sales at college.
No.
No. More like funions
and 12-packs of jolt
from the vintage soda store while
my roommates and I hacked Zelda 3.
So the princess would say
funny lines ripped from reruns.
What's that language you speak, boy?
Computer science.
Caltech. Advanced... dork.
And what would you do
with a computer degree from...
- Caltech?
- I don't know. I never got one.
Really?
My father died senior year.
Mom went a little off the rails.
I dropped out to help.
I'm sorry.
That was a long time ago, but...
thanks anyway.
She's good. She married
the security guard at her bank.
You have family?
Distant.
Don't take this the wrong way, but as a
cell phone salesman, I think I can ask.
Did you ever wanna be anything
other than a waitress?
Yes, I did.
What was it?
I can't remember.
What's this, Andy?
Oh, isn't it great?
That is the official promotional poster
for the Kramnik - Deep Fritz match.
Awesome match.
Just awesome. Most people cite
the '97 Kasparov/Deep Blue
as the watershed man versus
machine chess match. But...
Fritz would have wiped the floor with
Blue like Kramnik did with Kasparov.
Besides, the other
poster's impossible to find.
What is it you do, Andy?
Do you wanna see?
Yes, I wanna see.
All right.
Be hold...
the Turk.
The Turk.
Well, not the original Turk.
The original Turk was an automaton
constructed and unveiled in 1770
by the baron Wolfgang von Kempelen.
It played chess.
Is that what your Turk does?
It plays chess?
I know that sounds boring as hell.
Most people think so. But...
maybe I should put it this way.
My Turk plays chess
at a level that could defeat
every human player that has ever lived
and probably ever will live.
That's not bragging.
A number of AIs can do that now.
But the AI chess platform
is very valuable for artificial
intelligence developers these days.
What?
I thought I saw someone outside.
It's a prowler.
Back porch.
It's the police. There's been some
break-ins in the neighborhood.
- My...
- I have to go, Andy.
No, Sarah, wait.
It's 165 Mesrow. Sarah!
Again, what did it look like?
What did it look like?
Who cares what it looked like?
It was just a rack
of computer equipment.
Okay, but was there
obvious network access?
Do you know what kind of bandwidth?
Are you joking?
What about power supply?
Was there a cooling element,
- like a fan or something?
- John.
Mom, I'm just trying to get
a sense of the horsepower.
I wanna know if this thing was a...
dinky little homemade soap box
or if it was a full-fledged AI platform
capable of learning and growing
and taking on other applications.
It plays chess.
So did Einstein.
Have you ever heard of the singularity?
[SIGHS]
It's a point in time where machines
become so smart
that they're capable of making even
smarter versions of themselves
without our help.
That's pretty much the time
we can kiss our asses good-bye.
Unless we stop it.
Like you said you would.
[KNOCKING]
So I caught a break on a set of
fingerprints from our drug dealers.
I wanted to see your face
when I laid that on you.
See, the only fingerprint database
I hadn't checked was kid prints.
That's no joke.
That's one of your dead terrorists.
A black-haired, brown-eyed
35-pound four-year-old boy living
in Canton, Ohio.
And that's the look I wanted to see.
Hold up.
[HE SIGHS]
Did your crime scene guys find any
peculiar blood?
I think they got all the peculiar
they could stomach with these prints.
Lab says some blood evidence found at
my ci crime scene is almost human...
except there's no
red blood cells present.
I wanna see the blood
evidence from your guys.
I'll get back to you.
You're gonna...
double-check those prints, right?
On the kid, in Canton?
Have a party.
[DIAL TONE]
[SIGHS]
The one thing I hadn't thought of,
the one thing nobody thought possible
was the use of
a synthetic oxygen carrier.
[KEYBROAD'S TONE]
By creating a synthetic spear
that carries oxygen,
bringing nutrients to the skin,
it obviates the need for
the marrow interaction.
The real world applications are...
mind-blowing.
It's ready.
I have a video camera.
- Would it be all right if...
- Move away.
Who are you?
What are you?
Sarah?
Didn't you get my message? I returned
your call about the test results.
Yeah, I got your message.
You're healthy as a horse.
A healthy horse.
I got that from your message.
I wanted to talk to you
about prevention.
For cancer?
What you're doing seems to be working.
Specifically.
Don't smoke.
Get lots of exercise.
Eat leafy greens.
Don't snort asbestos.
I don't mean to make light,
but you've got no risk factors.
No genetic disposition.
Is there anything else
about your history that I should know?
No.
You've got children, right?
Yeah, I got two myself.
You worry.
You wanna make sure you're
always healthy and strong for them.
Don't drive yourself crazy
chasing the future.
We can't predict...
you know?
We can only...
try and prevent.
[DIAL TONE]
Andy,
it's Sarah.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You going to chem?
- Yeah.
What is going on?
No idea.
She is such a skanky, slutty whore.
I love this color.
It's tight, right?
This color's tight.
- What is it?
- Rash.
It's so tight.
I'm a pig.
I look pregnant.
Does it make me look fat?
Yes.
What the hell?
What's your problem?
You asked.
Bitch whore much?
I don't understand.
I said
bitch... whore... much?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at you.
[SOBBING]
You saw it, right?
Right? You saw it?
It's so...
freakin' big, and right out there!
It's freaking big.
Right.
It is, right?
Whoever's doing this is such a jackass.
I mean, who would do this?
And how would they even know?
My parents...
they're gonna kill me.
Kill me!
I mean, don't we have hall monitors?
I mean, how could someone just...
You're upset.
No kidding I'm upset.
My life is freaking over!
Here's a present.
It's tight.
ANDY: Well, I have to admit,
I wondered if I'd see you again.
SARAH: Miracles happen every day.
That's funny.
ANDY: That was a joke, right?
SARAH: If it was funny, it was a joke.
ANDY: So the... police recommended
I put in a security system.
Armed patrol, that kind of thing.
Can't really afford it, though.
SARAH: You think someone wants the turk?
ANDY: Eight years of my life.
Not just the software.
I customized the hardware too.
One month, I worked
so much on a motherboard
that I lost my sight for three days.
That really happened.
Those circuits are so small.
A lot of the gears I actually pulled
from gaming platforms.
Did you know that
the military uses them?
Yeah, I've got the guts of three Xboxes
and four Playstations daisy-chained.
Plus some seriously modded-out code
that I swear came to me in a dream.
And all this to beat
another computer at chess.
None of this to beat
Then what?
What are you doing?
Would you believe me
if I told you turk has moods?
Obviously not in the sense that you
and I understand mood, but sometimes
I'll feed it a particular chess problem,
and it'll solve it one way.
The next day,
I feed it the same problem,
it solves it differently.
Once in a while,
it can't even solve it at all.
Do you know why it does that?
No.
Yeah, neither do I.
Someday...
I'm gonna figure it out.
- Someday, Turk'll tell me.
- You talk about it like it's human.
Well, you never know.
What?
Too far?
What is it?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Do you like this color on me?
What?
I'm a bitch whore.
I have a new friend.
Did she tell you you were a bitch whore?
No. She cried.
Wait... what?
Okay, what the hell is this thing?
Jumper! Outside the gym!
Jump!
She's not gonna jump.
She's just trying to get attention.
- Jump!
- Dude, come on!
That's my new friend.
The crying one from the bathroom.
When?
Two hours, three minutes ago.
Four minutes ago.
She's upset.
Her parents are gonna kill her.
Did you do anything to her?
I tried to give her a tight present.
We gotta help her... now!
- No.
- I'm going up there.
Let me go...
I order you to let me go!
Don't be a freak.
Gotta go... now.
I could havedone something.
I was right there.
Maybe.
Come on, Mom.
John, people who wanna
take their own lives,
this girl...
if they're serious about it,
they'll find a way.
You didn't see her.
If you'd have seen her,
you wouldn't be talking like this.
What were you gonna do, be a hero?
Get your name in the papers, your face?
Isn't that what I'm supposed to be?
A hero? Isn't that who I am?
If it's just gonna sit inside me,
if it's just gonna sit in my gut,
then what are we doing?
What's the point?
Why not just give it to them
if we're gonna act like them?
I don't know how to help him.
Andy Goode must be killed.
[POLICE RADIO]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
Took his eyes, James.
He took his friggin' eyes.
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
On july 16th, 1945,
in the mountains outside
of Los Alamos, New Mexico,
the world's first atomic bomb exploded.
A white light pierced the sky
with such intensity
that a blind girl claimed to see
the flash from a hundred miles away.
After witnessing the explosion,
J. Robert Oppenheimer quoted a fragment
of the Bhagavad Ga, declaring,
"I am become death,
the destroyer of worlds."
His colleague, Ken Bainbridge,
put it another way when
he leaned close to Oppenheimer
and whispered,
"Now we are all sons of bitches."
[SARAH]
Now we are all sons of bitches.