[Sarah's Narrator]
In the future, my son will lead
Mankind in a war against skynet,
the computer system programmed
To destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync/Edit: ﬂ«»‚»‚ & Shocker
The Sarah Connor Chronicles
Season01 Episode05
Previously on terminator:
The Sarah Connor chronicles...
SARAH: Cromartie is here.
Are you forgetting that
I blew his head off?
CAMERON: He came through.
He knows we're here.
It's just a head.
[SARAH]
we're programmed to repair ourselves.
We're programmed to blend in.
there are other people here.
resistance fighters.
humans sent back from
the future by john.
Who have money and guns.
MAN: jumper outside the gym!
CAMERON: It's my new friend.
The crying one of the bathroom.
- We gotta help her now!
- No.
[SARAH]
I need you to look at these photographs.
Tell me if you recognize anybody.
TERISSA:  The young one.
His name is Andrew Goode.
He was an intern at
cyber dyne one summer.
Do you want to have
dinner with me tonight?
My Turk plays chess at level that could
defeat every human player that's ever lived,
and probably ever will live.
SARAH: you talk about it like it's human.
Well, you never know.
[SARAH]
Andy Goode must be killed.
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
Of all the training my son received
in the jungles of central America,
nothing prepared him better for
combat than the game of chess.
It taught him almost everything
he needed to know about war.
That to win you must be patient,
bold, calculating,
and most of all...
willing to sacrifice.
[PHONE RINGING]
Andy, haven't heard from you in a while.
sorry I've been out of touch.
But after the fire in my house...
how can I explain?
It was kind of a blessing.
Can you meet me?
Where are you?
A hotel in Pasadena.
I'm checking into a tournament.
a tournament?
Yeah, you know, chess.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Charley Dixon?
Agent Kester, FBI.
I need to ask you a few questions.
What is this about?
Sarah Connor.
Come in.
[SIGHS]
Are you really good at math?
Yes.
You wanna do mine?
We got a problem.
Andy Goode rebuilt his chess computer.
The Turk.
But you napalmed it.
Apparently he spent every minute
since then in a coffee shop in van nuys
rewriting the code from memory.
A good code is like a
good song in your head.
It's gotta come out.
Yeah, well, the song might
just blow up the world.
You should have killed him
when you had the chance.
And I'm surprised it's taken
you this long to bring that up.
I'm busy doing john's homework.
Andy entered it into a tournament.
Computer versus human?
Computer versus computer.
It's the new thing.
These programs are too smart and
powerful to play people anymore.
It gets better the
more we talk about it.
You're going to school.
You and tin miss can
meet me there later.
Mom, it's chess;
you don't know anything.
I know a bit about Andy.
Besides, you can't be absent.
Absent gets you on the radar.
Okay, I get it.
You go.
Can I have some money for lunch?
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
isn't this awesome?
God, I love robots.
Come here.
so is this one better or worse?
Well, it's different, really.
More adaptable, but less predictable.
Not as powerful for
now, but quicker on its feet.
It has a hunger for learning, but
sometimes the lessons it learns...
sounds more human.
Well, if you want an analogy, I'd say that
Turk i had grown into a brooding teenager,
and Turk ii is still more
of a precocious child.
Ah, speaking of brooding and precocious, this
is my partner, Dmitri Shipkov.
taught it to play chess.
She'll never sleep with you. Da, poka.
- You should plug that in.
- Yep.
Don't listen to him.
He's... he's just worked up
about the military contract.
We have a deal to split the money.
What military contract?
Well, the one the winner gets.
Why don't you people
get your story straight?
Is she dead or isn't she?
Sarah Connor survived the
explosion in the bank vault.
And so did her son.
Yeah, that was eight years ago.
You guys just figured that out?
[CELL PHONE VIBRATED]
Yes.
Yes?
Yes, what?
Yes, we just figured that out.
WOMAN:  babe, who was that at the door?
Good morning, ma'am.
He's from the FBI.
I'm asking a few questions.
- Charley, is something wrong?
- No.
I'm looking for the Connors.
Sarah Connor?
Your ex?
- I'm looking for them here.
- Here?
Mr. Dixon wanted to marry
Sarah Connor before you.
She's alive.
Maybe he's hiding her here.
What?
I already told you, no.
No, okay?
Look, all due (INDISTINCT)
the woman that i knew, Sarah Reese,
she blew herself up in
a bank eight years ago.
I never knew, and I do
not know Sarah Connor.
If you see or hear anything, call me.
Any time, I never sleep.
Just a reminder, grief counselling will be
available in my office throughout the week.
What are they doing?
They're writing notes.
For Jordan.
She's dead.
Yeah, I remember watching her fall.
Me too.
How will she get the notes?
She wonít.
But you
said...
sometimes things happen
and they're so bad,
people just don't know how
to deal with their sadness.
So they write it in a note.
But I thought people
cried when they were sad.
Sometimes it's not enough.
Are you gonna...
I didn't really know her.
I didn't either.
I like the note part.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[SPANISH CHATTERING]
Nice accent, white boy.
I have no idea what's with those guys.
They're always mess with me.
Yeah, man, I've no idea.
- I'm Morris.
- John.
Hey, uh, I saw you talking to
Cheryl Weston this morning.
Maybe no one told you cause
you're new but she's damaged goods.
She's my chem. partner.
Do you know her or something?
No one knows her.
Something crazy went on at the last school
she was in, but no one knows what it is.
Her dad's got her locked down tight.
[INDISTINCT]
It's truth.
Not much of it.
I'm just looking out for you, bro.
Yeah, you and everyone else.
[VOICE]
An extremely close match
between the American
and Japanese
computers here in the finals.
The Americans, led by programmer Andrew
Goode, have a slight positional advantage.
The Japanese seize control of
the center with bishop to c5.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[BARKING]
Do you know how many
grand masters are here?
How's Andy doing?
Well, that depends on what
your plans are for Andy.
On the one hand, he's in the
final round, on the other hand...
the winner gets a military contract.
Military?
Are you serious?
What do we do?
Cheer very hard for the Japanese
or Cameron will kill him.
[VOICE]
an unorthodox move by the Japanese,
leaving their queen
hanging on d6 square.
The American computer
calculating a response.
What just happened?
That bishop on c5 totally hammered him.
Black's in total zugswang.
Translation?
The Japanese just lost the queen.
They're in big trouble.
Andy's gonna win.
WOMAN: So that was quite
a speech earlier.
With the agent.
That wasn't a speech, it's was just...
just what it was.
What it was, was a lie.
What?
A lie.
You have a tell.
a what? A tell?
Yeah, a tell.
When you lie.
Do you know why you love me, charley?
I'm gonna tell you why you love me.
It's cause I'm not that girl.
I'm not that jealous girl.
I'm not that insecure girl.
I'm not that petty girl.
Of course not.
Yeah, so just don't make me
into that girl by lying to me.
If that woman is alive, if
you've seen her...
this is important.
I saw john.
What? Where?
Here. In our house.
In our house?
In our house? What did he want?
I don't know.
I think he just wanted to see me.
What are you gonna do about it?
I don't know.
They're fugitives, Charlie.
They're dangerous people.
Sarah's not dangerous.
Oh well, maybe not the Sarah you knew.
Sarah Reese, but Sarah
Connor killed a man.
We don't know that.
Well, what do we know?
What do you know?
[VOICE]
The Japanese desperately hoping for counter
play after the disastrous
loss of their queen.
Victory appears imminent
for the Americans.
Andy Goodeís Turk seized control
of the match in the middle game,
and now appears just
moves away from winning.
Rook to c2.
Checkmate. A shocking turn of events.
The Japanese team has
won the tournament.
It's over.
Andy lost.
But the other team...
they didn't lose their
queen, they sacrificed it.
Just like Byrne Fischer all over again.
Byrne-Fischer, 1956?
Never mind. The point is...
the Turk fell for a trap?
It's like it just... choked.
So now, what?
We go after them now?
No, their names weren't
in the safe house.
Andy's was.
- What computational error?
you put the bishop on e6 to begin with!
- You asked me to teach it chess... I taught it chess.
I can't help it if it's stupid!
Nobody's gonna want Andyís program now.
That thing's kind of crazy.
He could still be a threat.
It could still become skynet.
It could also become pong.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll just sit Andy
down and tell him everything.
Andy.
Who are you?
[SIREN WAILING]
Put your hands above your head!
Do it now!
Turn! Turn!
Spread 'em!
Put your hands behind your back.
Over here.
I'm so sorry, Andy.
What's this?
You should write Andy
a note if you can't cry.
Doesn't bother you
that he's dead, does it?
The world is safer without him.
JOHN: That was way too easy.
L.A.P.D. Firewalls really blow.
Show me what you found.
Okay.
No name, but he's got
this tattoo on his arm.
He's one of them.
That's a tattoo from a skynet work camp.
He's a resistance fighter.
From the future. Like the
three guys in the safe house?
He was the fourth.
Then you know him.
- In the future.
- So do you.
He's one of your best soldiers.
They've been watching Andy Goode.
Doing surveillance.
Same as us.
Well, not exactly the same.
He actually killed the guy.
That was not his mission.
You sent him here to wait for us.
Well, then I guess he changed his mind.
A lot.
I have to talk to him.
Talk to him? How?
He's in lockdown.
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[GRUNTS]
Freeze.
What are you doing?
Math.
I already did your homework.
Yeah, I know, but I still
have to take the test.
I need to know this stuff.
Then why did you ask me to do it?
Because maybe it's kind of hard to concentrate
on geometry when people keep dying around you.
You have no idea what
I'm talking about, do you?
You're grieving.
Grieving?
How do you know what grieving is?
I read all the notes.
Cameron Baum, Mr.
Harris wants to see you.
I know this is difficult
for you to talk about,
so I'm gonna need you to be strong.
Okay? Can you do that for me?
Yes. I can be strong.
People say you were the last person
to speak with Jordan before she...
died.
Is that true?
I don't know.
Are you asking me if people say I
was the last person to talk to Jordan,
or are you asking me if I was
the last one to talk to her?
I guess I'm asking if you were.
I don't know.
What did she say when
you did talk to her?
I mean, was it something
upsetting for you to hear?
She said, ìyou saw
it, right? Right? You saw it?
It's so freakin' big
and right out there."
She was talking about the graffiti?
It's freakin' big.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
- And no.
- No?
No, it wasn't upsetting
for me to hear it.
Did Jordan mention any names?
Any specific people
that she was upset with?
Her parents.
Anyone else?
The hall monitors.
You ask that question a lot.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
I don't think I told you anything.
Oh, okay.
Can I go now?
I'm done with grief
counselling, and I feel much better.
Yeah, please. Go.
Yo, john doe, you got a visitor.
Those hurt?
Sometimes they crank those tight
before they bring you in here.
That way, you might ask
me to loosen them up.
And I am able to
accommodate you in that.
It's a trick they do.
It gives us a connection.
But we already got a connection.
Your prints are everywhere.
Oven, light switch, toilet. Safe.
Wasn't us who found it.
But somebody did.
After the police thought
they cleared the scene,
somebody came back and
emptied the safe right quick.
Didn't force it either.
They knew the combination.
So we've got you running from the
scene of Andrew Goodeís murder.
And we've got you living
at, and disappearing from,
and most likely returning to
the scene of these three murders.
All of which would be
a prosecutorial bounty.
But I've also got forensic evidence,
linking this to this
Feeling connected yet?
What is it?
The forensic evidence linking
all these people... what is it?
Blood.
Not my blood.
No, not your blood.
And, technically, not even blood.
Some kind of synthetic.
Come on, man, help me out.
Tell me something I don't know.
We're all gonna die.
Yeah, I want him out
of local custody today.
He has more to say and I want him
on federal turf when he says it.
yes, this is Cameronís mother.
ms. Baum, you're aware of the recent
tragedy we've had here at school?
- Jordan somebody.
- Tallen.
When I spoke to Cameron about
it, she seemed strangely unaffected.
I'm sure you're doing
all you can as a parent.
It's been overwhelming for all of
us, first with the tornado, then the move.
Tornado?
I'm sorry, she didn't (INDISTINCT)
that might explain what I think might
be classic post-traumatic stress.
You're gonna have to speak up.
[CELL PHONE BLEEP]
You shouldn't be here.
I know who you are.
And I know who you are.
Who else but Sarah Connor would have
burned down that poor kid's house?
It was you, wasn't it?
On Andyís porch that
night. You've been watching.
You wanted to kill him, the
poor kid, and you did.
I didn't do it.
All I wanted was the Turk.
Somebody else killed
him and took the machine.
What?
He was dead when I got there.
He was dead and the Turk was
gone, and I hoped you'd done it.
You thought I killed him?
But you're here.
And the Turk is out there.
So we both failed.
You gotta get out of here.
If you haven't figured it
out, I have a t-888 on my ass.
Now if you found me, it will too.
- We should get you out.
- Go.
Find the partner, the Russian.
He's gotta be neck-deep in this also.
- You're dead in here.
- Go!
Please.
I won't be the bastard who brings
metal down on the Connors, so just go.
You're... you're prettier
than your picture.
Picture?
Yeah, it's actually how I clocked you.
My brother carried your snap for luck.
Who's your brother?
What does it matter?
You don't know the Reese
boys, and you never will.
Reese boys?
Derek Reese.
Brother's Kyle.
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
when john sent Kyle Reese back to protect me,
we had two days together.
He told me about the
future, about the apocalypse,
and the terror of a
world run by machines.
Kyle Reese saved my life.
He gave me a son.
He never told me that he had a brother.
He never told me we would have family.
That in our grief we are not alone.
Cheri.
Walk away.
John, please.
Lock and key, bro. Lock and k
mom's here.
I'm Morris.
Your brother's new best friend.
Cameron.
Nice grip.
Watch yourself.
Just lookin' out for ya.
Field trip.
I call shotgun.
I call 9-millimeter.
What's the E.T.A. On my prisoner?
All right.
[SIGHS]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[GRUNTS]
- Drop it. Now.
- Easy. Easy.
Run.
You stay close.
Take the jeep and follow us.
You metal bitch.
She's on our side.
(INDISTINCT) Lose him.
Let's go.
- Where's Cameron?
- Leave her, let's go.
Let's go.
Stay back
Get down
[GROANS]
Bring me the toolbox.
Switchblade.
Pliers.
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
Do something. We have to help him.
Don't let that thing touch me.
- We have to stop your bleeding.
- Get away from me.
Please don't move.
You're increasing your blood loss.
I can't fix it.
You took a bullet out of me.
He has internal damage.
He needs medical
attention, or he's gonna die.
A stun gun.
Are you nuts?
He needs a doctor.
What, so you're just gonna
go out and kidnap one?
There's an E.R. A mile away.
It's almost dark.
Mom, this is crazy, all right.
Even for you, it's insane.
And what happens when
you get caught? Then what?
I said we have to save him.
You don't even know who this guy is.
He's your uncle.
He doesn't know.
He's your father's brother.
His name's Derek Reese.
John.
Two females, approximately
5'6",120 pounds,
overpower you and your partner,
ambush your secure
vehicle, and kidnap my prisoner.
That an accurate summation of what
happened out here today, officer?
Yeah.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
5'6".
[SARAH'S NARRATOR]
If there is a flaw in chess
as a game of war, it is this:
Unlike war, the rules
of chess are constant.
The pieces unchangeable.
You will never win the heart of
a rook or the mind of a knight.
They are deaf to your arguments.
And so be it.
The goal of a chess game
is total annihilation.
But, in war, even as the blood beats in
your ears and you race after your enemy,
will stop you before you reach your target.
In war, unlike chess, rules
can be changed.
Truces can be called.
The greatest of enemies can
become the best of friends.
Derek.
He's not breathing.
Reese! Reese!
[SARAH]
In war, there is hope.
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync/Edit: ﬂ«»‚»‚ & Shocker