SARAH: In the future, my son will
lead mankind in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
NARRATOR: Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
My Turk plays chess at a level
that could defeat every human player...
...that has ever lived,
and probably ever will live.
This is my partner, Dmitri Shipkov.
I built the Turk, but Dmitri
taught it to play chess.
SARAH: You talk about it like it's human.
ANDY: Well, you never know.
Show me what you found.
JOHN: No name, but he's got
this tattoo on his arm.
That's a tattoo from a Skynet work camp.
He's a Resistance fighter.
Then you know him,
in the future.
CAMERON: So do you.
He's one of your best soldiers.
It was you, wasn't it?
You wanted to kill him, and you did.
I didn't do it.
All I wanted was the Turk.
Somebody else killed him
and took the machine.
You gotta get out of here.
If you haven't figured it out,
I have a T-Triple-8 on my ass.
Now if you found me,
it will too.
[GUNSHOT]
SARAH: He needs a doctor.
JOHN: What, so you're just gonna go out
and kidnap one?
Ugh, don't let that thing
touch me.
- We have to stop your bleeding.
- Get away from me!
- You don't even know who this guy is!
- He's your uncle. He doesn't know.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
WOMAN 1 [OVER RADIO]:
Possible forced entry and sabotage...
...at Vista Terrace power plant.
All available units respond.
Code 3.
WOMAN 2 [OVER SPEAKERS]:
This is an emergency evacuation.
Proceed to emergency exits.
MAN 1 [OVER SPEAKER]: Remain calm
and exit the building immediately.
MAN 2: Let's go.
MAN 1: This is an emergency evacuation.
Proceed to the emergency-lighted exit.
SARAH [IN VOICE-OVER]: They say that
when a person dies, the soul lives on.
The soul.
The thing that separates us
from the machines.
Cameron had burned the metal monster.
Two thousand degrees.
I suppose they did the same to Andy.
There was nothing left of either.
Nothing that told the story
of who or what they were.
Gone is gone.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
When I go, bury me in the earth.
Part of me died years ago
with Kyle Reese.
But a part of him lives on in John.
If that's not a soul,
I don't know what is.
[DEREK GASPS]
- The Triple-8?
- Vaporized.
The Russian, Dmitri?
- You found him?
- He took off after Andy's murder.
Now, if he has the Turk, then...
Put the machine on it.
She'll find him.
- It's...
- I know.
It's what they do.
- How is he?
- Better.
Still pretty out of it.
Is he gonna stay here? Or what?
[DOOR CLOSES]
SARAH:
Let's see if he lives first.
And somewhere in this city,
a naked cop bleeds in an alley.
The hand.
Couldn't acquire it.
- Why not?
- The FBI has it.
SARAH:
You're playing hooky.
Today? No, I can't
miss class today, Mom.
We have to find the hand.
Destroy it. No loose ends.
Cyberdyne built Skynet.
- With the chip, remember?
- And the hand.
Look, the feds have it now, Mom.
I can't help.
Besides, absent gets me on the radar.
I can play hooky.
Find Dmitri. Derek says he has a sister,
teaches ballet. Start with her.
Low profile, no guns.
You might wanna change.
Yeah, this is Sergeant Johnson,
Senior Property over at L.A.P.D.
Got a problem,
wonder if you could help.
- What's going on?
- We got this new booking officer, rookie.
I think he was drunk when
he logged evidence on a robbery we had.
Might have ended up
on your felony escape.
- What are you missing?
- Prosthetic hand.
- Really?
- Really.
DR number?
084476732.
I can send someone to pick it up.
- Mm. I don't see any hand on here.
- You sure?
Item 17.
Hey, hang on a second. Agent Ellison.
ELLISON: Yeah?
MAN:
I got L.A.P.D. Property on the line.
Asking about a hand.
From your felony escape.
They have it listed on the authorization
but we don't have a record of it.
I never saw any hand,
fake or otherwise.
Agent in charge says he never saw it.
Wanna talk to him?
No. No, no, I'll take his word. Thanks.
[SARAH GRUNTING ON VIDEO]
I wonder if God or the devil...
...or even death was sending me
a message from the future...
...all the way back through time.
"Machines, Sarah, machines.
You can pretend they're not, but they are
coming and they are faster and stronger.
And they have been built
to do one perfect thing:
To kill you.
They will kill you...
...and your friends and your family
and your mother and your father...
...and Kyle Reese and your son.
Your son."
"They will kill everyone you love
and everyone you hold close...
...and there is nothing you can do
about it...
...because they are coming.
They are coming
and they will find you.
Because that's what they do!
That's all they do!"
- That's all they do!
- I need help here!
Let go.
Get in here!
SARAH: They'll kill you!
MAN 1: Come on, where's that stuff?
- They will kill you!
Let me...
MAN 2: Now, if what you're saying
is true, Sarah...
...surely there would be
some evidence.
SARAH:
No one believes me.
Thank you.
This is where Sarah Connor
spent three years of her life?
DOCTOR:
This is it.
Dr. Silberman retired
right after she escaped.
Where is he these days?
Got himself a cabin in the mountains
near Arrowhead.
Growing his own vegetables
and working on his book.
We don't hear much
from him anymore.
I'd love to talk to any staff
that was here when she escaped.
Unfortunately, there's no one left.
Not even the janitor?
How long would you work here
if you could find another job?
All right.
MARIA:
Good.
Go on, reach down.
Excellent turn out. Hold.
Hold.
And close.
Beautiful.
Thank you. See you all next week.
WOMAN:
Bye, Neil.
What is she doing?
Pas de chat.
Step of the cat.
- Will you show me?
- That is the advanced class.
You are a beginner, yeah?
You have taken ballet before.
No.
The height is nice.
Beautiful feet.
But your upper body is little...
...mechanical, yeah?
Remember, you are a cat.
I'm a cat.
Come next week.
We need to develop your flexibility
and your imagination.
Remember, dance is the hidden language
of the soul, yeah?
[IN RUSSIAN]
MAN:
MARIA:
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
Looks like you're loading guns
that I know for a fact are already loaded.
True enough.
I loaded them.
DEREK:
Look...
...no offense, I just don't like firing
a weapon I didn't set myself.
Anyway, you should take it
into the kitchen or something.
Mom wouldn't like you doing this
in her room.
Why?
Because it's her room.
Listen, um...
...the paramedic that patched me up,
where'd he come from?
That's Charlie.
He was her boyfriend.
Her fiancé...
...actually. Long time ago though.
DEREK:
He's a liability.
Look, man,
he's not gonna tell anybody.
How do you know?
Because I know him. I trust him.
I can't believe you trust anybody.
Maybe it's just him.
You trust the machine.
- Cameron, she...
- Yeah, Cameron.
What a joke. Walking around
with a name like it's a person.
It's not a person. It's not something
you should be trusting.
SARAH:
What's going on?
Nothing.
I need you to get on the computer
and find an address.
You're making a mistake.
- How's that?
- The machine has gotta go.
You had me sending her out
to do our dirty work.
Dirty work is all they're good for.
Don't think
that you can train them like a pet.
It'll be the last thing you think.
- John...
- John doesn't know everything.
- You should be resting.
- No.
They never rest.
DEREK:
You can't have that thing here.
Can't sleep with it here.
That gonna help?
You never know.
Does it help to sleep
on the whole trunk?
Go into my bedroom again,
I'll bust your head.
SARAH:
What happened with the ballet teacher?
Dance is the language of the soul.
First, you have to have a soul.
I mean, about Dmitri or the Turk.
I'm going back today.
What's the status on the hand?
SARAH: Got a good idea who has it.
DEREK: Who?
- FBI Agent Ellison.
The guy who questioned me
in county lockup?
What, they only have one FBI agent
in this town?
SARAH: The only one
who could put this whole thing together.
From what I saw at his house,
maybe he already has.
Pancakes.
We eat at the table.
Your pancakes are getting cold.
JOHN: Here's Dr. Silberman's address.
SARAH: You're not hungry?
JOHN: No.
Since when?
MAN [ON VIDEO]:
Miss Connor, I'm from DCFS.
I've brought some paperwork.
Everything should be in order.
All we have to do
is cross the T's and dot the I's.
It states that you voluntarily
and unequivocally consent.
You've been advised of
the consequences of this relinquishment.
You understand that your consent
is irrevocable.
And once these papers are signed,
all parental rights will be terminated.
And sign here.
We'll get a certified copy to the judge.
I guess you're not hungry either.
You might have fooled them,
but not me.
I know you.
I know you too.
ELLISON:
Dr. Silberman.
Can I help you?
Special Agent James Ellison.
Well, hello.
What can I do for you, agent?
I'd like to talk to you
about Sarah Connor.
You like to come in?
Thank you.
I don't like to use the term "textbook"
in relation to any of my patients...
...but Sarah Connor was depressed,
anxiety-ridden...
...manic...
...violent with paranoid delusions.
Is that what it was? Delusions?
Robots, soldiers of the future,
apocalypse. You tell me.
Also, she could be
remarkably charming...
...and even persuasive.
Beware of false prophets.
Are you a man of the Book?
It has brought me comfort at times.
More tea?
Yes, yes, thank you.
SILBERMAN: Thing that most people
don't understand about psychiatry...
...is that it is an imperfect science.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO]
What are you doing here?
Watching you.
I'm a little out of shape.
Teaching takes all my time.
My brother says if you wanna be good at
anything, you have to practice every day.
Your brother is right.
Do you have a brother?
Yes.
Is he a dancer like you?
He plays chess.
So does my brother.
Excuse me.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Get lost.
[GRUNTING]
[IN ENGLISH]
Do you have any idea who this is?
No, do you?
Who are you?
You are just a girl.
How did you do that?
I'm looking for your brother.
Are you police?
I've already told the police
everything I know.
No, I'm not police.
But I do find them useful.
What do you want?
I can help your brother.
Tell me where he is.
Untie me.
FBI, that's a good touch.
What? Who...?
Who do you...?
Who do you think I am?
I know who you are...
...coming here
asking about Sarah Connor.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Matthew 7:15, the full verse is:
Beware of false prophets
which come to you in sheep's clothing...
...but inwardly,
they are ravening wolves.
You're from the future.
- You're one of them.
- I'm...? I'm...? Oh, come on.
Okay, if I was who you say I am,
then how could...?
How could you have poisoned me?
The tea was a test...
...but then it occurred to me
that you could be an advanced model.
Smart enough to trick me
into thinking you were passed out.
Oh, come on. Come on. Look.
Look, kidnapping an FBI agent
is a federal offense.
Carries a sentence of life in prison.
If you let me go now,
we'll forget this ever happened, okay?
- One sure-fire way to...
- Wait. Wait, wait. No!
No! You can't. No! No!
[SCREAMING]
[DOORKNOB CLICKING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
John hasn't been answering
his cell phone.
When he gets home,
will you tell him we need to talk?
Where you heading?
Arrowhead. I think Ellison
might be there.
He's a strong boy.
You know, strong opinions.
- I don't know where he gets that.
- His father?
Out of the picture.
That's too bad.
Can I ask you about my brother?
Kyle?
John told me he died fighting?
Do you know where he is now?
In the grass.
I can take you there someday
if you want.
SILBERMAN:
It's an honest mistake.
Can't be too careful.
Tell me...
...do you believe
in the apocalypse, agent?
Yeah.
I've read Revelations.
Could it be that the apocalypse
in the Book...
...and the predictions of Sarah Connor
are one and the same?
Um...
I suppose it's possible.
What do you think?
He came down the hall.
It was a large man.
I thought it was a man...
...until he threw the guard...
...through the window
just like a rag doll.
Not an ounce of emotion,
just blank like a death mask.
Then the other one came.
There was two of them?
They were different.
The second one was
almost beautiful, like, perfect...
...like a changeling.
The face of mercury.
What about Sarah?
She was there.
She was on the floor...
...and the boy was with her.
He was screaming.
And then the first one, the big one...
...I'll never forget,
he reached out his hand and he said:
"Come with me if you wanna live."
It was like God reaching out to man...
...like the Sistine Chapel.
The hand of God.
Hand of God.
Yeah.
Though...
...there's no proof,
so we don't talk about it...
...all of us who were there.
What if I told you I have proof?
What do you mean?
Piece of evidence I found
during my investigation.
That's why I came to you.
For your cooperation.
To show you that Sarah wasn't crazy.
Nobody...
...is crazy.
What is it?
The hand of God.
SILBERMAN: It's a good thing
you told me about this.
Yeah.
I told you, I'm on your side.
I wish that were true.
What does that mean?
Do you know what would happen
if the wrong people got a hold of this?
I can't let you stop her.
She's dead.
Well, so was Jesus once.
- You won't feel a thing.
- What? No, no!
Dug up some clean T-shirts for you.
Thanks.
I wasn't sure how many you'd need.
Depends on how long you're staying.
Not that great sleeping on the couch,
is it?
Slept on a few of them myself.
Yeah? When was that?
When my mom was locked up.
I kicked around.
Friends and foster families.
Mom was in prison?
Mental hospital.
You go around blowing up buildings
and ranting about robots, it happens.
That sounds rough.
There was this...
There was this one family,
Todd and Janelle.
I was with them for a while...
...and they were okay.
Of course, I hated them.
They wanted to adopt me.
I'm sure your mom would have died
before she let that happen.
Yeah, you'd think.
Look, John...
...what can happen
to a person inside four walls...
...screws with your head.
Makes you do things
you never thought you'd do.
Some people never give up.
Some people always fight.
Fewer than you'd think.
So you ever wonder what happened
to Todd and Janelle?
No.
I know what happened.
I got them killed.
Dima.
[BOTH IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
Tell him, come on.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH] You're the one who
reported the Turk missing.
DMITRI [IN ENGLISH]: Do you have more?
- What happened to it?
A man came to see me.
Offered me money to steal the Turk.
I owed money to the people who helped
me bring my sister into this country...
...so I changed the endgame protocols
in order for it to lose its last match.
If we'd won and we would have won,
I never could have gotten it out of there.
I was paid money for it, $20,000.
It wasn't enough.
I need more of these.
Please, I need more of these.
Who bought the Turk?
Okay.
That's all I have.
Okay?
Dima.
Thank you for explaining.
Where are you going?
Hey, where do you go?
MARIA: You promised you'd help us!
DMITRI: Hey. This way.
[DMITRI SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
IN RUSSIAN]
DMITRI:
Hey!
[MARIA AND DMITRI SCREAM]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MARIA SCREAMS]
[LIQUID SPLATTERING]
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
Apology accepted.
[YELLS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
ELLISON:
Help!
Get up.
Where is it?
She took it.
What? Who?
Sarah Connor.
She took it.
[LAUGHING]
Did you find the Turk?
Dmitri stole it from Andy
then sold it to a man.
Who?
Where's Dmitri now?
Dead. So's his sister.
Did you kill them?
No. It wasn't my mission.
I never wanted you to see that tape.
I was gonna destroy it.
But since you did,
did you notice the date?
The date on the tape?
June 8, 1997.
Do you know that date?
I do now.
It's the date you gave up
being my mother.
It's the date I broke out of there.
The day you came for me
I was coming for you.
Because about three seconds
after I signed that paper...
...I knew I couldn't live with it.
I was coming for you
and I was gonna die trying.
You almost did.
So did you.
And you were mad as hell about it.
Yelled at me...
...and told me
what a stupid move it was.
I might have oversold that a little.
I'll always find you.
SARAH: There was a time
I was a hero to my son.
He thought I walked on water.
He knows better now.
We all have weak moments...
...moments where we lose faith.
But it's our flaws...
...our weaknesses
that make us human.
They're here.
They're here!
They're everywhere!
Science now performs miracles
like the gods of old.
Creating life from blood cells or bacteria
or a spark of metal.
But they're perfect creatures...
...and in that way,
they couldn't be less human.
There are things machines
will never do.
They cannot possess faith,
they cannot commune with God.
Every tree that bringeth
not forth good fruit is hewn down...
...and cast into the fire.
They cannot appreciate beauty.
They cannot create art.
[PIANO MUSIC PLAYING
ON STEREO]
If they ever learn these things,
they won't have to destroy us.
They'll be us.