SARAH: In the future, my son will
lead mankind in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system
programmed to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time.
Some to kill him, one to protect him.
Today, we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
NARRATOR: Previously on Terminator:
the Sarah Connor Chronicles:
ELLISON: Your fiancée, Sarah Connor,
killed a man because she believes...
...that in the future he'll invent a computer
system that declares war on the world.
SARAH:
Andy Goode rebuilt his chess computer.
The Turk.
DEREK: Somebody killed him
and took the machine.
JOHN: No name,
but he's got this on his arm.
CAMERON: That's a tattoo
from a Skynet work camp.
He's a Resistance fighter.
- I know who you are.
- And I know who you are. Sarah Connor.
SARAH: These things, all of them are
programmed with specific missions.
[POWERS DOWN]
SARAH: We have to save him.
- You don't even know who this guy is!
He's your uncle.
He doesn't know.
John!
He needs medical
attention or he's gonna die.
John?
Is it really you?
SARAH:
He's not breathing.
On the night we first met,
John's father, Kyle Reese...
...told me words
I remember to this day.
He meant them as a warning.
I think of them as words to live by.
He told me of an apocalypse
yet to come.
Like a Pandora's box,
he unpacked every horror, every evil.
Every dark thing
that haunts our future.
He also left me an unborn son...
...to whom he bequeathed
what remained in the box...
...after the nightmares fled:
Hope.
[DEREK WHEEZING]
CHARLIE: Bullet nicked his left lung.
I got a fragment lodged in the tissue.
I can get it out, but will someone
tell me what was going on here?
She's a machine.
- She's a liar. She's a liar. She's a liar.
- Sedative, my bag.
DEREK: Everything she says is a lie.
Don't listen to her.
Don't, don't. Don't!
CHARLIE:
You heard him.
DEREK:
You get that bitch away from me! No!
- No. No. Get that bitch away from me.
- You heard him.
Get away from me! No!
CHARLIE: You want him to die?
- If I wanted him to die...
SARAH:
Cameron.
JOHN:
Mom, come on, what can I do?
I need the manual aspirator
to drain the lung, okay?
- You know what it looks like? Go get it.
- Yeah, I remember.
Oh, my God. Gunshots, punctures,
burns, some broken bones.
Second-rate medical treatment
if anything at all. Sarah, what...?
I need some more light.
Come on.
Just stay with me, okay?
You're an idiot, right?
It's an old wives' tale, a trick.
It doesn't work. It's all in your mind.
It works.
I don't do it,
I haven't been sick for years.
DEREK: It's because your guts are metal,
like your head.
If you were a little smarter,
you'd be a tin can.
I'm just saying
you're wasting your time.
Again.
- When I was in Century...
- Hey, Wisher, did you hear?
Brother Kyle was in
Century Work Camp.
- No, really?
- Go to hell.
Did he escape? Was he a hero?
He led John
through a slaughterhouse...
- ...without taking a pinprick.
- I heard it was two slaughterhouses...
...and that he carried Connor.
It was one slaughterhouse.
Many Connors.
Right, right.
[DEREK LAUGHS]
[RUMBLING]
Centaur patrol.
- What?
- I hate that thing.
- It's just a picture.
- It's Connor's mother.
- I don't get why he'd give you that.
- She's my lucky charm.
That's what makes me nervous.
Derek, Kyle, Connor wants us topside.
Track where the Centaurs came from.
I think we lost the trail, boys.
Let's give it a few more blocks,
north-northeast.
If I was a cyborg tank,
I think I'd come north-northeast.
I smell jet fuel.
Last time we found a tank factory
you smelled jet fuel.
Connor's looking for bigger fish
than factories.
Hear he's got squads out
looking for some Skynet secret weapon.
Don't they have enough weapons?
Why do they need a secret one?
What about it, Kyle?
Connor say anything to you?
No. Not a word.
[METAL SCRAPING GRAVEL]
What the hell was that?
Kyle.
HK!
Kyle!
CHARLIE:
There we go.
Eight years.
That's how long I've been in L.A.
Eight years
since my fiancée ran out on me.
Eight years since the FBI informed me
she was a homicidal...
...paranoid schizophrenic with an acute
dislike for anything mechanical.
For what it's worth,
I didn't believe them.
Then you blew yourself up.
You look nervous.
Would you like a sedative?
- There are sedatives in Charlie's bag.
- I don't want a sedative.
Do you know who that is,
who's dying on that table?
Yes, that man is First Lieutenant Derek
Thomas Reese with the 132nd SOC.
- Operational Specialty Tech-Com.
- No, I mean on a personal level.
Do you understand who he is?
Records indicate only blood relation
is his brother, Kyle Reese.
And what information
do you have about Kyle Reese?
Imprisoned at Century Sector Work Camp
with John Connor, 2015.
Escaped with John Connor, 2021.
He was officially declared
MIA in 2027...
...after being assigned to protect
Sarah Connor from a Skynet attack.
- Is that all?
- It seems like a lot.
It is.
It was all over the news.
Three days later, I packed a bag...
...hop on the bike,
drove to L.A. straight through.
I had to know.
I had to see it with my own eyes.
But I got here,
and there was nothing there.
Just a hole in the ground
where the bank used to be.
I couldn't go home.
How could I?
I didn't wanna leave you.
I didn't have a choice.
Gun to your head?
More like in my head. It's...
- It's complicated.
- Then uncomplicate it for me.
Kyle.
[CLEARS THROAT]
DEREK:
Hey.
Hey, you mind?
The water.
What's going on? Is he dead?
Hey.
Hey, buddy. You all right?
CHARLIE:
So...
Skynet.
Robots.
From the future.
- And you're a...?
- Yes.
- I'm a...
- You need a...?
- A minute?
- I was gonna say a drink.
Oh, yeah, that too.
Don't you have an endoskeleton
you need to disappear or something?
Yes, I've already prepared the thermite.
CHARLIE: Thermite?
CAMERON: It's an incendiary chemical.
It burns at 2500 degrees Celsius.
Hot enough
to liquefy this endoskeleton.
I know what thermite is, I'm just...
I'm still working my way around
endoskeleton.
SARAH:
There's beers in the fridge.
JOHN:
I looked for a lime. Sorry.
Are you mad at me
for getting you mixed up in all this?
Uh...
No.
I...
I just... I get... I'm...
I guess I wish I would have known
back then.
I wish you could have trusted me.
I did.
[GRUNTING]
[DEVICE HUMS]
[GROANING]
Kyle.
How long you been here?
I don't know.
I think I just got here.
No, you were here when I got here.
Timms.
- What's your name?
- Reese.
There was a Reese who busted out
of Century Work Camp.
With John Connor, a while back.
Mad dogs, could lead a pack, I heard.
Yeah, that wasn't... That wasn't me.
That's too bad.
What are they doing, Reese?
Is there a secret weapon?
Was Connor right?
DEREK:
I don't know.
We go where we're told,
we do what we're told.
Maybe Connor's wrong.
Maybe he's crazy.
You hearing music?
[PIANO PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
I swear I hear music, real music.
There's a room in the basement.
What happens there?
Maybe your friend will tell us.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
We should get the hell out of here.
Did you do something to him,
in the future?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
When they reprogram us,
they scrub our memories.
It increases the chance of success.
Success.
Of the reprogramming.
His lungs are hemorrhaging.
He's drowning in his own blood.
Charlie.
CHARLIE:
I stopped the bleeding.
I drained his lungs.
But your guy lost blood.
He needs a transfusion.
Sarah's O-negative,
the universal donor.
It doesn't matter. He needs three units
of his own type, AB-negative.
Bad news is, only one half of 1 percent
of the population are potential donors.
We don't find one,
you're gonna have a serious problem.
Then we take him to a hospital.
Drop him off anonymously.
He's wanted for Andy Goode's murder,
and escaping federal custody.
We should let him die.
Test my blood.
Test me.
You heard the odds, John,
200 in one.
Please, just test me.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Wisher.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Billy.
SARAH: It's not like donating to
the Red Cross, he needs a lot of blood.
- So I don't get a cookie and a sticker.
- I'm serious.
Look, I don't see anyone else lining up.
You took a hell of a chance
bringing Charlie.
Save me the speech, all right? I know.
You took a hell of a chance,
and it worked out.
Was that what he looked like?
Did they look alike?
A little bit, yeah.
Same build, same complexion.
Not the eyes, though.
Even when your father was screaming
about the machines...
...he had such kind eyes.
- We have to tell him.
- We don't, and we can't.
- He's family.
- He's a stranger.
- I sent him back here, I must trust him.
- Not enough to tell him about Kyle.
You didn't trust anyone enough
to tell them about your father. Anyone.
- Can I confess to you?
- I'm not a priest.
Far from it.
I'm a liar.
- And the devil.
- No, Billy.
And my name's not Billy.
It's not Wisher.
What?
My name's Andy.
Andy Goode.
All right, Andy.
I did this.
All of this, it's my fault.
What are you talking about?
I built Skynet.
You need to rest. You're very sick.
No. No.
I'm not sick.
I'm not sick. I did this, all of this.
I was part of a team.
A group, 10 of us.
Fifteen, I don't know.
We used names. We were liars.
I built computers.
I built a computer...
...a mind.
It became angry and scared.
And I couldn't reassure it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
[PIANO PLAYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
That's quite a kid you got in there.
You have no idea.
Same rare blood type.
And his name, Reese.
The same as yours when we met.
It all adds up.
He's not John's father.
- Not sure I'm ready to explain it.
- Let me guess, it's complicated?
Hey, you could have told me.
Would you have believed me?
DEREK: Kyle. Kyle.
JOHN: Charlie?
Mom.
DEREK: Where's Kyle? Where is he?
No, no.
JOHN: Mom.
Where's Kyle? Where's Kyle?
Where is he? Where is he?
Where'd you send him?
Okay, no. Mm-mm. No.
Get off of me!
Where is he?
Where did you send him?
Where? You owe me the truth!
Get this off. Get it off of me.
Get it off of me. Get it...
He's my blood.
He's my blood. He's my blood! He's...
I think they're gone.
What is this, a game?
DEREK:
Yeah.
It's always a game.
Reese, slow down.
Reese.
DEREK:
Oh, no.
No, God.
So who's Kyle?
He from the future too? Hm?
He come back before?
And he's John's father.
Yes.
They're brothers. He doesn't know.
- When you said John's father was dead...
- He is.
It was because of all of this?
Me.
We never had a chance.
ANDY:
Plasma burns.
Secondary explosions.
Skynet was here.
Maybe Connor and the others
fell back to the tunnel downtown.
Please, God.
[CLATTERING]
Stand down.
MAN:
Stand down, stand down.
- Reese. Derek Reese.
- Sumner.
I thought we lost you guys
to the junkyard.
You did.
What happened?
Skynet found it four nights ago.
We had a patrol out on the perimeter
before a Triple-8 snuck around us...
...and went straight for the hole.
Killed most, took some.
Rest easy. Connor and your brother
weren't here when it happened.
Where'd they go?
They found some Skynet complex
in Topanga Canyon...
...and decided to put all the firepower
we had into it.
Lost a lot of men.
- What was it?
- I don't know.
Some kind of research facility, factory,
something. No one would tell us.
Connor took a group,
including your brother, into the place.
Left the rest of us outside to guard.
Couple days later he came out,
ordered us to blow the place to hell.
So, what about Kyle?
What happened to my brother?
No one ever saw your brother again.
Take me to Connor now.
Hey, Sarah said I might be able to find
some more gauze out back in the...
Wow.
Hey, is that really necessary?
It's dead, right?
Or powered off, whatever.
Every component must be destroyed
beyond repair or recovery.
Even a single unaccounted-for piece
of the endoskeleton...
...could alter the course
of technological evolution...
...and hasten the arrival
of Judgment Day.
CHARLIE:
I'll... Yeah.
You know, little girl...
...you freak me the hell out.
On the outside,
you're just as pretty as a picture...
...but on the inside, you're a...
Hyperalloy combat chassis.
What...? Is that a complicated way
of saying "robot"?
Cybernetic organism.
Living tissue
over a metal endoskeleton.
Okay. Scary robot.
And here you are
carving up this guy...
...into chum.
He's not a guy. He's a scary robot.
Okay, he's a scary robot?
You? You're a very scary robot.
CAMERON:
You should go.
It's not safe for you here.
You're like a ghost come back.
And you're a Reese.
- Yeah, tell me about the other Reese.
- I told you, he's classified.
- We're family.
- We're all family.
Let me talk to Connor, he'll understand.
Kyle was his friend.
Connor doesn't have friends.
Heck, he doesn't talk to anyone.
- Fine. I'll find him myself.
- Reese.
Metal!
No!
- She's a machine. She's one of them.
- No, damn it. She's one of ours.
One of ours?
It's reprogrammed and just given
run of the place like pets?
This is Connor's show,
and that's what he wants.
Those machines kill.
They kill. It's all they do.
And now, they do it for us.
They helped us in Topanga.
- We'd never have done what we did.
- What did we do?
- Derek.
- What happened?
What happened up there?
What happened to my brother?
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
MAN: We got a red alert!
Get emergency response!
Go get her now!
Go, go!
Hey.
Do it. Do it.
Kill me now, you son of a...
Sometimes they go bad.
No one knows why.
What did you say to Charlie?
I freak him the hell out.
I'll bet you do. I'll just bet.
I know what you're thinking.
I may not know how you think,
but I know what you're thinking about.
What you're thinking about right now is
exactly what you should not think about.
I didn't leave Charlie
because he was a threat to me or John.
We're a threat to him.
Do you understand?
You were right to leave him.
You don't go near him.
You don't touch him.
Swear you'll leave him alone,
or so help me...
...I will find a way of taking you apart
piece by piece.
- I swear.
- So do I.
That thing's done, right? It's vapor?
One missing component.
His left hand. I'll find it.
Everything needs to be destroyed.
Everything.
- Everything.
- Every last bolt.
- Get it done.
- I swear.
CHARLIE: The best you can do for him
now is keep feeding him painkillers.
Restrict his movement.
No lifting, no running, no singing.
And absolutely no gunfights.
- Hey, if you need anything else...
- I won't.
Now, you see, that's not
what I was gonna say at all.
I know. I can't let you say it.
What can I say?
Goodbye.
What was that thing
that you always said?
"There is no fate but what we make."
Remember?
The more I think about it,
the more I realize...
...my fate was made before we met.
When John was born.
- Can't change it?
- Not trying to change mine.
- Trying to change his.
- Yeah, okay.
Wait, there's something else
I gotta tell you.
This is something
you really need to know.
I didn't tell him anything,
but if you ask me, it's a matter of time.
Always is.
Hey.
There's a storm coming.
John wants to see you.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
JOHN:
Derek.
Hey, Derek, it's okay. It's okay.
It's all gonna be okay.
Rest easy. It's okay.
What is all this?
So this thing, it works?
DEREK: He said it does.
I don't know how he knows,
but he said so.
- We go back...?
- Twenty years.
SAYLES: Set up a safe house,
gather intel, and then what?
"Hang in there, baby," till someone else
shows up and gives us more orders?
He didn't say anything about Kyle?
Not a word?
We can save Kyle.
We can save everybody.
- We can fix all the mistakes.
- How are we gonna do that?
Reese, how are we gonna do that?
Kyle Reese, your brother.
He came across time to protect me.
He died fighting the machines.
He was a soldier, and he was...
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
He was a hero.
SARAH: "Listen," Kyle said.
"Listen and understand.
The machine is out there.
It can't be bargained with.
It can't be reasoned with.
It doesn't feel pity or remorse or fear.
And it absolutely will not stop, ever.
Until you are dead."