SARAH: In the future, my son will lead
mankind in a war against Skynet...
...the computer system
programmed to destroy the world.
It has sent machines back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles.
Mr. Ferguson is ill today.
My name is Cromartie.
Do we have a John Reese?
Excellent.
JOHN: You changed the future,
you just didn't change it enough.
These things, they're here.
They're programmed with specific missions.
Took his eyes, James.
JOHN:
Jumper, outside the gym.
That's my friend.
The crying one from the bathroom.
- We've gotta help her now.
- No.
I could've done something.
I was right there.
And what were you gonna do, be a hero?
Isn't that what I'm supposed to be?
A hero.
Isn't that who I am?
Patient is female, 33.
Previous lipo and breast augmentation
with complications of seroma and scarring.
[CRASH NEARBY]
Hello?
SARAH: When John was little,
before bed, I used to read him fairy tales.
One night, I read him a folktale
called The Golem of Prague.
The story of a clay monster made
by a rabbi to protect the Jews of the city.
You shouldn't be back here,
the office is closed.
CROMARTIE:
You do reconstructive surgery?
You need a consult.
You'll have to call Monday.
CROMARTIE:
I need reconstructive surgery.
Look, you can either just leave now...
...or I can call the police. Your choice.
SARAH: I failed to remember
that at the end of the story...
...the Golem turns on its maker and kills him
as well as the rest of the town.
Now.
SARAH:
He didn't sleep for months.
I went to him and tried to tell him
it wasn't real, that I'd made it all up.
Somehow, that made it all worse.
Up a little late?
Covalent and ionic bonding.
No wonder you're still up.
I could never
get my head around this either.
It's not that hard.
So you wanna talk about it?
- Talk about what?
- You just seem down.
Downer than usual.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm fine.
John, I know what fine means.
Fine means you're upset
and you won't talk to me.
Fine means I'm fine.
I saw there's a memorial service
at school this week for that girl.
- Jordan.
- Jordan, right.
- Were you planning on going?
- I try not to make plans.
Plans are for people
in control of their own lives.
I don't want you to blame yourself
for what happened.
Who said I blame myself?
- What do you want?
- Cromartie's here.
- Now.
- What?
CAMERON: I've been monitoring the media
for possible threats.
Yesterday, arson at an Oakland dock
forced the rerouting of a shipment...
...of refined Coltan
to the port of Los Angeles.
- Coltan?
- Skynet will use it as a key element...
...in our endoskeletal alloy.
SARAH: It doesn't mean Cromartie's back.
How can it be Cromartie?
- Are you forgetting that I blew his head off?
- I remember.
That's why I went to find this.
You should watch.
It won't play.
Put it on Video 2.
CAMERON:
Oh.
- Thank you for explaining.
- Where'd you get this?
Check the paper tomorrow
for any dead anchormen.
I don't sleep.
There.
He came through. He knows we're here.
It's just a head.
His chip is intact.
We're programmed to repair ourselves.
We're programmed to blend in.
He might still need Coltan
for a missing piece. A leg, an arm.
He will rebuild and continue his mission
to hunt and kill.
I know what his mission is.
I still have the money
from the safe house.
We can go south,
set up across the border, off the grid.
Go south?
What?
I thought you said we weren't gonna run
anymore. We were gonna fight.
SARAH: This is different.
JOHN: You're right. This is different.
If Cromartie's damaged, he's vulnerable.
We know where he'll be.
If he got new skin, he'll have a new face.
- We won't know what he looks like.
- But we know where he'll be.
I can hack the port's schedule no problem.
We find the container and we wait.
We hunt him for a change.
Or we could run again.
The ship comes tonight?
- The one carrying the Coltan.
- Five a.m.
Like you're gonna drive.
Get the shotguns.
It's not like I can't drive.
And the C4 from the bathroom
under the towels.
- Cromartie?
- Not here yet. They're humans.
Keep setting the charges.
If he comes for that Coltan,
he'll have to come through here.
Is that Cromartie?
Cameron?
[GUN COCKS]
[POLICE OFFICER SCREAMS]
CAMERON:
He'll survive.
- He's human.
- Not a very strong one.
Mom.
Those other guys just stole the truck.
Does Cromartie have men working
with him? Does that happen?
You work with me.
We have to follow that truck.
MAN:
Keep it steady.
Lean forward.
That's Coltan.
If that's what you're made of,
no wonder you're so dense.
Not density.
Heat resistance.
T-600 models
had a titanium alloy endoskeleton.
But it was vulnerable to heat. Coltan alloys
have a much higher melting point.
You know what I love about you guys?
Even when you've evolved into the ultimate,
indestructible killing machine...
...you're not above self-examination
and improvement.
- Thank you.
- Please shut up.
Military tags?
Leave it.
MAN 1: All right, you heard him.
We need to move. Now.
MAN 2: And how about we get paid now,
seriously?
MAN 3:
How about you shut up and go now?
MAN 2:
Hey, hey. What are you doing?
He's not damaged at all.
That's not Cromartie.
Endoskeletal structure points
don't match.
He's too short.
Another one?
Why does he have all this?
I thought these things just hunt
and kill people.
They perform whatever mission
they're programmed for.
And what kind of mission is this?
Man, it weirds me out more and more.
We barely get a crime scene up...
...and the FBI's here like that.
Like you guys got some kind
of magic powers or something.
Thanks, Lou.
LOU: Sure.
Computers, my friend.
Logging the weird blood sample
that matches my other cases...
...then, poof, I appear.
Yeah, you're gonna put us all out of work
one of these days. Not that I'll mind.
ELLISON:
Wouldn't worry about that.
Always gonna need somebody
to clean up.
So who we got here?
Dr. David Lyman.
Plastic surgeon.
Office manager found him this morning
when she came to open up.
Swabbed your weird blood
out of the drain.
Otherwise, the place is clean.
Nothing missing. No motive. Zip.
- So, what's your interest here?
- I got six guys dead, no rhyme or reason.
Except some kind of blood
that isn't quite blood.
It's not natural.
I like natural.
Natural's reassuring.
It helps me sleep at night.
I meant more of the FBI's interest.
Oh. Well, ha, ha.
You know the FBI.
We're interested in everything.
DETECTIVE:
So this guy...
...comes in Friday night.
Leaves Sunday a.m.
It's the only lead we have
at the moment.
WOMAN: I thought he looked familiar.
He was a patient.
We did his chin and nose last May.
George Laszlo.
We still have the charges,
we can rig them at the door...
...and blow them when they drive out.
Cameron can take out...
Get in the car. We're going.
What?
John, the plan was to hunt Cromartie.
- That's not Cromartie.
- So?
You wanna walk in,
kick their asses and go for pancakes?
It doesn't work like that.
We're outnumbered.
We have her.
SARAH: We don't know what's going on.
That thing has real estate.
It has employees.
Who knows how many more are in there?
There's three of us. I'm not saying we run
but we need to step back.
- See what's going on.
- So we run, in other words.
Tell him to get in the car.
- It's too dangerous. We should go.
- It's always too dangerous.
It's war. War is dangerous.
If you die...
...they win.
How many of those things,
those endoskeletons...
...do you think they can make
out of that load of metal?
Because that's what we're talking about.
It's a truck full of enemy soldiers.
What if they're building them
right here, right now?
If I can get myself onto the truck,
we can track them by laptop.
John Connor, we're going. Now.
Five hundred and thirty.
- What?
- Endoskeletons.
Based on the approximate volume
of Coltan in the shipment...
...that's how many.
John.
Damn it, John.
CAMERON:
No.
If they see us, they'll find him.
MAN 1:
Yeah, we'll get rid of them.
MAN 2:
Yeah, we just have a couple more to load.
Here's the route we're taking.
Drop some of this Coltan off.
What do you think?
- You get Mark and let's get going.
- Got it.
MAN 1:
Okay, let's roll.
All right, guys. Come on.
Hey! You wanna tell me
what you're doing here?
[CHUCKLES]
- Have you seen a dachshund puppy?
- Huh?
SARAH:
They had Army uniforms.
Tags.
Where would they go?
They're going north.
John's phone.
You can track it online.
SARAH:
This actually works?
Wait, wait, wait. No, no, no.
The signal was lost.
- The phone might be damaged.
- Come on. Damn it.
- Come on.
- Breaking the computer won't help.
Do you have any idea what's going on?
I lost him. I lost John.
I understand.
It's impossible for you to understand.
Without John, your life has no purpose.
I can't believe I let him talk me into this.
You try to open your hands just a little
and it's too soon.
Is it?
The world ends in four years.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
JOHN:
Come on.
- What?
- Left you a message.
Davidson was buying at Houston's.
When you didn't show, they sent me
to check to see if you died or something.
- Did you die?
- You run across him on those Pico murders?
- John Doe's? Bar-code tats?
- No, who is he?
George Laszlo. Unemployed actor.
Got him on video at the murder scene.
Only suspect I got
but this file is straight vanilla.
Are you trying to impress a boss?
Wow, crank up the Sugar Ray
and call Monica Lewinsky.
It's 1999 again.
Sugar what?
James, you trying to get back
on the rising-young-star list...
...forget about it.
I mean, this case is a dog.
And you're not young.
Agent Stewart, can I help you?
You got some guy holed up in Room 3.
That would be my dog.
Laszlo?
STEWART: He asked if he needed a lawyer,
I told him it was a courtesy thing.
So, what's this all about?
It's about my case.
STEWART: Good case?
- We'll find out soon enough.
Did he strike you as a killer?
Everyone strikes me as a killer.
So, George, you're an actor.
Been in anything I've seen?
What is this about?
Just some questions
related to Dr. Lyman's death.
So anything?
I see a lot of movies.
It's been slow.
Well, it's picking up around here,
I'll tell you that.
I got six dead bodies
and a mystery man...
...who might be trying
to change his identity.
So is that why you got the work?
Chin and nose?
You kill a doctor to cover your tracks?
Dolores, meet Mr. Laszlo.
I was hoping that he would give us
a little blood sample.
If you're not my guy,
you're out of my file here in an hour tops.
Make a fist.
Great.
Just a little sting.
Can't seem to find a vein.
You guys are a bunch of fascists,
you know that?
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
Tell me where they went.
Lady, go to hell.
Where they went
or I'm gonna beat you to death.
And don't call me lady.
Tell me where they went, damn it.
CAMERON: if you beat him to death,
he can't tell us anything.
- I'm not gonna tell you anything.
- Okay.
Yeah, like you got the stones.
You can go...
...if you can get past her.
McGuire Gunnery Range?
This place is the size of L.A. county.
Where exactly are they?
She's talking to you.
Depot 37.
It's a decommissioned arms depot
in the southeast corner.
If you take the outer loop,
past all the old abandoned hangars.
It was an Air Force base in the Cold War.
I don't know what they're doing.
I was to guard the warehouse
and clean up when they left.
The man just needed some guys.
That's all I know, I swear to God.
Just drive faster.
MAN:
Badge, please.
Your tax dollars at work.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
What, you need more blood?
What the...?
Hey! Aah!
What are you doing?
Let me go. Put me down.
Put me...
[SCREAMS]
[TRUCK BEEPING]
MAN 1: Didn't you lock this?
MAN 2: Yeah.
MAN 1:
Damn it. Damn it.
Guy must have popped him.
Been bitching about his money all week.
MAN 2: You think he split?
MAN 1: You surprised?
Guy threatened to bail twice a day.
Let's finish and get out of here.
MAN 2:
Who tells Carter?
MAN 1: You. He's your friend.
- Friend? He's just a guy I met.
Six victims.
Different parts of the city,
different worlds, different lives.
What's the connection?
Greta was saying none.
Guys in the house were drug dealers.
But there's some blood matches.
And we got George here. George Laszlo.
And who exactly is this guy?
- Actually, Jim...
- James, not Jim. James.
Right. Right, apologies.
Uh, before you go on, I just wanna
make sure you're aware Laszlo was clear.
Blood sample came back.
Not a match to the plastic-surgeon's office.
We got blood? How'd we manage that?
I, uh... I finessed the samples.
And, yes, I heard it didn't match.
But I've been thinking
of another possibility.
Whoever killed Dr. Lyman
was in there for two days.
I'm thinking there's a chance...
...our killer had himself cut
to look like Laszlo.
Forced the doctor to operate,
then killed him.
Yeah, but wouldn't there be scars
and bruising?
The office has a hyperbaric oxygen system
which speeds healing.
And he could've used makeup.
STEWART: Actually, I considered this too.
I asked the office manager. They keep
detailed records of the anesthesia.
According to their log,
the levels were unchanged.
No one had surgery.
No one had anesthesia.
There's a possibility they didn't use any.
STEWART: I asked that too.
She said a job like that,
four, five hours under the knife...
...cutting that deep into the tissue
of the face, the nose, the eyes...
...you can't take that kind of pain.
It's impossible.
You got some kind of release
from this Laszlo guy, right, for the blood?
Last thing we need's a lawsuit.
So if there isn't anything else...
Hey, sorry, Jim.
Facts are facts.
Ooh. Sorry about that.
You know, if it doesn't add up,
it just doesn't add up.
It doesn't add up
because we don't have all the numbers yet.
James, nobody expects anything
from you on this.
Your ass is suitably covered.
Why you wanna rock the boat?
Last time I had a case
where this many things didn't add up...
...three people blew themselves up
in a bank.
Look, I don't know, Greta.
I just...
I just feel it.
Well, maybe you should try
feeling a little less...
...because you're going blind.
Hey.
[STAMMERING]
You can't just leave me here.
You can't...
Come on, hurry up.
It would've been faster to kill him.
Sometimes you seem inefficient.
I'm not for you to understand.
You said that before.
Well, I do things, you know?
Stupid, illogical, inefficient things.
Humans. Get used to it.
MAN 1:
I told the guy to just be patient.
Looks like he bailed.
CARTER: So he's gone?
MAN 2: Yeah, it doesn't surprise me,
he was bitching about the money all week.
Then I wanna thank you for your service.
[GUNFIRE]
[SIREN WAILING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
SARAH:
This is it?
This is Depot 37?
Did that guy lie to you?
CAMERON:
No.
This is it.
- This is where the factory will be.
- What factory?
Where I'll be made.
Me and many others. Right there.
It's inside.
Coltan's rare in the future. Much of it
was destroyed when the bombs went off.
He's stockpiling it
for after Judgment Day.
It's in the bunker where it'll be safe.
MAN:
Hey.
Shh.
Your gun, give it to me now.
I don't have a gun. I don't have anything.
I didn't shoot anyone. Your boss.
- Hey, Carter.
- Shh, shh, no, no, no.
Just listen to me for a second. Just for
a second, all right? What's your name?
- My name's John.
- What are you doing here?
I'm just like you.
In the wrong place at the wrong time.
- What's your name?
- Mike.
All right, Mike, listen.
We got a problem, okay?
Your boss, he's a... He's a really bad guy.
All right?
He killed those guys.
And he'll kill us if he finds us.
So we need to get out of here.
- Carter? He shot them?
- You've worked with this guy, right?
Have you noticed
that something's just off about him?
Like he'd just kill you just because.
So there's something wrong with him,
you know?
Yeah.
- We'll see if we can...
- No, no, no, don't.
This bastard owes me my money.
I'll take my share and theirs too.
Hey. Freak.
I'm talking to you.
Look, man, just open the door.
Thank you for your service.
What are you?
[COIN CLINKS]
Come on, come on, please.
It's not your fault.
Maybe it's yours.
If you had let him try to save that girl,
let him think he had a choice in the matter.
Maybe he wouldn't have gone off
the reservation.
- John does these things.
- Not the John I know.
The John I know.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
JOHN [OVER PHONE]: Mom.
- John, thank God.
- Mom.
- We're right outside. Are you all right?
- Yeah.
But listen, he's blocking the door.
It's like he's frozen.
He's frozen?
Yeah, and when the door shut,
it's like he went to sleep or something.
Standby.
He completed his mission.
He powered down to standby mode...
- ...until he's moved or triggered awake.
- Triggered?
The door.
They put him into standby.
Fifteen seconds.
That's the reboot time.
John, listen to me.
This is what I want you to do.
I want you to open that door and run.
The instant that door cracks open,
you run.
John.
Yeah, I run.
So, what do you think Future John
would do right now?
We'll see.
[SIGHS]
[SIREN WAILING]
John?
[TRUCK STARTING]
JOHN:
Come on!
- I thought you said you could drive.
- It's jammed or something.
Step on the clutch.
Hard.
If you're gonna be a hero,
you gotta learn how to drive stick.
[SIREN WAILING]
- Let's go.
- Can't he get out?
Drive.
[KNOCKS]
Mr. Laszlo.
May I come in?
Thank you.
Hey.
Pepperoni?
Ha, ha. I love those things.
My bosses told me
I should stay clear of you.
Legal reasons.
I understand.
But I thought I owed it to you to drop by.
- Give you a warning.
- A warning?
Well, there's a chance,
a small chance, but a chance...
...that there's someone out there
who might be trying to steal your identity.
Steal my identity?
- What would they do with that?
- What do people do with anything?
Steal, cheat, harm and intimidate others.
Damage the national psyche.
Anyway...
...if you see or hear anything unusual,
call me, any time.
Thank you for your help.
Sure.
Hey, have a nice day.
Have a nice day.
SARAH: Not every version
of the Golem story ends badly.
In one, the monster is a hero...
...destroying all those
that seek to harm its maker.
In another,
the Golem's maker destroys his creature...
...before it destroys the world.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Really.
How many times
do we gotta have this talk?
A lot, I think.
I should go finish my homework.
SARAH:
The pride of men, of parents as well...
...makes us believe
that anything we create, we can control.
Whether from clay or from metal...
...it is in the nature of us
to make our own monsters.
Our children are alloys all,
built from our own imperfect flesh.
We animate them with magic.
And never truly know what they will do.