SARAH [VOICE-OVER]: In the future,
my son will lead mankind...
...in a war against Skynet.
A computer system programmed
to destroy the world.
It has sent machines
back through time.
Some to kill him.
One to protect him.
Today we fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
To change our future.
To change his fate.
The war to save mankind begins now.
NARRATOR: Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles...
SARAH: Where are we?
CAMERON: Same where. Different when.
I want my new name.
My whole new me.
I'll track down Enrique.
I need three sets of papers.
My nephew has taken over the business.
You're in the system and everything.
SARAH: Uncle Enrique would be proud.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
He referred to you as a rata. Snitch.
Why would you do this?
CAMERON: Because you wouldn't.
- Why not stay in the past?
- You died two years ago. Cancer.
SARAH: I've seen that before.
CAMERON: Skynet work camp.
Resistance fighters.
JOHN: You sure there's money here?
CAMERON: Anything they valued.
Money. Guns. It would be hidden.
SARAH:
You told me we'd be safe.
CAMERON:
Skynet doesn't know you're here.
There's no directive to hunt you.
What if they found out?
Would they all know what to do?
Who the hell are you, man?
Ah...
CAMERON:
They do.
When I was in the mental hospital
I became obsessed with science.
Not all science, actually.
And not really science at all.
Scientists, and then
only nuclear scientists.
The ones who invented the bomb.
Oppenheimer, Heisenberg,
Fermi and Teller.
Pioneers. Geniuses all.
I read every book I could.
I wanted to understand.
Why couldn't they stop?
These fathers of our destruction?
And why wouldn't anybody
stop them?
And if I had the chance, would I?
[MEN GRUNTING]
Good morning.
- You look like hell.
- Up late.
Newspaper clippings,
surveillance photos, bank records.
Pamphlets from every high-tech company
in the state.
Even thought I saw the deeds
to city hall in here somewhere.
Those Resistance guys weren't sent
back here to be our support crew.
They're a Skynet hunting party.
Really? Are you sure?
Most of this is still a puzzle to me,
but there is one list in here I understand.
Employee list, Cyberdyne Systems.
Seems they thought
it was a good place to start. And it is.
She's not gonna be happy to see you.
She never is.
- You want me to come along?
- No. You have your own job to do.
A big one.
You're getting pretty good at that.
Thank you.
Still, it's not brain surgery
or anything.
It would be funny if you were some
advanced cybernetic intelligence...
...yet stumped by a stick of eyeliner.
No, it's not brain surgery.
Would have to be a lot sharper
for brain surgery.
Much better.
When you wear clothes, much better.
Okay, six ways in, six ways out.
The front opens to the street here.
Security's minimal.
Two armed guards in the morning.
Four in the afternoon.
If anything goes wrong,
there's a parking lot here.
Mom, it's high school, okay?
Not supermax. We can handle it.
We can handle it.
Don't you kiss me.
Or anyone else.
JOHN: Okay, now blend in.
CAMERON: Blend in.
Yeah, I mean don't seem like a freak.
You know what I mean, right?
Freak. Weirdo. Kook.
Oddball. Crackpot.
Strange duck. Queer potato.
Nut.
I've been reading the dictionary.
- I don't sleep.
- That's what I'm talking about.
You do that, you sound like a freak.
Don't walk around like my bodyguard.
You're supposed to be my sister.
You won't fool anyone.
I fooled you.
[SCOFFS]
What's that all about?
Appears to be a re-imagining
of a trompe l'oeil fresco.
I don't sleep.
Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling.
Take it off and put it in the basket.
Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling
in the basket.
In the basket, people. Come on.
The line keeps moving. Let's go.
Cell phones, hats, rings, and bling
in the basket.
Keep the line moving.
Cell phones, caps, rings, and bling
in the basket please.
Let's go. Come on. Thank you.
Cell phones, caps, rings, and bli...
GUARD 1:
Again with you, missy.
Cell phones, hats, rings and bling
in the basket.
GUARD 2: Hold that. Come through.
MAN 1: Come on.
Come on, we ain't got all day.
[SIGHS]
Excuse me. This is my sister.
Extra credit for you.
JOHN: Look, she's got
a metal plate in her head.
Really. It's a big one.
[BEEPING]
MAN 2: Look at this. All right,
metal head, let's go through.
I fell. Hard.
All right, let's go. Go ahead.
Cell phones, caps.
TARISSA: I thought you were dead.
- Well, I'm not.
Lucky you.
- You look...
- Different?
The same.
- Well, I can't explain.
- I wouldn't want you to.
- Is John...?
- He's good.
TARISSA:
What about that machine?
She's still around.
Not that one.
- The other.
- No.
Do you mind?
You brought it.
Danny's not here?
It's ten years, right?
He's at school.
- He hasn't come in a long time.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
What do you want, Sarah?
You never die
and you always want something.
I need you to look
at these photographs.
Tell me if you recognize anybody.
I know it's been a long time but...
[TARISSA SIGHS]
No.
Nobody. Sorry.
Because one of them may be involved
with Skynet right now.
They might not even know it.
Sorry to bother you.
I'll leave you alone.
The fourth photo.
The young one.
His name is Andrew Goode.
Andy.
He was an intern at Cyberdyne
one summer.
Miles liked him.
Is he going to die too?
Is that what happens now? He dies?
I don't know.
I hope not.
Well, if he does,
just make sure it matters.
Make sure it's not in vain.
No one dies in vain.
Agent Ellison.
They told me you were coming.
But I told them the last time
you worked a scene...
...Hoover was cross-dressing
at Quantico.
Ballistics.
I can already tell you mine are bigger.
Same gun that killed your boys here
killed one of my CI's. Enrique Salzia.
What's the connection?
He made fake paper.
Your guys had fake paper.
Hope you're not selling the terrorist-cell
theory because I'm not buying it.
- Why not?
- Look at the print report.
Cal. ID, NCIC, CDP, Interpol.
There's nothing here.
These guys were drug dealers.
Small-time.
Definitely not worth
you putting your tie on...
...and breaking open
your Thomas Guide.
Oh, yeah. We see this every day.
You didn't find that curious?
Why would anyone wire a safe
directly into the power?
Why's the sky blue, Ellison?
Don't overthink it.
The guys were druggies. They're not
rocket scientists, not terrorists.
Your guy sold my guys paper.
My guys whacked your guy
to cover their tracks.
Go back to your office.
Your desk misses you.
Right. Good one.
[SIGHS]
Somebody came back here
for whatever was in that safe.
They're out there.
And I'm gonna find them.
DOCTOR:
Hey, buddy, wait.
You can't go in there.
Hey. Hey.
[GRUNTING]
ANDY:
All right. Uh, the receipt's in the bag.
Let me know if you have
any problems.
You shouldn't have any problems
setting up the... The... You know.
You should be pretty happy.
MAN: Cool, that's so...
ANDY: Let me know
if you have any problems with it.
Enjoy.
MAN: Thank you.
ANDY:
Have a good day.
Can I help you?
No.
Andy. Just looking.
You just kept looking over
like you needed something.
That's the phone. Seriously, if I was
gonna be alone on a desert island...
...with only a phone for a companion
that would be the phone.
Is that something you would do?
[CHUCKLES]
May I?
Got a four-meg camera...
...texting... True texting too.
Not that SMS cartoon-bubble junk.
3G data access, 10 gigs free music...
...six hours of talk time
and 36 standby on your battery.
What happens if I press
these numbers here?
- Excuse me?
- These numbers? One through nine?
If I press seven of them
will someone talk to me...
...through the ear part up here?
Uh... Yeah.
Okay. I'll take three.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
ANDY [ON PHONE]: Hi.
Are you calling me?
Uh, I was just following up
to make sure everything's okay.
I just left the store.
ANDY: I know.
Okay. Do you wanna have dinner
with me tonight?
No.
Well, you answered too quickly.
Hear me out.
Just give me one minute.
- Thirty seconds?
- Talk fast.
Okay, first let me clear up the whole
desert-island-and-a-cell-phone thing.
- It seems strange if you picture it.
- I wasn't.
Right. Why would you?
It's an asinine sales pitch.
Nowhere to plug in the phone.
It would be worth less than a rock...
...when the battery died.
Couldn't even use it to open a coconut.
- This is you selling yourself?
- Selling myself? I don't know.
There's something immoral
about the whole selling process.
- And yet, that's your job.
- Part-time.
And I'm not very good at it. So I'm
actually less immoral than the average...
Anyway. Um...
Where was I?
- You're right.
- About what?
I answered too quick.
- Mr. Baum?
- Yes?
Take your seat, please.
- Hi.
Okay. Paper and pencil out.
Time for a pop quiz.
Here.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
TEACHER:
Come in.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I said come on in.
[CHATTERING]
I'm transferring in.
MAN 1: That's what I'm talking about.
MAN 2: What's up with that?
TEACHER:
Okay. Any open seat.
JOHN: What part about "Don't act like a
freak" didn't you understand?
Sit down.
[DOG BARKING]
[SPANISH RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
JAMES: So.
- So.
Like I said on the phone, your sweet
Uncle Enrique lived a colorful life.
One we have not yet painted in full.
You grow apart.
Every day's a new adventure.
Who can keep up?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I got an uncle who's like a father.
I also got one who's like a stranger.
How about you two?
More like an aunt. Chatty, chatty.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
All right. So you're not too close.
But he did call you three times
the day he was murdered.
- What did you chat about?
- Those Lakers.
- Really? What about them?
- Kobe. He's the bomb.
I always thought he was a ball hog.
He's all alone, man.
He's got no one else who can shoot.
Is that you, Carlos?
Now that your uncle's dead?
You all alone?
Yeah.
All these boys can shoot.
[LAUGHS]
- I didn't kill my uncle.
- No.
And you're too smart
to know nothing about who did.
I'll be in touch.
No, I know. The guy's 18 months
ahead of the Germans.
Yeah, well, I would
if I had that kind of grant money.
No, I'm not saying
the guy's a complete idiot.
It's not exactly
avant-garde science, is it?
Why don't they give money
to people on the cutting edge?
But they never do. They never...
[FOOTSTEPS]
[CHOKING]
Hey.
- How was school?
- I have a metal plate in my head.
She's gonna need a note.
I meant you, not her.
JOHN: Yeah, fine.
SARAH:
You're not gonna give me anything?
We went, we learned.
I didn't get killed and she didn't kill
anybody. It was a pretty good first day.
What about you, did you go?
SARAH: I did.
JOHN: How was she?
Surprised you weren't dead?
More like disappointed.
She ID'd
one of the safe-house photos.
Intern at Cyberdyne.
JOHN: Really?
What does he do? Work in a lab or build
rocket guidance systems or something?
- Cell phone salesman.
- Shut up.
Cell phone salesman,
and not a very good one.
CAMERON:
These need to be cleaned.
JOHN: Okay, so about
the cell-phone guy.
I'm having dinner with him tonight.
- Dinner? You mean, like a date?
- Not a date.
Are you going to kill him?
Kill him?
I don't know the first thing about him.
He interned at Cyberdyne in college.
His photo's in a pile of photos.
Nobody dies till I say so.
Tell her.
People die all the time.
They won't wait for her.
I fooled you again.
[EXHALES]
Who are you?
How did you find me?
What... What do you want?
Are you a veteran?
Is that what this is about?
Do you speak?
TERMINATOR [IN ROBOT VOICE]:
Read that.
How...? How did you...?
No, no, no. That's not possible.
That's an epidermal growth rate
that's not sustainable.
Keratinocyte and...
At that rate you couldn't possibly
maintain cell regulation or differentiation.
It's impossible.
TERMINATOR:
Possible.
Woo was wrong.
Thomason was wrong.
Parker and Lang were almost right,
but still...
...completely wrong. I was...
I wasn't even close.
TERMINATOR:
Can you do it?
Well, I'd have to go to my lab.
There's a whole mix of growth rates.
TGF-beta, PDGF, EGF...
I'd need...
You know, there's a lot of equipment.
Oh, and blood.
We need at least 20 units.
Preferably with tissues comprised...
TERMINATOR: I brought my own.
TERMINATOR:
Can you do it?
Yes.
Yes, I can.
SARAH [VOICE-OVER]:
In 1943...
...the German physicist
Werner Heisenberg...
...delivered a physics lecture
to a packed hall in Zurich.
One of the audience members
was Moe Berg...
...an ex-professional baseball player
working as a spy for the OSS.
Berg's task was to listen to the lecture
and determine whether the Germans...
...were close to perfecting
the atomic bomb.
If Berg discovered
that this was the case...
...he was to wait
for Heisenberg outside the hall...
...and shoot the scientist in the head.
He had never killed anyone before.
So what's your deal, Andy?
I can't imagine you majored
in cell phone sales at college.
No. No. More like Funyuns and 12 packs
of Jolt from the vintage soda store...
...while my roommates and I
hacked "Zelda III"...
...so the princess would say
funny lines ripped from reruns.
What's that language you speak, boy?
Computer science.
Caltech. Advanced Dork.
And what would you do
with a computer degree from Caltech?
I don't know. I never got one.
- Really?
- My father died senior year.
Mom went a little off the rails.
I dropped out to help.
I'm sorry.
No, it was a long time ago,
but thanks anyway.
She's good. She married
the security guard at her bank.
Do you have family?
Distant.
Don't take this the wrong way, but as
a cell phone salesman I think I can ask.
Did you ever wanna be anything
other than a waitress?
- Yes, I did.
- What was it?
I can't remember.
What's this, Andy?
Oh, isn't it great?
That is the official promotional poster
for the Kramnik-Deep Fritz match.
Awesome match. Just awesome.
Most people cite
the '97 Kasparov-Deep Blue...
...as the watershed man-versus-machine
chess match.
But, uh, Fritz would have
wiped the floor with Blue...
...just like Kramnik did
with Kasparov.
Besides, the other poster's
impossible to find.
What is it you do, Andy?
Do you wanna see?
Yes, I wanna see.
All right.
Behold.
The Turk.
- The Turk?
- Well, not the original Turk.
The original Turk was an automaton...
...constructed and unveiled in 1770
by the Baron Wolfgang von Kempelen.
It played chess.
Is that what your Turk does?
It plays chess?
I know that sounds boring as hell.
Most people think so.
But maybe I should put it this way:
My Turk plays chess at a level
that could defeat every human player...
...that has ever lived
and probably ever will live.
That's not bragging.
A number of AIs can do that now.
But the AI chess platform
is very valuable...
...for artificial intelligence developers.
What?
I thought I saw someone outside.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Uh, yeah, it's a prowler.
Uh, back porch. It's the police.
There's been break-ins
in the neighborhood.
My...
SARAH: I have to go, Andy.
No, Sarah, wait.
Uh, it's 165 Mesrow. Sarah!
Again, what did it look like?
What did it look like?
Who cares what it looked like?
It was a rack of computer equipment.
Okay, but was there
obvious network access?
- Do you know what kind of bandwidth?
- You're joking.
What about power supply?
Was there a cooling element?
- Like a fan or something?
- John...
I'm just trying to get a sense
of the horsepower.
I wanna know if this thing
was a dinky little homemade soap box...
...or if it was a full-fledged
Al platform...
...capable of learning and growing
and taking on other applications.
It plays chess.
So did Einstein.
Have you ever heard
of the Singularity?
It's a point in time
where machines become so smart...
...that they're capable of making smarter
versions of themselves without our help.
That's pretty much the time
we can kiss our asses goodbye.
Unless we stop it.
Like you said you would.
So I caught a break on a set
of fingerprints from our drug dealers.
I wanted to see your face
when I laid that on you.
See, the only fingerprint database
I hadn't checked was kid prints.
Ha, ha. That's no joke. That's him.
That's one of your dead terrorists.
A black-haired, brown-eyed, 35-pound,
4-year-old boy living in Canton, Ohio.
[SIGHS]
And that's the look I wanted to see.
JAMES:
Hold up.
Did your crime-scene guys
find any peculiar blood?
I think they got all the peculiar
they could stomach with these prints.
Lab says some blood evidence found
at my CI crime scene is almost human.
Except there's no
red blood cells present.
I wanna see the blood evidence
from your guys.
I'll get back to you.
You're gonna double check those prints,
right?
On the kid in Canton?
[SIGHS]
Have a party.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BEEPING]
The thing I hadn't thought of,
the thing nobody thought possible...
...was the use
of a synthetic oxygen carrier.
By creating a synthetic spear that carries
oxygen bringing nutrients to the skin...
...it obviates the need
for the marrow interaction.
The real-world applications are,
well, mind-blowing.
It's ready.
I have a video camera.
Would it be all right if...?
TERMINATOR [IN ROBOT VOICE]:
Move away.
Who are you?
What are you?
Sarah?
Didn't you get my message?
I returned your call about the results.
- Yeah, I got your message.
- Yeah. You're healthy as a horse.
A healthy horse.
I got that from your message.
I wanted to talk to you
about prevention.
For cancer? What you're doing
seems to be working.
Specifically.
Um... Don't smoke.
Get lots of exercise. Eat leafy greens.
Don't snort asbestos.
I don't mean to make light,
but you've got no risk factors.
No genetic disposition.
Is there anything else about your history
that I should know?
No.
You've got children, right?
Yeah, I got two myself.
You worry. You wanna make sure you're
always healthy and strong for them.
Don't drive yourself crazy
chasing the future. We can't predict.
You know?
We can only try and prevent.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Andy, it's Sarah.
[CHATTERING]
MAN:
Forget about it.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You going to chem?
- Yeah.
- What is going on?
- No idea.
WOMAN 1: She is such a skanky whore.
Ugh, disgusting.
WOMAN 2:
Dirty whore.
CHOLA: I love this color.
It's tight, right?
This color's tight.
- What is it?
- Rash.
It's so tight.
[SCOFFS]
I'm a pig. I look pregnant.
Does this make me look fat?
Yes.
What the hell? What's your problem?
You asked.
Bitch-whore much?
I don't understand.
I said, bitch-whore much?
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at you.
[WOMAN CRYING]
[BREATHES SHARPLY]
You saw it, right?
Right? You saw it?
It's so freaking big,
and right out there.
It's freaking big.
JORDAN: Right. It is, right?
Whoever's doing this
is such a jackass.
I mean, who would do this?
And how would they even know?
My parents.
They're gonna kill me. Kill me.
I mean, don't we have hall monitors?
I mean, how could someone just...
[CRYING]
You're upset.
No kidding, I'm upset.
My life is freaking over.
Here's a present.
It's tight.
[JORDAN CRYING]
ANDY: I have to admit,
I wondered if I'd see you again.
SARAH: Miracles happen every day.
ANDY: That's funny.
ANDY: That was a joke, right?
SARAH: if it was funny, it was a joke.
ANDY: So the police recommended
that I put in a security system.
Armed patrol, that kind of thing.
Can't really afford it, though.
- You think someone wants the Turk?
- Well, eight years of my life.
Not just the software.
I customized the hardware too.
One month, I worked so much
on a motherboard...
...that I lost my sight for three days.
No, that really happened.
Those circuits are so small.
A lot of the gear is actually pulled
from gaming platforms.
Did you know that the military
uses them?
Yeah, I've got the guts of three Xboxes
and four PlayStations, daisy-chained.
Plus some seriously modded-out code
that I swear came to me in a dream.
And all this to beat another computer
at chess?
None of this to beat another computer
at chess.
Then what?
What are you doing?
Would you believe me if I told you
Turk has moods?
Obviously not in the sense
that you and I understand mood...
...but sometimes I'll feed it a particular
chess problem, and it'll solve it one way.
The next day, I feed it the same problem
and it solves it differently.
Once in a while,
it can't even solve it at all.
- Do you know why it does that?
- No.
Yeah, neither do I.
Someday, I'm gonna figure it out.
- Someday, Turk will tell me.
- You talk about it like it's human.
Well, you never know.
What? Too far? What is it?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
[CHATTERING]
- Do you like this color on me?
- What?
- I'm a bitch-whore.
I have a new friend.
Did she tell you,
you were a bitch-whore?
No. She cried.
Wait. What?
Okay, what the hell is this thing?
MAN:
Jumper. Outside the gym.
[CHATTERING]
MAN 1:
Yo, man, check it out.
MAN 2: Jump! Jump!
WOMAN 1: Shut up.
She's not gonna jump.
She's just trying to get attention.
- Jump!
- Dude, come on.
WOMAN 2:
You guys are so mean.
CAMERON: That's my new friend.
The crying one from the bathroom.
When?
Two hours, three minutes ago.
Four minutes ago.
WOMAN 3:
She just wants the attention.
She's upset.
Her parents are gonna kill her.
Did you do anything to her?
I tried to give her a tight present.
- We gotta help her. Now.
- No.
I'm going up there.
- Let me go. I order you to let me go.
- Don't be a freak.
ALL:
Whoa.
[ALL GASPING AND SHOUTING]
We gotta go. Now.
I could have done something.
I was right there.
Maybe.
Come on, Mom.
John, people who wanna
take their own lives, this girl...
...if they're serious about it,
they'll find a way.
You didn't see her.
If you'd have seen her,
you wouldn't be talking like this.
And what were you gonna do,
be a hero?
Get your name in the papers?
Your face?
Isn't that what I'm supposed to be?
A hero? Isn't that who I am?
If it's just gonna sit inside me,
just gonna sit in my gut...
...then what are we doing?
What's the point?
Why not just give it to them
if we're gonna act like them?
I don't know how to help him.
Andy Goode must be killed.
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Took his eyes, James.
They took his freaking eyes.
SARAH [VOICE-OVER]:
On July 16th, 1945...
...in the mountains outside of
Los Alamos, New Mexico...
...the world's first atomic bomb
exploded.
A white light pierced the sky
with such intensity...
...that a blind girl claimed to see
the flash from a hundred miles away.
After witnessing the explosion...
...J. Robert Oppenheimer quoted
a fragment of the Bhagavad-Gita...
...declaring, "I am become death,
the destroyer of worlds."
[DISTANT SIRENS WAILING]
His colleague, Ken Bainbridge,
put it another way...
...when he leaned close to Oppenheimer
and whispered:
"Now we are all sons of bitches."
Now we are all sons of bitches.