[both laughing]
Oh, boy.
Beefcake.
I'll tell you.
That is a hoot and a holler.
[sighs]
This next episode is definitely
both Trey and I's
favorite episode.
It's called "Big Gay AI's
Big Gay Boat Ride."
In it, Stan finds out
that his dog Sparky
is a homosexual.
[Male Voice] How did your preoccupation
with homosexuality develop?
Well, we have noticed
that America
definitely has a preoccupation
with gayness,
but we felt there was
a part of homosexuality
that has been left unexplored,
and that's animal homosexuality.
[Male Voice] I know people are curious
about the two of you too.
Are you guys, uh...
a couple,
if you know what I mean?
You... you mean, are we gay?
Yeah.
Well, I am a little.
I guess we're all a little gay.
Even little Scratch here.
Yeah.
[Male Voice] You must have gotten a lot
of mail on this episode.
What kinds of stuff
do you get in the mail
from fans in general?
We have great fans
and great fan mail.
People write such interesting,
fascinating things to us
every week.
Let me give you an example.
"Dear Trey and Matt,
I like your show."
That's from Tom in New Jersey.
[Male Voice] Why does Kenny have to die
so often and so horribly?
Both: Because he's poor.
[softly] Aw.
[Male Voice] Guys, is there stuff
you put into the show
that's subliminal,
kind of like a little reward
for the fans who are
really paying attention?
Yes. We definitely feel
we owe it to our hardcore fans
to put hidden subliminal
messages in every episode.
That way, they can watch
the episode over and over
and find something new
every time.
For instance, in this episode,
if you look really hard,
you can find a picture of me
having sex with Matt's mom.
What?
So now sit back,
relax, and enjoy
"Big Gay AI's
Big Gay Boat Ride."
[pleasant music]
[twangy music]
# I'm going down to South Park #
# Gonna have myself a time #
All: # Friendly faces
everywhere #
# Humble folks
without temptation #
# Going down to South Park #
# Gonna leave my woes behind #
# Ample parking day or night #
# People spouting:
"Howdy neighbor!" #
# Headed on up to South Park #
# Gonna see if I can't unwind #
[singing indistinctly]
# So come on down
to South Park #
# And meet some
friends of mine #
Hey, where's the school bus?
We're gonna be late
for football practice.
Hiya, Sparky.
Who's that?
That's my new dog Sparky.
He followed me to the bus stop.
Wow, cool!
Good boy, Sparky.
Who's my best buddy?
Who's your boy?
Who's your buddy?
Ugh.
You're making me sick, dude.
He's part Doberman
and part wolf.
He's the toughest dog
on the mountain.
No way. Everybody knows
that Sylvester
is the toughest dog
in South Park.
[growling]
He's not meaner than Sparky!
Oh, yeah?
Let's see.
Hey, Sylvester!
Sparky'll kick his ass!
I'll put a dollar on Sylvester.
You're on, dude.
That's it, Sparky, kick his ass!
[dogs panting]
Huh. He's doing
something to his ass.
He's not kicking his ass,
but he's definitely
doing something to his ass.
Sparky, bad dog!
[mumbling]
What?
Yeah, dude.
I think your dog is gay.
What do you mean?
That dog is a gay homosexual.
[dogs panting]
He's just confused.
I think the other dog's
the one that's confused.
[mumbling]
Sick! Shut up, dude.
[whining]
# Stan's dog's a homo #
Okay, children,
I know that you're all
extremely excited
and nervous and anxious
about the homecoming game
against Middle Park.
Who's Middle Park?
What's homecoming?
But just remember
what I taught you
that football
is like making love
to a really beautiful woman.
You can't always score,
but when you do,
it makes all the trying
worthwhile.
Now let's start practice.
[whistle blows]
Uh, Mr. Chef, sir?
Yes, Pip, what is it?
I still don't have a helmet.
I know, Pip.
The school can't afford helmets
for everybody.
Yes, but couldn't we rotate
who doesn't have a helmet
every week?
Does it always have to be me?
Yes, Pip, I'm afraid it does.
Oh.
Sorry, son.
Now get your ass in there.
Hut, hut, hut, hut, hut.
Hut, hut, hut, hut, hut, hut,
hut, hut, hut.
Hike the damn ball!
[grunts]
[screaming]
Hey, how's practice
coming there, Chef?
Huh? Oh, fine, fine.
I don't have to remind you
just how important this game is
to us South Park alumni.
Elementary school alumni?
That's as far as most of us got.
You think we have a shot
at beating the spread
against Middle Park this year?
I don't know.
What... what's the spread?
Middle park by 70 points.
Hmm.
Hey, I got it!
I got it, I got it!
I don't think we have a chance.
Nonsense, not with my nephew
a quarterback.
Right, Stanley?
Huh?
[grunts]
Attaboy!
Great pass, Stan!
Come on, Ned,
we got to get our asses
to the bookie!
[whistle blows]
Okay, that was
a good practice, children.
We'll see you here again
tomorrow.
Hey, Stan, isn't that your dog?
Yeah, he must have followed
me to football practice.
You see, he is smart.
Uh, my dog Rex follows me
to football practice
all the time.
Yeah, but my dog
found his own way here.
That makes him smarter
than your...
[dogs panting]
Sparky, get down!
Oh, my God,
what is he doing to my dog?
There he goes again.
Get down, Sparky, down!
Stan forgot to mention
that his dog
is a gay homosexual.
Make him stop!
[yelping]
[laughing] I'm sure glad
my dog isn't gay!
Yeah, maybe you should
name your dog Sparkette, Stan.
[laughing]
Gay dog.
And so you see, Simon and Simon
were not brothers in real life,
only on television.
Thank you
for that presentation, Eric,
but the assignment
was on Asian cultures.
You get a D-minus.
Aw, damn it!
Who should we call on
next, Mr. Hat?
How about Stan, our little
South Park quarterback star?
Oh, good idea.
Okay, Stanley, you're next.
Um, I'm not really prepared
either.
Well, just make something up
like Eric did.
Okay, um,
Asian culture has...
plagued our fragile Earth
for many years.
We must end it...
Excellent. A-minus!
Hey!
Wow, cool!
Wait a minute!
Why the hell does he get
an A-minus?
Eric, Stanley just might
lead our team to victory
against the Middle Park Cowboys
for the first time in decades.
And we treat star athletes
better
because they're better people.
That's not fair!
Life isn't fair, kiddo.
Get used to it.
Stupid puppet.
[bell rings]
Don't forget your assignments
tonight, children.
They're due tomorrow
for everybody but Stan.
Mr. Garrison,
can I ask you a question?
Of course, Stanley.
What is it?
What's a homosexual?
Oh, well, Stanley,
I guess you came
to the right person.
Sit down.
Stanley, gay people...
well, gay people are evil.
Evil right down
to their cold, black hearts,
which pump not blood
like yours and mine,
but rather a thick vomitus oil
that oozes through
their rotten veins
and clots
in their pea-sized brains,
which becomes the cause
of their Nazi-esque patterns
of violent behavior.
Do you understand?
I guess.
Good, I'm glad we could have
this little talk, Stanley.
Now you go outside
and practice football
like a good little heterosexual.
##
You guys see me
block that defense today?
I was kicking ass.
You're gonna need to
kick more ass than that
to beat the Cowboys.
Hey, speaking of pounding ass,
here comes Stan's
little homo dog!
Shut up, dude!
Sparky, where'd you get
that pink scarf?
[barks]
Man, that is the gayest dog
I have ever seen.
He just needs some training,
that's all.
Sit, Sparky.
Good boy.
Now shake.
Now don't be gay!
Don't be gay, Spark.
Don't be gay.
[grunts]
Did it work?
I don't know.
He still looks pretty gay to me.
Hey, Stan, your dog been
to any pride marches lately?
[laughing] Yeah, maybe you
should take him
to a Barbra Streisand concert.
[laughing]
Stupid little gay dog.
Gay dog.
Come on, you guys.
I have an idea.
##
I want $500
on the South Park cows.
Are you crazy?
No, sirree, I'm telling you,
I got the line.
My nephew Stan is
the best quarterback
the school's ever seen.
I guarantee
they'll beat the spread.
I'm gonna put all my money
on the Cows.
I'll put $300 on the Cows
too, if they guarantee...
Hey, I want to put some money
on the cows too.
Whoa, whoa!
Don't get too carried away, now.
You better be right
about this, Jimbo.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Uh, don't...
Don't worry yourself.
Are you sure Stan is that good?
Well, not that sure.
I think we better come up
with a backup plan.
Uh, let's see here.
Hey, bookie, what...
What's the halftime show
gonna be?
You haven't heard?
John Stamos' older brother
Richard Stamos
is gonna sing "Loving You".
I love that song.
"Loving you"?
That's perfect.
Come on, Ned,
Middle Park's gonna get
a halftime show
they'll never forget.
Okay, Sparky,
we got you a present.
Now why don't... damn it, Sparky,
where do you keep
getting this thing?
No pink bandana, Sparky.
Bad dog!
Now pay attention.
Sparky, this is Fifi.
Ooh la la!
There he goes.
Attaboy, Spark, get her!
Yes!
Ah, crap.
Now what do I do?
Who cares if your dog is gay?
Maybe it's not that bad.
No way, dude, my mom says
God hates gay people.
That's why he smote
the sodomies in France.
[mumbling]
I know, Mr. Garrison said
that homosexuals
are evil, but...
but Sparky doesn't seem evil.
Well, maybe Mr. Garrison
is wrong.
You should ask somebody else.
Like who?
And now back to "Jesus and Pals"
on South Park public access.
Yea, many of you
are seeking answers,
and I am the way for you,
my children.
Let's open the phone lines
back up
for some questions.
Hello, caller,
you're on the air.
Yeah, is... is this Jesus?
Yes, my son.
This is Robert
from Torrey Pines.
I called last week asking
for advice on my ex-wife.
Of course, Robert.
How are things now?
Everything is much
better, Jesus.
She hasn't mouthed off since.
I just wanted to thank you
for the advice.
Oh, and for...
For dying for my sins too.
That was really nice of you.
Blessed art thou, Robert.
Next caller, you're on the air.
Uh, hi, Jesus?
I have a dog, and he's a...
He's a homosexual.
My son,
a lot of people have wondered
what my stance
on homosexuality is,
so I'd like to state
once and for all
my true opinion.
You see...
That's all the time we have
left for "Jesus and Pals."
Now stay tuned for
"Marty's Movie Reviews."
Damn it!
What'd he say?
I got cut off for
Marty's stupid movie reviews!
Oh, "Marty's Movie Reviews"
are on? Kickass!
Isn't there anybody
who can help me?
Isn't there anybody who cares?
Come on, dude,
we have to get to practice.
No, it's not okay.
I don't want a gay dog.
I want a butch dog.
I want a Rin Tin Tin.
[sighs]
[melancholy music]
##
Now, children,
we've got to handle
the ball better.
You've got to hold your football
like you would hold your lover.
Gently, yet firmly.
[funky music]
You want to be both nurturing
and clinging at the same time.
Oh, yeah.
# Just like making sweet love
to the football #
# Be naughty with the football #
# Mmm #
Uh, Chef?
# Spank it #
# Ever so gently #
Chef?
# Spank it #
Chef!
Oh, uh, sorry, children.
Uh, let's run some plays.
Ah, Mr. Chef, sir?
No, Pip, we still don't
have a helmet for you.
Righto, but how about
I'll use a helmet today,
and one of the other
children goes without.
That wouldn't be very fair
to the other children,
now, would it?
Oh, I... I guess not.
What we want to do here, Carl,
is put a trigger on that bomb
that makes it go off
at a specific moment
during halftime.
And what moment would that be?
Well, John Stamos' older brother
is all set to sing "Loving you"
during halftime.
We want that bomb to go off
when he hits that high F.
What high F?
You know...
# Loving you #
# Is easy 'cause
you're beautiful #
# Doot'n-doot'n doo-doo #
# Ahh #
So you want the trigger
on the "doot'n doo"?
No, damn it, the "Ahh"!
# Ahh # # Ahh #
[all singing]
Great.
# Doot'ndoot'n doo-doo #
# Ahh # # Doot'n doodoo #
You got it.
# Doot'ndoot'n doo-doo #
Both: # Ahh #
All right. Yeah, okay.
What's the matter, Stan?
You seem down.
I just... I can't concentrate
'cause my dog is gay.
Well, you know what they say.
You can't teach a gay dog
straight tricks.
Oh, stop filling his head
with that queer-loving
propaganda.
Say what? You of all people
should be sympathetic.
What do you mean?
Well, you're gay, aren't you?
What? What the hell
are you talking about?
I am not gay!
Well, you sure do act like it!
I just act that way
to get chicks, dumb-ass.
What's the matter, dude?
I don't know where Sparky is.
He usually follows me
to football practice.
Maybe he went shopping
for some leather pants.
Ow!
[melancholy music]
##
[dramatic music]
Hello there, little pup!
I'm Big Gay Al.
Have you been outcast?
Well, then,
I'm so glad you found
my big gay animal sanctuary.
We're all big gay friends here.
Would you like to live with us?
Come on in, little fellow.
Nobody will ever oppress you
here.
Have you guys seen Sparky?
He still hasn't come back.
Wow, it's been, like, two days.
I think he might have run away.
Did you check
the shopping mall...
Ow!
We'll help you look for him
after the game, Stan.
I'm not playing.
You what?
I'm not playing
in that stupid game.
I have to find my dog.
Come on, Ned, keep quiet.
Okay.
Hello there, Enrique.
What are we doing here?
Well, Ned, we always
kidnap Middle Park's mascot.
But this year, we're gonna
booby-trap it instead,
and when John Stamos'
older brother
hits that high F
in "Loving You,"
boom!
No more Middle Park players.
[both laughing]
God damn, I love football!
Sparky, where are you?
Where could he be?
[marching band music]
[all cheering]
##
Hello, everyone,
this is Frank Hammond,
South Park Public Radio, AM 900.
Welcome to tonight's matchup
between the Middle Park Cowboys
and the South Park Cows.
Well, it looks like Chef,
the South Park Cows' coach,
is a little nervous.
This is probably because
his star quarterback
has yet to show up.
Oh, come on, Stan.
Uh, Mr. Chef,
if Stanley doesn't show up,
can I use his helmet?
No, Pip, I'm sorry!
Sparky!
Play ball!
You're gonna have to
quarterback, Kyle.
But I never practiced
quarterback.
It's a little late
for that bullcrap now.
Filling in for quarterback
is number 12,
Kyle "Broslovski."
Hey, hey,
where's little Stanley?
Yeah, why the hell is
that little Jewish kid
playing quarterback?
Ned, look.
They've got Enrique
on their sidelines.
And it looks like that bomb
is still attached.
Yay.
[wind whistling]
Hi, little fella,
how are you doing today?
Fine, how are you?
I'm super, thanks for asking.
My gay dog ran away
and I was wondering
if maybe he came here.
Well, let's see.
Come on in.
Do you have lots
of gay dogs here?
We have all sorts of
gay animals here
at Big Gay AI's.
Over here we have a gay lion.
Roar.
And we have gay water buffalo,
gay hummingbirds.
Here's a gaggle of gay gooses!
Hi, fellas,
it's so super to see you!
Wow, it seems like the
animals here are really happy.
Of course they are, silly buns!
It's the one place
where gay animals
can really be themselves.
Do you like to dance?
[electronic music playing]
Cartman, you hike me the ball,
then somebody run,
and I'll throw it or something.
Ready?
All: Break.
You guys are toast.
Yeah, we're gonna pound
your heads in.
We'll just see about that!
Set, set...
[farting]
Damn it, Cartman!
What's the matter?
Cartman farted!
No, I didn't!
That was just my shoes.
Come on, Kyle,
we'll get a delay of game
penalty!
No way, dude!
Hike the ball!
Oh, dude, weak.
That's right,
you get back there.
Hike!
The ball is snapped.
Middle Park blitzes.
[all shouting]
Fumble!
Middle Park gets the ball.
They run it in for a touchdown!
The score is 7-0,
Middle Park,
with 14:57 remaining
in the first quarter.
Hells bells.
I haven't seen
a beating like that
since Rodney King!
Now, Frank, that's not very PC.
You're gonna get us
in trouble again.
Right, right,
I... I got to watch that.
If we lose our money
'cause of your nephew,
we're gonna hang you
out to dry, Jimbo.
Don't y'all worry.
You just wait till halftime.
[chuckles]
##
Sparky!
Hiya, Sparky, how's it going?
[barks]
I missed you, old pal.
You really had me scared.
[barks]
Come on, let's go home.
I can still make it
in time for the game.
We can work on making you
not gay together.
##
Sparky?
Young man, it appears
you still don't understand.
What don't I understand?
Come this way.
I have to show you something.
With just over a minute to go
in the half,
the score is
Middle Park Cowboys 52,
South Park Cows, zero.
[all screaming]
Oh, my!
I haven't seen an Englishman
take a blow like that
since Hugh Grant!
Dude!
Now, that is not cool.
Sorry, sorry.
Okay, Stan, I think
you should get in line
for my big gay boat ride.
Step aboard, Stanley.
[percussive music]
Hello, everyone,
and welcome aboard
the big gay boat ride!
On this adventure,
we'll be seeing
the world of gayness
throughout time.
And the South Park Cows
are set to receive.
There's the kick.
It's taken by number 23,
Kenny McCormick.
He's at the 50,
the 40, the 30...
[all shouting]
The little running back is down!
I think he's...
yes, he's been decapitated!
[gasps] Oh, my God,
they killed Kenny!
You bastards!
That's got to hurt, Frank!
Ouch-eroo!
Hey, come on,
that was roughing!
At least let us
scrape him off the field!
Looks like the South Park Cows
aren't even gonna beat
the 72-point spread,
not by a long shot.
You see, gayness has existed
since the beginning of time,
from the Egyptian pharaohs,
to the shoguns of Japan.
Uh-oh, look out,
it's the oppressors!
Christians and Republicans
and Nazis, oh my!
[gunshot]
Oh! Oh, gosh, that was close.
Okay, let's steer
our big gay boat out of here
and into a place where gays
are allowed to live freely.
All: # We are gay
and it's okay #
# 'Cause gay means happy
and happy means gay #
# We're not sad anymore #
# 'Cause we're out
the closet door #
# It's okay to be gay #
So what do you think, Stan?
This kicks ass.
I'm sorry I tried
to change you, Spark.
I just didn't understand.
Isn't this precious?
And now here to sing
the touching song
"Loving You"
is the one and only,
John Stamos' brother!
All right, Richard!
[piano music]
# Loving you #
# Is easy
'cause you're beautiful #
# Doot'n-doot'n doo-doo #
[off-key]
# Ahh #
What the hell?
He didn't sing the high F!
Richard Stamos
can't sing a high F.
He always screws it up
like this.
Ned, we are gonna
get our asses kicked!
# La, la, la, la, la #
It's obvious where
all the talent
in that family went!
Thanks for everything,
Big Gay Al.
[barks]
No problem, kids.
Are you sure
you don't want to stay
for some toasted
cheese sandwiches?
No thanks.
I've got to get back
for the big football game.
Come on, boy.
Oh, Stan...
when you get back to town,
tell them about us, will you?
Tell them there are
gay animals here
who need homes, desperately.
I will, Big Gay Al.
I will.
Oh, my carrot cake.
And these South Park Cows
are being absolutely
molested by Middle Park.
I haven't seen so many
children molested since...
I thought you said
beating the spread
was a sure thing, Jimbo!
Yeah, we all put our
life savings in this game!
You're a dead man, Jimbo!
Well, this should
just about wrap it up for...
Wait a minute, what's this?
Yeah! Yoo-hoo!
It's Stan, the South Park
star quarterback.
Where the hell
have you been, Stan?
I've been getting
my best friend back.
Just get in there, boy.
Give 'em hell, Stanley!
Jesus... now, I haven't
asked you for much.
But all we need is
one little score.
Please, please, Jesus.
Leave me alone.
Hike!
Stan hikes the ball.
He steps back to pass.
Hey, Stan, I'm open I think.
And he throws it to Kyle,
the little Jewish kid.
Oh, my!
I haven't seen a Jew
run like that
since Poland, 1938!
Dude!
Touchdown!
Yeah!
Whoo!
The clock runs out,
and the final score is
Middle Park Cowboys 73,
South Park Cows 6.
South Park beats the spread.
Yeah! Yoo-hoo!
Speech!
Stan, what do you want
to tell the world
about this stunning
almost victory?
Uh, it's really cool
that we beat the spread
against the Cowboys.
Yeah, all right!
And maybe we can beat 'em
even more next year.
Whoo!
And it's okay to be gay.
What?
Being gay is just part of nature
and a beautiful thing.
What the hell is
he talking about?
Uh, Stanley, you arrived
very late in the game.
Where were you that whole time?
I was with my new friend,
Big Gay Al.
He showed me
his big gay animal sanctuary
and took me
on a big gay boat ride,
where I learned all about
the wonders of gaiety.
It's true.
I'll show you.
But it was here.
It was all right here.
There... there was
a techno dance club.
Stan, you need to lay off
the cough syrup.
All right?
Seriously.
I'm worried about you, man.
Oliver!
I thought you ran away
all those months ago.
Sidney!
Willie!
Carlos!
I want to thank you so much
for bringing everybody here.
Oh, there you are, dude.
How's it going?
I'm super, thanks for asking.
It looks like now
my work here is done.
Good-bye, Stanley.
Peace be with you.
Wow!
[shimmering tone]
You guys, you guys!
I can do it.
Do what?
# Loving you #
# Is easy 'cause
you're beautiful #
# Doot'n-doot'n doo-doo #
Both: No!
# Ahh #
# Now you're a man #
# A man, man, man #
# Now you're a man, man #
# Man, man, man, man, man #
# Now you're a man #
# M-A-N, man #
# Man, man, man, man #
# Now you're a man #