I know a certain
kitty-kitty
who's sleeping
with mommy tonight.
[laughter]
That is a hoot and a holler.
This next episode
is by far our favorite.
It's called "Volcano."
In it, the boys go camping
with Stan's uncle Jimbo
and his friend Ned.
While camping, they encounter
a strange creature
in a deadly volcano.
I think the reason
that this episode is,
well, Scratch's favorite anyway
is because it deals
with an issue
that is really important
to Matt and I.
You see, we grew up
in the Colorado Rockies,
and there black bear
hunting is illegal.
Well, a few years ago
a man shot a black bear
and her two cubs out of a tree.
When taken to jail the man said,
"Well, they were coming
right for us,"
but he'd shot the black bears
out of a tree,
so it was ridiculous.
That's not funny.
What America's
really dying to know is,
is there really a Scuzzlebutt?
People have to understand,
these are all works of fiction.
There's no such thing as aliens.
There's no such thing
as Scuzzlebutt.
And there's no such thing
as Patrick Duffy.
What happened to Ned to cause
him to speak the way he does?
Well, Ned is actually
our favorite character
in all of South Park.
He had a laryngectomy
from smoking too much
and got throat cancer.
[imitating electronic speech]
So now he talks like this.
I guess we can all take
a lesson from Ned.
So sit back, relax
and enjoy "Volcano."
[gentle music]
[upbeat music]
# I'm going down to South Park #
# Gonna have myself a time #
Both: # Friendly
faces everywhere #
# Humble folks
without temptations #
# I'm going down to South Park #
# Gonna leave my woes behind #
# Ample parking day or night #
# People spouting
"Howdy neighbor" #
# Heading on up to South Park #
# Gonna see if I can't unwind #
# [muffled singing] #
# So come on
down to South park #
# And meet some friends
of mine #
Now you be careful, Eric.
The woods can be very dangerous.
Okay, Mom.
Ready to go hunting, Cartman?
Yeah, my Uncle Jimbo says
we gotta get up there early.
Right, Uncle Jimbo?
That's right, Stanley.
Animals are much easier
to shoot in the morning.
Here, hon.
I packed you Cheesy Poofs
and Happy Tarts.
Don't worry, Miss Cartman,
we'll take care of him.
I brought my old war buddy,
Ned, to keep things safe.
Hello, Mrs. Cartman.
How are you today?
Be sure to use
lots of bug spray,
and if you have
to poo-poo,
don't wipe with poison ivy.
[laughter]
Dude, that's sick, Mom!
And I know it can get scary
up in those woods,
but just remember,
Mommy's not far away.
[laughter]
Drive! Drive!
You give your mommy a kissy.
Drive the car, damn it!
Drive!
"Don't get scared up
in the mountains, Cartman."
Shut up!
I'm not scared of nothing.
Maybe your mom can give me
a kiss too, Cartman.
[muffled speech]
Oh, oh!
That's disgusting.
You piece of crap!
I'll kill you!
That's the spirit, boys.
Let's get that
testosterone flowing.
Yeeh!
Now, boys, boys, I need
to get serious for a minute.
I want you to understand
a few basic rules of hunting,
since this is your first time.
First of all, don't
ever walk with your gun
unless the safety's on.
Second, don't shoot anything
that looks human.
And third, never spill your
beer in the bullet chamber.
Uh, Uncle Jimbo,
we don't drink beer.
You what?!
Yeah, that's right,
I don't think eight-year-old
kids drink beer.
I like chocolate milk!
Well, we'll be doing plenty
of drinking on this trip.
After all,
hunter sober is like...
Fishing... sober.
It sure will be nice
to get out of the city
for a while,
away from civilization.
Well, here we are.
Okay, each of you young'uns
take a gun, a beer,
and some smokes.
Hey, I didn't get a gun.
Sweet. This is like
the gun I used in 'Nam.
You weren't in Vietnam, Cartman.
Were you stationed in Da Nang?
Cartman always
makes stuff up, Ned.
You can't believe
anything he says.
Hey, I'll blow
your freaking head off.
Hey, look out, son.
That's dangerous.
You're gonna spill your beer.
My Uncle Jimbo
says that after this
he's gonna take me
hunting in Africa.
Wow, that'll be cool.
My mom says there's a lot
of black people in Africa.
Boys, lookie there.
That there is
a Rocky Mountain black bear.
One of the few remaining
of its kind.
Isn't it beautiful?
My God,
it's coming right for us!
Hey, it wasn't
coming right for us.
It was just sitting there.
Shh, not so loud.
Now that there
is just a technicality.
What do you mean?
You see, boys,
the Democrats have passed
a lot of laws
trying to stop us from hunting.
Democrats piss me off!
They say we can't shoot
certain animals anymore
unless they're posing
an immediate threat.
Therefore,
before we shoot something,
we have to say,
"It's coming right for us."
Wow, you're smart, Uncle Jimbo.
Jimbo, look.
Oh, it's a deer.
Looks like about
a 45-gauge, Ned.
It's coming right for us!
Kickass!
Did you see that?
I was imperiled by
that ferocious, charging buck.
Rabbit, rabbit, five o'clock.
Let's move!
Move!
Is this hunting?
I guess so.
Uh, dude, I'm starting
to have flashbacks.
What?
Stand forth, pull up flank.
Look out for Charlies
up in the trees.
This one's yours, Stan.
It's coming right for us.
Shoot it, Stan.
I got your back, soldier.
I can't.
What the...
What's wrong with you?
I don't wanna shoot the bunny.
What the hell
are you talking about,
you don't wanna shoot the bunny?
You're babbling,
you're not making any sense.
You're hysterical.
I'm not hysterical.
I just don't wanna
shoot the bunny.
No nephew of mine
is gonna be a tree-hugger.
Yeah, hippie,
go back to Woodstock
if you can't shoot anything.
I can shoot you, fatass!
I can shoot you, too!
I'll kill you!
I'll fill you full of lead!
[rumbling]
Hey, what's that?
[humming]
##
[snores]
Hmm?
What the heck is this?
Yeah, Frank.
It's Randy.
Uh-huh. Good.
Yeah, listen,
the little needle is moving.
Yeah, it's going
back and forth really fast.
What does that mean?
Uh-huh?
Uh-huh.
Let me check.
Yeah, it's smoking.
Uh-huh.
Oh, really?
Really?
Oh, my God, a volcano.
[dramatic musical sting]
##
[slurps, sighs]
My weenies won't cook.
This wood won't burn.
Well, Ned, looks like
we'll have to use
the old Indian fire trick.
Yep.
[yelling]
[laughs]
Hey, stop, drop and roll, Ned.
Both: Whoa!
God damn it, Ned.
I just got that van.
How the hell are we
supposed to get home?
Oh, it hurts, it hurts!
Hey, you guys.
This works pretty good
right now.
But you see, Mr. Mayor,
you can't stop serving
Salisbury steak
in our public schools.
What's next, meatloaf?
We are quite aware
of your concerns, Chef, but...
Mayor, the geologist
is here to see you.
My geologist? Now?
Tell him the infection is fine
and I don't need
another checkup.
No, Mayor, that's
a gynecologist.
A geologist studies the earth.
Don't you think I know that?
How dare you insult
my intellect.
I went to Princeton
for God's sake.
You get out of my office.
I'm not in your office, Mayor.
I'm talking to you
through a speaker.
Just send in the geometrist.
Geologist.
You are fired, buddy!
Thank you, Mayor. It's
been great working for you.
Mayor, we've got
a very big problem.
Mount Evanson is about to erupt.
[dramatic musical sting]
What does this mean to the town?
Well, this graph shows
everything from normal to bad.
Right now, South Park is here.
[dramatic musical sting]
##
My God.
Mayor, some of
the school children
are up camping
on that mountain right now.
Oh, this is big.
Johnson, Johnson, are you there?
Uh, you just fired
Johnson, Mayor.
I'm his replacement, Ted.
Ted, we have got
a major crisis here.
I want you to get
on the phone and call
"Inside Edition," "Rescue 911,"
oh, and
"Entertainment Tonight."
You better get
my stylist on the phone, too.
Don't worry.
Things are under control.
And then Ned picked
up the grenade and... boom!
Blasted his arm clear off.
We spent three hours
looking for that damn arm,
but it was never to be found.
Some say it's still
crawling around to this day.
[growls]
[laughter]
Ha, gotcha!
Heh, that's not scary.
You were scared, Cartman.
You almost peed your pants.
Shut up!
I didn't pee my pants.
Hey, Ned, hand me that gin.
You boys want to tie one on?
No, no thanks.
That stuff tastes like pee.
Yeah, Cartman's pee.
Hey, you would taste my pee.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Can't you have a little alcohol?
Christ, look at that
little bastard go!
Now you see that, Stan?
Now that is
a dirty little bastard.
Hey, I'm a dirty
little bastard, too.
Hey, you guys,
I know a scary story.
Shut up, Cartman.
You can't scare anybody.
Oh, yeah?
You guys ever heard
of Scuzzlebutt?
What-lebutt?
Scuzzlebutt is a creature
that lives up
on this very mountain
and kills anybody
who dares climb to the top.
Why?
Because it loves
the taste of blood
and likes to add pieces
to its deformed body.
Deformed how?
Well, on his left arm
instead of a hand, he has...
A hook.
A knife.
No, a piece of celery.
Celery?
Yes, and he walks with a limp,
because one of
his legs is missing.
And where his leg should be,
there's nothing but...
Patrick Duffy.
Patrick Duffy?
Damn it, Cartman,
that's not scary.
What do you mean? Have you
ever seen "Step by Step?"
So he lives alone
on this mountain
and weaves baskets
and other assorted crafts.
They say that on quiet nights
you can hear him weaving
his baskets.
Ka-shink, ka-shink, ka-shink.
Cartman, you suck
at telling scary stories.
Yeah, give me that flashlight.
[muffled speech]
[rumbling]
What's that?
Maybe it's Scuzzlebutt
coming to weave us
into wicker baskets.
Hey, it might be.
Gosh, I hope he doesn't
cut me with his celery hand.
[laughter]
Screw you guys!
Fatass!
Go to hell!
Hey, Ned, why don't you whip
out the old cancer kazoo.
Let's do a little song.
# Kumbaya, my Lord #
# Kumbaya #
# Oh Lord, Kumbaya #
# Someone's crying, Lord,
Kumbaya #
They don't think
Scuzzlebutt is scary, huh?
Let's see how they like it
when they actually
see Scuzzlebutt.
I'll scare the hell
out of them tomorrow.
# Someone's crying, Lord,
Kumbaya #
# Oh Lord, Kumbaya #
[rooster crows]
Stan, Stan, wake up.
What, dude?
I don't know where Cartman is.
I think something took him away.
Where's my Uncle Jimbo and Ned?
They're out fishing with Kenny.
With Kenny? But this is
supposed to be my camping trip.
Why do they like Kenny so much?
Doesn't he like me anymore?
Well, Stan, you want
to know what I think?
What?
[farts]
What a beautiful morning
for fishing.
There's one.
There's a fish right there.
Got it.
Great instincts, boy.
Uncle Jimbo, Cartman's missing.
Who?
The fat kid?
Yeah.
Ah, hell.
I guess we better
go look for him.
Ned, you gotta cut it short.
Fire out the 12-20.
Well, I think
that's about the limit
for our fishing permit.
Oh, man, it smells
like dead fish.
[muffled speech]
Oh, man, that is nasty.
Yeah, I don't think
I've ever seen a kid
as cool as you, Kenny.
I'm making you
my honorary nephew.
[muffled speech]
[somber music]
The people of South Park
are humble and friendly,
but now a ticking
time bomb of hot lava
waits to engulf these people
and end their miserable lives
with one last fleeting moment
of excruciatingly painful,
burning agony.
Hey, I'm on TV!
I'm on TV!
Mayor, what are you doing
to prepare for this
inevitable catastrophe?
All we know right now
is that some of our children
are camping on that mountain
and... uh, I'm sorry.
Can I start over?
Huh?
You can edit this, right?
Ready? Three, two, one.
All we know right now
is that some of our children
are up camping on that mountain.
We can't do anything
until we get them.
Okay, people,
let's go get those kids!
Come on, everybody.
You gotta help the children.
Well, he couldn't have gone far.
Unless something drug him off.
There's not many animals
out today, Jimbo.
Yeah, it's almost like
something funny's going on.
[rumbling]
Christ, Ned, what'd
you have for breakfast?
I don't know, man.
I've got some bad gas.
Wait, there's a ram.
It's coming right for us!
Nice shooting, Kenny!
Here, you need a bigger gun.
Look!
I am Scuzzlebutt,
Lord of the mountains.
Behold my Patrick Duffy leg.
What is it?
Dude, it's Scuzzlebutt!
Cartman wasn't lying.
Holy crow! We could make
a mint killing this thing.
We'll be on the cover
of "Guns & Ammo."
This calls for some HJ-14.
[chuckles] Those guys
are totally scared.
Fire in the hole!
Holy crap!
Damn it, I think I missed.
What the hell
is wrong with you people?
Come on, let's move!
Move!
Wait, wait, ahhh!
Is it on?
Okay.
Okay, people, form groups
and search the mountain.
Report back here every hour.
You got that?
Mayor, I might have an idea.
Oh, what?
Well, if we can dig
a very large trench,
we can divert the lava
into a canyon,
and then it would bypass South
Park pretty much completely.
And that would be good, right?
I'm pretty sure.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Okay, people, change of plans.
Half of you grabs shovels.
These look like his tracks.
He must have gone this way.
Ned, prepare some HK-12
and some Plasticine.
I'll bet that sucker is headed
for a higher elevation.
The higher up it... bird!
The higher up it goes,
the better it can breathe.
Look, up there!
You guys, it's just me.
Are we sure it's Scuzzlebutt?
Does it have
Patrick Duffy for a leg?
I can't tell.
Let's kill it.
Got to get out
of this stupid costume.
Kenny, you take the front.
No, I can do it, Uncle Jimbo.
I want to bag that animal.
That's the spirit, kiddo.
Let's hunt!
You guys, you guys,
I was just kidding!
As some people of South Park
try desperately
to save their mountain town,
others look
for the missing townspeople.
But all must take
every precaution necessary.
Okay, people, listen up.
As we near the top
of the mountain,
the chances of our encountering
some lava becomes great.
Therefore,
I have special ordered
this training film to assist us
in volcano safety.
Mr. Garrison,
if you would, please.
[cheerful music]
Harbingers of sorrow,
natural disasters can be
the cause of troubling
and undesirable stress,
and a volcano is no exception.
But what should you do
if a volcano erupts near you
or your family?
Here, we see the Stephens Family
enjoying... Sunday picnic.
But suddenly,
daughter hears a noise.
It's a volcano.
Junior seems worried.
But have no fear, Junior.
Jane learned in school
what to do
when you hear a volcano erupt.
That's right, Jane,
duck and cover.
[rumbling]
So what will... do when you
hear a volcano erupting?
That's right, duck and cover.
Looks like you got the idea.
Duck and cover.
Thank you and good-bye.
Okay, any questions?
That has got to be
the most ridiculous
load of pig crap
I have ever seen.
That's enough out of you!
I'm gonna bag Scuzzlebutt,
then we'll see
who's a little bastard.
Hey, seriously, you guys!
Kill it, Stan.
Kill it.
Come on, Stan, kill it!
Oh, damn it, I can't do it!
You pansy!
Give me that gun.
Hey!
Cartman?
God damn it, don't shoot me!
What the Sam Hill?
I was just trying
to scare you guys.
You can put the gun down now.
So much for the cover
of "Guns & Ammo."
Yepper,
but I think we've learned
some important lessons, Ned. I think...
Whoa!
Holy crap.
The mountain,
it's blown its top!
[rumbling]
Oh, my God, they killed Kenny!
No, I'm okay.
[screaming]
Look, the volcano.
Quick, duck and cover!
[all screaming]
That lava is coming
right for us.
Oh, no, look.
What the hell is this
trench doing here?
We can't get across!
It now looks
as if the missing children
are trapped in the path
of hot, nasty lava.
God, please deliver
those darling kids from...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Three, two and one.
God, please deliver...
Help!
[grumbles]
[dramatic music]
Jiminy, it's the real
Scuzzlebutt!
What?
Scuzzlebutt's real?
Oh, my God!
Look at his leg!
Hi, kids,
I'm TV's Patrick Duffy.
Quick, Ned, shoot it!
[gun clicks]
Oh, no, out of ammo.
[grumbles]
What is that thing?
That's Scuzzlebutt.
Yeah, he has Patrick Duffy
for a leg and weaves baskets.
This isn't happening.
Everyone look away, please.
Nothing to see here.
Well, boys, I'm sorry
I got you all killed.
##
Ahhh!
Whoa, he built a wicker basket.
Hey, he's saving us.
[grumbles]
Scuzzlebutt saved the day.
And my calculations worked.
The lava's following
the trench into the canyon.
Hmm, where exactly
does the canyon go?
Uh...
[all screaming]
South Park is saved.
Hey, look, Kenny's okay.
[muffled speech]
And now these humble people
can rejoice and celebrate
their jovial victory
over nature.
I'm getting word that the chef
of the school cafeteria
wants to sing a song about this
thrilling struggle of humanity.
# Ooh baby every time
that we kiss #
# Hot lava #
# Every time that
we make love, hot lava #
# Hot lava #
# Lava so hot
it makes me sweat #
# Lava so warm and red and wet #
# Lava #
Mayor, what do you have to say
about this wonderful outcome?
Well, we owe everything
to this friendly,
yet misunderstood creature.
Thank you, Scuzzlebutt.
Friend.
Oh, how sweet.
I did it, I did it!
I finally killed something.
Oh, my God, what has he done?
Turn off the cameras.
Hey, that was easy.
No!
Why, God?
Why?
Damn it, Stan.
You shouldn't have done that.
What, why?
Yeah, make up your mind, dude.
Stan, some things you kill
and some things you don't. See?
No.
Only now, in this late hour,
do I see the folly of guns.
I'll never use a gun again.
[gunshot]
[muffled screaming]
But I just wanted you
to be proud of me,
like you were with Kenny.
But Kenny's dead now, Stan.
And you're always gonna
be my nephew.
And you just
can't kill anything.
You understand?
Dude, I don't
understand hunting at all.
Yeah, it's stupid.
Let's go watch cartoons.
Yeah, cartoons kick ass.