♪ The Simpsons ♪
(tires screech)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(screeches)
Here's your
caption boys:
"Local hero shuns spotlight
and pitches in."
What an angle.
I can't believe I'm spending
my Saturday picking up garbage.
I mean, half these bottles
ain't even mine.
(clears throat)
Let's have less conversation
and more sanitation.
(all grumbling)
Hey, where's Homer?
How'd he get
out of this?
HOMER:
Hey, everybody!
Up here!
Simpson, stop frolicking
and get to work.
Right away, Mr. Smithers.
I'll just walk across
these slippery ro... aah!
Oh, no! He's going
over the falls!
Oh, good. He snagged
that tree branch.
Oh, no!
The branch broke off.
Oh, good. He can grab on
to them pointy rocks.
Oh, no!
Them rocks broke
his arms and legs.
Oh, good.
Those helpful beavers
are swimming out
to save him.
Oh, no.
They're biting him
and stealing his pants.
Good Lord. He'll be sucked
into the turbine.
(all gasp)
Smithers,
Who was that corpse?
Homer Simpson, sir.
(sniffling)
One of the finest,
bravest men
ever to grace Sector 7G.
(sobbing)
I'll cross him
off the list.
(Bart laughing)
That dummy worked
like a charm, Dad.
Best 600 bucks
I ever spent.
Come on, boy.
We've earned this Saturday.
Now let's make
the most of it!
61, 62, 63...
Marge, we can't tell you
how sorry we are.
You have our deepest
condol-diddly-olences.
I'm sorry.
I-I'm just nervous.
I didn't mean
any disrespect.
What are you talking about?
You know, uh...
Homer's passing.
Away.
Into death.
What?
That's ridiculous.
Homer's not dead.
He's right out back
in the hammock.
Oh, Marge, of course
Homer's alive.
He's alive in
all our hearts.
Yes, Marge.
I can see him.
Hi, everybody.
Marge, I'm going to
give you the card
of our juvenile
counselor.
(doorbell rings)
A tombstone?
It came with
the burial plot.
But that's
not important.
The important thing is,
Homer's dead.
We've been saving for this
since your wedding day.
Get out of here
you ghouls!
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi.
Hmm?
Uh, excuse me.
Sir, I think there's
been a mistake.
Oh, no. No mistake.
Your electricity's
in the name
of Homer J. Simpson,
deceased.
The juice stays off till you
get a job or a generator.
Oh, and, uh, my
deepest sympathies.
Mmm... Homer?
That's my name.
When I asked you
if that dummy
was to fake your own
death, you told me no.
You go downtown first
thing in the morning
and straighten this out.
LISA:
Mom! Dad!
Bart ran into a doorframe
and bit his tongue!
BART: What the hell'th
goin' on heah?
Listen here. My name
is Homer J. Simpson.
You guys think I'm dead,
but I'm not.
Now I want you
to straighten this out
without a lot of your bureaucratic
red tape and mumbo jumbo.
Okay, Mr. Simpson
I'll just make the change
here... and you're all set.
I don't like your attitude,
you water-cooler dictator.
What do you have in that
secret government file, anyway?
I have a right to read it.
You sure do.
"Wife: Marjorie.
Children: Bartholomew,
Lisa..."
Ah-hah! See? This thing
is all screwed up.
Who the heck
is "Margaret" Simpson?
Uh... your youngest daughter.
(mimicking)
"Uh... your youngest daughter."
Well, how about this?
This thing says
my mother's still alive!
She died when I was a kid!
You see that stone angel
up there?
That's my mother's grave.
My Dad points it out
every time we drive by.
Mr. Simpson, uh...
maybe you should actually
go up there.
Huh?
Oh, Mom, I'm sorry
I never come to see you.
I'm just not a cemetery person.
"Here lies...
Walt Whitman"?
(yelling)
Damn you, Walt Whitman!
I-hate-you-
Walt-freakin'-Whitman!
Leaves of Grass, my ass!
Wait a minute.
Maybe it's that other grave--
the one that says "Simpson"!
(shrieking)
Oh!
Why does my death
keep coming back to haunt me?
Oh!
You awful, awful man!
Get out of my son's grave!
I hate to rain on your parade,
lady, but this is my grave.
Hey...
wait a minute...
Mom?
Homer?
I thought you were dead!
Oh, dang blast it.
Isn't anybody in this
dad-gummed cemetery dead?
I didn't want
to cause a fuss
but now that
you mention it...
Oh, Homer, you
grew up so handsome.
Some people say
I look like Dan Aykroyd.
I can't believe
you're here.
Dad always told me you died
while I was at the movies.
Oh, my poor baby.
You must have been so upset.
But I suppose Abe
has his reasons.
Yeah, well... where have you
been all this time?
Oh, it's a very
complicated story.
Let's just enjoy
this moment.
Mom, there's something
you should know about me.
I almost always
spoil the moment.
(burping)
I'm sorry.
That's okay, darling.
It wasn't your fault.
Hey, everybody, I got
a big surprise for you.
Presenting... my mother!
(gasps)
Your mother?
That's Grandma Simpson?
Can you
believe it?
I thought
she was dead.
Hello.
This is so weird.
It's like something
out of Dickens
or Melrose Place.
Where have you
been, Granny?
Did they freeze
you or something?
(laughing)
Oh, my,
such clever grandchildren.
So full of questions
and bright, shiny eyes.
I don't know what to say.
I finally have a mother-in-law.
(giggling)
No more living vicariously
through my girlfriends.
(giggles and coughs)
Hey.
Since you
were a no-show
at all the big
moments of my life,
you owe me years
of back presents.
Christmases, birthdays, Easters,
Kwanzas, good report cards...
Hmm. 75 bucks a pop
plus interest and penalties...
You owe me $22,000.
I'll Kwanza you!
Gaa! Gaa!
Homer, don't be so hard
on little...
(whispering)
What is his name?
This is my room.
This is my dresser.
It's where I keep my shirts
when I'm not wearing them.
Oh, yes,
right in the drawers.
(both laughing)
You remembered.
Oh, I've missed moments
like this... Mom.
I saw all
your awards, Lisa.
They're mighty impressive.
Oh, I just keep them
out to bug Bart.
Don't be bashful.
When I was your age,
kids made fun of me
because I read at
the ninth-grade level.
Me too!
Hey, Mom, look at me!
Look at what I can do!
I see you, Homer.
That's very nice.
Although I hardly consider
"A Separate Peace"
the ninth-grade level.
Yeah, more like preschool.
I hate John Knowles.
Me too.
(both laughing)
(both sighing)
Mom, you're not
looking!
You know, Lisa,
I feel like I have
an instant rapport with you.
(gasps)
You didn't dumb it down.
You said "rapport."
Got to run.
Grandma stuff.
Huh?
(turns dryer on)
There. Now no one should
be able to hear us.
What?
(turns dryer off)
All right, we don't
need the dryer.
What?!
Just shut up and listen.
There's something
fishy about Grandma.
Whenever we ask her where
she's been all this time
she changes the subject.
And just now when a
police car drove by
she ran into the house.
Yeah, I don't
trust her, either.
When I was going
through her purse
look what I found.
LISA:
"Mona Simpson."
"Mona Stevens."
"Martha Stewart."
"Penelope Olsen."
"Muddy Mae Suggins."
These are the calling cards
of a con artist.
Whoo-hoo!
I'm so glad
to have my Mom back.
I never realized
how much I missed her.
She's nice.
But?
I just don't think
you should get too excited
about the woman who
abandoned you for 25 years.
You could get hurt again.
First, it wasn't 25 years.
It was 27 years.
And second, she had
a very good reason.
Which was?
I don't know.
I guess I was
just a horrible son
(crying)
and no mother would want me.
Oh, Homie.
Come on, you're a sweet,
kind, loving man.
I'm sure you were
a wonderful son.
Then why did she leave me?
Let's find out.
Mother Simpson,
we'd like to ask you
a few questions
about your past.
Can't reminisce.
Sleeping.
(snoring)
Spill it, Muddy Mae,
or we're calling the cops.
Please don't.
Alright, then we'll call
your husband-- Grampa.
No! I'll talk.
I'll tell you everything.
I've wanted to tell you.
It all started in the '60s.
Take out wrenched ankle.
(buzzing)
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Oh, my little Homie Bear.
Time for bed.
Sing me my
bedtime song, Mom.
♪ Ooey, gooey,
rich and chewy inside ♪
♪ Golden, flaky,
tender, cakey outside ♪
♪ Wrap the inside
in the outside ♪
♪ Is it good? ♪
Darn tootin'.
♪ Doing the big Fig Newton ♪
Here's the tricky part.
(snoring)
Abe, isn't Homer cute?
Probably. I'm trying
to watch the Super Bowl.
If people don't support this thing,
it might not make it.
Joe Willie Namath
swaggering off the field
his sideburns an apogee
of sculpted sartorium.
The foppish follicles pioneered
by Ambrose Burnside
Appomattox, 1865.
("Sunshine of Your Love"
plays)
MONA:
His wild, untamed facial hair
revealed a new world
of rebellion, of change
a world where doors were
open for women like me.
But Abe was stuck
in his button-down
plastic-fantastic
Madison Avenue scene.
Look at them sideburns.
He looks like a girl.
Now, Johnny Unitas--
there's a haircut
you could set your watch to.
So Mother Simpson,
where did your newfound sense
of irresponsibility
take you?
I soon found people
who shared my views
at the state college.
(all chanting)
Anthrax, gangrene, swimmer's ear
get your germ lab out of here.
How could I
not become a radical
when we were fighting
a force of pure evil?
(all chanting)
Hey, hey, Mr. Burns
enough already with the germs.
Their flower power is
no match for my glower power.
Ooh!
That's some
nice glowering, Mr. B.
We'd met the enemy
and it was Montgomery Burns.
Drastic action had
to be taken to stop
his war machine.
I put Homer to bed, Abe,
and now I'm going out.
It could be a late night.
I'm meeting my destiny.
So long.
("Along the Watchtower" plays)
When this baby goes off
Burns' lab is going
to be history, man.
Germ history!
(laughing)
Oh, man,
I got the munchies.
(ringing)
(coughing)
No! No!
Wait a minute.
(inhales)
Bronchial tubes clearing.
Asthma disappearing.
Acne... remains.
But asthma disappearing.
(alarm ringing)
My germs.
My precious germs.
They never harmed a soul.
They never even had a chance.
Whoever did this
will never get past me!
(all yelling)
You poor man.
Let me help you up.
You
just made a very
big mistake.
You'll spend the rest
of your life in pri--
My asthma's gone.
Listen to me breathe.
(snorting)
Wah!
From that moment on
my life as I knew it was over.
Only one member
of the Springfield Seven
was identified.
She's been described as a woman
in her early 30s
yellow complexion
and may be extremely helpful.
For Channel Six News,
I'm Kenny Brockelstein.
Homer?
(sobbing)
I'll miss you, Homer.
I thought I dreamed that kiss.
(sniffling)
I'm so sorry
I misjudged you, Mom.
You had to leave
to protect your family.
How did you survive?
Oh, I had help from
my friends in the underground.
Jerry Rubin
gave me a job
marketing his line
of health shakes.
I proofread Bobby
Seale's cookbook
and I ran credit checks
at Tom Hayden's
Porsche dealership.
Wait a minute.
There's one thing
I don't understand.
In all those years, why didn't
you ever try to contact me?
But I did.
I sent you a care package
every week.
Aw come on, Mom.
We use that same line
on the kids
when they're at camp.
But I did. I really did.
I'll prove it to you.
Any undelivered mail
for Homer J. Simpson?
No... oh, wait. This.
That's what happens
when you don't tip your
letter carrier at Christmas.
Yes, I'd like to send
this letter
to the Prussian consulate
in Siam by aeromail.
Am I too late
for the 4:30 auto-gyro?
Uh... I better look
in the manual.
Oh, the ignorance.
Wait a minute.
I know that woman.
But from when,
and in what capacity?
(gasping)
It's her.
At last.
This book must
be out of date.
I don't see Prussia,
Siam or auto-gyro.
Well, keep looking.
(gasps)
Are you sure this is the woman
you saw in the Post Office?
Absolutely.
Who could forget
such a monstrous visage?
She has the sloping brow
and cranial bumpage
of the career criminal.
Uh, sir, phrenology
was dismissed
as quackery
160 years ago.
Of course,
you'd say that
You have the brainpan
of a stagecoach tilter.
At any rate, the F.B.I.
will track down
this mystery woman
and put her behind bars.
How does it happen, Joe?
How does what
happen?
How does a sweet young lady
mortgage her future for
a bunch of scraggly ideals
and greasy-haired promises?
Maybe she thought the war on
southeast Asia was so immoral
her end justified the means.
Gee, Joe, you haven't
been the same
since your son went
crazy in Vietnam.
It's a pain that never ends.
(Dragnet theme playing)
♪ How many roads
must a man walk down ♪
♪ Before you can
call him a man? ♪
Seven!
No, Dad, it's
a rhetorical question.
Rhetorical, eh?
Eight.
Dad, do you even know
what "rhetorical" means?
Do I know what
"rhetorical" means?
(doorbell rings)
Quick, Grandma, hide!
(pounding)
(crashing)
No door is going to keep me
from my meddlin'.
Stand up straight, Bart.
Abe?
What the...
Now, here's a piece
of bad news.
Oh, Abe.
You've aged terribly.
What do you expect?
You left me to raise
the boy on my own.
I had to leave, but you didn't
have to tell Homer I was dead!
It was either that
or tell him
his mother was
a wanted criminal.
You were a rotten wife
and I'll never,
ever forgive you.
Can we have sex?
Please?
Oh, Abe.
Well, I tried.
What's for supper?
Yeah, I might have seen her.
It's hard to tell
from this old picture,
you know?
Well, according to our
computer-aging program
she should look about...
25 years older.
Yeah, I seen her.
Uh, that is to say,
I saw her.
Look at me, Grandma.
I'm a hippie.
Peace, man. Groovy.
Bomb Vietnam!
Four more years!
Up with people!
You know, Grandma, I used
to think maybe I was adopted.
I couldn't understand how I fit
into this family.
Now that I met you
I suddenly make
a lot of sense.
I'm so glad to see
the spirit of the '60s
is still alive in you kids.
(Laugh-In theme playing)
Yup, I saw her.
That is to say, I seen her.
She seemed like a nice lady.
Well, that "nice lady"
set the cause of biological
warfare back 30 years.
We're only now
finally caught up.
Two more ladies come by
earlier that day.
One was real pretty.
T'other, sort of plain.
Ma'am, we're going to need
your assistance
in locating this individual.
(chuckling)
Oh, you're fresh.
Don't you want to play
"good cop, bad cop"?
Ma'am, we're all good cops.
I had no intention
of playing the good cop.
(chuckles)
Ew.
Look, we know
you bought the tombstone.
We know the fugitive
visited that tombstone.
Whose tombstone was it?
Just lift up
your coffee cups and see.
(gasps)
Good Lord.
Put out an A.P.B.
On a "Uosdwis R. Dewoh."
Uh, better start
with Greektown.
That's Homer J. Simpson,
Chief.
You're reading it
upside down.
Uh, cancel that A.P.B.
But bring back some
of them, uh, gyros.
Uh, Chief, you're talking
into your wallet.
Grandma, have you
ever thought
about moving back
to Springfield?
You could live
with Grampa again.
(laughter)
Oh, I'm a living joke.
You know, Lisa...
(phone rings)
it might be nice
to rest for a while.
Mom?
There's nothing to be
alarmed about,
but could you take one
last look at the family
and join me in the kitchen?
I've been waiting 25 years
for this moment.
("Ride of the Valkyries"
playing)
("Waterloo"
I'm sorry, sir.
I must have taped over that.
(volume increasing)
♪ Knowing my fate is to be with you ♪
Freeze.
F.B.I.
The jig is up.
All right, I admit it!
I am the Lindbergh baby.
Wah-wah. Goo, goo.
I miss my fly-fly da-da.
Are you trying to stall us,
or are you just senile?
A little from column "a,"
a little from column "b."
(panting)
Sir...
she's gone.
We made it, Homer.
It's all thanks
to our anonymous tipster.
But who are you
and why did you tip us off?
Well, it's 'cause of your
old lady that I got rid
of the asthma that was
keeping me out of the academy.
Thanks.
Sure. Just think of me
as an anonymous friend
who rose through the ranks
of the Springfield Police
to become
Chief Clancy Wig...
(dial tone)
Yak, yak, yak,
yak, yak.
(horn beeping)
Well, there's my ride.
The underground awaits.
(sniffling) At least this time
I'm awake for your good-bye.
(sniffing)
Oh, Homer.
Remember: whatever happens,
you have a mother
and she's truly
proud of you.
Oh...
Oh! Hurry up, man.
This electric van only has
20 minutes of juice left.
Don't forget me.
Don't worry, Homer.
You'll always be a part of me.
D'oh!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.