♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Ahh!
-(tires screech)
(humming)
(bell dings)
Here's your toast, Maggie.
I melba-fied it myself.
Oh, Lisa, honey,
I tracked down
those old newspapers
for your history project.
Wow, Mom, you didn't have
to go to this much trouble.
Oh, it was no trouble.
The hobos at the dump
were very helpful.
Except one man who seemed
to have mental problems.
(muffled)
Good morning.
Bart, it's class photo day.
No Dracula fangs.
But they told us to wear them.
No, they didn't.
Huh?
And don't put signs
on your sister.
Now, keep the lettuce
separate until 11:30.
That way
the lettuce stays moist
and the bread stays dry.
Huh? Huh?
Mom, you fuss over us
way too much.
Enjoy it now
because when
you're a grown-up
you'll have to take care
of yourself.
(whining) Marge,
there's a spider
near my car keys.
You did the right thing
by telling me.
Shoo. Get out
of here.
(sighs)
That's better.
Now that we're alone,
Papa Bear has a little
honey for his Mama Bear.
(giggling)
(gasping)
(reading certificate)
"Mineral bath,
facial massage."
How did you afford these?
Oh-ho,
never you mind.
What advantages does
this motor car have
over say, a train?
Which I could
also afford.
Well, you'll notice
how the heated gas pedal
warms your feet while...
...gently massages
your buttocks.
Well, Count Homer
shall we discuss the--
No, we shan't.
Yoink!
Homie, this is so sweet,
but I can't possibly go now.
The sink is full
of dirty dishes.
The trash needs
to be taken out.
The living room
is a mess.
Oh, we'll clean up
this afternoon.
What about Maggie?
I got my Dad
to look after her.
Behind ya!
Don't do that!
Come on, honey, you work
yourself stupid for this family.
If anyone deserves
to be wrapped up in seaweed
and buried in mud,
it's you.
Well, all right.
But I'm taking some of the ironing
with me in the ca-- Ohh!.
Tighten those braids, Missy.
-Hoist your flag, Dooley.
-(zipping)
Nelson, you look adorable.
I feel like
punching myself.
Bart, stop scratching.
You're messing up
your hair.
Ah!! Lice!
How on earth does a boy
get head lice
in this day and age?
We bought a wicker basket
from Trader Pete's
and he was passed out
inside.
(chittering)
Hey, how come I get lice and
nothing happens to Milhouse?
S-So cold.
So very, very cold.
See you in hell,
you wingless blood-suckers.
(tiny shrieks)
What kind of parents
would permit
such a lapse
in scalpel hygiene?
You'd better
check out his sister.
She could be rife
with them bugs, too.
Keep away.
Hey, come on.
Those are
prescription shoes.
I need them.
ALL: You have cooties,
you have cooties.
No, I don't.
SKINNER (on PA): Lisa Simpson,
report to the Principal's office
for head lice inspection.
(girls laughing)
Ow!
(garbled)
My tongue.
Head's up.
Principal Skinner,
I need some shoes.
Sweet Georgia Brown!
Something is rotten
at the Simpson house.
(touch tones)
(sighing)
This is so relaxing.
Homie, this was
a wonderful idea.
(chuckling)
Yeah.
If that mafia guy
weren't staring at us
I'd take off my towel.
MAN: Oh, don't mind a-me.
Look, I do it first.
Whoa. Would you look
at this place?
Sink full of dirty dishes.
Trash not taken out.
Living room a mess.
Stacks of old newspapers...
from 20 years ago!
MAN (on TV):
Get ready, gamblers
for the World Series
of Dog Racing.
(yowling)
What the--
(stammering)
Hm, a disheveled
and malnourished man
found sleeping
in his own filth.
Seems confused
and dehydrated.
Where's the baby?
That's her, ain't it?
Kids love that water.
Oh, my Lord!
Stupid babies need
the most attention.
WOMAN (speaking softly):
All is well.
All is well...
MAN (speaking loudly):
Turn tape over.
(tape rewinding)
WOMAN (speaking softly):
All is well. All is well.
(both sighing)
Children, where
are your parents?
I don't know.
They should
be here.
Yes, they should...
Tsk, tsk.
Those parents better
have a good excuse.
(door opens)
I love getting away
from this dump.
It's like I'm on
some wonderful drug.
(clearing throat)
What's going on here?
Child Welfare, ma'am.
Here's a little
bedtime reading.
Hmm?
"Squalid hell hole?
"Toilet paper hung in
improper overhand fashion.
Dogs mating
on dining room table?"
(whimpers)
What are you doing
with my children?
We're taking them where
you can't get them.
What?! No, you can't!
I won't let you!
Mrs. Simpson, restrain yourself
or you'll be arrested.
(moaning)
Now just relax, kids.
All we're doing
is taking you to...
(sinister tone)
a Foster Home!
(both gasp)
-Yay!
-Heydilly-ho.
Welcome to your new home,
neglect-areenos.
Kids, meet
your new foster family.
ROD & TODD:
We love you!
Uh, please don't hug me.
It sickens me.
I don't judge
Homer and Marge.
That's for a vengeful
God to do.
Mm-hmm. All we want to do
is give you kids
a good home
until they
get their act together.
You don't understand.
Mom and Dad
take good care of us.
That was a baby tooth.
It was loose!
Don't you worry,
little girl.
We'll get you some nice
county dentures.
"Parents are not
to communicate with children
and must stay at least
100 feet away at all times."
We leave you the kids
for three hours
and the county
takes them away?!
Oh, bitch, bitch, bitch.
I can't believe
I put my own pleasure
ahead of my home
and family.
That is so like me.
Oh, Marge, don't
blame yourself.
I'm the terrible parent.
The boy bugs
the hell out of me.
I can't help Lisa
with her homework.
The only thing I'm fit to
take care of is a houseplant.
Lousy houseplant!
Oh, son of a--
I'll teach you to--
(sputtering)
Go with it!
Here you go, Todd,
the City Edition.
Bart, I don't know if this
should be an extra.
Is your source
on this reliable?
Oh, I hate this place.
Yeah, it seems
like our house
but everything's got a creepy
Pat Boone-ish quality to it.
Hey, kids, nachos,
Flanders-style!
That's cucumbers
with cottage cheese.
(sniffing)
(spitting)
Oh, Bart, I know you're
still getting adjusted here.
Tell you what,
we'll do whatever
you want to do.
Watch Itchy and Scratchy!
Well, I guess a little
television won't hurt.
I used to let the boys
watch "My Three Sons"
but it got them all
worked up before bedtime.
(blowing)
♪ The Itchy & Scratchy show ♪
(doorbell rings)
Ah...
(screaming)
(evil laughter)
Why? Why?
Oh... my only son.
(laughing)
Daddy, what's
the red stuff
coming out of
kitty's ears?
Uh... that's just
raspberry jam.
Dad, should I poke Rod
with a sharp thing
like the mouse did?
No, son. No sirree, Bob.
Can you see them?
I can see Lisa...
but it might be
a starfish.
I got to call them.
(touch tones)
WOMAN'S VOICE:
The number you have dialed
can no longer be reached
from this phone,
you negligent monster.
-Oh...
-That's it.
We're going downtown
to get our kids back.
Right now!
We've always tried
to be good parents.
Please. I'm begging you
one mother to another.
You must have a family.
No. I don't care for children.
Now, wait a minute!
Okay. I'm not gonna win
Father of the Year.
In fact, I'm probably
the last guy in the world
who should have kids...
Well... wait...
Can I start again?
Fathering children is
the best part of my day.
I'd do anything
for Bart and Lisa.
-And, uh, Margaret?
-Who?
Lady, you got
the wrong file.
It's Maggie.
Oh, Maggie. I got
nothing against Maggie.
I can see you sincerely
want your children back
but you have a lot to learn
about being parents.
Before I can return
your children,
you'll have to complete
a course called
"Family Skills."
It teaches parents
to listen to--
-Communication. Gotcha.
-But it's important to--
-Listen, yes, I know--
-But there's more to it--
I have listening skills.
Mr. Simpson
would you please--
Shut up, Judge!
Peek-a-boo. I see you.
(giggles)
I never heard Maggie
laugh like that before.
Well, when was
the last time
Dad gave her that
kind of attention?
When she swallowed that
quarter,
he spent
all day with her.
I thought I could
ride this thing out
but everything's just
too weird here.
I know.
They put honey on pancakes
instead of maple syrup.
And they read Newsweek
instead of nothing.
C'mon you Gloomy-Gusses.
Who's up for a big bowl of
non-fat ice milk?
I want wintergreen.
Unflavored for me.
And then I saw my boy
in a burlap sack
and they told me
he had lice.
This story going
somewhere?
All right, easy there, Flub.
We're all going
to get a chance.
Mrs. Skinner,
why are you here?
The county is threatening
to take my Seymour away.
We had another fight over
the inflatable bath pillow.
I kept screeching and
screeching at him but--
Alright. Very good.
Now who knows how the Skinners
could have resolved
this problem?
Without resorting to violence...
or childish name-calling.
Anybody?
Okay, that's okay.
Because making a happy home
isn't like flipping on
a light switch.
Duh, light switch?
There are a lot of
little tricks to it.
Things you should have
learned a long time ago.
Such as: if you leave milk out,
it can go sour.
Put it in the refrigerator
or failing that,
a cool, wet sack.
And put your garbage
in a garbage can, people.
I can't stress that enough.
Don't just throw it
out the window.
This is so humiliating.
"Garbage in garbage can."
Hmm, makes sense.
Nighty night, my sweet
little foundling-a-dings.
But it's only 7:00.
Yeah, the sun is still out.
(children chattering)
(both sighing)
♪ They say your folks
can't pay the rent ♪
♪ So we're watching you
by act of government ♪
♪ Well, I don't know
if the allegations are true ♪
♪ But you got us,
and baby, we got you ♪
BOTH:
♪ Babe, we got you, babe. ♪
You know, Maggie hasn't been
a Simpson as long as us.
I think she's beginning
to forget Mom and Dad.
Remember how Mom used
to microwave our underwear
on cold days?
Or the way Dad used
to call the radio station
with fake traffic tips?
(both sighing)
They're ten feet away
and we can't even
talk to them.
I wish I could tell them
how much I miss them.
It's so quiet here
without the kids.
What I wouldn't give
to hear Lisa play
another one
of her jazzy tunes.
Saxa-ma-phone.
Aw...
I miss the way Bart
would say something
and then say "dude."
I wish I knew something
about the baby
I could miss now.
-You mean Maggie?
-That's it.
We've never been separated
from the kids for so long.
I don't know how much
more I can take.
(rapid doorbell ringing)
BOTH: That's Bart's ring!
"Todd smells."
Aw, I already knew that.
Look at the other side.
(both sighing)
Okay let's see if
we've learned anything.
I want you two to simulate a
typical household problem. Go.
Pa, I cut myself
on the screen door again.
Why you cotton-pickin'--!
(growling)
(gagging)
No, I got to pass
this class for my kids.
Son, let's stop
the fussin' and a-feudin'.
I love you, Pa.
I love you, Cletus.
(laughing and crying)
(cheering, applause)
(gunshots)
Well, children,
it's Saturday night
so what say we let our hair
down and play Bombardment--
-Yay!
Of Bible Questions?
Which version shall it be?
St. James.
The Vulgate
of St. Jerome.
Vulgate it is.
-Oh...
-Okay, for one gold star,
what Persian king exempted
the Levites from taxation?
-Ataxerxes.
-Righty-o!
(cough)
-NED: Well?
-I know!
No, son, we got to let
Bart and Lisa get one.
Come on,
this one's easy.
We give up.
Well, guess.
Book of Revelations...
fire-breathing lion's head.
Tail made
out of snakes.
Who else is it gonna be?
Jesus?
Je-- Jes--
Don't you kids know anything?
The Serpent of Rehaboam?
The Well of Zohassadar?
The Bridal Feast
of Beth Chadruharazzeb?
That's the kind of thing you should
start learning at baptism.
Um, actually, you see...
we were never baptized.
(gasping)
(moaning)
Oh, Neddie! Neddie!
Neddie!
No, that ain't
gonna do it.
(moaning)
I'm very proud of you people.
You've learned how to care
for your children,
how to maintain
your homes,
and you've all passed
the drug test.
Except for Marge.
Marge, you tested positive
for crack and P.C.P.
Oh, my!
Okay, the re-test
says you're clean.
Sorry about the mistake.
The only thing
I'm high on is love.
Love for my son
and daughters.
Yes, a little L.S.D.
is all I need.
All right,
sounds very good.
(laughter and gunshots)
Jeepers H. Crackers.
I'd better call the reverend.
Ned Flanders
is on the phone.
Hello, Ned.
Reverend, emergency.
I-- It's
the Simpson kids.
Eedily... baptism...
oodily...
doodily, doodily!
Ned, have you thought
about one of the other
major religions?
They're all
pretty much the same.
(crash)
Oh... damn Flanders.
Looks like I'm gonna have to
baptize you myself.
(air horn blares
"Hallelujah Chorus")
Kids, we're
good parents now.
Get your asses out here!
We missed you
so much.
(gasps)
He's going to baptize
our children?
Oh, no!
In the eyes of God,
they'll be Flanderseseses.
Until this I never thought
Homer and Marge were bad parents
but now I know
you kids need
a less
hell-bound family.
Just sit back
and before you know it,
you'll be part
of the Flanders flock.
(laughs)
You're gonna be
Lisa Flanders.
You're going
to be Bart Flanders.
Ah!
Oh, relax, Bart.
Your sister Maggie
isn't scared.
That's because she can't talk.
Daddily-doodily.
Where are we going?
Okay, okay. Don't panic.
To find Flanders, I just have
to think like Flanders.
HOMER'S BRAIN:
I'm a big four-eyed lame-o
and I wear the same
stupid sweater everyday and--
The Springfield River!
♪ ...I once was lost ♪
♪ But now am found ♪
♪ Was blind, but now I see ♪
Today we write a new page
in the Flanders family bible.
Who wants to be the first
to enter God's good graces?
Easy, easy.
(approaching car)
Oh, why do You hate my trains?
(tires screeching)
(roaring)
(grunting)
(yelling)
Son of a--
(gasps)
Do you reject Satan
and all
his empty promises?
(in slow motion)
No!
(sizzling)
(pained yell)
Wow, Dad, you took
a baptismal for me.
How do you feel?
Oh, Bartholomew, I feel
like St. Augustine of Hippo
after his conversion
by Ambrose of Milan.
Wait, Homer--
What did you just say?
I said shut your ugly face,
Flanders!
Oh. Fair enough.
Oh. There's my sweet
little Maggie.
Oh, Maggie, you're
a Simpson again.
(belches)
So, what was it like
at the Flanders' house?
Yeah, give me
all the dirt.
Let's see...
dirt... dirt.
Well, there wasn't
really much dirt.
There was a bunch
of old paint cans
in the garage, though.
(Homer laughs)
Old painty-can Ned!
(all laugh)
HOMER: I always knew he'd keep
his old cans of paint!
BART: Yeah!
MARGE:
How do you like that?
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.