♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-Aah!
-(tires screech)
(moaning)
Ugh. My mouth tastes
like an ashtray.
(burps)
(water running)
♪ Doo-doo-doo doo-doo-dee ♪
Smithers, wait your turn.
There's plenty of
hot water for all.
Sir! You weren't shot.
(sighs)
It was all a dream.
That's right.
The year is 1965,
and you and I are
undercover detectives
on the hot rod circuit.
Now let's burn rubber, baby.
(engines roaring)
(gunfire)
Wait!
That was all a dream.
Ah...
Hey, then maybe I haven't
become a hideous, drunken wreck.
Oh...
(belches)
Dozens of people are
gunned down each day in Springfield
but until now,
none of them was important.
I'm Kent Brockman.
At 3:00 p.m. Friday,
local autocrat
C. Montgomery Burns was shot
following a tense
confrontation at town hall.
Burns was rushed to
a nearby hospital,
where he was
pronounced dead.
He was then transferred
to a better hospital
where doctors upgraded his
condition to "Alive."
Now let's talk
to Police Chief Wiggum.
Oh, hiya, Kent.
Right now, we
are questioning
two witnesses who were
in the vicinity
at the time.
Did you see this guy?
Was he anywhere
near the parking lot
when Burns got shot?
No, it's no use.
They ain't talking.
Everyone in Springfield had
a reason to shoot Mr. Burns,
even us.
(all murmuring)
Bart, he broke
your dog's legs.
Grandpa, he
destroyed your home.
And Dad, well, you
kinda went berserk
when he couldn't
remember your name.
Berserk is right!
May I have some
iced tea, please?
Aren't we forgetting someone--
Sister suspect?
(nervous laugh) Yeah,
I was just getting to me.
Because of Mr. Burns,
they canceled my jazz program
and my friend Tito Puente
got fired...
But I could never
shoot someone.
-Could so.
-Could not.
HOMER:
Kids, kids, kids!
As far as Daddy's concerned
you're both
potential murderers.
The police already
have a suspect.
It's Mr. Smithers.
-Sure!
-He's a good suspect.
I bet he's the one.
Yeah! Smingers did it.
Case closed.
Now where's my hat?
I'm going
to the outhouse.
We don't have
an outhouse.
My toolshed!
Oh, Dad?
(moaning)
Could I have shot Mr. Burns
in a drunken rage?
No, no, not me!
I know in my heart I...
A gun...
And it's been recently fired.
Wait. I remember
leaving the town meeting.
I must have run into
Mr. Burns outside and...
(muttering)
(gunfire)
(gasps) Mr. Burns!
What have I done?
(sobbing)
Hey, Homer--
Us hotheads here
is gonna go tear down
Burns's sunblocking machine.
You want to come with?
Sure.
I've had it up to here
with these damn rickets.
Pull, Duchess, pull!
-(crashing)
-(screaming)
Um... Uh, what town
did we just crush?
Shelbyville.
(all cheering)
Oh...
This guilt is driving me mad.
I've got to tell someone.
Father, I'm not
a Catholic but--
Well, I tried to march in
the St. Patrick's Day parade.
Anyway, I've got
a rather large sin to confess.
(sniffles)
I'm the one who--
who shot Mr. Burns.
That's all I
needed to hear.
Boy, this thing
works great.
The man became
consumed by greed.
He'd steal from anyone.
This isn't a rival company
you're battling with.
It's a school.
People won't stand for it.
Pish-posh.
It will be like taking
candy from a baby.
Say, that sounds like a larf.
And when he tried
to steal our sunlight,
he crossed that line between
everyday villainy
and cartoonish super-villainy.
Bah!
He was a rank amateur
compared to Dr. Colossos.
(evil laughter)
Oh... Ow!
(groaning)
When is my lawyer coming?
(clamoring)
Dave Shutton, Springfield
Daily Shopper.
Who are you?
Where are you going?
Do your research,
Shutton.
Kent Brockman,
Channel 6 News.
How does it feel
to be accused
of the attempted murder
of your boss and mentor?
Kent, I feel about
as low as Madonna
when she found out
she missed Tailhook.
I'm going to say, "Ouch!"
for Madonna.
Hey, that's my Madonna gag.
That guy stole my gag.
And you stole it
from last Friday's episode
of "Pardon My Zinger."
Stole, made up-- What's the difference?
(nervous chuckle)
Mr. Smithers must have
seen that program too.
He never misses it.
At the town meeting,
he mentioned
that he watched
Comedy Central.
I made sure to note that,
as it seemed quite unusual.
Ye gods!
To the police station,
Krusty.
I am Melvin Van Horn
and this is my associate,
Hershel Krustofsky.
Hey, hey.
Officers, you have arrested
an innocent man.
Really? Oh, geez.
All right Colossos,
you're free to go,
but stay away
from death mountain.
But all my stuff is there.
(clearing throat)
I was referring
to Wayland Smithers.
Mr. Burns was shot
Friday at 3:00 p.m.
The very time that Smithers
was at home
watching "Pardon My Zinger."
So you see,
he couldn't have done it.
Yes...
You're right. I remember now.
I--I watched that entire show.
In fact...
I left the town meeting early,
so I could get home in time.
SMITHERS (slurring):
I got to run or I'll miss
the opening rank-out.
Get out of my way, please.
Slow down. The sidewalk's
for regular walking,
not for fancy walking.
SMITHERS: Out of my way.
I'm in a hurry.
You simmer down,
I'll let you go.
(gunfire)
So, instead of wounding
an evil old man
I may have killed
an innocent old man.
That's much worse.
About 50,000 volts worse,
if you know what I mean.
(grunting)
Sizzle!
Wait a minute. If a second
old geezer got shot,
how come nobody reported it?
(knocking)
Uh, hi.
Um, could we take
a look at your leg?
Yeah, that's real spruce.
You like it?
Whew, thank God.
Sir, I only hope
you can forgive me
for shooting
your wooden leg.
You shot who
in the what, now?
Okay, Smithers,
you're free to go.
And you, one question.
Do you know who shot Mr. Burns?
'Cause we are really
up the creek on this one.
And with the
prime suspect cleared
and found
completely innocent,
we must now ask ourselves
who could possibly
be as bloodthirsty
as Wayland Smithers?
I guess it's never
the most likely suspect.
Actually, Mom,
in 95% of cases it is.
The rest of the time,
it's usually
some deranged lunatic
who did it for no reason.
Hey, I had
a damn good reason.
He could never remember my name.
Who the devil are you?
(grunting)
(screaming)
Homer Simpson!
My name is Homer Simpson!
Well, I don't think
anyone in this family
is capable of
attempted murder.
Eh, you never know
what you're capable of.
I never thought I could
shoot down a German plane,
but last year
I proved myself wrong.
Nancy Drew says that all you
need to solve a mystery
is an inquisitive temperament
and two good friends,
and I've got an
inquisitive temperament.
Maybe I could help solve this.
(groans)
I think you're
a little young
to be investigating
an attempted murder.
Why don't you try
to solve the mystery
of who put that mud
in the freezer?
Who wants chocolate ice cream?
Me, me, me, me!
Okay, boys, we've got a clue.
The bullet they
took out of Burns.
Now, let's discuss
the uh... mo-tive.
LISA: Mr. Burns is the
richest man in town.
Maybe it's about money.
That's some good
thinking, Lou.
Hey, thanks, Chief.
LISA: Hey, I said that!
My name is Lisa Simpson,
and I made a chart of all
the suspects in the Burns case.
Look. Mr. Burns hurt
all these people financially.
Nightclub owner Moe Szyslak.
His bar was closed because
of Burns's negligence.
Liquor connoisseur
Barney Gumble.
When Moe's closed Barney lost
his only means of support:
Sucking coins out of
the love tester machine.
That's a real good way
to get sick.
LISA: Dedicated educator
Principal Seymour Skinner.
His school lost millions
when Burns pirated its
oil well.
And grounds tender
Groundskeeper Willy.
He lost his job
and his dream of owning
a fine crystal slop bucket.
And what about that jazz teacher
that got laid off,
you know, uh, Mr. Samba,
Señor Mambo-- What was it?
-Tito Puente?
-Yeah.
Well, he did vow revenge.
(chuckles)
But I can't see him
doing something illegal.
He's in show business,
he's a celebrity.
Let's roll, boys.
(police siren blares)
Revenge? Of course--
But why wound
his body with bullets
when I could set his soul afire
with a slanderous mambo?
Listen, if you will,
to my revenge.
Uno, dos, tres...
(playing salsa music)
♪ Burns won't last long ♪
♪ But an insulting song ♪
♪ Burns will always
carry with him ♪
♪ So I'll settle my score ♪
♪ On the salsa floor ♪
♪ With this vengeful
Latin rhythm ♪
♪ Burns ♪
♪ Con un corazon ♪
♪ De perro ♪
♪ Señor Burns ♪
♪ El diablo con dinero ♪
♪ It may not surprise you ♪
♪ But all of us
despise you ♪
♪ Please die ♪
♪ And fry ♪
♪ In hell ♪
♪ You rotten ♪
♪ Rich old wretch ♪
♪ Adios viejo ♪
(clapping)
-Ole!
-Yeah!
Okay, okay,
I believe you're innocent.
Gee, I hope all the suspects
are this much fun.
Hmm...
Now...
Now let...
Let me...
Let me think.
Oh.
Now I did...
I did go to the town meeting
with the intention
of ambushing Mr. Burns.
When it adjourned, I rushed
to the lavatory to apply
my camouflage makeup.
Blast! I took mother's
makeup kit by mistake.
Oh, excuse me, ma'am.
Superintendent Chalmers!
Oh, my God!
(distant gunshot)
So Superintendent Chalmers
can vouch for your whereabouts?
Oh, yes, but anything else
he tells you is a filthy lie.
I'm telling ye,
I could nay have shot Burns.
-(groans)
-(gun cocks)
This is your last warning
about that.
It's impossible for me
to fire a pistol.
If you'll check
my medical records
you'll see I have
a crippling arthritis
in me index fingers.
Look at them.
I got it from Space Invaders
in 1977.
Yeah, that was a pretty
addictive video game.
Video game?
Do you hold a grudge
against Montgomery Burns?
-No.
-(buzzes)
Alright, maybe I did
but I didn't shoot him.
(dings)
Checks out. Okay sir,
you're free to go.
Good, cause I got
a hot date tonight.
(buzzes)
-A date.
-(buzzes)
-Dinner with a friend.
-Dinner alone.
-(buzzes)
-Watching TV alone.
All right!
I'm gonna sit at home
and ogle the ladies
in the Victoria's Secret
catalog.
(buzzes)
-Sears catalog.
-(beeps)
Would you unhook this
already, please?!
I don't deserve this
kinda shabby treatment.
(buzzes)
Grandpa, I found
your cigar box
dug up in the back yard,
but the gun wasn't there.
Have you seen it?
You accuse me of everything
around here.
"Who put slippers
in the dishwasher?
"Who threw a cane at the TV?
Who fell into the China hutch?"
I was just asking
if you'd seen it.
There's no need
to be a prickly pear.
Oh, you're
the bee's knees, baby.
I missed you bad.
Were you talking
to me, Grandpa?
Um... Yes.
Ew...
We're still not close.
Boy! This is gonna be
an all-night brainbuster.
Yep, better drink some coffee.
Oh, we're out of coffee.
Oh, well, I'll just drink
this warm cream.
(snoring)
(distorted)
Huh?
I'm not following you.
(normal voice)
Look at Burns's suit! Yeesh!
Huh?!
I had an idea, Chief.
Why don't we
check out that suit
Burns was wearing
when he got shot?
Did you have the same
backwards-talking dream
with the flaming cards?
I'll drive.
Eureka!
Ooh, nice eyelash. Yours?
No. We need to find out
who it belonged to.
We want a DNA test.
Ooh-ooh-ee-ooh-oh.
That takes eight
to ten weeks.
(sighs)
Did I say weeks?
'Cause I meant seconds.
What do you got, the whole
town's DNA on file?
Uh-huh. If you've
ever handled a penny,
the government's
got your DNA.
Why do you think
they keep 'em in circulation?
Scan's finished.
Now it's going
to narrow it down
to the family bloodline.
♪♪ (fanfare)
(shuddering)
Homer Simpson!
Bingo.
Our gunman
has a name-o.
-Chief, Chief!
-Chief.
(clamoring)
(gasps)
Hey, Chief Wiggum
what are you doing?
What's going on?
I'm sorry, kid. We got
Simpson DNA on Burns's clothing
and your father was identified by
the old man himself.
(all gasp)
DNA, positive I.D.
Those won't hold up
in any court.
-Run, Dad!
-Hey ho.
Look what I found
under Mr. Simpson's car seat.
I swear! I've never
seen that gun before.
Then why are your fingerprints
all over it, sir?
(yelps)
This bullet matches the one
we took out of Burns.
Homer Simpson,
you're under arrest
for attempted murder.
D'oh!
Yeah, that's what
they all say--
They all say "D'oh."
WIGGUM: Yeah,
we need two cups of coffee,
and two orders of bite-sized
breakfast pancakes
with extra dipping sauce.
MAN: Please pull up to
the service window, please.
The wagon's too tall.
I don't want
to have to get out.
I'll just drive up
on the curb.
(grunting)
Blug.
Almost got it.
Drop the food,
Chief.
(yelling)
(horn sounds)
Dang fools.
Drive-through's not for parking.
(yells)
Diane, I'm going
to take my break now.
Hi, everybody.
Ho! Mer... Simp... Son.
Okay, that was
a little strange.
Um...
Tell me, how are
you feeling today?
Homer.
Simpson Homer.
D-oh... Simpson!
Hmm. That seems to be
all you can say.
When you were
in that coma,
did you feel your brain
getting damaged?
The police have such
a strong case against Homer.
Mr. Burns said
he did it.
They have Homer's DNA--
They have Simpson DNA.
It could have come
from any of us.
Except you,
since you're a Bouvier.
No, no, no, when I took
your father's name
I took everything that came with it,
including DNA.
Okay, Mom.
Anyway, my point is
the evidence isn't
as concrete as it seems.
Like those fingerprints.
They could have gotten
on the gun some other way.
Are you sure you don't
want me to hold
one of your ice cream cones?
Yeah, right.
You chose fruit.
You live with fruit.
D'oh!
Oh...
No... No... No.
Ew! Why is this
on the floor?
And we don't even know
whose gun that was.
Maybe somebody planted
it there to frame Dad.
No, we can't start
thinking that way
about our own
family members.
Suspicion could
tear us apart.
That's right.
We all got
to stick together
if we're gonna have
any hope of bringing
that awful Homer
to justice.
Here is a photo of
the fugitive from our files.
And now, Wayland Smithers,
who's been a real good sport
about that
wrongful arrest thing...
(whistles)
Has a statement
that he would like to make.
-Wayland?
-Thank you.
As Montgomery Burns's
closest friend,
I'm certain that there
is nothing he'd want more
than swift, brutal revenge
against Homer Simpson.
Therefore, I am offering
a $50,000 reward
for his capture...
Dead or alive.
Holy cow!
Me first! Me first!
Homer Simpson?
So, you finally
learned my name, eh?
Homer Simpson.
I've got no time for your
demented parlor games.
You won't be telling anyone else
that Homer Simpson shot you.
The scene of the crime.
There must be something here
that can clear Dad.
(cooing)
Clue, clue.
That's it! Oh, Mr. Pigeon!
I'd kiss you if you
weren't swimming with disease.
(church bell tolls)
(gasps)
So the DNA was right.
It must have been...
Oh, Dad!
MAN: Attention all units:
Homer Simpson has been sighted.
Proceed at once to Marvin Monroe
Memorial Hospital.
(gasping)
(angry cries)
Be careful when we capture him.
We cannot claim the reward
unless we have 51%
of the carcass.
Stop!
Don't shoot my dad!
He's innocent.
He wouldn't hurt a fly.
-Stop telling them it was me!
-Homer Simpson.
I'll kill you
for saying it was me.
Ho-mer Simp-son.
BURNS: What is the
m-meaning of this?
Smithers, who is this
beast that's shaking me?
D'oh!
Say it, Burns!
Say I never shot you!
Before...
Shot? (chuckles)
By you?
I'm afraid not,
my primitive friend.
Your kind has neither
the cranial capacity
nor the opposable digits
to operate a firearm.
The one who shot me was...
(yelling)
M--Maggie Simpson!
With the sunblocker in place
and the town aghast,
I was on top of the world.
So, I wanted to kick
up my heels
and indulge
my sweet tooth.
I feel like celebrating.
Oh, it's you. What are you
so happy about?
(gasps)
I see.
Yes...
(lips smacking)
That's the one.
Smithers had thwarted
my earlier attempt
to take candy from a baby,
but with him out
of the picture,
I was free to wallow
in my own crapulence.
I think you better drop it.
But the old axiom
was misleading;
taking the candy proved
exceedingly difficult.
I said, drop it!
(straining)
(gunfire)
Stricken, I lurched forth
in search of aid
but finding only
slack-jawed gawkers
I gave up and collapsed
on the sundial.
Then with your last
ounce of strength
you pointed
to "W" And "S"
Or, from your point
of view, "M" And "S."
Maggie Simpson.
What?
No, with my last ounce
of strength
I sucked out my gold fillings
and swallowed them.
Those paramedics
have sticky fingers.
Well, I'm just relieved
that Homer's safe
and that you've recovered,
and we can all get back to normal.
If Maggie could talk
I'm sure she'd apologize
for shooting you.
I'm afraid
that's insufficient.
Officer, arrest the baby.
(laughing)
Yeah, right, Pops.
No jury in the world's
gonna convict a baby.
Hmm, maybe Texas.
Besides, she didn't mean it.
It was an accident.
(gunshots echo)
♪♪ (salsa)
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.