♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
D'oh!
-(screams)
-(tires screech)
(pounding on door)
Come on, Simpson,
open up.
We know you're in there.
(water dripping)
Hmm... That one.
Someone's in here.
(crying)
No!
Oh, for
the love of...
Boy, I've never seen
a man so desperate
to get out
of five minutes
of calisthenics.
One, two, three, four.
Up, down, three, four.
This new exercise program
is great.
Yeah. Every muscle in
my body's getting a workout.
Especially my big, fat mouth.
Yeah. Especially
your big, fat...
Oh, wait.
Raise your right hock.
Aerate.
Raise your left hock.
I want to see
more Teddy Roosevelts
and less Franklin Roosevelts.
(groaning)
...Two.
Actually, homer,
that's just one.
See, each pushup
includes
both an up part
and a down part.
D'oh!
Hey, where's Charlie?
How did he get out of this?
He's at home
on disability.
Yeah, he got injured
on the job.
They sent him
home with pay.
It's like a lottery
that rewards stupidity.
Stupidity, eh?
Must hurt self.
D'oh!
Hmm, probably better
that didn't hit me.
(electircity hums)
-Yes?
-Hello.
May I help you?
Uh... Could you give
me a little push
in the opposite
direction?
Okay.
Thank you.
"Carpal tunnel syndrome"?
No.
"Lumber lung"? No.
"Juggler's despair"? No.
"Achy-breaky pelvis"? No.
I'm never going to be disabled.
I'm sick of being so healthy.
Hey, wait.
"Hyper-obesity.
"If you weigh more
than 300 pounds,
you qualify as disabled."
(fanfare plays)
You can do it, old boy.
Yes, I can.
Yes, yes.
That's the spirit.
If you gain 61 pounds,
they'll let you work at home?
Uh-huh.
That's the deal.
No more exercise program.
No more traffic.
No more blood drives
or charity walks.
Dad, I know we don't
do a lot together
but helping you
gain 61 pounds
is something
I want to be a part of.
-Dad!
-(screams)
I must protest.
You're abusing a program
intended to help
the unfortunate.
I'm not saying
it isn't sleazy, honey,
but try to see it my way.
All my life,
I've been an obese man
trapped inside
a fat man's body.
Have you told Mom
about this?
No, it would only
worry her.
If you want to add
to her worries, go ahead.
I guess I'm just
a little more grateful
for all she's done for us.
-Dad!
-Yes, sweetheart?
Obesity is really
unhealthy.
Any doctor will
tell you that.
Oh, yeah? Well, we'll
just see about that,
little miss smart guy.
(gasps)
My God, that's monstrous.
I've never heard
of anything so negligent.
I'll have no part of it.
Can you recommend
a doctor who will?
Yes.
Hi, everybody.
BOTH: Hi, Dr. Nick.
Now, there are many
options available
for dangerously underweight
individuals like yourself.
I recommend a slow,
steady gorging process
combined with
assal horizontology.
Of course.
You'll want to focus
on the neglected food groups
such as the whipped group,
the congealed group
and the choc-o-tastic.
What can I do to speed
the whole thing up, Doctor?
Be creative.
Instead of making sandwiches
with bread, use Pop-Tarts.
Instead of chewing gum,
chew bacon.
You could brush your
teeth with milk shakes.
Hey, did you go
to Hollywood Upstairs
Medical College, too?
And remember, if you're not sure
about something,
rub it against
a piece of paper.
If the paper turns clear,
it's your window
to weight gain.
Bye-bye, everybody.
Oh, it's a dream
come true, boy.
I can, nay, I must
eat everything
I've always wanted.
Now come on.
Every second I'm out of bed,
I'm burning precious calories.
Now get grabbing.
Eat around
the banana, Dad.
It's just
empty vitamins.
Lucky for you,
this stuff doesn't work.
I don't know.
Fish sandwich.
Are you sure?
Oh!
225? That means
I lost weight.
(clears throat)
Homer,
you're on the towel rack.
Woo-hoo!
Four more pounds,
and my dream comes true.
Working at home.
Here's your lemonade
and here's your beer.
Oh, you're such a vigorous
young go-getter.
When's your next
coffee break?
Anytime I want.
(tiger growl)
(tango music playing)
Oh.
Hey, Flanders, bad day
at the rat races?
Yeah, a crazy guy shot
a bunch of people
and the subway
ran over my hat.
Hey, Lise,
come look at this.
Neat.
-Hello, honey.
-Hi.
Um... There's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
Did you put on
a little weight this week?
I was going
to surprise you,
but what the heck.
Honey, I'm purposely
gaining 61 pounds
to get on disability.
(gasps)
Have you lost your mind?
Have you thought
about your health
or your appearance?
Oh, so, that's it,
isn't it, Marge?
Looks.
I didn't know you
were so shallow.
Oh, please.
I would love you if you
weighed 1,000 pounds, but...
Beautiful. Good night.
Oh.
I've got 15 minutes
to gain a pound
or I've got to face
another day at work.
Bad news, Dad.
We're out of food.
We're even out of the basic
elements of food.
You ate all the tarragon
and you drank the soy sauce.
I need a miracle.
Ah, honey, that looks
just like a real doughnut.
Dad, it says "Non-toxic."
Well, that's a plus.
Woo hoo-hoo-hoo!
I did it!
Uh, Dad,
towel rack.
(chuckling)
Oh, my.
(Mr. Burns
clearing throat)
I'm pleased to dedicate
this remote work terminal.
It will allow
our safety inspector here
to preform his duties
from home.
And so, excelsior
to you, mister...
What's the name
of this gastropod?
Simpson, sir. One of your
chair-moisteners from sector 7-G.
Yes.
Simpson.
Thank you for your pity.
Mom, are you
ever planning
to step in and put
a stop to this?
Normally, your father's
crackpot schemes
fizzle out as soon as
he finds something
good on TV
but this season, uh...
I'm looking for something
loose and billowy
something comfortable
for my first day of work.
Work, huh?
Let me guess.
Computer programmer?
Computer magazine columnist?
Something with computers.
Well, I use a computer.
What's the connection?
Must be the non-stop
sitting and snacking.
Well, sir, many of our clients
find pants confining
so we offer a range
of alternatives
for the ample gentleman--
Ponchos, muu-muus, capes
jumpsuits, uni-sheets,
muslin body rolls
academic and judicial robes.
I don't want
to look like a weirdo.
I'll just go with a muu-muu.
(alarm ringing)
ANNOUNCER: Arnie Pie-in-the-sky
with the morning commute!
Traffic this morning
is as bad as it gets.
Due to a fire
at the army testing lab
a bunch of escaped
infected monkeys
are roaming the expressway!
Despite the sweltering heat,
don't unroll your windows
'cause those monkeys
seem confused and irritable.
Hee hee hee!
I pity those poor suckers
on the freeway.
Gas, brake, honk.
Honk, honk, punch.
Gas, gas, gas.
8:58. First time I've ever
been early for work
except for all those
daylight savings days.
Lousy farmers.
"To start, press any key."
Where's the "Any" Key?
I see "Esc... "
"Ctrl... "
And "Pg-up"
There doesn't seem
to be any "Any" Key.
Whew! All this computer hacking
is making me thirsty.
I think I'll order a Tab.
Whoop!
No time for that now.
The computer's starting.
"Check core temperature.
Yes / no."
Yes.
"Core temperature normal."
Not too shabby.
"Vent radioactive gas?"
N-o.
"Venting prevents ex-plos-ion."
(chuckling)
Ooh, this is hard.
Where's my Tab?
Okay, then, yes.
Vent the stupid gas.
Ah, no!
The corn!
Paul Newman's
going to have my legs broke.
♪ Bart and Lisa
have to go to school ♪
♪ While I get
to stay home ♪
♪ Nyah, nyah, nyah,
nyah, nyah, nyah ♪
I like school.
Why don't you
live with it, then?
I would if I could.
Not me, sister.
When I grow up,
I'm going to be a lardo
on workman's comp,
just like Dad.
I wash myself
with a rag on a stick.
(guttural laughter)
Whoo, whoo, whoo...
Yeow!
Mom?
This whole thing
is really creepy.
Are you sure
you won't talk to Dad?
I'd like to, honey,
but I'm not sure how.
Your father can be
surprisingly sensitive.
Remember when I giggled at
his Sherlock Holmes hat?
He sulked for a week
and then closed
his detective agency.
Maybe you'll have
to hurt his feelings.
The longer he lives
like this, the harder
it'll be to go back.
Hmm, you're right.
Hmm! Maybe if I use
my least-nagging tone of voice.
(softly)
Homer?
Hmm.
(sharply)
Homer?!
(sternly)
Homer?
That's it.
That's the one.
Send him on in.
Dad?
Yes, honey?
Hmm. Mom just
baked a cake.
Ooh!
Homer, we need to have
a serious talk.
You dragged me all the way
from work for that?
Let's quietly and calmly
discuss the pros and cons
of your controversial
plan, shall we?
I--
Con: You're endangering
your health.
Pro: I'm drought
and famine-resistant.
Con: You're setting a bad
example for the children.
Pro:
I don't have to go to work.
Con: You're running
the air conditioner non-stop.
It's freezing in here.
Pro: Uh...
Uh... I love you?
Con:
I'm finding myself
less attracted
to you physically.
Marge, this is everything
I've ever dreamed of right here
and nobody's going
to take it away from me.
You never had
faith in me before
but let me tell you, the slim,
lazy homer you knew is dead.
Now I'm a big, fat dynamo
and where's that cake?!
There's no cake.
Oh.
"Vent radioactive gas?"
Y-e-s.
"Sound alertness horn?"
(horn blowing)
"Decalcify calcium ducts?"
Well, give me a word.
Give me a... Hey.
All I have to type is "Y."
Hey, miss doesn't-find-me-
attractive-sexually-anymore
I just tripled
my productivity.
Good. Good for you.
"Y." "Y".
Let's see, so many letters
to choose from.
I'll pick "Y."
"Y." "Y."
What? What the heck
are you doing over there?
(groaning)
There. You found the floor.
"Y, y, y, y."
"Y, y... "
I'm going out.
I run errands
during the day.
Could you pick me up
a lemonade and a beer?
(door slamming)
(mail slot clatters)
The mail. The mail is here!
Ooh! "An urgent plea
from Edward James Olmos."
"Lisa Simpson,
can you afford to miss
another issue
of the Utne Reader?"
Kids.
Free sample
of fabric softener?
Woo-hoo!
(dryer buzzes)
Mmm.
I can feel three
kinds of softness.
Dad, what are you
doing down there?
Washing
my fat-guy hat, honey.
ANNOUNCER: We now return
to search for the sun.
According to daddy's will,
I inherit
the entire plantation.
I'll see to it
you don't get apricot one.
(computer beeps)
Uh, what's your
Dad's job again?
He's a nuclear
safety technician.
What's he doing
with that broom?
Uh, what isn't he doing?
I heard that guy's ass
has its own congressman.
(guffawing)
Hey, leave my dad alone.
Just because he's overweight
doesn't mean he's bad.
He's a sweet man,
and he has real feelings.
Hey, what are you
kids looking at?
Hey, look.
He's trying to get up
to yell at us.
Don't make me
close that shade.
(groaning)
Hey, Homer,
you promised Mom
you wouldn't wear
your dress outside.
Nuts to that.
I'm going to the movies.
Shouldn't you be working?
I got someone
to cover for me.
(beeps)
One for honk, please.
Oh, gee, uh,
just a minute.
I have to check
with the manager.
That overweight guy
wants to see the movie.
I'm terribly sorry, sir
but I'm afraid
our facilities
are not equipped
to meet your needs.
What are you talking about?
What I'm saying, sir,
is that a man of your carriage
couldn't possibly
fit in our seats.
I could sit
in the aisle.
I'm afraid that would
violate the fire code.
MAN: Hey, fatty,
I got a movie for you--
A Fridge Too Far.
(laughing)
Shame on all of you.
Give me my dignity.
I just came here to see
"Honk if You're Horny" in peace.
Sir, if you
just quiet down,
I'd be happy
to treat you
to a garbage bag
full of popcorn.
This may surprise you, but you
can't buy me off with food.
I'm sick of all your
stereotypes and cheap jokes.
The overweight individuals
in this country
are just as smart and talented
and hardworking
as everybody else
and they're going to make
their voices heard.
All they need is a leader.
Huh!
I'll work harder than ever
before and show the world
overweight people aren't
undisciplined,
lazy and irresponsible.
What happened to my bird?
Oh. Marge?
Lisa?
Flanders?
"Explosion imminent"!
Oh, my God!
The plant's going to explode!
(metal rattling and groaning)
Hey, that thing's going
kah-kah koo-koo.
Who cares?
It's Homer's problem.
Wait. I know.
"Vent gas."
"Pressure too high"?
Oh!
"Tank must be
shut down manually"?!
Oh, stupid bird!
I never should have
put you in charge.
Why, you--
Oh, who am I kidding?
It's all my fault.
I got to call the plant
and warn them.
OPERATOR: The fingers you
have used to dial are too fat.
To obtain
a special dialing wand
please mash the keypad
with your palm now.
(shrill shriek)
(labored breathing)
I'm going to have
to shut it down myself.
Fat don't fail me now!
D'oh!
Oh!
Hey, buddy, you gonna
slow your car down and let me in
because I'm a big, fat guy
and I can't go anywhere
because there's going to be
some poison gas.
I mean it's gonna
be really poisonous!
Everybody's going to be dead,
especially me!
The ice cream man!
Hey, buddy, you got
to let me in your car!
T-take anything you want,
man, take it all!
(babbling)
Push out the jive.
Bring in the love.
I heard your dad
went into a restaurant
and ate everything
in the restaurant
and they had to close
the restaurant.
Hey! My dad may have gained
a little weight
but he's not some kind
of food-crazed maniac!
Oh, that's
raspberry.
(groans)
Oh!
-Ice cream!
Workers, please.
There will be time
for the frozen
pudding wagon later.
You still owe me
ten more Iroquois twists.
♪ Ten, hi-yi-ya ♪
♪ And nine, hi-yi-ya ♪
Get away, damn it!
Run for your lives!
I'll take
a rocket pop!
What can I get
for 30 cents?
Let go!
I got to get to the tank!
Heck, I can't decide
without the pictures.
♪ Six, hi-yi-ya ♪
♪ Four, hi-yi-ya ♪
Whoa-oh!
♪ Three, hi-yi-ya ♪
(whimpering)
♪ Two, hi-yi-ya ♪
(screams)
Stupid switch!
I wish I had
my reaching broom.
♪ One, hi-yi-ya ♪
Wait a minute.
There's probably a...
(screams)
Homer, your bravery
and quick thinking
have turned
a potential Chernobyl
into a mere
Three-Mile Island.
Bravo!
I think it's ironic that
Dad saved the day
while a slimmer man would
have fallen to his death.
And I think it's ironic that,
for once, Dad's butt
prevented the release
of toxic gas.
Bart!
We'll have you
out of there
as soon as our tech boys
get you decontaminated.
(laughs)
Thank you, Mr. Burns.
It was pretty scary
up there...
(laughs)
For a while,
I feared for my life!
(laughing hysterically)
Oh! Stop!
Now, Homer,
if there's anything else
I can do for you, please
don't hesitate to ask.
Mr. Burns, can you
make me thin again?
I guarantee it.
One.
One!
Bah! I'll just pay
for the blasted liposuction.
Woo-hoo!
♪♪
Shh!
CAPTIONS ENHANCED BY
ROUNDABOUT ENTERTAINMENT INC.