In the city,
drowned in the sea. Devil
rain for time.
The
after the.
Hey, the water looks great. I'm going in.
Hi, down now.
Barnett. Good job. You.
Got her? Okay. Bring her over here.
Hey, give us a hand.
Good. Good. You ready? Give me a hand.
All right. 1, 2, 3. Go. Grab her arm
all healthy. Push her up. Push her
up quick. Pull her up. You got her.
It's a man.
What? Huh?
There.
Are many differences between
being a lifeguard and being a pi.
Lifeguards run on sand.
PIs have run on everything.
I realized that as I chased
after a boardwalk con. Man,
we've been staking out all day.
You know, John Len once said,
and it's a wise proverb too,
that life is what happens
when you're busy making plans.
I didn't plan on meeting a beautiful
woman during a fist fight. Back off, man.
Just leave me alone. No way,
man. I chase you too far.
I'll let you go now.
Come on. Give it up. Huh?
You want me to hurt her?
What's your name? Cindy.
Cindy, sorry. About
a drowned man wearing a woman's dress.
A knockout named Cindy and
a man and a Nixon mask.
Funny how one thing can lead to another
even if they don't seem to have anything
in common at all.
Yeah.
What?
It's been a wonderful night, Miss.
Like we miss gorgeous,
witty, intelligible.
Handsome man. A delicious
candlelight dinner.
Dancing all night.
Life. The plane. It's a wonderful
too. Didn't you like it?
Yeah, it was okay. It was long.
Really? You didn't seem that way to me.
It actually three hours and five minutes.
. I didn't notice. It was so sad.
I must have gone through 20 Kleenex.
I.
Know you went through 25.
And how made you go through Mr. Macho?
Me. Oh, I, I think I sniffled once.
How could you not cry? So sad.
They were so in love. And when she died.
Uhoh, Here we go again.  26.
You know what the problem with men is?
Well, I, I've heard that
we're, uh, oversexed ill,
mannered insensitive workaholics.
Hate to ask for directions.
Uh, stop me when I'm wrong.
I will. You're missing the big one.
The big one.
Men are not in touch
with their feminine side.
What?
Look, Mitch, you're a great guy,
but it wouldn't have hurt if
you got in touch with yours.
Got in touch with what? Where you going?
Wait, Cindy, wait a minute. What.
What, what happened?
I don't know. We went to
dinner. I was witty. Charming.
We danced all night. I
was graceful, attentive.
We drove up the coast
to watch the sunrise.
And the next thing I
know is we're arguing.
Ah, get your mind off
it. Come help me. Look.
Ah, I don't want to get sand in my
shoes. What are we looking for again?
The Meritorious Moose.
Stan Feldman's Lodge. Man.
Will you hang up the phone? Cindy
Meritorious Moose Bogard is hired
to find the Malt Falcon and we are
hired to find the
Meritorious Moose partner.
A gig. A gig. That what this
all about with you and Cindy.
Well, she said I wasn't in touch
with my feminine side. She.
You know.
What? My feminine side. Oh.
She's right. Most men are. Yeah.
How do you know that?
Charlie. Jesse, right? Yeah. Uh,
hey, hey, hey. Come on. Let
get outta here. Hero.
Gerald says, same thing.
Hey. Hi.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm sorry to,
I don't know what happened,
but I don't know what the
whole thing was about. Okay.
Ah, good. Good dog. Good, good boy. Good.
Me. I'm,
I'm moose hunting. Found it.
Okay. See you later.
Darling's. Best friend.
Tired.
Dog. Chad.
Did you get the moose medal?
Recover? Is and got it.
Oh.
Well, I have some good news
too. We might have a case.
Oh, I hope it's somebody
who's got some money.
Same it. Chris Vogel. He called this
morning. He sounded really scared.
What's the problem?
I don't know. Are you supposed
to meet tonight in 15 minutes?
Give us the whole story. Where's Mitch?
Hey, Inside calling
Cindy. But you got there.
Mine. Don't even think about it.
Hey, you gotta handle the bills now.
I cannot handle the bills. Okay. I.
Know when they handle em all
the time and I handle 'em.
Just, Whoa.
Ben Miller and the snow.
And there's Cher.
And Madonna.
There's Marilyn and Ross. Who?
And she's dead.
Who are these people? Female.
Impersonate, sweeper. On a hell of a show.
Ryan?
Yes.
Hi, I'm Chris Vogel.
Hi.
We need to hire private detectives.
It's been two days since I was attacked
and the police still got no leads.
We thought we were scared before,
but now at these phone calls.
How many calls?
One last night and one this morning.
What does he say?
Death threats to all of us.
You mean you and the other performers?
Yeah. Myself, Randy, and Steve. Uh, just.
For the record, I think we can handle
this ourselves. We don't need you guys.
No.
Offense. No, no. None taken. But what
if you can't handle it without us?
No offense. Okay.
What's his.
Name? That's Randy Dillon.
Listen, don't take it personal.
He's plenty scared himself.
Now, uh, Chris, about our uh, feet.
Look, we pulled our money and we came up
with $600. Steal all your next. Chris,
you wanna strike your gotta go. Okay.
We're getting our stuff off. Stage.
600. Come on.
You guys just gotta come a time when we
stand by our 300 bucks plus expenses.
Come on. Yeah.
I say we max this thing out in
two days or ask for more money.
I say, you're right. That's
usual. I didn't say that.
Yeah, about what that was. The balls
are, We've had a girl who good.
I would call it wish I had a rabbit and
a hat with a back and a six to ball.
I wish I was like six nine so I can
give it Leo. Cause she don't know me.
But yo, she's really fine. You know,
I see her all the time. If you,
I don been in my dreams, like
I see my way, make her mind.
Cause I know she's living back. Her
boyfriend's tall and he play ball.
So how am I gonna compete with that?
Cause when it comes to playing.
I'm to be picking.
It and catch up. Pick it
off so I can up on the wall.
But sit up in Thes with the
girls who came to watch. You.
Know, I hear that cutting edge thing
in your music up there, but, uh,
go listen to some muddy and some
T-bone. You know what I'm saying?
Then come on back, we'll
talk about it. Thanks.
Hello. Listen.
Take this case and you're all.
Dead. Hello? Hello.
Cindy.
No, somebody's not too
happy. We're on the case.
Luck the guy.
Chris, what else can you
tell me about this guy? Man,
we don't have a whole
heck of a lot to go on.
Let's see the bat. The Nixon mask,
his weird voice. Oh, wait a second.
He said something when he was
chasing me. Something like, uh,
wait till your father gets home, Junior.
Okay, thanks.
Just wait till your father gets
home Junior. I'm telling you.
I know that line from somewhere.
Maybe it's from a movie or something.
Wait a minute, guys.
That phone call I got downstairs
was from the attacker. He said,
You better back off the
case or you're dead. Oh.
I mean, great. So now we're
risking our butts for 600 bucks.
Oh, don't pout.
I'm not ping.
So where do.
We start? First thing we should
do is check with the lapd. Huh?
See what your buddies
can dig up on the attack.
Yeah, sure. But one of us ought to
stick with Chris and his friends. Eh?
What's this.
Duncan's script?
Man, we better return this. You know how
he feels about it. Wait, wait. Hang on.
Bear's fair big a number
between one and 10. Five.
Seven.
It's two.
Five lower than seven here. This.
How come you always
get to pick the number?
I'm not pouting.
Say hi to Dunin for us, Mr. Vie. Thank.
You.
My funny Valenti.
Sweet.
Valenti.
Your looks.
Oh.
Mom, you're the best.
It's open.
Dunin. Hi.
Ryan. Oh, what a nice surprise. Come here.
Hey, who do you think should play
me in the movie? Uh, Macaulay Kin.
Sure, sure. Uh, I forgot your script.
Oh God. Thank you. Thank you.
Can I get you something to drink?
No wine, juice, water. No, no,
no. That's okay. No, no, no.
I'll just take a second. You know,
I'm waiting for a call from New
York about the paperback rights.
Now they're talking about putting
out the paperback before the movie.
I had no idea.
Mother was quite an amazing woman.
All those lies about a drinking
problem and a violent temper.
She was the perfect mother. Sweet, gentle,
kind. Just like on the TV show,
my movie will tell the truth
about Dahlia Valentine. Hey,
did you know that my funny Valentine was
the number one show for eight years in
the seventies? Mother was
bigger than Lucie Ball.
Are the awards hers? Yeah.
She received two for this
episode. Performance and writing.
Lucy didn't get one for that.
Hey, can I play it for you?
No. No. Oh, Duncan. No, I'm sorry. I
really have to go. Okay. I'm sorry.
Then maybe some other time. Oh.
See you later. Okay.
Hey, Carrie, How about a chili dog
with the works? Huh? All right. Uh,
hold the mustard, the relish,
the onions and, and the chili.
Okay.
Hey, you. Hi. You, uh,
you want a chili dog?
I think that to talk.
No problem.
I was outta line. I'm sorry
if I hurt your feelings.
No, no. It's okay. It's
just that, that, uh,
think about the feminine side. Well, it,
uh,  got me a little confused.
Right?
Can I get you some of the drink with.
That?
Can I ask you something?
Anything?
The last time, when was it?
? Uh, that's kind
of personal, isn't it?
I'll tell you when my last.
Time was. No, no. I don't want know. Or
when?
Half hour ago.
Half hour ago. On the bus. On the bus.
Perfectly natural for a
woman. My car broke down.
It's gonna cost a lot to repair. I have
to catch the bus to work. I was late,
so I did it. I just broke down and cried.
It's a catharsis. It's healthy.
Okay. All right. My last time, um,
I got it. That movie Field of Dreams,
Kevin Costner looks at his dad
coming out of the cornfield and says,
We play catch. One more
time. I cry. Great.
See, now that's progress.
Thank you.
Mitch. I have something else to ask you.
It's sensitive.
No, it's okay. Go ahead. I'm on a roll.
Can I borrow your car.
My car? Just for a little
while? Oh, you're right.
It's too much to ask. No, no. It's
quite all. Alright, take the car.
Thanks.
Have fun.
Think I'm gonna cry.
Ryan. C.
Oh gosh. Here comes darn.
Oh, he wants to thank us again. Any ideas?
Uh, urgent meeting. Okay. Top seeker,
very hush hush. Government. Will.
You have a devious mind?
Ryan? I like that woman.
Hi guys. Oh, what a beautiful day.
You would not believe the casting
problems I'm having on Viva Valenti Med
Ryan wanted to do it. Get this for scale,
but you know, I had to turn it down.
See,
I don't need the persona of some big
star interfering with my mother's essence
as a human being. I mean, you understand.
Do you understand though? You.
Absolutely. Definitely.
Right.
The actress that I cast will
have to understand who my
mother was on the inside.
Um, that's great. But we
have to, uh, go and Oh, oh.
Oh. Right, right, right. Did I tell
you guys I got all the domestic rights,
International rights
video and CD ROM rights.
I'm just waiting for New York to sign
up on the paperback rights and it is a
done deal.
Whoa. Look after the time. Uh, but we,
we have that meeting right to go.
Right, Right, right. Gotta go, gotta go.
Hang on just a second. Did I tell you
guys about Letterman and Lano? I did not.
I know that. I did not. They
possibly want me to produce. Right.
And maybe you crossed your fingers.
Direct a TV movie based on their lines.
What might be feature might be tv,
but most Likely's going to air.
If you guys are, You guys
are good. You guys are nice.
I will let you guys have a small part.
Hey, back at you.
I talked to Mitch. Mm-hmm. .
He said that the police don't have much
except that Steve Cutter served six
months on an assault charge.
And I'll check it out.
How was, uh, Duncan?
You.
Wouldn't believe his house?
Yeah. Would.
Just like, until your
father gets home. Junior.
You in there?
Steve,
you the.
Hey, Steve.
Oh God.
You sure you didn't see
anything? The room was dark.
Somebody popped me from behind. The
lights were What about, uh, Randy di No.
He said he was asleep
in his dressing room.
Kept coming up here.
You were lucky we got nail this guy
Chris. And he's got a bit of an attitude.
Duncan, just wait till
your father gets home.
Junior that line. It's.
Right.
On the tip of my tongue.
It's gotta be something else, huh?
You know something
besides both victims being
female. Impersonators. I'm
telling you the keys here.
I just don't know what it is.
Buchana, Alabama rider. Oh, hey
Cindy. How you doing? No, no, no.
Of course. Yeah. He's
sitting right here on,
Hey, honey, I left my keys.
No, no, no. That's okay.
I got a spare set. You sure?
All right, See you later. Bye.
.
. Very funny.
Cool. Wait a minute. What?
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got
the connection. Dahlia Valentine.
Dahlia Valentine,
The guy who played Joan Rivers said
the only person who didn't do Dahlia in
their act was Sid. Right? Yeah.
What does that give us? Uh, yeah.
What does that give us? That gives us,
I don't know. What does that give us?
My funny Valentine. My funny Valentine.
Come on. Come on. The theme song.
A dahlia's TV show. Just wait till
your father gets home, Junior.
Just wait till your father gets
home. Junior. That's what she always.
Said to her TV Key Duncan.
I'm lost. You're.
Too young. Uh, he.
Was a child star. He, he
played her son on the TV.
Show. You think Duncan did this?
I don't know, but there's
one way to find out.
We could just set a trap and have one
of the impersonators do. Dahlia got.
Huh? Which one? They're all
scared to death. Yeah. Um,
what?
He's a little tall, nice legs,
decent voice. Not great, but not bad.
What might even help him get
in touch with his feminine
?
Don't even think it.
.
Even when a guy is hopelessly lost, he
will not stop and ask for directions.
Women think we're too proud
or too stupid. I don't know.
But I have a feeling that I
may have just missed a turn.
Okay, Now.
Just hold still.
Oh.
Stop pouting.
Ooh. You going to be hot, baby?
Okay. You can gimme your honest opinion.
Alright? Okay.
Okay. Turn around.
So, Oh, you look great. Just like, uh,
Dolia Valentine. Except for
one thing. What? You're, uh,
boxed small.
You know, I'm gonna knock you.
To very funny.
You.
Know, this was not my idea. All right.
Hey, Cindy.
Matt.
Oh.
It's not what you think. Honest.
I knew you were too good to be true. I
knew it. I knew it. I didn't understand.
It's for a case. God. It's for a case.
Your keys.
Buy. Oh, wage. It's for a case. Nice.
Try, Mitch.
Well, you told me to get in
touch with my feminine side.
Hey, big girl. Okay, Ryan.
So, so what's the pledge?
Well, you'll find out in a minute.
Okay. Where do I get the feeling?
I'm gonna hate it. You stuck.
It's not that bad. See, look
what.
Whoop be Goldberg.
Me.
Will be Goldberg in that dress.
Now you must be dreaming.
No.
Garner mean. Well. I'm out in
front watching the audience.
You gotta be in the back, you
know, Undercover. Low profile.
Low profile in a dress.
Not me, babe. Come.
On.
This is the only way to do it. I
mean, you know, when in Rome, Duaz,
No. Garner, please look, it's your
size. It's your color. It's good. Yeah.
Read my lips. No.
Great shoes.
No. No.
Is it true about.
It's showtime and I definitely
had a case of the jitters. I mean,
it wasn't bad enough that I had
to go on stage dressed as a woman,
but I was also.
Baked.
Let me a choice, please. Will you
sit down? You made me so nervous.
I've had four cups of coffee.
I don't even like coffee.
Yes, son. Dunk.
Yeah, he's in the audience alone.
Where's Garner?
He's watching the crowd. He's
fine. Everything's fine. Um,
Mitch what? Mitch.
What?
Well, um, your,
your left one is higher
than your right one.
Oh. Um, can you fix it?
Yeah. You want me to fix.
Fix it? I'm not touching
though. Yeah. Two minutes,
Mitch. Very good. Good luck. Okay.
Okay. I'm ready.
Don't change your for me.
Not if you,
Mitch, Mitch.
Mitch, Mitch Whoopie.
It's me. Mitch. Am I Hell,
Mitch, are you alright? Who?
I'm alive. Thanks for that vest. Huh?
Could you, could you make off the shooter?
No.
I'll call 9 1 1.
Go, go.
Come on Duncan. Give it up, man.
What the hell's going on here?
Randy, put the gun down, man.
And we'll talk about this. Huh?
What the hell are you doing? Shut
up to, This is all your fault.
You should have cast me in
your movie. What? You're a man.
I am Dahlia Valentine.
This is my house. And you are a dead man.
Wait a minute. Uh, Duncan,
uh, talk to your mother.
She'll listen to you.
Mother. It'll be a great movie.
Everyone will want to come see it.
Who will play me?
Well, you, you are, you dia no
one, no one else could play you.
They tried.
I stop them.
You're the star mother as always.
Just wait.
Until your father gets home.
Junior,
Randy, man.
Bad call on our part. You got that right?
Thanks again, guys. Now
I really owe you. Hey,
did I mention that every a-list director
in town is fighting to do my movie?
I mean, every director. But to tell you
the truth, I'm gonna direct it myself.
I mean, you know, after all, who
knows mother better than me. I mean,
I've only had my whole
life to study her moves.
I know every inch of her up and down.
Yeah.
This $600 paycheck gotta almost pay our.
Rent. I not you to make
Lou almost halfway.
Mitchell Buchanan.
Yes. I'm Mitch. You're
not from the irs. Are you?
Not even close.
I figured you can get in
touch with your feminine side.
I could get in touch
with my masculine side.
I like it.
Ladies and gentlemen. Mr. Lou.
Raymond.
To be
to work all day. I, you
even do. I said
make love. I
wash my clothes.
I don't want you keep my home.
I don't want your money to, I said
love.
To
in the, It can blow your dreams.
There's a, you got, you can't
in the, you can hear the siren,
Devil.