In.
The city of.
People.
Are drowned in the sea.
And part time
the.
You can.
Good morning, Buchanan, It's me.
Hey you, you at the office?
Not even float. Check the
bluff behind your tower.
.
Wow. You real heartbreaker Ry when
you got a hot date or something?
Yeah. I wish more like the
Malibu Women's Club luncheon.
I'm lecturing on the
pitfalls of being a woman pi.
And then after that I'm gonna network
those rich ladies right outta their
faragamo pumps.
. I'm sure you will.
Listen. A potential client wants to meet
with you today. Her name is Jerry Ross.
Our office five o'clock. Okay.
I'll be there.
All right. Good luck.
Thank you ladies.
Thank you. You guys
were fantastic as usual.
Thank you Byebye sweetheart.
Use me.
It's your life, right? That's your step.
A tough day at the office, huh?
Hey, anytime you want to trade. Mitch.
Are you in a new case?
I'll know in three minutes.
Oh yeah.
Wow. What kind of case?
I don't know, Greg.
Don't tell me. I bet it's a murder, right?
A beautiful Malibu social like it's
whacked by a young jealous lover. Huh.
Uh. I'll know about, uh, two minutes.
This is gonna be big Mitch. I could
feel it. I could feel it. Just like, um,
the bogie multis falcon or, or
dub indemnity? Barbara Stanwick.
Mitch Buchanan.
Miss uh.
Jerry Ross.
Pacific Coast Yacht Club.
Right? Right. Very nice to meet you. Good.
What? Oh, . Oh yeah, yeah, sure.
Uh, coffee.
Perhaps two. Motor yachts were robbed
during the past week. Mr. Buchanan.
The most recent occurring last night.
What about the police?
Strict orders, No publicity.
Now since the thief apparently
boarded the boats from the water,
our club directors felt
that perhaps your, um,
lifeguard experience could serve
us well. Are you interested?
Yes. Yes, of course. Okay.
All pertinent information
concerning the two boats,
as well as I trust a sufficient retainer.
Um, this will be fine.
Tomorrow night launches our
affiliate marina golf tournament.
Folks are coming in from all over
California and we don't need any more
robberies. Understood.
Understood. Good.
Hmm. Clyde, I hope I spell Cline to you.
You're not serious.
This spells Clive to me.
Security guard.
Hey.
I'm up top, top making my rounds right?
Smoking a cigarette mind
and my own business.
All of a sudden I see a flashlight
now, another people out of town.
So I come up around here to check
it out. Oh, out of the blue,
this guy knocks me off on my. Down
the steps. Chase up the steps here.
Right around. Leave downs off the
side, man. Don't even see him again.
Just like that.
And after he knocked me down the
stairs, he ran up to the bridge here.
Climbed out that window.
Dove off right there.
Now.
Who might you be? Handsome.
It should all look like a law man.
Maybe I can mix a little
pleasure with business.
Hey.
Found this on the swim step. What is it?
Tape from the o ring on a scuba tank.
West.
Sea, maybe West Coast Divers.
You wanna check it out? Yeah.
Along with that security guy.
Mr. Buchanan. Hey.
Jerry Ross, I like you to
meet my partner. Garner lb.
How.
Do you do.
Ms. Ross? You know, if the owners
are this boat or scuba divers.
Mr. Buchanan, they're in their
late sixties. They drink martinis.
Very nice. Dana. This is
a very good night's work.
It's reward you for your
work. I'm gonna give you
$30,000.
You're dreaming again, Carl.
Okay? Nina, I'm in a good mood today.
Why don't we say 50 k?
Put a whole package.
I don't think I heard you.
Nina. Want you to listen Very careful
to me. Cause it's gonna be my last off.
$60,000.
75.
Tough Nina. Okay, 75 deal. Done.
So tell me something, Nina. What
we're gonna do with all this money?
Two more deals and I'm done.
Don, what the hell do you mean? Done.
Means I made my net and
I'm out of the business.
If you can't quit, you're
natural. Hey, you and me,
we could work the whole West coast, make
some real money. You know, something.
They got. Marin is all over the world.
Tonight and tomorrow
night, and then I'm done.
You're kidding yourself, Nina.
Once this gets in your blood,
it doesn't go away overnight. I've seen
it before. It never leaves your system.
Never.
Hey.
You're looking for me.
Just gonna borrow your water.
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey. There's a restroom for.
That. I don't need a restroom.
Hello? Oh, no, no, no, baby.
I love the club and I'm gonna turn
into a real money maker. Yeah,
me too. Mm-hmm. . Well,
I'm just gonna do a run, swim, run.
Okay. Byebye.
Run, swim run, Huh? In
training for something special.
? Yep. I'm gonna be
a lifeguard just like you.
So let's walk away.
Oh.
Okay.
Is that something about the fish burglar?
Oh, uh, no. It's nothing that exciting.
It's just insurance photos
from stolen jewelry.
Whoa. These are some serious dimes.
Yeah. Very serious.
This is one very cool case. You know,
it's all about money, power, and sex.
Are we talking about the same case here?
Uh, Ryan, listen, uh, since this is
such a biggie, if you need any help,
know that I'm available.
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
I'll keep that in mind.
Roll up your sleeves. McBride tr work.
Hey, what's this? Some clues.
Uh, receipts from the
West Coast dive shop.
We've got match your name and a date
with that piece of tape Mitch found.
Hey, you need some help?
Uh, yes. Yes. As a matter of fact,
we do  know this is a
great way you to get your feet
wet. A don't you.
That boy, Mitch. Perfect.
Easy, easy, easy, easy. No, no,
no, no. Don't get up. Don't get up.
Get my first aid kit. Don't get up.
All right. I'm gonna check you
out. Make sure nothing's broken.
All I feel so stupid. . It's okay.
You got a nasty bruise.
Here. Let me clean this up.
I haven't fallen like
this since I was a kid.
All right. I should
do. This is fine. Okay.
All right. Easy.
You're moving pretty fast out there.
Don't tell me you're gonna
gimme a speeding ticket.
No, but it means I'm gonna give you a
warning. Will you slow down, please?
Yes, sir. Nina. Cutter.
Mr. Bamp.
I promise to slow down if you
let me repay your fees. So.
Kind. Well, that's not
necessary. I'm glad you're okay.
You like lobster?
Uh, actually, I, uh, I love lobster.
Let me cook you dinner some night.
Well, that is an offer
that I cannot refuse.
Okay. Grab my hand, right? Okay.
Oh.
Sorry.
Excuse me. Hey.
Hold on your breath now.
Hey partners.
Hey, hey.
Think I got an idea. I
catch a little fish, bro.
Well, that's good. We just
go so far. We got Didley.
I checked out a security guard. He's
got a record for stolen cars, man.
This is way out of his league.
So what's your.
Idea in on and underwater surveillance.
So what are you gonna do, Mitch?
You're gonna wait in the water until
this boat burglar makes his move.
Yeah.
That's it.
Probably. Come on. There must
be a thousand boats in the ver.
Concentrate on the 15. Visiting
yachts with Liverboards.
They're all in for a
convention and dock. Same area.
All you guys gotta do is drink
bag coffee and eat donuts.
How.
You doing, Mitch?
Okay. I was starting to feel the cold.
Listen, I'll head down one more
time and cold tonight, huh?
Yeah, Roger that.
Yeah.
I had him. He disappeared and headed
west. I'll keep looking in the zodiac.
Watch your back.
You see any movement up there?
No. No place is like a morgue.
Hold it right there.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey,
Nina. Who is it? Mitch.
Mitch Buchanan.
Mitch.
I thought you were that cat where we've
been hearing so many rumors about.
No cats here. Size. Say, hey, water.
You look like you could eat some tea.
What's up?
Look, I've searched the whole
channel for him. No sign.
What do you say We call it tonight,
huh? We'll see you guys tomorrow.
See you tomorrow. Where are
you? Uh, I'm worth a friend.
A friend.
Affirmative. Over and out.
A.
No Mitchell's, lots of friends.
Oh, you're right.
I, uh, noticed all your
swimming trophies. Sprinter.
Backstroke.
Ah, backstroke. How far did you get?
Almost to the Olympics till a bad
rotator cuff ended that dream.
Hardly swim at all anymore,
but I love being by the.
Water. You ever do any, uh,
springboard diving or platform?
I love them both.
Scuba?
No, I'm a surface summer,
bad inner ear.
I think you have very nice ears.
Really?
I always thought they were kind of big.
No, no. I think that they're just right.
Better be careful. It's
one of my weak spots.
What about your left?
Especially the left.
I thought you didn't have time to play.
I don't.
Oh, wait, wait a minute. I, My
tickets. Oh, come on. Fifth row.
Oh, all right. They're yours.
You're killing me, man.
I just gave up my fifth row king tickets
for nothing. This is gonna cost you.
What?
You asked me to run the name Nina Cutter
through the police computer, right?
Well, this woman has no arrest, no
moving violations, no parking violations,
no nothing. The name in
the cutter is so clean.
It squeaks by who isn't in the cutter.
And why does Byron have my king tickets?
Like I told Ryan, I I met her yesterday.
I bumped into her again at the
marina last night. And, uh, well,
she lives on a boat, so I
just, when I check her out.
Oh, oh, oh, oh. I see. So there's a
little flutter of the heartstrings.
Whose heartstrings are a flutter.
Private investigations
may ask who's calling
Nina Cutter online one.
You very much.
Hey, you.
Hi. I just wanted to call and say that
I had a very nice time last night.
Yeah. So did I. You make
a wicked cup of tea.
How are your ears?
They're still tingling. I'd like
to make you that lobster dinner I.
Promised. Sounds good.
Are you busy tonight?
I am now.
Seven 30.
Seven 30 for lobster.
Looking forward to it.
See you then. Bye.
What? She's gorgeous.
Wants to cook me lobster.
She's got great ears.
So you're taking you to dinner?
No, no. She's taking me.
Well, that's really stupid.
Stupid.
That's what I said. Stupid.
What's your problem?
It's not my problem. You're the
one making a fool outta yourself.
Well, of having dinner with a
beautiful woman makes me a fool. And.
And you're jeopardizing
this investigation.
No.
I'm not. She's a suspect. We.
Checked her out.
Right? You wanted to have her
eliminated. So we eliminated her.
But she's a champion.
Swimmer lives on a bow.
She doesn't scuba dive.
Maybe she lied.
Maybe you're jealous.
Jealous. Is that what you think?
That's exactly what I think.
That I'm jealous.
Yes. Me having a wonderful lobster
dinner with a beautiful woman.
Think of that as a pre lobster
dinner appetizer. Have a good time.
You got a shirt I can borrow?
Yeah, sure.
I used to.
It was worth the pain.
I'll go get some more.
Okay.
Yeah.
Mitch, we finished the dive shop proceeds
and came up with some possibility.
Nina cutters on the top of the list.
Yeah.
Yeah. She, uh, field tanks on the days
of both the robberies and this morning.
Sorry man.
Thanks.
Mitch. What's wrong?
Oh, um, I gotta go.
Oh.
I hope it's nothing serious.
No, no. I, I just forgot. I'm working
the late shift for a very unhappy client.
Well help your clients big and
ugly there some beer. No teeth.
Bye.
She's pretty hot looking, Huh?
Who?
Nina. Cutter.
Yeah, she is.
And you like her a lot?
And what if she turns out
to be this cat burglar?
She'll go to prison and
I'll never see her again.
So what did you dry out
your wetsuits together?
She's got company.
All right.
I'll have Garner on the license plate
on that Lincoln through the computer.
This has gotta be his car.
I need a hundred thousand
Carl. Non-negotiable.
All right. Conditional that you
don't retire for another month.
Me and I got some ideas that
could make us both very rich.
Can't do that. Carl. Now
are you interested or do I
have to go somewhere else?
You must love your brother very much.
What did you just say?
Come on, Nina. I know what
you're doing with the money.
Lawyers fees for your brother. You
see, he used to work for this, uh,
yacht club until he was convicted for
embezzling half a million dollars.
My brother didn't do it.
He was framed by the board of directors
who were trying to cover up some shady
investments. How the hell did
you know about this? Anyway.
I got friends in low places. Nina.
I really admire your spirit,
but you're wasting your time.
Get outta here, Carl. This is over. Like.
Hell. It's over. Hey, we got a deal.
You don't just walk out on a deal.
Get out.
I see a point. It's just leaving.
He's a fence.
Yeah. Carl James Benke
specializes in jewelry.
He's been keeping a low profile lately,
but he's done six years of our time.
Is he still with Nina?
Yeah.
About two minutes away when bands
comes out, Sit on it. Uh, until I get.
Theres, Yeah, I Investigators,
You know, a Nina Cutter?
Yeah, I don't. Nina Cutter.
That's her boat right over there.
We know all about you Bains. In fact,
I've got some partners down in LAPD
who've been wondering where you've been.
Yo, you tell 'em that I've been clean
for the last three years in counting.
Well, maybe they'd like to know why you
just visited a suspected jewel thief.
Look, we want Nina Cutter Bains.
You give her up your driveway.
Oh look, I'll be honest with you, Alright.
We were talking about doing a little
deal, but that, that's over. Now. See,
my conscious got got the better than me.
The police will be real interested.
Okay, Look, you wanna know the
truth. I'll tell you the truth.
Where.
It is that she's doing
another boat tonight.
So what are you running away from home?
Funny. Part of my new plan.
What is this done?
Cutting edge technology
end half of our retainer.
What? It was on sale.
So with you guys on shore using these
night vision devices and me and the water
with my trustees sonar scanner, we
should have all the guest births covered.
What do you.
Think? Well, aside from the cost, it's
uh, well, better than your last plan.
Yeah, I gotta admit you.
Can you done yourself?
Why don't I feel good about it?
Well, don't worry, partner. I mean,
there's still a chance it's not Nina.
Yeah. Slim and none. Yo.
Guys, guess what?
I have just cleared my calendar so
I can help you guys out. No charge.
Well, what do you say? Yeah, ,
this is great. I promise you guys, I will
not let you down. I'm gonna go change.
Hey, growth. Yeah. No trench coats.
I can't believe this thing costs
650 bucks and it was on sale.
Oh, hey, come on now. This stuff is
gonna put you guys on the high tech map.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Yeah. Who wants to be a
speed bump on the info Super.
Highway?
Oh yeah. Yeah, you're right. Gar.
But you can't eat a night scope.
I'm in position.
Okay, we got you, Mitch.
Hang on guys. I got something.
You see any boats coming
in from the south?
Yeah. You got one sailboat
backing out from a dock.
It's too far out in the channel
or it's too big to be a fish.
Guys, this may be Nina,
if the yards still coming.
I'm honor guys. I'm right honor.
She's right under me.
When I lost her guys,
I'm going under
radio check. Garner. Do you hear
me? Gotcha. Loud and clear, Mitch.
I mean, This's pretty good.
No sign of her.
Mitch, you've got traffic
from the south. Wake speed.
I repeat traffic from the south. Keep
your head up, man. Traffic from the south.
Got it. Griffin, bold. I see her.
Remember sued. She's headed South.
South. Mitch, that boat traffic
is coming from the south.
I don't see it yet.
Mitch, that boat is getting
close. Do you see it? It's right.
There. I don't see it. I don't see it.
Mitch, that boat right on top of you Now.
See it. I see.
It's coming right at
her. Nina, stop. Nina.
She's hit it. She lost her air.
God. God, She's hung out on the keel,
so she's gonna drown going after her.
Stop the boat.
There's no time. Mitch,
how do we stop the boat?
I got an idea.
I don't know, man. Stopped.
I got her golfer back.
I'm on the surface.
Mitch. Mitch.
Okay. Okay. Okay, girl.
Easy. Just spit it out.
Slow and easy. Give a jacket.
It easy. I.
I checked into Nina's background
and found out some things
that you might wanna know about.
Wrong. I don't want to know.
Okay.
Nina has a brother in prison serving
three to five from embezzling,
half a million dollars from
the Pacific Coast Yacht Club.
Nice one. The family.
She thought he was innocent and then it
was a Senate she was stealing in order
to pay for the lawyers and
get her brother a new trial.
Still doesn't make it right?
No, it doesn't. But it shows
that she had good intentions.
Thanks. You're welcome,
dear. No,
how about you? One,
it can blow your dreams.
There's a got you can
in the
what's.