[Music]
he's in the cabin
Marty are you here
[Music]
there's one in the water
brilliant rhyme on the ball which is I
checked the boat before it went down he
wasn't on it
let's take a look he's on the forward
for God's sake just check the boat damn
it we've looked everywhere else
all right I'm gonna check it again but
I'm telling you to waste the time Toby's
in the spare air
[Music]
you
in a City of Angels under cover of night
people are drown
in a sea of light
[Music]
the devil's holding your life um
angel : rainbow time
[Music]
some
we Doris too late
[Applause]
[Music]
it's going to live
[Applause]
Oh
now
[Music]
[Applause]
John you new here something's wrong here
he wasn't on that part you're the
lifeguard
you're supposed to save her you let him
die
oh it's it's la verga keep us busy for a
year first assignment may be small but
this point I don't care well I'll tell
you what we'll do we'll get our feet in
the door and this let the money will
there what's going on I'm making some
changes well you just did a whole
makeover oh that was the big stuff but
we both know if you wanted to fly you
got accessorize swap what you got for
what's on that wall Oh put those on the
far I love a man who its presence inside
presence Oh Ryan um Mitch called said to
tell you he'd be a little late no not
today you didn't didn't did he say where
he is at sunset at sunset what is sunset
what is this like some code what is that
it's a server beach
so here you got a problem Eddie what's
up
you know if you ever been in a situation
where you know you're absolutely right
and everyone else thinks you're
absolutely wrong yeah it's got to stick
to what you know is truth
she's gonna get my 10 days in pass my
read check keep my nose clean and I get
suspended Eddie you weren't suspended
maybe not officially but when the man
says take some time off that amounts are
the same thing so what are they saying
Mitch Kramer blew a rescue buddy it
could have happened to any one of us it
didn't happen to anyone does it happen
to me Mitch I'm telling you there's
something wrong here
I don't know what to tell you I need
your help
hi are you alright you're not gonna hire
me if you want my help I'll give you my
help but you're not gonna hire me well
thanks yes I'm not going down without a
fight I want to know what really
happened I do it but I'm on suspension
that's why I need you to check things
out your lifeguard mitt you know what
goes on out here
all right all right let's go get
someplace warm and start from the
beginning huh Thanks
uh just a little confusion here about
this is not firm business this is
personal what is the case well I find
myself in a very difficult situation and
basically my life is falling apart my
wife has left me separated won't divorce
me has to do with children I want some
she doesn't we're so different really
I wonder Paul could you kind of get to
the point I the point is uh well I have
a mistress I suppose that's what you
would call her it when I say the word
mistress it seems wrong it sounds seedy
and viola joy that's her name joy
there's none of that she's really quite
wonderful I love her more than I thought
I could love anyone in this turmoil
she's been my Haven um I still don't
understand what's the problem I think
he's gonna kill me no not herself she's
gonna get someone what makes you think
that uh before me joy had another
boyfriend
[Music]
a well-connected man well-connected with
that business interests in Las Vegas
mobster I cannot believe that I'm in the
middle of something like this my wife is
gone which isn't a bad thing and now the
woman that I love that's gonna have me
killed all right Eddie tell me
everything from the top it's just after
lunch I'm in the Scarab heading back to
headquarters now I spot a 30-foot sport
Fisher dead in the water and it's
smoking
now I'm just about battling three clicks
from the marina entrance I call for
backup I head for the boat
this is scarab one said backup now
there's a woman okay I see you're
struggling to launch a dinghy right
there's smoke everywhere there's a guy
in the cabin who's tossing out
lifejackets engine fire no how can you
tell
smokes lighter swing me the guy in the
cabin come down
it climbs into the D
now by the time I get to the people of
the dinghy they moved away
okay so when I pull up again ADIZ
yelling
any saying if there's someone still in
the boat I swim out right
try to make it to the cabin I do make it
to the cab and I get to the smoke
everywhere it's bending forward wires
right
[Music]
are you here
and the cabin is Emily
you checked the head yes I did I saw
that there was nobody there I even
checked the engine compartment there was
nobody that was empty
all right how long that day I don't know
a minute give or take so now when I come
out I yell till I say she's still
screaming arms still on the boat and all
this excitement she's certain yeah yeah
[Music]
then the boat goes down back up then
arrives back up other lifeguards yeah
Mitch telling you we checked it okay
everywhere nothing
so I dived the boat I go right to the
cabin
[Music]
and you found him he was on the boat
yeah
Wow well so who's the Dead Guy
Marty Jennings he's the woman's husband
the other guys her brother all right
as crazy as a sound you tell me what you
think happened this was no accidental
drowning Mitch what'd the cops say well
they said that there was no evidence of
foul play so they want to push the
investigation you telling me you think
the guy was murdered why would they do
that I don't mean kill someone I mean
kill him this way
Donnell what caused the boat to sink I
don't know what caused the fire
I don't know that either Mitch man this
is a real mystery can you help me
Mitchum
I can sure try
who is it possible that your lifeguard
friend just blew it absolutely the hope
link so he's a very good way anyway
that's what I want you to find out would
you check with the coroner's office and
now talk to the guys downtown thank you
okay well then we need you to watch
Paul's mistress no problem
look the mistress has stashed away on
Paul Richards yacht ruins a storeroom in
the Yacht Club is our bird's nest it's
got a perfect view of which it's both
which by the way has already been booked
how that happened well the more you get
it himself
in fact this is his stuff five general
crystal receiver two extra bugs long
Lin's video camera the car has a homing
device and this is a tracker what part
of this is legal it's all legal
he owns the car he owns the boat at any
pace reform beautiful thing
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah its Mitch hey Mitch steady Eddy
you're calling to make me crazy you got
something to talk about come on I was
just calling to find out what's going on
how you doing you're calling to drive me
crazy now look relax okay go work out or
something and don't call me again hey
Mitch it's not easy being left behind
you know all right all right
look I'll meet you nights around 10
o'clock hi everything I know all right
remember how I was telling you I was
having this problem when chicks find out
that I cut up people for a living
well I have got a new approach yeah what
was in his stomach
lunch hot dog chili fries how long
between the time when he ain't what he
done Oh about an hour give or take you
know um I have this whole new method now
I tell them what I do but I make it
sound like Tales from the Crypt very
mysterious very McCobb what and this
works Hey
it has done wonders for my social life
you know McBride you have a very
sophisticated technique where'd you pick
that up at a Brooklyn general and then
at Northwestern was there anything
unusual about the blood workup a blood
workup hasn't come back in did you treat
this like a accident or a murder
accident most drownings are would you
have treated anything differently if
they had said it was a murder
come on McBride 27 bodies come in here
every day sometimes 40 bodies a day can
be as many as 180 200 bodies a week
still you're probably not gonna find
anything if you're not looking for it
looking for what footprints what print
we're come on you know we're soft tissue
body fluids the way you're talking you
make us sound like some murder yeah
that's exactly what I think
it was a murder based on what based on
the fact that the man was already
unconscious when he drowned listen give
me a call when the test results come
back have them check the pleural cavity
for traces of carbon tell you what I can
deliver those test results in person
maybe uh maybe over lunch what do you
think just call me you're still my dream
McBride keep dreaming
hey Felder I need this stuff like
yesterday
[Music]
hey joy it's Paul I'm gonna be hung up
tonight so dinners off I'll call you
tomorrow
[Music]
your eyes but the man we talked about
this number is very good told of you be
home
[Music]
ah yeah
hey how's it going well joy is waiting
on the hip man to call how you doing
well you're drowning is very suspicious
there's no trauma to his hands his legs
or his feet
Brian people don't drive without a
struggle they kick and fight yeah that's
right but from the contents of his lungs
he did drown and he did drown in the
ocean there's no alcohol there's no
drugs except for insulin but that's cuz
he was a diabetic now the complete blood
workup won't be ready until tomorrow so
I'm having them run tests on the liquid
from his lungs looking for carbon
residue if there's no carbon residue
from the smoke then that would mean that
he was dead before the fire started
which explains why Eddie didn't see him
and he wasn't looking for a dead guy
look good work huh call me back if you
get any more info okay all right I'll
call you later
hey hey it's going huh lady's waiting on
the call I didn't get much from the cops
about the drowning no evidence of foul
play
no real motive wife's loaded family
company lots of money Marty had no
enemies pretty likable guy give me a
favor will you handle it here I want to
pay a little visit to a grieving widow
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
cluck you're not ready to commit
giggles thank you
ah mrs. Jennings please yes right this
way thank you
okay
this is Jenny's first to let me offer
you my condolences I thank you mr. haha
you can't Mitch PK ah your friend Marty
no actually uh I'm a private detective
if this is about the insurance just go
talk to my attorney
no it's not I represent Eddie Kramer who
the lifeguard I'm found your husband I'm
sorry is there a problem here
I'm Doris his brother piers and this is
Mitch something-or-other he represents
the lifeguard who let Marty duck he
wants to talk about the excellent you
know that idiot lifeguard if he'd had
his eyes open he could have gotten Marty
off of that boat Corning Eddie he says
he looked everywhere well that's bull
marty was in the cabin I saw him there
door saw him there and your client
didn't know maybe he got scared and
that's okay except it's his job not to
get scared am I right or what
Marty stay behind to put out the fire he
loved that boat it's just trying to
think it's all right Doris now why don't
you win sideline down
my sister is taking this badly I'm sorry
if this lifeguard is getting all the
blame for this you know may be wrong but
that's the way it is look I'll see if I
can get everyone to ease off none of
this is gonna bring Marty back you have
a card
yeah well thank you for your time
oh thank you
[Music]
thought you said this would be easy
oh don't let a few questions rattle your
doors you got what you wanted
Marty's dead I'm scared what did we get
caught what won't what are you gonna do
first I'm gonna get this pi2 back off
and then we'll get closure on what we
were doing before the lifeguard
interrupted us
[Music]
we don't talk business on the phone
maybe tomorrow or o'clock on the marina
Hornblower at fisherman village
oh god I don't know if I can go through
with this your choice how I know it's
you
you won't whatever you think I look like
I don't I'll find you
[Music]
oh that's a strange reaction maybe I can
go home
[Music]
you know Lou Eddie is a damn good
lifeguard there's no way he'd miss a
rescue I'm just trying to make some
sense of what happened on the boat hey
miss check it out
at the time of the murder to kill his
completely whacked out nothing he does
make sense or is rational and then you
come along a couple of days later you
trying to make sense out of somebody
else's craziness it's good I'm done with
yeah yeah but what looking for a motive
a motive you know I work for a dude in
Jersey out of club one night his old
lady picked up by his picking put in his
brain cuz he wouldn't pass the peas
you're kidding that's what the cop said
to her had to be more to it than that
not to her that's what I'm talking about
you cannot make sense out of somebody
else's craziness
[Music]
alright I'll dive the boat tomorrow I'm
sure the answers are there I'll go with
you
no you can't you too close the case you
can't dine alone well I'll go with you
you certified
yeah I'm certified I don't photo shoots
for magazines up and down the coast and
I can document everything you're fine
all right here all thanks well you
obviously gonna need me who's all come
out here he's under lift yeah I know
excuse me are you with the P AI agent C
from upstairs here we are I'm Levi
Marcia I'm a private detective
I've been asked by a client to do some
work in this part of town and since
these aren't my streets I need some
people in know the area oh well do you
come to the right place
great let's get the money out of the way
first I can pay you $500 an hour to a
guarantee of 200 hours a guarantee of
200 hours what's the job well my clients
may be involved in some kind of legal
action regarding the boat sinking with
loss of life yeah the Eddie Kramer case
right my clients may need your expertise
you mean your clients need us to back
off let's be real clear about this I'm
offering you a legitimate job now you
can take it or don't that's your choice
sorry pal we already have a client
conflict of interest
that's all you needed to say
I see you
do you guys realize we just passed up
$100,000 yeah well we sure not
somebody's attention guess so
so back to her another problem
according to garner Paul's mistress is
supposed to meet the hit man tomorrow at
fisherman's village but she has no idea
what he looks like
neither Dewayne well no but if we can
spot him and garner can scare him off ie
I'm sure he's afraid of cops then you
become the head man
we get her on tape case closed all right
so I'll dive the boat in the morning
then I will meet you and put on my best
dinero
Oh
ah
was it something I said
I'll back off
don't make me have to talk to you again
well the next time
that won't be so nice
yeah
now what the hell do you think you're
gonna do we were paid to whip your ass
which we did
you'll be faint with us Chum we're just
doing a job and for us it's over unless
you want to make it personal no I'll go
on address the night off
ah
the man's a very determined item you
wouldn't buy off and I don't think we
scared him off I overheard him say that
he was gonna dive on the wreck and my
guess is he's still gonna do it
well then we'll stop him this is getting
totally out of hand well whose fault is
that
you know marty was your problem from the
beginning you married him you make him
crazy you drive him to a divorce and
then you tick him off so bad he won't
settle with you I told you that a
contested divorce would ruin us
but you didn't listen to me he'd never
listen to me the courts open up the
company books and in two seconds they
can prove we've been skimming for the
last seven years I offered him money too
late and too little
you thought marty was such a pushover
god you're the one I should have left
out on the boat
pretty grip let's do it
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go back down under some a couple
hundred yards suffer since women
all right here's what I think it
happened way from the brother on the
process of killing Marty they ripped out
the water cooling lines floods a boat
the open a fuel line issued a flare into
the engine compartment which starts a
fire burning up all the evidence now
everything is working perfectly then
Eddie happens to come along
they should have panicked but didn't I
know instead they stuffed Marty in the
seat Locker and they tie a bobber into
the latch the boat sinks the water rises
the latch comes loose the bobber lifts
up the cover on the seat Locker and out
floats Marty
well can we prove it Ryan well it'll
need more than that but it's enough to
get Eddie off the hook and that's pretty
much all we care about well let the cops
worry about the rest all right let's get
these photos to the police well that's
great
hey it's it's four o'clock we gotta go
yeah are you yeah I'll take care of it
okay look so we can communicate this is
the transmitter right this is the
receiver all right look you stay here
we're gonna go get her offer on tape
that's all I need
I can't believe this I didn't think she
really wanted to do this I still love
her you know it's ironic the woman who
made me feel so alive now wants to kill
me I wait here to ryan gets back
hey Mitch Mitch hey we got a problem
Eddie was by man he talked to Griffin
yeah and saw the pictures all right I
gotta go let me go
but no which we need you here Eddie's a
hothead if he talked to Griffiths all
those pictures he's gonna be going after
the widow and her brother you say that
no but he got crazy and split
uh Mitch there's joy all right you guys
gonna have your handlers without me bill
you're on um Joey doesn't know what the
hater looks like hang with me on this
loo what do we do where we can
I'll stay with Paul all we need to get
as a tape first listening a murder all
right
[Music]
he was that man
don't turn around keep looking the wall
are you the man supposed to meet yeah
well what exactly is it you want I have
an envelope in my purse and there's
$5,000 in it
she's gonna do it it's exactly what you
want us to do for this $5,000
let's go away and six reach for your
time bra time
yes I've changed my mind I don't want to
kill her her of course her
what did you think
here who's him the lawyer for what's
this oh god no I could never happened
I loved him it was his wife she's a
beast I mean she's ruining his life
I thought if I could get rid of his wife
then he'd be all mine but I just love it
she loves me oh she loves me
I said to come alone
the man you talked to on the phone hey
you're not he is
see what I mean bro what you make a hell
of a hit man you're here I heard it all
I thought you were gonna have me killed
Oh baby no I just got so tired of seeing
you miserable I'm so sorry
Oh love you gonna be back
craziness tsunami craziness
let's go really in that low life huh
what's you
after losing about the rack I was
expecting someone but I thought it'd be
the cops
you should have killed that P I look I
think it's time for us to leave we'll
take an extended holiday you tell your
friends you're grieving you need to rest
well let things cool down it doesn't
matter what they find at the wreck they
have no real evidence because there is
not what about him
delay him I discourage him give us some
time how far can I take it I don't care
were they where are they
relax they're by the swimming pool
follow me
where the hell are they going where the
hell is Eddie
man what's up
yeah
ah
Oh
[Applause]
the good news is they're forcing an
indictment based on our evidence so so
yeah well for you whatever Doris and
Pierce is just getting started
so Mitch I wanted to say want to say
thanks thank all of you really you're
great
no throw on the problem sure you would
have done the same for us well so what
now we've got this gorgeous day here
with no case what are we gonna do meet
I'm headed uptown where's a lovely lady
there who requires my attention
me I'm gonna sleep for a month see you
later
well I got seven beautiful models
waiting for me upstairs and I think they
missed me
yeah well that leaves us what do you
have in mind
Mitch surfing surfing your first surfing
lesson
serving now yeah that is if you're up to
is that a challenge an invitation but I
don't have a swimsuit I can get you ice
swims
Lenny abhorred drama
yeah all right surfing that that's good
I could be interested in that but I have
to answer the phone hello right McBride
uh yeah private investigating yes that's
what we did yeah sure we should probably
meet immediately yeah right now no great
all right will I'll meet you there then
okay all right buh-bye this could be big
this can be huge you know I'll call you
okay McBride I'll call you tell you
[Music]
they're the friends you've got to
you can't run
[Music]
here the
Oh
[Music]
and the devil is watching as we slide
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]