you ready I was born ready man you have
a race Burdett before no huh what's his
deal he's the big nasty kid bail any
time nothing random you either in or you
are out I mean and he holds the cash oh
that's cash Oh Gil cuz you've been
floating too many markers around town
get it done
you want to sharpen the edge no thanks
lately the only speed I do is bikes
boats and cars I'm an adrenaline junkie
try to stay clean if you want to get
dirty call me all right it's
mile-and-a-half back to the cement pole
and back pot stakes winner takes all and
the loser goes home and mom tell you
about when should I ready
[Music]
we're dead
[Applause]
[Music]
of angels under cover of night
people look Brown
in a sea of
the devil's holding your life on
[Music]
we do the : rainbow time
Boris too late before it
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
to the side
[Music]
I
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
you ready yeah I'm ready
you want another no no I've got to go
hey some of you today I'm just a little
distracted a little destruction I won
almost every point what's going on an
old girlfriend's coming in ha ha no
girlfriend well that'll do it why don't
you look happy about it no no I'm happy
she's coming she's just coming for a bad
reason she's coming for a memorial
service for her mother she died in that
car crash I'll get Kanan Doon know I
always thought she was the perfect one
Mitch perfect one you mean smart funny
easy to be with great looking great in
the you-know-what and has her own career
exactly and that's what scared me to
death
so you took off like a bat out of hell
and I've been wondering ever since if I
made the right call well you're a little
older Dale you're a little wiser you
know give her a second chance
take another look yeah she wanted to
move to New York to be an antique buyer
for this auction house do you know I
think it really was tell me I always
thought that she was in love with the
guy she thought I could be not the guy I
am
the white zones were the
unloading passengers oh no Parker
the lights out
thanks for meeting me
I was in Tokyo on a buying trip and they
called and said our car went up cliff
I feel cement
[Music]
I'm it's often a mutton fish comes of
messages lemons color bag but you know
after sir can you give us a second okay
Wow I've just been holding it in ever
since I heard guess it just needs some
safe arms
oh you have mine for as long as you need
my dear wife each of us I know has felt
glorious generosity at some time she
would never turn her back on anybody who
was in need and if she was your friend
then you would never be without you
would never be lonely I will miss her we
shared so much together loving marriage
her children life I thought of as my own
my beautiful stepdaughter Renee I
wonderful
stepson RJ
Aloha
My dear wife
onion alone okay
[Music]
sorry about your mother RJ yeah she was
good lady candy this is a snow friend of
mine it's Griff
hi Griffin I haven't tried to figure out
who could jump higher run faster spit
farther since first grade
yeah who won I did hey come on yeah I
did
you
[Music]
I'm so sorry sweetheart
but we'll get through this we'll do it
together
[Music]
excuse me Rene Rene
hey hey hey what is it let's read you're
so angry I don't think my mom died in an
accident
what I think she was murdered and I
think Robert did it did he say something
no well do you have any evidence
something you can tell the police it's
just this gut feeling I wish there was
some way I could prove it you know one
way or the other
I don't want to go through life with
this horrible feeling that he murdered
my mother and got away with it you know
I think there's someone we should talk
to come
why which is money money
my real father was a very wealthy man
when he died he left my mother and me my
brother everything
how long were your mother and Robert
Houston married well over four years do
you your stepfather get along no he puts
up a good act he's an actual sleazeball
he tried feed on me when I was in high
school are you kidding why didn't you
tell me I would have not that kind of
next week I had to tell anybody what
good would it do my mother was in love
with a guy and I was leaving for college
soon
well your mom and him having problems
they had been quarreling lately but she
acted like it was no big deal no big
fart about control he wouldn't be the
boss of everything of her life her mind
her money especially her money does he
get the money no he's the executor of
the estate RJ and I we receive our trust
funds when we turn 25 Artie's birthday's
in two weeks he'll be 25 or something
were to happen to you and RJ Robert
would get it off all right we're gonna
independent run on this guy I'm gonna
find somebody and get the inside track
but what kind of person would you relate
to
huh
he likes to live on the edge so let's
just give him a push you want a big
payday getting back on drugs once a
junkie always a junkie darling I lit the
candle he'll find the flame sooner or
later sooner
Oh was that a popper next generation
baby come here
[Music]
yes it's perfect
I'll write you a check excuse me that
piece is mine oh I think not
oh I think so it's a very special piece
they called me to tell me it was then
I've been waiting for weeks then you
should have had them put your name on it
well there are plenty of other clocks oh
this is not a clock this is in 1890
johan vienna regulator with the
porcelain face i know it'll go nicely
with my Gustav Becker the Westminster
chimes are out of this world
so it's price tag my husband taught me
that true beauties priceless huh all I
have to believe that it was you that
taught him thank you I'm flattered
I'm jealous love your husband oh don't
be he's dead
[Music]
I'm sorry actually it was a blessing he
was very ill and quite old even his
money couldn't buy help oh that's so
true I recently lost my wife you and I
are a sad coincidence well who's gonna
buy it you were me
why don't we make the decision over a
glass of champagne hey hi hey
[Music]
and well we're supposed to have dinner
together and he's very interested in my
late husband's estate and way past being
sad about his wife dying good news yeah
the medical examiner determined
glory' Houston's deaths we have injuries
consistent to a car doing a somersault
off a 200-foot cliff however we do have
a witness Veera Rose Tilley 86 years old
her and her boyfriend were there when
the car went out of control
quote she was zigging and zagging like a
chicken being chased by a fox unquote
think she could have been drunk no not
according to me there were no drugs or
alcohol found in her blood and why was
she zigging and zagging I don't know
they're gonna run some more tests she
find anything about the brother RJ is a
real throw freak he'll race anything
anytime anywhere any bets on it best big
he also had a little chemical dependency
problem which evidently he kicked now
he's into gambling and he's got big-time
tabs all over town did you happen to run
across a guy named Scheck no no who's he
she likes the collector for mr. and
Fonte I actually heard a story about him
and a client who was late on a payment
Scheck went in and charged interest by
nailing his palms to the table yeah well
RJ is living like there is dawn tomorrow
well if sex after him that's probably a
good way to go
[Music]
take it Jib want you to have it and
anything else you'd like
thank you
[Music]
okay this is a big house it's your house
your home you're welcome to come and
stay if you like
no I've kept my apartment I'm fine there
sweetheart I know that this has been a
terrible tragedy for you and I hope you
know that I'll always be there for you
if there's anything that you excuse me
we've been through this before
keep your hands to yourself
you know and stop trying to sound so
agreeable giving away things that aren't
even yours oh but they are mine
check the will
[Music]
look I don't wanna have this kind of
friction between us neither would your
mother right can I use your phony to
check my messages
of course
hi I'm nothing right now
[Music]
scribbles
everything okay Oh mister I'm fine
thanks for uh for these they mean an
awful lot to me
[Music]
look Renee if you ever want to get
together just to talk
goodbye robber
[Music]
you
hi I'm not home right now leave a
message and I'll call you back
hi Renee is Griff listen um you might
have been right to hire private
detectives my friends and I are checking
it out maybe just maybe your mom was
murdered so who's this guy that were
meeting with when a gardeners conference
uh no he is definitely from the other
side of the tracks what a gangster why
would you think that
I don't know what's in the box this box
um a gift a gift great so we're buying
information that's nice
no no no this is not money so
technically we're not buying anything
okay don't turn around with the largest
and scariest man I have ever seen is
walking over here all right it's got to
be him
whatever you do don't run
are they good the best me all summer to
find them
seashells [ __ ] she is gonna love this
one
don't know how to think all right
so from a kid's aquarium I'm sorry I
should have introduced myself right out
my name is Reese happily reason hi Ryan
McBride
pleasure your man's pilling some heat
what's the source
you know I'm fun thing yeah absolutely
look make her a loan shark
Houston's overworked the line of credit
100 large it's due and payable the final
notice was delivered last week before
the murder one other things
Houston's done this before same game
different name where Connecticut went
under the name of Ralph Austin I guess
he's got a thing about Texas thank you
thank you
one more thing
Margaret's cooking on Sunday while you
stop by I'll be there
why do you do that do what we made me
think the guy was like a mass murderer
size of bail bondsmen with a lot of
connections we used to work out together
before he moved downtown I you're the
one who jumps to conclusions we don't
buy information from thugs okay well
fine then I'll just never believe
anything you have to say ever again all
right
well wait I do like your new haircut
you're way too kind of falls on your
shoulder do like it wears a little
nervous that's not funny but you believe
me
[Music]
I'm wasted every war there the naval
says no driving and no brain surgery
tonight stay mellow and here
[Music]
hello Oh Renee it's me Robert I'm sorry
I know it's late what is it what's wrong
oh it's RJ he just called me screaming
at me threatening to kill me threatening
to kill himself he's he's out of his
mind just like the old days I think it's
whacked out and it's rugs or something
okay I'll go over there it's a good idea
that's a good idea
calling bound oh and listen if he locks
himself in like he used to do there's a
hide-a-key
under the red flower pot on the front
porch okay all right bye
[Music]
hello are you doing Richie Rich you
remember mr. and Fontan don't you yes
he's a good sign Richie
very good you see mr. Infante was
balancing his checkbook today you know
what I own some money not some a lot but
got your window Richie
[Music]
new suit you like it yeah it's nice
shape my stepfather has all my money i
funny
he called mr. in five date tonight mr.
font they told him of your business
difficulties they offered him a chance
to co-sign for you save your sorry but
you don't mr. Infante you're on your own
also we could find you yeah kissed you
adios for a dysfunctional family if you
ask me
[ __ ] I don't have money I can't get
money get it I'm giving you 10 minutes
to make some phone calls then I'm coming
in or Richie don't bleed on my suit
[Music]
oh my god Oh
jy I will shot you you're getting better
[Music]
he's back on directs its on himself I
I'm scared Ebola the idea where he go
not anymore
hi Jane I haven't enclosed in about
three or four years I don't know where
he goes I don't know who he hangs out
with you know what I'll do I'll check
out the old Serkan spread the word see
what I can find the phone that could be
r.j. Danny and I cannot find the keys
shoot wait wait wait wait a minute wait
a minute let's get your access code hi
Renee it's Ryan McBride listen I need to
ask you some things about the day your
mother died could you give me a call at
the office when you get in thanks bye
you got Coltrane star-69 yeah try it
hello hello that was him that was that
was Robert he's monitoring your messages
that means he must know about Renee
hiring you guys to prove that her mom
was murdered because I called him up
that message you stand for me
hey hey hey
[Music]
Donna okay um are you still wanted in
with Robert Houston if you need me to
okay well we think he might have used
some sophisticated herbs too isn't his
wife stuff which is really difficult to
trace okay I know he's not gonna
volunteer any information but I need to
find out if you can what he knows about
that kind of stuff or if he knows
anything at all no problem I'll see what
I can do okay
[Music]
are you wearing even I ever work sick
about any money why before come on now
okay fine
what's going on our game plan house my
little sister again huh buddy what could
you need the money for man
there's a pot stakes race the river
night oh come on man you're no shape to
race you're gonna get in some serious
trouble I'm already in serious trouble
okay I win the race I could buy my way
out
this is not enough okay well look I got
some rainy-day stash at home how much
you got I got enough for two you can't
beat you man you never have yeah well
maybe tonight's my night where's the
race Ballona Creek all right you're in
if I am okay
just like old times yeah yeah it's just
like old times
[Music]
Thank You Robert this was lovely I
wanted it to be special you're the first
woman I've been alone with since Gloria
died how long have you been in mourning
a week six days well I hate to break
your heart but oh no no I can't stay you
can't spend the night how disappointing
I have to fly to San Francisco well
maybe I'll come along let you take a
little side trip to Napa that could be
fun not this time got to put out some
fires my um late husband's relatives
around the warpath why you so surprised
you ended up with all their money but
they've hired someone um forensic
something or other trying to get a court
order to exhume the body are they trying
to prove that you killed him yeah I
think they are well I don't think you
have anything to worry about unless of
course you did it
well my lawyer says they can now find
chemical traces in the remains for years
well they can find man-made chemicals
but organic compounds unless they're an
enormous amounts are practically
impossible to detect
like what Oh lots of things I've got to
go call me when you get back absolutely
[Music]
hey let's find out scientifically
speaking yeah
loving you counting ellaby and McBride
match yeah hey Renee what's up
Griffin or J they went racing where I'm
a lot of craic how long ago how are you
I'm on my way
RJ is surface stone he's gonna be racing
at Ballona Creek tonight what in the
dark
Lola's rocks was he kidding well girls
gonna be babysitting him I'm not trying
to find a scarran kept the mouth of the
creek yeah
notify the police huh
[Music]
what's that I smell it it's easy money
and his trash who is he buddy of mine
he's racing until he buys in
she holds
who else is in yeah I'm in let's get it
on let's do it
wait
[Music]
fly baby fly
you
[Music]
ready
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
grip
[Music]
[Applause]
sweetheart I'm so sorry
touch me Rene you're upset my brother is
dead and you killed him easy Rene no
Griffin's true honey I wasn't even there
it was an accident Oh like mom no I
don't know how you did it but you killed
them both
come on baby let's go you know what I am
gonna prove it somehow I'm gonna prove
it you are a mirror I got it I got it
can I call you right back honor
okay what have you got oleander a plan
yeah it's also a poison it's a cardiac
stimulant causes respiratory paralysis
then unconsciousness and then death
associated his food jumped in a car
after I was down the mountain and POW
his kicks mmm-hmm digging in zagging
like a chicken being chased by a fox
well that's why her car was swerving she
was dead before she drove off the cliff
that's just a suspicion I think he's
gonna hold up in court
mmm that's the good news our proof is in
the grave
hi I'm not home right now leave a
message and I'll call you back
[Music]
hi Renee is Mitch
I was hoping Grif was with you I look
he's gone ballistic he's talking crazy
he says that your mother was murdered
and that he's figured out that she was
poisoned with oleander or something
Renee he's talking about exhuming the
coffin to get the proof of your mom
being poisoned but if you see him call
me as soon as you can
thanks bye
[Music]
got McGriff stop it you old [ __ ] I know
what I'm doing breaking the law that's
what you're doing he killed her okay
he killed Renee small the guy's gonna
get away with murder
if you can't dig up a brave man the only
way I'm gonna prove that son-of-a-bitch
poisoner hi come on you gotta stop stop
it stop it or I'm gonna have to knock
you out
make sure you don't like it fine go away
do what I've got to do rabbit shame on
you
have you no respect for the dead
[Music]
poisoned Oh didn't you tighter than a
divorce much less expensive you know you
can't get away with it don't you
on the contrary I'm two-thirds of the
way there the RJ gone that leaves only
Renee between me and five million
dollars the shame that figure it out
what are you gonna do I'm gonna shoot
both of you and bury you in the hole you
just stuck nobody will ever find you in
mine beloved wife's gray uh-oh
this isn't your wife's grave right no no
no your wife's grave is over there
this is just uh some hole we go yeah you
got enough that's plenty
Wow oh I like sir on the wrist all in
so I'm staying going
three years ago you wanted to climb out
Everest sail a boat across the Pacific
walk on the Great Wall of China shall I
go on now
I remember the list you and me
you fit yeah I know
finisher Dan last whoo yeah I come
across you in five years I'm not gonna
let you go again
[Music]
Oh your dreams
you've got to
you
the server
[Music]
in the particular
the devil is watching every side
[Music]
you can hear
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]