[Music]
you
in the City of Angels under cover of
night people not drown in a sea of light
[Music]
holdin your life home
angel : rainbow time
[Music]
[Applause]
before it
after the
[Applause]
[Music]
don't think this is gonna go down right
well my source says a guy supposed to
make the drop here on Tuesday and what I
hope so my feet are killing me
quit complaining it's the first time
I've been in the blocks as I started
this firm no no we started this friend
you me and Mitch
ah mr. Almy your memory is lacking
I started this firm don't you remember
horse I remember miss McBride that was
the day I needed some serious vocational
counseling so I wouldn't see [ __ ] was
on vacation I knew he'd been partying
all night so I wanted to catch him
before he fell asleep you know how mitch
is when he first wakes up uh no not
really
well let me tell you he is not a happy
camper
[Music]
[ __ ] I know you don't have water in
your ears open up go away or I won't be
responsible for my actions
Oh what oh what Oh Jenna's dirty mother
I'm on vacation sleepwear is optional in
fact sleep is optional
goodbye a fine example you make for
yourself always with his mother what do
you want I'm quitting the police work
again have another donut feeling the
paths gorilla V waffles on the meaning
of life old news seriously look the cops
boarded a freighter called the Burma
Dragon yesterday they got a tip from a
rundown pie in Santa Monica named Nicky
pine hidden in the hall eight ancient
Jade bracelets worth at least five
million do you wanna read your newspaper
and you are not a health drink ah listen
the word around is a major art collector
named Charles Landau was smuggling the
gev hair they can't peanut oil yet
fascinating what's your point the tip
about the gene was picked up by my
ex-partner in the LAPD Manny Alvarez
squinty Alvarez he's got a detective
she'll know I'm gettin his sand in
shorts do I detect a bit of envy or
model Bendery then say it I quit
put up or shut up Fisher cut bait an
expression I've never totally understood
but I'm sure applies me I'm going
running you're going running now I I'm
here the midlife crisis well I got my
own a boat the keys buzzing a restricted
channel near the custom stock
a scarab weird huh lock up will ya hmm I
guess when you've had one career your
whole life you start to question whether
that's all you'll ever be
that's what Garner was asking funny
thing is even though I loved being a
lifeguard I was starting to ask myself
that question - morning morning I'm
looking for the owner Andy I'm Andy well
aunt Raya
hi I'm a lieutenant mystery cannon lake
killer lifeguards um you're in a scarab
C F 0 0 3 1 MZ I sure do but it's
already out oh no no I'm not looking to
rent it I was just wondering why keeps
cutting through a restricted Channel buy
a custom stock I haven't a clue what can
you tell me who rented a some
middle-aged woman you know what I can
check the records but I'm just a little
busy right now
no problem you get a chance give me a
call huh
any information will be greatly
appreciated we got it nice day huh
Thanks
funny thing about a coincidence it takes
two pieces of luck
first garner tells me about the stolen
Jade bracelets found on the Bourbon
dragon then the boat I've been watching
speeds right by it okay small
coincidence no reason to worry right
wrong
years on the beach of topping to
recognize a potential victim before they
go in the water you want to stop them
before they get in too deep it's called
making a prevention but the second I saw
her I knew she wasn't the type I could
prevent from doing anything
[Music]
I'm gonna help you
um yeah I'm sorry could you help me find
slip 67 please
um no idea actually this dock is
off-limits in the public well maybe you
were lost no no no not at all um I'm
meeting a yacht but thanks anyway
Oh people don't birth their yachts here
it's a customs graveyard they don't even
let the cruise aboard Thanks
[Music]
morning they're good oh good morning you
must be Ryan McBride yes sir right on
time
it's nice to finally meet you mr. Klein
I thought for a moment that I made a
mistake well you never really know
listen I can't stand around and blab but
I brought you this for buying my
effective agency oh thank you
[Music]
here the keys open the doors hey no oh
sorry
[Music]
problem with missing a prevention is now
you have to make a rescue which is a lot
more dangerous
[Music]
myself later after we survived
survive
come on a chip so far on the boat should
we do now we don't we're gonna die come
on we wanted an explanation
oh my god allah god don't look at steel
I'm afraid of heights
[Music]
what are we doing I just keep moving
where are we going
what are we doing it's just gonna have
to trust me just you I don't even know
you
let's hope you get a chance what
back up market will not get wet wet they
might not survive before that's getting
out just kidding
I can't okay listen to me
hold your breath after we hit the water
swim back to the surface the water are
you crazy
I can't swim the kiswa no and so broad I
can I'm a lifeguard oh really what the
lifeguard doing out here
well actually I'm on vacation okay fine
clearly blowing - Catalina what are you
doing here I got knocked over the deer
sure
you
[Music]
what if one of those maniacs was Charles
land
I started thinking like a detective I
checked him out he goes parking tickets
so special by Landau he's been in people
cool a couple nails a big deal like that
gets a gold shield it's damn near
automatic and at this point the only way
I'll ever make the time what about the
girl she had people too her name is Ryan
McBride he's a private investigator from
New York blue in this morning's where
she thought this was a public dock she
was upset
you should go home
[Music]
can you do anything to help right yeah
you can hail me a cab
he'll you a cab uh they don't cruise the
waterfront for fairs oh that's right I
forgot this is La mass transit is a
three man boogie board
all right Alvarez she can go but what
about that bracelet pine gaber didn't we
get all the Jade yesterday that's not
part of the contraband captain Tony
that's just her plastic replica I
checked as I recall sir from my report
the Jade was hidden in the hall my
source gave me an item-by-item list your
little fall from your your beat aren't
you garner well I was first on the scene
Manny
well good you can be first back on the
beach we would want anyone cheating at
volleyball now would we
hey let me go now how do I get back to
my motel which will give you right
thanks officer
thanks officer oh don't thank me thank
Mitchie he's the one who pulled you out
of the soup but as he says he's a
lifeguard he does it for a living
I'm sorry I'm sorry
I don't mean to seem ungrateful [ __ ]
come on help me out here if she's
connected to Landau she could be the
because so long did you breathe too much
oil smoke she's connected to the guy who
passes the tip about the Jade pinky Ponk
scuzz his private eye on the beach he'd
take a case from a fly but paid him a
penny why do I have to drive her she
won't fit on my Beach but the first rule
of a good detective her hold on to what
you done and tell him the Kazon Landau
she is what I got
[Applause]
okay I need to find this address our
investigations santim like a 2000 Beach
Boulevard
[Music]
don't plug in me are you doing
we're looking for pine investigations
the address says it's here but we can't
seem to find a sign you know that's the
same thing Nicky always says but it
don't go with the wrench you see so what
can I do about that
Nicky Pines office isn't a nightclub
that's right man right up till step-down
hall thank you but hey he's not in maybe
the Secretary of roles is there check
with her there she is
did you tell her that Nicky's bar tab is
overdue please yeah sure
thank you ma'am
get down all right yeah well there is
something really really wrong here
yeah picking locks I don't know about
New York we have laws against breaking
an inner
[Music]
yeah let's have the bracelet welcome to
what are you doing here watching your
rear yeah well you watching mind one of
those thugs when the dock was roughing
up Ryan's hey hey what are you doing
here you can't go through his stuff it's
not yours didn't I mention that
yes it is I bought it I own every bit
paper clip and every moldy container of
coleslaw in that foul refrigerator
you bought Nicky Pines agency well I was
already neligan why do you think I was
meeting him this morning it was to get
the keys to my ultra-modern
world-class fully equipped p i-- agent C
Wow
you have had big time my last dime well
I'm gonna get it back if I have to shake
that man like a piggy bank
ah too late Nicky Pine died an ambulance
it's a murder case now
you've heard the expression buying a
bill of goods I'm not sure what a bill
of goods is but this one costs Ryan
McBride 25 grand I mean look at those
offices that's Italian perjury sitting
in Ryan that's an Italian furniture
store he's sitting in a man who uses a
pizza box for a blonde does not own a
dime
listen Noel from downtown whoever rented
that speedboat used a bogus ID a lot of
phonies in LA like this Nicky pine and
he had gold-plated references Cobbs
judges they all loved it damn right
Nicky wasn't prints hi I'm rose you must
be Ryan you're not waiting around here
for Nicky are you he's gone Al's bells
it was even on the radio blue is giving
away drinks downstairs in his memory
Half Price
you'll be a party bollinger 61 looks
expensive
not when Nicky bought it there's some
wheels parked in the garage out back
it's a little buggy Nicky picked up at a
police auction title is tied up in
Superior Court still figure it out
anyway it comes with the joint um
sorry about Nikki yeah see you
downstairs
I gotta clear my head
[Music]
want me to go with you guess not
Wow this should make Ryan feel bad now
if she really owns it consider the
source
what's that it's an auction program for
the day after tomorrow
wait a minute this looks just like the
bracelet Nikki gave Ryan I'm scepters
dysplastic June and this one's circled
for a half of Meghan you still think
she's connected to Landau well first I
show up at the doctor at the same time
then we find this in a car she just
bought the connected somehow
you know what did you not do it for them
find her
oh whoa I'll wing it uh let's take the
car the bracelet Ryan had was definitely
a plastic replica but land al certainly
didn't think so you know it's like
listening to the Blues once you hear the
music
you don't want to live without it except
in Ryan's case she was the one whose
life was on the line we had to find her
before Landau did
[Music]
Oh
boom-boom-boom-boom
I'm gonna shoot you right down right out
for your feet take your home put you in
my heart
boom-boom-boom-boom
walking down
don't you talking
that Baby Talk I like to like
[Music]
[Applause]
right back where I started you know I
have been looking for you all night
oh my really I'm touched
like [ __ ]
go back to your sunscreen and cut-offs
you shared some beautiful gunfire
together but I don't need a guardian
angel and I can't stand a warrior
looking very upset for somebody who just
lost 25 brain
which I was the baby in my family six
all the brothers the one thing about the
on sexes they don't like sissies so if
you're soft
you'll get dented well you had some
great body
I just learned to bounce back really
what are you doing out here feet and
seagulls
I'm waiting for inspiration some
detective I found the boat
there's not an inch between Point Dume
and Redondo a lifeguard doesn't check
out at least twice a day I asked my
friends to keep an eye out and they hit
pay dirt let's give your eyebrows
something
let's go a red hair red hair Mitch I'm
gonna feel yeah I got a feeling too
[Music]
Anna Anna it's a hair color
um dye job you know Ryan trying to make
some sense of this whole thing nobody
help i conned you into buying worthless
aids you show up he's in the middle of a
firefight tosses you a plastic bracelet
suddenly he's dead
good feeling there's not much difference
between being a lifeguard in the private
on both that the deal of sharks
I drove Ryan to her motel but the Sharks
had already ripped the place to shreds
[Music]
I'll call the police why they're just
gonna file it and forget about it
[Applause]
that's the guys trying to grab your
bracelet when this doesn't make any
sense it couldn't get out this where the
doors jammed
there's nobody out there either well had
it be somebody else
that guy didn't do this he was trying to
break in what's that what are you doing
this is what I do I'm a forensic
criminologist you know fingerprints hair
fiber it makes me feel better
Ryan may have felt better but Gunnar
wasn't thrilled getting us into the
police fingerprint computer okay here we
go
I'll be damned
look at this lrb i'll hurry up Ryan I
think your honors midlife crisis is
coming to a head pratik up call me that
you're trying to take it big at the
Karnas report you want to see the body
go to the funeral you better hurry up
though cuz they're scattering his ashes
at sea or fish I wouldn't talk to him
like that he's only broken my nose twice
in situations like this why are you in
the lab garner these are seagulls here
so you must be lost
you're not fit to be a crossing guard in
Yucaipa to take that from you squinty
three times a Murphy
[Music]
look who was in my room
don't tell me Nikki pine give it hell
[Applause]
[Music]
ha Rose we just came by to pay respects
thanks for inviting us
[Music]
Nikki here
Nikki Nikki you in there no no Nikki
he's not know what everybody else is all
of his friends are here
doctors lawyers judges everyone a man
would need to fake his own death where
is he we know he's alive
we found his fingerprints in Ryan's
motel room after he died rose we also
found the Scarab you know I must
compliment you you can drive and shoot
real good but you really should get a
new dye job that henna rinse just isn't
the color for you
[Music]
Nikki
up today girls
[Music]
seventy relax - stop this thing stop did
they hurt you sugar
he didn't I'll be happy to thanks for
busting up my party that carrying cost
me three then I have to thank all my
friends now what
during the rest
[Music]
what this boy these are top accounts oh
yeah
here's one from take and go liquor five
bucks an hour to watch tapes from a
security camera security camera what
I've explained to that thought this was
a French film I pay you 25,000 and it's
still not free and clear I mean I've
heard of people walking away from deals
before but what you did to me was so
crooked you had to kill yourself it
wasn't for your benefit kid I admired
you are save stories from the newspaper
about you okay how is it possible that
you are the same man that found that
Corvette in Steve McQueen's swimming
pool very case no one understands why
after 40 years of business you go after
a small-time swindle a half million
Burmese jadeite mmm this is real folk
and all I get for my trouble is a
plastic fake that leaves green marks on
my arm Nicky we found this in the car
you laughs oh yeah the car that put me
on to the Jade I picked that baby up at
a police auction in the trunk I found
hidden paperwork on a smuggling caper
that the former owner set up for none
other than Charles window Oh what about
the cops why they find that bracelet
Myra took it off the list just a little
bangle I knew they were gonna look too
hard I needed a distraction to get back
on board we just wanted to show Landau
huh Nicky died I mean we didn't want to
hurt nobody
I wanted to give the keys to Ryan but I
wanted land out to sea me toss that
bracelet to her of course I knew he'd be
looking for me later on
so I had to die cost me a lifetime of
favors
what a nice little sting we're gonna buy
a condo and a stop or the dishwasher
just once can I give something nice to a
woman like rose
who loves him oh sure but why cheat me
I mean why search my room it was you
wasn't it sure you know what a shell
game is well I'm sorry mr. pine but I've
never really considered myself a walnut
before excuse me
[Music]
beating the seagulls again
you know I felt right in tanukis boat I
was just the kind of pigeon he needed
you're mixing metaphors but it's my new
it to me you are impulsive gonna tell me
about it
you know last month I saved my boss from
this maniac who shot up a deli with an
ak-47 I figured yes
now he'll make me an investigator
instead he took all the credit sent me
back to the lab and he went on Jaylin
out so you decided to make a change yeah
I wanted it more you know what no he
deserved
[Music]
I think people should get what they
deserve especially crooks like Charles
Landing I figured since he wanted the
bracelet I call and offer him a chance
to get I am Charles Londo mr. Buchanan
we've never met but for some reason
you're meddling in my affairs I am I was
I was just helping a friend let me give
you the big picture somehow pine found
out about the Jade next he caused me to
make a deal for the bracelet the best
piece on the ship best piece it's
plastic
please let's dent dynasty worth half a
million I get there in time to see pine
toss the bracelet to his new partner
obviously I'd like it back
the point is I'm ready to deal
tell her I'll buy it half-price
fair's fair landau had taken the bait
but we needed to make sure he didn't
spit it out
Ryan had to show him the real bracelet
Rose agreed to let her wear the Jade but
only if Nicky didn't let it out of his
sight
mr. Landau we haven't met but
I feel I know you miss McBride how about
my car
it's a fine day for an auction yes it is
bidding can start anytime you like
[Music]
what's that old saying
life goes on you should have stayed dead
and again what do you want mr. chat
don't get so excited
I just want a opportunity to explain my
point of view with the whole deal your
point of view
thanks to you I'm out 5 million in Jade
now your partner here wants me to buy
back something I already own Pidgey
Pidgey Pidgey Hey here's what I want uh
I thought you wanted to buy it oh this
one kneel and make up for what I've lost
already thanks to him things are going
exactly according to plan I they're not
even close
[Music]
[Applause]
you really want to try me this better be
your best day
you like taking a chance
[Music]
you like fish what lots of fish
[Applause]
got it all on tape
thanks to you I'm out five million in
jade stereo Rose gave it to me beautiful
thing well what about the bracelet I
promised Rose I'd keep an eye on it
again break my promise to the woman my
lord now can I
they say you can't take it with you once
you're dead but Nicky had died once for
that bracelet and if he didn't bring it
back to Rose she'd probably kill him for
real they say you can't take it with you
but just once a man should be able to
give something nice to the woman who
loves
[Music]
you think you can change your life but
you can't even take a vacation from it I
wasn't on the beach but I was still a
lifeguard different kind me but then
there's more than one way try
Oh
[Music]
you sure you want to play another game
cost me a lot of money did I say when
we're playing for money let's go hey we
are taking off oh come on if it'll cheer
you up Andy said you could use her
scared anytime you want
you don't look cheer sorry
is it if you add things up it looks like
the McBride eller BPI agency is just not
gonna happen
even if I put in ten grand and go
partners the ellaby McBride baking sheet
yet would be too far in [ __ ] what
what's with all this guilt you're laying
on me I mean come on if I can help you I
would the most of the money I got saved
is for hobbies college education and I'm
not gonna touch that well what have you
thought of it is like an investment in
the rest of your life look come on Mitch
I mean I've seen your work you have
great instincts but wouldn't you just
want like to find a Corvette and see
McQueen swimming pool just want speaking
as a friend no N Oh
the minute he turned around I knew we
had it
oh that's right that's exactly how it
happened which totally proves my point
that I started this agency okay when you
ride you're right you're right you start
being yes but now I know I just couldn't
have done it without you and Mitch this
is true sir this is very true
you know what partner I've sold 56
hotdogs
since this morning at 250 a pop we are
in the wrong business well I'll worry
he'll show it's one thing about
industrial spies they're very punctual
where'd you steal uh your design for a
running shoe hmm
oh oh oh speaking the devil oh and here
comes number two there's the drug okay
let's do it okay but wait remember the
important thing is the bag not the man
let's go
[Music]
excuse me sir hi there's no car no back
bag
[Music]
[Applause]
your dreams
where the place you've got to
[Music]
here the
in the película
the devil is watching every slide
[Music]
[Applause]
you can hear
[Music]
[Applause]