[Music]
[Applause]
hold that spot right there dialing I'm
on my way
you're just gonna love
how long some more Muttley baby
[Music]
[Applause]
this whoa hey hey whoa
they're gonna travel engine do you have
a car phone yes
can I use it please what happened but
her boy Bernie's just he jumped off the
bridge baby I get BAM there yeah he's
doing under I have to call
there I just thought he went down right
there where I ever see him there right
there I think I see him
[Music]
Oh
oh she jumped do blue actually joke
that's the damnedest thing I ever saw
what what you know is a great jump but
where is a dinky stands no I don't
because you're the only one in the water
Oh God sorry we just wanted your car Oh
[Music]
piece of cake baby that's real cold
way to go Donna Oh think I look around
just jumping in a fire
oh that's why I say goes before
[Music]
oh okay we don't panic we relax they
call I would stop talking about
ourselves and if their reports of parole
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
in the City of Angels under cover of
night
people are drown in a sea of life
the devil's holding your life um
[Music]
angel : rainfall time
for easily get for it
[Music]
it's going to live
ah
now
[Music]
[Applause]
no I mean I'm sorry I'm sure they're
wonderful I've never heard of them
are you kidding me you never heard of
pipeline wipe out surfing The Strand
Beach bound hello and that my favorite
shifting was it god of this morning to
go look at the beach my board it was all
the beach I need to serve surf sir it's
all for me sir sir service where I wanna
be shifting sands still that dream I
wish you see haha I can't believe you
don't know that yeah I mean that's
that's a regular LA bohème no no no you
you can't enjoy musics I'm gonna for
labor by foreigners
La Boheme it's it's about musical
complexity sophistication it's it's
about emotion talk about emotion let's
talk about memories these guys played in
my first kiss first slow dance first
you know that is don't you know I'm
trying to figure it out I'm just finding
out now man I gotta get some shots hey
it's only a rehearsal even better
shifty Sam dad
I can't believe it yep that's buddy ray
he created the whole California Beach
Sun ah he's a beach Piccini I have got
to meet that man
me too hey are we doing almost set up do
it yeah Julio Oh give me a soda will you
hey buddy would you go to my husband's
tracks huh that heard it it's pure
trippy that man was a genius and a
seinen you trashed his record he put
such a saint Carmen how come you were
divorcing him huh at least I'm not
robbing is great huh like his old
brother it's a sad time why don't you
just leave us alone
whoa a groupie that can talk huh you're
overqualified for this band sugar
huh beach meetings supposed to be fun hi
nice to meet you mr. Kent I'm a big fan
hey buddy buddy goner enemy ah thanks
fellas what's the battery that's
wonderful guys it's really wonderful
really press that your book of memories
[Music]
the water
you
[Music]
[Applause]
good luck at the beach
or it was all within reach I need to
serve sir sir it's all for me serve
serve serve it's where I wanna be
you know
[Music]
[Applause]
she did say
[Music]
hey man kill the power
i'll call 9-1-1 no pulse
Hey
what you got
[Music]
ah when can we load our stuff in the
trucks well when the police finish their
investigation now what are they looking
for was an accident right was it I just
saw what you guys call the Wawa pen
it was hardwired into a powder so what
are you saying that the better was wired
to electrocute anyone who stepped off no
accident more like murder any ideas well
if you're looking for who might have
done it huh
try Glen old news Carmen what they
kicked him out of the band but he kept
on as a roadie I missed out on big money
it uh made you lie what are you doing
here anyway I'm here representing Martin
State yeah which all belongs to you now
Oh what do you say when Marty died the
divorce wasn't final instead of getting
half you get it all you accusing me why
don't you ask them about the music
publishing deal what do you good joint
ownership when Marty died everybody else
inherited millions money or revenge too
damn fine reasons to kill somebody my
god cut I've lost a brother and a cousin
won't you be happy until we're all dead
truthfully no
that on a put her on your top 40 suspect
list
[Music]
luckily if I shot before anyone finds me
Oh
[Music]
Donna want them to say like no sharks in
these waters what are our shots but no
dangerous ones
what's that the blazing wife Oh God
[Music]
there's someone in the water
it's a woman
[Music]
can't just drive fire well what do we do
with her
stop the boat
[Music]
okay where'd you come from
oh I'm freezing
listen you guys can just drop me
anywhere on land I'm sorry that's not
gonna be possible at the present time
but it'll only take you a few minutes
hey I've been on the water most of the
night yeah well I'm sorry we're in a
tight schedule yeah we're uh we're doing
research on abalone but the abalone
aren't going anywhere in the next hour
are they no but the tide is you see
there's a window when the tide flows and
when it ebbs and we have to be there in
escazu with the abalone where we're from
UCLA doing a biology project trying to
restore the abalone to its habitat
excuse me minutes
hey why don't you get one have a candy
boy some hot coffee
relax enjoy the way-out baloney think
she bought it it doesn't matter when you
think about it she's perfect car she's
gonna know what I'm the right mind would
take a woman along on a deal like this
you know she was out there all night
she's damn lucky to be alive I wonder
how she got there who cares
[Music]
can't believe it he was right next to me
and now he's he's gone I don't
understand it first my brother now my
cousin I don't get it
two guys in the same band dying in two
weeks that's a hell of a coincidence the
autopsy on Marty showed that his BAC was
0.21 so he was drunk enough to slip and
drown Oh
marty was cold sober for the last two
years after Carmen bailed on him no
drugs no booze he was gone to his AAA
meetings every day no he was he was
trying to stay clean he was on the wagon
maybe someone or something pushed him
off that night yeah maybe you know maybe
I should hire you guys maybe that's a
good idea
[Music]
hey buddy what just Mike doing pointing
outside
Oh Marty like to sample natural sounds
for his records you know wind chimes and
birds and waves just gives it a keyboard
is this the sampler yeah all right let's
see if I can filter some of those noise
out
slow down slow down slow down
I don't see anything you sure we're in
the right place yep this is the spot
something about all this is making me
nervous
what's going on here I mean you guys
know what's about a baloney than I do
Todd we got company
either their earlier whirling what's
going on here
look for now it'd be best for all of us
if you would just see got hurt time to
call it cowboy one no no not now let's
stay cool maybe we can make this work
after all
who are you guys time for formal
introductions and if you keep quiet if
you'll get out of this alive
[Music]
hey bro what's up thought you'd be long
gone
who the hell are you guys you ain't
Johnny with a pickup
Johnny sentence
who's the Betty just a friend along for
the ride
well I say two's company three's a crowd
hey bro it's wrong and more god it's no
problem
on the contrary bro it's a big problem
as you boys are all wrong
[Music]
No
I think they hit an artery call for help
ouch lost the radio where so aside when
I got him
[Music]
try
I got it what do I do here twice that's
a signal god tom Jason - shock
what do you help out here right now what
was this identify yourself you have two
agents bleeding to death and you're
wasting time we're on our way
[Music]
that heat-rays gig at the pier gave me
an idea I am putting together event and
now kind of thing is that that he raised
absolutely 1971 hahaha look at that big
hair serious bell-bottoms but you get
these rock-and-roller Rama
it's a memorabilia shop check the chick
that looks like buddy's girlfriend money
it is her and I zapped all five roles at
the pier look at this this is my shot of
Marni at the pier look and that's her
1971 yep I guess she found a time travel
portal Star Trek was right
[Music]
it's a high school address six years ago
maybe we can get lucky and when you find
out well we got two possible murders and
enough motives to fill Dodger Stadium
one thing an appreciation day not to
mention a blonde who doesn't age
[Music]
hello everybody home
a man
[Music]
hello
oh I'm sorry we didn't mean to disturb
you
you said come in so what you're not
disturbing me we're looking for Marty
morrow
Marnie
she's not here um are you related to her
army you look a little bit like her are
your sister I'm her mother
Oh what what's tomorrow
oh please call me grace grace um my name
is Mitch Buchannon I'm mrs. garner LRV
grace we'd like to ask you a couple of
questions about a group called the heat
rays did you know them yeah yeah I know
them very well
but we had a great time together we
we've traveled all over the world you
know on tourist Paris and friends I was
wonderful I was part of their family it
was the best part of my life
well I've got something here then down
thank you my angel I recognize that
picture with some taking out the old
kaleidoscope studios
[Music]
is that you yeah it was a recording
session
[Music]
why are you here you reporters no no
we're private investigators
two of the heat rays are dead
they don't call me I I don't say them
they don't come by anymore
this is why well we didn't mean to set
you
mrs. ray here has something important
that she thinks we should know all right
yeah I saw Jason the drummer um he was
playing with the power chords and moving
them before the rehearsal why didn't you
say anything before
my relationship with my former families
and all that warm and cozy huh well I
didn't want anybody thinking that I had
something to do Lucas's death I couldn't
sit back and let somebody get away with
murder where is Jason now oh he's
probably coiled under some warm rock
somewhere he doesn't do anything but
play golf and the drums uh look I gotta
go I just wanted to clear my conscience
well it was Noble just plain nasty
either way we gotta check it out
[Music]
lovely isn't it hot
yes left we're talking I'm going to ask
you again what were you doing with the
power course during the rehearsal
[Music]
just try to help me find out who killed
your
[Applause]
[Music]
hey excuse me hello thanks for
cooperation
hey great drummer huh he could do is
play in-a-gadda-da-vida can say is a
perfect candidate for a personality
transplant huh
[Music]
go
are you guys fine just a little
information man take a look at me
everything is gone banned everything
it's all there is to know who'd want to
do this who hated you and Marty and
Lucas enough to kill you
flip they're a family album you'll find
somebody Jason you know a woman named
Grace Morel no there's a picture huh
it's Marni buddy's girlfriend no that's
Ronnie's mother Grace Mauro look close
where the picture was taken over 20
years ago
it's a kaleidoscope we uh we cut a track
there what happened back then nothing
weakly cut a record which one sister we
made 27 albums over 100 singles it could
have been any one of them shifting sands
I can't remember he's try and think back
at the Kaleidoscope studios grace Moore
was there shifting sands Oh what
happened I told you I don't remember
look I showed this picture to Grace
Morrow it scared the hell out of her man
now what happened it doesn't matter it
was over 20 years ago
it does matter somebody killed your
brother somebody kills your cousin they
barely missed killing you
Jason what happened
kaleidoscope studio race morale shifting
sands we were in the studio for a couple
of days laying down the tracks for
shifting sands we finally got it right
we knew man
[Music]
which a grace whatever she hung with the
band no matter where you critique it
look up and she'd be there
[Music]
that's what we are called race enough
girl you couldn't get away from her
chicks like that back then
[Music]
just some difference
skyy into it way too much thought she
was part of the package that he nice
I have to assassin to be hung we got
hammered pretty good on champagne me
Marty and Lucas started playing around
with it sometime
no big thing just goofing
[Music]
[Applause]
he's got about a hint you know the booze
kicked in but he passed out in the
corner then you know one thing led to
another
you raped her she didn't say no she was
drunk she didn't have the chance you
don't understand man I own the world
in 1971 I could do anything I wanted
nobody ever said no nobody
what about buddy
he was soft you never even woke up he yo
I never told him what happened
then what about grace she got scared she
left the band probably hooked up with
another band or something
damn I lost my brother and my cousin I'm
sorry I swear to God I would do anything
if I could go back and fix things I mean
I mean if it's money no money can't buy
a life back
my buddy
what a grace they were newly passed out
that means Marnie doesn't know either my
brother my two cousins I'm next man
if you want to be safe let's just fit
the bed out safest place to be is in the
middle of the ocean you are right and
get Garner break and when go home no no
I'm staying here wherever you go my girl
we might want a little time alone she's
right man go home garner it's okay
hey I appreciate your concern man but
it's my boat and we're casting off I
don't think so
look I hired you let me fire you for
about an hour huh
come on be okay we'll be back before
nightfall and here we'll meet you right
here ready
this is not good
hey garner where's bunny they took off
in the boom we got a problem
Rona yeah here
[Music]
Thadeous [ __ ] I need a scare up as soon
as possible yeah at the dock no you
wouldn't listen to me
[Music]
are you doing oh this is all right I'm
feeling better already
back
[Music]
you know sometimes I feel like is it the
only friend I have except for you
[Music]
what are you doing
I like it buddy
they are money
[Music]
doing
all right hang on buddy hey guys
get a little closer
yeah we're gonna
[Music]
medico
thanks man thanks again all right
yoki
you should let him die Marnie buddy had
nothing to do with it Jason confessed to
the rape buddy was drunk that night but
he passed out you never even knew what
happened to your mom
[Music]
grab grip hey could you cover this for
me I lost my wallet
sure no problem huh this is a first
you're always so in control yeah
keep the change it's kind of nice to be
able to help you oh that's sweet Thanks
so how was your day
[Music]
interesting come on I'll buy you a drink
tell you all about it okay that's right
right right
how are you grace okay I'm okay buddy
sent me here he wanted to help out
somehow he signed over the royalties of
his new song to you he knows it can't
fix what happened tell him thanks okay
he also wanted to know if he could stop
by and say hello someday maybe someday
fine is anything you need expert
[Music]
I can see it in your eyes
something just stay right I can tell you
wanna know you start to show the pain
[Music]
the crane
I wanna see you smile
Lady Grey
[Music]
only for
ah lady crazy
[Music]
know your dreams
where the price you've got to think you
can't run
Oh
[Music]
in the penguin the devil is watching
every side
[Music]
[Applause]