In the city of Angels,
people drowned in the sea.
Devil
rain for time.
The
after the.
These are go weapons.
Don't screw 'em up. Rose.
Dam it. Nicky, what did I just say?
Sorry dude.
This is your first job, so you gotta
chill, man. That's real important.
You meditate?
Yeah, I'm cool.
All right, let's go through
this one more time. Manny.
Everybody's on the floor.
Get the register, cover you.
Nicky.
I stay with the car. After three
minutes I pull up to the door,
keep the engine running.
Come on, come on. What else?
What else?
Keep an eye out for cops.
And what's Nuro uno?
We're family and we stick together.
Oh, one more thing. Just gotta
go down quick. Boom, boom, boom.
Here you go.
Yo, chicken little. We ordered like
three Dino wings with corn feet,
I guess like chickens here. Can't count.
Let me ask you something, kid.
Have you always been a knucklehead or to
something you picked up along the way?
And have you like always been
a stupid chicken to work?
Have you ever stopped to think about
some of the things we do to survive?
Survival is primal and
we do what we have to,
but sometimes we cross over the line,
which is exactly what happened to me and
Garner when we took an undercover case
at a fast food restaurant that
had been robbed five times.
How's it going out there? Garner?
You really want to know? Not really.
I hate these cars. I hate the people
in the cars. I hate this heat.
Another sugar coated.
Ball. Tell me how you really feel.
I hate being in a chicken suit sweating
like a pig while you're sitting in air
conditioned.
Splendor. Oh yeah. Yeah.
How like it so lucky? I.
Don't
You ready little bro? No.
Screw up. Sneaky. Three minutes.
I said I'm cool dude.
All right, let's do this Manning.
Hold on to the air
conditioning. It blew up. Oh.
What are you doing in here.
Anyway?
Well, I thought I'd line the
nest for a while. Maybe Lazy May.
Oh, when will these perps show? Oh God.
Everybody on the.
You took a little on the now.
Got it.
You're.
Hoping to say halal. I want the payroll.
Take Get easy marriage.
It's on time left. How long?
Six hours and.
Change now. You waiting six hours. I'm.
Telling you, man. I'm sorry. I.
The.
Freeze. Put the gun down.
You put your gun down, man.
I'll cut her. Man.
We both cut.
One. What the hell you doing?
Cops don't take hostages.
We're not cops.
You okay?
Leave me here, bro. I'll
figure something out.
You hang tight. Penny. You punks are dead.
Go, go, go.
Are you be wearing your butt for a hat?
Wearing your butt for a hat.
It's colorful. Mr. Buchanan.
Hey. Hey, Garner. Oh no. Not Decker.
So I always wanted to ask you,
why the hell did you cross that road?
My brother gets.
Perfect.
Hey. Hi. Hello.
Car trouble.
Yeah, one of those dudes.
I've had those masquerade party.
Actually, I'm on my way home from work.
Really? Uh, you're a professional chicken.
? No, I'm a private investigator.
Uh, undercover job. Uh, Steakout.
At the coup.
.
Yeah. You you're funny. I like that.
So are you. So do I.
Well, you know, Birds of a fella.
I'm summer.
I'm gone.
I'm an attorney. Do you need one?
Um, well, no, but um,
I don't suppose you feel like picking
up a little chicken on the way home.
Well pop in. I just love
a man in a foul move.
A hundred dollars and 2 cents.
We nearly die of heatstroke
growing chicken suits for two days.
I get a gun to my throat and we get
paid a hundred dollars and 2 cents.
The corporation that owns a franchise
says that you only caught one
robber, insulted numerous
customers and hurt their business.
We also stopped at our robbery.
I thought they got everything
in the cash register.
Oh.
That, Well, they did not.
They didn't get the safe.
I thought there wasn't
anything in the safe.
Oh, picky, picky, picky.
Well, corporation says it. We're
lucky they're not gonna sue.
Sue, Sue a hundred bucks. Sue.
A great American tradition.
We isn't that white.
Michael. Uncle Jerry used to say, Leg
stinks. You lose your keys, you die.
But I like to think of myself as one of
those people who sees the cup as half
full. Still.
Sometimes we get dealt to bad card and
the chicken caper definitely came up A
deuce.
I don't know about this Duke. I
mean, we're talking murder, man. Hey,
I do the killing little bro. You
just cover my butt. You understand?
Hey, listen to me, Nicky. You
and me and Manny are family
and we stick together no
matter what. Yeah, I know,
but why does somebody have to die this?
And right now we're gonna get Manny
back and nothing else matters. Nothing.
You understand? I understand.
Childproof. I tell you what. Let's
call the kids openness thing.
That's a good idea.
There you go. Are you sick? Of what?
No, no, no, no, no. I got sign his
headaches. He's knocking right out.
Thanks Lou.
Oh, hey, Fell. Sorry we haven't
opened yet. We got another hour.
I'm looking for Mitchell
Buchanan and Garner.
Er b I have a job that
might be interested in.
Um, Mitch is patterning
his nose. I'm his partner.
Ryan McBride.
Pleasure.
Oh, there he is. Mitch. This is.
Um, Duke. Sosa. You remember
me, right? Mitchell,
block the doors man. Nicky, watch him.
You're too sexy.
All right. And I want you to call lapd.
I want you to say you've got a hostage
situation and I want you to tell him to
send the SWAT team and
then call Flash copy.
Flash copy.
You know the TV show?
Don't you know nothing man.
I got, I got it. I got it.
Take care.
What are you doing here, Decker?
All I did was kiss her goodbye.
We just gotta call him about a host
situation. Host situation here.
Is that the SWAT team? Nicky?
Three black and whites more common.
Give me another will Sweet Cheeks.
It's Ryan. The name is.
Ryan. That's right
Brian. It's a nice name.
A.
Sit down. Hey.
Easy man. Oh.
There's nothing I'm gonna like more
than putting a bullet in you Mitchell,
But that comes later now. Ryan,
I'd appreciate that beer.
That is one fine woman.
Hey.
Hey. I told you not to move Mitchell.
Next time I get serious.
Yeah. Mitch Mitchell can't
talk right now. He's a hostage.
Who the hell is this?
I'm Lieutenant Amanda Cash Hostage
unit. This is my show now. Sergeant.
Yes ma'am. Hey, here's what I need. One.
Get a DP crew down here in case
we have to turn off the power two.
Get the FAA to grant me a no flies
over before these media copies.
Drive me crazy. You clear on that?
No problem, Lieutenant.
Okay, big want you set at my office and
get some food down here. Bottled water,
coffee, black, some sandwiches,
Ham and sour. Dope. Go.
And who are you?
Leonard . M a Pi used to be
with LAP P. That's my office of there.
My partners a estrogen.
Do you have some information I can use?
No, but I know someone who does.
Just what I need the queen of trash.
Stormy Walters. You let her in.
You'll be checking parking meters.
How old are you, Nick?
Hey. 10 18.
That's old enough.
For what?
Stand trial as an adult.
Well, it's stand a no trial man.
Hey kid, there's only two
ways to get outta here.
Handcuffs or body bag.
Saw the conversation about
shut the hell up.
Yeah.
This is Lieutenant Amanda Cash Hostage
Unit lapd. To whom am I speaking?
I ask the questions for now. You in.
Charge? I am.
I have three hostages here and they
all die unless you do what I say.
You got that.
Understood.
Since Stormy Walter's in here for an
interview, I want to go on live tv.
Is that it?
Watch Stormy. You'll see what else I need.
He's got three hostages.
Three. Did he give any names?
Negative. But guess who
he wants to talk to.
Here.
We're ready.
Hang in there. Mitch.
You ready to.
Here? Let's do it. Okay.
You're live in five seconds. 4, 3, 2.
This is Stormy Walter's live
from Venice Beach, California,
where Armed fugitive Duke Sosa has taken
three hostages and has chosen flash
copy to issue his demands. Duke,
millions of flash copy
viewers await your words.
Most stormy. There's two things
I want. Are these people die?
That's Ryan, my other partner
in Lou Raymond who owns.
The club.
Okay. Duke, what do you
want? America's waiting.
I want my brother Manny Soso
released from prison, brought here.
It's a million dollars in unmarked
cash and I want it two hours.
You want me to agree with that?
Not a chance.
Tell me a little bit
about yourself. Mr. Sosa.
Call me Duke.
Duke. What has brought you to
this critical moment in your life?
Well, I think it all started when I was
10 years old and stole my first car.
I had my own gun by the time I was 13.
And what about your parents?
My old man was in jail the
whole time I was growing up.
They're never gonna release.
His brother from prison.
I'll get his fool in million dollars.
Either way, anything gonna kill.
Us? It's tragic.
How old.
Were you? Oh, that's a
very comforting, Mitch.
What we gotta do is find a way outta here.
What we need is a miracle.
And your brothers.
I raised them myself.
Ladies and gentlemen, this
is an incredible story.
What's.
This stuff too?
Well, there's just like painkillers
that make you kind of drowning.
How many left? Forced to bring three
or four awful of circumstances.
And is now in the most difficult
struggle of his young life.
That should be enough. Trying
to protect your brothers.
Have you ever had any problems
with the one or two times? I
What do you think you'll
accomplish by? Hey.
You ever done any time before?
Nah, that chicken joint was my first job.
Well, hey, maybe you better think
about what's happening here, man.
Cause you know, for murder
you can get 20 years. Man.
The one thing you don't want
to do is wind up in the joint.
And there you have it, Mr. And
Mrs. America. An exclusive wallet.
It's happening.
Interview with Armed Fugitive Duke
Sosa holding three hostages in Venice,
California. He threatens to kill.
Unless.
It's to mad or met.
You're sitting them in.
I have no choice. The situation is
non-negotiable. I have my orders.
Oh, come on. Give the guy what he wants.
So lies with three people that rich to.
I realize that I talk with my
superiors and the answer's no. Then.
Try again. You saw this guy's
rap shootings. A psycho.
When the queen of trash comes
out, the SWAT team goes in.
I'm sorry, Garner.
Position. I watch Door.
Don't show. We're coming.
Go, go, go. Keep train the door.
No, no. I think SWAT's about to go in.
There's no way.
The Hostage unit, which is pushing
us all back and quarter from Mile.
There's nothing I can do. Hey, hey,
hey. What are you doing? Hey, what's up.
With you fella? Look, it's okay.
The hostages of my friends.
So hear me out Stormy. I have a plan
that could make you bigger than her.
Geraldo.
Ah,
it's all happened A little bro. .
. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Manny's coming back and we're
gonna be Richard famous.
So much for that plan.
Net. Na Hayes wore some warm
beer. I need a cool one, Ryan.
Sure.
Boy. Ryan, I gotta tell you,
I love the way you walk.
We can distract this.
Guy. Well, he seems to be taken with Ryan.
Hey Nicky, come here and get a beer.
Maybe Ryan can get him to dance with her.
So Duke, is that your real name?
Yeah. Mile Man had a
thing about John Wayne.
Well then why isn't your name John?
Okay? Do you dance Duke?
What are you talking about?
Well, I mean, you might as well
pass the time somehow. Huh?
I think she likes me.
Nikki, What's matter? Duke?
Are you afraid of me?
I ain't afraid of nothing.
Good then.
Why don't you play as something.
I can do that.
Make it real slow and sexy.
I've got a room.
I've got a room with a view.
I've got a room. Um,
I've got a house full of
and a room with a view of the blue.
I said these walls,
they are closing in on me.
I'm talking about these walls.
They are closing in on me.
I don't have no.
He's singing about him himself. You know.
No way. I don't even have a tv.
Really?
He killed somebody Now listen.
Yeah. Yeah. His wife. It's 17 years.
Altra.
Why.
You? I think long and hard about
throwing rest of my life away.
Bed. Only room.
I have a room with a view.
Hey, hey, hey. And on the
first day at Big Noise, I'm.
Through in,
I don't even see you.
I said,
I'm in a house full of and a room with a.
You think I'm stupid?
What?
I get anywhere near that door and
there's two SWAT snipers out there just
waiting to pop me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah. Then you go stand there and
see how long it takes to be dead.
Then.
They would shoot me too.
I'm not a cop. I'm a pi.
We ain't finished dancing yet.
Sometimes life deals you ace.
It's one of those rare moments when
everything seems to come together at just
the right place and the right time and
it looks like the pot is all yours.
This wasn't one of those times.
Cool it, man. Yeah.
Duke, you're a hit. America wants to
see more of you. Are you interested?
Hell yes. When.
Your call, the sooner the better.
We don't wanna give the
advertiser sweaty palms.
My brother here yet, he's.
In route. But I think we should come in
now. We can do a family portrait later.
All right, let's do it. Great.
You have to tell cash. Yeah. Hold on.
Lieutenants. Oops. So.
Cash. I want Stormy Walters back in here.
Now I can't do that, Mr.
Suza. You can't do that.
I'm ordering you to do
that. Told you to shut up.
Oh.
Come.
Stay with them. Okay.
He d appear.
To be quite injured this time, but
will stay with him as long as we can.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ma'am, you gotta the back now, okay? Okay.
Okay, we're out. All right.
How you doing?
Okay, but the bunk can't
shoot straight, man.
He shot me right in the love handles
most protected part of my body.
Oh.
That's good news story. How I Mitch Ryan?
They okay, But that
dude, that crazy man. He,
he, he could pop him in a minute.
They need help. You gotta get in.
Give him some help, man.
I could have killed him.
Amanda. I was just warning you.
Get my brother here in 30
minutes or the next one is dead.
Big.
We got two.
I'll send Stormy in
Stormy. Long time. No, see
who's this?
Oh, that's just my sound guy. You
should have been here an hour ago. Duke.
You really captured the heart of
America. I mean, what can I say?
They're just begging for more.
I wouldn't wanna disappoint my public.
That's Garner Grinner.
What.
Are we doing? Hey.
Listen, Stormy, can I get this great idea?
I think my fans are
really gonna eat it up.
Interesting. What
you think I'm stupid Chicken.
Little did you get that?
Now check this out.
I'm gonna kill you today,
ladies and gentlemen. This
is truly unbelievable.
A fusion have been his hostage in
a life and death struggle here.
Live exclusive on flash. Copy come.
Oh
Nicky, my ankle's busted. Shoot him.
Don't do it. Nick. You can never
take this moment back, man.
Shoot him.
No, don't make me do it too.
Remember Nu uno Nick, we stick
together. You're the man Now Nick,
not him. You're the man.
Just do me a favor, huh?
Let these other people
go Don. He's a doctor.
You don't get him outta here. He's
gonna die. He dies. You take the fall.
We're talking the rest of your life,
kid. I don't wanna kill anybody.
Duke Randall. Go, go, go.
Give.
Me the piece. It ain't right, Duke.
They said they were gonna release
Manny, but it ain't gonna happen.
Nikki Duke is the one who lied.
That's what team is sitting out
there just waiting to pop us.
Unless we show him we're
calling the shots. Shoot him.
You still got a life kid.
You still got a life.
What kind of life? There's
nothing there, man. Nothing.
Not a thing. Shoot him.
I ain't shooting nobody, Duke.
Ah,
I'm sorry man. I'm sorry. You scared me
on Big Daddy. Oh.
Yeah. Now I know how
I move when I get old.
Imagine how I feel. I've been moving
like this for many years, man.
Crying. The wars over. We're here.
You sure was nice riding to Maker's
lunch. I didn't know if she could cook.
Yeah. Well you ever tasted her
coffee? What do you mean? Ah.
Might assume it's revenge.
Hello gentlemen. I hope you're hungry.
Hell, after two days of hospital
food, home cooking sounds great.
, after two days of listening
to you snore sleeping. Sounds great.
Well, at least I don't sing in my sleep.
How did you two end up
on the same room anyway?
A trick of faith. .
Well.
I hope you like it.
Compliments of California roasters.
.
Mr.
Buchanan.
It can blow dreams. There's a,
you got can the,
the
you what's.