reowww it's winter real rainy when I'm
gonna buy the sunshine and bring it with
us now whatever happens don't panic on
me have I ever
you're late fashionably cut the crowd
you got stuff I sure do
okay let's do with that
hey let's put a hole in that beautiful
suit ears give me the case don't be
stupid
nobody ripped off miles give me the case
get it in now
judge Rayburn you knowing yeah I know
him yeah his wife thinks he's spending
after hours with a particular defense
attorney exchanging more than legal
advice so she wants pictures it'll hold
up in court even in his court where do
they meet I don't know he's got a house
at the bottom of the hill hmm I'll
probably need a telephone talk to Griff
have you guys seen my keys what's the
rush what it's the DMV I made an
appointment so I wouldn't have to wait
in line and if I miss it I'm gonna be in
there for weeks mmm coaches bet fifth
ranks hi is Ryan here Charlie hi sis
you
in a City of Angels under cover of
people don't drown
in a sea of light
the devil holdin your life on
angel uh : painful time
ah
Oh Mitch garna this is my sister charlie
hi hi Charlie how you do look it's nice
to meet you Charlie Luce I'm gonna go
talk to Griff and see if you gotta help
us out okay great so what are you doing
here well I got a few days off from work
I took the red-eye in camera C so here I
am yeah I didn't catch it a bad time to
die I just wanted to surprise you yeah
you did surprise me I just I wish you
would have called so I could have
planned oh you never change and you know
me there's so much fun and not planning
um listen I've got to run to the DMV you
can come with me or you're more than
welcome to stay here mitch is gonna stay
here right
I think I'll grab a bite to eat I'm
starving
if you want I'll take you there's a
great restaurant downstairs the least I
can do for my partner sister is he
always asleep yes most of the time I'll
see you guys later
McCadden yeah yeah hang on it's for you
won't wash taking a rides desk
hello I cannot believe you left me there
hey how you doing how'd you get this
number
Rachel had it I want the money Charlie
bring it back listen I haven't taken a
vacation in two years I'm not gonna come
back right now now you can fire me if
you want it's nice being wanted but
you're gonna have to be patient okay
okay I'll deal with it when I get back
goodbye let's see I'm starved so that's
how she left New York and move to Texas
she doesn't talk much about me does she
know
when Ryan and I were growing up we were
inseparable wherever she went
I wonder who could always count on each
other did you know she was Miss Texas
you kidding you mean like in swimsuit
high heels a whole nine yards the whole
thing ah she could have gone on to Miss
America that didn't oh I didn't she
don't know I have to ask her
believe me I will Donna River second
like you didn't meet Ryan's sister
Charlie hi hi hi this is Donna
this is uh Donna's Club it looks
happening the food's great hey nice
outfit DKNY no Josh and how it looks
great thanks but not for California the
airline lost my luggage I can take care
of that don't you come with me oh boo be
right back
I'll be here so you own this place not
totally but working on it I never know
what could come up so I open my trunk
and voila Wow
welcome to my ready set go now let's see
I'm sure we can find something in here
for you here try this
what's the story with Mitch and lion how
should I know if they don't listen why
don't you just help yourself great thank
you
ah I love it it's perfect like it
thanks I'm going oh she's all set
good should be back in a minute she had
to use the phone you know it's hard to
believe she and Ryder from the same mold
I need a passport Dorn it's kind of
course I don't care how much it costs
all right we got a picture ok Wiis
pictures of themselves of course I don't
have one but I'm gonna be at this place
called nights with my sister do you know
what yeah yeah I know where I'll be
there tonight
hey and be discreet you got it hey Steph
is Mitch actually I'm not being a PI or
a lifeguard I'm just kickin it but I'm
out here on the north beach I know this
is a major rip be sure you keep
everybody out of the water see it hey
hey that was very cool of Donna to lend
me these clothes good so what do you do
for fun around here I saw this water
bike Oh actually they're called wave
rockers they look like fun well they are
you know I got a few hours uh you got a
bathing suit I take you for a spin right
here works for me
don't tell me you didn't take don't tell
me you're the wrong guy if you value
your life at all
dummy tell me what my briefcase is it's
Los Angeles
Los Angeles is a big city
I'll get Swiss with Charlie okay she's
staying with her sisters nap now I I
just spoke with the front of my daughter
she's already contacted and and she's
getting it out of the country
miss Angeles how thoughtful let me
guess.you I'm gonna fly there get my
briefcase bring it back to me
right
I want an address charlie this guy Doren
I don't have an address okay I just I
just have the sisters number she where
she works since it's a bi agency
somewhere in Malibu bi and Doran gets in
there okay
the last day was Walter
thanks a lot
come on
be rules to a stakeout stay alert don't
complain and take plenty of food got it
hey you right hey girl listen this wrap
us up no problem
hey you can see chair I just came from
Knights I'm looking for mission Charlie
if you see them anywhere I can't find
him
so listen about Mitch
if you're not why not cuz we work
together so never would stop me yeah I
know
come on he's just your type he's
good-looking he's smart he's solid as a
rock you know I have my hands on his
chest and I had to fall in the water to
cool off I guess I'm just missing out
aren't I
ah this is where you live yeah it's just
temporary you think about buying the
land and then living on it for a year or
so before I decide what kind of house I
want to build putting down roots yeah I
guess you can say that like Charlie sit
down for a second yeah so I don't hear
from you for over a year and suddenly
here you are you want to tell me what's
going on I told you I came here to see
you I'm your sister Charlie I know you
better than that you're not being fair
look I just don't want to see you in any
kind of trouble again listen to you who
the hell do you think you are mom no I
believe you took care of that is that
what this is all about
look Charlie there are eight million
reasons why I left New York and no
offense but you're one of them now I
didn't ask you to come here I don't
remember extending any invitation for
you just to show up like this
you know I'm sorry I wasn't as perfect
as you growing up and for the record I
miss mom too this was obviously a
mistake
drive me back I'm out of here
wait charlie please wait look I want to
believe you the thought of you coming
out here to spend some time with me is
great if that's really what you're here
to do but you don't understand what
you're asking me to do is throw away
everything that you've done in the past
and trust you
people can change give me a chance to
prove it
I'm sorry I'm glad you're here
I really am let's go out tonight
celebrate new beginnings my treat
oh let me just stay in and make some
popcorn and talk about all the times
California tame you down or what what
happened to that New Yorker we used to
stay up all night party well she got a
job come on we both need more excitement
on my first night here let's go tonight
I hear it's fun right yeah I think I
could use a good New York night out oh
now you're talking
alright Hitler
shucks
you're only three drinks would you like
to travel forth
see that weirdo took my picture yeah
he thought I was Demi Moore and I
thought no more estranged would you like
another drink I'm buying yeah sure
when you have a chance please hello miss
Texas why a dream here little lady
these are on your sister she is full of
information she's got a big mouth uh
sisters so what else did she tell you
about me Oh few things why did you go on
to Miss America but you would have won
no I will in my style I had to do it I
just did it to prove something to
Charlie uh-huh
so that's what's going on with you two
there's more to it than that
Charlie had been arrested for the
zillionth time my mother went to bail
her out like she always did and she was
killed in a car accident on her way to
Oh God enough Ryan I'm sorry you blame
Charlie I just never should have
happened as much as I want to it's so
hard for me to trust her she's so good
at telling you what she thinks she want
to hear and every time she comes into my
life she's in some sort of trouble or
she's about to find some
maybe she's here and put the past behind
her yeah maybe
would you excuse me I have some bills to
pay
morning good morning you cooked
breakfast
shocker isn't it yeah it is what'd I do
to deserve this you put up with me all
these years but this is all I get
good throw in some parsley you seemed
uptight at the club last night didn't
say a word the whole way home is is
there something I said or or did come on
tell me
uh here's very Californian to open up
okay you do whatever you want no matter
how it affects people don't you it's the
way I am you got a girl with a moment
cuz you don't know if it'll come back a
second time you should try it take a
shot of tequila kiss a guy cuz he want
to skydive you know something impulsive
makes life a lot more exciting
you could die tomorrow not everything
has to come from your date book what do
you really think my life is that boring
professionally no personally yes okay
well at least I know where I'm going but
how you get there is a fun part so what
fun parts you have planned for today
well if I can get a ride with you I
thought I'd go to the Strand check it
out yeah sure bro
but Lu
well so tell me now what brings you here
so her God talk to you about something
okay
garner there's something about Charlie
I'm not buying like what guy came into
the club last time took a picture her I
recognized up on the Strand he's got a
very bad rep feels an illegal paperwork
here they are
shouldn't you tell Ryan not just yet
right back
hey Donna morning good morning
oh my god it is
would you if I ask you an honest
question give me an honest answer as
long as it doesn't incriminate me um do
you think I'm personally boring yes
thanks
No
göran
I hope you finished because I got a book
and like now come on you can sleep later
where's the briefcase I don't know what
you're talking about I just get to order
t-shirts I am NOT interested in
conversation just that briefcase I swear
I don't know anything about any
briefcase I am NOT gonna ask you again
the guy to the beer behind it slow down
one of the cops
go to court get out of my way hey what's
your problem I'm in a hurry you can go
around and go down Jerry coming through
any questions harnessing you're dead Tom
what's going on my old roommate Rachel
her boyfriend's this guy named Rex he
found out I drove limos and I was good
at it he paid me a lot of money to drive
and not ask questions all I know is
these guys in Wall Street they wanted to
buy some very high-grade powder things
got way out of hand
so what's in the briefcase the guy was
talking about drugs cash 1.5 million
explains a lot look pitcher that was the
shooting and I was scared I didn't plan
on taking the briefcase I just did it
and came here I thought I'd be safe
you're far from gonna come on come on
huh hey John I need a ride headquarters
pronto
where's the briefcase the guy was
talking about the airline's lost it I
didn't want to carry it with me on a bet
what have they made me open it up what
would I say I swear on my chest way I
keep calling the airline I just want to
get it back what's your connection with
the dead guy and the guy who thought you
were Demi Moore give me a password to
get out of country what about the guy
chasing is how he know where you were
unless it got to Rex Rex knows Doren
yeah yeah that's me she got away
hey I don't know she was with some guy
all right I'll call you back
excuse me oh I'm sorry I didn't you
scare you do you have a sister fighting
with Charlie bunny chance yeah why
what'd she do now oh well you better
come with me okay uh you know what I
don't think so I do please
what the hell where's Ryan I don't know
what's wrong somebody busted into our
car I look something's coming down here
we can have a great diner
I need his heart to match he asked me
Mitch please Mitch they want their money
I don't know what they're talking about
you just take it easy put him on the
phone are you confused about any of this
no it's a straight swap call you in one
hour with the instructions get the money
don't be late I want the money or
they're gonna kill Ryan what money
Mitch the airline lost it I'm not buying
the airline crap no Ryan is gonna die
unless you start telling the truth where
is it it's at the airport I left the
briefcase with baggage claim if they
call house door who is that guy who
called for you yesterday that was Rick's
I knew something was up you must be
pretty good at reading people most of
the time never make a mistake
not yet
thank you
we call bud yet open it I can't I don't
know the combination
I drew what were you expecting a million
five cash where's Ally now Charlie miss
Rex I swear he didn't have the money or
or somehow he scammed it but these guys
think you have you're not gotta believe
I don't please Mitch you're gonna kill
me they don't have you
they have Ryan
you got the money
yeah we got it now listen good you have
Charlie meet us inside the old cannery
at the end of pier four in 45 minutes
she comes alone or her sister is dead
what are we gonna do exactly what the
man says except yeah exactly
you got one that's enough no choice
ister it's Ryan
you
well here's the stuff you wanted
remember how to use it to come with
instructions anymore
clear as a day you taught me don't tell
me I don't want to know
Hey
are you doing
she come alone yeah good girl
are you okay yeah I got what you wanted
I'm glad you remembered what you did
with my money open it I can't I don't
know the combo
well you seem like the type that would
figured out a way sorry to disappoint
you listen you got your money now let us
go I wish it was that easy but nobody
steals from me and gets away with it
if your friend Rex could talk he would
tell you that at least let her call my
sister had nothing to do with it she
doesn't even know about the money
they said everything's cool now just
just let us go
maybe I didn't make myself clear
come on come on
stay here
you guys okay yeah hey we got one more
guy to take care of know how to carry
him so what so this is your plan you
came in to save me with an empty
briefcase last time I checked petty cash
we're a million five short sighs work
didn't it
too bad
Hey hi you okay yeah
I sure wish I had the friends you do
yeah I'm pretty lucky listen you need to
worry about those guys following you
around okay I got me wearing striped
suits for a long time
messed up again could have gotten you
killed Mitch garner you are the way you
are I can't change you Charlie you gotta
change yourself
I'm so sorry
hey I know yeah we drive to the airport
tomorrow it's okay thank you
I hate goodbyes at airports listen when
I get my next paycheck I'll send you and
Donna the money for the clothes don't
worry about I'll take you out
you always do promise you'll come back
yeah next time I'll call first okay
for what it's worth Ryan didn't want to
believe me
why should she she's my sister it's what
you've always counted on
life is not as easy for me Ryan I knew
you'd be okay you've got friends that
take care of you I'm all alone anyway
I know you're gonna have a hard time
believing this with I really am sorry
I'm sorry too
there's some people who want to talk to
you in New York
I don't know where we go from there
you all right yeah
what's up with you but I'm still
thinking about that guy shot
you gonna shot him he shot me yeah silly
don't feel good about it it wasn't for
you and that gun I wouldn't be alive
thanks partner
hey Donna hey oh yeah are the guys here
yeah they are listen can't talk to you
person be sure
listen Ryan the other day in the parking
lot I didn't mean to hurt your feelings
oh no that's okay did I asked you were
just being honest came out a little
harsher than I ma'am
well if you didn't mean boring what did
you mean predictable predictable great
that's even worse
no nobody wants to be predictable
predictable dependable good solid traits
I just didn't want you to think I was
being catty oh no not at all no I didn't
think that for a second
well listen can I get you something yeah
yeah I'll have a drink I know I know
margarita blended no salt unless you
wanted something else no no no that's
what I want pretty boring huh well
predictable yeah
Hey
oh excuse me but now she's getting on
the table
what was that for just cuz I wanted to
does me we're going out or anything
go girl go
blow your dreams
there's a race
here sir
Oh
in the penguin
the devil is watching as we slide in
to
you