Sure you don't want to go up today.
Now I'm gonna gather.
The kids and feed them. Okay.
I'll try not to stay up too long.
See ya.
Oh my God.
After the.
In the city ofs under of night,
people are drowned in the sea.
The.
Devils hold in your life. Online.
Rain for time.
After.
The.
Someone's gonna die.
Hi. Hi.
Wow. All shined up. We ready for business?
Good morning, ladies. Good
morning. Why are we here? Um,
oh.
They're here to find out if
they're gonna keep their jobs.
And.
We're here to meet the new
owner and to sign this lease.
DG Marco, what's uh, DG stand for? I.
Don't know, but whoever this Marco is,
he's done a really nice job
with renovating Lous place.
Take him inside. That's good.
Over by the bar. Why? Goodness.
Maybe we should have brought a present.
I don't know. It looks like somebody died.
Hi, I'm, uh, Mitch
Buchanan. And, uh, well,
if you're going to be one
of the new waitresses here,
let me assure you that you'll be getting
all of my business. Well, thank you.
Sugar. I'm the owner.
Oh. But I will appreciate your
business. You're DG Marco,
Please call me Donna. You must
be garner eler. B I must be.
And of course, Ryan McBride. Hello.
I use the initials in
business cuz it's easier.
Change.
Is good. I I like it here. I do. Yeah.
Oh, that's awfully sweet of him.
Mm-hmm. . Hi girls.
Hey. Oh, you're also
lovely. Thank you so lot.
I think the customer should be paying
attention to you, not the prices. Oh,
that's so sweet. Those
uniforms have to go.
Oh, so do we. It's.
Nice to meet you. Okay. All
right. See you later. Bye.
So their corporate controller is killed
in an accident and three days later they
have.
A party.
Evidently, the party was planned about
three months ago after these people,
their clients fall in
from all over the country.
Wall Street, big bucks.
Why you?
Because I'm an old friend
and a very good dancer.
Guess those dancing lessons paid off, huh?
Yeah.
And speaking.
Of getting paid, what are we doing here?
All work, work, work. Will you just
lighten up and a enjoy of the day?
Look it.
I'm not real sure about this.
Don't worry, I won't. But.
You better not Well.
Not that hard anyway.
Hey Mitch. Oh, there.
There's that guy. Follow me.
Ah, ladies first. Hey yo.
Oh, thank you.
You look terrific. Thank you. You
too buddy. Yay. . Ryan,
I'd like you to meet Red
and Deborah. This is my.
Pleasure. Nice meet. Hi. Nice to meet
too. It's a pleasure. Nice to meet you.
All.
Of us tried to got here.
Yeah. Well, you know,
we're just putting up a
good front for the clients.
We're all still pretty numb
about what happened to Doug.
Sorry to hear about that.
It's a terrible accident.
Mitch. We don't think what happened
to Doug was necessarily an accident.
Look.
Let's go grab a bite and we can talk.
Last month our senior legal
counsel died back east,
fell asleep in his hotel
room, smoking in bed.
You don't think that was
an accident either, Mitch.
This was a five star hotel.
The smoke detector in his
room mysteriously fails along
with the hotel sprinkler
system. I don't think so.
So you've had two deaths.
What.
Are the cops say?
We haven't pushed the police
as far as everyone's concerned.
These are two separate accidents.
We're a public company.
The press will crucify us.
It could be just that
a coincidence. Anyway,
Brian, we've known Mitch since high
school. We need someone we can trust.
Someone who'll be discreet.
If this is our imaginations, just
tell us. And what if it's not?
We'll take whatever you find the
authorities and push like hell.
So is this the kind of thing you can do?
Oh yeah, definitely.
Great. I feel better already.
Oh, Wayne, can you start? Well, and.
It seems all your executives and
most of your clients are here.
So I'd say we can start tonight. That's.
Great.
Nick. Donald.
Hi. Hi. I've been looking.
For you too. Yeah, there's plenty
of time for that. First listen,
I want you to meet an old friend
of mine, Mitch Buchanan. Hi.
And his associate Ryan McBride.
Nikki Shater and Donald Janssen.
Two of Rankers best people.
Hello. Hello. Nice to meet you.
Bye. Very nice to meet you. Oops.
That's me. . I gave a
couple of folks. Mom, Omaha,
my little Harbor tour tied off
and some other guy slipped. Uh,
sounds like he's back.
.
Looks like the buddy's working. Well,
the Tommy's a little awkward for us,
that's all. Well, Mitch and Ryan are gonna
help us find out what really happens.
Doug. Oh, the private investigators.
Look, I wish you the best of luck, but
I really must get out of this night.
Air my hate, fever's killing me.
Dawn. Well,
I'm sure glad we're finally getting
some help here. And um, listen,
if there's anything I can do, please
let me know. We'll let you know.
Uh, there are a couple other people
I'd like you to meet. See you later.
Nice to meet you. Have fun.
Well, you got.
Any ideas?
Not a clue.
9 1 1.
Hey. Hi. How's I doing?
It's hard to say. They've got him
so doped up, but Deborah's whooping.
She's been here all night.
What do the cops find? Anything?
They still think it's an accident.
They haven't made a connection
between the other two.
Oh, they will. I need to know
more about what goes on at Ranker.
Right now. I have an office full
of people waiting for me. Well.
Can you meet me later for dinner?
What's both threaten and
Deborah out of the loop.
I really do have my hands full.
Nick, I need some information.
And I don't think Debbie's up
to a lot of questions right now.
Like what?
Well start off with. Who,
why? What's the motive?
Think corporate sabotage.
Someone's trying to ruin us.
Set us up for a hostile takeover
by destroying our management.
Team. All right. That's the
motive. But who, I mean,
who would want it bad
enough to kill three people?
I see what you mean. Okay. Where nights.
Love on the beach.
I'll find it. 10 o'clock.
10 O'clock. Thanks. Mm-hmm. .
Hey, how's he doing?
We've got him from touching
God to holding his own.
I'm afraid to ask anymore.
No. When RET and I were in college,
we played on the varsity water
polo team together. Right? Well,
we were sophomores so we didn't
get much playing time. Well,
when re finally got a shot, he comes in,
he gets slammed to the side
of the pool by two seniors.
He broke his wrist. But you
knew he kept on playing.
He didn't ask to be
taken down to the game.
Pat never told me that.
Kept on playing and he
scored two goals of this man
knows how to fight pain
and he knows how to win.
Cause no way he's gonna
lose his fight. Yeah,
but you gotta hang in and give him
all the strength. You can kill him.
I will.
Okay. Yeah. Okay.
So what'd you get from
the guys downtown Garner?
These were taken by the Malibu.
Sheriff's accident investigators.
Mm-hmm. . See this?
This is the aluminum glider strut.
You see these marks on
it? Mm-hmm. .
I don't think those are mal fatigue.
Are you saying that
somebody cut that hang.
Glider frame? That's possible. I
need to take a look at that strut.
Hey, did you know that Deborah
falls for divorce last year?
Yeah. Yeah, I heard about that.
But I also heard they patched
the whole thing up, but they.
Right.
Worked it out. What did the
police find at the marina?
Well, they pulled the boat up first thing
this morning. It was, uh, loose wires,
faulty fuel pump, leaky gas line.
Accident.
It looks like waited in.
Don't buy that at all.
Can you go in a favor downtown?
Probably.
Have him check for something sophisticated
like Gill Ignite or plastic laid
against the fuel tank and a
remote trigger, not a timer.
Well, that'll cost me a lot of
favors, but I'll see what I can do.
Also think I'll put in some undercover
time at Rain Corp. Pile around.
See if I can do up some dirt.
Gas, man again.
Oh, I think maybe telephone
man, this time. That's always.
Interesting. Very good. And you?
Well, I wanna find out what's
changed, Who's new, who's angry,
who profits, and who suffers
from all this. Great.
What about you?
Me? I've got a dinner day. Oh.
With.
Who? Nikki. She Nice work.
Ryan McBride. Confidential investigations.
Really a private dick.
Not my favorite choice of words.
I'm sorry. Would you like to sit down?
Uh, no thank you.
It's just you're the first woman that
I've met in this line of work. Uh,
what were you before? A cop.
The forensic specialist. And I'd love
to sit here and swap resumes with you,
but I'm in kind of a hurry. You got
a call from a Ms. Deborah Collins,
didn't you?
Yes. She said to, uh, cooperate.
So, uh, what can we do for you?
You've been rankers head hunter for.
Every new executive hired
in the last 10 years.
Great. All right. Well I'm
interested in the most recent say,
past year and a half.
Hello. Let's see what we have over here.
Alrighty. This is the latest.
Paul Ard. Corin tongs.
Nikki Shater. Yeah.
Yeah. What about.
Her acquisitions and development?
Impeccable background.
And before heard Donald Janssen.
Janssen went to Harvard
Wharton School of Finance.
A real up and comer.
Where was he during this two year period?
Uh, it could've been on sabbatical. I
don't, I have four more. Do you want 'em?
Yeah. Can you gimme hard
copies of these? Sure.
Then, uh, maybe we could do
some work on your resume.
Yeah, maybe we could.
I think we really could.
Hey. Hi. Wanna I join in? Sure.
Go ahead.
So what do you think of the pledge? You.
Like it. Love.
It.
What would make it better?
Um, pool table, bumper.
No regulation.
Competition. Size four and a half
by nine. Or bar size? Four by.
Eight. Four by eight.
You got it.
Just like that. Just.
Like that.
Why?
So you'll spend your time.
And spend your money.
Hey, you made it. Sit
down. Sit down between.
The rain and the traffic and.
Everything. No apologies needed.
Believe me. But wait, what's well worth?
Thank you.
What do you drink?
Uh, whatever You.
Have. Iced tea. Long.
Island?
No, strictly West coast.
Uh, I'll have the same bed.
Okay, so you have questions?
Yeah. Yeah. I got a few.
Do you have a list of suspects?
Well, I'm working on.
That. Am I on it?
Should you be?
Where did you get the
suspicious size police?
Fbi. Cia.
Uh, trying lifeguard.
. Lifeguard as in.
Beach as in the sand.
What's the connection between being
a lifeguard and doing pi work?
I don't know. Maybe I just
like helping people in trouble.
Ah, sounds like a white night complex.
Here's two nights of shining arm.
And damsels and distress.
Well, thanks again for coming, huh?
Wow. I hope I was up some
help. Anyway, I'm glad I came.
I needed to relax the.
Little relax. Must look at
your watch a dozen times.
For some habit.
Thank you. I feel a lot better knowing
that you and your team are on this case.
Hang on. I get it.
Have to wait until there are some
investigators. Uh, go through the rest of.
You. All right.
No, I'm not even close to, All right.
Police kept asking who wants to kill you?
Like I can pull out a list
or something, but you know,
then I kept thinking she's right. Someone,
someone I probably know wants me dead.
I'm scared I want to go home.
Maybe I can't go home.
Maybe it's not safe, right?
No, it's not safe.
I couldn't do much.
Come here.
There's a phrase that
lifeguards use. It's relax.
I gotcha. I gotcha. And if you want,
you can spend the night at my place
and I guarantee you'll be safe.
And tomorrow.
And tomorrow when the
sun comes up. We'll, uh,
we'll try and make some sense of
this. Make sure we keep you safe,
okay? Okay. Okay, let's go.
You.
Are quite the gentleman.
Alright?
Yeah.
I heard you and Nikki was killed.
Exactly. Almost. We were almost killed.
Just enough time to get away.
Well, you were lucky.
Yeah, that's what I thought too. Except
the timing was just perfect. I mean,
it was too perfect. Other couple of
seconds, parts of me would be in Oxnard.
Do me a favor, Will you? We're
on a check on this and see.
If, uh, they can trigger
an explosion. Yeah.
Yeah.
No problem.
10 To one. I find you here.
Gee, there's a safe bet.
I got no life, Mitch.
I'm either with the federal building
or I'm here. Take it for me. Way out.
Sad, isn't it.
Breaking my heart? Your
buddy. I need a favor.
Official. No, actually off the
record, I'm gonna background check.
Very deep.
That's gonna cost you own
buddy. Desperate, lonely man.
It's need to meet a woman. Oh my.
Now you're surrounded by woman.
All I need is an introduction.
Who? This time?
The blonde.
Cj?
Oh, no, no. Not cj. The other one. You
know the one that bought the, the club.
Nice. Donna, you want me to
fix you up with Donna? Mitch?
I don't know what is about her, but
she's like, she's like a goddess Now.
Come on p just an introduction.
I mean, it could be kids met.
She's got a guy very.
Rich. I'm not looking for marriage. Just
a little conversation. Come on Mitch.
Sammy. Think of it as, think
of it as a mission of mercy.
She's gonna kill me. Deal.
Great. Now what's the
name you want me to check.
Out? Woman Now, Nikki Shater.
Don't bother. Here's a four 11.
What'd you do?
I don't know. Maybe nothing.
But you don't think so? Okay.
I run from get up to get gone.
You're prince among things.
Mitch.
I'll talk to Donna and see when
she's gonna be at nights. And uh,
you can meet me there for a drink.
Round five.
After five.
Evening.
Sir. Good evening.
Good evening. How?
Hello
sir?
Hey Don. I need a favor. There's
a guy I want you to meet.
A guy he want me to meet.
Uh, actually I said that
wrong. He wants to meet you.
It amounts to the same thing.
It's just an introduction.
Introduction leads to
conversation, to invitation.
Then it's dinner. He's
charming. We dance. He's cute.
He says this. I say that. We
leave. He wants to go to my.
Place. It's not like that. Really?
I mean, well not this time.
Okay, How about if I came to
you and said I wanna set you up.
All you gotta do is say hello Donna.
The guy did me a tremendous favor.
What favor?
I needed some information on
someone and he got it for me.
How's he able to do that?
Well, he works for the federal
government. Treasury department.
Treasury department.
Why didn't you say so?
Then you'll do it.
She'll do it.
So what'd you get on
Janssen? Carbon monoxide.
Turns out older. Less seric
acid in his humidifier.
They've got him in a hyperbaric chamber.
Tell you the cops all over this now.
Knee deep and rising.
You can, Yeah.
Well thank you very much. Yeah.
Yeah. I told you after five
Ned Jud.
The Fed.
I wrote a background
check on Nikki. Dirty.
Looks like little Nick was in the
intelligence branch of the special forces.
The experts on sabotage and explosives.
Okay. She's got a working knowledge,
but, uh, what's the motive?
Father committed suicide. Turns out his
company was absorbed by rankers legally,
but uh.
She feels they steam more. Go revenge.
Hey guys, you were right.
This thing was modified.
I mean, it's not gonna
open any trucks. Bill.
Definitely light up the parking lot.
Get to the hospital and.
Uh, sit with Rick. Debbie.
She's got a condo at the marina.
Let's do it.
Nikki's really lost it, killing all those
people just to bring a company down.
Yeah. I just hope Debbie's
not her next victim.
You're crazy. Why are you doing this?
I said shut up. We can talk
this out. It's too late for.
That. Well.
You can get in the boat.
Come on. Come on. Move.
Sit down in the corner. What?
Sit down. God, you don't.
Have to do that. I'm never gonna
give you any trouble. I promise.
Yeah, that's what your
lawyer sold my father.
Just before they bought him
out at 10 cents on the dollar
before they crushed him.
Taking into the water. Now
col looks back up. Huh?
What
you
It's a bomb.
It's ready to go off.
If it's pulled loose.
I kick it out.
Hang on, hang on. I'll get you out here.
Come,
go, go, go.
You okay now? Come on.
So you're telling me that she had
the chance to jump and didn't?
Yeah, I guess she knew it was over.
Oh.
That's heavy.
What's that thing about? Uh,
vengeance. You're alpha revenge.
Dig two graves one for yourself.
Uh, speaking of digging
a grave for yourself,
how's that deal with Donna coming along?
? I'm about to find out. Excuse me.
Hey.
Mitch.
Hey, say bud. How are you? I'm good.
I looked at you. You look terrific.
Oh my gosh. She's.
More incredible than.
I remember. Yeah, I know. Um,
why don't you sit down and have a drink
here And what I'll do is I'll just,
you know, smooth things over. Let her
know you're here. Okay? Yeah. All buddy.
You look great. Nice.
Ah.
Excuse me. He's here.
Who?
Him?
Yeah. The.
Guy I told you he wanted to meet you.
Yeah. No, I don't think so.
Donna, you promised. No, I.
Didn't promise.
Okay. Well you didn't promise. But
look, the guy, gimme a huge favor.
Please don't let me down.
You know, it's very dangerous, this
business of meeting men in bars,
strange men, even familiar bars.
It always leads to problems.
Don't do this to me. Just an introduction.
Isn't that how it always starts?
How do we have this conversation?
And I'm still concerned.
Ah, did I mention he is with
the Treasury Department?
Yes. What if I find him interesting?
Are you messing with me?
I don't know. Am I?
You owe me.
Hi Ned, right?
Uhhuh.
I'm Donna. Welcome tonight.
Thanks. Pleasure to meet you. My.
Mind.
Nine too. Mitch tells me you're
a man in the know. Oh really?
Well, not, not exactly.
Well one thing you learn running a
bar, confident, good looking men.
Never have to brag. I
love that. It's very sexy.
So this is your first time at
night. It's allow me to buy your.
First. Oh, thanks. Have you
seen the patio? Oh, you love it.
So the department is that likers
only reason that I
blow dreams. There's a,
you, you.