[Music]
great shot no that's going to separate
me from the thousands got it
see that's my problem I'm unique no I
know I am I have something very special
way beyond my looks in my body I'm gonna
be the next great female action star
that everybody's looking for
okay I'm let's talk about the shot are
you sure you want to wear this harem
outfit
well Harry picked it out do you think
this is what's what you want what it's
not sexy enough no um yeah it's plenty
sexy but okay who's your favorite action
here um fly right fly okay um what's
with slide we're a harem outfit no no he
would not okay he be Evie stripped to
the waist he'd be greased down you have
a gun in one hand and a knife in yet
what the hell are you saying I'm talking
about the style of the shot what it says
it sounds like you're trying to see
Sondra topless no I didn't say that yeah
I think you did no what I said was
Stallone would be topless so she should
be well not necessarily but figuratively
I don't like the way you've been looking
at her from the get I haven't been
looking at her anyway I think you have
Harry don't be a jerk I'm your manager
right is that right please please please
please
look I'm just talking about a picture
okay I didn't mean to make you feel
insecure insecure okay not if not
insecure defense defensive okay not
defensive inadequate I don't know I'm
just I'm just trying to take a picture
that's here I know exactly what you're
trying to do you're trying to promote
milady
he is not I am NOT oh look there's no
need for that okay get your ass no
you're not so don't even think about it
quit if Harry is really making you look
like a fool oh oh I wish you hadn't said
that you know what I'm out of here okay
I took this gig because I needed money
what I don't need is this abuse Sandra
you can get someone else to finish the
shoot its Sandra what you called me
Sandra but it's Sandra I had
changed legally whatever Sandra Sandra
doesn't matter this is it over sorry
Harry no one humiliates me yo
[Music]
[Applause]
in a city of angels under cover of night
people don't drown
in a sea of light
the devil's holding your life um
[Music]
angel : rainbow time
in for it
[Music]
[Applause]
here she is but kena Morgan ladies and
gentlemen as chairman and CEO of Sun
bliss clothing I take a great deal of
pride and pleasure in announcing our
purchase of Azure blue effective Monday
morning you gave birth to Azure blue
McKenna Morgan helped it grow into the
most successful swimwear line in the
world I'll give you my solemn oath I'll
take good care of your child
Thank You Carl we are all very very
quick enough to easy
Makenna please please don't do this
thanks for caring we rock music very
exciting time larger manufacturing and
designing talent do this okay you can't
throw away 20 years I love you back off
hey wait ladies and gentlemen where we
have all to all your questions back if
you'll follow me over here the viewer
you're a bunch of concerning that's my
wife
Thank You Jon right over here
McKenna mr. powers will answer any
questions you have right over here
she doesn't want to talk to go away
we were talking and it was hopeful I
mean it wasn't certain but it was
hopeful and then six weeks ago she goes
off to a fat farm has her eyes done
maybe she's just trying to change her
life I don't know there's just something
very very strange going on and I know
he's gonna think I'm crazy about this
but
I don't think McKenna's Makenna not
doing any duh I know I know it's just
that woman I saw at the press conference
the other day I don't think it's hurt I
know it's well I saw a picture in the
paper children oh I know well did she
act like McKenna yeah but something in
my gut tells me otherwise
you always said go with your gut right
you want me to see her yeah
that's why I came here see I know you'll
tell me straight but if it is her please
don't tell her anything about this oh I
don't want her thinking of me any worse
than that she already does okay I'll see
you thanks Mitch just talk to Dewey he's
carrying a lot of weight yeah yeah he's
going through it divorce Oh that'll do
it
so you look nice you on your way to a
workout yeah actually it's an investment
at the community listen Mitch if I buy
into this gym I have to find a way to
attract new clients you work out right
every day why fear fear of what good
someday I won't be physically able to
pull somebody out I'd surf out there no
that won't work people don't respond up
here work out a lot really just Liddy
what when I walk into the room I don't
want to be ignored
ah let's chance of that happening cookie
have a good workout let's see
[Music]
yes my name is Mitch Buchannon and I'm
here to see my kin I'm Morgan is she
expecting you I know I'm an old friend
one minute please
[Music]
[Applause]
hi Lindsay yeah McKenna sends her
apologies but she's very busy is there
something I could do to help um no does
she know I'm here
absolutely I will only take a couple
minutes I'd like to see her it's about
Dewey that's what she thought
could I be candid he's become very
strange very erratic lately I mean the
other day he caused a major disruption
at our press conference she's actually
become quite afraid of I told her to get
a restraining order on him but for the
moment she refuses if you're doing I
keep him away well I'd still like to see
her it'll just take a minute please it's
important I wish I could I'm sorry I
tell you what how about if I see her
long enough for her to say she doesn't
want to see me please of course follow
me
[Music]
watch your step
you
[Music]
sorry to disturb your McKenna but mr.
Buchanan insisted no Mitch Kenna how are
you okay sorry to barge in on if it's
about Dewey save it
I'm not interested really worried about
now he's worried why not two years ago
when it would have made a difference
sorry Mitch I can't be bothered with
Doreen I told him it was a bad time why
don't you give me a call and we'll do
lunch
[Music]
I don't want this husband and his friend
becoming a problem I understand
so was it McKenna or not I don't know
I'm not sure see what I mean okay
be specific McKenna was always affection
no real touchy this this lady was cold
she was aloof she said let's do lunch
that's exactly what I'm talking about
it's the little things
those aren't little things guys that's
nothing maybe maybe not
but at least I'm not crazy I don't know
know by me then what happened to her if
this lady is an imposter
it's a very good question
[Applause]
[Music]
hey huh I need your opinion on something
good I need yours on what well I'm
trying to come up with a signature drink
like a house special exactly I've been
working on it all afternoon these are
the ones I like okay
okay try this I'm gonna call the one I
select perfect nights Donna I'll tell
you right now I don't like it the glass
the glass all this junk it's like you're
trying to hide something that's horrible
noted okay just taste it all right mmm
I'd keep the salad this definitely needs
to be covered up okay now taste this one
maybe a little sweet but try it a little
sweet huh yeah yeah
water water Wow it's the first time I've
ever gotten that reaction from a man oh
no it wasn't you it was there got a
little carried away with the grenadine
that's horrible
Sandra I'm in Sandra what's up Harry is
looking for you
who's Harry her boyfriend oh no no no no
no it's not like that
what does Harry have a knife or
something I don't think so but he's real
mad this is just terrible all I wanted
was that one great picture you know so
casting directors would see me for what
I really am and what's that
um Sandra here wants to be the next
great female action hero the next who's
the latest exactly I'm dying of thirst I
don't know
this is delicious okay said Donna this
is good let me see
mmm it's perfect well ladies I'm sorry I
have to interrupt this but I have to go
in I wouldn't worry too much about Harry
I wasn't I was worried about you that is
so sweet of you but I think I'll be fine
well I warned him yes you did
we need something solid to prove whether
it's McKenna or not thank your friends
right but how do we get those
we'll find get into the house into the
bathroom or the office
I need a cosmetics jar letter opener a
pen anything that she's touched recently
if I can get you in the house
I can get the fingerprints excuse me hey
Grif got a minute more time I'm kind of
busy Mitch yeah I can see that I thought
maybe if you uh that's some time maybe
you could help me with something I'm
talking about a case yeah I like diamond
yeah one second uh ladies thank you very
much that's a wrap so what type of case
murder oh yeah all right here's what I
want oh well the number you last when we
cannot tell oh the photos she ordered
already but since she didn't order any
photos won't she think I'm nuts only it
was the real McKenna if it's not she'll
buy into it say you'd like to deliver
them just like she asked when I go along
when you're inside its long shop it's
all we got three 901 736
hello hey this is a Griff Walker the
photographer my speak with McKenna
please uh where she's not available
right now
what do you need tell him the photo she
ordered already yeah those uh prints
shorter to ready well when did she order
these prints before she went to the fat
farm before she went to the fat farm
listen is McKenna there can't you speak
with her just send him over don't know
the guy pick your liver look what's
going on I get a rush order for McKenna
she tells me that it distills the new
line and then hand deliver them okay
hand-deliver all right I will
now what take some pictures of the girls
and bikinis put them in an envelope and
you and Ryan deliver them sounds good
[Music]
oh hey I got the pictures where's Miss
Morgan she said to leave them so just
send you the bill and thank you very
much no problem in um let me show you
what I did real quick see you explain it
to her that's not necessary
sure actually I'm uh
I'm a little busy so um I'm sorry is
there any way I could borrow your
restroom with these yeah actually meet
you I should have drank all it follow me
thank you first order right
[Music]
okay make a prince
can I help you um hi I was just looking
for the bathroom oh it's right through
there just got a little turn around
[Music]
what's going on
nothing she was she was just I was
looking for the bathroom
I I got lost it's really beautiful have
a nice day
thank you
[Music]
Gardner's friend downtown Randy's most
I'm belong to McKenna the real McKenna
when the others well there are some that
we can't identify at all but then there
are others that we can't identify and
they do not belong to him the imposter
right well the maid well Ryan or anybody
else who is using the office yeah look
DMV has some matches there are two that
belonged to domestic help and one
belongs to a certain Jessica Aitken's a
cocktail waitress slash actress from
Tupelo Mississippi well guess who wins
Jessica's been in town for seven months
DMV has an address on her well hairs
blonde not brunette like McKenna's
natural blonde let's guess no green eyes
not brown like McKenna's same height
about the same way did do we ever
mention Jessica to you know but yeah
should be training right now I'm fine I
want to bring up the date anyway okay
we'll check out Jessica hey Jer
[Applause]
[Music]
you're on
I
we want em
[Applause]
[Music]
this is it
she's probably back at the house right
[Music]
now it's locked yeah it's locked right
what are you doing
right that's that's breaking and
entering no no I'll be gentle just
entering hey hey hey
you need the jaws of life for what who
are you the manager
oh well then hi there
we're friends of Jessica's from back
home in Tupelo Mississippi yeah we are
we were just supposed to meet her here
then go out to dinner yeah it just
amazes us how y'all figure out those la
freeways well we thought we were late
and as it turns out we're half hour
early yeah um you suppose we could just
wait in there for I can't let you in you
can come back or I can tell her you were
here take your choice all right well
we'll come back thank you thank you
let's check out huh cable guy 7d just a
gakuen not home
oh man I might have to come all the way
back you got cable
nope well it's no more trouble to hook
up to and there's one yeah Mitch yeah
free cable huh whatever works alright Oh
[Music]
videotapes Dateline interview October
1994 central plaza Fashion Show in 1995
[Music]
good afternoon ladies and gentlemen and
welcome to this year's azure blue
Fashion Show we're very excited about
good afternoon ladies and gentlemen and
welcome to this shows Asia aloof Fashion
Show come up north Jessie lose the
drawers as much as we did
thank you very much good afternoon
ladies and gentlemen and welcome to this
year's Asian food fashion show
Haymitch yeah I found a file called
McKenna she's got a personal history
from the day she was born
family members co-workers list of
enemies look here on her friends get you
beginnin left guard with dewy divorced
ex-wife Gail one son homie I guess at
the wedding in 1987 speaker at the
serving hall of fame indoctrination
looks like she's got a crib sheet on
who's who and we can do his limes it's a
crash course on McKenna Morgan 101 you
know it Jessica dyes her hair and pops
in some brown contact lenses face her
nose John and with those videotapes of
McKenna she can learn to walk the walk
and talk the talk do he's right
she's not his wife you know if they kill
McKenna on Friday night saw the company
Monday morning boom hey des
keep her away from family friends she
and Dewey are separated they haven't
slept together in months they don't even
talk they don't see each other
you can do it huh do your homework you
can get away with murder all it takes is
48 hours a weekend in town let's talk to
the manager
[Music]
where's the woman who lives here hadn't
been around for a while would you know
where she is she could be at work do you
have that number I don't even know where
she works so if there's any emergency do
you have any way of reaching her
I got a pager number so tomorrow we
signed the contracts and after the sale
is finalized you divorce your husband
get the big payoff and then retire from
the world of fashion just like we play
it I spent a lot of time learning this
part I haven't had plastic surgery is
there a point to all this yeah the point
is I really like this life people want
to take my picture ask my opinion on
things I tell you it sure beats the tar
outta slinging drinks for tuefel oh well
yeah it's been a nice ride and today's
it's gonna be a nice memory I think
there's a way for me to stay here and be
McKenna Morgan well that's not gonna
happen so don't push it
[Music]
hello hello did you page me say comes
this your apartment manager the guy here
wants to talk with you
[Music]
all right listen very carefully your
life depends on how well you understand
me and what you do after I hang up are
you listening
yes who is it my party mentor synthetic
water League
all right when this is over and he has
what he wants he's gonna kill you do you
believe me yes I do
all right if you want to live we have to
meet you come here right now
and I can help you okay I have to go to
my apartment no no no not the left of
the papers are signed the manager has to
go in everything you gave me to study is
right there out in the open okay fine
I'll have Leo take you I don't want you
going anywhere alone until this is all
over but before you go what do you say
we take a little trip down memory lane
huh just so you get a clearer picture of
exactly what it is I can do
now I tried to talk her into selling
that company for three years we've had
this conversation at least 100 times in
the last three years why don't you get
at your head now is the time just so you
realize a pronto no final you at the
fact that you even bring it up so
ridiculous what are you doing
closing a deal I gave one last chance to
make a life-or-death decision she made
the wrong one
get in here
[Music]
give me the gun come on come on
I set the gun down remember and you
picked it up let's go let's go go
[Applause]
you weren't wearing gloves were you hmm
now you go do what you got to do but you
remember one thing your prints are all
over that gun
[Music]
what happened the sprinklers went off my
clothes my air before you go in you have
to sign off come on down in the office
not can you just her she just has to
sign a release uh hey there excuse me
you hi there dad you look nice and
strong could you help me move this out
of the way please
please come on help a girl out Oh how's
it going how do you think it was
terrible before your phone call who's
your friend detective Byron brown LAPD
perfect look not that any of this makes
a difference but I never knew what he
had planned when I took this gig and
then after he killed McKenna I was in up
to my eyeballs and too afraid to run
well we're gonna need more than that
guys got a hell of a lot of money it's
gonna take more than circumstantial
evidence to convict it like a body and a
smoking gun I know where the body is or
at least where it was three days ago we
need you to cooperate this Aitken's
forget it I talk I die we can protect
you Yeah right he's gonna try and take
you out whether you talk or not now your
only chance is to help us nail him huh
no way
look you don't cooperate you're on your
own
you
[Music]
Makenna does the apartment is a disaster
gotta get your drink thanks Chad Lindsay
get in you mr. Lindsay I hope I'm not
interrupting
who's this think of me is a business
partner business partner that's correct
look who the hell is this gloves my
friend put things in proper perspective
hello Chad who is this you're a very bad
boy at a very bad shot guess what I'm
live okay we'll talk later bye
McKenna we'll be in touch
[Music]
you're going now
okay here we go
[Music]
see no but they're gonna dump these by
now
I gotta wait for the barge could be full
there it is I mean she's got to be in
open it up she looking for me judge
[Music]
how the hell does it matter
where's the Englishman he'll be here
good why
why did you try to kill me because I
made Azure blue the success it was I
made all the decisions you made the
magazine covers I made you rich and
famous and now I'm gonna take what's
mine and I'm gonna make sure that you
and your partner are good and dead
[Music]
your plan almost worth oh it still will
be getting well actually it won't
we have you on tape why did you try to
kill me cuz I'm a - you're blue the
success it was pity old boy isn't that
all that work for naught
Tojo's good sugar
Makenna is dead
[Music]
you
alright alright come on come on
one yeah come on all right let's go
you all right yeah I'm fine you yeah
well he's lucky you're a bad shot
who's a bad shot mister I wasn't aiming
at him
Yeah right what was it hey listen shut
up you trying to tell me in the dead of
night you fire off one round it hits the
tank in the exact spot causing that tank
to explode it try to tell me
yes that's what I'm trying to tell you I
can wanna was a fluke it was not nobody
is that good you saw it
[Music]
hey I want to talk to you yeah run but
that's not gonna change anything if I
don't get you today I'll get you
tomorrow
thought you were gonna keep on Ryan was
it running Harry just trying to find a
place where we wouldn't be disturbed
oh yeah if we were in public you might
think people are watching so what you're
free to get your butt whipped in public
no I just wanted this to be private want
to make sure this is really between you
and me and you're not doing this for
Sandra but for yourself
why are you doing this area you know why
no I really don't because of what you
did what did I do you know you know what
I think I think you're doing this
because you're scared scared yeah I
think you really love Sandra but you're
scared you may lose her oh is that what
you think yes I think if you stop for a
second you realize that that fighting is
gonna get you nothing this is between
you and me this is between you and you
between me and me absolutely so what you
want what you're afraid to lose between
what you love and what you fear I mean
is the same for all of us Harry one way
or the other I mean when we're mad at
someone isn't it ourselves were really
angry well you know what I think
not what do you think I don't know what
the hell you're talking about
okay but this thing huh Spice again I'm
gonna break every bone in your body are
we clear huh don't make me go through
this again
[Music]
you
and we're quite the same is it no it's
not the light that clouds the wind Pat
McKenna loved the water I know she did
I'm going to go away for a while the
mountains I think understand that you
know I never thought I'd get tired of
looking at the ocean
thanks for everything
for being there
I see
[Music]
there's a place you've got to
you can't run
you're the sir
Oh
[Music]
in the blink of an eye
the devil is watching every slide
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]