You know, some people think the beach
closes after the sun goes down, Uhuh.
That's when it really starts to
heat up, especially if you're a pi.
Now I know what you're
thinking. Mitch is a lifeguard.
What does he know about
being a pi? Well, uh,
they both involve rescuing people.
Turns out my best friend Garner went
partners in a bankrupt detective agency
with a beautiful brunette Pi who left
New York for the California son and
adventure. What can I say?
When someone yells help,
I jump in with both feet.
And I hope you do too,
as we introduce a new series of private
eye adventures called Baywatch Nights.
Sit back and enjoy the ride
in the city of angels under of night.
People.
Are drowned in the sea of life.
The.
Devils hold in.
Rain for time.
After the
the.
My dad told me that every once
in a while you meet a woman.
So beautiful that it knocks the wind
outta you. Maybe today was my turn.
Fantastic. Fantastic.
Great. Right? Wonderful.
That's wonderful, darling. Work
it. Come on now. You love it, baby.
That's wonderful, darling. Beautiful,
beautiful. Give me more of that.
That's wonderful. Wonderful.
Okay, now make a love to it.
Fantastic. Yeah. I need to
reload. Okay, let's take five.
Let's take as long as I want. Love.
Actually.
Hey Ken. I'm a
reading business.
Bummer. I'm totally
thinking about quitting.
Oh no. Future in reading futures.
How would I know?
Is that uh.
What I think she is?
Depends. Who do you think she is?
You know,
you know it's a drill on the TV ads with
pearls and the champagne and the diving
Bloods.
Cassidy.
Cassidy. Right. Model
of just a first name.
It's a photo shoot for a magazine.
Um, more perfume, I think.
What's.
Perfume called? Lust.
No, you're Aura.
I feel lust. You're radiating.
Mind your own aura.
Well, you're a but. Huh?
How you doing? I stud.
Fine. Thanks.
Not you. Him. That's his name.
.
I knew that.
Mom. Cassidy.
Hi. I know I'm Mitch.
So.
Welcome to our turf.
And what does that mean?
I work.
Right up there.
And what's right up there?
Private.
Detective agency.
Really? Yours?
Um, not so private. I have two partners.
But no. Ready?
I gotta go to work. Come on, stud.
Uh, I can, I gotta go to work too. See ya.
Ryan McBride grew up in Texas and got
our PI license in New York. You know,
women can really complicate your life,
especially if your partners with one.
It's an explosive combination. Hey
guys. Hey. Trust me. Anything happening?
We.
Got a job.
Great.
. What? Missing body.
No, no, no. It's not Missing
bodies. Missing persons. Missing.
Persons. Body. Body. The Crabtree
funeral home somehow misplaced.
The dearly departed Mrs. T whistle.
They'll pay us real money to find it.
Oh God. We sunk that low.
I.
Have Now we need a contract found
the other day under the letter R.
No contract should be under the letter
C I would be rebound relationships. I.
You set up the file
twisted Nikki Pine did.
Fight my head up.
Hello? LB McBride. Buchana
alphabetical alphabet. Hello? Hello?
Hello? Hello. It's.
The blinking one. Mr. ER.
Banks. They are all blinking. Ms. McBride.
Hello? No, we we didn't order any.
Hang on anybody if you like
Pepper. Any pizza. They.
Take check.
We're good.
Our name was Alexa,
a supermodel whose photograph was
on the cover of a hundred magazines.
But this was our last photo session
when I was eight. I got my
first major league baseball.
One day he met McGinty. Uh, he was 12.
Well, he walks up to me and he says, Hey,
gimme your ball. I said, Make
me, He did. I was a mistake.
I've never forgotten. Look.
At, go away and leave me
alone. Were you clean?
Hey. Hey. Leave a lady
alone. You okay? Cassie.
Go away. This is none your.
Business. P just.
Get the hell outta here. Just calm
down. Will you? I'm piece of me. No,
I don't want a piece of you. You just
let the lady go her way. You go Yours.
Okay. Come on. You and
me right here, right now.
I'm not gonna break my
knuckles on your brick head.
Not over.
Not over you. Okay.
Yeah. What's his problem?
Glad I could help. Don't
mention it. You're welcome.
Oh, Lot of tea whistles.
. If you find a relative,
what are you gonna say?
I represent your dead aunt's funeral
home. And uh, I ain't got nobody. Oh,
you wanna come across a hammer?
Uh, yeah, I saw them in the
files. Hammer's under d.
D.
I don't know why. And I don't know
why this computer keeps saying,
What's the password? Butt
head. I just don't know.
You count. Beep.
Hello?
Garner.
Oh.
Shoot. I thought I had it beat this
time. How does this devil phone.
Work?
Mitch? I, uh,
help.
Sick. Little Valentine.
It's not the first time. Other
letters. Heavy breathing on the phone.
Hangups. You have any
idea who it could be? No,
I don't know who he is, where
he is or why he's doing this.
Have you gone to the police?
Yes. They said they can't
do anything unless he.
Restraining order. But if he's
a serious darker knucklehead,
it probably won't do much.
Good. What about that guy with the go
tea today? The big guy who hasling you?
Could he be the guy?
I don't know. He could be, but
Paparazzis are always sneaking around.
I I don't know who he is.
Look, I'm scared to death.
I wanna hire you guys to protect me.
Um, bodyguard.
Around the clock. I'll
pay you whatever it costs.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I was uh, just checking the locks
on the windows and the doors. Okay.
Go ahead.
What's that for?
It's like my sleeping pill with
it Here. And you downstairs.
I know I can sleep.
.
Uh.
Don't worry. I took lessened.
Okay.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Guy with a goe. He you
right in front of me.
Seems kind of weird, don't you think?
Well, we've been shooting
on the beach show a week.
Probably followed me around to get
some photos and 'em to the tabloids.
That's what they do.
Yeah.
Try not to worry.
Why worry? I got a
bodyguard and a lifeguard.
Round The clock protection
means three eight hour shifts.
And I got the graveyard after a
bottle of Merlot and then some
Cassidy was definitely
out for the evening.
Oh.
My god. God. He was standing right there.
I hired you to protect me.
Cassidy. He didn't get past
me. The alarm didn't go off. I
wait a minute.
I checked this last night. It was locked.
I open it. I always sleep with it open.
Well, is it connected to the alarm system?
Yes, but I kept it out of the
loop. Look, it's upstairs.
There's nothing for him
to climb on outside.
Oh my God.
Oh my god.
And Little league. I was a pitcher by
catcher and I communicated through signs.
One finger was a fastball.
Two fingers a curve.
Holding hands is a sign too.
But I didn't know the game
she was playing or the rules.
Only one way to find out.
A very professional holding hands.
The boss.
Oh, I'm just scared.
Oh, you're real lucky. All I
wanted to take was pictures.
It's not the first time
models and actresses.
If they in the spotlight weirdos
try to get at them all the time.
This is the first time anybody's
gotten this close in my house.
My bedroom.
He won't again. Okay.
You last night that got
me thinking about Alexa.
Do you know?
No. Who is she?
Well.
She was a friend of mine, My
best friend. Another model
I found her body at the bottom of a cliff.
Police said it was
suicide. I know it wasn't.
Why do you say that?
Everybody said that she was
depressed, drinking and taking drugs,
but she was never happier. Look,
I had just turned down a perfume
campaign because I was too busy with the
swimsuit calendar. I
suggested her and she got it.
She was on top of the world.
So you're saying why can make suicide?
I was in Denver the night that
she died and I called her.
She told me that somebody was
stalking her. Threatening her.
You think he pushed her off the cliff?
Wait a minute. Do you think he's our guy?
Yes. Cassidy. Why didn't
you tell me this before?
I I didn't wanna believe it. Okay. This,
this guy was in my room taking
pictures of me while I was sleeping.
I'm just so happy that
you're here with me.
Cause.
I don't think I would get through.
This.
It's okay. You want to have to
Three fingers was a change up.
change up always
caught you by surprise.
You knew you shouldn't swing at
it, but you just couldn't help it.
All right. You'll be with her during the
photo shoot this morning, right? Every.
Second and Gar. Spell
me in the afternoon and.
We'll all be there for the fashion show.
Yeah.
What?
Something's.
Wrong.
What?
Ah, this is not your color.
. Let your guard
down. She'll kiss you too.
We gotta break in the T Whistle
case. His name Raja Rajari.
Beji . He was inside
Mrs. T. Whistle's. Coffin.
I guess you'd call Raja Madre.
Kind of a bookkeeping era.
Six foot five, six. Uh, go
tea. Built like the Terminator.
Are you looking for a
paparazzi or a viking? .
That's our Cassidy file. If your
guy's taking pictures of her,
he's gonna be trying to sell
them to me. He's not Bunny.
Ah, no thank you. A bunny.
Ah, no thanks.
Why the dollar sign.
Money shop? Oh, front page. Cassidy
and Jag are caught in steamy Denver.
Love trust. That's not big Jager. I know,
but it sure looks a lot
like him. Don't you think?
He's a Denver undercover cop? But I
thought it was close enough to go.
For it. By the time he won. Sus
you sell a million copies. Exactly.
But my boss thought it was too
risky and he killed it. Too bad.
Not really. Publisher fired
him and I got his job.
.
I like the way you guys think. You
got the instincts for this field.
Do you wanna do a little snooping
around and see what you can dig up?
What about the truth.
Exactly?
Oh, I, uh, almost forgot.
I found this picture.
The rag mag. What can
you tell me about it?
It's just me. At the new Denver airport.
We threw party and kick
up the swimsuit calendar.
Is that the night Alexa died?
Yeah.
I called her from the hotel. She had
just gotten a new Tama perfume campaign.
But I told you all of this. I got home
two hours after they found the body.
You know, you almost
sound suspicious of me.
Excuse me. You know you really shouldn't
be here. Oh, . Yeah. Um,
I, uh, you're right in.
The middle of a major girlfriend.
Let's try. You go outside and do.
Your guy thing. Oh, come on.
They're professionals. They don't.
Care. I do.
There by the.
Is.
I thought you were watching her.
I was. I wasn't watching the mirror.
He got within 20 feet of her.
It got busy back here. I'm sorry.
Maybe I can get some prints.
Hey, take me home. Yeah, yeah. Come on.
Sorry sister.
When she's not reading
ta cards on the beach.
Destiny likes to help out in the office.
It sure would be nice if she
came with a set of instructions.
Ever look at something now You
should be able to figure it out.
You just can't drive you absolutely nuts.
Yeah, I checkbook. Huh? It's
got a real negative aura.
.
Your contracts.
You figured this mess out.
It's not a mess. It's in perfect
numerological harmony. See,
every letter has a number and you
add them up. And contract is a four.
The rest of the fours are filed under f.
C is under F? Yeah. Oh. Where
would you look for a hammer.
In hardware store?
No, no. , I mean filing.
You know Numerologically speaking?
Oh, um, Hammer. D.
D Oh, uh uh. What's wrong?
The telephone. It's haunted.
What are you doing?
We're skiing away the evil papers.
Oh. Hello? Buchanan. L being McBride.
Oh sure. Cool. It's Gardner. How'd.
You do that? Hey buddy. Justin.
Oh, Butthead. How beg your pardon? The
password for the computer. You know,
what's the password? Butthead.
It's butthead. Kind of cute. Huh?
What's wrong? Uh, yeah, I
can come over early Howard.
Be there half hour.
Oh great. All I got.
Is women who sleep with their son's,
girlfriend's, father's all operates.
A repeat or try watching her all though.
I'm no good at math. Help me. Uh.
Add something up here.
Sure.
One. I dusted it.
There are no suspicious fingerprints
and it's not in his own handwriting.
He doesn't want to get caught.
.
I talked to some shrinks
and obsessive stalkers.
Usually want their victims to know who
they are. Like how much they adore them.
Two. Do you find it odd
that Goe has his little Ted,
Ted with her, like right in
front of your lifeguard tower?
Yeah. I asked her the same thing.
She told me she'd been filming up and
down the beach all week and that she was
easy to find.
Okay. Three.
She got very bad reviews from her
buddies backstage at the fashion show.
Jealousy.
Maybe, maybe not.
Did you know that she lost
a Tamar perfume campaign?
Because she has a drinking problem.
Ryan, these are all very good questions,
but so far Cassidy has very good answers.
Okay? For and foremost, I saw
you kissing a client. .
Oh.
God. Hey, it's wrong to get involved.
Is that what this is all about?
I mean, come on. It was a moment.
She was needy. She was scared. I was
hired. We were hired to protect her.
Oh.
What is that? Is it, what
is that testosterone.
I
search for
No.
Cassidy. What?
We gotta talk. We will later.
No, no, wait, wait, wait.
This whole thing is happening
way too fast. I wanted to,
Who was that?
Um.
Yeah.
Okay.
Should you call the police or something?
Yeah.
It's okay now. Huh? It's over.
Yes. I'd like to report a death.
I got halfway to the plate before I
realized I misread the sign I got tagged
out at home. Even if you only miss
by half a step, you'll still miss.
But I still had one more bat. I.
Know when you came to the precinct
and showed us the letters,
I thought it was some per
getting his sick kicks.
Who was he.
Not carrying any id, But we'll find out.
She saved your life tonight and
a bad guy's outta yours forever.
Everybody was lucky tonight except Tim.
Oh god, it's over.
Well, I guess you won't be needing
your bodyguard anymore, huh?
I guess I want
What's wrong? What's the matter?
It's been a hell of a
night, huh? Look, I, uh,
I think I'm gonna take off.
I'll see you soon, Mitch.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Hey, we heard on the radio. That
was a close one. You okay? Yeah.
You were right.
No, you have to narrow that down.
I usually am. Okay, come on.
I'm sorry. Hey, listen, it
all worked out for the best.
No. No it didn't.
And when I'm working as a lifeguard,
I know the ocean. I know the sand.
I know the people. I know what kind of
trouble they're gonna get into. Man.
I gotta learn to trust my instincts.
I'll being a private investigator,
I saw it coming. Check these out.
The stalker took these when she was
asleep. Each one's a little different.
The blankets have moved
the pillows in a new spot.
So what are you saying?
She took them herself
with an automatic timer.
Everything got moved when she climbed
back in the bed for the next picture.
The letters.
She made him herself and I bought it.
It'd be so hard on yourself. You weren't
the only one who dropped the ball.
Dropped the ball, Huh? Man's
dead. If I've been sharper,
he might still be alive.
You're not gonna do something stupid.
Nope. Been there, done
that. Watch some help. Nope.
This one's mine.
Huh?
Mitch, you scared me.
Haven't even started yet.
Had you know that I was here.
I followed you. He took his wallet.
So you knew where he lived, huh? Hmm.
Gotta be in here somewhere.
What? Oh, you know.
What.
Photographs of you pushing
Alexa off the cliff.
Are you crazy? I was in
Denver when she died.
I can prove it.
Oh, you don't have to. I have a
picture of you at the airport.
I didn't land in LA until two hours
after they found the body. Uh.
Uh. That's when you were supposed
to land. Remember? You know Cassidy,
Something about this picture
kept up me look real close.
There's a clock on the wall.
You were at the airport five hours before
your plane was scheduled to take off.
You must have had a lot
of bags to check. Huh?
I had to ticket on the nine 15.
Flight. You didn't use it.
I checked with the airport.
You took an earlier flight. You
were home hours before Alexa died.
Look.
I really don't wanna talk about Alexa.
No, I know. And I know why.
When I was out by the pool, you went
inside. You took your cell phone.
So I wouldn't notice you called
him, said something like,
You in I'll pay you the money. I want
the photographs and the negatives.
Come over tonight. Leave the
alarm off in the door unlocked.
I didn't do any of that. Mitch. I swear.
This is your cell phone.
I'm gonna press redial.
Yeah, it's grim. I'm gone.
Leave a message grim .
He has a name. You know,
I couldn't figure out why you would go
through a dead man's pockets unless you
were hoping to find something
before the police did like his id.
What are you.
Trying to, You killed Alexa
Crimes was a SLE ball.
But he wasn't stalking you. He
was just blackmailing you. Me,
I'm the sucker. You hired for an alibi.
Sorry. Cause I really
had a good time with you.
You won't shoot me.
I'm not going to prison. I've
already killed two people.
What makes you think
I'm not gonna kill you?
Failure is not in my vocabulary.
But as I sat in nights
feeling sorry for myself,
I realized that my first case is a pi
was about as successful as my first day
as a lifeguard. I had a lot to learn.
At least Cassidy wouldn't be doing
any photo sessions for a while,
but a man named Grimes might still be
alive if I had trusted my instincts.
From.
The funeral. Our first We Money.
Oh, it's a beautiful thing.
A telephone bill from the phone company.
Do you know what it cost to call Calcutta?
Oh. How did Raja Andre's
family take the news?
Not well. Can't blame him when they
took it a lot better than the, uh,
t whistles are going to.
They cremate in Calcutta.
Oh.
And he is being FedExed
home in an envelope.
Who gets to make that phone call?
Uh, wait a minute. Uh, wait.
A minute. Hey, hey, wait a minute guys.
And then you, I in my garden
and you went straight for my erritory.
It.
Can blow your dreams.
There's.
A, you got.
You.
Can.
In the.
Sirens,
Devil.
You.
Can hear.