[Music]
in the City of Angels under cover of
night people are drowned in a sea of
light
[Music]
in your life um
in Devon : rainbow time
[Music]
[Applause]
very slowly
[Music]
[Applause]
in this yeah but you miss your firing
mark by five feet outlet point banned
everything keys on me you mr. Jeff you
will fire it's kind of hard to do when
you're in midair
he's right dear you missed your mark
keep your mouth shut there's no place
for a woman on this job enough
that was sloppy
very very slowly it would go smoother if
you wouldn't have this green kid I'm
sorry sir but he sorry sorry gets us all
killed on payday
you spoil one more rehearsal in your
outdoor set clear yeah but he
[Music]
there are nine seconds off the mark you
have got to be over that fence in under
one minute so when you're gonna tell us
what our target is when you need to know
hundred thousand dollars a piece should
purchase a little patience they're all
supposed to be the best things and
frankly I haven't seen it again
this time with the lights out so you
better be shot
[Music]
what's the deal huh we've been over 40
minutes well I'm sure she's a very busy
woman an empire like sander in cosmetics
is it run by itself but she's the one
who said today in the shop I mean yeah
yeah bad things are doing stand around
name one Oh Evelyn that is definitely
one
hello I'm sorry to keep you waiting
hello there I'm Ryan MacGregor Khan the
phone uh-huh these are my associates
Gartner Ellerbe how do you do my other
partner Mitch Buchannon hello hello sit
down sit down so what can we do for you
you can help me get my son back how long
has he been missing
oh he's not missing he's lost and I
really don't know what to do this is
Todd his father died when Todd was seven
and I was just starting my business back
then so a typical story I guess I was
just too busy to spend a lot of time
with him he he went to several private
schools got kicked out of a couple of
them uh he tried college and that didn't
seem to work out I'm afraid he's heading
for trouble again again yo he sad does
some trouble with the law what kind of
trouble Oh
minor infractions really drunk driving
when he was 14 uh armed robbery when he
was 17 mrs. Sandrine armed robbery is
hardly a minor infraction oh it wasn't
his fault oh no no no he just was
hanging out with the wrong crowd my
lawyers got him off with probation mrs.
Andry what exactly is it that you want
us to do for you I want you to find out
what Todd is into now and what's wrong
with him
what he needs to get his life back on
track when was the last time you saw
your son this morning 3:00 a.m. he had
some bruises I could get in a fight who
knows he wouldn't talk to me about it
but then we don't talk that much
anymore why us your agency is on the
beach and Tod spends most of his time
there you have to know your competition
to win and I want to win my son back
[Music]
I'll pay you double your going rates we
have an agreement that's fine
keep in touch
[Music]
we haven't met I'm s we're not going to
a double the raid who cares
there's an expression throwing money at
a problem I understand it I'll just
probably never be able to afford it I
think Francis Sandrine has a very tired
arm first the gym and sail boarding at a
massage and manicure with his buds the
young club tough day was he going next
to get his role that's Paulo's weird
little cranky today or that kid doesn't
have a silver spoon he's got a silver
shovel and on a sugar Carter tell me how
you really feel Mitch I had a pallet the
department run a check that war should
have done hard time for that armed
robbery when his mother's high-priced
lawyers got him a get out of jail card
same with a drunk driving beef and a few
other bus she conveniently forgot to
mention that kid is a knucklehead and
he's finding himself maybe just deep
little time yeah he needs a little time
about a year in the county jail
[Music]
here comes
interesting Rupa
[Music]
looks like he's slumming shall we
[Applause]
[Music]
think you can make it I can see I can't
[Applause]
[Music]
what the hell was that I don't know but
it hurts my knees just to watch
you know everyone in that group look
like world-class skaters to me
oh the term is inline skaters and what a
lot the point is there must have been in
some kind of competition in their lives
so forth so if there was an event to see
somebody be sober tickets
somebody's taking action I hope you bet
on inline skating
are you kidding people bet on which
pigeon poops first what we need is a guy
who takes a connection a sports promoter
a bookie bath pebble drunken pebbles run
Kim yeah Paul his son I love a riptide a
couple years ago he thinks he owes me
trying to pick up Todd again and to
stick to him like yeah and I will talk
to peppers
in any business who you know sometimes
makes the difference between success and
failure it's pretty much the same in the
p.i business with one exception the who
love who you know tend to be how should
I put colourful take a look at this
anybody in here leap out at you oh god
she's still gorgeous who is she
haha Margo vanda's oddly freestyle champ
still in time no no no that was three
years ago she got arrested for trying to
rough up her nearest competitor bank
scandal in Sweden no no I never did know
what happened to her I was like she made
bail about him
Oh Pancho Dawson two time national
inline skate Series champ
yeah but from competition because of
reoccurring knows can't be I sense a
developing better next I can't believe
it what are all these people doing the
one place good question who is he Dena
Dena actor Dunkeld dieter country yeah
disqualified from the Nationals last
year
why tested positive for steroids for
openers Danny beat the hell out of the
doctor
best I heard he was still on the lam
what about him uh Sandrine local
up-and-coming any good look at her like
this if you could buy him for what he's
worried and sell him for what he thinks
she's worth you could retire what I
don't know something isn't right here
don't jump us what everything no no no
nothing for me uh I'm in training Helia
no relish about them so Mitch yeah how's
the gumshoe business story okay
why it's three to five on a street your
agency's going down a torch
do yourself a favor pal don't look it
thanks Ben
but that's a [ __ ] come on load them up
will you feed me
[Music]
how'd it go with pebbles well he gave me
some names to go along with the faces
not a nice group what are you doing you
supposed to be dog in time no you just
shoot off at the country club uh picking
up in about three hours let me tell you
something this kid is headed for the
biggest trouble in his life just can't
sit around here and wait for it to
happen huh we got stuck coming at him
from all angles well what kind of angles
you have in mind
for openers yours
[Music]
all right I got five sixes all it is one
sorry need to quit a winner see you guys
tomorrow
oh thank you very much for the
contribution oh oh ding sorry you're
you're Todd Sandrine yeah thank God I
finally met you yeah definitely thank
God I'm a major fan well I saw you take
third at the pro roller blading
championship last month
oh thanks you're fantastic I thought I
should have one oh definitely judges
were blind that tweaked invert fakie you
did was unbelievable really
what'd you say your name was oh I'm Lila
Claire you ever need a president for
your fan club I'm I'm applying for the
job fan club yeah you you don't have a
fan club no oh we gotta talk
ouch not even happy here yeah and then
she was really pissed when I dropped out
of college I mean she had fixed the
whole cheating scandal at the Board of
Regents but you know I just wasn't into
it it was like too regimented you know
there there was no challenge yeah yeah I
know what you mean you know and then my
mom wanted me to learn the cosmetics
business I mean what a joke who wants to
devote their life in a tricking old bags
into thinking they could look young
again yeah I know what you mean yeah the
the blading things okay right but my
next year I'll be champion and then what
you know I've I've raced cars I've raced
boats you know what it it all just gets
a little bit stale after a while so what
do you get free excitement I mean what's
next well actually I'm involved in
something that is a real challenge and I
mean big-time
Hey I gotta go okay
you can't go um you haven't heard all my
ideas for the fan club yet yeah I know
look um uh me me here tomorrow okay save
time but time
[Music]
you're not good enough to blow up a
half-hour practice beach boy
and go to hell man
hmm beginning on the restless well I
guess that settles that about him
[Music]
whoever the gray-haired guy is the work
boss comes to mind
whatever the show is looks like he's
running it and he kept not to laugh the
dark Todd went to straight home after
that where is he now at standing massage
appointment after they work out I can
see why you needed it I'll pick you up
in about an hour his face part was when
he saw the boss man I'm at 87 we never
should have taken this job but kids
headed for a big fall yep and we are as
safety net no boy
[Music]
what's going on here you're just rolling
around the pier in the middle of the
afternoon when my son has been injured
I'm just saying please please have a
seat
did Todd say how it happened he took a
spill on his blades well he lied to your
mother it all has to do with some gang
of kids hanging out with gang yeah yeah
he's in way over his head
Todd wouldn't join a gang he's a little
wild he's not a bad boy
now mrs. Sandra he's a very very bad boy
you know what we ought to turn him in
right now for his own good
this is what I pay you for
mrs. Sandrine we searched his car his
glove box is full of unpaid parking
tickets there's probably a warrant out
for his arrest right now look all we
need to do is talk to his probation
officer
maybe scare him a little bit that'll get
him off the streets and keep him out of
harm's way he'd go to jail yes ma'am
he'd go to jail the best thing that
happened to him look if my son's in
trouble no there's no other badet he is
in trouble
hey you just get him out of it or look
at some little can well I'll tell you
what garner hey hey
I think we are telling to take this job
and come on you guys we promised this
woman we can find out what her kid was
into what's missing in his life what do
you need to get back on track okay okay
so what's our next move we gotta get
tons of tension Ryan already took the
first step
yeah I got a date with him in an hour
good I'll take that date do you
absolutely by his new probation officer
and she's got a zillion ideas posters
write videos autographed sports cards
going international with the fan club I
mean I can't wait till you guys meet her
this is one wrap mark haggerty's my pee
Oh mark a Gertie is on permanent stress
leave you'll go into the tank for 72
hours 72 hours outstanding parking
warrants hey my mom Bart and Ernie a new
car
he's supposed to take care of things
like this really I'll make a note of
that hey I'd like to speak to my mom's
employer sorry pal your mommy's not
gonna buy you out of this one let's go
bye-bye
I don't grand a week what are you
smoking I can give you 2,000 right now
what are you doing you offering me a
bribe
look I have a long-standing engagement
tomorrow okay I can't break what
engagement is that I'm first violin la
Phil Harvey I you know what if you can
make it two maybe you could make it
fine how about ten
mommy doesn't like me to travel around
help pocket change on a scale of 1 to 10
this is definitely a 10 $10,000 and we
can't even afford a new lamp
there's supposed to scare him not shake
him down yeah whatever's going down is
going down tomorrow you take your finger
off you get taped to my finger to the
land oh sorry
hey guys you know by chance mention the
names Maxie's in zipper grande Oh
Sheriff or Robin Kemp to you did he know
who are they well they're all the same
man i fax this my old mentor in New York
and he sent it to Interpol they came
back with several hits
does the name Scarborough mean anything
to you come on you guys I'm serious
the Scarborough robbery three years ago
in The Hague remember diamonds that's
the one says here they hid on
snowmobiles and made off with the crown
jewels then there was the gold shipment
stolen from the Italian Treasury in
Venice they got away on jet skis
unfortunately several members of that
team weren't spendable can't got away
clean so we got here snowmobiles jet
skis one-of-a-kind crimes each with a
different mo each with a high body count
among the robbers ha ha each time Kemp
gets away says here he's number two on
Interpol's list of the ten most wanted
what Sandrine could just be another
sacrificial lamb and whether you like
him or not we can't just let him go out
there and buy the ranch it's by the farm
but we know what you mean
what's this Robin Kim pup do now we
don't know whatever it is it's big and
it's going down tomorrow my movie there
and I
three small packages be carried from the
car for the stairway leading down into
the building and that is the only time
that we're going to have an opportunity
to strike you're going to hit the
Treasury Department really then have
some $20 plates so as you can see timing
is everything
sorry I'm late
you all have your individual assignments
once DITA blows the gate you to go to
your designated pickup points in the van
would collect you are there any
questions
suit up mr. Kemp
this guy's gonna screw us up bad
after the hid get him
mrs. Sandrine was $10,000 there I can't
believe it he actually tried to bribe
someone he thought was his probation
officer I wonder where he gets that you
did buy his probation officer a new car
didn't you
I just wanted to be sure Todd was
treated fairly you know what the problem
with Todd is you me yeah you you bail
him out of everything the kid has no
idea how to go through life without a
mother bailing amount of problems isn't
that why you hired us to make sure if
the kid gets in trouble were there to
fix it I just want to know what's
missing in his life so I can provide it
he's looking for a challenge and he
never gets one now he's involved with an
international group of armed robbers I
don't believe that I think you're wrong
no no no no that's what you want to
think I'm going back to work I told you
the boys are knuckle in his mother's
been buying a lot of toys left I think
she's a good mom she just started 15
years too late if brains were loving
that boy couldn't sell a flea
[Music]
you know being a p.i isn't like the
movies where the good guy always has the
right answer I understood that we would
make mistakes and learn from them what I
didn't count on were the mistakes that
make you cringe who stopping
[Music]
gracious what's that if that's tied I
got a problem
excuse me who are you who are you FBI
CIA FBI and CIA
what are you doing driving sanguines car
he gave me $100 to drive it around town
charge up the battery a little so I
thought I'd do a little shopping where's
Todd I don't know am I in trouble or
well not exactly but
[Music]
Aaron go for
what what I'm not crazy that's what
let's try to do
[Applause]
beautiful day late dollar short
hey hey hey hey hey
so this is what they're up to what let's
see
fifth what's that James James Jamerson
fifth and Jamison well wait a minute
we're fifth and Jamison fifth Treasury
Department
[Music]
I listen up it's two minutes away now
pickup points
[Music]
[Applause]
where
I profit
[Music]
that goes in the LA River that we're
gonna practice in the other day but
we'll never catch them on foot
we can't on that so who are we FBI Oh No
CIA FBI
we need your bike wait a minute who that
will you you telling CIA man you stand
back or you face imprisonment okay okay
and call the cops
[Music]
[Applause]
let's never get on the right all right
coming up
[Music]
when arrest
[Applause]
[Music]
that's close call me let's go out of
here
[Music]
I thought John Wayne
in the box
[Applause]
the jobs over beach boy
so are you
[Music]
Thanks welcome
hey your escort services
[Music]
pack it now
[Applause]
[Music]
well I'd say he came away pretty lucky
yeah ended up with a two-year suspended
sentence with one hitch yeah a hitch in
the Marine Corps yeah do you good [ __ ]
man I think you're right I hope so
listen this might sound weird but thanks
thanks for busting me
best of luck down there hey super fine
[Music]
hey you just might make it I tell you
something that I cannot stop thinking
about those brand-new crisp $20 bills we
wouldn't you just love the Royals
Treasury Department pretty blank I love
it Swami right about now
which reminds me you owe me 20 I paid
you back when this morning left it on
your desk that didn't give it yeah I
know I did
hey you owed me 20 now we're even don't
forget you owed me 20 oh I did what you
paid me back no I forgot all right let's
see that'll be seventeen fifty or an
even 20 if you're a compassionate tipper
don't look at me don't even think about
me
Semper Fi Mac
thanks Mitch anger the other word you
got nothing but anger
[Music]
get him now
there's a place
[Music]
watch
[Applause]
[Music]