[Music]
[Applause]
Hey hi there you don hi no you good good
I uh wish I could join you but uh won't
do well I'm not so see ya you uh wearing
protection yeah don't worry I'm a
practicing safe son okay uh you know
beginners can really cook out here
well I'm no beginner no you're not
see ya bye
come on turn around come on give me one
look
thank you
yeah
hey guys blackball today no surfing
sorry
[Music]
I'm sorry you can't what do you want
I'm gonna kill myself what wait um
what's your name doesn't matter matters
to me I'm Caroline
Garth stupid huh no no I like it it's
very original you don't you don't meet
too many cards you know you Garth Brooks
why do you want to kill yourself or are
you in trouble
are you sad did somebody hurt you yeah
I'm sorry
what
what does that mean it just means I'm
sorry that you're hurt yeah oh god no
please wait done um it's not worth it
okay what whatever you're doing for it's
not worth it whoever did it to you
they're not worth it Garth you're young
you have your whole life ahead of you
you you can do things your life will get
better I promise you'll be happy again
you don't know anything about it you
don't know anything I know that I don't
want you to kill yourself I don't want
you to die
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
I won't kill myself
I'll kill you
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
in the City of Angels under cover of
night
people don't drown in a sea of light
[Music]
the devil's holding your life um
angel : rayon for time
something's gotta give
[Applause]
or is too late
get for it
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
you're very pretty thank you
so then why kill me you wouldn't
understand
you know you're the first girl I ever
met named Caroline
[Music]
[Applause]
new Intel right do me a favor new me
Caroline's phone is off the hook can
check around yeah hold on a second
yeah it looks like she's got a friend
there with her she must have knocked it
off by accident I'll walk down and check
it out thanks new me
[Music]
excuse me
sorry to bother you but I forgot her
sunblock would you have any I could
borrow yeah yeah sure come on
[Music]
never saved anybody's life
I mean you're a lifeguard so I figure
yes would you ever get like a a medal or
something for doing it
[Music]
card I know I know you really don't want
to hurt me
if I ask you a question would you answer
me truthfully Caroline
all right
yes
am i homely or just plain there was a
big argument over which one a long time
ago
[Music]
I want to know what you think I value
your opinion
yay I'm sorry I really am
I hate him with people raise their voice
don't you so tell me what do you think
which one
[Music]
[Applause]
I think they very nice-looking guy
[Music]
really thank you
when you ever
kiss me
[Music]
[Laughter]
dispatch this is tirade there's a crazy
guy chasing Carolyn and she's got a gun
on me he's crazy you try to commit
suicide and I tried to stop him in
anything he was gonna kill me Oh
headquarters
kill me please
easy easy alright go st. vigeous
ASAP
[Music]
see you two get fired up huh you got to
meet you
anybody see what happened lay man sorry
anybody anything
no oh thanks excuse me yeah uh I don't
know exactly
I saw a suspicious-looking guy I mean
there was just something about him I
don't know just weird
and I saw him running down the beach ah
what's going on Mitch Harvick is the guy
took out Louie he's got blood on his car
he's gonna cut us here I don't know what
he's talking about hey take it easy will
ya
taking the headquarters check it out
[Music]
yup that the guy yeah all those nice
things you said about not wanting me to
die your method didn't you go I'll get
him out of here no one's ever said stuff
like that to me before
Carrie I love you I love you
all right now we're gonna take a look at
the proper way to approach a potential
drowning victim okay Chris be the victim
help al Donna what's the procedure
approached the victim heads up so he can
see me offering the can tell him to take
the can what if he doesn't take it then
leave the can and leave the victim
that's exactly right
see if Donna had tried to fight him they
could have gone down they both would
have drowned but we always say never
ever take the victim to the rescue
thanks guys
so when do we get to practice
mouth-to-mouth resuscitation tonight in
your dreams all right see you next week
[Music]
I'm locking up Caroline you got
everything
hey Eddie have you seen anybody messing
with my bag no just your a regular grip
a little munchkins are running amok why
is something missing no nothing thanks
the minute I opened the box I got a
chill yeah well he said he was very very
sorry
who Garth Evan Youngblood
apparently Garth price the attorney
brought in this doctor who claimed none
of this would have ever happened at poor
Garth had only taken his Prozac yeah
listen to this it was an unusual Alpers
caused by the failure to take prescribed
medication highly unlikely to occur
again quote unquote well he's in jail
though right was but he saw me swore
that he'd take his medicine and nothing
like that would ever happen again so
they let him post bail
[Music]
so was him
thank you for taking me home it's just
with CJ and Stephanie out of town a
little nervous so I can understand what
you've been through a box okay it's just
such an invasion you know listen can I
get you some coffee no no I'm gonna get
out of here I you need some rest
Mitch would you stay please
[Music]
[Applause]
hi Carrie
it's Garth I hope you like the necklace
I carry it's me again
Garth will talk to you mr. 12 coughs
Mitch she's called 12 times
all right listen but he's gonna be okay
we'll just change the number tomorrow
it's unlisted
[Music]
he's been in here
all right it's gonna be okay Brian yeah
I asked me look he's been inside her
apartment you're gonna need a
restraining order
yeah we're anywhere all right I'll get
on it all right Thanks
you're not staying here tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
lifeguard lady hi pretty flowers they're
yours what that man said these are for
you
[Music]
tower Kevin is Mitch there
over me
haha but we were never formally
introduced my name is miss Buchanan it's
nice to meet you again Mitch
my name is God I know what your name is
what I don't know is what you think
you're doing here I join the beach
it's beautiful day isn't it she's got a
restraining order against you yes I know
but that was your idea wasn't it Mitch
Court says you can't get within a
hundred yards yeah I know that too
then I respect the law
I forgive me for sounding like a
know-it-all Mitch but you and I are
standing exactly 100 yards away from
Tower seven you can measure if you want
I did
alright get a new phone number new locks
on the door locks on the windows every
lifeguard on the beach knows what's
going on he gets within one inch going
over the 100-yard limit he's busted you
gonna be okay I'm scared
I know I know look the guy is just some
sick coward getting his kicks he'll get
tired I'll go away me a lot of people
behind you who knows your name
nobody Kerry how did he get this number
Mitch tell me you're there are you there
please pick up let's talk this out I
need so desperately to speak to you
she doesn't want to talk to you but I do
my little man-to-man talk over the
telephone it's too impersonal
what do you say we get together where
are you a good try but no look I know
the address you gave to the police is a
phony you checked me out
I'm flattered listen I'll tell you what
I'll get in touch with you tomorrow
eleven o'clock we'll have that talk Oh
Mitch tell Kerry I said sweet dreams
[Music]
Haymitch this was upstairs
10:59 punctuality is both courtesy and
compliment when I was eight years old
somebody made me write that a thousand
times it's a good way to remember
something you know you're scaring the
hell out of her don't you
flowers presents that's affection Mitch
listen
she doesn't want your flowers she
doesn't want your affection she doesn't
want your presence really what does she
want mansion you know no she wants you
to leave her alone and soda why don't
tell me what to do that's done that's
over it is you isn't it do you like her
and you're saying all these things
because you want me out of the picture
you're not even in the picture you
weren't there in her Tower
you didn't hear all the nice things she
said about me I'm just looking
she said that she said that because she
was trying to keep you from killing I
would be an idiot to believe your
version an empty-headed little [ __ ] you
ever hear that expression you ever been
called that I have I don't recommend it
but I see it all now you're jealous of
me
you're afraid of me she saved my life
she loves me she loves me please don't
hit me don't hit me again are you doing
[Music]
mr. Buchanan told me we had to get
together and have a clock that's not my
girlfriend he likes her jealous
everything
why were you hitting him I wasn't
hitting him Sam you know me better than
that the guy was hitting himself he was
beating himself I know it sounds crazy
but the guy's a nutcase
he was a nice guy he just lost control
and love can make you do funny things
officer Mitch I like you always have so
I'm gonna warn you you leave this guy
alone could come down to your word
against his
he could drag your butt right in the
court
[Music]
I told the officer I'm not gonna press
assault battery charges this time but I
strongly suggest you seek some
professional help to control that anger
of yours [ __ ]
I'm willing to forgive and forget
what do you say we done Sam
[Music]
you'll love this I ran his name through
every computer file I could think of and
didn't find anything so I tried the US
Army the army mm-hmm
seems Garth Youngblood is a legacy
lieutenant colonel Garth Evan Youngblood
senior was a big hero in Vietnam he was
a member of the Rangers and also won the
Medal of Honor
what about our boy you serve our country
mm-hmm for a while until they gave him a
section a because he was mentally
unstable that's no surprise huh well I
use my dad's Navy connections in order
to get a meeting with the Army
psychiatrist who just so happens to be
the same one that gave Garth Youngblood
jr. his leave Garth lives in the very
dark and very cold shadow of his
legendary father the Army psychiatrist
figures that it was not random that he
walked into Caroline's Tower that he
spent some time on it and probably hand
Victor
[Music]
[Applause]
Hey are you doing your pictures
yeah we'll stop it I don't like it
you're bothering me
oh really the parolin doesn't like you
bothering her but you don't see
understand
say cheese guard come on say cheese
smile smile that is nice you're gonna
like that in guard what I just can't
figure out what your better side is your
right or your left yeah I get it neither
you know what kind come here a little
closer there we go you know what I think
I'm gonna call these stalking the stuff
we go away whoa they're gone settle down
out here hold on let me get some black
and white I think you look better in
black and white yeah where are you going
get back here oh yeah this refracted
light is great you know it's very
European guard Oh little feisty aren't
we oh that's great yeah
[Applause]
okay guys that was a terrific workout in
our first meet is in two days and the
most important thing to remember about
that is hey that's right okay everyone
go home see you tomorrow bye
[Music]
oh he scared me I'm sorry Caroline I
thought if I said anything I'd scare you
even more so it's okay I heard about
that guy who's bothering you I'll walk
you to your car Thanks
just give me a minute I'll be right out
[Music]
somebody else
[Applause]
sweet dreams Carrie
[Music]
[Laughter]
how do you like your Tower
I built it just for you I can't see you
why are you doing this to me because you
saved my life
if you see all those newspaper articles
and they're all about you saving your
hero I miss this is your medal I don't
wanna go home
you know that don't you you wouldn't
answer
would you ever kiss me
[Music]
no you will you know it's always
different at night
here the seagulls the people on the
beach please what how is that possible
as soon as you find out something you
call me need to find out nothing call me
whatever he's got Caroline what what do
you got anything I just got some
pictures in another president we bought
this candy in San Pedro
the Garcias st. Peter I don't know I
don't know but it's a start
San Pedro is a busy place Mitch it's
gonna be someplace it's isolated uh what
about a house maybe maybe for some place
where he feels safe what did Ryan say
his background was military right uh
yeah his uh dad was an Army Ranger way
man
worth the army ranger station in San
Pedro doing Nam yeah yeah for MacArthur
it's been closed for years it's a long
shot but let's go
[Music]
there's his van
alright you stay here you block the exit
nobody gets past you alright
careful Mitch
[Music]
the enemy is broken through the picket
line sir
[Music]
your line
[Applause]
[Music]
Caroline
Red Alert sir
the enemy has reached our perimeter they
won't get across our line sir
[Applause]
I won't let you down this time dad
[Music]
[Applause]
Caroline
[Music]
your line
y
she's mine
[Music]
[ __ ] Caroline
means hurt get me out of here hold on
let me let me go get something
[Music]
hey you okay yeah where is it it's over
[Applause]
[Music]
open the door carry headquarters
I carry
I hope you like the necklace I'd sure
like to see a real soothe and I was
thinking maybe in sweet dreams here
buddy like it's our Carrie
[Music]
Carrie I love here we'll save my life
you're a hero this is your method would
you ever kiss me Carrie hey Caroline
[Music]
can never work
no no Caroline will ever hurt you again
oh god I know he's dead
[Music]
it just isn't done yet I know
he will be
someday he will be
[Applause]
[Music]
there's a face
you
[Music]
here the fair
[Applause]
[Music]
and the devil is watching every slide
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
to
[Music]
you