In the city,
drown in the sea.
Devil.
Rain for time.
After the.
Okay. Whoa, Ill dignified.
Oh, baby. What's it mean? Turmoil. See,
this is the hang man. Dishonesty.
Some, uh, lies have been told.
Hey, this is all mumbo
jumbles at the beach. Okay.
I'm not all that superstitious.
I'll walk under ladders.
Black cats don't freak me out. But
last night there was a full moon.
It's my opinion that if bad
things are gonna happen,
they're gonna happen during a full moon.
I broke my leg skiing during
a full moon. My wife Gail,
filed for divorce during a
full moon. Ah, the memories
a full moon. And our client, Mrs.
Vander, Kellen wanted to Noah,
her husband was being a wayward boy.
The old playing her with wine routine.
Okay.
. Wow. What's he doing?
Warm enough?
Here comes the.
Pitch.
What, what.
Range? Rota. But that's one big rock.
Uhhuh. Huh?
See a tower big with three,
three peaks empty.
A chimney at my house. It's
incredible. How'd you know?
Well,
the tower card and the
chariot card has one to three
easy little peaks. Cosmic combo.
I'm.
Okay. We gotta hear what
old bad boy Burt saying.
So how do we get this over there?
Yeah. Getting ready to fetch. Boy.
. All alright. Come on.
Right.
Ah, excuse me. Excuse me.
Oh, excuse me. I'm so sorry.
We're not very good at this. I'm
sorry. Excuse me. Go ahead. Excuse me.
Wow. Victoria, that is a beautiful ring.
Thank you very Watch Destiny. Wow.
Let's see. Ace of Cups, the lover's card.
I see a new man in.
Your life. A handsome la Ladia.
Hope deity. Oh, to die for
Uhoh.
Your Or just hiccuped
something wrong. Well.
I cannot shake the feeling
something bad's gonna happen.
Yeah.
I can feel that. You know what? You
should go see my friend Mitch Buchanan.
He's a private investigator. He
could quiet your karma. Thanks.
Oh, baby, I just love this necklace.
You mean the looks so beautiful.
Good contact.
Oh, baby.
A hang man.
And the 10 of swords.
What?
It's bad news.
Death. Someone close to you.
Excuse me. Would I find
a Buchanan? Upstairs?
Actually, you find him right here.
A Mitch, What can I do for you?
Well, um.
It's a little embarrassing.
Get outta.
Here.
For me.
You shouldn't have.
Oh baby.
For you we're private. Invest. You're, uh.
What? I Yes, wife.
Yeah, Mom, about you were cheating
on her and stealing her jewelry.
Nice necklace.
Taping.
This.
Well, you've been a very bad Ooh
baby. That is your name, isn't it?
Why?
Yeah.
I.
Time out. Huh? Time out.
Okay, time in.
How much does he want for this?
Hundred bucks.
Do you think it's.
Worth it?
I don't know in bad shape.
Why don't you buy a car? I.
Don't wanna drive. Mitch.
Like harmony.
With nature.
Carbon.
Monoxide makes Mother earth cough.
Bugs are four. Hey. Yeah.
What happened to my friend Victoria?
I told her, wait, but soon as I
got back she was gone. She split.
Huh?
Um.
Tell me, hang on, tell me. Hang on.
Grab my, come on, come on.
That's come on.
Frigo kid.
They're live and.
Hey, hey.
We have yet to get any
official sheriff's department.
What's the deal? She's okay.
Crew.
Bug you. Pardon? Crew right's.
A vegetable. That's old.
Crap. Eck crew is an offwhite
color a stately. Powerful.
Yet.
Graceful color.
Stately. Powerful. Yeah.
Yeah. Grace. Graceful.
It's a good professional
color. Don't you think? It's.
So female.
Sorry. I went with my instincts. What
would be a good male color? Blue.
Black.
Black and blue. Great.
Our office will look
like a furnished bruise.
Er was named a client friendly color
and nine out of 10 designer oriented
surveys.
Nine outta.
10.
Black and blue.
The nightmare.
Exactly. You like that.
Group in a salad? It's like Aveta
myth, which just happened on my bike.
You know, it was just like cart's
nightmare. And the forest of the screams.
Remember?
Uhuh.
Uhuh. Well.
He saw the world through the
eyes of the predator, right?
Excuse me.
That's what I did.
Story.
I don't know.
Heidi, what do you have in the.
Face? Death. The.
Body was discovered by a
jogger just a short time ago.
The coroner's office has initially listed
the cause of death as strangulation.
The victim,
Victoria Magruder had recently moved to
the Venice Beach area from her Native
Scotland.
I saw her strangled through his eyes.
You saw who strang.
Her? The princess of the shining flame.
Remember that, right? Had I sent you.
Yesterday?
Yeah. Well, I read her TA cards and,
and she got the Ace of Cups and
the Lovers card, and I told her,
You're gonna meet a man to die for.
Guess.
It was right.
Destiny says she saw the
lady from Scotland strangled.
She wasn't physically there.
She was psychically there. Okay.
It's weird, but who knows? I mean, there
are some things we just can't explain.
Hope we got an a, a in algebra.
Nobody can explain that. Anyway,
I was headed for the coroner's
office and they were.
Re chasing the roots. Why.
Goi? Oh, come on. Tell me.
You know about Gari? Well.
Sure.
Gari, uh, a nice color shade darker than.
He's on a color. He was a killer.
Direct was a guy back in Vermont,
killed a full 10 year
old girl in the forties.
Her best friend saw the whole
thing. So intense for mine.
Totally blocked it out. So you're like
20 years uhhuh. 20 years to recall it.
For press memory.
Sally, just your.
Rafael, Sally, Jesse
had repressed, remember?
No.
She did a show about people.
Who did? I didn't see.
That one. I have it on tape. Oh my God.
Why did I leave New York? All right,
listen, this woman, you write her
terra cards a lot of times, right? Huh?
All right. She told you a lot
of things about her life. Yeah.
She told me about Scotland and she told
me about her grandmother's diamond ring.
Oh, um, he took it, by the way. Killer.
There.
Well, there's your Scotland,
your princess with a
diamond on top of her head.
Your romance to die
for and your strangler.
The hangman's news.
What, what are you saying? The destiny
bottled up her memories about this woman.
Then the cork popped and she
imagines she saw a strangle.
If the metaphor fits, wear it.
Because she's your mom. That's why hoby,
it won't kill you. Now, don't,
don't, don't, don't do that. Ow.
Call waiting is not a
good thing. By the way,
Destiny was right about the diamond ring.
Speculation. No.
No, no. I talked to the corner
and they found marks on a ring.
Finger marks could have been
made by a ring being yanked. Oh.
Could have, could have been nicked
slicing carrots. Look, Mitch,
I like destiny. It's hard not to,
but you gotta admit the girl
is a little sp at at times.
She's harmless.
You got the hots for her.
Hey, . But you got a bigger
name on the other line. Ooh,
Kelsey. Huh?
Well, look who's here.
Who baby? What do you want?
I just wanted you to know that
since you medaled in my life,
the former miss is wonderful
is throw me out of the house,
cut off my allowance and
filed for divorce. Well,
you were a bad boy cooking. Yeah.
Well, don't be surprised if I get.
Money.
You see any money? The, uh, lottery edit.
I see loneliness.
Me. Wrong guy. Never lonely.
I've got the job of my
dreams. I've got my cat.
I've got cable. Okay. A little bit.
Ooh. But I also see.
A new love life.
Oh, terrific. Uh, try to
see, we about five, seven,
that short little haircut and,
uh, whole eggs . Yeah.
What's the matter.
Burner? Do you believe.
Me? What about her?
No. Uh, about the murder I saw.
Well, I know. I figure,
uh, if I believe one,
I gotta believe the
other in, you know what?
I sure could use a new love life.
No. No.
What what is it? Don't,
She's saying something
again, Mitch. Whatever it is,
it's scaring the hell out of.
What? Talk to me. What do you see?
It's the man, the king of Why? Who's that?
I read a serial card. No, negative.
He's a really bad danger. Where is he?
I see water and canal and breaches.
That's Venice Beach. Come on. Come
on, come on. Let's go. Come on now.
Keep talking. Just describe it. It's.
Okay. It's a house, like a, like kids,
like gle, like a gingerbread house.
And it has melty windows and,
and a tower with three feet. I.
Think I know the house.
I don't know. I don't.
It's okay. Look at me. Look at me. I
promise you nothing will happen to you.
Now. Come on. Come on.
In. Let's go. Let's.
It's.
I don't want to, I know
he's in there. It's.
The glass door. Call the paramedics.
He's not breathing. Yeah. How many of
the paramedics at 4 0 1 Dell Street,
please.
3, 4, 5, 3, 4, 5.
1, 2, 3, 4.
I'll check.
Would've.
Been our first anniversary
come November 8th or ninth.
But I get confused.
Tony was my fourth husband.
He was my stepfather.
I'm li ad I I tried to fight the
guy off, but, but he was huge.
You're strong. He was
choking me big time and I,
I couldn't breathe. Why do you think
he broke in, sir? I don't know. Maybe.
Maybe. He thought we had money
in the house or something. Uhhuh.
And I see through the killer's
eyes. What do you mean, man?
I saw him strangled.
Could we finish this letter?
Sure. Thanks.
I don't wanna do it. Watch it ever again.
Don't ask me. Okay.
It's over, huh?
The Muscle Beach type. You know,
tattoo ponytail, the gnarly beard.
Hi, Destiny. I guess you were right.
Someone close to me did die.
Looking for you.
Hi.
You okay?
Yeah. Just, uh, spring
cleaning my aura. You know,
I've been thinking a lot
about what Lion said.
Yeah, me too.
I mean,
storing away memories of people then
letting my imagination trick me.
It's weird, but I guess it could happen.
What I don't get is how did I know there
was gonna be a murder before there was
a murder?
Destiny heard about these
tests. They do in Russia.
I put one person in one room and
another person in another room.
One person can tell with
the other person is doing.
Saying and thinking. It's called.
Uh, Empathics.
Right? Empathics. You
can do that, can't you?
Destiny? That's a gift.
Like a curse. It's just so
confusing. You know? I just,
I've decided to keep my
brain empty of all Fox.
Well, if anyone can do that, you can.
A cup of coffee.
She's.
So scared. She won't read cards anymore.
Well, then she can read the
bumps on people's heads.
You're not got an idea. I don't
think I want to hear it. I.
Think we should hire Destiny.
I knew I didn't want to hear
it. No, I'm not kidding.
Her. No. She figured out the files.
She exercised the phone system. She.
Can cook. Which tofu isn't
food. It's a fungus mean.
Come on. I like the girl, but
work with her for my dead body.
Thank you.
No, You know what? I'm sorry. She's
a nice girl. I feel bad for her.
She's going through a lot of hell right
now. I wouldn't wanna be in her shoes.
Hey, found this. Sitting at the bar.
Somebody's got a secret admirer.
Secret Admirer, huh?
Yeah. Card says Destiny.
Oh God. Hers, the princess
of the Shining flame.
Who's.
Victoria? The, the
redhead who died. Oh God.
He was here.
Well, still is.
Let's go. I on the, Wait a minute.
We know a guy who steals jewelry from
women and gives it to other women.
Ooh.
Baby. Absolutely.
Well, only the killer could have
the Ring and Destiny could be his.
Next target. And we don't take
our eyes off. Destiny 24 7.
Okay, wait a minute, y'all, I mean,
let's listen to the description here.
Muscle Beach type, blonde hair
long. That's not, Ooh, baby.
Well, maybe he wore disguise or something.
Nobody wears disguises.
Since Ryan was busy tailing.
Ooh, baby. Burt around town.
It was up to me and Garner
to watch over. Destiny.
The key to surveillance is the
ability to blend in your surroundings.
If the obstacle is now this card, well,
it represents danger. So you might
wanna take up to new extra precautions.
Be a little more careful. The, if the,
It's, uh.
Understand.
Mines don't talk. Oh.
Let me tell you. See the eyes.
That blue is the where? The
color gold. What your teeth bud?
What your teeth. What your teeth.
Papa Mama. What? Your teeth?
Your hair. Straight. Hey, he's about.
Six, two big old belly orangey
kind of hair spiked out.
Like he stuck his finger in a socket.
You've seen him? No.
Give to
you.
Okay.
Wrong guy.
Forget.
Fool.
Bad things.
Was in the office looking for me.
Maybe.
The connection isn't with the victims.
Destiny made me the
connections with the killer.
Maybe
all I know is that I keep seeing people
getting killed and that I might be
next. I don't wanna talk about it anymore.
I'm.
So.
I promise you, we're gonna
catch this guy. Okay?
Yes. Divorce is painful,
but you'll heal in time.
.
So you got to keep this house and
the desert condo and the settlement.
That's.
Uh.
Very nice.
.
Yeah.
No.
What do you see?
Oh.
It's.
Too intense. He's draining
all my energy. Oh, car.
He's gonna kill again.
Who, who's he gonna kill?
Oh.
Brian.
Talk to me. Where is she? Where is she?
No, I don't want, He
said I didn't have to.
We're talking about Ryan here.
Look at me. I know you're scared,
but he's going to kill her and you
can help her. Now where is she?
I not sure. Um,
beautiful houses and it's, Oh.
Ah.
Could you call me? You're
here. No. On your cell phone.
The killer is going after
Ryan. Man, get your car.
I'll get in my gun outta the office.
I feel deaf.
I keep watching. Keep watching. Whatever
you see, you tell me. Okay, dude, me.
Destiny.
Talk to me. What do you see?
Cliffs like a, a bluff.
The ocean ain background.
There's.
Um, these statues like on a fountain.
Statues On a fountain. What kind
of statues? What kind of statues?
They're um, what do you
call, um, gargoyles? There's.
Two Gargo. Two of them.
What else?
Okay. Okay. Now what
else do you see? Destiny.
I see light. I think.
Uh, a beam sweeping through the sky.
That's.
A lighthouse.
Hurry.
The lighthouse.
There.
Its there.
It's.
Hurry.
He's
are I'm Destiny's boyfriend.
They ugly things with the wings.
Yeah, I got it. I'm on it. I'm
You.
Drop a gun, throw it behind you. Now.
I want hurt her. Lyle. Huh?
She never hurt you. .
I was there at nights.
I heard your friend.
He wanted to give Destiny the job.
It would've made her so
happy over my dead body.
You said.
It's just for your speech.
For you. It's not to me.
Put the gun down while,
let's talk this. Hey, nobody needs.
To get hurt.
Come on. Be smart, Lyle.
I love Destiny. And I would've
done anything for her.
I already have
Mr. Elvie. Thank you, Mr. Buchana.
Well.
We found this in his room.
That's exactly like the one you
painted. Like he copied you.
He did, He watched me do it.
We shared the same spirit for a while.
Okay, well, one of these days,
I'm gonna write all this down,
and when I'm ready, I'm gonna
read it and figure it out.
I just, I can't explain it. You know.
I can't explain it away either.
So, what do you wanna do with this?
Carto could only escape
the forest of screams
by covering the eyes of the predator.
The guys are downstairs. You wanna join
in in a little while? Okay. All right.
Well, we'll see you downstairs.
Thank you. Uh, you take plastic? Yes.
Hey, Ken, you okay? Yeah.
Thanks. Anytime, Billy,
how about never again?
Why are you so fidgety?
I feel like somebody's,
somebody's watching me
can blow dreams. There's a
can in the.