in a City of Angels under cover of night
people are drown in a sea of life the
devil holdin your life on
angel : rainbow time
is too late
it words
six months ago I met a man at the
mission club his name is Grant Stiles
handsome charming and very young we
started seeing each other and before I
knew it he had swept me off my feet
god this is humiliating
it's okay Julie we're friends well first
I started giving him little gifts you
know weekend trips to a white and we
became very close so when he asked me
for money to invest in this business I
didn't hesitate how much $100,000 what
kind of business was this I don't know
some sort of investment company then he
said he had lost the money in the stock
market and could he have some more well
I told him no and then when he stopped
seeing me I realized he was some sort of
gigolo well the problem is he hasn't
broken any laws yeah I know I know but
you know I found out I wasn't his only
victim and that's why I'm here I just
don't want him preying on other lonely
women okay what do we care yeah where is
this guy now at the Mission Club to
catch a gigolo I decided to become a
gigolo so I worked out a little harder
that week borrowed from serious threads
copped an attitude and voila
Orion she was gonna be my sexy but oh so
innocent target
by
in good hands as usual right cross like
this sweet Marga nothing went on at the
mission club that Margo the social
director didn't know about we figured if
grant Stiles was able to prey on women
there Marga was somehow in on the action
all we had to do was drop a few hints to
her about Ryan's availability and the
trap will be set miss fuller nice to see
you
Margo aha I'd like you to meet a very
dear friend of mine Rui Anna my Anna
it's a pleasure to meet you hello it's
nice to meet you I've just spotted the
bar if you excuse me I'm gonna go have a
drink see you later poor thing her
husband died about six months ago he
left her a fortune but money can't fix a
broken heart
just ask me well I think I'm going to go
play a little game of gin and see if I
can get even richer good luck okay see
you later
get out of ginger ale please
hello
usually me thanks you come here often uh
what's your sign
don't let me get something gets a
Scorpio I'm warning you I've got a
million of these band icebreakers you
know that I believe okay let me give you
that a stop I'm grant Stiles
do you come here often hi I'm Brianna
Davis let's meet you by Hannah Davis
it's true
although I don't consider myself over
the hill yet living in a town of hard
bodies sometimes makes it hard to ignore
the aging process so when I walk into
that beach club the reaction from the
locals sent a smart clear to my toes
burnout
I don't know why I joined this club it
is so boring nothing ever happens right
Oh mother Mary is coming this way girls
bones over there come on time
Wow do you speak English
actually I speak six languages Oh
everything all right Tim is full are you
a member of the club sir oh he doesn't
have to be Margo he's my guest very good
mrs. bola enjoy uh-huh
now I bet you like French schanberg I
know a little Bistro down the beach I
just bet you do see
those hands are gonna be gossiping about
this for months
you drive safer I will okay goodbye
darling thanks a lot Aunt Clara I owe
you
hi it's Mitch you know what to do
Thanks come on come on Mitch pick up the
phone pick up the phone this is
important I checked everywhere else I
know you're there
oh come on come on I got a problem I
gotta pick up phone hang on hang on
hey Mitch I need some help tracking down
Bobby Bahama is Ryan busy yeah yeah
she's tied up on the gigolo case
come on catchy break loose bar couple of
hours sorry partner no can do
um how about yestiny I'll give me a
break Hey look she's a sweet kid but her
elevator does not go all the way to the
top okay last time
Bobby Bahama jump be stiff dis bouncing
450 cheese he hired us to find him now
Bobby Bahama I heard is staying at Annie
pepper Tony's house comes here every
Tuesday to pay people who'd Bobby oh I
hate this game so Bobby Bahama hired you
Benny
Riggs hire need to find bobbybot for
jumping off Danny Pappa Tony's house no
no no no baby for jumping bail bail
that's him
corner be careful
Oh
so far everything was going just as
planned
Brian was Grant's newest meal ticket and
I was his competition the only thing
that bothered me was that Ryan seemed to
be enjoying all this a little too much
Miz McBride you are a vision Thank You
mr. weekend coffee no no no my body
can't take any more fluids you knew I
had nine ginger ales today hmm
so how is it going with grant fine after
a few pop flies I'll let him get to
first base really in high school first
base was a kiss
yeah still is hey he wants to see me
tomorrow so uh what are you gonna let
this guy do huh hit a couple of doubles
maybe blast a Grand Slam or what well
he's pretty hot he's got such a cute
look I said how far you gonna go this
game kid well I don't know Mitch I mean
as far as I have to this is a job I'm a
professional do we have some sort of
problem here no no no problem
Oh
hey hey boy how's it going today ah
Bobby Bahama who else what's the problem
the man is like smoke he is here he's
there then poof he's gone look I need
your help on this one Mitchell
destiny didn't work out look don't even
mention how the woman's dangerous to my
help
I want you Orien my partners I'm sorry
pal we're pretty tied up on the gigolo
case how long a couple of days can't it
wait no it can't wait I want this weasel
he leaves a bad taste in my mouth you
know this is not the Gunnar lrb I know
McGann er ever be I know has put a
hundred of these guys away the Gunnar
Arabi I know taught me everything I know
about catchin bail jumpers now if
anybody could put this guy away you
can't now go out there and do it yeah
you're right you're absolutely right
bahama is mine oh and I take back what I
said about destinies elevator not going
to the top she doesn't even have an
elevator
guy for song girl
can't do windows Dave darling I'd do
more than windows
I'm pretty then
can bill it
ah yeah nice and lonely I'm trying to
sell it actually she's got too many
memories for me
hey you don't by chance know somebody
needs a five million dollar fixer-upper
do you
I'll look around
crap why'd you stop
are you
hello hello what Robert Vaughn
I'm Ryan a Davis and
you've been watching absolutely not I
was actually looking at someone else but
you kept getting in the way nice along
the rules tomorrow girl calm down Gronk
I'll handle it okay excuse me mr. Baum
Robert bond may I have a minute
this is my turf mister and I want you
out somehow I got that feeling there are
other clubs along the beach work then
this one's lookin no I don't see it that
way Mario come on America was built on
the spirit of competition I'd like to
hang around you're walking a very
dangerous line Mr Bond I can't hold
grant back forever
come on Stevie you're my last chance
give me something all right look if you
hear anything call me yeah
Wow
what's up best today I'm worried about
you garner this negative energy
surrounding you could be very hazardous
to your health
you know what's hazardous to my health
I'm knucklehead named Bobby Bahama
chasing that fool for a week now
keeps slipping through the cracks along
with my 10% now
call girls whoa call girls
Bobby Bahama likes call girls redheaded
call girls
redheaded cargo yeah
stakeout
you
it's hard to say
then I really love you
cuz I've gambled love before
I took my chances
last two many wars
and rutile all the big
when I'm reaching out
on the inside
and it's getting easy
not cry
I need bones
I trust in you softly afar
would you excuse me for a minute I'm
gonna say who are some friends stay warm
Matt cut it thank you thank you what are
you doing what am i doing was it all
about it's mine let's kiss what about me
what about it's a little over the top
don't you think you're slobbering all
over you I'm a professional I can handle
a little slobber that was a lot of
slobber can we talk about something else
please no do you really think that this
fight thing is gonna work yeah yeah yeah
piece of cake just as planned okay uh
Mitch oh wow
kickboxer huh um he said continue
Oh
No
you
while Ryan and I set the trap for Grant
Stiles Gunnar and destiny were staking
out a local watering hole favored by
working girls
they found that Bobby Bahama had a
yearning for redheads
so destiny changed the color of her arm
interview
sergeant elevate is that you it's me
Jacqueline and Heather you're looking so
hot gardening yeah
ah listen he's I can't talk right now
working undercover so do me a favor
I've been trying to favor you for three
years now Ellery don't you keep saying
no okay grumble uh ladies are kind of
busy here okay be safe and use a party
hands never leave home without in search
oh there sweet thing window-shopping red
hair really turns me on
it's very emotional color
well let's party I got a sweet
I like a take-charge home what are you
gonna do to me
excellent a little gangster huh
something like that we're like a big I
love this you're gonna love this one
mmm you're a real mood eater aren't you
yeah I am that's disgusting
yeah that's me William 302 destiny he is
a disgusting meter hurry
wasn't it
favorite dancer wash my entire life whoa
beaker pay you are a fabulous dancer oh
thank you do anything you're not good at
yes money
yeah I'm terrible with money money is
one of my specialties
oh is it really yeah I own an investment
for you dude yep oh I don't think I
should have that last class red wine
feel a little excuse me maybe I could
help you out there's a lot of ways to
make your money work for you oh no I
have lawyers and accountants they handle
that
don't tell me you live here all along
yeah
my sister lives with me but she's in
Europe must fear and then there's the
housekeeper but she lives out in the
guest house so you can see why it's all
only and why I want to sell it well
consider your lonely nights over hmm
that's really sweet
so ten 1371 my birthday not I'm just
kidding you just feel better when
they're in the safe you want a drink
yeah cognac would be perfect okay found
my weak spot there only one actually
last time I counted I had about a
hundred you like a sensual mind feel
ready to it's from over
why don't we wait on that explosion
I mean it's moving a little faster you
think okay okay whatever your little
heart desires
just call me I'll be here can I
yeah hey hey how'd it go
no he went fine I'm glad he's gonna
drool all over your Aunt Clara's carpet
when he saw that Sierra he's definitely
interested
speaking of drooling uh any more kisses
good night match ah man
okay I've been better
thanks for coming Mitch who did this to
you Julian grant me doesn't matter no no
it does matter it matters big time why
why'd he do it oh he said I was telling
all these lies about him to the women at
the club [ __ ] I just want to forget
about this I just want to get on with my
life
Julie you got to go to the police why
you'll just come after me again no I
won't let that happen
[ __ ] I just want you off of this case I
just want to drop it okay
I'm sorry actually we are right on top
of this guy we are this close to busting
him Mitch I'm just so afraid I'm just so
afraid I know I know but if you turn
your back now and gets away with it he
gets away with it he doesn't to somebody
else
remember why you hired us in the first
place hmm
Julian could have killed you I'll talk
about the next one all right
okay okay I'm telling you Mario she's
not interested investments I know the
signs
fine then we move on I already have
somebody picked out then you're not
interested in Jules what I'm not
interested in grant is prison it's just
sitting there waiting to be picked I
know the combination that tiaras worth a
half a million I don't care if it's
worth ten million
the answer's no no that's your problem
Margo you're always thinking too small
find someone else to run your little
errands
Vienna okay Mitch he's here
ready ready
Breana
uh what the hell are you doing grant I'm
not really sure how to say this exactly
but I'm in love with Robert and I no
longer want to see
come on oh cinch it yeah you are you did
good work
hey so do you
professionals
what are you doing out here here have
some water you look like you can use it
Thanks
what was that yesterday what was what
in the pool that was work
yeah work
he's sure
I'm positive
yeah yeah positive absolutely it was
what I mean
we're professional yeah
fashions
thanks for the idea
Haymitch
yeah
watch yourself tonight okay good
10 13 17 come to Daddy smile you're on
candid camera you know you are a hell of
a pilot on your knees
maybe you can convince some of your
fellow inmates to invest in your company
thanks for making me stand up for what I
believe in believe me it was our
pleasure you know I just wanted to run
away and hide I know you did but you
didn't and because you didn't the man's
in jail now well I just don't know how
I'm ever gonna repay you we are paying
in fall welcome take care huh yeah
and
oh pretty cosmic night huh
oh sure why dwell well what is going on
between you two
Wow there's like some serious cosmic e
coming off what I I think you two should
be alone no just me listen wait you
don't know there's me
she is so sick so silly
it can blow your dreams
there's a phrase
come
the devil is watching every slide
Oh
you