This call must be rooted
through the exchange operator.
Thank you. It is important.
I'll hold.
Hey, it looks like the little
guy got himself in some trouble,
huh? Okay. All right.
Now I'm not gonna hurt
him. Heard him. Okay.
He's gonna hold him when I get this off.
Well, you really got himself wrapped up
in there, didn't he? Easy, easy, easy.
Yeah. Okay, okay, Okay.
Okay. You want help?
Tell you what? When your hands
over his way, that's a good,
Make sure nothing's broken. Doesn't
seem like anything's broken. Right.
Okay. Say hi to your friends for us.
Okay? Thanks for your help.
I'm Mitch. What's your name
here on vacation. Oh,
I sure hope your bunch of banding here
cuz the water is awesome. Operator.
Operator don't understand.
That's your mom.
Come up.
In the city. Ofs under of night.
People are drowned in the sea of life.
Devil.
Hold
rain
after the.
Sun.
The.
How many are they? What's
going on over there?
Is that Mitch in the middle of
all that? Yeah, it is. Mitch,
let's check it out.
Black Lincoln Town car. And
it was headed south on pch.
Well you're not giving me a lot. Three
Asian men in a black Lincoln town car.
Didn't you get a partial on the.
License plates? No. No. It was blacked
out. Hey. Hey Roy. What happened?
I think this uh, little girl's
mother was just kidnapped.
Who are you or his
partner in? What private.
Detective agency did? Did you notice
how they were dressed and Yeah,
they were wearing suits. They weren't
street bangers, that's for sure.
I think they were pros. Did
they leave her on purpose?
No. No, No. They wanted her too.
Have you seen the woman or child out here.
Before? No. No I haven't.
It's okay. It's okay. Honey. What's.
Your name sweetheart? If you tell
me it'll help me find your mother.
Her mother called her
Marico, right? Marico.
Marie Rico? Yeah. Is that your
name? Do you speak English?
Yeah.
Do you think she's mute?
No. No. I heard her scream.
She's uh, she's terrified.
Well, I'll take her downtown to St.
Fs while I try to find her mom and
figure out who she is. Okay? Come.
On sweetheart. Hey.
Hey.
You know what? This nice lady is
trying to help you find your mom.
What you gotta do though, is
you gotta go with her. Okay?
Cuz we can't leave you alone.
Okay? I'll go with you. Okay?
Can I appreciate it? Okay.
Oh, we found this coat by
the phone to look familiar.
Her mother had it around her shoulders.
She's got some white powder on it.
It.
Looks like talum.
No, it's uh, it's corr.
It's grainier than Tal.
You wanna ride with me? All.
Right, thanks. I'll.
Follow you and bring you back. Thanks.
A lot.
Hey Donna.
Hey.
Lou. Raymond.
Hi babe.
You look great Lou.
Well thanks. So do you. Thanks.
Hey, what brings you back to Malibu?
Well, I got a gig in
Santa Monica tonight. See?
So I thought I'd stop by
and see what's going on.
Oh, that's nice. Yeah. Gonna get you.
Something. Cup of coffee. Be fine.
You got it?
Cool.
But this is no joke. Is it Lou?
Yeah. Wish it was.
But how do they keep getting away with it?
Well, you see money talks.
They're from rich families,
so they got nothing but
time on their hands.
So they get their kicks by trashing bars.
That's not the worst of it.
They're coming here when?
Well, my friend says today.
Your friend. How does
your friend know this?
I can't tell you that, babe.
Okay, but he's reliable, right?
Yeah, he's reliable.
So Lou says the source is reliable.
Says he is the best.
Hey guys.
What's.
Up? Hey.
Griff. Hey Griff.
Seems like a serious me.
Man. It is. What's going on?
Now's got a little problem.
Oh yeah, Can help.
There's a trio of want to be tough,
rich kids going around trashing bars.
Looks like nights may be next on my list.
Oh, when do they think
this is gonna happen?
Today or tonight? What.
Do you guys call the.
Cops? No, no, no.
What I don't need is for nights to
get a reputation is a trouble spot.
Yeah, I'm sure we'll handle this
little problem. Uh, you house.
Ah, yeah, I like that. I'm ready.
Where's the child?
The mother was on the phone.
There's too many people.
We have to leave the child.
Take her to some.
It's okay. It's okay
honey. Come on. Come on.
I know the nuns here. She'll be fine.
It's okay honey. It's okay.
ba. It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, come here. I got, I
got you. Okay, now listen.
Listen to me now. This is nice lady over
here is gonna help me find your mom.
But you gotta stay here
while I do that. Right?
Come on sweetheart. You must be hungry.
Let's go get something fun to eat. Okay?
Come on.
She'll be fine. Don't worry.
Thank you
little girl was scared of
death. Breaks your heart.
Yeah, I know.
Hi. What can we do?
Well we can see if we can help
locate the mother. I mean,
we do have the only witness
besides finding missing
people is one of the things
we do.
You know why I like you?
Absolutely.
Take that. Here we go.
Take care. Your time up.
There. They're.
Three.
Knuckle. Yeah.
They don't look so tough. Rack them
up. Just little. Thank you sir.
Live Minnesota fence. Action. Here we
go. , I think I can handle this.
Check out is great. She thinks.
Does she think she can handle this?
Here we go.
Seven back here. Oh yeah.
Hi guys. Mind if I join you?
Not at all.
So are you having a good time?
It's better now that you're here.
No, I heard a vicious rumor.
Really?
But some guys are going around bashing
bars and generally acting like idiots.
We heard about those guys.
Well, it's not gonna happen here.
Why not?
Okay, just why don't you,
you know, just relax. Huh?
Who the hell are you?
Willie hop?
Yes, he will.
Listen. Listen. What's your name?
Jack. Jack.
Why don't we settle this peacefully
with a game of pool? You win.
You can stay drinks on me, You lose, you.
Leave.
Rack of ch.
So Jack, tell me, what's your game?
Eight ball call shot. No slot.
Oh, not me, Jack.
The lady.
I'll rack him.
Three.
Ball. Corner pocket.
Man. I've been hustled
before, but what a ride.
Donna.
You are I really, really good.
The best.
Thanks.
You can.
This is Detective Harrison.
Yeah, Detective, what's up?
Do you have that little
girl? Because if you do.
No, I don't have her. You're telling
me you lost her. How could that happen?
This isn't a jail. No one picked
her as a runner. She makes contact.
Let me know immediately. Okay?
You do the same.
Maco took off. I'm gonna go look for her.
You want some company?
No, no. Just stay here in case she calls.
Okay? Thanks.
Have you found a child?
Not yet. What? Have your
progress Master smile.
More difficult than I
had thought. One thing,
we must not have another incident.
Like what happened at the beach?
That was your plan. Not ours.
Now you'll listen. Na, you
are sent here to work for.
Me. I will sit here from Japan
to work, but not for you.
I work for the men in
Tokyo or at the moment,
not pleased with the
decisions you are making. I.
Will this operation from nothing.
Some people say you are slipping.
How dare.
You? This whole tobacco,
starting with the murder is
your doing The computer disc,
her lover is stole. Could
bring us all to our knees.
It has all the number codes to
bank accounts, deposits, payments.
Every illegal transaction is on that disc.
I'm aware of its importance.
Things got just a little out of hand.
Maybe it's you who are out of hand.
How are you feeling? Heroku.
Your daughter has run
away from the police.
Then you do not know where she is.
She will be found. We're not criminals.
What do you call kidnapping?
Necessity.
The disc you hold could ruin us all.
You have my word that you and your
daughter will be sent to Japan where
you'll be well cared for.
You've only to give me the disc.
When I know my daughter is
safe in Nagoya with Father.
Then you will get the disc.
I did not come here to waste time.
The beauty of this instrument is that
it causes great agony, even death,
but leaves no marks.
I am not afraid to die.
My guests are waiting.
By all means, join them.
Excuse.
Me. I'm trying to find
mother. Why?
Yes?
Tell me you have the child.
No, Mr. Summa. I am still looking.
Report to me tomorrow.
I will be there.
Hey, come here
man. You wanna make some
money? Seen this girl?
Yeah. Want you to look around,
See what you can find out for me.
Hey, call me at this number. Got.
Hey. Hey. Uh, she's
gone. I mean she is gone.
I looked all over Little
Tokyo. No sign of her.
Up early. Hum Mitch.
Yeah. Thanks. Thank you. I thought of
that little girl out in those streets.
You know, if this was a ransom kidnapping,
we would have a note
demanding money from someone.
Right? What? Who?
If it's not Rico's mother could be dead.
You know, I got one piece
of information to move on.
Do you remember the powder
on the mother's coat?
Yeah.
The detective said that it
wast, but I didn't think so.
So I snuck a sample to check it out.
It turns out it was a heavy rice
powder that only Japanese geisha use.
Japanese cas. Mm-hmm. . Uh,
I'm right back.
Good morning. Um, well I know you.
I wasn't sure it was you Mr. Buchanan.
I am Captain King Nara
Imperial Japanese Navy retired.
Mari is my granddaughter and
her mother is my daughter.
I went to the police.
But they tell me Marco is gone
and no one knows where she is.
Now I have come to ask for your help.
I saw your picture in the newspaper.
You saved my granddaughter. And
because you are a private detective,
you and I might have a
better chance than the.
Polices naka here. What can you tell us
that will help us find your daughter?
Huh? In Nagoya, My daughter
was a geisha for many years,
but when her husband
died, she came to America.
To work as a geisha.
Yes. Unfortunately, I do not know where,
I did not approve of her live Japan.
And we have not spoken
much since until yesterday.
Why? What happened?
She called very upset,
told me she was in trouble and
afraid for her and medical's lives.
Did she say why?
Only that she had
something somebody wanted.
Did she say what?
No, but she was frightened
and she disconnected.
Does your granddaughter speak
English? Mr. Nacara? Hi.
Very good English talk in a school class.
She wouldn't talk to anyone. I mean
she wouldn't even say her name.
It can only mean she has
pledged a code of silence.
Code of silence. Why?
To honor her mother's wishes.
Yeah.
Hey.
Yeah. It's me. Okay, listen. I talked
to the people at the Japanese Museum,
Museum and they said they don't know
of any local Japanese restaurant,
nightclub, anything that's got
geisha as part of its scene.
It's not our day.
Yeah, but I do have some good news.
Please. I need some.
Well, I started thinking about the
costumes. So I checked them out.
I got a long list of people who
make the GE costumes itself.
But then I started thinking about the wig.
You know that black shiny pompadour
thing with the ivory come in it? Yeah.
Right. Well, there's only one lady in
LA who makes the repairs then. Yeah,
her name is Lily and she's
at 9 1 1 Spring Street.
I'm there now.
Nine 11. We're on away. Okay, we.
Gotta leave.
Can I help you?
Hi, uh, my name is Ryan McBride.
I'm a private investigator.
I'm looking for this little girl. Her
name is Maria Nacara. I was wondering,
have you seen her?
Do you work with a man called.
Mitch? Yes. He's my partner.
Come with me. Are.
You sure? It's the.
Girl. Hey. Hey, we . Hey, hey.
Oh, sorry. Don't want
side that.
Truthful. Hi darling. Hi. My name
is Ryan. I'm a friend of Mitch.
Do you remember Mitch?
Yeah. He's on his way.
He's gonna be here in
a couple minutes. Okay?
Okay.
Uh, no, no, no. I, I'll
get it. Okay, I'll see.
You are very brave. But
the odds are hopeless.
You'll get yourself and the
people you are trying to save.
Killed.
Find the girl.
Mr. Nu. Here, stay here.
Oh, look, I must help.
You can help me if you stay here.
I dunno.
Look over
you. All right,
Ryan, Mom.
Mitch. There are three of them.
They're armed and they've got.
Marico. No, no, we got her. She's
okay. Time to come on the cops. No.
No. When.
They see the police, they
will kill my daughter.
Please Mitch. Don't
let them kill my mommy.
No, no, no. It's not gonna
happen. I promise. Okay.
Really? Is there any place that you know
of in Los Angeles where Geisha actually
performed? Hi. At the private
compound of Manoa. Samora. Come.
On.
Here you go Don. How is it? Good.
Vi You remember my man Scott Mooto works
in the Asian investigation section in
lapd?
Yeah. What's.
Up? Well it seems they've had their
eye on spiral industries for quite a.
While. Oh, before.
Couple of months ago, one of
their executives was murdered.
The case is still open. But
here's what's interesting.
They have lots of business parties
and at those parties there are.
Geisha girls.
You bet more or less young women dressed
as geishas who speak fluent Japanese.
Some born in the us some born in Japan.
Does this sound like applies
that hero might work? It.
Is possible, yeah. Why would
somebody kid a geisha girl?
I don't know.
But what could your daughter have that
these guys want badly enough to kill for?
I don't know.
Well, guess what folks? There's more.
Hey, this is the guy
that grabbed Mario today.
Who is he.
Name? Odeo business executive. Uh, part
suspected shooter for the Japanese.
Za. Can Ryan's positive
Id get us a search.
Warrant. Oh yeah. In fact, we even have
the address to some our industries.
How long for the warrant?
Three, four hours.
Oh, we cannot wait. No, we're not gonna
wait. Ryan, would you? Yeah, let's.
I'm not a violent man. Hero.
Go. Please.
Don't make me do this.
Where is the girl? Any luck?
Step aside.
Last chance.
Where's the disc?
I would've given the disc to tomorrow,
but never to You.
Have the plane ready in two hours.
Any covering flight plan filed?
If there are any problems,
call me immediately. Ato,
The van has left. His
body will never be found.
He had a long life and a brilliant career.
Just the end was a little sloppy.
Somewhere in here is one bullet
the blood of a summer. I
may run through your veins,
but you have the mind of a pe.
How long can you hold
your breath? Long enough?
Thank
hero. Hero.
It's okay.
It's alright.
Ma Rico safe. He don't.
He don't. Go guys over. Father, are you.
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me.
Thank you for being so kind to my dad.
It's okay.
Rich song. Hey, these are for you.
Is this the souls of the Samurai?
Kenji? I'm honored, but I I
can't accept this gift is too.
Much. Oh, it is not a gift. The
souls of the I'll never given,
only earned.
You have demonstrated the heart
of a true Japanese warrior.
Take them and continue
to bring them. Honor.
Welcome.
It is time for us to leave. Where is Mari?
Oh, I will get her. No, no, no. Just,
just a minute.
Let
Oh you.
Hey. I got a present for you,
uh,
from me to you. Remember the
first time we met the Seago?
It's for you. Thanks Mitch. I love you.
I love you too.
Can blow your dreams. There's a
in the, the,
you can.