[Music]
bailiff
Baelor
[Music]
gimme that you
[Applause]
[Music]
margon Court is now in session all rise
for the Honorable Cole Watkins what do
you want what do you think I want I'm an
animal and I should not be allowed free
access to the community that ring a bell
now you're out of water
[Music]
Oh
ah
[Music]
in a City of Angels undercover
people are drowning in a sea of light
[Music]
holding your life um
angel :
rainbow time
sums up
there is too late
[Applause]
[Music]
son
[Applause]
I was going to live
how
[Music]
[Applause]
how are you detective resort well we got
Bob two male Caucasians the first 35
years old
bailiff shot through the heart second
fifty-five years old cause of death
appears to be blunt force trauma
tentatively identified as Cole Watkins
judge Watkins the same you know man and
more fire brimstone than a revivalist
preacher but he was always fair he
apparently died of massive head injuries
caused by repeated blows from his
honours own gavel
our murderer was definitely not a fan of
his honor there's something in his mouth
yeah we didn't touch that
and we judge lectures killer before
sentencing in the life talk about making
him eat his words
this guy Larkin was your caller Whitney
yeah
me and garner illa P I'll put out an APB
on the hell did Larkin ever get out
[Music]
how did he ever go
97 I mean I wonder why aren't we
ambitious this morning just trying to
get in shape for the annual Carolyn the
Dory race oh can I try it yes sir
how'd you hate it exercise I know but it
looks like fun
fun no fun is on the ocean
here's hardware alright alright so
listen so back to the point so you met
this woman where I told you between the
snow tires and the all weather radios
this is in town for the convention the
bunting is the manufacturers posters
bunny
her name is bunny yeah what should you
stand around a bikini selling retreads
well I'm having lunch with her later at
nice you're that curious why don't you
stop by and saint-lo oh you mean I'm in
for some big surprise well as it just so
happens I'll be there anyway because I'm
having lunch with Davis whatsit Davis
Davis Hollingsworth from the Connecticut
Hollingsworth did I not mention him yes
we have dumpers old flame some sparks
never die
Davis is from a mainline banking family
about his true passion is film so he's
in town to bid on movie studio the
entire studio hey that's the agency
phone we grab it
chata delle Erbe and McBride Mitch is
that you yeah who's this
Leah Leah Broussard Leah ooh I could
feel that look right through the phone
now what is she calling for and why
doesn't she just go away
oh no no no just surprise no judgment
here
Leah learned a long time ago not to get
between a man and a woman I need to talk
to a Mitch it's important police
business
uh Leah there's no way I can get to
touch the garden right not right now but
look he'll be at nights around noon it's
on the Strand have you see him before I
do tell him
Larkin's out
Turner's ex parte sounds like more than
an ex-partner to me yeah yeah she wants
you know they say there's one love you
never get over
yeah she's Garner yep well be quite
introspective the lunch of lost ones
garner Leah you and Davis Hollingsworth
a third and you and miss all-weather
radials oh well they go hit the showers
join me in your dreams
on second thought
[Music]
shut
yeah this is going to be a very
interesting glitch
[Music]
hi
I smelled problem Johnny Larkins been
popped out on appeal now I know the
world truly has gone nuts they were
supposed to put him under the jail
pikas worse he killed judge Wolk is last
night and made sure we knew it was him
he's just getting started so everyone
aware of that because you put a circle
the wagons I know
and whatever list he's made up you're on
it you two
where's the phone it's around the corner
[Music]
wait a minute I think I see a Davis
heading this way
Ryan do you look like sunshine it's
wonderful to see this place suits you
Thank You Davis Hollingsworth I'd like
you to meet Mitch Buchannon oh yes
Ryan's told me all about you
most i discount is hyperbole a bar man
your best single malt two fingers neat
with a water back I have had a
frightfully hideous day damn it pumpkin
it's great to see you like this it makes
this whole trip worthwhile even if
everything else falls right through the
floor so how long are you staying well I
thought a week but the way people in
this town refuse to make decisions it
could be a month I mean half has
anything ever get done by sentiments
exactly two hours waiting for a meeting
only to have it postponed
hey you mm sorry I'm late oh no problem
you cannon you know this creature bunny
this is Davis and um pumpkin bunny is in
town on a promotional tour for
Beauregard time really
Bobo's an old friend whatever he's
paying you it isn't enough that's sweet
so what exactly is your title I've heard
miss all-terrain snow and go Mitch what
have you been telling these people
actually I'm vice president of marketing
oh that's great
you're dead let's all get a booth shall
we
brain idea ah but just give me a second
I want to say hello okay oh um yeah I'm
gonna go with him but then we'll join
you in a minute okay snow one go
hey you okay yeah yeah well you don't
look fine
um no school is cooler seven side you
can garner your partner if it concerns
you it concerns us
somebody wants to kill Leah and me
Oh
when John Larkin was sentenced to life
without parole he swore he'd get even
with everyone involved and his
conviction in the same amount of time it
took the jury to deliberate 36 hours and
you only arrested this guy I didn't
think much about Larkins threats then
was facing life but he's out now
he's already murdered the judge that
sensitive huh Leah how you doing oh this
is my partner Ryan crime hi Howie I
gotta go the assistant DA who prosecuted
has been murdered Oh God we're going
along um Davis
I'm really sorry something's come up we
have to go no no no no no don't worry
your pretty little head pumpkin will be
fine
bunny its piss off don't worry about it
Mitch call me later
Tata
did I mention I was going to buy a movie
studio marker no it's okay there
[Music]
Bob round always like pushing iron said
the barbell crushed his larynx
take this out justice delayed is justice
saver
Larkin wants you to note well yeah it's
work I went through some uniforms around
he refused him he said he could handle
it himself well he may have been able to
but not on the down stroke of a bench
press he knew exactly when and where to
hit it guys definitely done his homework
he made sure Brown could see him in the
mirror part of his plan
yeah he taunts his victims what's the
point in killing a cop you can't seems
greed some kind of psychotic vengeance
it's probably what sustained him in
prison
Leah if I were you I get some more
security the other people are less cuz
obviously what you got now so I'm
working I think you're right tell you
the about what you let me see you home
I'm a cop I can see myself home I should
be seeing you home you allergic to my
cat you don't have a cat
watch your back son so what do you say
we go see how bunny and Davis are doing
pumpkin
that's funny it's funny
[Music]
hey Donna hey hey we left a couple of
non-combatants inside your scene
oh if you're referring to the prepster
in the radio queen they left our menara
about an hour ago
oh my no listen guys I'd love to chat
but the planes waiting at Santa Monica
Airport and my dates waiting in Vegas so
you're going to Vegas now sure don't
have to be back till 6:00 a.m. I'll see
you guys have fun c ya why is it commies
ago no Davis wasn't your type it
yeah well bunny wasn't your type either
really yeah you know I can tell I think
what is your type I don't know that I
have one what you mean someone who's
easy to be with just constantly fill the
air with words who's smart who's got a
great sense of humor and who cares much
more about others and she does about
herself
oh is that
nobody I know so what about physical
attraction absolutely necessary and
she's gotta be great kisser what about
you what's your type you me hmm sort of
the Eagle Scout with an attitude type
but you're not on my list because I
don't dance
where I work but if I did I'd run Little
Miss racing slicks and everyone liked
her right off the truck
[Music]
Ryan yes
oh great kisser really nobody's ever
said that before
see ya
moment of decision to come in or not to
come in
sure choice
I'm sure you ready to start this up yet
part of me is it's funny all I can
remember right now are the sweet times
oh yeah plenty though but um we both
know we don't really work on me I know
and I haven't changed meaning so it
would be stupid wouldn't it beyond
stupid best thing I could do right now
or say goodnight and get there laddie
since when have we ever done what's best
there's that means understand we
wouldn't want to be inconsistent when we
you
[Music]
I do have some wine in the kitchen why
I don't get nervous leer I could still
go
sergeant I'm ellaby but you get to keep
score you see I'm gonna take the others
on first and then I'm coming back after
you and it's not a damn thing you can do
about it
it's my collar creative revenge
yeah yeah they leave this nasty headache
a few cuts she got it so he was another
whole time you hope it's okay mom take
it easy exactly what do you want yeah
just sit down just sit down
he wants you out of control man he's
getting off on your rage don't you see
that Mitch he is anticipating every move
he knew I take Leah home this guy said
herself for a long time planning this
thing out now it's gonna take a lot down
thinking all right gentlemen let's
really get to know this guy shall we
whoo I know it I know I know this is one
how's it going out there Mike
- this is one committed - all clear
[Music]
are you doing mr. marks slow mature
detective I put a fresh pot of coffee on
would you like to cut thanks I would
[Music]
mr. Jory Foreman marks
you know I got one question it's been
eat then why I never did anything to you
hell I don't even know you
why did you stick your nose into my
business I was on the jury yeah it was
my duty duty it was your duty to send a
man to living hell
[Music]
well vodkas not the classic serial
killer like Bundy or Gacy but he
definitely shares some of their traits
like what well he's a loner he's
meticulous he hates Authority he
definitely wants some respect
particularly yours why mine cuz you beat
him in some perverse way he respects
that he admires you he wants to finish
everybody off and have you cheering for
him at the end
Televi yeah we got three more victims
detective and the jury foreman included
Dutch might be interested yeah thanks
[Music]
what he just got three minutes
what are the sugar
[Music]
two cops in a civilian
got stopped the sky
we get less than 12 hours
[Music]
here we are playing catch-up but he's
got the damn bull gotta find a way get a
step ahead of this guy well where's he
getting all his money he's got his
transportation I don't know he's a loner
he didn't have a forwards perfect family
what about in prison you think we can
get ahold of the warden Pelican Bay and
find out who his friends were in there
sure that's a that's a good idea that I
can go up there and talk to some of
those friends so if you had me well I
should go oh all right come on that's a
maximum-security prison there's some bad
boys up there Ryan's right I'm sure
those guys want to talk to her and do
you
yeah okay I just have a little headache
I just wanted to go see how you were
doing listen call me of a couple of
hours - my hair won't turn gray okay how
is they're doing not usually here we go
guys okay
Larkin's buddy is Mohammed Aziz made up
some money stealing cars then set up a
pipeline overseas shipping cars to Asia
in the Middle East so you trade not cars
or the drugs pure uncut heroin miss
McBride yes Terry Cooper any system one
nice to meet you please have see I just
want to talk before Aziz comes in this
visit was a request by LAPD it's been
approved oh I know I know I just like
you to tell me what this is all about
well we feel that mr. Aziz has some
information that could help an
investigation already in progress you
know who is easiest
I've read his file yes this is a
powerful very dangerous man who in many
ways has more control over the prisoners
in here than we do I'm sorry I don't
follow the point the point is if you get
him talking I have some questions I
would like you to slip into the
conversation mmm
mr. Cooper I can appreciate what you're
trying to do and I'll be glad to help
out in any way that I can just as long
as it doesn't interfere with my case
well I can recognize a non-answer when I
hear one
Oh what the hell I understand well
whatever you can do
private investigations it's an
interesting career choice for a woman
let's just say I like being my own boss
deep ooh I would think you'd be able to
relate to that mr. Aziz ah you must be
desperate
why because I'm here because I only get
called mr. Aziz when someone truly wants
something from me what do you want
Ryan McBride private investigator I need
your help my resources are a bit limited
at the moment oh I think you're being
modest I think a man like yourself would
be able to get anything he wants even in
here judging by your weight and muscle
tone I would say that you have steak or
fried chicken at least three times a
week feel now that you mention it and
all the protection you need from your
little homeboys thanks to our friends it
costs to have friends mr. Aziz and
that's how I know that your business
associates on the outside are still
pumping money into your hands can I help
but if the wheels of commerce have a
life of their own
alright look on your right to the point
I need to know what John Larkin did in
order to obtain your support everything
in here is done on the barter system so
he had to have something to trade for
your little favor
you know he's killed six people since he
was released the man does know how to
hold a grudge all that man knows how to
do is kill
that's not lying I wouldn't want to have
my name in his pocket
Thank You mr. Zee she's been a lot of
help ok here it is
state of California versus Mohammed Aziz
he went to trial January 9 here's a
prosecution's witness list
Oh Ernie watts for prior arrests well if
there's a chance for a retrial it would
benefit as used to have already watts
out of the way
professional sticks about lovely I'm
gonna help you lose in Venice
wot's honey watch
[Music]
to
so much for any watch
you're doing better than I thought
ellaby but still no cigar have a nice
day
catch up with this son of a [ __ ] where
the hell's he going goner
who's left garner Carter are you there
yeah Lee are you okay
[Music]
yes nice to hear your voice - can you
listen up wanna see this [ __ ] alive
again you just do as you're told and
you'll meet us at the same plant Playa
disco in one hour
come along she is dead
[Music]
she okay yeah
yeah let's get out here hey garner
you're talking to us pal you want to
tell us the truth
this is out of your hands I gotta do
this by myself bargain has Lea doesn't
he he wants me to meet him alone
one hour where the old steam plant play
investor scatter good plant he said to
come alone or he'd kill her don't you
see that's exactly what he wants you to
do don't you think I know that you're
not going there without us I'm not
getting Lea killed garner he's gonna
kill her anyway
you just want you to see it before he
kills you
talk to me alright the way I see it this
is the first chance we got to get one
step ahead of this guy Garner I know the
scatter good plant like the back of my
hand I'll show you something there's a
planet there's something about this
place
there's no way this guy could know I'm
the air is the underwater entrance
[Music]
maybe your old partners gonna stand you
up detective but I don't think so he's
gonna be here because he's a damn hero
where the hell are we Larkin really
wanna know
yes I really want to know
hi you're a dead man Larkin we are will
confuse down
you and God are dead you are my piece de
resistance I'm gonna be here to enjoy
every moment
ah
you're really sick Larkin you know that
I know
don't you ever fall guard is gonna die
[Music]
Donna Bailey hanging in there
our girl
[Music]
when our baby
no we won't
[Music]
wait
Turner she's going in man thanks Kamau
display I know you are here I tell you
what I am point 10 and then she is
history
you hear me 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 see
that I'll be able to hold her breath
[Music]
about where I can see y'all come on baby
give it your best shot
let's try elevate your better move she's
going down
[Music]
come on [ __ ] come on man you gotta be
yeah it'll be there you gotta admit
ellaby I've done it myself here come on
make your move
you hear me
you can run Ella fee but you can't hire
come on
that's what I want to see that you'll be
a damn hero
right out baby there's no way you're
gonna say right now
[Music]
[Applause]
I listen stay here you'll be all right
don't you've got some backup
[Music]
what the hell
come on come on partners gone and Joe
and me
it's overlocking drop the weapon I'm
impressed I said drop the women put
their hands on your head or you die
it's not my style
[Music]
met you guys okay she's alright another
hot shower will chair
[Music]
you can blow your three
with a face
[Music]
in the night
the fur
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
the devil is watching every slide
[Applause]
[Music]
you