[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
you've angel under cover of night
people are drown in a sea of light
[Music]
the devil's holding your life um
angel : rainbow time
[Music]
[Applause]
Dorris too late before
[Music]
[Applause]
why
because he shoots a girl in the shower I
should do business with him he's
cranking it up killing out couriers
Laura was the second one he's extorting
me and you think I should take it he
wants a little taste give it to him dope
business that's what you call it
do you remember the game we used to play
when we were kids I'd faint you'd flinch
I get a free shot yeah and if you didn't
flinch you get another free shot at me
I never flinched not once
this ain't this fool you
ball
how does he want it cash delivered by
someone he knows and trusts Bobby Taylor
boy that's a funny man
his ex-girlfriend the only one of my
people he trusts you know I think he's
still carrying a torch for her she's
perfect that's Cory I have ADD you know
Marie you may be right
maybe I should do business with the
connote I thought Bobby retired she just
done retired
find her
let's go
[Music]
here's to wealthy clients hey their
bills
[Music]
you know champagne was invented for
moments like this
aha - more champagne woman's drink -
duck hmm
Wow less stuff is really am it's kidding
to my head I'm I'm not a trained care of
it
yeah you better slow down a little bit
that seasick build me that mixture well
in the champagne oh don't be silly I'll
be fine
Cheers hello whoa should add so much
champagnes on it you're right wait easy
easy and fun okay okay I know it just I
got it I got it with just little even
have my thank you are you fine wait I've
got it oh thank you that's kind of nice
actually uh what really you have a very
strong and steady lifeguard arm come on
come on it you know what
uh no I don't I think this champagne is
getting to me
well okay okay okay just stay right here
party right there oh whoa
gotcha uh is your oh yeah yeah it's um
I'll see Ellis you have any champagne no
I have no champagne ah all bachelors
have champagne and why are you still a
bachelor
what's your problem uh put on some
coffee coffee you want a coffin
[Music]
Haymitch did I ever tell you how much I
love my job in Malibu then you garner
well Ryan I'm uh glad you're happy
Mitch ask you question anything how long
have we been working together a while
can I ask you another question sure how
come you never ripped my clothes off
um Ryan you know it's the 90s men just
don't go around ripping women's clothing
off without permission you want me to
rip your clothes off you have to ask
well it's not very romantic
well romance is in short supply these
days have you ever wanted to what rip
off my clothes you know it's really late
what do you say we uh we go to bed huh
sounds good no no no no to sleep sleep
great yeah I don't want cool I know you
don't want to go sleep with you'll thank
me in the morning okay what what don't
you find me attractive very well good
uh Ryan we made a deal
we did yeah yes we did
remember business and pleasure do not
mix okay then hmm good night coward uh
the word stupid comes to mind
jerk
can't unzip my dress
hey I fell uh yes you did um come on up
you go thank you
time to go night-night all right is this
foreplay no this is not formal a yeah oh
here we go
fine thank you
that's foreplay
sweet dreams
[Music]
oh you cannon no more deals
hey hey mornin watch it the doorbell oh
we put that in before he left
how's he doing with his mom he's doing
great says he loves Minneapolis but he
misses a beat yeah yeah I get you oh my
god really who's that what that oh that
um Ryan oh no no no nothing like that
she um mixed champagne and Dramamine on
a trip back from Catalina I didn't feel
like schlepping her all the way to
Malibu and believe me she was in no
condition to drive
hmm oh my god excu oh my god Ryan what
did you do last night
you okay uh fine thanks um I'll be right
out thank you you brought your own
cardinal rule and slept with your
partner way to go genius
now what um um
fine ah you just
go downstairs tell him uh what'd you
tell him um it was just the UH what was
i drinking those um champagne yes of
course huh
it was just the champagne that's that's
reasonable he'll understand good morning
Ryan
we're going out for breakfast would you
care to join us coffee
no thank you uh but thank you uh I go
now excuse me
she doesn't know district no she thinks
something happened last night well you
you gotta tell her I will
[Music]
Bobby Bobby are you okay Bobby hey
original recipe you marry a guy that
still buy an original recipe Bobby
you wanna back you wanna back yes and be
cool get around here William Galvin Stan
it's fine no cops
[Music]
let's put the gun away put the gun away
put my drive toy try let her go
that's my wife let her go
[Applause]
[Music]
hey Donna drip listen I need a favor and
I need a rent check groove no make that
rent cash I'm sorry about the rubber
chick okay I'm on the arm all over town
but that's changing yep I guess I could
do that again
cliff spare me okay this is incredible
the way the light hits your face makes
you glow like the lights coming from
inside you you're three months behind
look it's time for me to no matter who
says what about my so-called sugar daddy
I still have to make this place work
yeah well look I promise I'll make up
the rent Donna but first I really need
this favor what is it
okay some people are gonna come looking
for me what people I don't notice people
and I need you to tell him that I that I
took a two-month fashion getting Hong
Kong yeah and and I left last week you
do that come on please
pass over the brownie grab Donna come on
have a heart
look this isn't just a camera this is my
soul okay keep it get back together huh
yeah well I'm working on it
I got that favor covered Oh
Thank You Donna deal hey why are these
people looking for you
I think they want to kill me
hey garner hey listen um I I need some
pepper spray pepper spray yeah anything
you need a license without stuff Biff
what's it nothing you know just in case
no I can't give you any pepper spray
well how about a gun a gun
you need some help Grif yeah here come
on I'll show you
Mitch what are you that Bobby who they
say they'll kill her if I go to the cops
Mitch you gotta help me take a look at
these so what do these have to do with
your friend Greg Oh
Greg's the paparazzi King right he asked
me to get some nude photos of this hot
model who calls herself mystique ax I
never would do this kind of junk except
I needed the money so how does the
pepper spray fit into mommy's now it
takes me a while but I get the shot now
I think someone's trying to kill me
kill you why this and
[Music]
this this right here is my shot
but with Gregg's byline yeah and it gets
Wilder I took this shot around 11:00
yesterday and dropped the negs off by
Craig's well last night he sends them
back no money so I go over to his house
and the cops are all around her what did
the cops say I don't know I didn't talk
to him I choked and I ran
well Gregg's in the hospital with a
busted head so I'm thinking whoever
trashed Greg may come looking for these
look at the side table what the mirror
so one in the next room
the killer
[Music]
man garner what should I do what you
shoulda done him in the first place you
should have gone to the cops
when I'm scared well you ought to be
I've missed you Bobby right I need you
to make a run no W normal fee forget it
I can't it's got to be done it's got to
be you I'm retired
are you going to make me do something
we'll both feel very bad about my mule
days are over I'm not about to risk
carrying illegal stuff through customs
in some foreign Airport oh no no no this
is a local it's a milk run local why do
you need me for that
it's to Boyett to Boyett he's been
squeezing me for a piece of the action
lately I'm paying him off he knows you
he trusts you I trust you so yes
specifically that you make the delivery
Jordan I'm out of that I have a
different life a husband I had him
tailed make sure he didn't run to the
cops
bring him in
well well look at you mr. Beach each
chair beat shoes well I was beginning to
think you guys are gonna stand us up
come on
darn about you Oh so what's up the
message sounded kind of needy
this is Grif walking like I I don't know
if this is such a good ass from the back
you guys working on that mr. Kummer yeah
any nominee only one former Irish soccer
player Felix Dennis there's a lot of
money power women axis sex on the rough
side they did mistake her for a couple
of months Grif took that photo of
mystique that was in the paper yeah and
I don't want to be involved at all
Thanks you may be next on Phoenix's
Ignis after what happened to Greg well
I'll try to make that case before that
happens
good I don't want a grift to be muscled
in the meantime any objections of uh pay
the man a visit you my guest won't be
stepping on that undermine he owns a pub
called Brennan's in Santa Monica books
Brit action soccer rugby plays pretty
good
[Music]
Bobby speaks Farsi and Thai and French
and Mandarin Chinese how do you know
that
well I ran her driver's license and her
social security number and her credit
cards through a friend's computer it's
pretty amazing what they can find out
about people Albert did you know about
any of this no I mean she'd ordered the
French restaurants but what else do you
know
well she was a runway model Milan I knew
that airline hostess I knew that she
stripped in a club in West Hollywood I
didn't know that the Cleverley paws oh
she was there a year or so before you
two met I didn't know well then nothing
there's no visible income she traveled a
lot about nine hundred and forty
thousand frequent flyer miles in 16
months and a bank account that nearly
matches the miles no I should get that
money she doesn't have a job this isn't
my Bobby
I guess the shoes of you yeah that'd be
my call to a mule courier someone who
delivers certain things to certain
people and has nice perks travel and a
lot of tax-free money I need a drink
well we have coffee right over here
coffee's not gonna cut it
bars downstairs I don't even know the
person you're talking about it it's not
my Bobby it's not my book
well let's get started the last place
she worked
so when was the last time you saw a long
time a couple of years I hurt you got
married which is a real stretch you got
any phone numbers or addresses yeah I
got a card on her great could you fax
that to me please
[Music]
don't turn around Albert don't turn
around I know your wife is my wife yeah
meet me in the men's room
the men's room what are you afraid of
Barrett the men's room your wife got it
[Applause]
Wow she's got a lot of phone numbers
I'll run him see if I find any names and
addresses
what's wrong I'll talk about it okay not
now maybe not ever why are you snapping
at me I'm not like why don't you go get
Albert we'll see if you recognize any of
these phone numbers okay okay I'll get
him good we know if there's some kind of
problem let's get it out is it about
last night what about last night nothing
nothing
so we have nothing to discuss okay I'll
get him good
okay I'll BAM I'll get him
[Applause]
[Music]
okay Albert let's take a little walk
don't you go
hey Albert you back here
[Music]
you've got to remember the smart cumin
was always finding themselves a little
niche it's what their soccer player
Phoenix is about it's nothing hold it
wait wait
w C's over there ball from Ed John he's
got a sweet little bookmaking operation
going on riding this power soccer run
new cricket all the expats come here to
better more money nice thing about the
Brits is they don't carry guns
what are you kidding just got so linked
in this it's not bad it's not bad skinny
thinking yeah
I was born there hairy guy yeah Queeny
Mike damn yeah I'd like to see tonight
sweetheart I was eight o'clock sound hey
and wear that sexy lingerie for me okay
Felix Dennis I'll call you back
sweetheart
who the bloody hell are you I mean you
kill mystique at the cops don't come
estiga but I don't care about that I'm
here because of my friend isn't sleeping
thinking you're gonna back him down
don't know the man photographer the
picture in the paper reel better
yeah I here's the point he is with me I
want you to be real clear on that
now see he's with me he's with you the
next menthol bird will probably have a
badge in a warrant you're going down
[Music]
he'll sit up Bobby are you okay yes what
did they do to you god I was so worried
if anything ever happened to you your
face who did this to you
Bobby part of me feels like I don't even
know you anymore
Farsi Mandarin nearly a million frequent
flyer miles stripping in a club
I'm sorry Albert I didn't mean to hide
it what did I think less of you I would
die for you baby
well he's willing to do his part your
slime Jordan that's not news Bobby you
make the run or Albert here dies of
unnatural causes what's the run deliver
a briefcase to Boyett in Union Station
no piggy I'll do it sit down and shut up
I'm not a patient man Bobby
[Music]
okay but not like this a wardrobe change
to make a run I only wear these four
kidnappings haha you're the best
I don't know how I ever let you go
there's never your choice
[Music]
here's what I got from Bobby's emergency
numbers one is her sister one is out of
service one is some guy who moved to
Montana and one is registered under a
company owned by Carlos Jordan Carlos
Jordan well I've heard of him and none
of it's good Marina towers right
[Music]
what are you looking at nothing yes you
are you were looking at me
I wasn't watch the building I am well
you weren't you were looking at me
Ryan I I glanced at you
oh don't watch the building or I will be
my guest
fun and read the paper don't look at me
you know if you've got something you
want to talk about like it off your
chest let's go let's get out of here go
ahead
[Music]
fine regarding the other light all right
here we go yeah that's them let me see
oh I'm looking at them
yeah that's Bobby no
something's coming down coke please
just a simple job bumping Bobby don't do
the shut up do not let this out of your
hands until Jordan
leave my ears alone I know my job fine
just put it down in front of Boyett and
leave
[Music]
all right there goes Bobby you stay with
him huh
so
what's our doesn't matter now if you
know or not the briefcase is a bomb she
sets it down in front of that pond scum
Boyet boom what about Bobby what about
it yeah
[Music]
all right all right I want to call my
lawyer get me a phone I want to call my
lawyer
[Music]
nice mouth not just looking for a friend
yeah bass this is Lester there's a guy
in the main station looks like nobody's
home
[Music]
Wi-Fi as a briefcase it has a bomb
inside gonna Bob would you put it down
just get into this guy's boy yet this
guy man oh yeah I told Ryan to stay with
Vaughn either the traitor they go oh no
don't alright cuz that way
hello Bobby
all right there long time no see
gorgeous he's ever been
I hear you've been getting your kicks by
killing some of my friends Laura Zoey
both dead man has to make a living
it was wrong had to get Jordans
attention I'm in a cash crunch nothing
personal
so it was tomorrow
open the bag when you see what's in it
I hope you choke on it
[Applause]
what are you doing Ryan it's a ball Oh
terrific
I'll cross me thank you double I'm
telling you man she's carrying a ball
[Applause]
baby baby okay I never see me on this
what you want to stay clear that's not
giving me I did know I mean I do but
after what you did for me how can I just
hide it I feel like such a a low-life
gutless pencil-neck geek yeah except you
can't exactly
have here thank you
you just gave me the nails for the man's
coffin you do understand that you got to
be the hammer yeah I understand if these
pictures end up in court don't have to
testify it could come back action from
Felix well that's a chance I'm gonna
have to take
kids data set don't he just
hey hey
how'd you sleep last night great you uh
look can I ask you a question
Haney what happened at your house after
kal'leena after Catalina yes
Mitch after Catalina you really want to
know yes all right
nothing
nothing nothing did you say that was
great
you were great no you said I was great
in bash
Brian you slept in my bed I slept on the
couch nothing happened
really really sighs you made an
agreement when we opened up the agency
not to have our personal and business
lines maple
do you want to change that no wish I'd
never made it as a matter of fact don't
ever make me make those kind of promises
again hello chance
[Music]
we're the race you got to be
come
[Music]
the devil is watching as we
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you