[Music]
[Applause]
you've angel under cover of night
people are drown
in a sea of light
[Music]
the devil hold in your life um
angel : rainbow time
[Music]
[Applause]
there is too late
it burns
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
any more than chicken no more than there
was an hour ago oh god I hate
surveillance that was better than
watching security tape from taking the
liquors well I prefer that than the
sitting in the middle of an asparagus
field for god sakes
besides out we got 30 bucks a tape Mon a
little more time don't forget we catch
this guy we get a 10% recovery
ever since garner got his pee I'll
Ison's he's been waiting for a sign his
life has really changed but so far it's
been long hours short path
bogie two o'clock that's our man big Don
dream come true Donny you know he goes
about 20,000 a month out of that trunk
I always wanted who took the quarters
out of those condom machine big Don it's
a cash business one for the company 1000
we gonna make a fat check on this with
partner all these gotta do is get those
pump shot keys to look the other way
oh he's their dream come true hot
stereos CDs boom boxes
you hear something no to imagination
no it's not I hear something it's quiet
maybe too quiet
[Music]
I hate surveillance hmm
page 1 of the PI handbook says that when
a case goes bad you just dust yourself
off and get ready for the next one you
never know who will come walking through
that door can we help you
I guess so I mean if you're the new
detectives hi how are you hi my name is
Buchanan and this is Ellerbe and you've
already been missed be bribed regular or
up hazelnut DK nickman it's only $2,000
but I guess it's the principal I worked
for that money I want it I know the
feeling
the woman who owes me Francis Cirelli
kept putting me off she's starting some
new business and has expenses and so on
Tuesday she finally agreed to pay and
Wednesday she was gone what kind of work
do you do for her
well you've heard of those 976 numbers
yeah phone sex two bucks a minute I saw
the ads that's what the customer pays I
just get a flat 20 an hour it's acting
they give you scripts and parts the
lonely housewife the teenage nurse you
[Music]
hi baby it's candy oh I was hoping you'd
call
what do you want to talk about and so on
that's very good very good look I was
broke I hadn't worked in a year I'm a
good actress maybe you've seen me on
Days of Our Lives I was in Carson's
nightmare oh yeah you you you were the
one with the straight razor uh you watch
that uh I was on the split ship
I saw an ad in the trades for 976 Heat
I felt creepy about applying and my
boyfriend didn't want me to do it at all
now I just want my money and to just
forget about it
well I'll fill out a standard contract
for you fifty dollars an hour I thought
look I'm sorry I took your time I
thought that I could afford it because
he worked on a 20% contingency but would
you excuse us for a minute please
we just got burden a continuance she's a
client she needs our help we need her
business to even at Nikki Pines right so
gentlemen how about it
I mean money's money
Ms Nichols you have a deal
[Music]
so we took the case and Addie promised
to pursue real acting jobs and give up a
phony sex career hello and you can't
hide from me where is my money you
you owe me friend y'all keep it down
keep it down turn it here
I don't get it you dial the phone number
the answering machine picks up but it
doesn't ring on the other side
well maybe the ringers off Fran Frances
Arella
well who looks at the store the who's
got a big reason to hide she owes people
a lot of money somebody trying to slug
the door I don't touch that looks like
somebody cut a knuckle there's some
staining I'll test it I'll check the
neighbors okay
Hey hmm
excuse me we're looking for friends this
Arella has an office around the corner
hello hello what who are these guys my
name is Mitchell Buchanan and this is my
partner grinder elevate they don't want
nothing mr. sax in fact we do um how
about a polite answer to a polite
question have you seen Frank Cicero
don't know him
310 around the corner if you see her
will you please ask her to call us this
is not it this is not why I became a PI
trolling for deadbeats getting spit on
by guys like that I'm seriously
considering buy the chicken franchise or
something I'm telling you
where's Ryan she's supposed to be at the
car
by random you see but you can leave a
message
hey guys guys up here I found fries
answering machine but it's not the one
that's picking up hey who's this nutcase
[Music]
let's take it easy of coming up wait man
O'Hara leave are you mad at me
[Applause]
[Music]
having two partners isn't always easy
especially when one of them is an
independent woman with her own methods
of solving things sorry Mitch
[Music]
how mighty buddy crows gonna be one
thing I scream free love yeah we prove
that I also prove that somebody's real
nervous about a people like question
yeah let's try this thing off huh
[Music]
it was in mr. stilinski's physics class
where I learned Isaac Newton discovered
the laws of the universe by watching
apples drop out of trees wall number
three every action has an equal and
opposite reaction since then I learned
was true for apples isn't always true
for people did you see who was driving
the truck no no we didn't get a good
look at him
no guy named Steven Saxon I met him I
worked in his bullpen near friends
office why it was the only one we asked
about Fran I mean if it was him II
seriously overreacted what's his problem
crook that's his problem old porn and
sex scenes the same you poke a stick in
their nest they're gonna bite I say
write it off $2,000
Darren hates to admit that we're broke
well we're not he's going to pick up a
roster we'll just look back at this is
her struggling young actress period huh
hell man you can't beat living in Malibu
even if it is the guest house even if we
do have to cut the grass Oh City huh you
got it the owners are traveling as they
say ah nice bike what are you racing
across country
yeah off-road in money three weeks out
of five this year butter blew the [ __ ]
heats up all my winnings you know yeah I
know
back to square one President Clinton's
office you still got it Whistler I
suppose that's against the law
actually about ten of them well better
to use your talents for the good of
society my man yeah some course officer
ellaby hands up just garnered these days
her office number is five five five
eight nine seven six
it rings but not in her office machine
picks up but you can't find it
think you can do it hey piece of cake
but it might be an unlisted number and
if I tell you that would be against the
law wouldn't it look you owe me a favor
I kept you out of jail and got you a job
playing with all this stuff you like
good just call her and tell me what you
can hi it's Fran I'm busy but you can
leave a message
we got us a swing out here pardon me
it's what the our marketing office
refers to is called following the office
phone and the home phone are redirected
to a third number but she's got another
number can you tell me the address it's
not an address it's a mobile see I can
get you even in a quarter mile you know
with interference but you got to take it
from there city saw you the transmission
site 881 that thing up there's our cell
phone antenna
well those things are all over the city
man there's gonna be a lot more of them
beepers cell phones portable fax
machines and those little log computers
the UPS guys carry around they all use
little power radio and lots of antenna
well every call she got in here 27 since
Tuesday all from the sale site which
means she's got to be close by you are
like the sound of this we miss a scruffy
area we got railroad spurs and
warehouses I mean not a place a woman
who'd hang around for three days oh no
thanks no none taken
well that's also not a place a woman
would actually carry around an answering
machine with room and figure that one
out now find her and we will oh yeah now
this this is the gear the proves used to
track illegal equipment now I am told
that with these you can track any
cellular phone in
[Music]
Ryan do you read me yeah I'm right here
go I found her she's in a car loaded a
computer with some sort of voicemail
software just keeps answering her phone
one is still working after three days
yeah which is that I can save her
[Music]
as for the victim she was strangled from
behind I'm going to send this ring to s
ID for a serum series it's got a sharp
stone and under the stone what's
probably blood I think she cut her
killer like this oh hi Dennis
is she yours hey both ah we lost track
of you miss McBride people don't usually
wander down here without a pass
Oh professional courtesy she knows my
best friend back in New York we were
trading recipes Ryan don't forget you
won't be okay I guess I still do for now
I just need the name of your client
oh come on don't start up with that
client privilege crap don't don't go
there
detective if we had any information that
would help you find the killer of
Francis Raleigh we'd give it to you but
we don't sorry I liked you better when
you want our tea in Ghana let me tell
you something for nothing
I'll bet I know who your client is I'll
bet it's one of my two suspects it's
either a head burger with a record name
Stephen Sachs he found missing persons
on her or it's a woman who left ten
angry messages on that computer you
found in the car
Eddie Nichols
well I was happy because detective
Winfield confirmed that our two suspects
were identical to the LAPD's Ryan was
happy because she got some prime corned
beef and Garner well he's just happy
being a PI now we're talking know what
we did the long bye
yeah too long for me you guys seem to
like it in the morgue governor you're
right The Long Goodbye this is a very
special moment it's like our first
client privilege oh please it's a book
by Raymond Channel mhm about a PII who
she was a sky from the coast that man
could write cops never say goodbye
they're always hoping to see you again
in the lineup first detective book I
haven't read Philip Marlowe private eye
you remember bow cockpit
yeah you never gave the cops in it she
stood by his client they beating threw
him in jail
he wouldn't rat on a client never beat
him up today badly yeah black and blue
twice that's why I'm a PI they ever get
the cars money clothes I want to be
there for one person who's counting on
me more than anyone else our client
I'll meet you back at the office
[Music]
so you founder UPI stick to it I'll give
you that
don't you want to report that to
insurance company you know sending a
message to Snoopy privatise isn't
covered with my policy why'd you care
what we're looking for
I mean you filed a missing persons
report on her yourself
why'd you lie to me about knowing her
why not
you
Haymitch daddy in there and just heard
about Fran
guys okay I'm scared the bullies want to
talk to me how can you suspect daddy
she couldn't strangle anybody she hasn't
got the strength well actually it
doesn't take much I mean with the
element of surprise and the right grip
any adult can crush someone's trachea
but why would I do that well Fran olya
next to hate section do money's the best
motive there is sorry it is what the
cops think I mean we're on your side
they're also talking to Stephen Sachs
what's his mother I don't know his
office was in the bullpen where worked
but I never got near it she did the
hiring form but remember I told you that
she was starting a new business there
you go another good motive competition
can we get into his honours hello it's
in use around the clock the only ones
who get in are Sachs and the girls on
the phones exactly are they hiring for
the phones always for the phones now
you're talking go into his bullpen under
cup how who oh no oh no no not at all
you're not getting me to go up there I
can't do that
sure you can it's easy you want me to go
up there and talk too much as socially
crippled mouth-breathers no way that is
not for me
oh how divine a phone sex operator
mother will be so proud okay quit
whining me bride deal with it
Oh
hi this is candy may I help no no no
that's not gonna turn anybody on
especially these mouth breathers mm-hmm
breath breath that's key word here okay
mmm hi this is candy can I there works
can I help you
so um what's your name Oh Mitch huh
Wow that name just drives me wild so
Mitch tell me what you look like and
don't leave out any vital statistics uh
oh what's that sound oh that's me
wishing you were here so I can blow in
your ear Oh Mitch mm Oh Mitch you're so
wonderful kiss me
boom please just just kiss me Oh would
be so Oh
hi how long were you uh I was rehearsing
mm-hmm
okay so now we both know I can't cut it
as one of these phone sex bimbos
I sound like mr. ed with asthma haha
actually I thought she sounded kind of
sexy oh yeah go on
really really thanks but I can't be like
that with some weirdo I don't even know
yes you can
I can't yes you can I won't 976 ouch
that's a specialty bit and we don't
normally recommend the new girls start
on that one why don't we break you in on
the teenage nurse shy schoolgirl
dangerous ain't hurt [ __ ] up here
standard candy and what does the
standard candy do fifty-five minutes an
hour and a five-minute break no food at
the desk
can't talk dirty with your mouth full
huh just kidding don't let mr. sexy
reading or so in and you'll be just fine
oh he sometimes monitors the calls so no
private stuff
okay
[Music]
Oh
how do you read not clear Ryan you sound
tense relax we'll be fine okay hear a
phone ring yeah me too
well answered I'm not looking forward to
this
okay here we go hi this is kandi may I
help you
[Music]
you're disgusting Pig oh no no no no no
no don't listen to what they say just
just keep talking this is candy onion
has about ten okay um
fantasize you're locked up in a room
alone with uh Clark Gable
there's a Clark Gable a little too old
for you guys never mind just fantasize
okay there's a phone go for it go for it
hi uh oh
this is candy how can I help you well
sure
yeah yeah me too not really
really what are you wearing I really
can't make it you with me really where
are you now
[Music]
what do you always have a
tell me for having you too much thank
you
[Music]
Hey
be able to hear what I hear
[Music]
whatever you want to
and then I want you to carry me to the
bedroom
[Music]
no do you
whatever
[Music]
standby I'm going for it
[Applause]
my problem I'm in
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
okay where's the office allele that's in
the back
[Music]
two months ago Fran told me she was
going independent I wished her luck she
was gonna need it this is a rough
business but despite what you think it
is a business it's a sick business I
just been an hour talking to your
customers they're pack of howling
weirdos well you may not like what they
have to say but the FCC and the Supreme
Court say they have the right
unlike breaking into my office so you
were just waiting in here I took a good
look at you you weren't quite right so I
came back in through the private door
from the hall now you couldn't not oh of
course
cops do have you on there mr. suspect so
it looks good to play yeah what open
house I get the feeling you weren't too
upset about Fran leaving she ran all
kinds of games on people if she wanted
to Welsh on somebody's salary she'd make
a tape of their phone calls now nobody
likes to listen and hear himself being
the hurt me girl maybe that's what she
did to your client no we saw her office
door honey people were angry besides
Eddie tell me about I even saw one guy
put his fist through the wood you saw
that well I heard him yelling for us or
some guy trying to grow a beard he was
really ticked off
while I was fram for you she could drive
anybody nuts
[Music]
still an old story my wife wants corned
beef no no no thanks what's is this
gonna be hello
it's a woods funner from the hole in the
door hmm I got a blood type on it send
it to the lab DNA testing takes months
so I'm hoping I can get a prize well
maybe we'll get nothing
hmm we'll be lucky to get lucky oh no
that is a fillip model 9 yeah we could
use mr. Marlowe at this point we're all
getting at his money back is one thing
getting her life back is quite another
yeah things like that again hello
anybody home
good thing you didn't use that voice at
the phone sex operator god I was
terrible wasn't I no mama you were
wonderful no I was terrible what did
anybody hang up on you no I hung up on
them well there you go yeah actually I
guess I wasn't that bad huh hey big boy
boo you sound really hot I just love to
eat you up with a spoon I just no no no
not you no sorry ray no um could you
come up with any finger prints for me
you're kidding
all right you're the best thanks a lot
okay I owe you one we have a print and
an owner does he have a beard Newton was
a smart man he knew for every action
there is an equal and opposite reaction
that is the more you try to keep
something bottled up the worse it wants
to get out Annie will you please stop we
got to talk about this what's left to
talk about I still don't think that it's
my fault you went to work for those
cretins not me
yeah I went to work work I get the
feeling you think I was hooking or
something Darren oh who cares anyway I'm
a suspect in a murder that's what's
important know what's important is your
career and getting back to it I'll get
back to it first they have to find who
killed Fran you shut up about Fran who
cares about a dead woman we do
how long have you been listening long
enough to hear how Darren wants you to
live your life she's had it with you to
consider yourselves fired
Darren thinks it's better for the police
to handle it do you know what blood
serum is how are you doing this is a
piece of wood take him from Francis
rally's office didn't I tell you to get
out of here Darren let me hear this long
story short the blood type of the hand
of the guy that punched in the door at
Fran's office matches the blood type of
her killer you see while the killer took
Fran she thought she was wearing a ring
that got him like that and when you're
being chucked from behind you can only
reach her killer in a few places the
head in the face oh I'll bet she cut you
down stop it you're crazy
ah you follow daddy on Tuesday and after
she left you're the one that killed Fran
I didn't see the cuts on your knuckles I
missed him the other day because the
grease
I did it for you a she had tapes
[Music]
he's on his way Roger that
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
it can blow your dreams
there's a race
[Music]
Oh
in the penguin the devil is watching as
[Music]
[Applause]
call
[Music]
[Applause]