hey I'm sorry man and to give me her yet
I wouldn't come back I left my jacket in
the car take a Z kids no problem really
it's in the car yeah yeah but it's cool
man has forgot on you know hey come on
kid don't be silly no big deal
get your jackets alright man
scared the hell out they told me no
matter what I do I'm not supposed to
beer when you showed up you know just
leave the car and split I saw you I
don't know I'm just glad it's cool
oh yeah it's cool okay but you know the
next time somebody tells you to do
something do it
yes sir okay
cheap-ass jacket wasn't worth your life
kid
in a city of angels under cover of night
people are drown in a sea of light
in your life um
we do luck : rainbow time
there is too late
it burns
it's gonna live
alright hey thanks for doing this for me
- I really appreciate ribs say that
again and I'm leaving he only asked me
to do this because we knew I wouldn't
charge a real model would want money
you're cheap Grif I am not cheap okay I
am broke now there's a difference you
know in fact I wish I did have money so
I can show people just how generous I am
yeah well I Ward this but I brought
these in case you want something
beautiful um no no it's gone it's
perfect okay
Hey oh hey hey guys fishing you guys are
going fishing yeah I'm gonna trying to
talk Mitch into this for weeks
okay let's just do it okay okay here's
what I need you to do reach into that
bucket pull out that bottle okay what do
you see just your hand just my hand yeah
Grif you have me out your dress like
this for my hand uh yeah that's all the
shot calls for well you ready what
nothing nothing let's just shoot it yeah
okay a little bit of left there you go
oh that's beautiful so why are we
meeting him here we could have met him
at night or in the office that said he
wanted the meeting innocuous he said
that people might be watching you since
he fishes every morning seems to work
anyway what difference does it make
where we meet him guys don't us a heck
of a lot of favors meet him anywhere he
wants all right no no don't you hate it
fishing I could have chose something
else who say I hated fishing I'm a great
fisherman Thanks wait I forget is this
gonna have to be irca FBI okay thanks
okay you're the full day hey guys thanks
for coming
you look very stressed all right so
what's this all about everything we say
is confidential
I'm looking for a man by the name of
Bradley Thurman I have reason to believe
that he's somewhere in this Cubs arrived
a couple of days ago right
freighter private yacht how do you know
that just gonna have to take my word for
it
Thurman ran 401k plans for an Arizona
mutual fund ran off with a hundred
million in bearer bonds we tracked him
to Belize we had him and we lost and we
found out of year all kinds of plastic
surgery mints this guy's built himself a
whole new identity
now we're really sure there's somewhere
around here with his new face and a very
very big bank room why here
oh you know he's a an action junkie you
know fast cars faster women son and fun
kind of got that kind of thing you lying
around for a while then move on
everybody's after this guy what makes
you think we can find it before you guys
too well you know the area besides your
contacts are completely different from
ours people trust you all right give me
everything you got on this guy and we
find out anything we'll let you know in
an interval I need you to be really
proactive on this one this isn't a favor
you helped uncle nail this guy and
whatever we recover you'll get 20% hey
you gotta fight you'll bite that's a lot
of money but that's for a conviction
nope based on whatever we recover so
could be nothing right he's all and let
him run I am letting him run but it
could be right tighten the drag will you
relax
don't let him go underneath the pier
look I gotta get out of here
there's the files on them everything you
need to know is right here read it mom
you got
my net
look at something whoa
what is it dinner hey where are you
girls from wanna go get a couple of snow
cones you know where there's some real
good ones
daddy you girls don't like snow cones
making a lot of noise yeah but those
girls were pretty enough to deserve some
noise
I had some problems
I heard kick came back to the car he was
told not to
I got pictures aligned in an address
everything's about set you dulled for a
few days and we're ready to go
Wow
whatever it is it sure smells great yep
yet why'd you stir the result own make
sure those are stale wait a minute I
didn't tell you how to fish you don't
tell me how to cook risotto him any
heart on the skirt yeah actually yeah
here's a what he looks like when he left
New York now these are all computerized
portraits of what he could look like now
with surgery gain or loss of voice
Entertainer huh wasting time if the FBI
had one turned him into a Doberman
Pinscher I'd seen them all on the mall
yesterday
well the FBI file that Ned gave me was
more psychological oh good you can
change the face but you can't change the
man Oh Sherlock can you tell me about
this mr. Thurman well most of it's an
obvious type-a personality when at any
cost loves the competition loves the
good life the action well there are lots
of places on the planet where a man with
money can find what he's looking this is
ready let's eat
Yeah right she was smoking catch it
clean cook oh wow there's something to
be said for Pioneer stock the risotto
was pretty good
got it ain't it cooked so tell us more
about our guy right um okay well he
wants to be noticed he wants to be
respected um he's a very bad winner and
an even worse loser he went to to
physically dominate men conquer women uh
his entire persona is wrapped up in
competition all physical action
one-on-one macho stuff I just say what
his game is yeah um racquetball tennis
squash anything with a racket was the
guy loved to spend money but he knows
that the FBI is gonna be watching all
the legitimate car dealerships major
department stores for extra-large cash
purchases so he'll be buying off the
street all right I'm sure you can cover
that but grannies quilt say listen I'd
love to stay and help you guys do the
dishes but I gotta talk to some folks
about who's new and who's spinning loft
well while you're doing that I'm gonna
go talk to Ned because we don't have the
full story here he's hiding something
Donna hey good hey I got the first bag
that you might like to see them remember
the other day when you said you admire
Ryan Mitch maybe he's the one that's the
great light I mean just non-stop one
great thing after another
maybe great to do a photo essay on yeah
I got like a day and a night in the life
of Mitch Buchannon what do you think you
better ask him first gonna know what you
do is you take the pictures first okay
and then I'll show me if he doesn't like
him will tossing hey don't wanna see
your crews oh I'm sure they're great but
I've seen my hand
yeah well the client is gonna love them
that's not like three okay believe it
down yeah I think I got what you're
looking for but that's about half the
guys in a beachy yeah I mean visitors
well this guy be new you know maybe less
than a week pretty visible and athletic
yeah there's a guy been around the last
couple of days he fits tennis a guy
around Johnny's a pool hustler no no no
more physical and there's a lot of no
muscle that's around but he'll even I
can't flock all out
wait
what about racquetball what Easton very
aggressive runs off a lot of the
mountain walk me over yeah yeah
georgeanna v okay your source won't even
get out of the gate never get out of it
except you got company
rid of that damn thing is a cup
where's Lauren talk award I'm not on the
force anymore
haven't you then hike I'm out of here
you're not a cop I deal with you well
I'm not a cop but you do have to do
wrong the rules don't apply
you got no juice so there's nothing to
trade I gotta be honest with you when I
was on the force boy I hated guys like
you I think you know everything you sell
here stop hey you heard him no warrant
no way you're getting in there stolen
from some poor soul was probably
terrorized maybe even
hey wait a minute hey wait a minute
yeah when the thieves sold it to you boy
you didn't care about it at pac-man I'm
looking for a new place in town sure
lots of cash only by weight a knack kick
it away
top of the line
what oh she got this nice little joy huh
he'd be looking for a big screen a box
fine bird Oh Oh buddy
sure would be interested in a hot new
set of wheels wait maybe maybe I know
guy who fits you're crazy you know that
well that was quick got something I went
through his profile now either the
profile is incorrect or you didn't give
us enough information sermons not here
on some vague hot night in the city he's
too specific if you don't tell us what's
going on we can't help you can't do that
why not cuz it took an oath you took
enough what are you a priest now no but
there are lives that depend on my
keeping that oath you coming to us to
find this guy's personal isn't it when I
went through his file I noticed there
was a wife and child after the
arraignment there's no mention of them
there's no address no nothing does him
being here have anything to do with that
wife and child
yeah
so she didn't testify against him but
she blew the whistle testified for the
grand jury
and now she's in some variation of the
witness protection program but somehow
he found out where she is which I can
understand how that happens because
those people are so careful unless
somebody goofed
now did you goof
yeah
we goofed
and now he knows where she is and he
wants to kill her take his daughter
well we need to go tell Mitch before he
gets in over his head
there's a guy in depression nope
well here about a week there you Monica
oh what a real core Diana
he gets on nobody can't get him and
that's me next victim hey my man we'll
play all right send him in here let him
take his whipping like a man hey kick
his butt
hey Eddie you mind if I borrow your
rocket for a few minutes no problem
thanks Mitch hello well it might not be
much competition for you yeah that's
alright what the hell it's nothing but
something to do right name's Mitch I'll
let you sir
okay yeah
hey Han de Paul Hindemith locked you out
that's illegal
hey come on what do you arrest here you
want to call a hinder nah play on just
so we both know the rules
oh sorry man
gonna hinder
13 a way to government yeah I should
have some money on this
that sound that's now I get some going
game boy let's go let's go
yeah yeah way to go come on let's go
again right now you want some action on
this
I'll cover whatever it is you want come
on let's go I gotta get going
hey nice Rock nice work Thanks
gizmo's heard about this place huh
that's pretty hot get some chalk on the
street yeah that's too bad it's cool for
a while but then she flirts find out
about it then you get a move on you know
what I mean you gotta check it out and
maybe I'll see you there
anything's possible
acts like you better know Fred Thanks
that was I need this guy checked out huh
where he drives where he goes where he
does anything even get huh good all
right stay out of jail we yeah uh-huh
Nasri where the hell are you been you
owe me money
Oh
oh hey boss the guy's been taking my
picture
find out why let's go
don't let him get away
Cobra you're on the way get out the way
you
see ya
stupid idiot hey what what is wrong with
you what is wrong with you stupid idiot
what is wrong with you how do you let
him out of your sight
you're stupid idiot you're a stupid
idiot
I got a lot on a couple of guys but
instead mine's a definite maybe
yeah stronger than a maybe couple of his
guys let's try to rough me up
what cuz I took his picture why would
you do that
why because I thought you guys might
want them Ned about Thurman's wife and
daughter can he get to them well I'm
making arrangements to have him moved of
course you realize this is just gonna
buy some time I mean eventually if he
spends the money he'll find him Mitch
how sure are you about this guy you bet
I'd like Ryan to check him out I told
him I be at this dance club tonight and
want to make sure I get his attention
I asked Donna to come along too good
garna meanwhile why don't you and I go
check out your guy and then we'll meet
you later god
this is the name and address I got from
my fence he's new spending a lot of cash
no visible source of income well he's
got good taste I give him that that does
fit the profile
so you're the federal officer how would
you have us well usually when we get a
suspect we get a phone tap credit check
bill the file no time for that mitch is
waiting we got to nominate this guy I
take him off the ballot okay what would
a local cop do either get inside or get
him outside break in oh man I don't know
about that we could mess up his fancy
car
well that would get him outside but what
if he's not our guy pretty mean thing to
do but wait a minute snow days
maybe it's the housekeeper
oh that's not our guy bye and love
doesn't fit
oh my god check out all the toys come on
let's get out of here
it's just doing
if I get you another drink
thank you well don't be obvious but he's
correctly over your shoulder
well I can see why you weren't hurry
this afternoon ladies
ladies you two are beautiful enough to
die for I have to tell you you know I
could swear that you and I have met
somewhere I don't think so
and I usually remember when I'm
interested
welcome to gizmos we're here to dance
dance dance party party party is
everybody ready for a good time let me
hear ya
mooch Kenneth
maybe okay
let's give them something to talk about
is he watching her it wasn't me oh
thanks Roger
it is this is the house
okay let's go
stay on the side
fabulous
so what do you think does he fit like a
glove
all right the ganas Turner's dancing to
calling the cap wait don't you wants to
be here when all the action starts
that's right I go why cuz you're favored
gonna get hurt
yes well do you want to dance no I don't
it's FBI ma'am that judge sent us you
have to change locations I know it's
sudden but it's for your own safety
okay not a word not the word
did you uh I had no idea
beautiful give me something
don't be scared
we drew a blank so where's your guy
right over he's gone all the way right
now we got to find this guy I look on
the side
I'll check the Co room all right I'll
get the balcony
pick up
no luck no answer Mitch he got her I
gotta call this in
no not yet whatever by the time they get
their asking you what went wrong it's
gotta be out of the country what's the
fastest most secure way out of here
private jet
let me see you from mimic some calls
private jets international registry
let's find out detective there are four
planes leaving one Santa Monica one
Burbank to LAX all right I got Santa
Monica what's the guy up on goober gonna
find who calls in huh hey garner we've
been looking all night still no luck
how about you no luck here either I just
checked Burbank Thurman's not there
all right we're still de la axe Ned's
checking the rosters have you heard from
Mitch nothing I called no answer okay
why don't you hit that way just in case
right I'm on my way
come on let's go No
huh
there's nothing be scared of sweetheart
oh honey daddy's got you yeah this is
gonna be fun
where's that pilot should be here no one
pay the guy a lot of money to be on time
firing okay let's go yeah huh well you
see that big beautiful airplane you're
gonna take a little trip on that to your
brand-new home what do you think of a
sweetheart and yes come on let's get
right a minute even go hey go right on
in there
what are you doing there's this car
alright you stay in the car
what and just wait get on the phone call
Ryan and jela we found him but just stay
in the car alright
hey it's me
yeah we found him Brits Santa Monica
hangar 8 great we're on our way
they found him great where Santa Monica
Airport angry
Oh
bitch
I thought I told you to stay in the car
yeah I know but riot oh hey hey hey
thanks
hey thank you guys for cluding us you
know you didn't have to
yeah but not that doesn't mean one
accepted Donna you may not need mine but
I do do you know the potential is 20
million dollars I mean 20 million well
that depends on what we recovered okay
so it's Stan so it's fine I'm gonna get
in top again hey you're here
hey guys hey gonna check lay it on us
get each other to the UH absolutely
it's incredible four hundred fifty eight
dollars and 97 cents
four hundred and fifty eight dollars and
97 cents look that's 20 percent of what
we've recovered everything else is
either missing or too deep ever find
what is 458 dollars divided by five Ryan
ninety one sixty ninety one sixty hmm
not bad first money I've made as a
private eye Hey
it can blow you
there's a place
we
in the penguin
the camel is watching every slide
to the years