[Music]
[Applause]
in a City of Angels under cover of night
people don't drown in a sea of light
[Music]
holdin your life um
angel :
rainbow time
[Music]
[Applause]
or is Julie
[Music]
[Applause]
I was going to live
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
we're gonna split up me to the pier Who
am I
later I want it now we thought to get
out of here
[Music]
here we are lab sunset reef best place
for lobster
don't forget Willie never forget just
past the pier left at China Cove water
so clear you can see forever all right
back in a Jif
[Music]
why don't you play here by the shul I'll
be back before you know it I think I
might be the Sun casts a day soon we're
gonna live in a real one I love you son
I'm not here today
[Music]
where have you been where's the money
the police were everywhere I have to
ditch the money we're in an alley a
garbage can
you're lying um I'm not a swear on what
is life I wouldn't lie to my own brother
the hell you wouldn't
now
take it easy
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
well he where's the money where of you
and your daddy bean will he listen to
your uncle I'll
[Music]
[Applause]
things can happen to you as a child that
are so terrifying you block them out of
your memory forever if your Willie Logan
you live by your wits your talent and
your friendship with a mentor
unfortunately memories have a way of
surfacing again even terrifying memories
can come back when you least expect them
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
you
and
[Music]
[Laughter]
Oh
okay hey not bad day trick a very good
day sir
whoa out of here you have a math
assignment I've gotta get the painting
time a wedding
Hannah bar mitzvah what a mess rich
Breck we're on that road brick honey on
that road
[Music]
I don't think it's naphtha alright
go
[Applause]
[Music]
quick hide I'll see it home okay
[Applause]
[Music]
where's the boy tell me or I'll kill you
the difference between being a lifeguard
and a private eye is that a lifeguard
has to spot trouble and respond Private
Eye gets hired by someone who's already
in trouble either way a stranger's life
is suddenly in your hands
unfortunately private eyes can't always
spot the victims as easily as lifeguards
ah
hey you missed a spot really yeah we're
out there anywhere see this pot here his
mind you want to park here it cost you
five dollars no no no our rent includes
two parking spaces yeah it does I'll be
anywhere you want a park oh come on Lou
this is a very expensive car if I park
it out there it could get dinged that's
why I don't park mine out there don't
you understand your car's not even here
today didn't drive today then nobody's
using your spot unless they give me
violence wait you didn't drive today
how'd you get here
yeah Betty got a love being the owner
man yeah I like open meets free cannon
well you just found out you're a private
eye right sure AM my name is Willie
Simon well what can I do for you we'll
examine how my dad didn't come home last
night and I was just wondering if you
could help me find him step into my
office
hey sugar
I don't know how much a private eye cost
but you can have this Willie the guy who
chased you and grabbed you do you know
who he is
no she call the police ah didn't listen
kids where's your mom she is sick in bed
um here's a picture of my dad
his name's Ned Simon I'm really worried
about him will you find him well we're
gonna need a signed contract signed by
an adult I tell you what I'll drop you
off your your mom can sign
where's she live uh 105 Seth Firestone
but she's not there she's at a sister's
place my auntie ins I thought she said
that she was home sick in bed yeah she's
sick in bed at onions place so I'll give
you the contracts and get her to sign it
how much do you charge
well our usual fee is $3 an hour very
low overhead a one hours deposit is
customary okay
we'll bill the Rose to you after we find
her dad all right
see ya yeah huh she's sick in bed at
Auntie m's house
this isn't Kansas toto three on down two
moves card town 105 so far astern yeah
what's the deal
bogus little bullet well we're on the
payroll why are we Kahlan hey I'll take
these pictures around see if anyone's
seen the missing Ned to Simon do it want
a Chevy one a fool that old car making
you bull hurry on down the mers car town
105 off I told ya
[Music]
huh what do you think baby who is it hey
buddy its Bhishma canon open up hey
thought you lived at 105 South Firestone
oh no my lives in lolly pee Oh who's
this my mom that's your mom huh that's
kind of funny cuz I have a picture of
your mom in my house too what do you
mean well the other day when I was
shopping for picture frames this exact
same person was in those picture frames
isn't that weird so is your name really
Willy Willy
[Applause]
[Music]
don't let it get away I'm not letting
him he's doing it all by himself
look there okay
[Music]
okay so now where do we look anywhere
but here all right let's split up
I'll take Venice I'll take Paris
[Music]
instead of going to Europe we went to
Child Protective Services I recognized a
child who's the man that's Ned Simon the
boy's father
I thought certainly it's not the boy's
father no he's been ID'd on the beach he
is a musician he is Ned Simon
he may be Ned Simon but he's not the
child's father why is that
Willie Simon no it's not it's with a
Logan are you sure certainly I'm not
surprised that the name is Logan know
that she's certain hmm he's been in the
system since 1988 and Logan Willie T
father Victor died when the child was 5
years old what about the mother Marlene
died during the birth of the child kids
had a pretty tough the child has made it
tough for all of us who work in the
system it's burdensome he's been placed
in foster homes time and time again and
every time he runs away
it is so troublesome now we haven't come
across him for the past 18 months where
is he we don't know and to be honest
with you miss Belle de if we did we
wouldn't tell you we'll find him we
can't have him running around the
streets with some vagabond musician can
we well catch him and when we do we will
place him in a foster home again and
he'll run away again
sooner or later most certainly I don't
like your attitude
I don't like yours either miss Belle de
I don't even like you really I don't
either
thank you
you know may I just be my guest
thank you the child is not just a
burdensome case file nor is he
troublesome he is just a scared little
boy that got lost in a bad shuffle and
he along with everyone else on the
planet except for you wants to be loved
by everybody else am I done doesn't feel
like you miss Belle de are a sourpuss
constipated and I hope that is your only
excuse for acting like this Butthead
there all done
open the rap stars oh I ran the name
moving through the computer and I who
were the colossal company I did I doubt
you know I think I had the gigantic bird
er
so would you get I got the normal a
double cheese monster no no in the
computer
oh well with his dad was bad guy so what
his uncle Victor Logan and his brother
Lyle robbed a bank about 70 years ago
got 400 grand Wow
they later they found victory with 238
loves his brother why for them there
hey y'all nobody knows they nabbed uncle
Lyle for the robbery he did a few years
in San Quentin down for your
entertainment pleasure huh
he was released four days ago well he's
got to be the guy who's after Ned and
Willie you guys we gotta find Willie now
let's go
now I'm asking you nicely where's the
boy not gonna tell you never okay
touching it so stupid do you realize
what you're saying
huh you value his life more than your
own go ahead kill me you no good me dead
once you're almost dead I'm gonna use
you as bait to find the boy
Oh
[Music]
you
the word on the street was that net was
in the hospital and since never was the
closest Willie had the family I had a
feeling the little guy might be there
[Music]
you've got to get better
I just got it you're me you were team
freakin fret remember please wake up
come on let's go home together promise I
promise I'll keep up for my studies my
bed you're all of God don't leave me
love you
[Music]
it's okay he's okay trust me Hey look oh
why don't we let him get some rest
come on
I'll take this jump in
[Music]
hey do young
be ready to me
[Music]
I'll put the sauce on top to zoom the
sauce I always saw surly you fork don't
you I beg your pardon
Oh stalled forks poke holes in the skin
that's the juicer
how often do you talk every three
minutes not four not to in fact now so
when do you sauce with its time
you're doing this drive me crazy aren't
you uh-huh is it working
yeah I think so
[Laughter]
Willy go long ha ha no good hey egg ah
just talked to the hospital
hmm he is in serious but stable
condition you know where Oh Fabian I
know all about you in there pretty tight
huh yeah he's been taking care of me for
the Posche yeah and I can show him all
right it's been teaching me stuff we're
not both talking I even eat carrots now
all right so like yeah I know
catching a minute huh okay I think you
should stay at my place for a while
safer what if he decides to ease on down
the road again
well we'll just have to ease on down
after him I'll put this tracking device
on his belt
[Music]
ever known Assam music triggers memories
memories of your childhood funny how
music can bring back memories from long
ago and far away
[Music]
better soon
run
[Music]
[Applause]
I was really beautiful Willie yeah I
took me to a very nice place partner
how'd you get so good in that thing
anyway practice usually got a lot of
time to myself
my real father oh he wasn't around all
that much I can't even remember what it
looks like and my mom hmm the Blues
who's the best BB King oh yeah I have
this dream that I get to jam with him
huh just a dumb dream yeah that he named
his guitar he calls it Lucille
it must be a very special lady your name
for your acts Marlene Marlene
[Music]
let's go get up point
perfect
[Music]
the cashews
hey where the troops I don't know I I
just got up a few minutes ago Orion's
cars outside well maybe they went for
wrong Willie's on the moon
[Music]
Willie $400,000 Willie where is it I
don't know after the job we split up and
your father took the money according to
plan
you killed my dad and I'll show you what
hey I'll kill you get on tell me where
it is wise little bug is telling the
truth you should be right over
you know what I think no I don't want
you maybe yeah I think even here I hate
it
I'll get the flashlights but I hate
you know secondhand smoke kills too well
that's the least of your problems you
see this controls the water level in the
reservoirs in the Santa Monica Mountains
in a very very rainy winter thousands of
gallons of water rushed through here
three times a day in fact there's a
release due in a few minutes at 9:05
exactly and if you don't cooperate I'll
walk out of here you drown
flashlights always remind me of that
movie et remember the guy with the keys
in the woods but don't talk about movies
why not cuz I just saw Jurassic Park
scared me to death
Jurassic park's not a scary movie
evasion of the Body Snatchers that's a
Syrian moves you stop talking about
scary movies what are you scared I'm not
scared I'm trying to focus on a calm
place a babbling brook apart at
something Jurassic Park
see you remember if you try keep going
uh we went out in the dingey she told me
to wait
we went to go get lobsters for dinner
and he took this box with him we didn't
bring it back and he didn't have any
lobsters either yeah but where did you
go in the dinghy way out and we always
go for lobsters sunset reef
check me there why wait a minute what
about me but what you think you can't
just leave me down here
I like mobster too
please all right guys please
[Music]
hey guys over here I'm over here alright
yeah that was that was uncle Lyle he
killed Willie's father and he's taking
really to get some money okay what back
what time is it is something ever 9s
what time exactly it is 905 exactly then
that would be water
come on
that rate
let's go
[Music]
just past the pier
let the China Cove one so clearly see
forever
just past the pier
the China car
[Music]
Gordon I'm a 1 from the Coast Guard
and PD on alert we're in your way
[Music]
will a okay let's go ah
alright you hang here I'm going after it
[Music]
you
ah
hi-yah
[Music]
you
[Applause]
cops all around how would i Scout myself
but we have to be ethical
or what would it mean Oh
would you give your name
[Music]
[Applause]
not a bad day prick
very good die Freck
[Music]
there's he here yeah buddy so are you
gonna tell them our own
tell me what well uh Mitch garner and
Ryan here bill went to bat for us courts
willing to let me adopt you you get to
be my dad
forever and a day
[Music]
excuse me ladies and gentlemen excuse me
is there Willie Logan in the house
no but there's a really Simon all right
well it's Simon hey let's give Willie
Harry I want to come up and bring your
guitar and play of your nose force these
gentlemen
Willie Simon
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
you
[Music]
[Applause]
pretty key right here you can play Mayor
John an O play me yes sir
is this a Jane mr. kair it could be but
dreams do come true mr. Sylar can we jam
let's get it on will you say
[Applause]
[Music]
all night long
honey Rock
[Music]
not backing down
can blow your dreams
we're the race
[Music]
[Applause]
the penguin the devil is watching
[Music]
[Applause]
here
[Music]
you