Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
[Judy in Spanish]
[chuckles]
[in English] You gotta
be fucking kidding me.
[in Spanish]
[Fidel]
[door opens]
[Judy sighs]
Mmm.
[vehicle approaches, stops]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
[sighs]
[Steve] Life goes on, right?
And for Escobar, that
was a pretty good thing.
He remained at large, protected
by an army of sicarios...
in a city that refused
to give him up.
Pablo kept his lawyers
working overtime...
continuing to negotiate
his surrender
with Colombian Attorney
General De Greiff.
But it was bullshit.
Why surrender when you're
holding all the cards?
He was free. And
business was booming.
LEADER OF THE SEARCH BLOC KILLED
For those of us tasked
with catching Escobar,
Carrillo's death was
a punch in the gut.
- [chatter in Spanish over radio]
- But life went on for us as well.
Centra Spike was still
busy gathering intel.
The brass was still
reviewing and approving it.
And it was still
finding its way to us.
But, shit, man...
you can have all the
intelligence in the world,
but if nobody's there to
act on it, what's it worth?
Nothing.
All it adds up to is a
growing stack of unread files
on a dead man's desk.
We were back where
we started: nowhere.
- [upbeat Latin music plays on radio]
- [in Spanish]
[Pablo]
[chuckles]
[sports chatter over radio]
[Pablo]
[upbeat Latin music playing on radio]
[chuckles]
[in Spanish]
[in English] You're breaking
my fucking heart, baby.
[in Spanish]
- [Connie speaks indistinctly]
- [in English] She's good with kids.
I'm so sorry for your
loss, Mrs. Carrillo.
I keep wondering if it's
better to know the truth.
I don't follow.
The things they said about my husband,
about what he did before he was killed.
Did he shoot a child?
Did he kill that boy like
they said on the news?
No. Absolutely not.
Your husband
did everything in his
means to get Escobar.
But he did not cross the line.
Well, that was rough.
- I just kept looking at her, thinking...
- Hey.
It's not gonna happen to me,
it's not gonna happen to us.
You want me to come home?
Just make sure you're still
you when it's all over.
So three years in the
jungles fighting FARC.
Hugo Martinez chose his
own path a long time ago
and he hasn't deviated from it since.
He's methodical, favors
procedure and strict protocol.
Do you think you can get him to do it?
[Steve] How do you get a man
to take a job that nobody wants?
Don't get me wrong.
There was no shortage of brave men
in the Colombian National Police.
But signing up to replace Carrillo
as the head of the Search Bloc
would take a lot
more than bravery.
Gaviria couldn't count on
someone raising their hand.
It would take a certain kind of
pressure to find the right volunteer.
[in Spanish]
[applause]
[Gaviria]
[band plays up-tempo patriotic music]
[crowd applauds]
[upbeat Latin music plays on radio]
- Carlos!
- Tata!
[chuckles]
[Carlos]
[Steve] Business was pretty good.
And a large part of that was due
to a guy they called the Lion.
You might remember him
as a Medellín hustler
who used to stuff bricks of cocaine into
his jacket and smuggle them into Miami.
Well, he stayed in Miami
and he made it his town.
[woman moans]
[Steve] He was responsible
for a smuggling network
that brought in Pablo's cocaine
by the ton. He was great at it.
But getting cocaine into the
States wasn't really the problem.
The problem was, what do
you do with all that money?
Sure, some of it could
stay in the States.
And the narcos did that.
They bought crooked banks,
real estate, car dealerships,
race horses, art, you name it.
But if you're gonna
run a cocaine empire,
you need to have a
lot of cash on hand.
And getting cash back
into Colombia wasn't easy.
Let me put it this way:
This is what a ton of
cocaine looks like.
And here's what the same
ton of cocaine looks like
when it's converted into cash.
See the problem?
Lion had to be creative with
how he got that money to Pablo.
And he was. His shipments
showed up like clockwork.
But the deeper Pablo went into
his war with the government...
the more important
these shipments were.
Pablo needed more
money than ever.
Without it, he was fucked.
[in Spanish]
[scoffs]
[phone rings]
[in English] Okay, here we go.
[engine starts]
[chatter in Spanish]
[dialing phone]
[man in Spanish]
[sighs deeply]
[mutters]
[in English] Oh, shit. That's Velasco.
[in Spanish]
[Trujillo]
[dials phone]
[line ringing]
[Trujillo]
[Javier]
[Carlos]
[automatic gunfire nearby]
[men shouting]
[man whimpering]
[man grunts]
Hey!
[door opens]
[gunfire]
[grunts]
[Latin music plays softly on radio]
[in English] Mr. Ambassador,
I believe people fall into
two categories, basically:
those who rely on hope...
and those who rely on faith,
who see a system at work in
the world and are devoted to it.
It may be religion,
but in the case of
police work, a method.
I'm guessing that you
fall on the faith side.
Correct.
We can catch Escobar
in any number of ways.
But if the one we choose
furthers an already
strained relationship
between the Colombian
people and its police,
a strain caused by years
of corruption and abuse,
then we'll have lost.
Even if we catch him.
Your philosophy is our
philosophy, Colonel.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Thank you very much.
- [Crosby] Good to sit down with you.
- Mr. Ambassador,
the whole world is
watching how we handle this.
I won't allow it to be corrupted by...
outside interests or darker instincts.
[in Spanish]
[starts engine]
[Don Berna]
[grunts, breathing heavily]
[screaming]
[sighs]
[people chuckling, chattering nearby]
[in English] Let's go. Get in.
[in Spanish]
[whistles softly]
[Pablo]
- [chuckles]
- [laughing]
[men murmuring]
[Blackie]
[upbeat Latin music plays on radio]
[Carlos]
[Carlos chuckles]
[knocking]
[sighs]
[in English] We're polishing
this bottle off pretty fast.
Listen, I am not missing my
flight for anything tomorrow.
Mmm?
No.
You sure you can't stay?
I can't leave Olivia with
my sister forever, Steve.
- Anyway, you'll be in Medellín.
- Ah.
You know, I met the
new head of Search Bloc.
- Yeah?
- He's an interesting guy.
I have a good feeling about him.
Before I forget, I want you...
I want you to give this to Olivia.
Meant to be good luck.
You keep it then.
I am gonna miss you.
[in Spanish]
[all]
[in English] A fucking grid search?
Isn't that how they caught the
guy who shot Abraham Lincoln?
- It's a change.
- Yeah, it's dated and conventional.
Well, we tried going
bullet for bullet with him,
and you saw how that ended up.
Oh, so that's it?
A week ago you volunteered to
jump into a chopper with Carrillo
and now it's a change?
Don't worry about it, man. We'll all
feel better once Escobar's in the ground
- one way or another, right?
- There is no other way, Javi.
Search Bloc is the only game in town.
You really think this
asshole can get it done?
I don't know. Maybe he'll surprise us.
Okay.
Grid search it is.
[sighs]
[in Spanish]
[chatter in Spanish]
[Steve] Of course, Peña knew the
information he had given Berna
was already bearing fruit.
- [gunshots]
- [woman screams]
[in Spanish]
[Steve] The Castaños and their men
were efficient, if not always subtle.
[indistinct Spanish]
What's newsworthy about
a few dead sicarios
in the murder capital of the world?
- [man grunts]
- [impact thud]
- [gunshots]
- Of course, I'm not sure Javi knew
just how fucked up things
were really gonna get.
[in Spanish]
[Steve] Hard to feel sorry for a bunch
of drug dealers getting whacked, right?
These guys had sown a lot of
violence over the years...
killed a lot of people.
[man shouts in Spanish]
It was about time
they got some payback.
But turning a bunch of
well-armed vigilantes loose
on the streets of Medellín...
was like pouring gasoline on a fire
that was already out of control.
[in Spanish]
[indistinct chatter]
[together]
[door opens]
[Hermilda]
[whispers]
[Steve] Martinez was right.
We all need a method.
Something to cling to when the
shit around us gets so deep,
we might go under.
Something to guide us home when
we feel we've lost our way.
If we're lucky, someone gives
us a method and we follow it.
If not, we find our own.
Pablo's enemies had
found their own method.
And it was an ugly one.
They had opened up a
new war against him,
striking from the shadows.
Showing him that, even in
his hometown, he wasn't safe.
[in Spanish]
[Gilberto]
[Steve] And the moment their
method became apparent...
[in Spanish]
...the message was clear.
There was a new player in town.
What does it say?
And they weren't fucking around.
"Your days are numbered, Pablo.
No one around you is safe."
- [flies buzzing]
- Signed "Los Pepes."
Who in the hell are Los Pepes?
[Latin guitar song plays]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com