_
[upbeat Latin ballad playing]
[Pablo sings along in Spanish]
[song continues]
[indistinct chatter in Spanish]
- [chaotic chatter]
- [cocks handgun]
[La Quica shouts indistinctly]
_
[woman gasps]
[continues singing along]
- [man shouts] _
- [gunshot]
[women scream]
[gunshot]
[song continues]
_
- [Rosa sobbing]
- [taking deep breaths]
[gunshot]
[joint hisses out]
[song ends]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[Steve] Imagine this,
President of Colombia goes on
TV and tells the whole world
he'll never make a deal with you.
Now a normal person
thinks, "I'm fucked."
But Pablo Escobar, he thinks
that's just your opening offer.
So the man finds a way to respond.
_
[clears throat]
[Steve] And how did
Gaviria take Pablo's offer?
I think it's safe to say that
he didn't really care for it.
But it wasn't just
Gaviria Pablo was talking to.
In his mind, he was also
negotiating with the leader of the free world.
_
[Steve] You see, the problem was, George
Bush had his own plans for Escobar.
We will, for the first time,
make available the appropriate
resources of America's armed forces.
And for the drug
kingpins, the death penalty.
[Steve] And with a commander in
chief who used to be the head of the CIA,
well, you can use your imagination
as to what "appropriate
resources" might mean.
He started by appointing
a new ambassador.
Badass former Navy man, Arthur Crosby...
who specialized in Latin American
affairs and counterterrorism.
Next, he dug into his old CIA Rolodex,
where there was no shortage of
guys who knew how to fight dirty.
And he sent us one of those, too.
Lastly, and what Peña and I like to
call his own personal "fuck you" to us...
he sent us something he
thought we must need: a boss.
Now just how long that person would
be my boss remained to be seen.
_
[indistinct chatter in Spanish]
[Maritza] _
_
[Crosby] My title might be "ambassador,"
but that's some
bullshit politician's word.
I know what it means to
be on the front lines.
And everybody in this room wants the
same thing, to take down Escobar.
Now as a veteran of numerous conflicts,
I learned one immutable truth:
the only way to succeed
is by working together,
by communicating, by sharing
intelligence and collaborating.
Understood?
Uh, this is Claudia Messina. She
is the new DEA country attaché.
She'll be taking over all DEA
operations in-country. Messina?
Thank you, Ambassador.
The DEA will be opening field offices
in Cali, Cartagena and Barranquilla.
As far as the Medellín
team is concerned,
they will be housed out of CNP
headquarters until further notice.
But only after some personnel
changes have been made.
All right, now as far as long-term
intelligence is concerned,
that's under the purview of the
CIA, the station chief, Bill Stechner.
Bill, you have anything
you'd like to add?
I'm good.
[low chuckle]
All right, who's here
from Centra Spike?
I am, sir. Edward Jacoby.
All right, let's get Centra
Spike back in the air immediately.
I want to know every
word these assholes say
and all information flows through
me and I will disseminate as I see fit.
Yes, sir.
When Escobar sticks his fucking head out,
we're gonna nail that son of a bitch.
[Messina] What about him?
Other than the fact that he
wasn't here today.
Well, I suggested that he stay home.
You mentioned making some
changes. What exactly does that mean?
It means I'm making some changes.
Murphy's a good agent. He's done
a lot of good work down here.
Yeah.
Looks like it.
Do you have any idea the
strings that were pulled
to get that guy not to press charges?
Sounds to me like the guy would've
had a dog sniffing up his ass
before he got on the plane.
Maybe Steve did him a favor.
Was that a thank you?
Be straight with me, Agent
Peña, and I'll be straight with you.
I don't need a guy like that
making my life more difficult.
- And making the DEA look bad.
- Ma'am...
Messina. Or boss.
We've been down here a long time.
You've been down here
all of what, two hours?
It may not make the front page, but...
a lot of the intel we
have is because of Steve.
He's a good man. He's going
through some shit right now.
You know, he was at the airport
to stop his wife from leaving the
country with their kid.
He didn't make it.
Add that to watching
Escobar build a five-star prison
and then walking out the back door.
We both deserve to see this through...
boss.
[Steve sniffs, clears throat]
Have you, uh... had anything
to eat in the last 24 hours?
This new boss... Messina...
what do you know about her?
Only what I've heard.
She's out of New York.
- Doesn't put up with any shit.
- [Steve sputters]
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Am I out?
I don't know.
Well, I ain't ready to go home
yet, Javi. I'll tell ya that.
- Damn it! She's fucking...
- [bottle top clatters]
- Take a shower. Sober up.
- [sighs]
Talk to you.
_
[video game noises]
[Velasco] _
_
- _
- [La Quica sighs]
_
[Steve] Now, Gaviria had made it clear
that the government was not
to negotiate with Escobar.
But Colombia Attorney
General Gustavo de Greiff
didn't give a shit what
the president wanted.
Unlike the US, where the attorney
general is appointed by the president,
in Colombia, the Supreme
Court chooses the attorney general,
whether the president likes it or not.
And in the case of Gustavo de
Greiff, you bet your ass Gaviria didn't.
_
[Fernando] Uh-huh.
[up-tempo Latin music plays on radio]
Listen, thanks for
talking to Messina, man.
I mean it. You saved my ass.
One more fuck-up, Murphy...
Oh, I know.
Is it gonna happen again?
I don't know.
[Steve] DEA politics weren't the
only thing we had to navigate.
The Pinzón plan was in full effect.
He was doubling down on police presence.
Medellín was under martial
law and the base of Carlos Holguín
would look like Fort Apache.
Me and Javi were officially
guests of the CNP.
With all the comforts and amenities
that a guest of the National
Colombian Police could expect.
Which was zero.
And we weren't alone.
The DEA, CIA, Centra Spike and
the army, all under one roof.
It was one-stop shopping for
all things Pablo Escobar.
After Gaviria announced a new $1.4
million reward for Pablo's capture,
Colonel Pinzón
activated a new tip line.
And apparently he thought Javi and
I were just the guys to oversee it.
Forget about the fact that
my Spanish was for shit.
He was sidelining us and there
was nothing we could do about it.
Pablo would even have his men
call in just to fuck with us.
[phone rings]
_
- [loud fart over phone]
- [men laughing]
[Steve] I'm not sure what we expected.
To many people, Escobar was a hero.
It was like asking
Chicago to rat out Michael Jordan.
And those that didn't worship Escobar,
they were simply too scared to call.
But we had a system anyways.
One tip in a particular
location didn't mean shit.
A second call with the same
information still might
not be worth acting on.
But three calls on the same location
from three different sources?
- _
- Yeah?
Now, that had to be checked out.
Hey, I said it was a system.
I didn't say it worked.
Fuck me.
- [man shouts in Spanish] _
- [guys laughing]
[Steve] Our inability to
catch Escobar was frustrating.
But back in Bogotá, it was
becoming a real liability.
_
[sighs] _
[door closes]
_
- [man] _
- [clears throat, coughs]
_
[man] _
[buzzing]
_
[Limón] _
[slams door]
[buzzing]
_
[objects clattering]
[La Quica] _
_
[retreating footsteps]
[stammering] _
_
[Javier] Get ready to
get your balls snipped.
So... your wife left.
You're upset, knocked a
few back to numb the pain
and then decide to take it
out on some Wall Street scumbag.
Yeah, something like that.
Isolated incident?
Yeah.
Look, I know I've been in
Colombia for all of about 20 seconds.
Mm.
Before that, you and Peña had complete
autonomy to call your own shots.
It's gonna take you a minute
to get used to the new order.
You don't trust me yet? That's fine.
But if I'm gonna have your back, I
need to know that I can trust you.
Otherwise, I have no problem sending
you back to your wife in Miami.
Am I making myself clear?
Loud and clear.
Excellent.
You're dismissed.
[sighs]
[sighing]
_
I got "La Quica" and "toilet."
All right, well, now, that I got.
We can't take that to Pinzón. He'll
laugh us out of the office.
_
Maybe we can get Centra
Spike to do a flyover,
see what they come up with.
Be a lot better than
the fucking tip line.
I'll be right back.
[chatter in Spanish over radio]
- A toilet?
- It's a long story.
- Give me the CliffsNotes.
- Look, just do me a favor
and ask them to sweep
over that specific area.
We're looking for any chatter from
Escobar's sicarios. Anything at all.
You recognize a voice, you come get me.
[man over radio] Duvall 1-4-4-3-6, we
heard some chatter at 1600 megahertz.
Be advised.
_
[woman] _
[Velasco] _
That is definitely
Velasco. No ID on the girl.
What's the deal with the other call?
[garbled radio chatter]
The quality's too
poor for voice recognition.
[Steve sighs] All right... these
were taken about two hours ago.
What's here is fincas, fincas.
Everything else is just smaller houses
here, here and here, and the outskirts.
You can probably eliminate the
smaller ones, not Escobar's style.
Which of the fincas have road
access both east and west?
[Javier] This one here.
It's rough terrain down the back of
the mountain, but it's drivable.
[Steve] It's gotta be the one.
We'd have a good chance if we
came at him from both sides.
[Messina] This is good.
Great. What about Pinzón?
We're gonna need
vehicles, we're gonna need men.
Leave Pinzón to me.
_
[Messina chuckles]
What did he say?
He said no.
Oh, she's not gonna last. She
gives up pretty fuckin' easy.
[Steve] But Messina didn't give up easy.
She called Crosby...
Crosby called Gaviria...
and in less than 15 minutes...
- I understand.
- ...Pinzón was gettin' a kick in the ass.
_
[Steve] I guess everybody
works for somebody.
_
[Steve] Just because we
could make Pinzón dance
didn't mean we could call the tune.
We would've gone in stealth. Surround
the fucker, then grab him.
Pinzón didn't do shit that way. He
liked kicking down the front door,
waking up the whole damn neighborhood.
_
- _
- [knocks rapidly on door]
_
[knocking continues]
- [Pablo whispers] _
- [indistinct whispers]
[trucks approaching, stopping nearby]
[Pablo whispering] _
[indistinct whispers]
[indistinct shouts in Spanish]
_
[indistinct whispers]
[soldiers chattering above]
[silent mouthing]
[glass clinking]
[footsteps, chattering above]
[indistinct whispers]
[low, indistinct chatter]
_
[Steve] Don't forget that
Pablo made a career
of staying ahead of the cops.
A lot of the fincas he used had
tunnels built just for this purpose.
Even though he didn't like using them.
I guess you could say that he
was paranoid, but then again,
if people are actually after you, that's
not paranoid. That's just smart.
Peña! Messina!
[low chatter in Spanish]
He was here.
_
[spoon clinking in cup]
[Steve] You know, in all
the years I chased Escobar,
I could count on one hand the
times we almost had him.
And each time, we forgot the
two most important things
we already knew about him:
Close doesn't count.
And Pablo is never more
dangerous than when you almost have him.
- [soldiers speak indistinctly]
- [chatter in Spanish over radio]
[Steve] With all the cops on the
street, it was easy to forget...
this was still Escobar's town.
He tolerated it all in the
interest of negotiations.
[man whistles]
Chasing a man and his
family out of their home
- in the middle of the night?
- [indistinct]
That wasn't a negotiation.
To Escobar...
well, that was an act of war.
_
- [man whistles]
- [indistinct chatter in Spanish]
_
[whispers] _
[upbeat Latin ballad playing]
- [song continues]
- [tires screech]
[men grunting]
- [shouts in Spanish] _
- [tires squealing]
[engine revving]
[song continues]
[men shouting]
[indistinct chatter in Spanish]
- [men grunting]
- [people screaming]
- [man cries out]
- [groaning]
_
[indistinct chatter]
[song continues]
[chaotic chatter]
- [indistinct shouts]
- [sirens wailing]
[newswoman reports indistinctly]
[overlapping chaotic chatter]
[man screams]
Peña!
[song ends]
[soft guitar music plays]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --