Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
_
[slow Latin guitar music playing]
[sighs]
[alarm clock beeping]
[beeping continues loudly]
[Pablo] Tata.
[birds twittering]
[Pablo in Spanish] _
[gunshot]
- [sniffing]
- Pablo.
- _
- _ [sniffs]
_
[sighs, sniffing]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
[Valeria in Spanish] _
_
[Valeria] _
- [Valeria] _
- [Eduardo] _
- _
_
- [sighs]
- _
_
- [softly] _
- _
[Pablo breathes heavily]
Hmm.
_
[Pablo] _
[Steve] When Pablo
Escobar starts believing
the pen's mightier than the sword...
you know you're getting to him.
Carrillo's attacks on Pablo's facilities
in Medellín were putting him
- under more and more pressure.
- [in Spanish] _
- [Steve] The way Carrillo saw it...
- [gunshots]
... each sicario we took out
got us one step closer to Escobar.
[in Spanish] _
_
[reporters chatter in Spanish]
[Steve] While everyone could agree
it felt good emptying
Pablo's pockets...
[in Spanish] _
[Steve] ... they weren't
all sold on the method.
Is it true?
- Not to my knowledge.
- Don't play word games with me.
If that kid's telling the truth,
Peña and Murphy were there.
They're the only Americans
that asshole trusts.
I find it hard to believe that Colonel
Carrillo would want American witnesses.
Exactly what he wants.
Guarantees they won't say shit if people
start asking questions. And guess what?
People are asking questions.
Look, if Carrillo wants
to walk out in the streets
and gun down every sicario in Medellín,
God bless him.
But our guys can't be
there when he does it.
Understood?
Understood.
It's been quiet for about a week.
Nothing of significance.
But a phone we connected to Edgar Prisco
popped up three times last night.
All within Manrique,
the same three-block vicinity here.
They just can't fucking help themselves,
can they?
My men did a drive-by early this morning
and identified a potential location.
Right here. The pool hall.
[male sports announcer
chatters in Spanish over radio]
[snoring]
[in Spanish] _
_
[man snorts, chuckling]
[loud snoring]
- _
- [grunts]
_
- [grunts] _
- [phone beeps]
_
- _
[Edgar] _
_
[shouting in Spanish]
[motorcyclist] _
[honking]
[man in Spanish] _
[chatter in Spanish]
_
[woman scoffs]
[panting]
Murphy! Not a good neighborhood
to get yourself lost in, eh?
[gunshot]
Fuck.
[panting]
[grunts]
[people chattering in Spanish]
[voices echo in Spanish]
[door opens]
[door closes]
- [baby crying nearby]
- [Steve] Shh, shh, shh.
[woman] _
- [man] _
- [Steve in Spanish] _
[softly] _
- _
- [gun cocking]
[whispers] Fuck.
[Javier in English] Murphy! Gavera 37!
You need to get up here!
Murphy, get in the car.
The fuck were you thinking?
[whispers] This fucking close.
[Steve] We were
definitely getting closer.
And so who could blame
the "Gentlemen of Cali"
for starting to think about a future
without Pablo Escobar?
[in Spanish] _
_
[chuckles] _
- _
_
[soft chuckle]
[Velasco] _
_
- _
[man] _
_
[phone ringing]
- _
-
_
[Limón] _
- _
- [Fernando] _
_
[sighs]
[Steve] If it seemed
like Escobar's world
was crashing down around him,
it was actually about to get worse.
Remember when Pablo collaborated
with M-19 communists
during the Palace of Justice siege?
By doing that,
he pissed off the Autodefensas...
an extreme right-wing paramilitary group
that was in direct conflict
with the communist guerrillas.
[man in Spanish] _
_
[Steve] The leaders of the Autodefensas
were the Castaño brothers:
Fidel and Carlos.
Carlos is the one
barking orders at people.
In the late 70s, their father, Jesús,
a prominent landowner,
was kidnapped by the FARC guerrillas
who demanded 50 million pesos
for his ransom.
But his sons were
only able to come up with 16.
Well, that didn't cut it.
So the guerrillas
beat the elder Castaño to death.
From that day forward, the right-wing,
psychopathic, commie-killing
Castaño brothers
swore never to rest
until their father was avenged...
[man shouts in Spanish over loudspeaker]
... and every last guerrilla
driven from the countryside was killed.
[in Spanish] _
[Steve] Even innocent villagers
who simply lived in
guerrilla strongholds
were put to death because
they lived under communist subjugation.
And in their efforts to wipe out
the communist guerrillas...
the Castaños caught the attention
of some like-minded friends.
- [in English] Mr. Stechner.
- Good to see you, my friend.
- Welcome. Have a nice trip?
- Thank you. As always, as always.
[in Spanish] _
[chuckles, speaks English] These weapons
are better than the last ones.
They should be.
Thank you, Mr. Green, for the continued
support of your country.
I haven't used that name
since the School of the Americas.
I know you're waging a great war
against communism in these jungles.
We will not stop
until the last communist is dead.
[Bill] Another struggle is emerging.
One that is essential to
our, uh... shared cause.
Escobar.
[Carlos] Escobar deserves to die.
But our fight is here in the
jungle, against the guerrilla.
Yes, and Pablo's still
strong in Medellín.
Yeah, strength is exceedingly relative.
An alliance is forming...
with the objective
of taking out Escobar.
Who?
Rival elements from
the trafficking world.
Look, what matters most is that
when Escobar's taken off the board,
the right parties are in a position
to make sure order is maintained.
And that strategic Colombian resources
and revenue streams...
don't fall into the wrong hands.
[up-tempo Latin music playing]
[in Spanish] _
_
- _
[Carlos] _
_
- _
[rooster crows]
[mooing]
- _
_
[scoffs]
- _
_
[sighs] _
[Tata chuckles] _
[Pablo] Mmm.
_
- _
[Pablo sighs]
_
- _
- [in Spanish] _
_
[in English] Get the lecture from Messina
about not leaving base?
Yeah.
Crosby must've really
laid into her on that one.
- Where you going?
- Out. Off base.
Okay, I guess it means "Fuck that."
[knocking at door]
[in Spanish] _
- _
_
- [sighs]
- _
_
[in English] Her name is Maritza Rincón.
She works at the market across from
the brothel where the girls were killed.
Where we almost had La Quica
and the other guy...
Jhon Burgos. Goes by "Limón."
He used to drive the girls around until
La Quica made him Escobar's chauffeur.
This girl Maritza was actually
in the back seat serving as a cover
while Escobar was in the fucking trunk.
- And he knows her how?
- They grew up together here.
[Carrillo scoffs softly]
So this guy Limón,
there's no record of him.
There's no known connection
between him and Escobar,
yet somehow he ends up the driver.
Makes sense for La Quica to hire someone
the police didn't know about.
What does she want out of this?
A ticket to Disneyland?
She knows she doesn't get shit
if it doesn't pan out.
[in Spanish] _
_
[in English] You were
there. You trust her?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
When we get the location, I want
Centra Spike up in the air to confirm.
[in Spanish] _
- [in English] All right. This is good.
- Let's go.
[in Spanish] _
_
[sighs] _ [clears throat] _
[resumes typing]
[phone rings]
_
[softly] _
- _
_
_ [laughing]
_ [grunts]
_
[phone rings]
Peña.
_
[in English] I need to know
if there's activity around this address.
You get a match on a voice,
you find me immediately.
Okay. You got it.
[distorted voices over recording]
This was recorded about
- five minutes ago.
- You can barely hear it.
Let me clean it up.
[Pablo in Spanish] _
- That's Pablo.
- We have to move now.
- Yeah.
- [Messina] You two are staying here.
Gotta be fucking kidding me.
Crosby finds out you
went on another raid,
we all get a ticket home.
Crosby doesn't have to know shit.
It's not negotiable.
We'll be in radio contact.
Jesus.
[in Spanish] _
_
[man] _
[indistinct chatter over radios]
[in Spanish] _
[in English] Copy that.
Watch your six, guys.
How's it looking out there?
[in Spanish] _
_
[chuckles]
[in English] Cheap bastards.
Don't forget to pick me and Peña up
some cigars on the way.
[in Spanish] _
[indistinct shouting over radio]
_
[man shouts in Spanish] _
[indistinct shouts]
_
[in Spanish] _
[indistinct shouts]
[men yelling]
_
[in English] Goddamn it, speak to me!
We need people there.
_
[grunts]
[man yelling in Spanish] _
Fuck!
[in Spanish] _
_
[whispers] _
[sirens wailing in distance]
_
[in English] I'll go back to Bogotá
with the body until the funeral.
They call his wife?
Yeah, she's on her way from Madrid.
This ain't on you, Javi.
It's on Escobar.
And one way or another, he pays.
We all do. Right?
[ambulance siren wailing]
[knocking at door]
This isn't your fault, Peña.
- No?
- No.
- I got played.
- We all got played.
We all had the information,
it was backed up by Centra Spike...
Stop.
Just...
You know, you coming here...
you say all the right things.
Doesn't make a damn bit of difference.
Colonel Carrillo's funeral
will be tomorrow.
[door closes]
I don't do funerals.
[slow Latin guitar music plays]
[in Spanish] _
_
- [rain pattering]
- [approaching footsteps]
[thunder rumbles]
_
[sighs]
- _
_
[Gaviria] _
[softly] _
[bell tolling]
_
- _
[La Quica] _
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Where's Olivia?
She's at home. With my sister.
Hey, you okay?
- [whimpers]
- Hey.
[soft sobs]
[in Spanish] _
_
[Don Berna] _
[mid-tempo Latin music plays]
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com