_
Okay. Here we go again.
Let me break it down for you,
four thousand soldiers...
a 250-man team of Colombia's
elite forces...
tens of thousands of rounds fired...
...seven dogs...
...and four fuckin' helicopters.
Pablo Escobar was surrounded
in the middle of fuckin' nowhere.
There was no way he was
getting out of this one... right?
_
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Yep.
Life ain't fair, man.
Pablo Escobar? He was headed home.
As for me and Connie, well,
we were in some deep shit,
and I hadn't even heard the news.
This is what I do. This is my job.
No, don't you dare say this is your job.
I know what your fucking job is.
And it doesn't entail being kidnapped
by a Colombian drug cartel.
Listen, I'm sorry, I am. I
know it must've been tough for you.
Listen, but Connie, I was
never in any danger.
I'm here now, back with you.
Hmm?
All I want... is for us to be safe.
I want to get the hell out of this
place and I want to go home.
- Murphy.
- Escobar's out.
- What?
- He's fucking out.
He took Sandoval hostage during the
siege and when the
army went in... he escaped.
Walked right out.
Pick me up in ten minutes.
I'll meet you downstairs.
Escobar's escaped.
And you know what?
I was happy about it.
The fox was out of the cage
and the hunt was on.
Yeah, it was the biggest law enforcement
blunder of all time.
Fortunately, it wasn't our blunder.
_
Pablo Escobar has escaped from prison.
He is out of that prison again
after a bizarre showdown between...
By morning, word was out on the streets
and all eyes were on Medellín.
This wasn't just a
manhunt... this was an invasion.
Gaviria was willing to go
door to door to catch Escobar.
And we wanted to be a part of it.
After all, we
represented America down here.
We thought of ourselves as
the guys who could get shit done.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...
- Jesus Christ.
Agent Murphy, Agent Peña. DEA.
_
- Name Pinzón mean anything to you?
- No, don't know him.
You see this?
Well, it looks like
we're not invited to the dance.
_
Yeah, you mean when nothing's
left inside.
_
_ Huh?
Now keep in mind...
the Medellín cartel
wasn't just one big gang.
It was made up of a bunch
of smaller gangs.
A collective, so to speak.
And as far as Pablo was concerned,
he was still their leader.
In his mind, every trafficker in Medellín
had to pay tribute to him.
Only a guy who'd killed
thousands of people
could think Judy Moncada would
forget what he'd
done to her husband Kiko
and his business partner
Fernando Galeano,
the guys who were running
his business while he was inside.
Fuckin' psycho. He thought
that they were stealing from him...
and naturally, they got the
short end of the stick.
_
Why he thought Judy'd
be okay with that...
Well, she wasn't.
And alongside her brother Jaime,
and head of security Diego Murillo,
a.k.a. Don Berna, they'd
broken away from the Medellín cartel.
And now that Pablo was out,
they wanted payback.
And as for the other
gangs, they were all up for grabs.
Take the Prisco brothers, for instance.
The oldest of whom, Ricardo,
was a respected member
of the medical community.
He didn't know who to side with.
Neither did the Gallón gang,
who became famous a year later
when they murdered Colombian
soccer player Andrés Escobar
for accidentally scoring a goal
against his own country in the 1994 World Cup.
But this wasn't a soccer
game. This was the blow business.
And whose side they
chose would come down
to two things, who offered
the better deal
and who had the better chance
of winning the war.
_
Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Mmm?
_
Mmm.
_ Hmm?
_
- _
Looking for a place for your
next corporate retreat?
Or maybe a quiet getaway
for the whole family?
How about 360 degrees of
unobstructed views of the Antioquian countryside?
Sixty thousand square feet
of creative living space.
Perfect for entertaining.
Look no further than La Catedral.
One man's prison...
is anyone else's palace.
Yep... it was a beautiful place.
And when the Colombian
cops were done with it,
they were gracious enough to
let us pick through the leftovers.
This and Mein Kampf.
Two classics of 20th century literature.
Yeah, what do you think the rent's
like? I'm thinking about moving in.
Hey, Javi, you think the, uh...
the Hague would want a couple of these?
How are you not wearing rubber
gloves touching that shit, man?
We should take this stuff to our office.
It's better than any of the shit we got.
Fuckin' Pinzón's
guys have taken everything
that's useful. There's nothing.
Look, I think I found something
that might help.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
Wait.
_
After La Catedral, the next
stop was Carlos Holguín...
the old police training academy
that had been repurposed as ground zero
in the search for Escobar.
The new honcho was Colonel Pinzón,
the guy who was famous
for his love of Uncle Sam.
As a courtesy to your government,
I'm allowing you to participate
in this manhunt.
But... I set the limits
and all decisions rest with me.
If this condition is unacceptable,
take it up with the president.
Of course, Colonel.
I hope we didn't get
off on the wrong foot.
Not at all. Every operation
needs a well-defined hierarchy.
I hope this will be an
adequate space for you to do your work.
What, you're talking about this? This...
This is more than adequate.
- Gracias, Colonel.
- Welcome.
Oh, wow, this is from 1962.
Like most tricks Pablo employed,
the audacity and simplicity
of the taxi was pretty damn good.
I mean, who in the hell would think
that the seventh richest man in the world
would be riding around in the
trunk of a piece of shit taxi?
_
As smart as it was,
Pablo wasn't the kind
of guy who left anything to chance.
Despite his absence, he still
had a loyal following in Medellín.
And a network of spotters...
kids mainly.
And they were everywhere in the comunas.
The spotters could identify
which streets to take
and which ones to avoid.
_
- _
Mmm.
_
Seriously? Directly in front of me?
I don't spend enough time
looking at your face?
That's better.
_
Nothing?
You picked up the "American"
part, right?
Murphy!
_
- You think it's legit?
- Let's find out.
How credible is your source?
It was an unsolicited phone call.
She asked to speak to an American.
We would just need a
couple of cars and a few men.
Well, my men are either busy
here or outside in the street.
And I'm not relocating men
to chase down bullshit tips.
If this turns out not to be bullshit,
La Quica could give us Pablo.
So go. Go ahead.
Since when do you need an excuse
to go to a whorehouse?
_
One vehicle, three men.
Gracias.
_
Alleys run along the
house here... and here.
We'll keep the other car
waiting around back.
_
- Murphy.
- Hey, it's me.
Hey, honey. Um...
I'm just in the middle of something.
Let me call you right back.
We're at the airport.
You're where?
I can't do this.
I'm taking Olivia and we're
going back to Miami.
No, no, no. Listen to me, please.
Please, you can't just
do it like this. You can't.
My sister's offered to help us out for
a while, so we'll be there if you need us.
Connie.
It's not right, Steve, to keep
Olivia here with everything that's going on.
Not when I can take her someplace safe.
You're safe in Bogotá. You're
right beside the goddamn fuckin' embassy.
Look, I have to go.
Connie, please. We can talk about this.
Do not get on that airplane. Wait, okay?
I'll be right there. I'm on my way.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey. I'm here. Okay?
- She's at the airport.
- Go.
I'm sorry. I gotta go. Guys, sorry.
All right.
_
Flight to Miami.
Gate 39, but... Sir, you can't go. Sir!
I'm DEA. I need to get on this flight.
I'm sorry, sir... Sir, I'm
sorry, but the plane has already left.
Sir, please. You can't be here.
Sir!
_
Just fuckin' drive.
Enjoy.
- Get you feeling pretty good?
- Huh?
Oh, fuck. Thanks, man. Shit.
Phew!
You wouldn't imagine what
a kilo of that stuff cost.
Come on.
- How about you, golden boy?
- What are you talking about, man?
Time it's processed, shipped,
distributed to your buddies on...
the Upper East Side? Yeah.
Hey, man, we don't need
any problems here. We cool?
Six.
Lives.
That's how much it cost.
What do you think about that?
That was six people.
Six people were murdered
every time you and your
buddy over there...
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah?
Whoo!
_
Fuck.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --