[low rumbling, growing louder]
[horses whinnying]
[engines racing]
[in Spanish]
[Gustavo over radio, in Spanish]
[Gustavo cackles]
[up-tempo Latin music plays]
♪♪
[excited chatter in Spanish]
[honking]
[laughing]
[overlapping chatter]
[kissing]
[laughing]
[Pablo]
[low chuckle]
[Poison]
[Carlos]
[vehicle doors slam shut]
[Latin guitar theme music plays]
Sync and corrected by ~LittleDuck~
www.addic7ed.com
Narcos 2x06
Los Pepes
- [festive music playing]
- [children chatter indistinctly]
[Steve] Colombia is a Catholic country,
so Christmas is a big deal.
But the people of Medellín
always take it to the next level.
And despite the manhunt
for Pablo going on around them,
this year was no different.
Call it faith, optimism,
or stubbornness,
the people of Medellín thought
they'd seen it all, but they hadn't.
In fact, they hadn't seen anything yet.
[low murmurs]
PABLO MERRY CHRISTMAS
LOS PEPES
HAPPY HOLIDAYS
Medellín was about to get a show
they would never forget.
[in Spanish]
[woman in English]
[overlapping arguments]
[Gaviria]
[all]
[Martinez]
[in English] So Los Pepes
is an interesting new wrinkle.
Well, are you surprised?
Escobar's got a lot of enemies.
I heard from Messina this morning.
There's a lot of eyes on them
and us, so she wants us to steer clear.
- Are you working for Los Pepes, Murphy?
- No, I'm not.
Then I guess we're good.
[Latin music plays over radio]
[in Spanish]
[phone rings]
-
- [Berna]
[Steve]
For Los Pepes, it was easy.
They had all the man-on-the-street
intelligence they needed.
If they'd heard a guy, take Jairo
for example, was in a certain vicinity,
they just asked around
and they'd find him.
But for us, well,
we had to go door-to-door,
asking for help from people
who don't tell cops shit.
[in Spanish]
[Steve] Los Pepes, on the other hand,
had no problems.
They were quite persuasive.
[murmuring in Spanish]
Sure, once in a while,
we got lucky and picked somebody up.
But it was rarely the guy
we were looking for.
[arguing in Spanish]
[Steve] It was slow-going.
[Martinez in Spanish]
[in English] We're too late.
Says they already got him.
We finally get corroboration on Jairo,
Martinez orders the raid...
So?
Well, so, how does Los Pepes
get here first?
Maybe he got followed.
Or the dumb fuck shot his mouth off
and somebody else got lucky.
Mmm. That's it?
That's all you got to say on that?
Yeah.
If it worries you, look into it.
[Steve]
"Look into it"? Right.
Nobody was looking into it.
Why would they?
Pablo's crew was turning up dead
all over Medellín,
and Jairo became the latest victim.
The terror that Pablo had spread
across the country
was finally back on him tenfold.
Los Pepes' method was working.
And you better believe
it was getting to Escobar.
IN DEFENSE OF THE COLOMBIAN PEOPLE
[Carlos in Spanish]
[Juan Pablo]
Pablo.
[Tata]
[Hermilda]
[Pablo]
[Blackie]
- [low chatter]
-
- Thank you.
- Oh!
[woman taps on crystal]
[chatter continues]
[Gilberto] As gratifying as
these displays may feel,
[in Spanish]
[in English] Centra Spike
give us anything good for Christmas?
Well, Blackie's been getting calls
from Envigado.
The son of a bitch has got a girlfriend.
Here, I'll give that to Martinez.
I'm sure it's gotta get vetted.
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
[line ringing]
[Berna in Spanish]
[Steve] I didn't know how Los Pepes
was beating us to the punch.
Not yet anyway.
What I did know was that if Search Bloc
was gonna have any kind of impact
on the hunt for Pablo,
we'd have to play the game
better and faster.
All right, Blackie's had a girlfriend
in Envigado for a while.
According to Centra Spike,
the last known intercept
places her somewhere in this vicinity.
Yeah. And how's that relevant?
Intel says she's pregnant.
I know protocol is to vet intel,
wait for corroboration,
but I feel this one in my gut, sir.
Blackie's gonna show.
Los Pepes keeps getting the jump on us,
sicarios are gonna keep winding up dead.
This way, we get to Blackie first,
bring that son of a bitch in
and get something out of him.
Well, we could set up a perimeter.
No one walks in or out.
[Steve]
Collapse that perimeter house by house.
- [Martinez] Yeah.
- [Steve] Sounds good to me.
[groans, in Spanish]
[Blackie]
[chatter in Spanish]
- [in English] Hey!
- Hey.
What's going on?
Martinez gave the green light
to go after Blackie.
- It's a good thing, right?
- Yeah. Right.
Goddamn Christmas miracle.
[in Spanish]
[man over radio]
[Berna]
[in English]
We're moving in. Let's go.
[phone ringing]
[in Spanish]
[affirmative murmur]
- [in English] What's going on?
- Some shit's going down at checkpoint.
[in Spanish]
[Steve in English]
What the fuck is this?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[in Spanish]
[Carlos]
[in English] Put the fucking gun down!
[in Spanish] Easy! Easy!
[Javier clapping]
[softly]
[whispers]
- Let them pass.
- Okay.
Well then, thank you.
[in English]
Trying to avoid a bloodbath, brother.
[in Spanish]
[Trujillo]
[sighs]
[in English] When were you gonna tell me
about your new friend Carlos Castaño?
He's not a friend, he's a...
he's a man with a shared interest.
Jesus Christ.
I hope you know what you're doing.
Don't worry.
It's not gonna blow back on you.
- No, it's not me I'm worried about.
- I can handle it.
These aren't the guys
you wanna be messing with.
They're gonna do what they're gonna do
with or without me, right?
At least this way...
I'm on the inside and I can control it.
- Make sure it doesn't go too far.
- So that doesn't go too far?
The good guys, they got guns
pointing at their fucking head
- and the bad guys get away with it?
- Who are the good guys, Steve?
That's us?
[in Spanish]
[sighs softly]
[Steve] Los Pepes may have
seemed to be running the board,
but Escobar still had a trick or two
up his sleeve.
Remember I told you Ricardo Prisco
was a licensed doctor?
Well, he was.
And as such, he had privileges at just
about every hospital in Medellín.
Including the one where the Los Pepes
gunman he shot was recovering.
Unfortunately for that guy,
Dr. Prisco paid him a visit.
[in Spanish]
- [muffled screams]
- Shh!
[whimpering]
[Pablo]
Mmm.
Pablo.
[men murmur in Spanish]
Maria.
[whispers]
[scoffs softly]
[overlapping chatter slowly subsides]
- [low chuckles]
- -
[murmurs of agreement in crowd]
- [crowd] Cheers!
- [applause]
[up-tempo Latin music plays]
[whispers indistinctly]
[indistinct chatter]
[music continues nearby]
- [explosion]
- [people screaming]
[Diego]
[woman moans]
[chaotic chatter]
[woman sobbing]
[sobs]
[sobbing continues]
[Pablo]
[La Quica]
[Carlos]
Right?
[sighs]
[in Spanish]
[in English]
Did you see this?
Reports of a massive bombing
in Cali last night.
Gilberto Rodríguez's
daughter's wedding?
[chuckles]
I know of only one person in Colombia
with the balls big enough
to go after that guy.
Yeah, Pablo Escobar.
He had to have had a damn good reason.
I'd like to shift some of our resources
from Medellín to Cali.
Now's a bad time
to deviate from Medellín.
Cali is trafficking
in the billions right now.
- If they get a free head start...
- You're not wrong.
But you're thinking about this
too logically.
The best thing for you right now
is to keep your head in the game.
Because right now,
the game is Pablo Escobar.
Right. Escobar.
I'll see you at the party tonight.
We could all use a few hours' break
from this shit.
I'll see you there.
Manuel.
[in Spanish]
[Christmas song plays in Spanish]
[man in English]
Welcome, Mr. President.
Welcome, Ma'am.
♪♪
Yeah, Bogotá is beautiful.
It's a lot more like
an American city than I thought.
I didn't know it'd be so cold.
- Good to see you.
- Thank you.
[in Spanish]
[church bells tolling]
[murmurs indistinctly]
MERRY CHRISTMAS
[engine starts]
♪ [tension building] ♪
[overlapping chatter]
[in English] Mr. President.
Lovely party, Ambassador.
It's nice we can pretend
we're all friends.
Believe it or not, the State Department
does the guest list, not me.
I can't wait to tell them that
he wants us to legalize drugs.
He thinks I should
publicly condemn Los Pepes.
They're criminals.
Their activities cannot be condoned.
Even if one does approve of the results.
[sighs]
Mr. President, I'm no one to bullshit.
Maybe that's hurt me in my career.
Yes, Los Pepes are an ugly business.
They're getting to Escobar.
That's all that matters at the present.
If I condemn them,
I have to police them.
With politics and war...
the trick is in the timing.
Watch how they evolve,
how their actions are received.
And, uh, up till then,
pretend they don't exist.
Well, we can if you can.
[singing "Silent Night" in Spanish]
What are you up to in here?
Have a drink.
Thanks.
Saved me a trip to the bar.
Call it inter-agency cooperation.
Hmm. That's a joke.
And it's funny.
Cheers.
So where are you from, Bill?
Originally, Oregon.
You were in Afghanistan, right?
Well, I could tell you that
but then I'd have to...
Funny.
I know Bill Haler.
He was our guy in Afghanistan.
Oh, yeah.
DEA Bill, we used to call him.
I liked him. Stayed in his lane.
So, as I'm sure you know,
I recently asked for a resource redirect
into some emerging players
in the trafficking world.
- A group based in Cali. Ring a bell?
- [sighs]
We're not gonna talk
about work, are we?
My request was denied, Bill.
- We were just getting to know each other.
- So I spoke to DEA Bill.
- He's in Washington now.
- You don't say.
And he told me the roadblock
was caused by the agency.
Something about an ongoing operation.
He actually said,
"That sounds like CIA Bill."
Look, I don't care what you do
with the commies and the paramilitaries.
But as soon as your
ongoing operations involve narcos...
you're in my backyard.
[door opens, closes]
[in Spanish]
- [gunshots in distance]
- [dogs bark outside]
- [gunshot]
-
[automatic gunfire]
- [shouting in Spanish]
- [screaming]
[gunfire continues]
[panting]
[automatic gunfire nearby]
- [screams]
- [glass shatters]
- Quickly!
- [overlapping gunfire]
[gunfires]
[overlapping shouts]
[gunfire continues nearby]
[overlapping gunfire]
[grunts]
[man grunts]
- [glass shattering]
- [gunfire continues]
[indistinct shouts in Spanish]
Carlos!
- [Tata] Pablo!
- Carlos!
[grunts]
- [scream] No!
- [groans]
[gunfire continues]
[screaming]
[shrieks] Carlos!
[sobbing]
No!
[softly]
[voice trembling]
[in Spanish]
[sirens wailing in distance]
[clicks of the camera]
- [Tata sniffling]
-
[softly]
[sniffling]
[slow Latin guitar song plays]
Sync and corrected by ~LittleDuck~
www.addic7ed.com