[ARCHIE] Previously on Riverdale...
How did Hiram Lodge pin
Cassidy Bullock's murder on me?
[WARDEN NORTON]
He paid Mr. Bullock's friends
to say that they saw
you pull the trigger.
It's my understanding
that they're in hiding.
I'd hide in the mines by Shadow Lake.
The Warden said if I did
this, I'd finally ascend.
[JUGHEAD] You're breaking
Archie out of juvie?
[VERONICA] We'll need a
distraction to disorient the guards
and hide Archie's play for the grate.
Find him right now!
Joaquin, where are you
going? Back to the Serpents?
No. I joined a different gang.
- Game Master, where is the...
- [BOTH] Red Paladin?
[VERONICA] Everyone in this
room is part of the pact.
No one knows of Archie's
whereabouts, capisce?
[ARCHIE] Does Hiram Lodge own you, too?
[WARDEN NORTON] My soul belongs
to no mere mortal, Andrews.
But he's watching us,
he's always watching.
[BETTY] Oh, Archie.
What does it mean?
How are we gonna get out of this mess?
[JUGHEAD] Betty.
I saw him.
The Gargoyle King.
Jug, what the hell? Just now?
As I was walking home.
I followed him into a clearing.
Betty, there are others.
There's, like, ten of 'em.
They look like his disciples.
Like, they were worshiping the king.
- Oh, my God.
- They had on these masks,
like, they were a gang.
A gang of gargoyles.
- Well, let's go after them.
- No.
We shouldn't push our luck.
Not until we know more.
Well, who could they be, Jug?
Joaquin.
[GROANS]
Joaquin told Kevin about a new gang.
And then Joaquin ran into the woods.
We know Warden Norton is playing G&G,
and Joaquin was doing his dirty work.
It's just another piece
of damning evidence
that Warden Norton could
be our Gargoyle King.
[BETTY SIGHS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[ALICE] Where have you been, young lady?
There's a manhunt for
Archie Andrews underway.
Police with guns and dogs
all over the streets of Riverdale.
Did you have something to do with this?
No, Mom.
We didn't even hear about
his escape until this morning.
The warden from that juvie
killed himself last night.
What?
How come?
RIVW's reporting that he was found with
blue lips.
So he was playing G&G.
Mom, did you know Warden Norton?
Why would you even ask that?
Because he had ties to Hiram Lodge
who played G&G with you 25 years ago.
Are you sure you don't remember him?
Yes, I am sure, Elizabeth.
I've told you everything that I know.
I miss this.
I missed you, Archie.
Ronnie.
I may know where the
Shadow Lake boys are.
The warden said he thought
they were camping in
the abandoned mines.
I just need to get there.
No, Archie. I don't
think you understand.
Outside this bunker, there
is a manhunt going on,
road blocks, checkpoints,
"Wanted" posters with your
strong jawline all over town.
I need to find those witnesses.
The warden said all
three guys were paid off.
They're the only ones
who can clear my name,
so I can stop running.
Paid off by my father, no doubt.
[EXHALES]
Archie.
This is a long shot,
but when Betty was working on your case
with Attorney McCoy and your mom,
that was at your house, right?
Yeah.
Are the case files still there?
Yeah, but they've been through them all.
And, Ronnie,
my dad can't know where I am,
or that you saw me.
I don't want him wrapped up in this.
I feel bad enough you're involved.
Hey.
This was the only way to
get you out of that mess.
Ronnie, I took that plea deal
because I was tired
of putting my friends and
my family through hell.
All the people who have helped you,
are doing it because we love you.
So, I need you to trust me
to handle this,
and stay put.
[SHERIFF MINETTA] Archie is a murderer,
and we know he didn't
escape alone. He had help.
Hiding a convict
or withholding information from the law
is a felony offense.
So, whoever's aided and
abetted Archie Andrews
is just as much of a criminal as he is.
I was busy all day, Sheriff.
You can check my browser history.
If you know what I mean.
[LAUGHTER]
I don't even know this Archie person.
And on Mondays, I host
a group for teen Farmies.
We are still accepting members.
Where were you, Miss McCoy,
at the time of the breakout?
Don't look at me, sir. I, uh...
I...
I was in the music room
practicing.
Alone?
I'll be looking into all of your alibis,
and if I find out later
that someone in here was involved,
then you can say goodbye to this school,
your hopes and dreams,
your music, your entire future.
All of it goes away just like that.
So, again, to be clear,
if you know anything that...
Sheriff Minetta, back off!
[THUDS]
[BOY] What just happened?
My God, is she okay?
[JUGHEAD] Another seizure.
As if things weren't crazy enough.
I know. First me,
then Ethel, then Josie.
What's the connection there?
Speaking of connections,
with Warden Norton dead,
there goes our theory of
him as the Gargoyle King.
Maybe not.
Look.
There is the connection
between our parents
and Warden Norton right there.
Warden Norton was the RROTC
instructor of Riverdale High.
Yeah, the same year
our parents started the Midnight Club.
What this proves once more,
is that our parents continue
to hide things from us,
and it all started with
the Midnight Club, Jug.
Featherhead was the first
blue-lipped death on record.
Somehow I need to get
our parents to start talking to us.
Force them into telling us the truth.
Even if that means
backing them into a corner.
What do you have in mind?
Depends whether or not I can
borrow Veronica's speakeasy.
Okay, well, while
you're working on that,
I'm going to rally the Serpents.
We have to find Joaquin.
As Norton's accomplice,
he's probably our best shot
at figuring out what was
going on inside Norton's mind.
Bye.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[SWEET PEA] Minetta's
trashing tent city, Jug,
looking for Archie.
All right. I propose
a manhunt of our own.
I want every Serpent on the
ground searching for Joaquin.
I don't want a stone left unturned.
You know, Serpents don't
just shiv other Serpents.
Then what the hell do
you think got into him?
Well, according to
Archie, Joaquin did it
for Warden Norton.
And when the Warden confronted Betty,
he called Archie the Red Paladin.
Plus, the Warden poisoned himself
with cyanide and blueberry Fresh-Aid.
And he worked for Riverdale High
before the Detention Center.
The question is, was he
playing G&G with someone,
or for someone?
And since he's dead,
Joaquin's the only one
who can know the answer.
Right. Joaquin may not be alone.
Kevin said that he might
be rolling with a new gang.
Those Gargoyle creeps you saw?
Exactly.
And if the gang is working for the King,
then they're gonna take us right to him.
Archie, you haven't eaten your burger.
[SIGHS] To be honest, I'm not
feeling so hot right now, Kev.
[GROANS]
Let me see your bandage.
Okay.
That is definitely infected.
Great.
No worries, Arch.
Betty's got connections.
She'll know what to do.
[BETTY] It's okay, Kevin. He's a doctor.
We can trust him.
Oh,
and bring small bills.
Elizabeth.
Don't tell me this is your doing.
I sent the invitations
from the Gargoyle King.
What?
And, look, you all came.
What are you up to?
All of the secrets end now, Mom.
And this was the only way to do it,
to get all of you together.
Someone in this room is a murderer.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Alice, we promised each other
we would never talk about this.
I mean, who else did you tell?
I told Betty to protect her,
so she wouldn't play the game.
And it worked. I'm not playing the game,
but many of your kids are.
This is about protecting
them, don't you care?
Care? Josie had a seizure this morning.
I should be with her right now.
Not here rehashing the past
when it has zero relevance.
Attorney McCoy, it is relevant.
Your daughter is playing the game,
along with Kevin and Cheryl,
and even your son Reggie, Mr. Mantle,
no matter how many
black eyes you give him.
I would never hit my son.
Another lie.
Guys, it was bound to get out sometime.
Our children need to know the truth.
So, Betty, where do we start?
With the dead warden
from Archie's juvie.
He was also the RROTC instructor
when you guys were in high school.
Mr. Keller, you were
a cadet at the time.
Did you play the game with him?
Major Norton just confiscated it.
Straight manual, that's all.
Mr. Lodge, you had business
dealings with Warden Norton
until he died.
What were they?
And did you know that
he was playing G&G?
None of your business,
and not a clue.
And what about Ascension
Night? Was he there?
How are we supposed to answer that?
We're all high off our gourds
hallucinating gargoyles.
Wait, FP,
you saw it too?
Oh, this is such a waste of our time,
and I actually have a job
that I need to get back to,
so if you'll excuse me.
No, Hiram.
Let's just get this over with.
Otherwise, it will never end.
Betty, you wanna know
who poisoned the chalice.
The Game Master is the
one who sets up the game.
So, my instinct is telling me that
the culprit was Penelope Blossom.
My guess is maybe she grew
the poison in her greenhouse.
You don't grow cyanide, Hermione.
A fact that only a Blossom would know.
It was Daryl Doiley.
We were both Game Masters,
and he was secretly in love with me.
He put poison in the chalice,
because he wanted us to ascend together.
But I said no.
I assumed
the chalices were emptied afterwards,
but they were not.
Years later, Daryl came to me
riddled with guilt over
that tragic incident,
and seeking comfort.
And I refused him again.
We were both married
with families and...
I was afraid, you see,
of revisiting that unholy night.
So, he left.
The next day
he was found dead in his garage,
sitting in his sedan,
engine running, windows up.
[SIGHS]
Dilton Doiley's dead. Dad did it.
Well, that explains how Dilton
got his hands on the game,
and why he started playing it.
No, but that doesn't explain
who the Gargoyle King is today.
- Jughead and I saw him.
- What do you mean, you saw him?
In Fox Forest, and we've been
trying to track him down ever since.
Why do you think Jughead
started playing the game?
He's not still playing, is he?
I'm afraid so, Mr. Jones.
And he's made some
really weird connections
between the game and Riverdale,
which he wouldn't have...
Look, I've heard enough of this.
The boy is gonna be the death of me.
Satisfied, Elizabeth?
No, Mom.
Not even close.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Thanks. Did you find Joaquin?
[BOY] Centreville Serpents spotted him
at the Last Resort Youth Hostel.
- We're on our way now.
- Grab him.
Take him to Fox Forest
near the foot bridge.
- I'll meet you there.
- On it, boss man.
Going somewhere, boy?
Yeah, I'm gonna go meet the Serpents.
Yeah? Like hell, you are.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
What I should have done the
second I saw you playing.
You're addicted.
G&G's like a drug. It's
gotten into your blood.
I'm not addicted.
I just need to ascend,
so I can find the Gargoyle King,
and put an end to all this.
You're right.
You sound nothing like
an addict. My mistake.
It's time for you to sober up, boy,
for your own good.
[GROANS]
Keep it clean and dry.
As for the infection,
I have some antibiotics
in the back room.
That is, if you have something for me.
Thank you, Dr. Curdle Jr.
Betty said to pay you in small bills.
[SIGHS] Archie, we should
get back to the bunker ASAP.
I can't go back there, Kev.
I'm going to Shadow Lake to those mines
to find the guys responsible
for putting me away.
How far do you think you're
gonna get on foot and alone?
Will you help me, Kev?
Veronica is going to kill me.
[SHERIFF MINETTA] Okay, Donnie.
Let's try this one more time.
Come on. I don't have all day.
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
It's been edited.
[HIRAM] Veronica.
Are those Archie's case files?
He's not going to be behind
bars ever again, Daddy.
That's a promise.
[DOOR CLOSES]
There are too many
variables up at Shadow Lake.
Take care of them.
All of them.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[BETTY] Jug?
- Are you...
- Betty.
Are you hungry?
Jug, what the hell?
You don't happen to have one of those
trusty bobby pins on you, do you?
Always.
Did your dad do this?
Yeah. He doesn't like me playing G&G.
That's my fault. I'm sorry.
It came out when I was
talking to all of our parents.
Yeah. How'd that
sit-down go, Miss Marple?
Penelope Blossom said
Daryl Doiley is the one
who poisoned the chalices.
Oh.
Dylan's dad?
- You think...
- Dead? Yeah.
Pretty convenient, right?
The one man who can't confirm
or deny Penelope's story.
- So, I don't buy that.
- Neither do I, Jug.
So, I called Dr. Curdle Jr.,
and asked if he could pull
Mr. Doiley's autopsy report for us.
Do you think you can
handle this one by yourself?
Sweet Pea and Fangs
may have found Joaquin.
Just be careful, Jug.
I know we're getting
close to something, Betty.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Veronica, what's up?
Seriously, Kevin,
you had one job to do.
Put Archie on right the hell now.
Don't blame Kev, Ronnie. It was all me.
If you tell me you're
going to Shadow mines...
I am. It's my one shot to clear my name.
No, it's not.
I found something.
Ten minutes of Sheriff
Minetta's interrogation
of the Shadow Lake boys was deleted.
I just have to find the missing footage.
But wouldn't that have
just been destroyed?
No. My father always hangs on to dirt,
in case he needs to
lord it over someone.
Do you think it's in his study?
Something as radioactive as this?
He'd keep it far away from himself.
Closer to,
let's say, the Mayor's office.
Well, it's worth a look, Ronnie,
but it's not gonna change my plans.
Fine.
But you tell Kevin that if
he doesn't get you back to me
in one piece,
I will eviscerate him.
[PANTING] So, what's the plan?
I mean, what if these guys are armed?
And you're a sneeze away
from tearing those stitches, Archie.
I'm fine. Shh.
Always my birthday.
Holy crap.
Please be it.
[SHERIFF MINETTA] Okay, Donnie.
Let's try this one more time.
Ten thousand a piece,
and all you have to say is
that you saw Archie Andrews
kill your friend Cassidy Bullock.
If that's not proof of coercion,
I don't know what is.
Come on, Internet.
Come on.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[GLORIA] She's in here.
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
- Come on.
- Hello.
[KEYS JANGLING]
I'm the Mayor's daughter.
I have a right to be here.
False. Her mother and
father specifically told me
to call the Sheriff's Department
if she ever broke in again.
Okay, this is not necessary.
- [MAN] Get up.
- [JOAQUIN GRUNTING]
[MAN] Get up!
[JOAQUIN GRUNTING]
Look what we found on him.
[GRUNTING]
So you jumped ship
for the Gargoyle gang?
You have a lot of explaining to do.
[GASPS AND COUGHS]
So why don't we start
with why you shivved Archie
instead of protecting him,
like you were supposed to.
The Warden said I had no other choice.
You don't know what it
was like in there, Jug.
You do anything to survive.
For me, it was being the
Warden's pawn. A... A chess piece.
In some ways, he was a pawn, too.
What does that mean?
I saw him with these game cards
that... that told him what to do.
Whoever sent them to
him wanted Archie dead.
From the moment he was locked up,
he was already marked.
[JUGHEAD] Marked with what?
This symbol...
the Warden branded on Archie's hip?
What does it mean?
No. No.
Pick him up.
- No, no! Argh!
- Get up!
Hey, just... Just stop.
[WHISPERS] Just stop.
Sacrifice.
It means that...
It meant that Archie had to die.
I... I'm sorry, Jug, I
know he was your pal. I...
Oh, Archie's alive, Joaquin.
Then it won't be for much longer.
Who's giving Warden Norton his orders?
No.
Okay.
- I don't think you understand, Joaquin.
- No.
I can't let you go until you talk.
I saw them meet once.
But you know him, Jones.
The man in the black suit.
[JUGHEAD] An ancient evil,
long forgotten, has awoken.
The embodiment of pure
malice and cruelty.
So it's finally happened.
You've lost your mind.
You met Warden Norton in high school.
And all this time, you've
been sending him quest cards
instructing him how to
torture and then kill Archie.
You're not just the criminal
kingpin of Riverdale.
You're the Gargoyle King.
- What did you call me?
- The Gargoyle King.
The Ghoulies and this new gang
of Gargoyles are your soldiers.
Southside is your kingdom.
You orchestrated Archie's arrest
to put him under Warden
Norton's sadistic thumb.
The game is how you've
been communicating with him.
Pulling the strings.
Back in the day, you
killed Principal Featherhead
in the same way you tried to kill me
and in the same way you
tried to kill Archie.
You're the Gargoyle King, Hiram.
I'm not a 16-year-old nerd
playing games to live out my
overactive hormonal fantasies.
I'm not the Gargoyle King,
because you know what?
[WHISPERS] That's not a real thing.
Nor am I the murderer that you
and Betty Cooper are looking for.
But if homicidal parents
are what you're after,
may I suggest Clifford Blossom?
Hal Cooper? Tom Keller?
And perhaps...
even your own father.
They'd all make solid suspects.
[PHONE RINGS]
Now if you'll excuse
me, I have to take this.
[RINGING CONTINUES]
You'll see yourself out, won't you?
[SIGHS] This is Lodge.
She did what?
What exactly were you hoping to find
in your mother's office, Veronica?
Does Mom even know what you've
been hiding on her desktop?
Your mother doesn't
have a computer anymore.
I've requested to speak to a lawyer.
It's my right as an American citizen.
So get your lapdog, Sheriff Minetta,
to bring me to the phone.
Minetta. Hmm.
He's otherwise engaged.
But let me see what I can do.
[FRED] Yeah, Veronica, is everything okay?
Have you... Have you heard from Archie?
He asked me not to tell
you, Mr. Andrews. But...
Archie's headed for the mines
by Shadow Lake with Kevin
to look for the guys who
testified against him.
And my intuition tells me Sheriff
Minetta might be doing the same.
Okay, uh... I'm... I'm on the way.
Wait.
Tell Archie I found
what I was looking for.
I just have to get it to the judge.
- Veronica...
- Oh, and on that note,
would you also mind calling
Attorney McCoy for me?
[SIGHS]
[DIALING]
[BETTY] Okay, I'm confused.
Why is there no mention of carbon
monoxide in Mr. Doiley's file?
Because it was not the
cause of death, Ms. Cooper.
Daryl Doiley was indeed found in
a running car with the windows up.
But there was no trace of
carbon monoxide in his lungs.
That can only mean he
was dead beforehand.
Then how did he die, Dr. Curdle Jr.?
Oleander.
If ingested, it's one of the most
poisonous plants known to mankind.
In my opinion, Ms. Cooper,
Daryl Doiley's death was a
murder disguised as a suicide.
Can that be proven with this file?
Unfortunately, no.
This is from my father's
personal collection.
Fine. Then I'll just have to
question whoever closed the case.
Doctor, who was the Sheriff at
the time of Mr. Doiley's death?
- [BELL JINGLES]
- Thank you for meeting with me, Mr. Keller.
- Sure.
- Mr. Doiley's death was classified
a suicide by carbon monoxide
poisoning by your department.
Yet, oddly enough, there wasn't
a trace of it found in his lungs.
What is this, Betty? Is
this just another ambush,
because I didn't kill anybody.
Maybe not, but you're
complicit in a cover-up.
Who were you protecting?
All of us.
Your mother included.
Someone murdered Daryl Doiley,
and whoever was pulling
the strings back then
may be the one killing people today.
The truth is, it could have been
any member of the Midnight Club.
But only one of us grows
oleander in their greenhouse.
Now, I know this because I saw it
when I was investigating
Jason Blossom's murder.
- Uh, wait, Mr. Keller...
- [CELL PHONE BUZZES]
- Can...
- [CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Yeah, Fred. What?
Son of a gun. All right. All
right. I'll be right there.
- Mr. Keller...
- I gotta go.
[BELL JINGLES]
Come on.
[KEVIN GASPS]
Let's keep going.
- [KEVIN] Oh, my God.
- [ARCHIE] No.
It's the Shadow Lake crew, Kev.
[KEVIN] And Sheriff
Minetta was just here.
Hey.
[MAN WHIMPERING]
This one's still alive.
- We gotta get him to a hospital.
- Archie...
Sheriff Minetta shot
these guys because of me.
I can't have anymore blood on
my hands. Now grab his legs.
[ENGINE STOPS]
Someone's sending us a message, Jones.
- What's the message?
- Come on.
[JUGHEAD SIGHS]
Joaquin.
Who do you think did it?
Uh...
I don't know.
The Gargoyle gang or Hiram Lo...
[SIGHS] Could be anyone.
That symbol on his forehead...
Sacrifice.
I have to get to Archie.
[ENGINE REVVING]
We're too late.
For all we know, Archie and
Kevin never made it here, Fred.
- [LINE RINGING]
- Yeah, this is Tom Keller.
I'd like to report a multiple 187.
Two young men, Shadow Lake mine.
Gunshots.
Police were just called to Shadow
Lake hospital. A boy was brought in.
Critical condition with gunshot wounds.
- Is it Kevin or Archie?
- They can't tell me.
No ID. Come on. We should go.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES] I just heard from the nurse.
He didn't make it, Archie. They...
They say he lost too much blood.
I'm sorry, man.
Everywhere I go...
Everything I do just
leads to more death.
More pain.
Those guys would still be alive
if I wasn't in the picture.
Archie, let me remind you,
those guys weren't innocent.
Okay? They were...
They were criminals.
They didn't deserve to die for it, Kev.
Hiram Lodge has done everything
in his power to destroy me.
And he won't stop until I'm dead, too.
Even if by some...
Some miracle, my innocence is proven...
I don't think I can
go back to Riverdale.
Attorney McCoy, thank
you for posting my bail.
How's Josie doing?
She's resting And what
about you, Veronica?
You tell me.
If one has concrete proof of coercion,
and tampering of evidence...
would that be enough to
free the wrongfully accused?
[BETTY] Mrs. Blossom.
Please, Betty, call me Auntie.
Auntie Blossom...
Mr. Doiley died from oleander poisoning.
Do you have that flower
in your greenhouse?
Even if I wanted to
poison Daryl Doiley...
I wouldn't use oleander.
It leaves traces.
You know, Betty, I came here to help you
out of the kindness of my heart.
But if you're looking
for someone to accuse,
it was your own mother who wrote the
article reporting Daryl's suicide.
So maybe you should
ask yourself, and her,
what reason she had for
covering up a murder.
Well, do you have anything
to say for yourself, Mom?
[SIGHS] You have shaken
every tree today, Elizabeth.
I'm sure there's nothing left to say.
How about the fact that you helped
cover up Daryl Doiley's murder?
Oh, Betty, when will you stop?
When you stop lying to me, Mom.
Mr. Doiley didn't die from
carbon monoxide inhalation,
like you wrote in this article.
Someone staged it to
look like a suicide.
Someone afraid of what
Mr. Doiley might say.
Thanks to Sheriff Keller, there
was no murder investigation.
- You all have a hand in this.
- [SCOFFS]
You're all just circling
the wagons, playing a part.
Why, Mom? Who are you protecting?
Mom?
Stay here. I'm gonna
check the circuit breaker.
[BETTY] No, I'm coming with you.
[LOUD KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Who is it? Who's there?
- [KNOCKING CONTINUES]
- Mom...
Hello?
Betty, call 911.
[LOW CRACKLING]
[BOTH GASP]
[POPPING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
Oh, my God.
They were in here.
[LOUD CLATTERING]
Get behind me, Betty.
Mom.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I was looking for Jughead, but
someone slammed the door in my face.
- I was trying to get in.
- FP,
the Gargoyle King is in the house.
- He's in the house!
- Shh.
[WHISPERING] It's okay.
Excuse me. A boy was
brought here. He was shot.
- Dad?
- [SHERIFF KELLER] Hey.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Um... Where's Archie? Is...
He's okay, Mr. Andrews, but he's gone.
He, um, he left you something. A note.
Someone let you out of your cage, I see.
What do you mean, Hiram?
You didn't know, Mom?
Your husband left me in a jail cell
for putting my nose
where it didn't belong.
But it was so worth it.
What are you talking about?
Archie, of course.
I found the deleted tape of
Sheriff Minetta coercing witnesses.
Attorney McCoy is meeting
with the judge as we speak
to overturn Archie's conviction.
Your henchman, Minetta... [CHUCKLES]
is going down.
And if you two evildoers
go down with him...
So be it.
[ALICE] We're no longer safe, Betty.
And that attack was only the beginning.
It's become clear that you're
not gonna drop this investigation
no matter the consequences.
And this house is no longer safe.
Which is why...
I'm going to the Farm
with Polly and the twins.
Well, have fun, because I'm
definitely not going to the Farm.
No, you're not.
[DOOR OPENS]
Edgar said that you would resist
and that we should send you elsewhere.
Mom, what... What's happening?
Betty, there's no
safer place for you now.
The sisters protected
me. They protected Polly.
They'll watch over you now.
Mom...
Mom!
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you doing this?
Because I love you, Elizabeth.
Hey! Mom...
- Let me go! Mom!
- [CELL PHONE RINGING]
What do you mean he's gone, Kevin?
Believe me, I tried. Archie
said he couldn't come back.
Only because he doesn't
know he's been exonerated.
- And you let him go alone?
- Not... Not alone.
- He called...
- [CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Archie?
- [EXHALES] Veronica.
I'm so glad you called,
Archie. We did it!
Attorney McCoy worked it out
with the judge. You're a free man.
I shouldn't be
surprised. You're amazing.
I promised you'd be free by homecoming.
Veronica Lodge always keeps her word.
Thank you, Veronica.
For everything you've ever done for me.
No need to thank me, lover.
Just tell me where to pick you up.
[SIGHS]
Ronnie, I...
I can't come home.
Didn't you hear me?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Sheriff Minetta's going to
prison for a long, long time.
But your dad is still out there.
And I can't escape him.
As long as we're together,
he'll be hunting me down,
and everyone close to me is his target,
- and that includes you.
- Where are you?
I'm not letting you go off
God-knows-where and alone.
I'm not alone.
Ronnie, when I first met you...
you were it for me.
Everything I could have ever wanted.
I saw our whole future.
Because we're endgame, Archie.
I hope you know how much I love you.
[VOICE BREAKING] If you
loved me, you would come home.
Come on, Ronnie, you know in
your heart I'm right about this.
It just hurts to admit it.
Don't you make me say goodbye
to you, Archie Andrews.
Because I don't wanna
hear it back. [SOBS]
I can't.
I can't, I...
[SOBBING]
[SNIFFLES]
Goodbye, Veronica.
Some money, a change of clothes...
Granola bars, juice boxes.
Thank for coming out here, Jug.
Sure you wanna do this, man?
Leaving is my best option, Jug.
It's my only option.
I don't disagree.
[JUGHEAD SIGHS]
Joaquin is dead.
That symbol that you got branded on
your hip, he had one on his forehead.
It means "sacrifice."
What?
- Who the hell is doing this, Jug?
- I don't know.
I have a feeling Hiram
Lodge is a part of it.
He always is.
Don't worry, I'm not
letting you out of my sight.
You ever hop a train before?
[ARCHIE] No.
You'll figure it out.
I know you've looked down on our
practices in the past, Ms. Cooper,
but I want to assure you that
we're going to make you well.
You're safe with the
Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Nothing can hurt you in here.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --