Previously
on Riverdale...
So, my dad played G&G
in high school.
All of our parents did.
- What's that, Hiram?
- Fizzle Rocks.
This house is
no longer safe.
They'll watch over you now.
Mom! Are you out of your mind?
You're safe with the
Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Framing Archie for murder?
Conspiring to keep him
locked away?
An old-fashioned prison break
might be your best option.
You're breaking
Archie out of juvie?
Ten thousand apiece.
All you have to say is
that you saw Archie Andrews kill
your friend Cassidy Bullock.
Your henchman, Minetta,
is going down.
You know, if you added a
couple of slots, table games,
you'd have quite
the little goldmine.
Hiram Lodge has done
everything in his power to destroy me.
I don't think I can
go back to Riverdale.
- I'm not letting you go off alone.
- I'm not alone.
Leaving is
my best option, Jug.
The two young men
had been walking for days.
Looking at them, you might
think they were brothers.
And in a way they were.
Brothers.
Fearful that Hiram Lodge
might catch up to them.
Hi, this is Betty.
Leave a message.
- -
Hey, Betty, it's me.
I'm just trying you again,
hoping you're okay.
We're just looking
for a place to settle down.
I'll let you know
when we do. Okay. Uh...
I love you. Bye.
Still no answer?
Look, Jug,
maybe you should go back.
I'm fine.
Really, dude,
I'm gonna be fine.
Archie, no offense, but Betty took
down a serial killer last year.
You can't go for five minutes
without being kidnapped or getting
the crap kicked out of you.
That was before you were marked
for death by Hiram Lodge.
It would be nice to stop
looking over my shoulder all the time,
- just find somewhere to
settle, you know? -We will.
When we find the right place,
we'll know.
We're gonna feel it.
Or maybe we're already there.
Nice try. Let's get a couple
more miles in before nightfall.
Come on, Jug. We gotta bunk somewhere.
You're trespassing.
Now, let's see you do
a little turn, nice and slow.
Who are you?
I'm Cal. This is Biff.
From Centerville.
I don't like liars.
Shoot 'em, Gracie.
Wait! Wait.
We got robbed on a train.
They took all our money. We've
been walking for days. Just...
We're looking for some food and some
water, and we'll be on our way.
Put the rifle down.
- I don't trust them.
- Do as I say.
I'm Laurie Lake.
This is Gracie.
You boys like stew?
So, where's everyone else?
I only meant
a farm this size, I thought there
would be more people working it.
A lot of the men in town are
at a job down the river.
Our father and our brother went with them,
but they come back every now and then.
You guys have somewhere
to stay for the night?
- We're good.
- No.
We should be
getting out of your hair.
Or you could stay the night, if you
don't mind sleeping in the barn.
That would be amazing. Is there
anything we can do to repay you?
Just some farm work.
I have some bales of hay
I need to move.
Just stay
out of the main house.
Dude, we can't stay here.
One night, Jug.
What's the problem?
I don't now. Something about
this place weirds me out.
It's a little too American
Gothic, even for me.
You're right.
Where is everybody?
And when I asked her what
her dad and her brother did,
didn't it seem
like she was lying to us?
You mean, like we are, Cal?
Am I interrupting?
Nope. Not at all.
I brought some extra blankets in case you
guys get cold in the middle of the night.
Oh, thank you, Laurie.
All right.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
- Seriously?
- What?
We have to stay on task.
No distractions.
I totally agree.
Hey.
You missed eggs
and bacon for breakfast.
Meanwhile, you are
literally moving bales of hay.
Yup.
Feel free
to help out, too, Jug.
Actually, I was gonna head
into town for a little bit
and take some pictures
before we hit the road.
Remember?
Like we said we would.
Are you gonna be okay here?
I think I'll be fine, Jug.
Excuse me?
Hi.
I'm... I'm a little lost.
I saw some strange symbols
on the sides of the buildings.
They didn't look as faded as the rest.
You know what they mean?
The town wasn't
always like this.
First, it was
the Jingle-Jangle.
Now we're back
to Fizzle Rocks.
Fizzle Rocks?
Like the candy I used to eat
back when I was a kid?
That's normal Fizzle Rocks.
What we got nowadays is
laced with drugs.
As for them symbols,
they started
showing up in town
about the same time
Fizzle Rocks trickled in.
You've already done so much for me,
you don't have to do this too.
I used to do this
for my father.
And you did move all that hay.
My dad's
a construction worker,
so I'm used to physical labor.
Well, there's a lot of that
around here.
If you and your friend want to
stick around for a few days.
I'm not sure about Cal,
but I would be, I think.
There's something about this place
that just makes me feel at home.
I don't know why.
I'm sorry, Laurie.
I just... I can't
do this right now.
There's a girl back home.
There always is.
Even though we're not together
anymore, I still love her.
If you love her, Biff,
then why are you here?
Because of her father.
And my past with him.
Sometimes, when you're
trying to survive,
it's easy to lose sight
of who you are.
Laurie, my name's not Biff.
It's Archie Andrews.
And I'm from a small town
called Riverdale,
which I can't go back to.
Because of your girl's father?
Hiram Lodge, yes.
I'm sorry
I lied to you.
It's okay.
Archie Andrews.
Around here everybody's
running from something.
Let me see
about getting you some lunch.
Are you a King?
I'm actually a Game Master.
I started as a Hellcaster,
just like you.
- What level?
- I was three.
On my way to four.
Where did
you guys learn to play?
Our older brothers
used to play,
before they left town.
Yeah. I noticed that
there are no men here.
- All gone to work building a prison.
- Prison?
My brother told me
it's not just for prisoners.
It's for making
Fizzle Rocks, too.
So, the prison doubles
as a drug lab?
Where are you shackin' up,
Game Master?
Uh... Lake Farm.
Ugh. Gracie's house?
We used
to be friends with her.
Always acting like she's
too good for everybody,
even though her daddy works for
the Man in Black like ours do.
- Who's the Man in Black? -
He's always in a black suit.
He gets driven around
in a black car.
This town's his now.
Hiram.
I made you some more eggs,
I hope you don't mind.
No, that is more than okay.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
You helped me with the hay,
and you helped me pass
the time a little bit quicker.
So, in my book, we're even.
These are delicious.
Are you all right?
Come on, let's get you out of here.
Laurie knocked me out.
Where the hell is she?
She's inside,
with Hiram Lodge.
What?
I don't understand. How do
the girls even know him?
Shh. I think her dad
and her brother work for him.
They make drugs
inside the prison,
which all the kids take
when they play G&G.
All of this is
connected, Archie.
Hiram owns this whole town,
and probably many others
just like it. Let's go.
Or we could stay and fight.
- No, Archie.
- This is our one chance
to take it all back.
Hiram is gonna walk in here
thinking that I'm tied up.
Let's surprise him
and take him out.
That's a bad idea, trust me.
There's gotta be something
in here we could use,
- a pitchfork.
- Hey, look at me.
You're not thinking clearly. It's two
against four. And they have guns.
I get how bad you want this.
But we are under-prepared.
They're going to kill us.
Archie. Archie!
Look at me.
- Hey. Don't say what I think
you're going to say. -Jughead!
I can kill him.
- I can.
- I know.
But right now,
we've gotta go
while we still have time.
There's nowhere
he won't follow me.
I can't run from him.
Just let me end this nightmare
once and for all.
He's coming.
Archie, I know
he's ruined your life.
He's ruined a lot of lives.
But one day, he's going to get
everything he deserves. I swear.
But it's not today.
It's not right now.
- Okay? We have to go.
- Jughead...
All right, if you do this,
if you kill him,
will Veronica
ever forgive you?
Before I let you in,
to be clear--
Yes. Yes. Archie in exchange
for your brother and father,
their debt to me will be paid.
You have my word.
What the hell is
going on here?
Where is he?
You know,
for a second back there,
I didn't think
you were gonna listen to me.
Neither did I, Jug.
Neither did I.
You were right
about one thing though.
Hiram's gonna follow you,
or us, wherever we go.
We're always gonna be
outnumbered and outgunned.
So, what's the plan?
We'll go see my mom.
You sure we should do that?
Got a better idea?
What are you doing?
I'm leaving the Pembrooke.
Veronica.
I realize that
you're upset about Archie,
but you can't just
go running after him.
Save your breath, Mom.
I'm not going after Archie.
Okay. Then what's
this all about?
Convenient, isn't it?
Sheriff Minetta goes missing
just as I find
ironclad evidence
that he coerced those Shadow Lake
boys into giving false testimony.
Minetta was a corrupt man.
He had many enemies.
Is that a murder confession?
Okay. Veronica,
first of all,
I sincerely hope that
you don't believe
I'm capable of--
I honestly don't know
what to believe anymore.
Which is why I'm leaving this house
of horrors while I still can.
Maybe you should too.
He's my husband.
Right. Well, you and Daddy can
pop open a bottle of Cristal
because he finally did it.
He finally won. He finally drove
Archie and me away for good.
It's not the Five Seasons,
but it'll do.
- Morning, Pop.
- Veronica.
You're in early.
What time did you get here?
You know what they say
about the bird and the worm.
What's up, Ronnie?
Still bummed about Archie
bailing on the world?
That's on my list
of woes, yes.
What else?
We work all day and all night,
and yet we're
barely scraping by.
The numbers
just aren't adding up.
It may not be
the Copacabana yet,
but business is steady.
One thing I learned
from my father
is that steady is one bad
week away from broke.
We'll never turn a profit
selling five-dollar mocktails
to high schoolers
who sit here all day
playing some
stupid board game.
So, what you're saying is
we need
to start a side hustle.
So, now you want to turn
your speakeasy into a casino?
For one night only.
You yourself suggested it.
And I've done my research.
I've heard all about your very
exclusive blackjack club in the city.
So, I thought, "Who better to show
me the ropes than Mr. 21 himself"?
What's the deal on the table?
If you agree
to provide me with some games,
and if you bring some
of your high-roller friends
who are guaranteed to play,
I'll give you 10%
of the proceeds.
Fifty.
- Twenty.
- Thirty.
Twenty-five.
And that money will be
all yours, Elio.
Come on. Everything you do is
in your father's shadow.
Don't you wanna step out
on your own, finally?
How are you gonna
cover expenses?
The house always wins, right?
I'm counting on that
to be the case here.
But in terms of startup costs,
should the unthinkable happen,
I took out a second mortgage
against Pop's.
A gambler.
I like it. I'm in.
And, Elio, do me a favor. Let's
keep this arrangement between us.
I don't want any third-parties sticking
their noses into our business.
Nice uniform.
What are you doing here?
I'll take
a cafe con leche, please.
Anything else?
Your mother's
worried about you.
As am I.
We both know
you've been struggling
ever since
Archie abandoned you.
I also heard
through the grapevine
that you're hosting
a casino night.
- So?
Instead of coming to me
for advice and help,
you went
to one of our competitors?
It's ironic,
for all your high talk
on wanting
a legitimate business,
you're now inviting a bunch of
criminals over to play cards?
Times must be tough.
They're not criminals.
They're Elio's friends.
And how do you think Elio's family
built their gambling empire?
They're cheaters.
And criminals.
And they're gonna
rob you blind.
Yeah. Well, you would know
all about that, wouldn't you?
Are you angry about something?
Am I angry?
You drove Archie away.
Did I? I swear I read in the papers
that he was cleared on all charges.
So you just came here to
twist the knife, is that it?
No.
I came here to remind you
who your true allies are.
Your mother and I,
we're still here for you,
to welcome you back
with open arms,
because we're family.
And that will never change.
Get out, Daddy.
Your drink, Ms. Lodge.
Just how you like it.
Perfect. Thank you.
Veronica.
See, Reggie. This is
exactly what we needed.
Thanks to Elio,
we're gonna pull in bank.
Yeah. Or he's gonna break it.
What do you mean?
Your generous friend Elio is
on a hot streak.
He hasn't lost
a single hand all night.
He's gonna wipe us out.
We're gonna be bankrupt.
I thought
the house always wins.
How is this happening?
He's gotta be cheating.
I'm not surprised,
'cause my father said
Elio's a criminal
from a family of criminals.
Want me to rough him up?
Throw him out?
No.
That's not
how we do things here.
Especially not to a member
of a crime family.
But don't worry, Reggie.
Veronica Lodge is not about
to go quietly into the night.
- Dealer bust.
- Yes.
Hey, Elio. Big night?
I've never had
such a run of luck.
Hope this doesn't put
a huge dent in your take.
You mean our take?
Well, it seems like
either way, I win.
Do yourself a favor,
cash out.
And walk away
while you still can.
Or what? You'll call
your father for backup?
I heard you weren't
even on speaking terms.
Deal me in.
- What are you doing?
- Raising the stakes.
One hand of blackjack, winner takes all.
Just you and me.
What am I playing for?
This.
The deed to Pop's.
And, by extension,
La Bonne Nuit.
Fine. You asked for it.
Let's play.
Twenty.
Nineteen.
I'll tell you what, you'll always
be welcome at my speakeasy.
I might even
rename it "Veronica's."
The game's not over yet.
Trust me, princess.
It's over.
Hit me.
Twenty-one.
Ms. Lodge wins.
That... That's impossible.
Why, Elio?
The house always wins.
Isn't that what they say?
You made some serious coin, V.
We did.
We're in the black, Reggie.
It was
a very successful night.
Hmm. You could
have lost it all,
you know? But you didn't.
You pulled it off.
I swear, I thought
Elio was cheating.
Can you keep a secret?
Mmm-hmm.
A couple of hours before we
opened the doors to casino night,
my father summoned me
to his study.
What is it, Daddy?
You said you had some important
news to share with me,
and I'm on a bit
of a time crunch.
Some business associates
have informed me
that your friend Elio has nefarious
intentions going into your casino night.
Something you're not aware of.
Like what?
Like he's planning on fleecing you
because he thinks you're weak.
Because you're no longer
under my protection.
Okay.
Say I believe you,
what would you suggest I do?
You beat him
at his own game.
Like his father,
Elio is a compulsive gambler.
The bigger the pot, the more
he wants to stay in the game.
The best way to beat players like
this is fast, with no remorse.
One hand, winner takes all.
The deck's stacked
in your favor.
The deck's stacked.
Wait, so you want me to cheat?
It doesn't matter
how you win, mija,
so long as you're
the last man standing.
Now, I have the name of a dealer
you might want to bring in.
Johnny Goldwater.
He's got nimble fingers.
Twenty-one.
Wow!
So, you scammed the scammer.
Oh, Reginald,
it doesn't matter how you win,
so long as you're
the last woman standing.
Was it a good night?
Yes. It was excellent.
You know, this place has been
in my family for generations.
It's a family place, at heart.
Crime-free.
Pop.
The speakeasy wasn't making enough money.
And neither was the diner.
So, I had to take a big swing.
Bend the rules a bit.
Please.
For your own sake, Veronica,
don't be like your father.
Pop, deep, deep down,
maybe my dad's not so bad.
You haven't heard
the news yet, have you?
Sheriff Minetta's body was
found in the marsh last night.
At least they think
it was his body.
They don't know for sure
'cause it was decapitated.
And the hands were sawed off.
Make them think
that you're sane.
Tell me
what you see, Elizabeth.
A dead body,
you idiot.
I see a toy.
A teddy bear with a bow tie.
Just pass this test,
and then you can
start investigating.
And what
do you see now?
The Black Hood.
A butterfly.
A Monarch butterfly.
Hmm.
And now?
Remember
to smile, Betty,
and you'll be
out of here in no time.
The old jungle-gym
at Riverdale Elementary.
I used to play on it
every recess.
Very interesting.
Step forward, Nellie.
It's time for your candy.
My mom
and her delusions.
She has a fondness
for this place.
She thought the sisters would
keep me safe
from the Gargoyle King.
She probably didn't realize she was sending
me right into the belly of the beast.
- What is this?
- A treat.
Every patient gets candy
for good behavior.
Fizzle Rocks.
AKA, drugs.
Why are
the sisters dosing us up
with the same stuff
the Midnight Club took
the night of Principal
Featherhead's murder?
Thank you so much.
Bless you, my child.
And what-oh-what
is in that file, I wonder?
How are
you settling in, roomie?
Ethel.
What are you doing here?
Sister Woodhouse thought
that you might benefit
from having a roommate who's familiar
with the system around here.
What a nightmare.
Fun.
Uh, did you just come
from art class?
Oh, no.
That's my warrior board.
It's like a visual collection
of my destiny.
It also helps me
manifest my goals.
If I didn't already
have an escape plan,
I'd really start
going crazy in here.
As soon as I have what I need,
I'll find the door marked "X"
in the basement that Veronica
used when they broke Cheryl out.
Isn't the King marvelous?
Ever since I came here,
I've been having the most
wonderful conversations with him.
Wait, what are you saying?
That you've actually been talking
to the Gargoyle King in person?
Yes. We've become very close.
Really?
Do you think
you could introduce us?
No. That's
Sister Woodhouse's job.
What is?
The sisters take patients into the Gargoyle
King's chamber when they misbehave.
The other girls are
scared of him, but I'm not.
Uh... Where's his chamber?
I can't tell you.
That's Sister Woodhouse's job.
Hmm. You'd tell Jughead.
About Jughead.
I wasn't going to mention this,
but, since you brought him up,
Betty,
I don't think Jughead's
into you anymore.
We connected when we played
the game together, and
things got pretty hot
and heavy in the bunker.
This psycho bitch.
Oh, he definitely told me
about how you blackmailed him
into kissing you.
I knew you would do this.
You have always acted
like you're better than me.
- You and all your shallow friends.
- What are you talking about?
This isn't Riverdale High.
The rules are different here.
I'm the queen bee.
Not you, Betty Cooper.
And if you wanna get better,
you have to
change your attitude.
And you have to be honest
with yourself,
and with others.
And you can start
with what you threw
into the trash.
Ethel, I'm sorry.
I want to be your friend,
if you'll have me.
Can you just not
tell anyone about the candy?
Could you just
keep it between us, please?
Roomie?
Okay, Betty. I'll keep
it our little secret.
Thank you.
But you really should
take the candy.
It's super delicious.
Be careful
of the thorns, girls.
Very good, my child.
That's funny.
The sisters don't serve
maple syrup in the cafeteria.
And why would Claudius Blossom
be making the delivery?
Wait, what the hell?
What kind of business does Hiram
Lodge have with Sister Woodhouse,
and how are the Blossoms
connected to it?
Hey. Do you know who that is?
They call him
the Man in Black.
He's an angel donor.
Helps the sisters
with anything they may need.
Isn't that nice of him?
Yeah. Amazing.
Wait a minute.
According to my mom,
Hiram was the one
who brought the Fizzle Rocks
to Ascension Night
all those years ago.
Back to it, Betty. Idle hands
make the devil's work.
Bite me.
What did
Hiram give the sisters?
And what did
Woodhouse give him?
Maybe there's a clue in those
files they're keeping.
If I can just find the right
office or records room.
Wait, this must be the Gargoyle King's
chamber Ethel was talking about.
What do you think
you're doing?
This area is off-limits.
Ethel, I...
Do you know where
the medical archives are?
Sister Agnes sent me to fetch
some files. I got kinda lost.
Silly Betty.
Only the infirm are
allowed in the infirmary.
It's time to go back
to our room now.
While I'm watching.
Okay.
Acting normal.
This is me, acting normal.
All I need is a pen, a bobby pin
that hasn't been dulled down, or...
A paper clip. Bingo.
Hey, Betty. Come play with us.
Uh, no thanks, Ethel.
Betty, you said
we were friends.
And friends play together.
This isn't how I imagined
myself getting to those medical files.
But since only the infirm go
to the infirmary...
You wanna be
real friends, Ethel?
Hmm. That's weird, because real friends
don't kiss each other's boyfriends.
That's because
the Gargoyle King wants
- Jughead and me to be together.
- Oh, yeah?
We're gonna be a ship.
Oh.
Ethelhead?
In your dreams.
You're just jealous.
You're jealous that Jughead
and I are worthy,
and you're not,
but here's the thing, Betty.
Okay? You're never
going to be worthy.
And the Gargoyle King,
you're never gonna meet him.
Here we go.
Sister Woodhouse, help!
She's having a seizure.
Ethel, get the nurse.
Yes, Ethel,
get the nurse.
And God willing, she'll take
me exactly where I need to go.
There, there, Elizabeth.
You're going to be all right.
We'll get you
to the infirmary.
Well, they bought it.
They actually believe
I had a seizure.
Let's re-evaluate her dosage
as soon as possible.
Yes, Sister Woodhouse.
Jackpot!
There you are.
"Elizabeth Cooper."
"Two doses of Bullio Lapis,
mornings only.
Sporadic seizures.
Patient seems to be
responding well to testing.
Per H.L., increase dosage
after first week."
H.L.?
Oh, my God!
Is Hiram Lodge using patients
at the Sisters' as lab rats?
And what is
Bullio Lapis? Unless...
Fizzle Rocks.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Now that I have my proof,
it's officially time
to get the hell out of here.
The door to escape is
in the basement.
"X" marks the spot,
just like Veronica said.
I'm so out of here.
No.
No. No!
There she is.
Ethel. Sister Woodhouse.
I just... I got lost again.
I told you she was up to
no good, Sister Woodhouse.
Restrain her.
No.
No!
What are you doing,
Sister Woodhouse?
You've been
a very bad girl, Betty.
You haven't been
taking your candy.
Ethel.
- Steady her.
- No. No!
My King. My savior.
Guide me through the night.
Bless me with your darkness,
gift me with your flight.
She needs a good, strong talking
to from the King, I think.
I was wrong.
You are gonna meet the King.
No.
The King awaits you.
Now, let's try this again,
shall we?
Tell me what you see, Betty.
A dead body.
What do you see now?
The Black Hood.
And now?
The Gargoyle King.
Wonderful, wonderful work.
You've already made progress.
My King, my savior.
Guide me through the night.
Bless me with your darkness,
gift me with your flight.