[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
Ladies, gentlemen. Been months
in the making, but we're here.
Welcome to the new Southside.
You asking me to join the Serpents?
I wondered how you felt
about being my queen.
I'll sell the Whyte Wyrm to you,
for Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
[Betty] No more evil.
You have no power over me.
I have someone who can help you, Mom,
from the Farm.
Needs a lot of work, Dad.
But I'm up for it if you are.
[Weatherbee] And your new student
body president, Archie Andrews.
[all cheering]
You got Andre to kill that boy
at Shadow Lake, Cassidy.
When I do prove this,
I'll just come for you.
[Hiram] Steps have been taken to dissolve
the glue that holds them together.
Sheriff, what are you doing?
You're under arrest for the murder
of Shadow Lake resident Cassidy Bullock.
[Jughead] It's the
calm before the storm.
The summer before your junior year
in high school.
And how do you spend it?
Working some brutal summer job
that actually makes you look forward
to going back to school.
Or maybe you have an internship
that doesn't pay much.
That's okay,
because it's for a good cause.
- [woman] Focus on that.
- [Mary] No, no. See what I mean?
[Jughead] Or... maybe you spent it
at Sweetwater Swimming Hole.
You... and the best friends
you'll ever have.
Or maybe you spent most of June,
July, August in a courtroom,
supporting our pal, Archie Andrews,
who was on trial
for a murder he didn't commit,
despite the DA's closing arguments.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
the evidence and testimony
that was presented
in this court tell a dark story.
That Mr. Andrews has a history
of violent behavior.
That he started not one,
but two masked vigilante groups.
That he assaulted an innocent boy,
who was helpless with two broken legs.
That he went wilding
in the Southside of town,
and threatened to shoot a young man
in the face.
That while partying with his friends
in the town of Shadow Lake,
Mr. Andrews ran into the woods
and shot the victim, Cassidy Bullock,
point-blank in the head.
Now, Mr. Andrews claims
that it was his girlfriend's father's
doorman who shot Mr. Bullock.
A shot Mr. Andrews claims
to have heard, but not seen.
[gunshot]
Who knows the truth of what happened
that terrible night
in the woods near Shadow Lake?
I'll tell you who.
That man.
Archie Andrews may be a varsity athlete,
and he may be a sensitive musician...
but he is also...
a cold-blooded killer.
Ladies and gentlemen, we know for a fact
that Archie Andrews constantly puts
the needs of others ahead of his own.
We know that he helped
to solve the murder of Jason Blossom.
We know that he offered both friends
and enemies shelter
when they had nowhere else to stay.
We know that he punched
through a river of ice
to save the life
of his classmate Cheryl Blossom.
Well, let me remind you that there
were no witnesses to the actual killing.
There was no murder weapon.
There is no motive.
At the end of the day,
all the prosecution has
is cloudy testimony
from unreliable people.
Now, it is my solemn duty,
as a mother, to protect my son.
But as an attorney,
it's my duty to adhere to the facts,
to the evidence.
There is nothing here that proves
that Archie Andrews is anything less
than an innocent boy.
Thank you.
Thanks, Mom.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
the charge is first-degree murder.
You may retire
to begin your deliberations.
[bailiff] All rise.
Okay, can you just level with us, Mom?
What do you think Archie's chances are?
Baby, I'd say fifty-fifty.
If you had to come down
on a side, Mrs. McCoy?
- You were great in there, Mary.
- Thank you, Fred.
It's only the most important case
of our lives.
You were amazing, Mrs. Andrews.
Well, Betty,
your help this summer was a godsend.
- [chuckles]
- Have you guys seen Archie?
[sighs]
[Veronica] Archie?
There you are.
How you holding up?
Yeah, good, Jug.
What were you thinking about just now?
How you're gonna walk out
of this courthouse a free man?
No, I...
There was this place...
we've never been before, Ronnie,
but Betty and Jug,
remember Sweetwater Swimming Hole?
- We went every summer.
- I was just thinking about that place.
Yeah, me too. What made us stop going?
Oh.
Probably when we got covered in leeches.
Was that us, or was that a movie?
- Definitely us.
- [Jughead] That was us.
I'd like to go.
- Hopefully you can take me, Archie?
- Hopefully.
[Kevin] Guys.
It's time.
Judge asked us back into the courtroom.
[judge] The jury is still deliberating.
But I've dismissed them.
They're sequestered,
and I've instructed them
not to read anything about this case,
nor to discuss it with anyone.
We'll reconvene Tuesday morning,
after Labor Day.
My advice to you, young man,
is to spend this weekend with
your family and your loved ones.
That's all.
This just buys us more time
to figure out what we need next.
Hey, Archie.
- Have a terrific weekend.
- [Mary] Fred!
- [Archie] Dad, stop.
- No, no.
Guys, guys. Come on.
Hey, stop.
Enjoy.
Thanks, Pop.
Dilton. Ben.
What are you guys playing?
- It's called Gryffins...
- Shut up, Doiley.
If we could only find the gun
that Andre used to kill Cassidy.
[Veronica] I've torn
The Pembrooke apart.
After the riots, my father wiped any
and all traces of Andre.
He wouldn't have brought it back
from Shadow Lake.
- That's probably where he ditched it.
- So, we go back to Shadow Woods?
- We've looked.
- Let's look again. With metal detectors.
If we get Andre's gun,
we can plant it on...
- No.
- [Archie] No.
I don't wanna do that,
spend what could be my last weekend
looking for evidence that isn't there,
planting it who-knows-where.
Archie, we have three extra days
to prove that you're innocent.
- What would you have us do, Archie?
- What the judge said.
After the worst summer ever,
I want us to have a great,
normal Labor Day weekend.
Can we do that?
If that's what you really want,
Archiekins.
It is, Ronnie.
So, what should we do?
[Willa J's "Like It or Not" playing]
♪ Like it or not ♪
♪ When I get going
They know where I'm gonna stop ♪
♪ That's what I do
Like it or not ♪
♪ That's who I am
That's who I be, that's what I got ♪
Greetings, chums. I
wanted to let you know
that after the three amazing months
I had with Toni,
riding motorcycles cross-country,
we're celebrating with an epic
end-of-summer pool party at Thornhill.
You're all invited.
Of course, given the fact that Archie will
most likely be walking the green mile
while the rest of us
are walking the stage at graduation,
I understand if you're not up for it.
Invite who you want,
but give them fair warning:
I'm in the mood for some hell-raising.
Toodles.
♪ La-la-la-la-la
La-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Like it or not now
That's who I am ♪
[Alice] So, you've written down
your words for the release ritual?
[Polly] Yeah. How about you?
- [Alice] I'm working on it.
- [Polly] Betty. Come.
Have some milk oolong tea.
It's an incredible detoxifier.
No, I'm okay, thanks.
Where are you off to?
Another therapy session?
No, Dr. Glass is tomorrow.
I'm going over to Archie's.
Honey, before you go back to school,
I think it's important that you spend
some quality family time together.
- Edgar thinks it's important.
- Oh, yeah. Edgar from the Farm.
No. Yeah. We'll...
We'll talk about that later, Mom.
Can I just say, Mr. Andrews,
watching you punch Hiram Lodge
in the face was...
incredibly cathartic.
Almost got me landed in jail.
[grunts]
All right, give it a try.
You do the honors.
[clearing throat]
[car starting]
[Fred chuckles]
[engine revving]
Yeah. There you go.
[car turns off]
- We did it, Dad.
- Yeah, we did.
We sure did.
Just in time.
Guys, excuse me a second.
I'm gonna go in the house.
Betty.
I have to ask you a favor.
If I do go away...
will you check on my dad?
Invite him over for dinner?
Once my mom goes to Chicago,
he'll be alone.
Arch.
The jury is still deliberating.
That's a good sign, okay?
You don't need to put
your house in order.
Betty, promise me.
Please.
Of course.
[Veronica] It's not gonna work, Daddy.
Your Iago-like attempt
to keep me and Archie apart?
It'll fail.
Veronica,
I've no idea what you're talking about.
How about a refresher?
Framing Archie for murder.
Conspiring to keep him locked away.
You set all of this in motion.
I know it, everyone knows it.
Only you can stop it.
So, stop it.
Do it now.
But, mija, I have nothing
to do with this.
That boy is a criminal
with a history of violence.
He's innocent.
You know he is.
He doesn't deserve this.
He'll be alone in there.
He'll die in there.
- Archie brought that upon himself.
- No. You.
You can change everything.
Please, Daddy.
- It's beyond my control.
- I'm begging you, as your only daughter:
Help Archie.
Save him.
Please.
It's simply beyond my control.
We know Hiram took over the Southside,
'cause he's colluding with the Ghoulies.
But I need to know
what he's up to exactly.
All right, Fangs, you're up. I need
you to find the Ghoulies' new lair.
If you see them, don't engage with them.
This is just a recon mission.
Can't be risking another gang war.
I just need confirmation
that what Hiram's up to
has nothing to do with the Serpents
or Riverdale High.
Will do. You got it.
Hey, boy. Come have a look.
[chuckles] Might be my best one yet.
How's it feel to be an honorary Serpent?
Feels pretty savage, Jug.
Archie, the first thing I learned
at Southside High
was that you need to roll with a crew
to survive.
There'll be Serpents
in juvenile detention.
Find them. Sit with them.
That tattoo's gonna get you in,
- but it's also gonna get you protected.
- [FP] Yeah, Jughead's right.
Up to a point.
Serpent ink will help
keep your body safe,
but you still gotta worry
about protecting this, eh?
I speak from experience.
Your mind is the first thing
that goes when you're locked up.
But if you can keep your head on
straight, you can get through anything.
You just...
gotta keep your wits about you, Red.
Mom, what are you doing with my diaries?
I was telling Edgar about them,
and he feels,
and I agree, you should burn them.
What are you talking about? Why?
You've been filling these pages
with so much pain
and suffering over the years.
You need to let that go.
Okay, Dr. Glass says journaling
is a perfectly healthy outlet.
And I respect what your therapist says,
Betty, but these diaries are your past.
And your past is crushing you.
- Edgar says that...
- What, Mom?
What does some guru
who's running a Heaven's Gate commune
for pregnant runaways
and wives of serial killers
have to say about my diaries?
We know that you look down
on the Farm, Betty.
But Edgar has done nothing but help me.
He's encouraged me to embrace everything
that I was ashamed of,
- and become the best version of myself.
- Mom,
- I can't deal with this right now.
- But...
Isn't that the problem?
You're not dealing with it.
The trauma from last year,
what happened with your father,
that Chic person?
You're running around a mile a minute,
and you need to be sitting still.
Listening to
what your soul is telling you.
Okay, I'm listening to my soul.
And what it's saying is:
"Get the hell away from your mother.
She's been body-snatched."
There's something else
you should know about Betty, Mom.
[Beach Boys' "Good Vibrations"
playing on speakers]
♪ I'm pickin' up good vibrations ♪
♪ She's giving me the excitations ♪
- ♪ I'm pickin' up good vibrations ♪
- ♪ Oom, bop, bop ♪
♪ Good vibrations ♪
Hey, Josie, never thought I'd say this,
but I'm excited for school
to start back up.
[chuckles]
Mostly 'cause I'll get to see you
in the halls every day.
Sweet Pea,
I told you when we started this,
our summer fling was gonna be just that,
a fling.
With a three-month expiration date.
Yeah, I know,
but haven't we been having a good time?
[chuckles] I'm not saying we haven't.
But nothing,
not even a tall, cool drink
of sweet water like you,
is gonna distract me from my music.
♪ When I look in her eyes ♪
♪ She goes with me to a blossom world ♪
So, Moose, you know those movies
where friends make a pact
to lose their virginity
by the end of the school year?
- Uh-huh.
- I've been thinking,
since we've been hanging
out all summer...
maybe we should make a similar pact
of our own,
but on a slightly accelerated timetable.
Like, by Halloween at the latest.
Reg, if I do go away,
you gotta step up and lead the Bulldogs.
I'm already captain, bro.
Yeah, I'm not talking
about on the field.
Work with Jughead to keep the peace
between the Serpents and the Bulldogs.
No more Circles...
Red, Dark, or otherwise.
Done. That bloody chapter is over.
Sick tat, by the way.
♪ I don't know where
But she sends me there ♪
♪ Oh, my, my, what a sensation ♪
♪ Oh, my, my, what elation ♪
[sighs]
- What you thinking about, babe?
- Archie Andrews.
He saved my life, Tee-Tee.
What happened that day on the river,
Cheryl... we've never talked about it.
I lost hope.
And I did something really stupid.
Archie Andrews was there to save me.
And now there's nothing I,
or anyone, can do to help him.
[sighs]
[pop music playing on speakers]
V?
Are you okay?
I went to see Mrs. Andrews
and Attorney McCoy...
to ask them to put me on that stand.
I wanted to get in front of that jury
to tell them the truth
about my father...
to see if that might make a difference,
but they said no.
That I was too late.
Maybe not, Veronica.
Josie.
Look, you didn't hear
this from me, but...
the jury's sequestered
at the Five Seasons, third floor.
Room 301.
And security's tight, but...
I think I can get you in.
[Betty] What are you thinking, V?
That I only need to get
to one jury member
to convince them that my Dad's
the villain here, not Archie,
for there to be a hung jury.
Which would give us more time
to prove Archie's innocent.
Jughead.
- What's up?
- It's the Ghoulies.
Those bastards have Hot Dog.
Are you absolutely
sure this was Hot Dog?
Hundred percent, man.
They must've snatched him on Riot Night.
He looked skinny. Don't think
the Ghoulies feed him enough.
Lucky those animals
aren't slow-roasting him on a grill.
- What do we do, Jughead?
- We'd be going behind enemy lines,
outnumbered,
open to attack from all directions,
and risking another gang war.
No Serpent left behind.
That includes our spirit animal.
Okay. We deploy after dark.
It'll be a stealth mission.
- Gonna be quick.
- [Betty] Jug.
Last time you went into
Ghoulie territory,
you were beaten
to within an inch of your life.
- He'll have backup.
- [Jughead] We'll be quick.
- They won't even know we were there.
- I'm coming with you.
- No.
- No. Don't you dare tell me
that it's too dangerous, Jug.
The Serpent Queen is a warrior queen.
So, if you're on the
front lines, so am I.
Okay.
Let's bring Hot Dog home, shall we?
[Mary] We tried to stack the jury
in Archie's favor.
Women, mothers. But I don't know.
Maybe it backfired.
Mary, you did everything that you could.
[sighs]
I don't know, Fred.
I just think if I hadn't left Riverdale,
if I hadn't gone to Chicago...
I was here and I couldn't stop Hiram Lodge
from getting his claws into our son.
Dad, Mom.
Don't blame yourselves for what I did.
Taking Hiram's side against you, Dad,
was the biggest mistake I've ever made.
But it was mine. It's on me.
You guys are the best parents
anyone could ask for.
Everything you've done for me,
I don't deserve it.
Whatever happens to me on Tuesday
is what I deserve.
No. You are a good kid.
You got manipulated by a mobster.
But you do not deserve
to be framed for murder.
Your mom... Son.
Your mother and I will always love you.
[Fred sighs]
Housekeeping.
Moonlighting, Ms. Lodge?
Sheriff Minetta.
I have to say, your
father knows you well.
He anticipated you might pull a stunt
like this.
[Hermione] Jury tampering?
Pero para Dios, what were you thinking?
What I've been thinking
for the past three months.
Archie. How do I help Archie?
Daddy's a monster, Mom. You know he is.
But you just stand by him, complacent,
like some Park Avenue trophy wife.
With all due respect, Veronica,
you're his daughter.
Now, that affords you a certain amount
of protection that I don't enjoy.
He'll never harm a hair on your head.
I can't say the same for myself.
I won't leave you alone
in the world with him.
- Mom...
- I'm a prisoner, Veronica.
But I am not his puppet.
[dog whimpering]
[Toni] It's been an hour,
and no sign of anyone.
All right. Sweet Pea?
You guys keep lookout.
Hey.
Hey, bud.
Hi, buddy.
Hiya, Jonesy.
Welcome back to the Southside.
- Cheryl...
- Not yet, cousin.
I thought this mangy mutt might get you
to show up.
- We need to talk.
- No, we don't, Penny.
- I'm here for the dog.
- If you didn't want trouble,
why have you sent spies all summer
to get in our business?
Back off.
Unless you want a replay of Riot Night.
Yeah. I've been sending scouts.
I was looking for Hot Dog.
Now that I got him...
we're good.
Not so fast.
Your jacket.
The Southside isn't yours anymore.
You're no longer the Southside Serpents.
Really, Penny? A jacket?
We could always just take it
off your limp, dead body.
I also heard Ponytail's a Serpent now,
your Northside queen.
Maybe we'll go after her next.
Fine. You can have the jacket,
as long as you and the Ghoulies
stay out of the Northside.
Oh, you don't get to make demands.
[screaming]
Cheryl!
Told you I'm in the
mood for hell-raising.
That's it. Just kill them all.
Cheryl, aim your next arrow
between Penny's eyes.
You and your Ghoulies take one step,
she'll release the arrow.
Cheryl doesn't miss.
Congratulations.
You just made the Northside fair game.
- Come on.
- [man] Little doggie.
See you soon, Jonesy.
Come here.
Hey. Come here.
Come here, boy.
Right, let's go.
Wait, stop.
Hey.
- Wait, stop.
- [gunshot]
That was...
[panting]
[FP] Hey, Dilton came by to see you.
- He did?
- Mm-hm.
- What for? Did he say?
- No, he wouldn't talk.
Weird kid.
No kidding.
So, how's Hot Dog?
Sleeping under the trailer,
but he's bouncing back.
Yeah?
How are you?
[Jughead sighs]
Uneasy sits the crown?
Well...
Penny's got the Northside in her sights,
Cheryl's a loose cannon...
Betty is a target, and, uh...
We're not the Southside
Serpents anymore.
Screw the Southside.
You're a Serpent...
by blood,
and no one can take that from you,
or any one of us.
[car horn honking]
The pharmacy called. Polly answered.
They can't complete
an Adderall prescription
that was requested by your doctor
because you had one refilled
in Greendale two weeks ago.
Then they must have
mixed up their dates.
I don't know.
I'll call Dr. Glass.
Except there is no Dr. Glass.
Polly did some digging.
He doesn't exist.
You've been forging prescriptions
for yourself.
We're worried about you, Betty.
You've been lying about
going to therapy,
now you're making up a psychiatrist
to scam medication.
Seriously, Mom?
You give me a hard time
for trying to re-up a prescription
that you shoved into
my hands a year ago?
It was before Edgar explained
the dangers of pharmaceuticals.
Okay, enough.
You're actually buying this Farm crap
that some huckster
named Edgar Evernever is selling you.
He's helping us move on.
- And he can help you, too, sweetheart.
- Oh, really?
Oolong milk and wanting
to burn my diaries
is helping you get over the fact
that Dad murdered four people
and tried to kill us?
If you genuinely believe that,
you are in denial, Mom.
No, Betty. You are.
Do you realize that that is the first
time you've mentioned Dad in months?
You call me and my friends crazy,
but you're the one with a secret life,
hoarding stolen drugs,
hiding from your pain.
You may hate the Farm...
but they healed me,
they healed Mom, and they can heal you.
But first, you need to admit
that you're sick.
[car horn honking]
[5 Seconds of Summer's
"Youngblood" playing]
♪ Youngblood
Say you want me ♪
♪ Say you want me
Back in your life ♪
♪ So I'm just a dead man
Crawling tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause I need it
Yeah, I need it, all of the time ♪
♪ Yeah, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You push and you push
And I'm pulling away ♪
♪ Pulling away from you ♪
♪ I give and I give and I give
And you take, give and you take ♪
♪ Youngblood
Say you want me ♪
♪ Say you want me
Out of your life ♪
♪ And I'm just a dead man
Walking tonight ♪
Last one in gets a Sticky Maple.
[all laughing]
♪ So I'm just a dead man
Crawling tonight ♪
♪ 'Cause I need it, yeah
All of the time ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ You push and you push
And I'm pulling away ♪
♪ Pulling away from you ♪
♪ I give and I give and I give
And you take, give and you take ♪
♪ Youngblood
Say you want me ♪
♪ Say you want me
Out of your life ♪
♪ And I'm just a dead man
Walking tonight ♪
Guys, no matter what happens in court...
this... is the best last day of summer
a guy could ask for.
Archie.
What if you make a break for it?
Past that tree line is a road that
goes through the mountains to Quebec.
- Jughead.
- Serpents north of the border
will keep you supplied.
You don't deserve this, Arch.
Any of it.
And what if I do?
- Why would you say that?
- Because I'm guilty.
I didn't kill Cassidy.
But I left him alone with Andre.
If I hadn't walked away that night,
he might still be alive.
And not just Cassidy, all of it.
All of last year.
I didn't kill anyone.
But I could've.
I have to take responsibility for that.
[Betty] Jug, I'm not ready
for summer to be over.
I don't think I can handle it.
What do you mean? Sure you can.
Jug, this summer, I haven't stopped,
or slept a wink, working
on Archie's case.
I've barely looked up since May, and...
My mom and Polly think
that I've been... hiding,
or avoiding, and they're right.
Maybe I should stop taking Adderall,
start seeing a therapist for real.
Either way, come Tuesday,
it'll all be over,
and I'll have to face everything.
Everything that has happened,
everything that will happen.
All these things
that I don't have control over,
they just terrify me.
Betty.
We're gonna get through it.
From now on, we're partners.
In Serpents, in life...
All of it. Okay?
Ronnie.
Whatever you're about to say, Archie,
please, don't make me cry.
If I do go away,
I don't want you visiting me
in that horrible place, okay?
Oh. Rest assured,
if the unthinkable happens,
I will be taking the bus every week,
with all the other prison widows,
and bringing you Magnolia cupcakes
from New York.
As well as working on your appeal.
I promise.
That's what I don't want,
you spending the rest
of high school waiting for me.
No. You are not breaking up
with me tonight, Archie.
- Ronnie, I...
- Archie.
I am not letting my dad take away
the one thing that I love.
It's not happening.
You know, it's weird, Ronnie.
The thing that keeps me up most nights
isn't that I might get shivved.
It's that I won't
graduate with you guys.
It's stupid, right?
I don't think that's stupid at all.
Are you ready, Archie?
Hey, come here.
Be a good boy, okay?
Good boy.
[knocking on door]
Hey.
- Mr. Jones, is Jughead home?
- I'll get the bikes warm. Hurry up.
Look, Dilton,
now's not really a good time, okay?
Ben and I... We thought
it was just a game.
A stupid role-playing game, but
it's not. It's so much more.
He's real.
Who?
Who is?
Look, I gotta get to Archie's trial.
The Gargoyle King.
Look, I can't talk right now.
Wanna wait here for a little bit?
Try and get some rest? Yeah? Okay?
We can talk about this when I get back.
- All right?
- Yeah.
[bailiff] All rise.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
Your Honor, we haven't.
- What does that mean?
- [man] We're deadlocked, six-to-six.
And it's not gonna change.
So be it.
The jury is dismissed.
Thank you for your service.
So, what happens now?
- Judge will declare a mistrial.
- We have to go through this again?
Shh.
[clears throat] Your Honor.
In lieu of another trial,
the State is prepared
to offer a deal for a lesser sentence.
Instead of prison, time served,
plus two years in juvenile detention,
if Mr. Andrews will plead guilty
to the crime of manslaughter.
- Your Honor...
- I'll take the deal.
- No, Archie.
- Archie.
- We have to discuss this.
- Mom.
I can't put you
and everyone else through this again.
Your Honor, I accept the deal.
Son, just so I have it straight,
though it's legally within your rights,
you're ignoring the advice
of your counsel,
your own mother.
Yes, Your Honor. I'm guilty.
Mr. Andrews,
the court accepts your plea of guilty.
You'll be taken directly
from the courthouse
to the Leopold and Loeb
Juvenile Detention Center,
where you will serve out your sentence,
beginning immediately.
Court is adjourned.
[pop music playing]
- I'm sorry, Mom.
- Oh, Archie. I love you so much.
We're gonna get you out of there, bud.
♪ What's on the other side ♪
♪ Is closer than it seems ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ Smoke up in the sky ♪
♪ You take my key ♪
♪ Mm, mm... ♪
I love you, Veronica.
No. You can't take him away.
He's innocent. He didn't do anything.
♪ Remember me here ♪
♪ Mm, mm, mm, mm ♪
♪ 'Cause I would walk through the fire ♪
♪ And I would give you ♪
♪ Every last breath
Till there's nothing left ♪
♪ And I would walk through the fire ♪
Hey. I've already written the appeal.
I'll file it from Chicago,
and as soon as we get a date...
We'll get him home, Mary.
One way or another.
[Keller] You have our word.
I'll prove that Hiram Lodge framed our
son and make the son of a bitch pay.
Whatever it takes.
[Hermione] This is Mayor Lodge.
Are you happy now, Daddy?
It all worked out,
just like you planned.
Archie didn't play by your rules.
He threatened you, so, you punished him.
You destroyed his life.
You think I did all this
to hurt Archie, mija?
Because he threatened me? No.
It's because you betrayed me.
This is your punishment.
You chose that boy over blood.
My own daughter.
You don't have a daughter anymore.
Dilton?
[birds flapping wings]
Dilton.
God.
- [grunting]
- Ben, Ben.
Hey, hey. Ben. Look at me.
Look at me. Come on.
Help! Help!
[babies crying
and people whispering nearby]
Mom?
Polly?
No.
[gasping]
Betty.
Oh, my God. Betty. Help.