[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
Are you engaged to Edgar?
Edgar and I have a deep understanding
of one another.
-How'd it go?
-Great.
No one suspects anything.
-Little last-minute boost.
-[Mad Dog] He's juicing.
-Take it to level the playing field.
-I don't take that stuff.
Something's wrong.
Ronson's on some kind of crazy drug.
We need a doctor.
[Jughead] You moved to town
to take the drug trade from Hiram Lodge?
Someone's looking
to reopen the candy store.
He needs
to know exactly what you're doing.
No, he doesn't.
[FP] You hurt a lot of people, Kurtz.
What were you thinking?
The ultimate quest.
One final game
for you and your family.
Save the little princess.
What the hell did you do? What did you do?
-[Jughead] Jellybean?
-Jellybean!
[Jughead] Dad.
[FP] The hell is that?
"I invite you to play a round
of Gryphons and Gargoyles,
the outcome of which will determine
Princess Jellybean's fate."
Hey.
Why is the door wide open?
What's wrong?
Where's JB?
She was taken.
By the Gargoyle King,
and his loyal servant Kurtz.
We have to find that son of a bitch.
Find him?
He's outside in the back of my cruiser.
Ms. Ronson?
Yes?
We did everything we could.
I'm very sorry.
[Elio] How did this happen?
[Patel] We'll know more
after the autopsy comes back.
We need to see him.
Of course. The nurse will show you.
[girls sobbing]
-Dr. Patel.
-Yes.
Listen, there's something you should know.
Randy was juicing.
Excuse me?
You gave it to him.
I would never give
one of my fighters drugs.
What Randy chose to put into his body,
unbeknownst to me,
is not my responsibility.
Well, aren't you manager of the year?
-His blood is on your hands.
-[Elio] No.
No, his blood is all over Archie's hands,
literally.
Better lawyer up, Andrews.
You killed him in that ring,
and you know it.
[shouts]
Where the hell is my daughter?
Tell me,
or I will kill you right here, right now.
Where are you keeping her, Kurtz?
With an associate.
Being very well taken care of.
-[shouts]
-[Jughead] He's not gonna tell us.
Accept the invite to play.
Let's see if you can bring Jellybean home.
[chuckles]
He's crazy.
How can we believe anything he has to say?
I've played this game enough
to know that guys like Kurtz
are completely devoted
to the Gargoyle King and his rules.
If we play, and we win,
we can get Jellybean back.
I'm sure of it.
We'll agree to your terms.
We'll play.
Of course you will.
First, your avatars.
Mr. Jones,
you'll be Deadeye,
like in high school.
Jughead...
you'll remain the Hellcaster.
And Mrs. Jones, you'll be...
the Alchemist,
I think.
Deadeye,
you're up first.
[Fred] Son, from everything you've said,
it's clear that Randy died
from those drugs.
An autopsy will support that.
You're innocent.
But I'm not, Dad.
I knew.
I knew Randy was juicing.
I could've stopped the fight,
but I didn't wanna forfeit.
If I had...
I'm never stepping into that ring
ever again.
I can't.
[Veronica] Thanks for meeting us.
I understand
I missed quite the fight earlier.
That's not why we're here.
Betty has a favor she wants to ask you.
Mr. Lodge,
my dad is incarcerated two hours away,
in a windowless cell.
It's a horrible place.
And he heard about your facility,
and how some of the cells even have views
of Sweetwater River.
Yeah, the waterfront rooms.
They're quite peaceful.
He would like to be transferred to one.
And I thought, since you own the place,
maybe you could help.
Think of all the publicity.
I'll see what I can do.
[cell phone buzzing]
-Mad Dog?
-What'd you do with the drugs I gave you?
-They're in my locker at the gym. Why?
-Archie, you need to get rid of them. Now.
Police showed up at Elio's gym.
Had a warrant. Did a full sweep.
They didn't find anything,
but what if they hit up El Royale?
-I'm on my way.
-I'll meet you there.
Come on, man. Hurry up.
I got it.
Hands up. Both of you.
[sirens wailing]
[man] Go ahead and check them.
He's got nothing to do with this.
You've reached your first challenge.
This one's easy.
It's called Cards on the Table.
Inside two of these pouches
is a white marble.
Inside the third is a black one.
If you choose the black one,
you must reveal your secret.
-Simple enough.
-Call it what you want.
We've been playing Secrets and Sins
since high school.
Alchemist.
Why don't you begin?
Hmm.
Be honest.
The King already knows
your darkest truths.
-I don't have any secrets.
-Mom.
Jellybean's life is on the line.
If you don't say something, I will.
What's he talking about?
I'm the new Fizzle Rocks dealer
in Riverdale.
And Kurtz used to work for me,
before he lost his damn mind.
What?
And you knew about this?
You didn't tell me, boy?
Don't blame him.
I told him not to say anything.
I wanted to keep you out of it,
to protect you, to protect the family.
How's that working for Jellybean?
Huh?
You're the reason
that this psycho kidnapped our daughter.
-You brought this into our lives!
-Dad.
I've heard enough.
We need to finish this damn game,
and get Jellybean back home,
safe and sound.
But there will be a reckoning.
Hey, Dad.
It's Josie.
Um... I saw you have a gig
at Tuba-dour in Seaside.
Uh, would you maybe
wanna grab some dinner beforehand?
Call me back, and let me know.
Well, everyone's gearing up
for the big wedding.
You know, between your mom and Edgar.
Yeah, I'm-- I'm aware.
There's also something else
you should know.
After the big wedding,
Edgar is planning
to adopt Juniper and Dagwood.
[sighs]
I posted your bail as soon as I could.
Thanks, Ronnie.
-We'll pay you back.
-That's the least of our worries.
Elio's been a busy bee.
[Elio] Randy Ronson's autopsy
has revealed the ugly truth.
And what truth is that?
That he was, indeed,
taking performance-enhancing drugs,
provided by his competitor,
Archie Andrews.
[Alice] Alice Smith repor--
This is nuts.
Elio's the one who gave Randy the drugs.
That may be impossible to prove.
He's setting me up
to take the fall, Ronnie.
-Am I screwed?
-With me in your corner?
Never.
I'm going to dog-walk that lying cad.
But we do need to play defense.
How do we do that?
First things first?
Drink up, boys.
[toilet flushing]
Man, this is humiliating.
Well, I guess you've never been on parole.
I am pleased to announce
that the results of the drug tests taken
by Archie Andrews and Mad Dog Moore
have both come back negative.
And as the investigation
into the horrific death
of Randy Ronson continues--
He murdered our brother.
Ms. Ronson, I assure you, Archie didn't.
You should fry for what you did.
Ms. Ronson,
believe me, if I could take back what--
Oh, did you get that?
I'm so sorry.
I wish it were me and not him.
I think you're not alone
in that sentiment, Andrews.
[Doris] Evelyn.
Have you already received
your meningitis vaccination?
No, the Farm doesn't believe
in putting foreign substances
into our bodies.
Check my file.
My father wrote Mr. Weatherbee a letter,
opting me out
-of all elective medical procedures.
-[sighs]
"Check my file."
I think I just might.
[thunder crashing]
"Transferred from St. Joe's Prep."
Finally, you've reached your next quest.
[thunder crashing and rumbling]
"Steal some treasure from the realm."
What treasure?
-He wants us to commit a robbery.
-You gotta be kidding.
-I'm the sheriff.
-Mm-mm. Not tonight.
Tonight you are the Deadeye.
And your target...
the tavern.
If everything is a parallel for Riverdale,
then the tavern is Pop's?
Consider it Jellybean's ransom.
And the money you obtain
is gonna get me out of town.
You're not going anywhere.
Only way this ends
is with you in the ground.
If I die, so does Jellybean.
But if I leave with the money,
then she lives.
And we all win.
[knocking on door]
Archie, did you run here?
It's pouring outside.
[Archie] I can't stop thinking
about Randy.
And Randy's sister
and what she said to me,
that I'm a murderer.
Archie, this is not your fault.
-This is on Elio, not you.
-I still feel responsible, Veronica.
I just-- I wish...
I knew how to help them.
Maybe...
El Royale can host a charity boxing event.
-We can raise money for their family.
-No. No boxing.
Okay, fine.
Um, we can host a benefit concert
at La Bonne Nuit.
Josie has been calling me
about doing a set,
so, let me talk to her,
and the Ronsons, okay?
Okay.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
Hi. Is this the Gilroy Academy?
I'm Doris Bell from the principal's office
at Riverdale High.
We have a recent transfer
who attended your school
a couple years back, Evelyn Evernever?
I'm just checking our records.
What grade was she in?
A junior?
Yes, that's what I thought.
Thank you so much.
Five for five.
Ms. Weiss,
do you remember Edgar Evernever?
From the Farm?
I can't find out anything about his past,
but I did find something
about his daughter, Evelyn.
She's been repeating her junior year,
enrolling in different high schools,
pretending to be 17 for over a decade.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
I think, from what I've found,
Edgar works on the parents,
while Evelyn is sent to high school,
to recruit teens into the Farm.
It's a cover for their cult.
I just need concrete proof.
I'm happy to make some inquiries.
I'll see what I can find out.
Thank you, Ms. Weiss.
I can't believe we're doing this.
We're in and out in 30 seconds.
Let me do the talking.
Kind of reminds me of the old days, huh?
-You guys have done this before?
-We're not getting into this.
[gun clicking]
Thanks again for coming, Dad.
It's nice to catch up.
My next tour is gonna be a long one.
Well, that's actually why
I wanted to meet up.
Recently, I've been the headlining act
downstairs at La Bonne Nuit.
But Riverdale is a small town,
and I wanna broaden my musical horizons.
So, I thought...
maybe I could go on tour...
with you.
Josie, it's a hard life,
being on the road.
Please, just come and see me perform.
I've got a set tonight.
[FP] Everybody on the ground, right now!
Get down.
[Jughead] Get down!
No.
Pop. Pop. Don't.
This isn't what you think.
-Go, go. Go.
-[Gladys] Hurry.
We gotta go. We gotta go.
-[FP] Go. Get out of here. Now.
-Damn it. We gotta go.
Go. Save Jellybean!
Now do you see why I need
to get the hell out of this town?
Oh, my God.
And then there were two.
Cops are probably on their way over here.
We gotta move him somewhere.
Yeah. Oh, I got a place.
[Betty] I have good news, Dad.
Your transfer papers have been processed.
Mr. Lodge says you could be moved
by the end of the week.
Thank you, Betty.
Yeah.
But something's bothering you.
What is it?
Edgar Evernever decided he wants
to adopt the twins after he marries Mom.
No, that can't happen.
Juniper and Dagwood must be protected.
I agree.
That's why I'm talking to a social worker.
Well, there's someone else
who might help you.
Someone uniquely motivated to help you.
[Betty] Auntie, I need your help.
Edgar Evernever
and the Farm have nefarious intentions.
I can feel it.
He plans to adopt your grandchildren,
and raise them as his own.
Polly, my mom, even Cheryl,
they made their decision.
But the twins are innocent. Helpless.
Auntie, you know what it's like
to be adopted into a family
that only wants to control you.
Dagwood.
-Where's Juniper?
-She's staying.
We get the boy, but Edgar keeps the girl.
Those were the only terms
that they would accept,
despite my threats
to come after the Farm in court.
They're twins.
You can't separate them.
And Edgar isn't even their father.
But Polly is their mother.
-It was her decision.
-No, Auntie.
Betty, it's a miracle
I could negotiate the release of one twin,
Jason Junior.
Don't feel bad. This is a win.
But, I--
[Elio] Slow day?
-The hell are you doing here, Elio?
-We have some unfinished business.
Fifty-thousand dollars,
courtesy of the Gilded Gloves.
Despite what happened to poor Randy,
you did win. It's yours.
I don't want your blood money.
Don't be a fool, Archie.
You went 12 rounds in your first fight.
You're a winner.
I could take you all the way to Vegas.
I'd call you the Riverdale Reaper.
People would pay a lot
to see you in the ring.
After all, you're a killer now.
Three against one. Bad odds, even for you.
Get the hell out of my gym.
Consider my offer, Reaper.
Kurtz is an insidious bastard.
I mean, even if we save Jellybean,
we still lose.
I just robbed Pop's at gunpoint.
It was unloaded, but still...
How can we stay in Riverdale after that?
We don't.
[sighs]
We get in the car, and we drive up north.
And we keep going until we find a town
where nobody knows us.
You just don't get it, do you?
Riverdale's our home.
Dad and I live here.
We're happy here.
It's you.
You destroyed that.
[Veronica]
I talked to Randy's sister earlier.
On top of everything else,
Elio is denying them
Randy's insurance money.
They've got nothing.
Well, he can't do that.
Well, I was hoping we could make
your show tonight a benefit, Josie,
with the proceeds going to the Ronsons.
Absolutely, Veronica. Whatever you need.
I'll do my best to make it back
in time for your set.
-[Josie] Back from what?
-Settling up with Elio.
What the hell?
Sleepy time's over, Kurtz.
What's the next challenge?
It's a doozy.
A trial with the Cyclops.
Cyclops?
That's not a character class
that I've ever read about.
I might know what he's talking about.
[Veronica] I'm sorry, Josie.
I double-checked at the door,
but your dad didn't pick up his ticket.
Why am I not surprised?
-Are you sure you're still up for this?
-Yeah. [chuckles] I'm fine.
And the show must go on, right?
Okay. Break a leg, girl.
[Archie] Where are you going at this hour?
The Reaper himself.
Finally come to your senses
and reconsidered my offer?
No.
But I will be taking that prize money,
after all.
[chuckles] I thought it was blood money.
You made a promise to the Ronson family.
That money is theirs.
So, give me that check,
and I'll let you leave here in one piece.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
Still wanna call me the Reaper?
You should be paying the Ronsons
ten times this.
This was once the Gargoyle lair.
Come. Come on.
Now it's a Serpent den.
Tonight...
a battlefield.
Penny Peabody?
-You're the Cyclops? I thought you were--
-Dead?
Is that what Mommy told you?
No, it was an eye for an eye.
Though I'm sure she wishes now
that she had finished the job.
Your weapons will be the sai.
As decreed by the King.
[audience clapping]
[Amy Winehouse's "Back to Black" playing]
You ever held these before, Jones?
Once or twice.
Players, on my mark.
Let the battle begin.
♪ He left no time to regret ♪
♪ Kept his lips wet ♪
♪ With his same old safe bet ♪
♪ Me and my head high ♪
♪ And my tears dry ♪
♪ Get on without my guy ♪
♪ You went back to what you knew ♪
♪ So far removed ♪
♪ From all that we went through ♪
[screams]
Mom.
It's a two-player game. If you move again,
your sister will pay the price.
[shouts]
Stop! You just need
to defeat her to complete the quest.
You did that.
Let's go.
[panting]
[yells]
I guess you'll be limping home.
Come on.
Let's get you to the hospital. Come on.
♪ We only said goodbye with words ♪
♪ I died a hundred times ♪
♪ You go back to her ♪
♪ And I go back to ♪
♪ Black ♪
[audience cheering]
[knocking on door]
Ms. Weiss.
What is it? What did you find?
Betty, I followed your paper trail.
You were right,
Evelyn is much older than she appears.
Twenty-six, to be exact.
[sighs]
I also found this.
Evelyn is Edgar Evernever's wife.
Not daughter.
[phone dialing]
Toni.
Are you in a place where you can talk?
It's urgent.
I've gotta get back into the Farm.
And then there was one.
I just dropped my mom off
at the emergency room
for a broken arm and a ruptured kidney.
My dad's been shot.
And my little sister's being held
against her will.
So, you are going to take me
to Jellybean right now.
Fair enough.
But I'll drive.
And you'll wear this.
[sighs]
You gave a wonderful performance tonight.
Thanks, Dad.
But I have to be honest,
I thought you bailed on me. Again.
That was my intention.
When you're on the road, gig after gig,
you gotta get up on that stage,
and give it your all, no matter what.
Hard truth is you gotta wanna play music,
more than anything else.
Do you?
One hundred percent.
In that case, start packing.
We got a show in Asheville, North Carolina
tomorrow night.
Thank you, Ms. Ronson,
for agreeing to see me.
I can't begin to imagine
what it feels like to lose a brother.
Randy...
had demons.
More than you know,
he had a history with drugs.
We were on our own really young,
and I... did my best
to raise him and my sisters right,
but at some point,
he made his own choices.
What's this?
The prize money from Gilded Gloves.
And some donations
Veronica pooled together.
And there'll be more.
[sobbing]
Thank you.
[Betty] Hurry, it's up ahead.
You're a lifesaver, Toni.
Well, you know what they say.
Takes a village to mercy-kidnap a child.
[cooing]
Come here. Let's go.
[door thuds]
This way.
Toni, what's happening?
According to Edgar...
only what was preordained.
No.
No, not you, too. Why?
My whole life,
I've been searching for a family.
The Serpents, the Pretty Poisons.
I've never felt such belonging
as I do here at the Farm.
Mom. Mom.
You can't marry Edgar.
He's already married to Evelyn.
You think I don't know that?
There are no secrets here at the Farm.
I don't...
I don't understand.
Why are you all smiling?
What is this about?
You, Betty.
It's about getting you to this crossroads.
Join us.
-[all chanting] Join us.
-Everyone you know...
-Join us.
-everyone in your life, is here,
-in this room.
-Join us.
Your mother is here.
-Your sister is here.
-Your best friend, Kevin, is here.
-Join us. Join us.
-Your principal is here.
-Join us.
-Your cousin Cheryl is here.
Join us.
-Be a sister to Polly.
-Join us.
-Be a godmother to Juniper.
-Join us. Join us.
Join us.
-Join us.
[all] Join us, Betty.
We welcome you.
Yes.
Catch her, please.
Stop, Betty, please!
-Betty.
Stop.
-Betty
-Betty, wait.
Betty.
Well done, Hellcaster.
You have made it
to the valley of darkness...
and now your vision has been restored.
Where are we?
Where's Jellybean?
Surely you must be familiar
with the story
of "The Lady and the Tiger"?
Behind one of these doors is your sister.
Behind the other is your doom.
The final challenge is simple, Jughead.
Choose one.
Hey, what's the twist?
-Whoa, whoa!
-Get in.
Climb into the ice tomb,
and the princess will be freed,
with but a phone call.
Get in.
No.
Not until I know she's safe.
Put her on.
Hey, Jellybean?
[Jellybean] Hey, Jug.
-Are you all right? Where are you?
-I just got home.
I'm hanging out with my pal Ricky.
Don't be mad, but we've been playing G&G.
I know you said not to, but--
It's okay.
[sighs]
See you soon, all right?
-All right.
-Get in.
All right, all right.
I did what you wanted.
Tell Ricky to let her go.
Calm down, Hellcaster.
Acolyte?
The Hellcaster has been contained.
You may kill the princess.
Kurtz!
You cheated!
[shouting]
What the hell?
Jellybean.
Jug.
Oh, I'm so glad you're okay.
-Where's Ricky?
-He left right after you called.
-He said that to turn the screw.
-What?
No. Nothing.
Come here. Come here. Come-- Come here.
♪ We won't back down
Write this in the sky ♪
♪ We own the night
And we fear nothing ♪
[chuckles]
I heard your show was amazing.
It was.
I'm really sorry
I didn't make it back in time.
It's okay.
You had a lot going on.
Archie...
there's something I need to tell you.
I've decided to go on tour with my dad.
What?
[chuckles] Josie, that's...
Wait, when? Like, over the summer?
No. Like, immediately.
-You're gonna come back, though, right?
-Maybe.
We'll see.
Archie, I've loved our time together.
But we're not endgame.
And that's okay.
Your life is here in Riverdale,
and mine is...
somewhere out there.
Who knows where?
Maybe New York.
Well, I was gonna ask you to prom,
but now...
[groans]
You are too cute for words.
[Kate Cunning's "Eve" playing]
Dad will be out of jail in a couple days.
Attorney McCoy cleared everything
with the judge.
Said he was under duress
when he committed the robbery.
Hmm.
That he was.
You know, people are going to find out
what really happened,
and about what you did.
How are you gonna answer for all that?
First thing tomorrow,
me and JB are hitting the road.
No.
She can't keep going on the run with you.
She deserves better than that.
She should stay with Dad and I.
And so should you.
Stay.
Stay with us.
Face the music.
Whatever happens,
let's get through it as a family.
Jughead.
As wonderful as that all sounds,
it'll probably be best for everyone
if I just disappear for a little bit.
Until your dad cools off a bit.
And then what?
Maybe we could try again.
Randy's dead.
Mad Dog left my gym.
Casa Grande's reputation
has been called into question.
Don't worry about your gym.
You still have my financial support.
What about Andrews?
I really thought he was gonna kill me
the other night.
-Let me handle him.
-What about your truce?
There are two Archie Andrews.
There's the one who saved my life
at the hospital after I'd been shot.
And then there's the other Archie,
who pointed a gun at my head.
He was there to kill me.
That's the real Archie Andrews,
the one with murder in his heart.
The Riverdale Reaper.
-He's done with boxing.
-Yeah, with my daughter in his corner?
We'll see about that.
Archie, get in here.
I need a sparring partner.
Archie.
You need to get back on the horse soon,
or you never will.
Yeah, well,
maybe that's exactly the way it should be.
I don't wanna be known
as the Riverdale Reaper.
You made amends with the Ronsons
the best way you could.
And now...
it's time to look to the future.
You're not Riverdale's Reaper.
If anything...
you're its Red Hope.
[sighs]
Please?
For me?
[May & Robot Koch's "Bad Kingdom" playing]
♪ In the early... ♪
[both chuckling]
Thanks, Ronnie.
Anytime, champ.
♪ Watching full glasses
Through blank eyes ♪
♪ This is not what you wanted ♪
Why can't I just come with you, Mom?
Because I'm gonna be doing a bunch
of dumb work stuff.
Believe me, you're gonna have so much
more fun here with your dad and Jughead.
Come here.
You take good care of my babies.
All right?
And yourself.
You, too, Gladys.
♪ Vacuous winter stare ♪
♪ Worn out version of yourself ♪
♪ Too tough to fall ♪
[chuckles]
Betty. Betty, where have you been?
I've been calling you nonstop.
Why? What's wrong?
Your dad, and a few other inmates,
were being transported
to my father's prison, and...
there was some kind of...
accident.
Did he escape?
No.
But, Betty...
there were no survivors.