-[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-So, my dad played G&amp;G in high school.
[Betty] All of our parents did.
-What's that, Hiram?
-Fizzle Rocks.
This house is no longer safe.
They'll watch over you now.
Mom, are you out of your mind?
[Woodhouse] You're safe
with the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
Framing Archie for murder,
conspiring to keep him locked away.
An old-fashioned prison break
might be your best option.
[Jughead]
You're breaking Archie out of juvie?
[Minetta] Ten thousand apiece.
You say that you saw Archie Andrews
kill your friend Cassidy Bullock.
Your henchman, Minetta, is going down.
If you added slots, table games,
you'd have quite the little gold mine.
[Archie] Hiram Lodge has done everything
in his power to destroy me.
I can't go back to Riverdale.
-I'm not letting you go off alone.
-I'm not alone.
Leaving is my best option, Jug.
[train horn blaring]
[Jughead] The two young men
had been walking for days.
Looking at them...
you might think they were brothers. And in a way, they were.
Brothers fearful...
that Hiram Lodge might catch up to them.
[Betty on recording]
Hi, this is Betty. Leave a message.
[Jughead] Hey. Betty, it's me.
Just trying you again.
Hoping you're okay.
We're looking for a place to settle down.
I'll let you know when we do. Okay.
Uh... I love you.
Bye.
Still no answer?
Look, Jug, maybe you should go back.
I'm fine.
Really, dude, I'm gonna be fine.
Archie, no offense, but Betty
took down a serial killer last year.
You can't go five minutes
without being kidnapped
or getting the crap kicked out of you.
That was before you were marked for death
by Hiram Lodge.
[Archie] It would be nice to stop looking
over my shoulder.
-Just find somewhere to settle, you know?
-We will.
When we find the right place,
we'll know. We'll feel it.
Or maybe we're already there.
Nice try. Let's go a couple more miles
before nightfall.
Come on. Jug, we gotta bunk somewhere.
[gun cocks]
[girl] You're trespassing.
Now let's see you do a little turn,
nice and slow.
Who are you?
I'm Cal. This is Biff.
From Centerville.
I don't like liars.
Shoot them, Gracie.
Wait. Wait.
We got robbed on a train.
They took all our money.
We've been walking for days. Just--
We need some food and water,
and we'll be on our way.
Put the rifle down.
-I don't trust them.
-Do as I say.
I'm Laurie Lake. This is Gracie.
You boys like stew? Where's everyone else?
I only meant...
A farm this size, I thought there'd
be more people working it.
A lot of the men in town are at a job,
down the river.
Our father and our brother went with them.
They come back now and then.
You have somewhere to stay?
-We're good.
-[Archie] No.
We should get out of your hair.
You could stay, if you sleep in the barn.
That's amazing.
Anything we can do to repay you?
-[clearing throat]
-Just some farm work.
I have some bales of hay I need to move.
Just stay out of the main house.
-Dude, we can't stay here.
-One night, Jug.
-What's the problem?
-I don't know.
Something about this place weirds me out.
It's...
a little too American Gothic, even for me.
You're right. Where is everybody?
When I asked what her dad and brother did,
it seemed like she was lying.
You mean like we are, Cal?
-[chuckles]
-[Laurie] Am I interrupting?
No. Not at all.
I brought some extra blankets,
in case you guys get cold.
Thank you, Laurie.
All right.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
-Seriously?
-What?
We have to stay on task. No distractions.
I totally agree.
No distractions.
[rooster crowing]
Hey.
You missed eggs and bacon for breakfast.
Meanwhile,
you are literally moving bales of hay.
Yep.
Feel free to help out, too.
I'm going into town,
take some pictures before we hit the road.
Remember?
Like we said we would.
Gonna be okay here?
I think I'll be fine, Jug.
Excuse me.
Hi.
I'm, uh... I'm a little lost.
I saw some strange symbols
on the sides of the buildings.
Didn't look as faded as the rest.
Know what they mean?
Town wasn't always like this.
First it was the jingle-jangle.
Now we're back to Fizzle Rocks.
Fizzle Rocks. Like the candy?
I used to eat that when I was a kid.
That's normal Fizzle Rocks.
What we got nowadays...
is laced with drugs.
As for them symbols,
they started showing up in town
about the same time
Fizzle Rocks trickled in.
You've done so much for me.
You don't have to do this, too.
I used to do this for my father.
-And you did move all that hay.
-My dad's a construction worker, so...
I'm used to physical labor.
Well, there's a lot of that around here.
[chuckles]
If you and your friend wanna stick around
for a few days.
I'm not sure about Cal, but...
I would be, I think.
There's something about this place
that just makes me feel at home.
I don't know why.
I'm sorry, Laurie.
I just-- I can't do this right now.
There's a girl back home.
There always is.
Though we're not together,
I still love her.
If you love her, Biff, why are you here?
Because of her father...
and my past with him.
Sometimes when you try to survive,
it's easy to lose sight of who you are.
Laurie, my name's not Biff.
It's Archie Andrews.
I'm from a small town called Riverdale,
which I can't go back to.
Because of your girl's father?
Hiram Lodge. Yes.
[sighs] I'm sorry I lied to you.
It's okay. Archie Andrews.
Around here,
everybody's running from something.
Let me see about getting you some lunch.
[girls giggling]
Are you a king?
I'm actually a Game Master.
-Started as a Hellcaster, like you.
-What level?
Almost three. On my way to four.
Where'd you learn to play?
Our older brothers used to play,
before they left town.
Yeah, I noticed that
there are no men here.
-All gone to work building a prison.
-Prison?
My brother told me
it's not just for prisoners.
It's for making Fizzle Rocks, too.
The prison doubles as a drug lab.
Where you shacking up, Game Master?
-Uh... Lake Farm.
-[Tiffany scoffs] Gracie's house?
-We used to be friends with her.
-Acts like she's too good for everybody, even though her daddy works
for the Man in Black like ours do.
-Who's the Man in Black?
-[Pearl] He's always in a black suit.
Gets driven around in a black car.
This town's his now.
Hiram.
I made you some more eggs.
I hope you don't mind.
No, that is more than okay. Thank you.
Don't thank me.
You helped me with the hay,
and helped me
pass the time a little bit quicker.
In my book, we're even.
These are delicious.
[inaudible dialogue]
Are you all right?
Let's get you out of here.
-Laurie knocked me out. Where is she?
-She's inside.
With Hiram Lodge.
What?
I don't understand.
How do the girls know him?
Her dad and brother work for him.
They make drugs inside the prison,
which the kids take, then play G&amp;G.
All of this is connected, Archie.
Hiram owns this whole town.
Probably many others like it.
-Let's go.
-Or we could stay and fight.
No, Archie.
This is our one chance...
to take it all back.
He'll walk in thinking I'm tied up.
Let's surprise him and take him out.
That's a bad idea, trust me.
-There's gotta be something. A pitchfork.
-Hey. Look at me.
You're not thinking clearly.
It's two against four. They have guns.
I get how bad you want this,
but we are underprepared.
They're going to kill us, Archie.
Archie, look at me.
-Don't say what I think you're gonna say--
-Jughead.
I can kill him.
-I can.
-I know.
But right now we've gotta go,
while we still have time.
There's nowhere he won't follow me.
I can't run from him.
Let me end this nightmare,
once and for all.
He's coming.
Archie, I know he ruined your life.
He's ruined a lot of lives. One day,
he will get everything he deserves.
I swear. But it's not today.
-It's not now. We have to go.
-Jughead.
All right, if you do this,
if you kill him...
will Veronica ever forgive you?
-Before I let you in, to be clear--
-Yes.
Archie in exchange
for your brother and father.
Their debt to me will be paid.
You have my word.
♪ Do you have a feeling in your heart? ♪
What's going on here?
Where is he?
♪ It's always been there
No matter how far that you run ♪
♪ Setting sun ♪
[Jughead] For a second there,
I didn't think you'd listen to me.
Neither did I, Jug.
Neither did I.
You were right about one thing, though.
Hiram's gonna follow you,
or us, wherever we go.
We'll always be outnumbered and outgunned.
So, what's the plan?
We'll go see my mom.
You sure we should do that?
[Jughead] You got a better idea?
What are you doing?
I'm leaving the Pembrooke.
Veronica.
I realize that you're upset about Archie,
but you can't just go running after him.
Save your breath, Mom.
I'm not going after Archie.
Okay, then what's this all about?
[sighs]
Convenient, isn't it?
Minetta goes missing
just as I find evidence
that he coerced the Shadow Lake boys
into giving false testimony?
Minetta was a corrupt man.
He had many enemies.
Is that a murder confession?
Okay, Veronica.
First of all, I sincerely hope that...
you don't believe I'm capable of--
I don't know what to believe anymore.
Which is why I'm leaving
this house of horrors while I still can.
[sighs]
Maybe you should, too.
He's my husband.
Right, well, you and Daddy
can pop open a bottle of Cristal.
Because he finally did it. He finally won.
He finally drove Archie,
and me, away for good.
It's not the Five Seasons, but it'll do.
[ringing]
["Good Luck Charm" playing on speakers]
♪ Don't want a four-leaf clover ♪
♪ Don't want an old horseshoe ♪
-Morning, Pop.
-Veronica.
You're in early.
-What time did you get here?
-Uh...
You know what they say
about the bird and the worm.
[chuckles]
[jazz music playing on speakers]
What's up, Ronnie?
Still bummed about Archie bailing
on the world?
That's on my list of woes, yes.
Hmm. What else?
[Veronica] We work all day
and all night...
and yet we're barely scraping by.
The numbers just aren't adding up.
It may not be the Copacabana yet.
But business... is steady.
One thing I learned from my father...
is that "steady" is one bad week away
from broke.
We'll never turn a profit
selling five-dollar mocktails
to high-schoolers who sit here all day,
playing some stupid board game.
So, what you're saying is
we need to start a side hustle.
So, now you wanna turn your speakeasy
into a casino.
For one night only.
You yourself suggested it.
And I've done my research.
I've heard all about your...
very exclusive blackjack club in the city.
So, who better to show me the ropes
than Mr. Twenty-One himself?
What's the deal on the table?
If you agree to provide me
with some games...
and if you bring some
of your high-roller friends,
who are guaranteed to play,
I'll give you ten percent of the proceeds.
-[scoffs] Fifty.
-Twenty.
-Thirty.
-Twenty-five.
And that money will be all yours, Elio.
Come on.
Everything you do is
in your father's shadow.
Don't you wanna step out
on your own finally?
-How are you gonna cover expenses?
-The house always wins, right?
I'll count on that to be the case.
But in terms of startup costs,
should the unthinkable happen...
I took out a second mortgage
against Pop's.
A gambler.
I like it. I'm in.
And, Elio, do me a favor. Let's keep this arrangement between us.
I don't want third parties sticking
their noses into our business.
[rock music playing on speakers]
Nice uniform.
Why are you here?
I'll take a café con leche, please.
Anything else?
Your mother's worried about you.
As am I.
You've been struggling
since Archie abandoned you.
I heard through the grapevine
that you're hosting a Casino Night.
-So?
Instead of coming to me
for advice and help,
you went to one of our competitors?
It's ironic for all your high talk
on running a legitimate business,
you now invite a bunch of criminals over
to play cards?
Times must be tough.
They're not criminals.
They're Elio's friends.
And how do you think Elio's family
built their gambling empire?
They're cheaters. And criminals.
And they're gonna rob you blind.
You would know all about that,
wouldn't you?
Are you angry about something?
[sighs]
Am I angry?
-You drove Archie away.
-Did I? I swear I read in the papers
that he was cleared on all charges.
So...
you came here to twist the knife.
Is that it?
No.
I came here to remind you
who your true allies are.
Your mother and I,
we're still here for you.
To welcome you back with open arms.
Because we're a family.
And that will never change.
Get out, Daddy.
[upbeat jazz music playing on speakers]
Your drink, Ms. Lodge.
Just how you like it.
Perfect. Thank you.
Veronica.
See, Reggie?
This is exactly what we needed.
Thanks to Elio...
we're gonna pull in bank.
Yeah. Or he's gonna break it.
What do you mean?
Your generous friend Elio
is on a hot streak.
He hasn't lost a single hand all night.
He's gonna wipe us out.
We're gonna be bankrupt.
I thought the house always wins.
-How's this happening?
-He must be cheating.
I'm not surprised.
As my father said, Elio is a criminal,
from a family of criminals.
Want me to rough him up? Throw him out?
No. That's not how we do things here.
Especially not to a member
of a crime family.
But don't worry.
Veronica Lodge is not about
to go quietly into the night.
-Dealer busts.
-Yes. Come on.
[crowd cheering]
Hey, Elio.
-Big night?
-I've never had such a run of luck.
Hope it doesn't put a huge dent
in your take.
You mean our take?
Well, seems like either way, I win.
Do yourself a favor.
Cash out.
And walk away while you still can.
Or what?
You'll call your father for backup?
I heard you weren't on speaking terms.
-[crowd cheering]
-[laughs]
Deal me in.
What are you doing?
Raising the stakes.
One hand of blackjack, winner takes all.
Just you and me.
What am I playing for?
[Veronica] This.
The deed to Pop's.
And by extension,
La Bonne Nuit.
[crowd groans]
Fine. You asked for it.
Let's play.
♪ And I've got all the time ♪
[man] Twenty.
Nineteen.
Tell you what.
You'll always be welcome at my speakeasy.
I might even re-name it "Veronica's."
Game's not over yet.
[Elio] Trust me, princess. It's over.
Hit me.
Twenty-one.
[crowd cheering]
Ms. Lodge wins.
That, heh-- That's impossible.
Why, Elio?
The house always wins.
Isn't that what they say?
♪ In these wicked games
We play on and on ♪
[chuckles]
You made some serious coin, Vee.
We did.
We're in the black, Reggie.
-It was a very successful night.
-Hmm.
Now, you could have lost it all, you know?
But you didn't. You pulled it off.
I swear, I thought Elio was cheating.
Can you keep a secret?
Mm-hm.
Couple of hours before we opened the doors
to Casino Night,
my father summoned me to his study.
What is it, Daddy?
You said you had some important news.
I'm on a bit of a time crunch.
Some business associates have informed me
that your friend Elio
has nefarious intentions
going into your Casino Night.
Something you're not aware of.
Like what?
He's planning on fleecing you,
because he thinks you're weak.
Because you're no longer
under my protection.
Okay.
Say I believe you.
What would you suggest I do?
[Hiram] You beat him at his own game.
Like his father,
Elio is a compulsive gambler.
The bigger the pot,
the more he wants to stay in the game. The best way
to beat players like this is fast,
with no remorse.
One hand, winner takes all,
the decks stacked in your favor.
The decks stacked?
Wait, so, you want me to cheat?
It doesn't matter how you win, mija,
so long as you're the last man standing.
Now, I have a name
of a dealer you might wanna bring in:
Johnny Goldwater.
He has nimble fingers.
[crowd cheering]
[Goldwater] Twenty-one.
-[laughing]
-Wow.
-So, you scammed the scammer.
-Oh, Reginald.
It doesn't matter how you win,
so long as you're the last woman standing.
Was it a good night?
Yes. It was excellent.
You know, this place has been in my family
for generations.
It's a family place at heart.
Crime-free.
[sighs]
Pop.
The speakeasy wasn't making enough money,
and neither was the diner,
so, I had to take a big swing.
Bend the rules a bit.
Please.
For your own sake, Veronica,
don't be like your father.
Pop, deep, deep down...
maybe my dad's not so bad.
You haven't heard the news yet?
Sheriff Minetta's body was found
in the marsh last night.
At least they think it was his body.
They don't know for sure,
because it was decapitated.
And the hands were sawed off.
[Betty] Make them think that you're sane.
Tell me what you see, Elizabeth.
[Betty] A dead body, you idiot.
I see a toy.
A teddy bear with a bowtie.
Just pass this test,
and then you can start investigating.
[Woodhouse] What do you see now?
[Betty] The Black Hood.
A butterfly.
A monarch butterfly.
Hmm.
And now?
[Betty] Remember to smile, Betty,
and you'll be out of here in no time.
The old jungle gym
at Riverdale Elementary.
I used to play on it every recess.
Very interesting.
Step forward, Nellie.
It's time for your candy.
[Betty] My mom and her delusions.
She has a fondness for this place.
She thought the Sisters would keep me safe
from the Gargoyle King.
She probably didn't realize
that she was sending me
right into the belly of the beast.
-What is this?
-A treat.
Every patient gets candy
for good behavior.
[Betty] Fizzle Rocks.
Aka, drugs.
Why are the Sisters dosing us up
with the same stuff the Midnight Club took the night
of Principal Featherhead's murder?
Thank you so much.
Bless you, my child.
[Betty] And what, oh, what
is in that file, I wonder?
How are you settling in, roomie?
Ethel.
What are you doing here?
Sister Woodhouse thought you might benefit
from having a roommate
who's familiar with the system.
[Betty] What a nightmare.
Fun.
Uh... Did you just come from art class?
[Ethel] Oh, no. That's my warrior board.
It's like a visual collection
of my destiny.
It helps me manifest my goals.
[Betty] If I didn't already
have an escape plan,
I'd really start going crazy in here.
As soon as I have what I need,
I'll find the door marked X
in the basement
that Veronica used
when they broke Cheryl out.
Isn't the King marvelous?
Since I came here,
I've had wonderful conversations with him.
Wait, what are you saying?
That you've been talking
to the Gargoyle King in person?
-Yes. We've become very close.
-Really?
Think you could introduce us?
No. That's Sister Woodhouse's job.
What is?
The Sisters take patients
into the Gargoyle King's chamber
when they misbehave.
Other girls are scared of him,
but I'm not.
Where's his chamber?
I can't tell you.
That's Sister Woodhouse's job.
Hmm. You'd tell Jughead.
About Jughead...
I wasn't going to mention this,
but since you brought him up...
Betty.
I don't think Jughead's into you anymore.
We connected
when we played the game together,
and things got pretty hot and heavy
in the bunker.
[Betty] This psycho bitch.
Oh, he definitely told me about
how you blackmailed him into kissing you.
I knew you would do this.
You always acted
like you're better than me.
-You and all your shallow friends.
-What are you talking about?
This isn't Riverdale High.
Rules are different here.
I'm the queen bee, not you, Betty Cooper.
And if you wanna get better,
change your attitude.
And you have to be honest with yourself,
and with others.
And you can start
with what you threw into the trash.
Ethel, I'm sorry.
I want to be your friend,
if you'll have me.
Can you just not tell anyone
about the candy?
Can you just keep it between us, please?
Roomie.
Okay, Betty.
I'll keep it our little secret.
But you really should take the candy.
It's super delicious.
[Agnes] Be careful of the thorns, girls.
Very good, my child.
[Betty] That's funny.
The Sisters don't serve maple syrup
in the cafeteria.
And why would Claudius Blossom
be making the delivery?
What the hell?
What kind of business does Hiram Lodge
have with Sister Woodhouse,
and how are the Blossoms connected to it?
Hey. Do you know who that is?
They call him the Man in Black.
He's an angel donor.
Helps the sisters
with anything they may need.
Isn't that nice of him?
Yeah. Amazing.
Wait a minute. According to my mom,
Hiram was the one
who brought the Fizzle Rocks
to Ascension Night all those years ago.
Back to it, Betty.
Idle hands make the devil's work.
[Betty] Bite me.
What did Hiram give the Sisters?
And what did Woodhouse give him?
Maybe there's a clue
in those files they're keeping.
If I can just find the right office
or a records room...
Wait, this must be the Gargoyle King's
chamber Ethel was talking about.
[girl screaming]
[girl grunting and whimpering]
[girl sobbing]
Hush. Hush, child. Hush.
[Ethel] What do you think you're doing?
This area is off-limits.
Ethel, I...
Know where the medical archives are?
Sister Agnes sent me to fetch some files.
I got kind of lost.
Silly Betty. Only the infirm are allowed
in the infirmary.
Time to go back to our room now.
While I'm watching.
Okay.
Acting normal. This me acting normal.
All I need is a pen,
a bobby pin that hasn't
been dulled down, or--
A paperclip.
Bingo.
Hey, Betty, come play with us.
Uh, no, thanks, Ethel.
Betty, you said we were friends.
And friends play together.
[Betty] This isn't how I imagined myself
getting to those medical files,
but since only the infirm
go to the infirmary...
You wanna be real friends, Ethel?
Hmm. That's weird,
because real friends
don't kiss each other's boyfriends.
That's because the Gargoyle King
wants Jughead and me to be together.
-Oh, yeah?
-We're gonna be a ship.
Oh.
Ethelhead?
In your dreams.
[chuckles]
You're just jealous.
Jealous that Jughead and I are worthy,
and you're not, but here's the thing, Betty, okay?
You're never going to be worthy.
And the Gargoyle King?
You'll never meet him.
[Betty] Here we go.
Sister Woodhouse, she's having a seizure.
Ethel, get the nurse.
[Betty] Yes, Ethel, get the nurse.
And God willing,
she'll take me exactly where I need to go.
There, there, Elizabeth.
You're going to be all right.
We'll get you to the infirmary.
[Betty] Well, they bought it.
They actually believe I had a seizure.
Let's re-evaluate her dosage
as soon as possible.
Yes, Sister Woodhouse.
[Betty] Jackpot. There you are.
Elizabeth Cooper.
"Two doses of Bullio Lapis, mornings only.
Sporadic seizures.
Patient seems to be responding well
to testing.
Per HL, increase dosage after first week."
HL?
Oh, my God.
Is Hiram Lodge using patients
at the Sisters as lab rats?
And what is Bullio Lapis? Unless...
Fizzle Rocks.
Oh, my God.
Okay, now that I have my proof,
it's officially time
to get the hell out of here.
The door to escape is in the basement.
X marks the spot. Just like Veronica said.
I'm so out of here.
No.
[Ethel] There she is.
Ethel.
Sister Woodhouse.
I just-- I got lost again.
I told you she was up to no good,
Sister Woodhouse.
Restrain her.
No.
[grunts]
What are you doing, Sister Woodhouse?
You've been a very bad girl, Betty.
You haven't been taking your candy.
Ethel.
-Steady her.
-No.
[grunting]
My King. My Savior.
Guide me through the night.
Bless me with your darkness,
gift me with your flight.
She needs a good, strong talking-to
from the King, I think.
I was wrong. You are gonna meet the King.
No.
The King awaits you.
[Betty screaming]
Now let's try this again, shall we?
Tell me what you see, Betty.
A dead body.
What do you see now?
The Black Hood.
And now?
The Gargoyle King.
Wonderful, wonderful work.
You've already made progress.
[Betty] My King. My Savior.
Guide me through the night.