[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
I wanna be more than just your errand boy
or casual hookup.
I wanna matter, Ronnie.
I just went through a wrenching breakup.
I'm taking things slow.
[Josie] Sweet Pea, I told you,
our summer fling was gonna be just that,
a fling.
Can I kiss you?
Archie.
I can't spend all my time
cooped up in that house.
It sounds like you regret
moving in with me.
I've been hearing rumors
that you moved to town
to take the drug trade from Hiram Lodge.
It's about time the Joneses got a taste
of the American Dream.
What are you gonna do now?
Protect my dad and run my mom
out of town. Wanna help?
-Brother Kevin?
-[Betty] Groups like the Farm
prey on emotionally vulnerable people.
[Cheryl] Midge was murdered
during your production of Carrie.
This year's musical is Heathers.
Any questions?
Heathers: the Musical?
Now, how in God's name is a play
about teen violence and suicide
a good idea in Riverdale?
Especially after the tragedy
of last year's musical?
Please, Mayor Lodge.
Yes, Heathers deals with teen alienation
and desperation.
But its characters long for simpler,
more innocent times.
Its ultimate message is a rejection
of nihilism.
If you'll just listen to the lyrics
of the first song. Evelyn?
[pop music playing on speakers]
♪ We were so tiny
Happy and shiny ♪
♪ Playing tag and getting chased ♪
♪ Then we got bigger
That was the trigger ♪
♪ Like the Huns invading Rome ♪
♪ Welcome to my school
This ain't no high school ♪
♪ This is the Thunderdome ♪
♪ But I know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Life can be beautiful ♪
♪ I pray ♪
♪ For a better way ♪
♪ If we changed back then ♪
♪ We could change again ♪
♪ We can be beautiful ♪
-♪ Just not today ♪
-Dweeb.
♪ Things will get better
Soon as my letter ♪
♪ Comes from Harvard, Duke or Brown ♪
♪ Wake from this coma
Take my diploma ♪
♪ Then I can blow this town ♪
♪ Dream of ivy-covered walls ♪
♪ And smoky French cafés ♪
♪ Fight the urge to strike a match ♪
♪ And set this dump ablaze ♪
♪ But I know, I know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Life can be beautiful ♪
♪ I pray, I pray ♪
♪ I pray ♪
♪ For a better way ♪
♪ We were kind before ♪
♪ We can be kind once more ♪
♪ We can be beautiful ♪
♪ Just not today ♪
I had a dream I was searching
for a needle in a haystack.
-Care to interpret, Dr. Freud?
-Your plan is a good one, Jug.
Your mom can't start dealing drugs
without a lab to make them in.
So, you find the lab, shut it down,
and stop her before she gets a toehold.
That's the goal for the week.
♪ And I know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Life can be beautiful ♪
♪ I pray ♪
♪ For a better way ♪
♪ We were kind before ♪
♪ We can be kind once more ♪
♪ We can be beautiful ♪
♪ Just not today ♪
Look, listen.
You guys don't know
what your kids are thinking,
what they're dealing with.
-♪ Why ♪
-♪ Why do they hate me? ♪
♪ Why don't I fight back? ♪
♪ Why do I act like such a creep? ♪
♪ Why won't she date me? ♪
♪ Why did I hit him? ♪
♪ Why do I cry myself to sleep? ♪
♪ Somebody hug me ♪
♪ Somebody fix me ♪
♪ Somebody save me ♪
♪ Send me a sign, God ♪
♪ Give me some hope here ♪
♪ Something to live for ♪
Are all of you this miserable?
Well, there is Cheryl Blossom,
floating above it all as Heather Chandler.
♪ I love Heather ♪
♪ Heather and Heather ♪
She was a real mess
after her breakup with Toni.
But then she gave herself the role
of HBIC.
Veronica and Betty
are playing the other Heathers,
Heather McNamara and Heather Duke, but...
Cheryl's the mythic bitch.
♪ And you know, you know ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ This could be beautiful ♪
♪ Mascara, maybe some lip gloss ♪
♪ And we're on our way ♪
♪ Get this girl some blush ♪
♪ And, Heather, I need your brush ♪
-♪ Let's make me beautiful ♪
-♪ Let's make her beautiful ♪
-♪ Beautiful ♪
-♪ Okay? ♪
-♪ Okay ♪
♪ Out of my way, geek ♪
♪ I don't want trouble ♪
♪ You're gonna die at 3 p.m. ♪
♪ Don't you dare touch me
Get away, pervert ♪
♪ What did I ever do to them? ♪
♪ Who could survive this?
I can't escape this ♪
♪ I think I'm dying ♪
♪ And you know, you know ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ Life can be beautiful ♪
♪ You hope, you dream ♪
♪ You pray ♪
♪ And you get your way ♪
♪ Ask me how it feels ♪
♪ Lookin' like hell on wheels ♪
-♪ My God, it's beautiful ♪
-♪ Beautiful ♪
-♪ I might be beautiful ♪
♪ And when you're beautiful ♪
♪ It's a beautiful frickin' day ♪
Greetings, Heathers family.
Before we start today,
there's been a slight change
to our creative team.
You all know Evelyn Evernever has been
helping me produce the musical.
But I've also asked Evelyn to step up
and be my co-director.
Yay. [chuckles] So fun.
What? Kevin.
No. You always direct the musical alone.
Which has been
incredibly stressful, Betty.
Especially after last year's events.
[scoffs]
Can we just not talk about Midge, please?
Now, how about we do a rundown
of everybody's parts,
catch Evelyn up to speed?
I'm playing Veronica Sawyer.
Outcast, turned Heather,
turned outcast again.
Hi, I'm Sweet Pea.
Um, I'm playing JD,
Veronica Sawyer's bad-boy love interest.
Reggie Mantle, aka jock Ram Sweeney.
Gonna bro it up with my bud Arch, here.
Just two single straight dudes,
doing some theater.
[Kevin] Given how much dancing
there is in Heathers,
Evelyn and I felt
we should bring on a choreographer,
so, give a big Heathers hello
to Riverdale's resident Fly Girl,
Toni Topaz.
[all cheering]
Um, does anyone have a chainsaw?
Because what the...?
[Evelyn] Everything in your lives matters.
There are universal truths
within each of your personal experiences.
A you inside of me,
a me inside of you.
In rehearsal, we are going to explore
our own personal traumas and experiences,
and exorcise them through our art.
[claps]
All right, Cheryl, Veronica, Betty.
"Candy Store" set and costumes are ready.
Go get changed.
So, this number is about
the Heathers' undeniable power.
Each of you can get anything you want
at any time.
So, really unleash that force.
We'll start with some simple steps.
Yeah, we got it, thanks.
Uh, Toni has some fantastic choreo.
How very.
But my Heathers and I have worked out
our own choreography.
Come on, Cheryl.
I'm trying to be professional here.
Can you not?
♪ Are we gonna have a problem? ♪
♪ I like lookin' hot ♪
♪ Buying stuff they cannot ♪
-♪ I like ♪
-♪ Drinkin' hard ♪
♪ Maxin' Dad's credit card ♪
-♪ I like ♪
-♪ Skippin' gym ♪
♪ Scaring her, screwing him ♪
-♪ I like ♪
-♪ Killer clothes ♪
♪ Kickin' nerds in the nose ♪
♪ If you lack the juice ♪
♪ Go play duck, duck, goose ♪
-♪ Let your mommy fix you ice cream ♪
-♪ Whoa-oh-oh oh ♪
♪ Or come hang with me ♪
♪ And tonight we'll be ♪
♪ Dirty-dancing with the football team ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Honey, what you waitin' for? ♪
♪ Welcome to my candy store ♪
♪ It's time for you to prove ♪
♪ You're not a loser anymore ♪
♪ Then step into my candy store ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Well, honey, what you waitin' for? ♪
♪ Welcome to my candy store ♪
♪ You just gotta prove ♪
♪ You're not a doorknob anymore ♪
♪ Then step into my candy store ♪
♪ You can join the team ♪
♪ Or you can bitch and moan ♪
♪ You can live the dream ♪
♪ Or you can die alone ♪
♪ You can fly with eagles ♪
♪ Or if you prefer ♪
♪ Keep on testing me ♪
♪ And end up like her ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Honey, what you waiting for? ♪
Shut up, Toni!
♪ Step into my candy store ♪
♪ Time for you to prove
You're not a lame-ass anymore ♪
♪ Then step into my candy store ♪
♪ It's my candy store ♪
♪ It's my candy ♪
I know what you're up to.
Lowering Sweet Pea's solo?
Cute.
This entire musical is just one big
recruitment drive for you, isn't it?
I'm sorry, I don't follow.
The Farm is sponsoring the play.
You strong-armed your way
into co-directing.
Your warm-up sermons,
exorcising trauma through art.
Screams "cult recruitment."
Betty...
dissect these trust issues.
The Farm is producing,
and I'm co-directing the musical
for one simple reason.
To have big fun.
In fact...
Yeah, okay. Um, ahem.
Everyone, hi. Um...
I know that cast parties are usually
after opening night,
but the Farm will be hosting
a little get-together tonight
-at the former Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
-Sweet.
And, um, I know it may seem
a little weird, or Method-y, but...
come in costume.
-Whoo!
Great, Kevin.
-[girl] Totally.
-[boy] Let's go.
Anything big come over the radio today?
As a matter of fact, there were a string
of pharmacy break-ins, and, uh...
I wasn't sure I was gonna tell you this,
but, uh, Tent City was ransacked.
Our old trailer was stolen.
Wait, missing pharmaceuticals,
and a stolen house on wheels?
Doesn't that sound like the makings
of a mobile drug lab?
It's possible, sure.
I mean, Riverdale's filled
with a lot of desperate folks.
Maybe the Serpents
and I can help you look for it.
What, the trailer?
-Boy, it was worthless.
-Not to me.
-That was our home for how many years?
-Too many.
Just popping in to change.
There's a cast party tonight.
Don't wait up.
Uh, Veronica...
we have to talk.
-Your mother and I are separating.
-What?
No, you're not.
Very funny.
Um...
I'll be staying
at the Five Seasons indefinitely.
Wait. What is happening?
It's already been decided.
We wanted to tell you in person.
No, Daddy, whatever this is,
we can figure it out as a family, just...
Can someone please tell me
what's going on?
Ask your mother.
[door closes]
Mom?
-He knows, Veronica.
-Knows what?
The truth.
He knows I sold the drugs
out from under him
while he was in the hospital.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna take a bath.
You have fun with your friends.
[Veronica]
Given the night I've been having,
I, for one, could use a libation, so...
salud.
[laughs]
-[boy] I'll take one.
-That's the spirit.
Whoo!
I wonder what your father, Edgar,
would say about all this, Evelyn?
No need to wonder.
♪ Dad says, "Act your age" ♪
♪ You heard the boss
It's time to rage ♪
♪ Blast the bass
Turn out the light ♪
♪ Ain't nobody home tonight ♪
♪ Get down, it's all cool ♪
♪ Jump right in my heated pool ♪
♪ Punch the wall and start a fight ♪
♪ Ain't nobody home tonight ♪
♪ Ah, the folks are gone ♪
♪ It's time for big fun, big fun ♪
♪ We're up till dawn ♪
♪ Having some big fun, big fun ♪
♪ It's time to overflow ♪
♪ That hot tub on the patio ♪
♪ It's big fun ♪
♪ Big fun ♪
Veronica, you're looking good tonight.
♪ A hot guy smiled at me ♪
♪ Without a trace of mockery ♪
♪ Brainiac cleans up all right ♪
♪ Veronica is hot tonight ♪
♪ This night's all a blur ♪
♪ How did I get so popular? ♪
♪ Don't get close, you might ignite ♪
♪ Veronica is hot tonight ♪
♪ Dreams are coming true ♪
♪ When people laugh
But not at you ♪
♪ I'm not alone, I'm not afraid ♪
♪ I feel like Bono at Live Aid ♪
♪ Big fun ♪
♪ Big fun, big fun ♪
♪ I'm actually having... ♪
♪ Big fun ♪
♪ Big fun, big fun ♪
♪ The party's hot, hot, hot ♪
♪ It's time for big fun, big fun ♪
♪ You need a Jell-O shot ♪
♪ We're having big fun, big fun ♪
♪ Dang, dang
Diggety-dang-a-dang ♪
I can't believe she actually came.
I need a refill.
It's time to let everything go.
Follow my lead.
♪ Dang, dang
Diggety-dang-a-dang ♪
♪ Diggety-dang-a-dang ♪
♪ The folks are gone ♪
♪ It's time for big fun, big fun ♪
♪ We're up till dawn ♪
♪ Having some big fun, big fun ♪
♪ Our folks got no clue
'Bout half the stuff their children do ♪
♪ It's big fun ♪
♪ Big fun ♪
[all] Whoo!
[boy] Woo-hoo! All right.
Can I confess something?
I was afraid
this was never gonna happen again.
Me, too.
But maybe you and me
are meant to be together.
Maybe we're endgame.
Reggie...
Hungry, Kevin? Here.
It's an organic brownie
with Farm-grown maple mushrooms baked in.
-Oh.
-Try it. They're... transformative.
Enjoy the ride.
With a big gulp of water.
Fountain's in the hall.
So, last night was big fun.
But now it's time to dig deep.
So, we're each gonna share something
that we've never told anyone before.
Big or small.
So, does no one have a burden
that the rest of us can help shoulder?
I'm being haunted by Midge's ghost.
I've been thinking about her all the time
since rehearsals started.
I just feel so guilty--
I've been seeing her, too.
Not her ghost,
but in nightmares.
[chuckles]
How beautiful.
Through revealing their truth,
these two young men
have found an unexpected connection,
perhaps more.
So, um...
-Who would like to go next?
-[Sweet Pea] I got something.
Now, I know it was just supposed
to be a summer fling,
and, uh, she didn't want a relationship,
but I did.
So, it really blew to see Archie
and Josie getting cozy last night.
Arch...
are you and Josie dating?
Well, I mean...
[Josie] Uh...
-[Reggie] Did you know about this?
-What?
No, I had no idea.
The fact that your ex-boo
has a new girlfriend
has nothing to do
with you suddenly being all-in with me?
Veronica?
Anything to share?
I just found out
that my parents are separating.
My family's unconventional,
to say the least,
but I always thought,
no matter what, they'd stay together.
And that is what we,
in the theater, call a breakthrough.
-So, I guess people know about us now.
-Yup.
He's a real class act, that Sweet Pea.
Josie, is it such a bad thing?
Why not make it official?
Why not be boyfriend and girlfriend?
Archie...
Okay.
The other day,
when you asked how we got together?
We were lonely.
It's not exactly strong bedrock.
That's what you think we are?
Just lonely souls, filling the void?
So, that's the real reason.
You wanted to get back together
'cause your parents are splitsville.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-I wanted to ignore it.
To feel better.
You make me feel better.
I know how it must seem,
and I would understand
if you never wanted to talk to me again.
That's not what I'm saying.
And truly, it sucks about your folks.
But I don't think this is something
we should be doing right now.
[Reggie sighs]
What's your damage, Child of the Corn?
I just thought you might wanna see
what's happening in the hall.
Um, did you have a lobotomy for breakfast?
You're wearing my signature color.
You don't own the color red.
Red existed before you.
Not at Riverdale High.
Here, I invented red.
I am red.
Sorry,
but this school's not big enough
for both of us, faux-Pink Lady.
And I was here first.
So, go to Centerville High,
or Westerberg.
I don't care.
But you have until first bell Monday
to clear every trace of yourself
out of these halls.
Copy?
♪ The demon queen of high school
Has decreed it ♪
♪ She says Monday, 8 a.m.
I'll be deleted ♪
♪ They'll hunt me down in study hall ♪
♪ Stuff and mount me on the wall ♪
♪ Thirty hours to live
How shall I spend them? ♪
♪ I'll jump right on my motorbike ♪
Or...
♪ Here's an option that I like ♪
♪ Spend these 30 hours gettin' freaky ♪
♪ All hope is gone ♪
♪ I'm a dead girl walking ♪
♪ I'm on your lawn ♪
♪ Before they punch my clock ♪
♪ I'm snappin' off your window lock ♪
♪ Got no time to knock ♪
♪ I'm a dead girl walking ♪
Uh, Toni, Peaches, what's going on?
Shh.
♪ Had to see you
Hope I didn't wake you ♪
♪ But I intend to hold you
Till I break you ♪
♪ 'Cause Cheryl says I gots to go ♪
♪ You're my last meal on death row ♪
♪ Shut your mouth
And lose them tighty-whities ♪
♪ And you know, you know ♪
♪ You know ♪
♪ It's 'cause you're beautiful ♪
♪ You say you're numb inside ♪
♪ But I can't agree ♪
♪ So, the world's unfair ♪
♪ Keep it locked out there ♪
♪ In here it's beautiful ♪
♪ Let's make this beautiful ♪
-[both] That works for me.
-Stop.
Stop.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have brought you guys here.
I can't do this.
[Jughead] Sweet Pea and Fangs
are on musical detail,
but the rest of you have your groups
and grids.
Scour the area, find my trailer.
If I'm right,
it's being used as a drug lab,
and we need to shut it down.
First sight of it, call me ASAP, okay?
[boy] All right, Jug. You got it.
-You wanna go hunting with me tonight?
-I wish.
But I heard from...
well, eavesdropping,
Evelyn called a closed rehearsal
for select cast members
in the Gargoyle Chamber.
Can I borrow your camera?
♪ [Evelyn singing] They made you cry ♪
♪ But that will end tonight ♪
♪ We'll burn it down and then ♪
♪ We'll build the world again ♪
♪ Our love is God ♪
♪ We can start and finish wars ♪
♪ We're what killed the dinosaurs ♪
♪ We're the asteroid that's overdue ♪
♪ The new world needed room ♪
♪ For me and you ♪
♪ I worship you ♪
♪ I'd trade my life for yours ♪
♪ They all will disappear ♪
-♪ We'll plant our garden here ♪
-♪ Plant our garden here ♪
-♪ Our love is God ♪
♪ May the one become many ♪
-Hey.
You got my text. You came.
Um...
I wanted to talk to you.
Wait.
Can I go first?
Look, if you don't wanna be
in a relationship
because you're not into me,
then that's fine.
But if you do like me...
then let's start figuring out what we are,
and what we can be to each other,
for real.
Let's clean the slate,
and let's fight for this.
Let's fight for us.
♪ Hey, Mr. No-Name-Kid ♪
♪ So, who might you be? ♪
♪ And could you fight for me? ♪
♪ And hey, could you face the crowd? ♪
♪ Could you be seen with me ♪
♪ And still act proud? ♪
♪ Hey, could you hold my hand? ♪
♪ And could I carry you ♪
♪ Through no-man's-land? ♪
♪ It's fine if you don't agree ♪
♪ But I would fight for you ♪
♪ If you would fight for me ♪
♪ Well, whoa, you can punch real good ♪
♪ You've lasted longer
Than I thought you would ♪
♪ So, hey, Mr. No-Name-Kid ♪
♪ If some night you're free ♪
♪ Wanna fight for me? ♪
-♪ If we're still alive ♪
-♪ I would fight for you ♪
-♪ If you would fight for me ♪
Check that out.
Principal Weatherbee,
Heathers is being used
to indoctrinate students into a cult.
It looks like
these two boys are simply rehearsing.
No. No, no.
This is part of a religious ceremony.
A ritual.
The Farm is a fully sanctioned club,
Ms. Cooper.
Approved by me,
after I read Edgar's doctrines,
which, I must say,
I found quite fascinating...
appealing.
Jug, you'll never believe this.
I think Weatherbee is part of the Farm.
[Jughead] Yeah, well, I have news, too.
Can you meet me at Junkyard Steve's, ASAP?
What is that, drain cleaner?
No.
It's an olive branch.
-So, you're here to beg for clemency?
-No.
For us.
What are we doing?
What are we even fighting about?
Babe, what was love like in your family?
It was...
all-or-nothing.
Pure adoration, or distilled hate.
Thornhill was a den of shadows.
And J.J. was my only light.
Then...
he died.
And it was dark again.
Until you.
And then it felt
like you were disappearing on me.
But I'm not gone.
I'm right here.
And maybe...
it's not too late for us.
[Jughead] Tonsils called it in.
Oh, my God.
This was my childhood home.
My mom destroyed it.
How the hell did we get here?
When did our lives go from worrying about
who's gonna sit next to us on the bus
to drug lord mothers?
And serial killer fathers.
And unstoppable cults.
[Kevin] This is the emotional climax
of the musical.
"Seventeen" captures the longing
all the characters feel
for what they've lost.
Their teen innocence.
What are we gonna do?
I've got a crazy idea.
♪ Let's be normal ♪
♪ See bad movies ♪
♪ Sneak a beer and watch TV ♪
♪ We'll bake brownies ♪
♪ Or go bowling ♪
♪ Don't you want a life with me? ♪
♪ Can't we be 17? ♪
♪ That's all I want to do ♪
♪ If you could let me in ♪
♪ I could be good with you ♪
♪ People hurt us ♪
♪ Or they vanish ♪
♪ And you're right
That really blows ♪
♪ But we let go ♪
♪ Take a deep breath ♪
♪ Then go buy some summer clothes ♪
♪ We'll go camping ♪
♪ Play some poker ♪
♪ And we'll eat some chili fries ♪
♪ Maybe prom night ♪
♪ Maybe dancing ♪
-♪ Don't stop looking in my eyes ♪
-♪ Your eyes ♪
-♪ Can't we be 17? ♪
-♪ Is that so hard to do? ♪
-♪ If you could let me in ♪
-♪ I could be good with you ♪
-♪ Let us be 17 ♪
-♪ If we still got the right ♪
♪ So, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ I wanna be with you ♪
-♪ I wanna be with you ♪
-♪ Wanna be with you ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
-♪ You're the one ♪
-♪ I choose ♪
Maybe...
Maybe we can steal the trailer back,
while everyone's at the play.
Arch can lend me the keys
to his dad's truck,
and I can just move it,
get it out of my mom's hands.
Is this idea maybe more emotional
than practical?
-Because another thing you could do is--
-What?
You let it go.
[Veronica] Come back home, Daddy.
So what if Mom tried
to get rid of your drugs?
Do you wanna know the real reason
why we're getting a divorce?
I found out that your mother tried
to have me killed.
Twice.
I can't believe that.
Oh, mija, yes, you can.
In fact, I think part of you already knew.
You always say...
family is the most important thing.
Family is trust.
You and your mother betrayed me, so...
there is no family anymore.
Veronica, your solo's up.
I was gonna talk
about the devastating loneliness
your character feels
at this particular moment,
but it seems like you're already there,
so, take it away.
♪ I float in a boat ♪
♪ In a raging black ocean ♪
♪ Low in the water ♪
♪ And nowhere to go ♪
♪ The tiniest lifeboat ♪
♪ With people I know ♪
♪ Cold, clammy, and crowded ♪
♪ The people smell desperate ♪
♪ We'll sink any minute ♪
♪ So, someone must go ♪
♪ The tiniest lifeboat ♪
♪ With the people I know ♪
Don't worry, I'm not Parent-Trapping you.
I recognize
your irreconcilable differences.
But I do have a request to make.
Come to opening night. Together.
That's all I ask.
To make one last happy memory.
♪ I'm hugging my knees ♪
♪ And the captain is pointing ♪
♪ I thought I was captain ♪
♪ Still, the weakest must go ♪
♪ The tiniest lifeboat ♪
♪ Full of people I know ♪
-[Gladys scoffs]
-[sighs]
Well, finally. We gotta motor in ten.
-Whoa, what the hell happened?
-Are you okay?
I'm fine. It's just some scratches.
-JB, would you pick me out a clean shirt?
-Okay.
What, did you piss off a cat in heat?
Some tweaked-out Fizzle-head
was playing G&G in the middle of the road.
The candy store is definitely back open,
but I am gonna find
whoever's cooking that crap.
[Gladys] Drugs.
It's terrible.
What a nightmare.
Dad, if you're okay,
I think Betty and I are gonna ride ahead.
-We'll just meet you at the play.
-[FP] Okay.
Why? What's going on?
Just a quick stop.
Little pre-show tradition.
Sign my program later?
-[boy] Hey, Evelyn.
-Hey.
Just... Right here. Thanks.
It's ten minutes to places, cast.
[all] Thank you, ten.
[Josie chuckles]
And now for my favorite part.
Blot.
Parfait, this color was made for you.
We have to get you a tube.
[laughs]
-Where have you been?
-Hi. Sorry. We had to make a quick stop.
What is all over your faces? Soot?
-Get to makeup, stat.
-Okay.
Betty, make sure he knows his line
and choreography for the finale.
-Okay.
-My line?
-Yeah.
-I'm not part of the cast.
No, it's kind of a big statement song now.
Kevin wants everyone in it.
Don't worry, follow my lead.
It's basically just a costume change.
Come on.
♪ [singing] Listen up folks
War is over ♪
♪ Brand-new sheriff's come to town ♪
♪ We are done with acting evil ♪
♪ We will lay our weapons down ♪
♪ We're all damaged
We're all frightened ♪
♪ We're all freaks
But that's all right ♪
♪ We'll endure it
We'll survive it ♪
♪ Martha, are you free tonight? ♪
Jeez.
Talk about watching your childhood
go up in flames.
Are you okay?
I'm surviving.
'Cause you're here with me.
♪ I can't promise
No more Heathers ♪
♪ High school may not ever end ♪
♪ Still I miss you
I'd be honored ♪
-♪ If you'd let me be your friend ♪
-♪ My friend ♪
♪ We can be 17 ♪
♪ We can learn how to chill ♪
♪ If no one loves me now ♪
♪ Someday, somebody will ♪
♪ We can be 17 ♪
♪ Still time to make things right ♪
♪ We want a better world ♪
♪ So, why not start tonight? ♪
-♪ You know, you know, you know ♪
-♪ Let's go be 17 ♪
-♪ We can be beautiful ♪
-♪ Take off our shoes and dance ♪
-♪ You know, you know, you know ♪
-♪ Act like we're all still kids ♪
♪ 'Cause this may be our final chance ♪
-♪ You know, you know, you know ♪
-♪ Always be 17 ♪
-♪ We can be beautiful ♪
-♪ Celebrate you and I ♪
-♪ You know, you know, you know ♪
-♪ Maybe we won't grow old ♪
♪ And maybe then we'll never die ♪
♪ We'll make it beautiful ♪
♪ Beautiful, beautiful ♪
♪ Beautiful ♪
I knew my dad would like it.