- [NARRATOR] Previously on Riverdale:
- I'm Cassidy.
We'll take what we want,
and then we'll go.
[VERONICA] If you tell me
you're going to Shadow Mines...
[ARCHIE] I am.
They'd be alive,
if I wasn't in the picture.
Andrews, warden wants to see you.
Killing that boy at Shadow Lake,
you have no one to blame but yourself.
[ALICE] The warden from that juvie
killed himself.
[BETTY] I saw you with Hiram Lodge.
You're testing his
drugs out on patients.
- Why?
- I only answer to one authority, Betty.
[BETTY] Let's convince them to escape.
Give them the opposite
- of the Gargoyle King, which is...
- [ETHEL] The Gryphon Queen.
The king is dead.
You're all free.
What are we gonna do with all these
kids? They have nowhere to go.
The bounty on your pal Archie
is why you gotta cut him loose.
- I won't just ditch Archie.
- [ARCHIE] Your mom's right, Jug.
Wherever I go next has gotta be alone.
[GLADYS] We'll get you to the border.
I know a guy who can help.
Town's under quarantine.
Governor's orders.
No one in or out.
[JUGHEAD] What hero's journey would be
complete without a self-imposed exile?
Witness Archie Andrews.
Just as Luke Skywalker went
to planet Dagobah,
so, too, has Archie been
in the Canadian hinterlands,
wondering what dark demons
he would have to conquer
before being able, finally, to go home.
And speaking of home...
Since Riverdale's quarantine,
the crime rate in town had risen.
There'd been, for instance,
a series of daring cat burglaries.
[CHUCKLES]
You make an extremely sexy Robin Hood,
Tee-Tee.
Stealing from the rich,
to give to, well...
us.
You're so crazy.
I love you.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
[JUGHEAD] It's been five weeks since we
were cut off from the rest of the world.
The quarantine's been lifted,
but the town still hasn't
gotten its pep back.
Blossom. Topaz. Break it up.
- Bite me, Moose.
- One of the new school rules.
All physical contact must be kept
to a minimum.
That doesn't make sense. There
haven't been any seizures for weeks.
- Everything tested came back negative.
- RROTC doesn't make the rules, Toni.
No. You just enforce them,
like the crypto-fascists you are.
Come on, Tee-Tee.
[JUGHEAD] Though aboveground, Riverdale
was a haunted shell of its former self,
underground, at Veronica's I.
Bonne Nuit, life was beautiful.
♪ Come hear the music play ♪
♪ Come blow that horn
Start celebrating ♪
♪ Right this way
Your table's waiting ♪
♪ No use permitting... ♪
Cheryl. Toni.
Welcome, ladies.
I've got your usual
table waiting for you.
- Merci, madam.
- Enjoy.
♪ So, come to the cabaret ♪
What's the good word, Reginald?
[SIGHS] The kegs are tapped out,
we've got more empty bottles than full.
Hell, even your mocktails
are selling out tonight.
- [CHUCKLES]
- It's nuts.
♪ And I love ♪
♪ A cabaret ♪
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[SIGHS]
- What was that?
- No, not again.
Just go back to sleep, Jug.
Pray that that didn't wake up my mom.
The Gargoyle King,
he's coming to kill me.
Hey, hey, hey.
No.
He's not, Hannah.
It's just a bad dream, okay?
That's all over, remember?
- The Gargoyle King is dead.
- The Gryphon Queen, she slayed him.
She saved us.
Exactly, Tyler.
[HANNAH] Okay, but since we're up,
can we play?
Please?
It really does make us feel better.
Okay, just one quick round,
and then back to bed.
What is this?
Who does this belong to? Huh?
They're Tyler's. He's been taking them.
Tyler.
Where did you get the Fizzle Rocks?
An unnamed Serpent dealing Fizzle Rocks?
Sure he wasn't lying?
If it was a lie,
Tyler came up with it pretty quickly.
A Serpent dealing Hiram Lodge's drugs,
like we're one of his gangs.
This is my fault. I
was gone for too long.
I left the Serpents high and dry.
I left you high and dry.
No, you were protecting Archie.
Yeah, and while I was busy
protecting the Red Paladin,
Hiram made a play for the entire town
and he got it.
Fizzle Rocks are everywhere.
Weatherbee's running Riverdale High
like a police state.
We don't even have an
elected sheriff yet.
Quarantine?
Why would he want the town quarantined?
Can't just be because he wants
to expand his candy business
and make more money, can it?
Hiram was paying the Sisters
to test out his drugs
on the patients there.
I don't see how
he could possibly get away with that.
Attorney McCoy and I are just trying
to get Sister Woodhouse
and the rest of her nuns to rat him out.
And we're close, I think.
God, could you imagine?
Hiram Lodge finally
paying for his crimes,
brought down by the testimony of nuns.
Well...
maybe that means
Archie could come back home.
Wherever he is.
This is KDK12 to KDK1. Over.
[WOMAN] This is KDK1. How are things
looking in your neck of the woods? Over.
Same as the last few weeks.
Quiet and clear. Over.
Glad to hear it.
Still thinking about staying on
for another rotation,
or you ready
to leave the wilderness behind? Over.
I might sleep on it.
I'm still figuring things out.
Not sure if I'm ready to go back yet.
Copy that.
Oh, we've been getting
some bear sightings,
so, stay vigilant
while you're clearing the trails. Over.
Will do, ma'am. Over and out.
[CCR'S "LOOKIN' OUT
MY BACK DOOR" PLAYING]
Come on.
♪ Just got home from Illinois
Lock the front door, oh, boy! ♪
♪ Got to sit down
Take a rest on the porch ♪
♪ Imagination sets in
Pretty soon I'm singin' ♪
♪ Doo, doo, doo
Lookin' out my back door ♪
Shoot.
[SIGHS]
What the hell, man?
[DISTORTED VOICE] Veronica
Lodge hasn't paid what she owes.
[REGGIE] Let me go.
I'm sorry that this happened, Reggie.
With my father breathing down our necks,
I suppose it was only a matter of time.
- [GROANS]
- Sorry.
Thanks.
Every time I make a beer run
across the border,
I've changed it up,
never taking the same road twice.
He got lucky.
Daddy made it very clear...
that if I. Bonne Nuit was
to continue operating
in a post-quarantine Riverdale,
I'd have to give him ten percent
of my earnings for the privilege.
If you start paying him
for protection now,
you'll never stop.
But there are ways to
minimize that price.
Five percent feels fair.
And once Daddy reviews
these well-cooked books...
he'll be none the wiser.
Has anyone ever told
you you're a badass?
- [BARKING]
- Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay, we'll go this way. Come on.
Come on, Vegas.
[BRANCHES CRACKING]
[GROWLING]
[BEAR ROARING]
[VEGAS BARKING]
This is KDK12 calling KDK1.
KDK12 to KDK1. Do you read me?
[WOMAN]
This is KDK1. We're receiving you. Over.
I need help. I've been attacked.
By a grizzly. I'm in bad shape.
How severe are your injuries? Over.
- It's bad.
- Stay calm. Help is on the...
[RADIO STATIC]
You're cutting out.
Apply pressure and are you able
to dress the wound?
Hello?
Damn it.
[GRUNTING]
It's okay, boy.
They said they're on their way.
We just gotta stay calm.
Good boy.
[BARKING]
Good boy, Vegas.
[WHIMPERS]
[ALICE] I am exhausted, Betty.
We don't have the resources
to shelter these... children.
But the Farm does.
Mom. No.
Well, they can't stay here.
Can this please just wait
until after the trial?
The only reason they left the Sisters
is because I convinced them to trust me.
They've imprinted on me.
I'm their Gryphon Queen.
Fine.
But as their queen,
they are your responsibility, not mine.
[BETTY] Let me get this straight.
Regardless of the fact
that the Sisters abused children,
and tested Hiram Lodge's drugs on them,
which is why they're in jail,
awaiting trial,
their lawyer doesn't want us
to harass them?
It gets worse.
I told Sowerberry
that we'd give the Sisters immunity
if they agreed to testify against Hiram.
He informed me that the nuns
had taken a vow of silence.
So, what if I testify?
You already admitted you were
all on drugs at the Sisters.
- Drugs that caused hallucinations.
- I know what I saw.
I believe you, Betty.
But a jury won't.
I like to give people the benefit
of the doubt.
I like to believe they can change.
But you never do, Daddy.
If this is about the attack
on your delivery truck,
I only know what I've heard.
That someone sent the Gargoyle Gang
to apply pressure to you.
World's gotten scary
these last few weeks.
Well, I'm ready to face reality.
I need protection, and...
you're the only person
who's offering it.
It's nothing to be ashamed of, mija.
Fifteen percent, drop in the bucket.
No Gargoyles will mess
with your contraband again.
Unfortunately, business has been slow.
Hmm.
How does five percent sound?
Really? Because Leo and Nico tell me
that your parking lot's
been packed every night.
Right, guys?
Mm-hm.
Well, well.
New coat, new capos.
You're walking tall these days.
Hope those nuns in jail don't crack,
and talk about
how you were their candy man.
I'll settle for ten percent.
But I need to see your books.
Naturally.
♪ [SINGING] Loves me ♪
♪ Well, all the odds are ♪
♪ They're in my favor ♪
♪ Something's bound to begin ♪
Josie's sounding incredible.
Only the best at I. Bonne Nuit.
♪ Happen sometime ♪
♪ Maybe this time ♪
♪ I'll win ♪
[JUGHEAD] All right, Serpents.
It's come to my attention
one of us has been dealing Fizzle Rocks.
Slinging dope is not what Serpents do.
So, from this moment on,
we're going clean.
There will be no selling or doing drugs.
No crime of any kind will be tolerated.
Anyone that breaks the Serpent Code
will be exiled.
- Permanently.
- I think it's pretty ridic
that you vanish for a month
on some vision quest with your bestie,
only to return
and lecture us about responsibility.
We got no money coming in, Jug.
How are we supposed to eat?
Survive?
We'll figure it out and get back to you,
Fangs. All of you.
In the meantime...
"In unity there is strength."
[ALL] In unity, there is strength.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[SCREAMING]
Help me!
I'm so, so sorry this happened to you,
Josie.
I'm paying someone a lot to make sure
this exact sort of thing doesn't happen.
They were from your father's gang,
weren't they?
You know,
whatever problems you've got with him,
I can't be dragged into them.
Either you get this
mess straightened out,
or I. Bonne Nuit finds itself
a new headliner.
[POLLY] They helped me. Gave me freedom.
Gave me back my life.
At the Farm,
you won't be the only ones doing chores.
Everybody's equal.
Um...
Polly. Evelyn.
What the hell is going on?
Mom called.
She said that you had your hands full.
Want a T-shirt?
Um, no. And neither do they.
Guys, don't take anything
from these two vampires, okay?
- They're bribing you.
- Betty doesn't know what she's saying.
When I escaped the Sisters,
the Farm became my salvation, my family.
Okay, as your Gryphon Queen,
I promised to protect you,
and keep you safe.
- And trust me, the Farm is not safe.
- Not safe?
Did you tell them how the Gargoyle King
and his henchmen broke into this house
and terrorized you and Mom?
What about these drugs we found here?
How can you be protecting them
if you allow them
to put dangerous chemicals
in their bodies?
I didn't know.
I don't know how they get them.
They're too scared to tell you,
because you're a Serpent.
But they told us.
A Serpent dealer named Fangs Fogarty.
[JUGHEAD] If you were hard up,
you could've talked to me.
The quarantine happened.
I needed money. You were gone.
Then you talk to me.
What do you need money for?
[SNIFFLES]
My mom's sick.
She's got treatments
that we can't pay for.
You're like a brother to me.
We could've helped.
- I was ashamed.
- So, you started dealing Fizzle Rocks?
Where'd you get it? The Gargoyle Gang?
I'm out now.
Punishment for breaking
the Code is exile.
However,
you've had a rougher year than most.
[SIGHS]
I'm willing to look the other way,
but this has to stay between us, okay?
- If I catch you dealing...
- You won't.
I'm done.
[TONI] Is that...?
A Glamergé Egg worth more than the GNP
of most developing countries?
Why, yes, Kitty Cat, it is.
[TONI] Okay, let's go.
Wait, Tee-Tee.
I'm feeling particularly brazen tonight.
[ARCHIE] Cassidy?
Good. You're awake.
Time to play.
- This isn't real. You guys are all dead.
- You keep saying that.
But then how are we here,
talking with you?
I'm dreaming. I must be.
Or I'm hallucinating
from the loss of blood.
Or we're here, and this is real.
No.
I went to juvie... after being framed
for your murder, Cassidy.
I found you three in the mines
after Sheriff Minetta gunned you down.
If what you say is
true, and we are dead,
it sounds like it's all your fault.
If you ever wanna return to Eldervair,
you're gonna have to play.
And win.
Come on.
One round, at least?
One round.
Any luck, Ms. Weiss?
I'm on the phone
with Child Services nonstop, Betty.
But...
But it's gonna be hard getting the kids
you're housing adopted or fostered.
There's concern about the trauma
they've suffered.
Yeah, well,
the Sisters really did a number on them.
Any luck getting the Sisters
to testify against Hiram?
They've taken a vow of silence.
It's part of their religion.
Religion?
Mm-hm.
Betty.
As a social worker, I've had dealings
with the Sisters over the years.
And there's something you need to know
about their affiliation with the Church.
[VERONICA] Josie was stalked, Daddy.
By those Gargoyles of yours.
So, tell me, if I'm paying you
ten percent for protection,
why is my headliner harassed?
Because you had the audacity
to try to deceive me.
Cooking the books?
That's the move of a rank amateur.
Now I want the full amount I'm owed.
And your mother's Glamergé Egg
that was stolen.
- Come again?
- One of your Serpent school chums
broke into our apartment
and stole your mother's bauble.
And based on the calling
card they left...
I'm guessing it's
probably Cheryl Blossom.
Anyway, get it back for me, won't you?
Why is this my responsibility?
Because you have more to lose than me.
[VERONICA] You need
to fix this, Jughead.
If Cheryl took the Egg, why come to me?
Why not go to her?
She's dodging my phone calls.
Besides, aren't you her king?
- Why are you and your father aligned?
- We're not.
He's squeezing me.
He's squeezing my business.
Now, not only does he
have me paying him protection,
he's got me on this wild-goose chase
to get my mom's stolen Egg back.
- You pay your father protection money?
- Against his very own Gargoyle Gang.
What if you pay less money
not to be in business with him?
- What are you suggesting?
- Let the Serpents work for you.
Get real protection
from your father's goons.
And the Serpents get jobs,
with a steady income.
This is a win-win.
Get me that Glamergé Egg back,
and we have an accord.
Your turn, Red.
"Defeat the Hooded Specter of Death."
Go on.
The challenge reveals the weakness.
The weakness is
what keeps you from winning.
[MAN] Give me your wallet!
[GUNSHOT]
[ARCHIE] I did it.
Now am I finished playing this game?
[NORTON] The Red Paladin returns.
[ARCHIE] Warden Norton?
Take a load off, my boy.
We're just getting started.
I won't play the game
with someone who died from it.
I didn't die.
I ascended to the kingdom.
And what about Joaquin?
Did he ascend, too?
That was his reward for stabbing me,
wasn't it?
That was the card Mr. DeSantos drew.
His do-or-die moment.
You know all about those,
don't you, Archie?
Didn't you have one yourself?
With the Black Hood?
Yes.
And I stopped him, but I'm still
trapped here, in this hell.
Then that wasn't the moment.
The place and time
where it all went wrong.
Roll the dice,
and you may find the path
that leads back to Eldervair.
We know your secret, Sister Woodhouse.
The Church disbanded
the Sisters of Quiet Mercy
during Vatican II,
over allegations
of cruel and inhumane practices.
You and your sisters haven't been nuns
for more than 60 years.
Which means your vow of silence
won't hold up in court.
Here's the new deal.
Testify against Hiram Lodge,
and I won't have you charged
with the following crimes:
Child endangerment,
illegal drug testing, human trafficking.
[SIGHS]
Fine.
What do I need to do?
Swear in court that Hiram
Lodge gave you money and drugs
for illegal testing.
You'll have immunity.
[JUGHEAD] Serpents.
Earlier today...
I brokered a deal.
Got us a paid gig.
From here on out,
we'll be working security detail
for Veronica Lodge,
her speakeasy, and her employees.
- Long live the Serpents. Whoo!
- [ALL CHEERING]
Settle down.
It's good news,
but I've also gathered us here
for less celebratory reasons.
Cheryl, Toni.
- Come up here.
- Excuse me?
What did we do?
You broke into the Lodge apartment
and stole a Glamergé Egg.
So what if we did?
Well, more than that,
you left your calling card...
attaching yourself, and, by extension,
all of the Serpents to your crime.
I'm not afraid of Lodge.
What's he gonna do?
Call the sheriff?
- Oh, right, there is no sheriff.
- That's not the point.
You broke the Code.
- Turn in your jackets and go.
- [TONI] Are you serious?
I'm a Serpent by blood.
You can't take that away from me.
[CHERYL] You hypocrite.
Give your buddy Fangs a pass,
but crucify us?
In case you're wondering how we know,
Fangs told Sweet Pea, who told me.
Who told me.
If you ask for our jackets,
shouldn't you ask for his?
Jug.
You're right.
- Fangs, give me your jacket.
- Hey. What the hell, man?
It's okay, Sweet Pea.
Some leader you are.
Fangs.
[JUGHEAD] Cheryl? Toni?
We'll go, but we're keeping our jackets.
Fine. But I need that Egg back.
Come again?
You need to give me that damn Egg.
Or Veronica won't give us the contract.
Why would I care? I'm not a Serpent.
Because I believe
that you still have honor, Cheryl.
And it's getting cold out,
and the rest of us don't
get to go back to Thistlehouse.
[VERONICA] Well done, Torombolo.
Cost me a lot to get that ugly
thing back. You put it to good use.
Oh, don't you worry, I shall.
And in the meantime,
you and the Serpents have
your first assignment.
You ever hear of the Gargoyle Gang?
[BETTY]
Tyler, what the hell happened to you?
You lied to us.
- What do you mean? I would never.
- You said he was dead, but I saw him.
I saw the Gargoyle King.
[ALL GASPING AND CHATTERING]
What? Where?
Fox Forest.
He was there, with other Gargoyles,
his gang. They beat me up.
The Gryphon Queen is a liar.
And if she lied
about the Gargoyle King being dead,
- maybe she lied when she says we're safe.
- I'm not. You have to believe me.
The Sisters are going
to testify against the Man in Black,
and then you will all be safe.
Where, Betty?
Where will we be safe?
It's your turn, Red Paladin.
Go on.
Pick your Quest Card.
What does it say?
"Kill the Gargoyle King."
Are you sure?
Read it again.
"Kill the Man in Black."
You have your marching orders.
Slay the dragon.
Good luck.
The Gargoyle King.
The Man in Black.
How many names do you have, Hiram?
I know why you've come.
Do you genuinely think
killing me will solve all your problems?
It's what I should've done that night.
In here, my do-or-die moment,
before you had me arrested.
Yeah, it was awfully stupid of you
to come in here,
threaten me,
tell me all your plans.
What was I supposed to do?
Not have you arrested?
Put that down, Archie.
You're not gonna...
[HIRAM GRUNTING]
I don't understand.
What are you doing here?
I thought... I thought it was over.
You're almost done.
Just one last round to play.
[BETTY] Have you been working
on any new songs, Arch?
I'd love to hear some of them.
I haven't played guitar in forever.
I'm not the same person anymore.
I don't wanna do this.
- I don't wanna play with you.
- You have to.
- It's the only way back.
- Back to what?
Eldervair.
Riverdale.
Innocence.
Come on, Arch.
Time to play.
[BETTY] Thanks for meeting me
on such short notice.
A lot of the freed patients
from Sisters of Quiet Mercy
have been orphaned or disowned.
My mom and I have been housing them,
but that is becoming...
untenable.
So, if any of you are willing or able
to take a few in,
just until the Sisters testify
against Hiram,
and he's behind bars...
I could take, you
know, some of the boys.
And with Archie gone, I have the room.
I've saved many children from that
particular circle of hell before
and I'm happy to do it again.
Nana and I will board some girls
at Thistlehouse.
And we have a pull-out here.
I'll house a couple.
Thank you.
[FP] What about this
deal with the Lodges?
Veronica, not the Lodges.
Oh.
She's still a Lodge, boy.
Don't ever forget it.
As I recall,
you worked for the Lodges once.
Does trashing that drive-in
ring any bells?
I want you to be a better king than me.
- Make us players, instead of pawns.
- That's what I'm trying to do, Dad.
Put me in.
I'm tired of sitting on the sidelines.
I'm not made for it.
- We gotta stop meeting like this.
- [DISTORTED VOICE] Shut your mouth.
Trash the cargo. All of it.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Let's go.
- [MAN] Come on. It's an ambush.
Get them.
Tried to tell you.
Get him up.
I want you to go back
to your Gargoyle King,
or your Man in Black, or Hiram Lodge,
and I want you to tell him that
Veronica is now under the protection
of the Serpents,
and that Riverdale has not fallen.
Go.
Mom?
Where are they? Where are the kids?
After that one was attacked, I called
Edgar, and asked him for advice,
and he came, and took them to the Farm.
Edgar did?
You only missed him by,
like, five minutes.
It's your turn, Archie.
You have to pick a Quest Card.
Is this the last level?
Sure feels like it, doesn't it?
You don't have to do this, son.
He's the one who got
me into this trouble.
Not the Black Hood.
Not the Gargoyle King, not Hiram Lodge.
Him.
It's the only way.
You could forgive him.
It's too late.
You are not the villain
you think you are.
I've hurt everyone.
There's always another path home, son.
Not for me.
If I ever wanna go back
to Riverdale again...
I have to destroy that part of me...
that's weak...
that's bad, that's stupid.
Just come home, Archie.
I can't, Dad.
I have to do this one thing first.
I'm sorry, Dad.
- I'm sorry for letting you down.
- Wait.
♪ Maybe this time ♪
♪ I'll be lucky ♪
♪ Maybe this time he'll stay ♪
♪ Maybe this time ♪
♪ For the first time ♪
♪ Love won't hurry away ♪
♪ He will hold me fast ♪
♪ I'll be home at last ♪
♪ Not a loser anymore ♪
♪ Like the last time ♪
♪ And the time before ♪
Fangs, my dad and I were talking.
We wanna give you another shot
at redemption.
- What are you thinking?
- We want you to go undercover.
Join the Gargoyle Gang.
We need a man on the inside
of Hiram's drug operation
so we can take him down.
Are you in?
It'd be an honor.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Attorney McCoy? I was just reviewing
our questions for the Sisters.
Don't bother, Betty.
- The Sisters are gone.
- Gone?
How?
An anonymous donor posted their bail.
Hiram Lodge.
Then they took off who-knows-where.
But not before leaving a message.
"We go to join thee."
Does that mean anything to you?
Oh, my God,
I think I know where they went.
[VERONICA SINGING]
♪ Something's bound to begin ♪
♪ It's got to happen ♪
♪ Happen sometime ♪
♪ Maybe this time I'll win ♪
♪ 'Cause everybody ♪
♪ They love a winner ♪
♪ So nobody loves me ♪
♪ Lady Peaceful ♪
♪ Lady Happy ♪
♪ That's what I long to be ♪
♪ Well, all the odds are ♪
♪ They're in my favor ♪
- ♪ Something's bound to begin ♪
- [VEGAS BARKING]
Come on, kid. Come on, wake up.
Wake up, kid.
♪ ...sometime ♪
♪ Maybe this time ♪
♪ I'll win ♪