[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
[crowd cheering]
[Norton] That kid is a star.
Can I kiss you?
Archie.
You broke the code.
Turn in your jackets and go.
I'm a Serpent by blood.
- What's this?
- [Cheryl] A gang, and you're the leader.
[Veronica] I think my mom may have
hired someone to shoot my dad,
so she could make a profit
from the sale of his drug operation.
Let's end this nightmare.
Find the drugs and destroy them,
before my mom sells everything.
[Hermione] What did you do?
I used the cash from the sale
to pay off Governor Dooley.
And now my buyer is coming
and they are gonna want blood.
Here's your money.
Or as much as we could get of it.
We'll figure out a payment plan
for the rest.
[Jughead] Gryphons and Gargoyles.
Serpents and Ghoulies.
Riverdale was a veritable jungle
of mythological creatures,
species jockeying for power...
and at the dark heart of it all...
[Gladys] Good morning, sunshine.
Wakey, wakey.
Breakfast is served.
Wow, Mom.
[chuckles]
It's way better than the normal breakfast.
- Morning.
- Sleep on it wrong?
- There's no right way to sleep on a couch.
- Want the bed?
- No, I'm fine.
I need coffee.
- You let her drink coffee?
- [chuckles]
[chuckles] Okay. It's fine by me.
Help yourself.
I gotta get to work. Hey.
You need anything, call me.
- Morning, Betty.
- Morning, Mom.
Is that your wedding dress?
It is.
I'm getting it altered.
Why, are you getting married?
In a sense.
I'm being baptized into the Farm.
I'm sorry. You're what?
Edgar says I'm finally ready.
All of the women from the Farm
are gathering Sunday night
at the new facility.
[Hiram] Mija, can I see you for a moment?
I'm getting caught up on things.
Hopefully you could answer a question
that's been nagging me.
In the short time I was laid up,
some very valuable equipment
and stock went missing from my prison.
Didn't Mom say that she had
to have it destroyed because of the feds?
Yeah, she did.
Tall Boy, an ex-Serpent, tried to kill me.
FP, an ex-Serpent, is now sheriff.
Gladys, a Toledo Serpent,
is back in town after years away.
And suddenly,
I'm out some very valuable assets.
If I didn't know better, I'd say
the Joneses pulled a fast one on me.
They strike me as opportunists,
not master schemers.
At a minimum, they'd need the help
of someone close to me
to pull anything like this off.
Oh, well.
The truth will shake out.
It always does.
- How about we skip class...
- [chuckles]
catch a matinee at the Bijou?
Oh, wow, you are sweeter
than a strawberry milkshake, Arch,
but I've got a meeting
with our college advisor.
Maybe we can meet up after school.
- I'm training with Mr. Keller then.
- Oh.
Are there any college scholarships
for boxing?
No, but stepping
in between those ropes, Josie,
it gets me and keeps me
in a good headspace.
Helps me focus.
Forget about everything outside the ring.
Well, almost everything else.
Yeah, well, just don't go messing up
that pretty face, Andrews.
It's growing on me.
It was the weirdest thing, Jug.
My mom's usually rubbing the Farm
in my face,
but now she's shutting me out.
Like she's washed her hands of me.
Which is even more terrifying.
And they're definitely up
to some serious shadiness,
like they're entrenching.
I was trying to dig up some dirt online
on the Farm.
Couldn't even find a photograph
of Edgar Evernever.
Not one, Jug.
That's weird.
You really wanna protect your mother,
maybe it's worthwhile
just embracing this whole baptism thing.
Or at least pretending to embrace it.
Might help to keep tabs on her,
make sure she's safe.
Come on.
[speaking indistinctly]
- Where is everyone else?
- We're down another eight.
- Another eight?
- [Sweet Pea] All girls.
Where are they all going?
Turns out Toni and Cheryl started
their own gang.
- All the girls are defecting to it.
- The Pretty Poisons.
So, what do you want us to do, boss?
Nothing.
This is all
because I banished Cheryl and Toni.
I need talk to Toni,
get her back into the Serpent fold.
The rest will come back, too.
They need to be reminded
what it means to be a Serpent.
I'll make this right.
[Keller] One-one-two.
Spider.
Your hand up, right? It's the first thing
I learned boxing in the Army.
You got a nasty habit
of telegraphing your punches.
You do that with an experienced fighter,
he'll see you coming from a mile away.
With all due respect, Mr. Keller,
those guys at L&L sure as hell didn't.
Get me a fight, a real fight,
with some of the guys training here.
- I can show you.
- Archie.
You've got good speed, all right?
And you got some power.
But you got no technique.
You have to learn that.
Until you do,
don't think about your first fight.
How long are we talking about?
Archie, you're not ready.
How can we know that
until you get me in the ring?
I need to know
if boxing is a viable option for me.
Trust me. Boxing is not something
you wanna do half-assed.
Good workout. Hit the showers.
This week's payment.
So, here's the deal.
My dad suspects that you
and FP are behind his recent troubles,
that you came back to Riverdale
to steal his drug trade.
Why is that my problem?
Because he's fired up
about rebuilding his empire
and you don't wanna get in his way.
Also, maybe you don't want him to find out
that Mommy tried to sell his business out
from under him, am I right?
No comment.
[laughs]
Clue me in on your dad's moves,
and that debt you owe me,
I might ease it slightly.
You want me to spy on my father? For you?
- That's not gonna happen.
- I don't wanna cause a drama here.
I just wanna get what's owed to me.
Plus a little bit more.
And now it looks as though I'm in a race
with your dad to rebuild the candy trade.
Who do you wanna be in charge?
Me...
or him?
You.
I want my family out of drugs.
We both want the same thing.
What's the problem?
Either you get Hiram out of my way...
or... sniff out what he's doing.
Let me know, so I can stay ahead of him.
I know what you're after, Elio,
but it ain't happening here.
Any boxer in this dump would be lucky
to fight Randy.
- It's just good business.
- [man] For you, sure. Not for me.
Elio.
Archie Andrews? You training here?
Yeah.
And if you need an opponent for your guy,
I'll do it. I'll fight.
How many bouts do you have
under your belt?
Well, none.
But I gotta get in the ring.
Otherwise, what's the point?
It's your lucky day.
Congrats, you just got your first fight.
One condition.
I need you to guarantee that you'll lose.
Are you serious?
Throw the fight,
make Randy here look good doing it.
No, Elio, I'm not taking a dive.
It's a golden opportunity
to start to make a name for yourself.
That's how it goes. Start building a rep.
First step to becoming a champ
is fighting a champ.
Boxing's like any other profession.
You gotta pay your dues.
But in this case, you also get paid.
Five thousand dollars.
- For one fight?
- Three rounds, that's all.
My guy gets another win,
you get on the board.
For a guy like you,
this is as good as it's gonna get.
I wanna get paid first.
Today. Now.
Half now, half after the fight.
You'll thank me, Red.
Let's go.
I'm worried about you, Daddy.
About our family.
I know you were dealing drugs.
But the drugs,
and the equipment you used
to manufacture them,
it's all gone.
You have an opportunity to go clean.
- To build a new empire.
- No.
- What opportunity were you thinking?
- Refocus on your prison.
Get it back on track.
You can fill the cells with criminals
and make more money
imprisoning drug dealers
than supplying them.
And it's legal.
That's good.
But you're thinking too small.
Here's what I'm thinking instead.
Penny Peabody used the Ghoulies
to manufacture, distribute, and sell...
candy.
Now that she's MIA, her gang is...
Well, it's leaderless.
Up for grabs.
If I gain control of the Ghoulies,
I regain control of the trade.
You're a Topaz.
Being in the Serpents is your birthright.
We are a family. I'd like you
to reconsider joining the gang.
You want me back in the Serpents?
Make me queen.
I mean, since I'm legacy and all, right?
[sighs]
- You know I can't do that.
- Because of Betty, right?
Then I'm not coming back.
What do the Pretty Poisons provide you
that the Serpents can't?
An opportunity to lead.
With the Pretty Poisons, I rule.
- We're a sisterhood.
- You're Cheryl's vanity project, you mean.
And you're wrong
about the Serpents still being family.
That's what we used to be. Not anymore.
Alice, you're gonna look
like heaven on earth.
[Alice] What do you think, Betty?
I think it's really pretty, Mom.
I'm so happy you decided
to be a part of this.
- You know how much this means to me.
- Of course, Mom.
Oh. Uh, Alice, I need those forms back.
Oh, right. They're right here.
What forms?
Just boilerplate.
Elizabeth.
What kind of baptism requires
a signed release form
exculpating the organization
in case of "bodily harm or death"?
[Alice] It's a standard form.
I signed one scarier
when I joined 23-Hour Fitness.
Your mother is on the verge
of discovering something
people spend their lives looking for
and never find.
No need to be afraid or stand in the way.
Um, there is if she's gonna get hurt.
It's just like Edgar said.
You're a detractor.
But I'm not gonna let you ruin
this day for Mom.
Fine, but if Mom dies,
then her blood is on your hands, Polly.
[sighs]
You look beautiful.
My father's going after the Ghoulies.
He says they're the cooks and the runners,
so, if you wanna win this war,
you need soldiers to fight it.
Well...
it looks like the pretty bird
bought herself another day.
Keep up the good work, little magpie.
Hey, hey, hey.
You took a fight against Randy Ronson?
Are you nuts?
The guy is 12-and-0 with ten KO's.
You haven't fought a round.
I have to prove myself somehow.
Elio's giving me a chance to do that.
Ronson, he fights dirty.
He sucker-punched one of his opponents.
The guy nosedived into a stool.
He hasn't walked since.
Archie, you make the call,
you cancel the fight,
or you find yourself a new coach.
[Cheryl] Archers, draw.
Anchor your hand
at the corner of your mouth.
Use your dominant eye.
Now relax, my pretties.
Release.
Brava.
Now go again.
Nice work, Poisons.
They have an excellent mentor.
They certainly do, babe.
Something wrong, mon trésor?
Jughead.
He tried to convince me
to rejoin the Serpents.
That worm. What did you say?
No, obviously.
He had the audacity
to call us a vanity project.
But don't worry, babe.
I'll find a way to put him in his place.
[sighs]
Time to show Jughead
just how poisonous we pretties can be.
- Heads or tails for this. Ready?
- Heads.
- Tails, mine. [laughs]
- Tails, what?
- [Sweet Pea chuckles]
- [Fangs] Oh.
- [Sweet Pea] Hey.
- [Fangs] Well, ladies. Evening.
Uh, look, girls.
We don't want any trouble
from your little sorority.
Don't call us girls,
and don't belittle us.
Or what?
You gonna challenge us to a pillow fight?
Seriously, Cheryl, what is this?
We're the Pretty Poisons, peabrain.
And we're here to deliver a message
to you and your leader.
That we are not to be dismissed,
or trifled with.
Ladies, introduce yourselves.
- Hey, we just don't want any trouble.
- Take it easy.
[thudding and grunting]
[Fangs and Sweet Pea] Hey, hey, hey!
- Ow.
- You guys are a joke.
Jug, if you don't get your house in order,
more people are gonna defect.
More gangs will start popping up.
And the Serpents' little piece of the pie
is gonna get smaller and smaller.
Store's open for suggestions, Mom.
You got any?
You need numbers.
Now, I happen to know for a fact,
the Ghoulies are up for grabs.
Ever since I took care of Penny,
they've been leaderless. Recruit them.
The Ghoulies tried
to burn down Pop's on Riot Night.
So, tame them,
and give them something they want.
Trust me.
This is your only shot at survival.
Hey, Tee-Tee. Check out my new nail color,
called Vigilante Violet.
What do you think?
I heard what you and the girls did
to Sweet Pea and Fangs.
The Serpents needed to know
the Pretty Poisons are here to stay,
- and we're not to be trifled with.
- I said I was going to handle it.
The purpose of our gang isn't
to air out your petty grievances
or to pursue your personal vendettas.
It's for protection and community.
I sent a message, planted a flag.
Cut the crap, Cheryl. Let me ask you this.
Is this gang mine or yours?
It's... yours, of course.
Then never deploy the Poisons
that way again without asking me.
Is that clear?
As a bottle
of sparkling San Junipero water.
- Hey.
[chuckles] So, I'm singing a little Tina
at La Bonne Nuit on Sunday night,
and I wouldn't mind having you on guitar.
- Sunday?
- Yeah.
I can't. I got a match.
What, your first fight?
Yeah.
That's major, Archie.
Why didn't you tell me?
[sighs] I'm gonna lose.
With that attitude, yeah, you are.
No, I'm the fall guy.
I get paid to throw the fight.
Oh, hold on.
That sounds shady.
It's a shortcut.
It'll get me in the game,
get my name out there.
It's like, before you can be a headliner,
you gotta be an opening act.
[groans] But getting paid
to be beaten down?
Josie, I'm an ex-con
who walked out of the SATs, remember?
Look, you've been dealt
some truly rotten hands, Archie, no doubt.
But you've gotta turn it around
for yourself.
With dignity.
It's a lot of money. Five grand.
Oh, wow, five grand. That's...
That's what you think you're worth?
I know you're looking for something.
We all are, in this messed-up town.
But selling yourself out
to be somebody's punching bag?
No, you're worth more than that.
[Betty] Kev, I need your help.
- Betty, what is it? What's wrong?
- The Farm is a cult.
My mom is joining a cult,
and no one but me seems
to be worried about it.
- Betty...
- Just listen to me.
The only way to get real dirt on a cult
is to talk to a cult escapee.
So, I started Googling,
and I found all of these articles.
Dozens of stories about people
who have escaped.
The Farm?
I have a list of over 30 names,
all escapees.
- You have to help me call them.
- I can't help with this.
Why? Why not?
After what happened with Moose,
and him leaving town,
Evelyn started talking to me.
She helped me a lot.
She even said she'd introduce me
to some cute gay Farmies.
Kev, please, tell me you're not thinking
about actually joining the Farm.
What if I am?
Don't be so ready
to see the worst in people.
It isn't healthy.
Ghoulies. They're a drug club.
They can't be house-trained.
That's the Gargoyles, Dad.
The Ghoulies just need a strong leader.
Dad, I can be that.
But I'm going to need a carrot
that only you can provide.
It'd be easier
to get the Ghoulies to join us
if I could say we had immunity
from the law now that you're sheriff.
Your mom put you up to this?
Not even in town a week,
and she's making moves.
Coming to you with this ask was my idea.
It's risky,
but if we don't bolster our numbers,
we will go extinct.
As long as I don't have
to sign anything, yeah.
You tell them Sheriff Jones hasn't
forgotten where he's come from.
It'll be live and let live.
Mi amor, have you been in touch
with Governor Dooley lately?
He hasn't been returning my calls.
No, no, not since the quarantine.
I saw that you were putting out
our best bottles of rum.
Are you thinking
of having Donald over for drinks?
[chuckles] Oh, no,
those are for Gladys Jones.
Now that she's back in town,
I thought it may be prudent
for her and me to have a sit-down.
[Veronica] We had a deal.
I deliver payments
and morsels of information,
and you stay the hell away from my family.
Hey, your old man called me for a meeting.
If you breathe one word to him
about me or my mother,
I'll tell your son that you're hoping
to take over the drug trade.
Wow.
You're trying to shake me down. [chuckles]
That is awesome.
Look, I don't care.
Blab to him all you want.
He won't kill me for it.
Which I can't say the same
about what your father will do to his wife
if I spill the beans.
Watch it, Mrs. Jones.
Things could get messy for you.
I'm just taking care of business,
little lady.
And if my meeting with your father
doesn't go my way,
you better say an Ave Maria for Mommy.
Look, I can't do it.
I can't throw the fight. Here.
It's too late, Andrews.
We had an agreement.
You show up, you fight, you lose,
and everyone gets paid.
- I shouldn't have agreed. I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
Andrews, I don't just arrange fights.
I arrange bets on fights.
A lot of dangerous men put down
a lot of money
in anticipation of Ronson beating you.
You don't show up,
then they're gonna come after me.
And I'll send them after you.
And if you decide to try
and go rogue in the ring,
try and win, say,
Ronson will end you, right then and there.
Any deviation
from our agreement whatsoever
will end very, very badly for you.
See you on fight night.
[Jughead] So, you're the last one.
The last Ghoulie standing?
Where's the rest, Verne?
After we lost Malachai, then Penny...
no one knew who to look to, who to follow.
So, most Ghoulies went to the Gargoyles,
started playing G&G.
Now that Tall Boy's dead,
who's their leader?
Closest thing to a leader
is a whack job named Kurtz,
who keeps the game going.
Do you know where he is?
Can you tell me where to go?
[loud rock music playing on speakers]
Are you Kurtz?
I'm here to talk.
One leader to another.
I'm the Serpent King,
and I'm here to make an offer.
You're all wanted for making
and dealing Fizzle Rocks.
But if you
and your Gargoyles join my gang,
I can promise you immunity
from the sheriff's office and the law.
Law.
Immunity.
I have looked into the eyes of the King.
And his...
is the only law.
The law of Gargoyles,
carved in stone.
Right.
So, you wanna play a game?
I'm a game master.
Let me be your game master.
You think Gryphons and Gargoyles...
is a game?
You are mistaken.
You come here as a king,
but you are not a king.
And you think we are playing a game.
But we are living...
a prophecy.
And you are all just sacrifices,
waiting to be made.
The Gargoyle King lives.
He will decide.
And he will choose.
And only the worthy will ascend.
Stick the jab.
Attaboy.
Mr. Keller.
You got a sec?
What do you want, Arch?
You're right.
I thought this fight with Ronson would
help jumpstart something, anything.
But I'm not ready,
definitely not on my own.
And Elio paid me
to throw the fight with Ronson.
He did what?
I have no choice but to fight Ronson.
I'm worried he might kill me.
If I'm gonna stand any chance of survival,
I need you in my corner.
I've seen some tape on Ronson.
He's strong...
but he wasn't in the Army,
or didn't go through the meat grinder
of juvie like you did.
- You'll do what I say, Archie?
- Yes, sir. Everything.
All right. Let's go see what we can do
to make sure you don't get killed.
[Veronica] Excuse me.
Mind if I join you?
Hi, I'm Veronica Lodge.
You look familiar. Have we met before?
I don't believe we have.
You're Jughead's mom, right?
Mija, I was hoping
to have a private conversation.
Aw, what's the big deal? Let her join.
She's so gorgeous.
And you do trust her, don't you?
Yes, I do. I trust her very much.
So, we can speak freely?
Absolutely.
Okay, shall we?
[Gladys] So...
what is the point of this meeting?
Intimidation?
Word on the street is
that you're starting from scratch.
You really wanna go up against me?
[Gladys chuckles]
I'd pose the same question to you.
Here's my offer.
I focus on the candy trade,
you focus on the prison.
You stay out of my way,
and I stay out of yours.
Huh.
That's interesting.
My daughter made the same pitch.
But I'm afraid it isn't an option.
Well,
in that case, Hiram,
there is something you need to know.
Daddy...
I've been thinking.
If you agree to this scenario,
I could get behind that.
Help you.
Just like you've always wanted.
It's what the family needs right now.
Everybody wins.
Okay.
I'll focus on my prison,
you'll run the streets.
But I need a steady stream of prisoners
to make this arrangement worth my while.
I guess your husband... [chuckles]
the sheriff, can help me with that.
Abso-freaking-lutely.
What about Madam Mayor?
Is she going to be a help or a hindrance?
I wouldn't worry about that.
She will not be a factor...
either way.
Hi, I read the interview you gave
to The Buffalo Beat.
Did you happen to be a member of the Farm?
[woman 1] How'd you get this number?
I don't appreciate calls like this.
Yes, I understand. I won't call again.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[woman 2] Yeah, did you call me,
and leave this number?
Yes, yes. Um...
My name is Betty Cooper.
I have some questions for you
about the Farm.
I can't say anything over the phone.
They might be listening.
Will you meet me in person?
It would need to be somewhere private,
away from prying eyes.
I have the perfect spot.
How soon can you be in Riverdale?
[Elio] Glad you decided to show, Archie.
Wise man.
Yeah.
But I'm not taking the fall.
What are you trying to prove?
Go down in Round Three like we decided,
everyone walks out happy and in one piece.
Deal's off.
You heard the man.
Kill him.
How'd it go with the Ghoulies?
They don't exist anymore.
They're part of the Gargoyles now.
Same guys, different masks.
Did you recruit them?
No. I'll find another way
to save the Serpents.
Gargoyles aren't the answer.
I don't want them near us.
They, uh...
They're in so deep into G&G.
It's like they're lost in a jungle.
Take it easy, boy. Get some food in you.
[Betty] Thank you
for meeting me so quickly, Martha.
The Farm had places like this.
Secret places.
Hidey-holes.
When did you leave the Farm?
Six years ago.
My sister Marigold
and I joined at the same time.
I ran away.
I left The Farm right after she died.
I'm so sorry.
- How?
- Happened during one of their ceremonies.
What kind of ceremony?
The Farm believes
that if you can get close enough to death,
you'll see the truth.
They claim that you have
to survive an extreme ordeal
in order to achieve ascension.
What?
What do you mean, "ascension"?
The promise of the Farm.
And the first step towards it
is the baptism.
Baptism?
My sister drowned during hers.
Oh, my God.
I have to go. I'll be in touch.
♪ Out of the ruins ♪
♪ Out from the wreckage ♪
♪ Can't make the same mistakes this time ♪
♪ And I wonder when we... ♪
Remember what I told you.
Ronson's not used to
fighting his way out of the third round.
All right? So, keep moving.
Work the jab, circle away from his power,
stay off the ropes.
He'll gas himself out,
you'll knock him over like a bag of flour.
- [man] Seconds out.
- Attaboy. Let's go.
♪ We don't need another hero ♪
♪ We don't need to know the way home ♪
♪ All we want is life beyond ♪
♪ The Thunderdome ♪
♪ Looking for something ♪
Mom, it's Betty. Please, call me back.
♪ We can rely on ♪
♪ There's gotta be something
Better out there ♪
♪ And I wonder when we ♪
♪ Are ever gonna change, change ♪
♪ Living under the fear ♪
♪ Till nothing else remains ♪
[bell rings]
♪ All the children say
We don't need another hero ♪
How you doing, Red? He knows you're hurt.
He'll try to end it in this round.
We'll use that to your advantage.
You're gonna slip that right hand
and catch him with the uppercut.
♪ The Thunderdome ♪
♪ So what do we do with our lives? ♪
Now get in there, make him pay.
[referee] Let's go, boys.
[Keller] Attaboy.
♪ Will our story shine like a light? ♪
♪ Or end in the dark ♪
Go, Archie.
You got this.
Go, Randy. Come on, Randy.
[Keller] Do it, Archie.
No, no, no. Come on.
Stay on him, Arch.
Attaboy. Don't let up, don't let up.
God.
[bell rings]
♪ We don't need another hero ♪
♪ We don't need to know the way home ♪
You're doing great. This is it.
No matter what happens, you've done great.
All right? If you wanna win this fight,
you're gonna have to knock him out.
You gotta go for the KO.
I can do it. He's getting tired.
Okay. You got three minutes.
Choose your point, put him on the canvas.
All right, let's go.
♪ Beyond the Thunderdome ♪
[cheering]
[Keller] Attaboy, Archie.
Go on, go after him.
Go after him.
Do it, Archie.
Do it.
Do it. Stay on him. Stay on him.
- [bell rings]
- Attaboy.
[crowd cheering]
[Keller laughing]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have a split decision.
Judge Williams scores eight to seven,
Ronson.
[crowd cheering]
Judge Anderson scores nine to six,
Andrews.
[crowd cheering]
And Judge Paterson scores eight to seven
for your winner
and still undefeated welterweight,
Randy Van Ronson.
[crowd cheering]
Keep your head up, Arch.
You won that fight. No doubt.
[Evelyn] Happy day, friends.
We are gathered here tonight
to celebrate the baptizing...
of Alice Smith.
Now, this is a day of rebirth, of course.
And as such, it is important to remember
that birth is no easy feat.
It is a trauma
to leave the comfort of our wombs.
We push, tear, and spring forth,
crying and gasping for air, for life.
Today, Alice Smith, you will rip off
the weight you have carried,
you will break
through the barriers restraining you,
and you will emerge
into the light of your destiny.
Are you ready?
I am.
Then may the one become many.
[all] And the many, one.
Stop! Stop.
Get off of her.
Help me.
[whimpering] She's not breathing.
Polly, she's...
Oh, my God.
Somebody call an ambulance, please.
[coughing]
Mom, you're okay.
- [gasping]
- You're okay. You're okay.
[Alice] Betty.
[Betty] It's okay.
[Josie chuckles]
Ugh, well, so much
for not messing up your pretty face.
Yeah.
How was your show?
Oh, I killed it.
[Josie chuckles]
Like you did here.
I guess you decided
not to throw the fight.
Oh, well, it's a win in my book.
Do you wanna maybe
go get a milkshake at Pop's?
To celebrate?
Unless you have a better idea.
♪ Hey, baby ♪
♪ What you doing to me? ♪
♪ Your love is bewitching ♪
♪ I'm caught up in your games ♪
♪ One look in your eyes ♪
♪ Got me hypnotized ♪
♪ Hey, baby ♪
The governor finally returned
my phone calls.
And we had
the most fascinating conversation.
What did Donald say?
It's funny.
He informed me
that you made a contribution to him...
not a day after I was shot.
Around the same time
that you were getting rid
of my business holdings.
Anything you'd like to share, mi vida?
- Daddy...
- Stop.
- Hiram...
- It was me.
I burned your drugs and equipment.
Mom was covering for me
with that story about the feds.
And I'm not going to apologize for it.
I did it for us.
For all of us.
Well...
you owe me $75,000, Veronica.
That's how much you burned away.
Fine.
I can live with that.
Gargoyles. Jellybean.
It's okay, kids. Stand down.
The hell is this? Are they here with you?
I did what you couldn't.
Ugh, take off those stupid masks.
This is a bad idea.
Sweetheart, sometimes,
beggars can't be choosers.
I know you guys will find a way
to work together.
We need all the manpower we can get
to take this town back.
Trust me.
God, she's not answering.
- Who isn't?
- This woman who escaped from the Farm.
I wanted her to tell you what she told me,
which is that they're dangerous, Mom.
I don't know what you remember, Mom.
But Polly held you underwater.
They didn't let you come up.
They tried to kill you, Mom.
No, Betty.
I was reborn.
I saw it all.
My purpose.
My destiny.
Just like the Farm promised.
Just like Edgar said.
Mom, no.
Now that I've been baptized,
I can finally purge the last thing
in my life that's been holding me back.
Which is what?
This house.
I'm gonna sell this house.
We're gonna all be together.
You...
me...
Polly, the twins...
Edgar, Evelyn, the Farm.
All one.
Together...
forever and ever.