[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
How did Hiram Lodge pin
Cassidy Bullock's murder on me?
[Norton] He paid Mr. Bullock's friends
to say that they saw you pull the trigger.
It's my understanding
that they're in hiding.
I'd hide in the mines by Shadow Lake.
The warden said if I
did this, I'd ascend.
[Jughead]
You're breaking Archie out of juvie?
[Veronica] We'll need a distraction
to disorient the guards
- and hide Archie's play for the grate.
- [Norton] Find him!
Right now!
Joaquin? Where are you going?
Back to the Serpents?
- No, I joined a different gang.
- Game Master.
- Where is the Red Paladin?
- The Red Paladin?
[Veronica]
Everyone in this room is part of a pact.
No one knows of Archie's whereabouts,
capisce?
[Archie] Does Hiram Lodge own you, too?
[Norton] My soul belongs
to no mere mortal.
He's watching us. He's always watching.
[Betty] Oh, Archie.
What does it mean?
How are we gonna get out of this mess?
[Jughead] Betty.
I saw him.
The Gargoyle King.
Jug. What the hell? Just now?
Yeah. As I was walking home.
I followed him into a clearing.
Betty, there were others.
There's like ten of them.
They looked like his disciples.
Like they were worshiping the king.
- Oh, my God.
- They had on these masks.
Like they were a gang.
A gang of gargoyles.
- Let's go after them.
- No. We shouldn't push our luck.
- Not until we know more.
- Who could they be?
[Archie] Joaquin.
Joaquin told Kevin about a new gang.
And then Joaquin ran into the woods.
We know Warden Norton
is playing G&G.
And Joaquin was doing his dirty work.
Another piece of damning evidence that
Warden Norton could be our Gargoyle King.
[Betty sighs]
[police sirens wailing]
Where have you been, young lady?
There's a manhunt
for Archie Andrews underway.
Police with guns and dogs,
all over the streets of Riverdale.
- Did you have something to do with this?
- No, Mom.
We didn't hear
about his escape until this morning.
The warden from that juvie
killed himself last night.
What?
How come?
RIVW is reporting
that he was found with blue lips.
So, he was playing G&G.
Mom, did you know Warden Norton?
Why would you even ask that?
Because he had ties
to Hiram Lodge,
who played G&G
with you 25 years ago.
Sure you don't remember him?
Yes, I am sure, Elizabeth.
I've told you everything that I know.
I missed this.
I missed you, Archie.
[chuckles]
Ronnie.
[grunts]
I may know where the
Shadow Lake boys are.
The warden thought they were camping
in the abandoned mines.
I need to get there.
No, Archie, I don't
think you understand.
Outside this bunker,
there is a manhunt going on.
Roadblocks, checkpoints, wanted posters,
with your strong jawline all over town.
I need to find
those witnesses.
Warden said all three
guys were paid off.
They're the only ones
who can clear my name.
So I can stop running.
Paid off by my father, no doubt.
[sighs]
Archie.
This is a long shot, but...
when Betty was working with
Attorney McCoy and your mom,
that was at your house?
Yeah.
Are the case files still there?
Yeah, but they've been through them all.
And, Ronnie,
my dad can't know where I am.
Or that you saw me.
I don't want him wrapped up in this.
- I feel bad enough you're involved.
- Hey.
This was the only way
to get you out of that mess.
Ronnie, I took that plea deal...
because I was tired of putting my friends
and my family through hell.
All the people who have helped you...
are doing it because we love you.
So, I need you to trust me
to handle this.
And stay put.
[Minetta] Archie is a murderer.
And we know he didn't escape alone.
He had help.
Hiding a convict
or withholding information from the law
is a felony offense.
So, whoever's aided
and abetted Archie Andrews
is just as much of a criminal as he is.
I was busy all day, sheriff.
You can check my browser history,
if you know what I mean.
[classmates chuckling]
I don't know this Archie person.
And on Mondays,
I host a group for teen Farmies.
We are still accepting members.
Where were you, Ms. McCoy,
at the time of the breakout?
Don't look at me, sir. I, uh...
I...
I was in the music room.
- Practicing.
- Alone?
I'll look into all of your alibis.
And if I find out later
that someone in here was involved,
well, you can say
goodbye to this school,
your hopes and dreams.
Your music, your entire future.
All of it goes away, just like that.
Again, to be clear,
if you know anything,
now's the time
to tell me...
Sheriff Minetta, back off!
- [boy 1] What just happened?
- [boy 2] Is she okay?
[Jughead] Another seizure?
As if things weren't crazy enough.
I know. First me, then
Ethel, then Josie?
What's the connection there?
Speaking of connections,
with Warden Norton dead,
there goes our theory
of him as the Gargoyle King.
Maybe not.
Look.
There's the connection between
our parents and Warden Norton.
Warden Norton was the RROTC instructor
of Riverdale High?
Yeah, the same year
our parents started the Midnight Club.
This proves once more
that our parents continue
to hide things from us.
And it all started
with the Midnight Club, Jug.
Featherhead was
the first blue-lipped death on record.
Somehow I need to get our parents
to talk to us.
Force them into telling us the truth.
- Even if that backs them into a corner.
- What'd you have in mind?
Depends whether or not
I can borrow Veronica's speakeasy.
Okay, while you're working on that,
I'm going to rally the Serpents.
We have to find Joaquin.
As Norton's accomplice,
he's our best shot to figure out
what was going on inside Norton's mind.
Bye.
[Sweet Pea] Minetta's trashing tent city,
Jug, looking for Archie.
I propose a manhunt of our own.
Every Serpent searching for Joaquin.
No stone left unturned.
Serpents don't just shiv other Serpents.
What got into him?
According to Archie,
Joaquin did it for Warden Norton.
The warden confronted Betty,
called Archie the Red Paladin.
Plus the warden poisoned himself
with cyanide and blueberry Fresh-Aid.
And he worked for Riverdale High
before the detention center.
The question is, was he playing G&G
with someone or for someone?
And since he's dead,
Joaquin's the only one who can know.
But Joaquin may not be alone.
Kevin said he's rolling with a new gang.
- Those gargoyle creeps you saw?
- Exactly.
And if the gang is working for the King,
then they're gonna take us right to him.
Archie, you haven't eaten your burger.
To be honest,
I'm not feeling so hot right now, Kev.
[grunts]
Let me see your, uh, bandage.
Okay.
That is definitely infected.
- Great.
- No worries, Arch.
Betty's got a connection.
She'll know what to do.
[Betty] It's okay, Kevin. He's a doctor.
We can trust him.
Oh, and bring small bills.
Elizabeth.
Don't tell me this is your doing.
I sent the invitations
from the Gargoyle King.
- What?
- And look, you all came.
What are you up to?
All of the secrets end now, Mom.
And this was the only way
to get all of you together.
Someone in this room is a murderer.
[Hermione] Alice, we promised each other
we would never talk about this.
- I mean, who else did you tell?
- I told Betty to protect her,
- so she wouldn't play the game.
- And it worked. I'm not playing the game.
But many of your kids are.
This is about protecting them.
- Don't you care?
- [Sierra] Care?
Josie had a seizure this morning.
I should be with her right now.
Not here, rehashing the past,
when it has zero relevance.
Attorney McCoy, it is relevant.
Your daughter is playing the game,
along with Kevin and Cheryl.
Even your son Reggie, Mr. Mantle,
no matter
how many black eyes you give him.
I would never hit my son.
Another lie.
Guys, it was bound to get out sometime.
Our children need to know the truth.
Betty, where do we start?
With the dead warden
from Archie's juvie.
He was also the RROTC instructor
when you guys were in high school.
Mr. Keller, you were a cadet then.
Did you play the game with him?
Major Norton just confiscated
a stray manual. That's all.
Mr. Lodge, you had business dealings
with Warden Norton until he died.
What were they? And did you know
that he was playing G&G?
None of your business, and not a clue.
What about Ascension Night?
Was he there?
How can we answer that?
We were all high off our gourds,
hallucinating gargoyles.
Wait, FP. You saw it, too?
Oh, this is such a waste of our time.
I have a job that I need to get back to.
So, if you'll excuse me...
No, Hiram.
Let's just get this over with.
Otherwise, it will never end.
Betty, you wanna know
who poisoned the chalice.
The Game Master is the one
who sets up the game.
So, my instinct is telling me that...
the culprit was Penelope Blossom.
My guess is maybe she grew the poison
in her greenhouse.
You don't grow cyanide, Hermione.
A fact that only a Blossom would know.
[sighs]
It was Daryl Doiley.
We were both Game Masters.
And he was secretly in love with me.
He put poison in the chalice,
because he wanted us to ascend together.
But I said no.
I assumed...
the chalices were emptied afterwards,
but they were not.
Years later, Daryl came to me,
riddled with guilt
over that tragic incident,
and seeking comfort.
And I refused him again.
We were both married
with families, and...
I was afraid, you see,
of revisiting that unholy night.
So, he left. The next day...
he was found dead in his garage.
Sitting in his sedan,
engine running, windows up.
[sighs]
Dilton Doiley's dead dad did it?
That explains how Dilton got his hands
on the game,
and why he started playing.
No, but that doesn't explain
who the Gargoyle King is today.
- Jughead and I saw him.
- What do you mean?
In Fox Forest. We've tried to
track him down ever since.
Why do you think Jughead
started playing?
- He's not still playing, is he?
- I'm afraid so, Mr. Jones.
He's made some really weird connections
between the game and Riverdale,
- which he wouldn't have...
- I've heard enough.
Boy's gonna be the death of me.
Satisfied, Elizabeth?
No, Mom.
Not even close.
[cell phone buzzing]
Fangs. Did you find Joaquin?
[Fangs] Centerville Serpents spotted him
at the Last Resort Youth Hostel.
- We're on our way.
- Grab him.
Take him to Fox Forest,
near the footbridge.
- I'll meet you there.
- On it, boss man.
- [FP] Going somewhere, boy?
- To meet the Serpents.
Yeah? Like hell you are.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
What I should have done,
the second I saw you playing.
You're addicted. G&G's like a drug.
It got into your blood.
I'm not addicted.
I just need to ascend,
so I can find the Gargoyle King,
and put an end to all this.
You're right.
You sound nothing like an addict.
My mistake.
It's time for you to sober up, boy.
For your own good.
[Archie grunts]
[Curdle Jr.] Keep it clean and dry.
As for the infection,
I have some antibiotics
in the back room.
That is,
if you have something for me.
Thank you, Dr. Curdle Junior.
Betty said to pay you in small bills.
- We should get back to the bunker.
- I can't go back there.
I'm going to Shadow Lake, to the mines,
to find the guys responsible
for putting me away.
How far do you think you're gonna get,
on foot and alone?
Will you help me, Kev?
Veronica is going to kill me.
[Minetta on video] Okay, Donny.
Let's try this one more time.
Come on. I don't have all day.
What the hell?
[rewinding]
Oh, my God. It's been edited.
Veronica?
Are those Archie's case files?
He's not going to be
behind bars ever again, Daddy.
That's a promise.
There are too many variables
up at Shadow Lake.
Take care of them. All of them.
[Betty knocking on door] Jug?
- Are you...?
- [Jughead] Betty.
- Are you hungry?
- Jug. What the hell?
You don't have a trusty
bobby pin, do you?
Always.
Did your dad do this?
Yeah. He doesn't
like me playing G&G.
That's my fault.
I'm sorry.
It came out when I talked
to all of our parents.
How'd that sit-down go, Miss Marple?
Penelope Blossom said Daryl Doiley
is the one who poisoned the chalices.
[groans]
Dilton's dad?
- Isn't he...?
- Dead? Yeah.
Pretty convenient, right?
The one man who can't confirm
or deny Penelope's story.
- I don't buy that.
- Neither do I, Jug.
I called Dr. Curdle Junior and asked
if he'd pull Mr. Doiley's autopsy report.
Think you can handle this yourself?
Sweet Pea and Fangs
maybe found Joaquin.
Just be careful, Jug.
I know we're getting close
to something, Betty.
[cell phone ringing]
[Kevin sighs]
Hey, Veronica. What's up?
Seriously, Kevin? You had one job to do.
Put Archie on right the hell now.
Don't blame Kev. It was all me.
If you tell me you're going
to Shadow Mines...
I am. It's my one
shot to clear my name.
But it's not.
I found something.
Ten minutes of Minetta's interrogation
of the Shadow Lake boys was deleted.
I just have to find the missing footage.
- Wouldn't it have been destroyed?
- No.
My dad hangs on to dirt in case
he needs to lord it over someone.
Think it's in his study?
Something as radioactive as this?
He'd keep it far away from himself.
Closer to, let's say,
the Mayor's Office.
It's worth a look,
but it won't change my plans.
Fine.
Tell Kevin if he doesn't
get you back to me in one piece,
I will eviscerate him.
So, what's the plan?
I mean, what if these guys are armed?
And you're a sneeze away
from tearing those stitches.
Kevin, I'm fine.
Shh.
[man] Tango-ten-Charlie...
[Veronica] Always my birthday.
[chuckles]
Holy crap. Please, be it.
[Minetta] Okay, Donny.
Let's try this one more time.
Ten thousand apiece.
You just say that you saw Archie Andrews
kill your friend Cassidy Bullock.
If that's not proof of coercion,
I don't know what is.
Come on, Internet.
Come on.
- [knocking on door]
- [Gloria] She's in here.
[knocking continues]
- Come on.
- Hello?
I'm the mayor's daughter. I can be here.
False. Her mother and father told me
to call the Sheriff's Department
if she broke in again.
Okay. That's not necessary.
[Sweet Pea] Get up.
Get up!
[Joaquin grunting] Look
what we found on him.
So, you jumped ship for
the gargoyle gang?
You have a lot of explaining to do.
[grunts then coughs]
Why not start with why
you shivved Archie,
instead of protecting him,
like you were supposed to?
The warden said I had no other choice.
You don't know what it's like there.
You do anything to survive.
For me, it was being the warden's pawn.
A chess piece.
- In some ways, he was a pawn, too.
- What does that mean?
I saw him with these game cards
that told him what to do.
Whoever sent them wanted Archie dead.
From the moment he was locked up,
he was already marked.
[Jughead] Marked with what?
This symbol...
the warden branded on Archie's hip?
What does it mean?
No, no.
- Pick him up.
- No, no, no.
Just... Hey, just... Just stop.
Just stop.
Okay.
Sacrifice.
It means that...
It meant that Archie had to die.
Look, I'm sorry, Jug.
I know he was your pal. I...
Oh, Archie's alive.
He won't be for much longer.
Who's giving Warden Norton his orders?
- No.
- Okay.
- I don't think you understand.
- No.
I can't let you go until you talk.
I saw them meet once.
But you know him, Jones.
The man in the black suit.
[Jughead] An ancient evil long
forgotten has awoken.
The embodiment of pure
malice and cruelty.
It finally happened.
You've lost your mind.
You met Warden Norton in high school.
All this time,
you've sent him quest cards,
instructing him how to torture
and then kill Archie.
You're not just the criminal kingpin
of Riverdale. You're the Gargoyle King.
- What did you call me?
- The Gargoyle King.
The Ghoulies and this new gang
of gargoyles are your soldiers.
The Southside is your kingdom.
You orchestrated Archie's arrest to put
him under Norton's sadistic thumb.
The game is how
you've been communicating with him,
pulling the strings.
Back in the day,
you killed Principal Featherhead
in the same way you tried to kill me,
and in the same way you tried
to kill Archie.
You're the Gargoyle King, Hiram.
I am not a 16-year-old
nerd playing games
to live out
my overactive hormonal fantasies.
I'm not the Gargoyle King.
Because you know what?
That's not a real thing.
Nor am I the murderer that you
and Betty Cooper are looking for.
But if homicidal parents
are what you're after,
may I suggest Clifford Blossom...
Hal Cooper, Tom Keller.
And perhaps...
even your own father.
They all make solid suspects.
[phone ringing]
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to take this.
You'll see yourself out, won't you?
[sighs] This is Lodge.
She did what?
What exactly were you hoping to find
in your mother's office, Veronica?
Does Mom even know
what you've been hiding on her desktop?
She doesn't have a
computer anymore.
I've requested to
speak to a lawyer.
It's my right as an American citizen.
So, get your lapdog, Sheriff Minetta,
to bring me to the phone.
Minetta. Hmm.
He's otherwise engaged.
But let me see what I can do.
[Fred] Yeah, Veronica,
is everything okay?
Have you heard from Archie?
He asked me not to tell you,
Mr. Andrews, but...
Archie's headed for the mines
by Shadow Lake with Kevin
to look for the guys
who testified against him.
My intuition tells me
Sheriff Minetta may be doing the same.
- Okay. Uh, I'm on the way.
- Wait.
Tell Archie
I found what I was looking for.
I just have to get it to the judge.
- Veronica, I...
- And on that note,
would you mind
calling Attorney McCoy for me?
[Betty] I'm confused.
Why is there no mention
of carbon monoxide in Mr. Doiley's file?
Because it was not
the cause of death, Ms. Cooper.
Daryl Doiley was indeed found
in a running car with the windows up,
but there was no trace
of carbon monoxide in his lungs.
That can only mean he
was dead beforehand.
Then how did he die, Dr. Curdle Junior?
Oleander.
If ingested, it's one of the most
poisonous plants known to mankind.
In my opinion, Ms. Cooper,
Daryl Doiley's death was a murder,
disguised as a suicide.
Can that be proven with this file?
Unfortunately, no.
This is from my father's
personal collection.
Fine. Then I'll just have
to question whoever closed the case.
Doctor...
who was the sheriff
at the time of Mr. Doiley's death?
Thank you for meeting me, Mr. Keller.
Sure.
Mr. Doiley's death was classified
as suicide by carbon monoxide poisoning,
by your department.
Yet oddly enough there wasn't
a trace of it found in his lungs.
What is this, Betty?
Is this another ambush?
Because I didn't kill anybody.
Maybe not,
but you're complicit in a cover-up.
Who were you protecting?
All of us.
Your mother included.
Someone murdered Daryl Doiley.
Whoever was pulling the strings back then
may be the one killing people today.
The truth is it could've
been any member of the Midnight Club.
But only one of us grows oleander
in their greenhouse.
Now, I know this because I saw it
when I was investigating
Jason Blossom's murder.
- Uh, wait, Mr. Keller, can...?
- [cell phone buzzing]
Yeah, Fred. What?
Son of a gun. All right, all right.
I'll be right there.
- Mr. Keller...
- I gotta go.
Come on.
Let's keep going.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, no. It's the Shadow Lake crew.
[Kevin] And Sheriff
Minetta was just here.
Hey, hey.
He's still alive.
We gotta get him to a hospital.
- Archie...
- Minetta shot them because of me.
I can't have any more blood on my hands.
Now grab his legs.
[Sweet Pea] Someone's sending us
a message, Jones.
- What's the message?
- Come on.
Joaquin.
Who do you think did it?
Uh...
I don't know.
The Gargoyle Gang, or Hiram Lodge.
It could be anyone.
That symbol on his forehead.
Sacrifice.
I have to get to Archie.
[motorcycle revving]
We're too late.
Well, for all we know, Archie and
Kevin never made it here, Fred.
Yeah, this is Tom Keller.
I'd like to report a multiple 187.
Two young men, Shadow Lake Mine.
Gunshots.
Police were called
to Shadow Lake Hospital.
A boy was brought in.
Critical condition with gunshot wounds.
- Is it Kevin or Archie?
- They can't tell me.
No ID. Come on. We should go.
I just heard from the nurse.
He didn't make it, Archie.
They said he lost too much blood.
I'm sorry, man. Everywhere I go...
everything I do just
leads to more death.
More pain.
Those guys would still be alive
if I wasn't in the picture.
Let me remind you, those
guys weren't innocent. Okay?
They were... They
were criminals.
They didn't deserve to die for it.
Hiram Lodge has done everything
in his power to destroy me.
And he won't stop until I'm dead, too.
Even if by some... Some miracle,
my innocence is proven...
I don't think I can
go back to Riverdale.
Attorney McCoy,
thank you for posting my bail.
How's Josie doing?
She's resting.
And what about you, Veronica?
You tell me.
If one has concrete proof of coercion
and tampering of evidence,
would it be enough
to free the wrongfully accused?
[Betty] Mrs. Blossom.
Please, Betty. Call me Aunty.
Aunty Blossom...
Mr. Doiley died from oleander poisoning.
Do you have that flower
in your greenhouse?
Even if I wanted to
poison Daryl Doiley...
I wouldn't use oleander.
It leaves traces.
You know, Betty, I came here to help you,
out of the kindness of my heart.
But if you're looking for someone
to accuse,
it was your own mother
who wrote the article
reporting Daryl's suicide.
So, maybe you should ask yourself,
and her,
what reasons she had
for covering up a murder.
Well, do you have anything
to say for yourself, Mom?
[sighs] You have shaken every tree today.
I'm sure there's nothing left to say.
How about that you helped
cover up Daryl Doiley's murder?
Oh, Betty. When will you stop?
When you stop lying to me, Mom.
Mr. Doiley didn't die
from carbon monoxide inhalation,
like you wrote in this article.
Someone staged it to
look like a suicide.
Someone afraid
of what Mr. Doiley might say.
Thanks to Sheriff Keller,
there was no murder investigation.
You all have a hand in this.
You're all just circling the wagons,
playing a part.
Why, Mom?
Who are you protecting?
[thunder rumbling]
- Mom?
- Stay here.
- I'll check the circuit breaker.
- No, I'm coming.
[banging on door]
Who is it? Who's there?
Mom. Hello?
Betty, call 911.
Oh, my God.
They were in here.
Get behind me, Betty.
Come on.
Whoa, whoa. I was looking for Jughead,
but someone slammed the door in my face.
- I was trying to get in.
- FP, the Gargoyle King is in the house.
He's in the house.
Shh.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
- A boy was brought here. He was shot.
- [Kevin] Dad?
[Keller] Hey.
- You all right?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Um, where's Archie? Is...?
He's okay, Mr. Andrews, but he's gone.
He, uh... He left you something. A note.
Someone let you out of your cage, I see.
What do you mean, Hiram?
You didn't know, Mom?
Your husband left me in a jail cell,
for putting my nose
where it didn't belong.
But it was so worth it.
- What are you talking about?
- Archie, of course.
I found the deleted tape
of Sheriff Minetta coercing witnesses.
Attorney McCoy's meeting with the judge
to overturn Archie's conviction.
Your henchman, Minetta...
[chuckles]
is going down.
And if you two evildoers
go down with him,
so be it.
[Alice] We're no longer safe, Betty.
And that attack was only the beginning.
It's clear that you won't
drop this investigation,
no matter the consequences.
And this house is no longer safe.
Which is why...
I'm going to the Farm,
with Polly and the twins.
Well, have fun.
Because I'm definitely not going
to the Farm.
No. You're not.
[door opens]
Edgar said that you would resist.
- And that we should send you elsewhere.
- Mom, what's...? What's happening?
Betty, there's no safer
place for you now.
The Sisters protected me.
They protected Polly.
They'll watch over you. No. Mom.
Mom.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you doing this?
Because I love you, Elizabeth.
Hey. Mom.
Let me go. Mom.
[cell phone ringing]
What do you mean, "he's gone," Kevin?
Believe me, I tried.
Archie said he couldn't come back.
Only because he doesn't know
he's been exonerated.
- And you let him go alone?
- Not... Not alone.
He called...
[cell phone ringing]
- Archie?
- [sighs]
Veronica.
I am so glad you called, Archie.
We did it. Attorney McCoy worked it out
with the judge.
You're a free man.
I shouldn't be surprised.
You're amazing.
I promised you'd be
free by homecoming.
Veronica Lodge
keeps her word.
Thank you, Veronica.
For everything you've done for me.
No need to thank me, lover.
Just tell me where to pick you up.
Ronnie, I...
I can't come home.
Didn't you hear me?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Sheriff Minetta's going to prison
for a long, long time.
But your dad is still out there.
And I can't escape him.
As long as we're together,
he'll hunt me down.
Everyone close to me is his target.
That includes you.
Where are you?
I'm not letting you go off,
God knows where, and alone.
I'm not alone.
Ronnie, when I first met you...
you were it for me.
Everything I could've ever wanted.
I saw our whole future.
Because we're endgame, Archie.
I hope you know how much I love you.
[sobbing]
If you loved me, you would come home.
You know in your heart
I'm right about this.
It just hurts to admit it.
Don't make me say goodbye to you,
Archie Andrews.
Because I don't wanna hear it back.
I can't.
I can't. I...
[crying]
Goodbye, Veronica.
Some money.
A change of clothes.
Granola bars, juice boxes.
Thanks for coming out here, Jug.
Sure you wanna do this, man?
Leaving is my best option, Jug.
It's my only option. I don't disagree.
Joaquin is dead.
That symbol you have branded on your hip,
he had one on his forehead.
It means "sacrifice."
What?
- Who the hell is doing this?
- I don't know.
I have a feeling
Hiram Lodge is a part of it.
He always is.
Don't worry.
I won't let you out of my sight.
["The Ballad of Paladin" playing]
You ever hop a train before?
No.
♪ Paladin ♪
We'll figure it out.
♪ Paladin, Paladin, where do you roam? ♪
♪ Paladin, Paladin, far, far from home ♪
I know you've looked down on our
practices in the past, Ms. Cooper.
But I want to assure you
that we're going to make you well.
You're safe
with the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.