[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
Dilton Doiley and Ben Button were found
in the woods with blue lips.
We made a pact
to never revisit that night.
- Gryphons and Gargoyles.
- Wonder if Ethel was playing with them.
If any of us talk to any grownups,
he's gonna get very, very angry,
Who? The Gargoyle King?
[snarling]
- She's having a seizure.
- Ethel. Help is coming, okay?
We both flipped the coin.
He was scared to ascend.
But I'm not. Soon you'll fly, too.
- [Jughead] Ben, no! Ben!
- [Betty] Ben!
I'm Evelyn. You're Betty Cooper?
Your mom and your sister
study with my dad.
- From the Farm?
- Yeah, that's right.
Edgar Evernever.
I won't tell anyone
about the other night.
Oh, my God. Betty.
Stop the riot.
[Norton] You impressed me today.
You've been tapped.
You're gonna be my new Mad Dog.
[door opens]
[footsteps approaching]
Well?
Had time to think?
The answer is still no.
Then I'll see you in another week.
This feels right, doesn't it?
I'm glad the Farm, uh, opened you up
to the possibility of us.
[chuckles]
What are you thinking about, Alice?
It's been three weeks.
No more suicides, no more blue lips.
As far as the town's concerned,
it was just two boys
taking their own lives
for whatever reason.
Hopefully it ends there.
With Jughead and Betty on the case?
You know that's not likely.
Betty, what are you thinking about?
Do you think it's sort of...
ghoulish for us to be crashing
Dilton's bunker like this?
This bunker is the only place in town
we can get a modicum of privacy.
- My dad's watching me like a hawk.
- Same with my mom.
Ben's death haunts me, Jug.
He didn't scream.
Why not, I wonder.
Because that's one of the rules
of Gryphons and Gargoyles?
Betty, that's what we're missing.
There's no rulebook, no player's manual.
What if that's the key to all this?
Ethel, Ben, and Dilton talk about it
like a religion.
Yeah, or a cult.
And every cult has its king.
Sorry I kept you waiting, Mr. Andrews.
How can I help you? My son.
I wanna see him.
Today.
Your son is quite a firebrand.
He started a riot.
I'm afraid
his visitation privileges are suspended.
I was told by witnesses
that your guards started that riot.
That's a very serious accusation,
Mr. Andrews.
It's been three weeks.
I will decide when it is appropriate
for him to receive visitors again.
Was there anything else?
Yeah.
You'll be hearing from my lawyer.
[Veronica] I'm in trouble here, Bee.
I'm up to my eyebrows in bills.
Pop's is hemorrhaging money.
Well, how far along is the speakeasy?
Is it close, at least?
Vee, what?
What is it?
The speakeasy's ready.
- It has been for a while.
- What? Why haven't you opened it?
I've been waiting for Archie.
I just...
I wanted him to be there,
dancing with me on opening night.
A part of it all.
This is exactly what Archie didn't want.
For you to just put your life on hold.
You need to focus on yourself
for a change.
I'm saying this to you as your friend.
Open the damn speakeasy.
Veronica says
she'll have a pretty strict dress code
at her speakeasy.
Of course we're
calling it a speakeasy.
And, uh, what are you getting at?
Hey, Ethel's back.
Yeah, she's talking
to that weirdo girl from the Farm.
Oh, my God.
What if the game is
connected to the Farm?
Ben, Dilton, and Ethel
started playing the game this summer,
which is when the Farm
and the Evernevers moved to Riverdale.
Evelyn's dad, Edgar, is their leader.
My mom won't stop talking about him.
- He's like a kind of...
- King?
What do you know about
him and the Farm?
Basically nothing.
- Should we start with Evelyn or Ethel?
- Ethel.
Evelyn... creeps me out.
Last time we talked to Ethel,
she had a seizure.
We'll be more gentle this time.
[Josie] Hi, Pop.
Looking for Veronica? This way.
Pick up the phone, dial 642.
[phone line dialing] -[Reggie] Password.
- I don't know.
Stonewall.
[Reggie] Close enough. Whoa.
[Josie chuckles]
- Come on in.
- [Josie] Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
I died and went to
Kander and Ebb heaven.
Veronica.
Welcome to La Bonne Nuit.
I hired some Serpents from the Whyte
Wyrm to serve drinks. Mocktails only.
La Bonne Nuit is not in the business
of corrupting minors.
Not yet.
Josie.
I need star power.
I would love for you
to be my resident chanteuse.
Are you for real?
Mm-hm.
I have been working like whoa
to find my sound now that I'm solo,
and I haven't had
anywhere to test it out.
Ooh, this is the perfect opportunity.
And, Kevin,
I'd love for you to be our emcee.
So long as I can sing now and then.
But of course.
Or as we like to say at La Bonne Nuit,
mais oui.
[phone rings]
Hey, Pop. What's up?
[Veronica] Penny Peabody.
I don't believe we've had the pleasure.
Now, what the hell do you want?
[chuckles] No, no, no.
It's not what I want.
It's what you want.
Protection.
The Ghoulies are offering
their services...
for a modest price.
Let me guess.
Protection from you, right?
[Penny] It's a nice place you got here.
And... as above, so below, I'm guessing.
Maybe even nicer down there
in the speakeasy?
I'd hate for something bad
to happen to it.
Food for thought.
I'll let you chew on it.
Up and at 'em. We're going for a ride.
[boys grunting]
Welcome to the Pit.
Joaquin.
When you refused my offer,
I tapped a replacement.
I knew you were friends
with Mr. DeSantos.
As you can see, he's nearly reached
the end of his... usefulness.
Only you, Mr. Andrews,
can decide how he ends it.
Back in his cell, safe and sound.
Or in the infirmary on life support.
I'll do it. I'll take his place.
[crowd cheering]
[security alarm buzzes]
Andrews, meet the rest of the team.
The name's Baby Teeth.
May not look like much,
but I leave a mark.
That's Thumper,
and Peter. Archie.
You better start hitting this bag,
before the captain comes over.
Rules of the fight:
Bare knuckles till knockout.
Warden sells the tickets.
Guards place bets.
Everyone profits.
Except us.
Get perks if we win.
What happened to Mad Dog?
Quit the chatter.
Best you don't ask many questions.
Just the ladies I was looking for.
President Blossom, First Lady Topaz.
I need help spreading the good word
about my speakeasy.
Go on.
In exchange for
promoting La Bonne Nuit,
I'm offering you no cover
and free drinks all night. Mm-hm.
[Cheryl] Well, well, well.
Heavy card stock, and valet parking.
You don't take the
subway to the Met Gala.
Hand them out at your discretion.
And Sweet Pea and Fangs
should be in attendance.
Hmm.
Ethel. Hi.
Are you eating alone?
Do you mind if we...?
The doctors put me on medication.
To stop the seizures.
I was having them multiple times a day.
It's very strong.
Look, if Betty and I did something
to trigger your seizures, we're sorry.
We were trying to help.
Like you tried to help my boyfriend,
Ben, when he threw himself out a window?
Ethel...
when you collapsed,
did you have any visions?
I honestly don't remember.
Okay.
Well, how long have you been friends
with Evelyn Evernever?
Evelyn's the best.
She visited me in the hospital,
is helping me get better,
- so I can titrate down my meds.
- Was that her idea or her dad's?
Wait, have you met Mr. Evernever?
If you're so curious,
check out Evelyn's peer support group.
Weatherbee gave her permission
to start a student chapter
of the Farm here.
[school bell ringing]
Ethel?
Before Ben...
Uh...
He mentioned reuniting with Dilton
in the Kingdom.
You know what that means?
Two people died,
playing Gryphons and Gargoyles.
G&amp;G.
We have no idea why.
This is a crazy question.
Do you have a rulebook
or a player's manual?
You mean the scripture?
Yes. That.
Do you own a copy?
I can't just tell you that, obviously.
Please? Princess Etheline.
Don't call me that.
You haven't earned that privilege.
You're not worthy of
the King's scripture.
Yes, but I wanna be.
I wanna be worthy.
Could you please show me how?
Meet me tomorrow night
at Dilton's bunker.
But... just you.
Sorry, Betty, but you'll never be
worthy, no matter how hard you try.
Well...
looks like you're on Ethel Muggs detail.
And I...
am in need of some serious peer support.
These were upstairs for you.
Hopefully it's the last
of the deliveries.
Excellent. Thank you, Reginald.
[Reggie sighs]
Wait. What the hell?
Dude... this is a serious stash
of jingle-jangle.
Yes, but it's not mine.
I don't know how...
[phone ringing]
Hey, Pop. What's up?
Sheriff Minetta's upstairs?
We have been set up.
I can't get caught with this.
Mom would kill me.
Um, tell him I'll be right up.
I'll stall, but get rid of it. Now.
Sheriff Minetta.
What can I do
for Riverdale's finest today?
- I'm here to do an inspection.
- We've had all our inspections.
Except mine. Do you
wanna show me around?
What's up, sheriff?
Looking for something in particular?
[Minetta sighs]
Anything illegal.
Also...
I'm collecting donations.
Donations?
That's right.
For Riverdale's
underfunded Sheriff's Department.
Mm.
I see.
This isn't a shakedown?
Make the donation in cash.
I'll come back
to collect after your opening event.
Break a leg.
How much do you wanna bet those drugs
were a present from Penny Peabody?
[scoffs] This is ridiculous.
First the Ghoulies,
then Sheriff Minetta.
Think it's coincidence
they both work for your dad?
Of course not, Reggie.
My father's clearly trying to bait me
into some kind of... confrontation.
But I'm not going there.
At least...
not until I'm properly armed.
Hello? [Evelyn] Betty.
Evelyn.
You snuck up on me.
What are you doing here?
Well, I came to learn
more about the Farm.
Am I early?
No. No, the Farm just needs some time
to catch on.
- Yeah.
- But it will.
Uh...
Pizza?
No, I'm good. Thank you.
I also came here to talk to you
about Ethel Muggs.
She said that you're helping her
with her seizures.
Trying to.
Yeah, with my dad's teachings.
I just... have to get her off
that darn medication.
- Wait, you're not taking any, are you?
- No, no. I'm not.
I am considering it.
Um, I'm still having convulsions.
How often are they happening?
Once or twice, daily.
I was hoping that your dad could help.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Wakey, wakey, eggs and bakey.
I hear one peep out of you,
it's back to solitary for a month.
You got it?
[crowd shouting]
[bell dings]
[grunting]
- [man 1] You gotta be kidding.
- [man 2] What the...?
- [man 3] Come on.
- [man 4] What the hell?
[Golightly] Andrews.
Winners get perks.
Special requests for lunch?
You ever heard of a place called Pop's?
[security alarm buzzes]
To the winner goes the spoils.
That's a wicked uppercut you got there.
What'd the warden say
about ending the fight so quick?
What do you mean?
[Toni] The motorcycle in the back.
Nice.
Okay. [chuckles]
That one's cute.
Serpettes,
have either of you seen Jughead?
I have a problem
that has his name all over it.
You mean True Detective?
He's busy canoodling
Nancy Drew, no doubt.
But how can we help?
Penny Peabody paid me a visit.
That Viper bitch showed her face
on the Northside?
Followed shortly thereafter
by Sheriff Minetta.
My father's clearly puppeteering them.
I wanna call them off.
But... I need leverage against him.
Blackmail material, you mean.
Antoinette Topaz,
you are speaking my language.
Jughead has been keeping tabs
on the Southside.
[Toni] He has.
For instance, we know
that over the summer
the Ghoulies set up shop
in the basement of the Whyte Wyrm,
which your father owns.
Sweet Pea and Fangs think they've
turned it into a jingle-jangle lab.
Lucky for you I used to bartend there,
which means I know all the secret ways
in and out.
[The Archies' "Jingle Jangle" playing]
♪ Being kinda pretty ♪
♪ And down here in the city ♪
♪ Find it isn't easy to be smart ♪
♪ When tryin' to untangle ♪
♪ The Jingle from the Jangle ♪
Okay. We move quickly, but quietly.
♪ La, da, da, da, da, da, da ♪
♪ Sing me, sing me, sing me
La, da, da, da, da, da ♪
Sweet Pea and Fangs were right.
Yeah.
The jingle-jangle business is booming.
Should be plenty of admissible evidence
for blackmail, Veronica.
♪ Sing me, baby
La, da, da, da, da, da, da ♪
[scoffs]
Ethel.
Welcome to your first game.
Your entry point to the realm
of Gryphons and Gargoyles.
The magical kingdom of Eldervair.
First things first.
Do you wanna be the Radiant Knight,
Arcane Invoker, or Hellcaster?
Uh, Hellcaster.
Good choice. That was Ben's avatar.
I was supposed to ascend with him,
but he betrayed me
and finished the game with Dilton.
Leaving you high and dry.
Doesn't matter.
Pick a Quest Card. Let's get started.
[Betty] Mom?
Why are all those cars parked outside?
Betty, please, join us.
Sit.
Evelyn told us you're ready
to meet the Farm.
I thought
Mr. Evernever would be joining us.
[all laughing]
No. You don't just meet Edgar.
There are certain levels that you need
to attain before meeting Edgar.
First you start by
meeting a few Farmies.
Today can be your first testimony.
Testimony?
It's just a conversation.
An open, nonjudgmental conversation
about all the bad things you've done
in your life.
What kind of stuff would
you like to know?
Everything.
Speak from your heart.
From what your mother and Polly told us,
we know you've been through so much.
Between your dark kinship with your
father and the role you played
in disposing of the dead body
in your kitchen.
Wait. What? What?
Mom. Wait, you...? You told the Farm
about Chic and the shady man?
Are you out of your mind?
Oh, everything that we talk about
at the Farm
is kept in confidence.
We know all each other's secrets.
The wig.
The webcamming.
Okay. Okay.
If tonight's all about
open conversation,
then let's talk about how you,
Evelyn, were there
at both my seizure and Ethel's. And about
how the Farm showed up in Riverdale
at about the same time as a crazy game.
- Elizabeth, what are you talking about?
- It's a game.
It's called Gryphons and Gargoyles, that
made Ben and Dilton kill themselves,
all to appease some creature
called the Gargoyle King,
who, for all we know,
is Edgar Evernever.
The first time any of us heard
of Gryphons and Gargoyles
was from your mother, Betty.
How does that make any sense?
Mom, how do you know
about Gryphons and Gargoyles?
Betty. We're here to talk about you,
not your mother's past.
My mother's past?
You know, Evelyn, you were right.
It's too soon. Betty's not ready.
Mom.
You...
- You...
- Betty.
No. Don't touch me.
I'm fine.
Okay. You've crossed the old footbridge
to find two doors.
One is made of shimmering gold.
The other is just plain old maple wood.
Which door do you pick?
- Let's go with Door Number Two.
- Well-picked, Caster.
You've entered a secret chamber.
You're in the middle of a circle,
composed of gryphon bones.
Two chalices sit before you.
Ethel.
No. No way.
You wanted to prove your worthiness.
You have to drink
from one of the sacred goblets.
Like Ben and Dilton? You're asking
me to play Russian roulette.
To play Gryphons and Gargoyles.
Is there poison in
these Fresh-Aids?
That's gargoyle blood,
as you well know.
Flip for your fate.
If I do this...
- you promise to give me the scripture?
- I promise.
The King as my witness.
Gryphon.
Salut.
How do you feel?
Okay... I think.
Hey, rulebook. Come on.
You have to kiss me first.
My God, Ethel. Are you serious?
It's in the scripture.
The Hellcaster kisses the princess
or doesn't get the treasure.
Fine.
- Is this the only one?
- That I'm aware of.
All right. It's all in here.
The characters...
[scoffs] Oh, Betty's gonna
lose her mind over this.
What are you doing? Put that down.
- You okay?
- Jughead.
Come on. Come on. I'm
gonna call you 911.
Jeez, come on. Come on.
[Ethel] Jughead?
- What happened?
- You're in the hospital.
You ingested poison,
but they got you the antidote in time,
so, you're gonna be okay.
Protocol for anyone on suicide watch.
Suicide watch?
- But I didn't try to...
- You did.
When your parents get here,
be honest with them.
- You have to tell them about this game.
- I can't.
I'll never tell them.
Neither will you. If you do,
- I'll say you mixed the Fresh-Aid.
- It's over.
This game.
Whatever game you were playing...
is over now, Ethel.
No.
It's only just beginning.
You've proven yourself, Hellcaster.
I told him.
I told him that you were worthy enough
- to spread his gospel.
- Who?
Don't be dumb.
The King, of course.
The King isn't going to
hurt anyone anymore.
I'll make sure this doesn't
end up in anyone else's hands.
Okay?
Thank you, Hellcaster,
for helping me finish my game.
All right, Daddy.
Cards on the table.
I'm not paying protection
money to anyone.
Not Penny, not Minetta,
- and especially not to you.
- Veronica.
A bit of advice,
from one entrepreneur to another:
Don't make enemies
of people trying to help you.
Help me? Okay.
Here's the deal.
You tell your lackeys to back off,
or I'll send these photographs
of your drug lab to the authorities
faster than you can say Heisenberg.
Hmm.
I doubt these will have much traction
with Minetta.
[chuckles] I won't go to Minetta.
I'll go to the FBI.
Oh, and also,
I want $10,000 a week in perpetuity.
That's right, Daddy.
I'm shaking you down.
You can keep those, by the way.
I have copies.
The governor's hosting a fundraiser
in Seaside.
But I'll be back for your next match.
Which is what I want
to talk to you about.
Ending a fight in a single punch
is not entertaining enough.
Tonight,
your opponent should be no trouble.
Punish him.
Give us a show. And savor it.
Make it last,
oh, five or six rounds, at least.
That should fully sate
the crowd's bloodlust.
And mine. Understood?
Yes, sir.
I thought being here...
I'd pay for everything that I did.
But what the warden wants me to do,
to become...
is so much worse.
When you were little,
I used to get calls from your school.
Telling me that you had been in a fight,
usually protecting someone.
The warden wants six rounds, Dad.
He wants blood.
There's nothing that I can do.
Your seventh-grade teacher told me
one thing's for sure.
"By the time Archie gets out
of junior high school,
he's gonna know how to throw a punch,
and how to take one."
There are other ways of putting
on a show for the warden.
Figure it out, son.
[Alice] Are you going someplace?
It's Veronica's opening night.
I won't miss it.
You never had any intention
of working with the Farm, did you?
You wanted to meet Edgar
so that you could attack him, I suppose?
You realize, Mom, that by telling them
your deepest, darkest secrets,
like about the shady man,
you're also implicating me,
and FP,
and Jughead.
They would never use
my testimony against me.
Mom...
what do you know
about Gryphons and Gargoyles, huh?
What did you tell the Farm?
We can't let ourselves
be strangled by our past.
So, you're just gonna tell them,
but not me?
Not your own daughter?
I trust them more than
I trust you, Betty.
[pop music playing]
♪ Tiny things glittering... ♪
♪ Ooh look at 'em stare ♪
♪ Something sweet, if you please
I make magic everywhere ♪
♪ Anything you want, I got it Why
don't you pull it out of my pocket? ♪
Wow. Welcome, ladies.
Right this way.
♪ Voilà ♪
Hello, ladies. Hey.
How are you ladies doing tonight?
Toni, you look dashing.
[Toni] Vee, your bar is amazing.
Thank you.
[Cheryl] Finally a launch
does something good for this town.
I couldn't have done it without
my favorite power couple. Excuse me.
Thanks, babe.
I hid the manual in the trailer.
Thing is like a goldmine.
- I'll have to show it to you tonight.
- Well, Ethel is gonna be okay, right?
Physically.
But I think she's gonna need
a bit of deprogramming.
Oh, well,
she can keep my mom company, then.
The Farm got way deeper into her head
than I thought.
And she knows something
about G&amp;G, Jug.
And you still have
Fresh-Aid on your lips.
[Reggie] Ronnie.
- What is it, Reggie?
- We've got a problem, topside.
Veronica.
What's this?
Another shakedown?
No. I thought it might
feel more at home here.
A cherry on top of
your accomplishment,
which will be a roaring
success, I'm sure.
[clearing throat]
I know you don't wanna hear this
from me now.
But I'm still proud of you.
I'm glad you came, Daddy.
If only so you can see
how a legitimate business is run.
Follow me.
[Axelle Red's "Excusez-Moi"
playing on speakers]
Reggie, keep an eye on him.
Ladies and gentlemen.
On behalf of Veronica Lodge,
I thank you all for coming
to the grand opening of La Bonne Nuit.
Now please welcome to the stage
the one and only Ms. Josephine McCoy.
[crowd cheering]
Oh, my God. I am
obsessed with that gown.
[chuckles] Thanks, Kevin.
♪ In olden days ♪
♪ A glimpse of stocking ♪
♪ Was looked on
As something shocking ♪
♪ Now heaven knows ♪
♪ Anything goes ♪
♪ Good authors, too ♪
♪ Who once knew better words ♪
♪ Now only use four-letter words ♪
♪ Writing prose ♪
♪ Anything goes ♪
♪ The world's gone mad today ♪
♪ Good's bad today ♪
♪ Black's white today ♪
♪ Day's night today ♪
♪ And all the guys today ♪
♪ That women prize today ♪
♪ Are just... ♪
- Hit me.
- What?
Hit me. The warden wants a show,
he'll get a show.
Come at me.
Hit me, come at me.
That the best you got?
Come at me, wuss. Make me bleed.
♪ Anything goes ♪
♪ When every night ♪
♪ The set that's smart is ♪
♪ Intruding in nudist parties ♪
♪ In studios ♪
♪ Oh, anything goes ♪
♪ So, though I'm not ♪
♪ A great romancer ♪
♪ I know you're bound to answer ♪
♪ When I propose ♪
♪ Anything goes ♪
♪ If driving fast cars you like ♪
♪ If low bars you like ♪ ♪
If old hymns you like ♪
♪ If bare limbs you like ♪
♪ If Mae West you like ♪
♪ Or me undressed you like ♪
♪ Why, nobody will oppose ♪
♪ Anything goes ♪
♪ And all the pains you've got ♪
♪ If any brains you've got ♪
♪ From those little radios ♪
♪ Anything goes ♪
♪ Anything... ♪
That kid... is a star.
♪ Anything... ♪ [crowd shouting]
What is all this?
Mad Dog's hand-me-downs.
You're our new champ.
Mr. Andrews.
A token of appreciation...
for your performance.
You've got quite a future
at Leopold and Loeb Detention Center,
Mr. Andrews.
You and I, we're just getting started.
[yells]
[panting]
- [Jughead] What the hell?
- [Betty] What happened?
Where did you get this?
- Have you been playing?
- No.
Don't lie to me.
I still see the blue on your lips.
Mom, what are you doing here?
What are you two hiding?
- Where'd you get that?
- Who gave it to you?
- Something...
- [Betty] Jug.
Do not say anything.
- Not until they tell us what they know.
- You're looking through my stuff?
You don't get it. This game is...
It's pure evil.
- No one's ever gonna play it again.
- Hey.
Hey, stop.
- No, no. Stop.
- Don't do that. Dad, I'm begging you.
No one's gonna play,
but the book may be our best shot
- to find out what happened.
- How many copies are there?
- That's the only one.
- You can't destroy it.
FP, do it.
[knocking on door]
Congratulations on your opening night.
Speakeasy's beautiful.
Iconic, you might say.
Mm-hm.
- You left a little early, I noticed.
- I had some business to attend to.
Showing up with my portrait,
knowing I have photos of your drug lab?
Must mean you cleared
it out of the Wyrm,
and moved it to a new location.
Right?
What drug lab?
[security alarm buzzes]
What, no burgers?
After the show you put on,
I expected steaks and lobster.
I found something in my cell.
A small rock hammer
Mad Dog kept hidden in a book.
I think he kept it as a reminder
that no matter what happens in here,
there's still a world outside
that's worth getting back to.
Only way any of us get out
is in a body bag.
Not me. And none of you, either.
We're escaping.
Somehow...
we're gonna get the hell out of here.
Count me in.
Maybe it's for the best.
What do you mean?
Flipping through that manual felt
like... Like I was reading evil.
They played the game, Jug.
My mom, your dad.
That's why they were so down on us
investigating Ben and Dilton,
and why they freaked out
over us having the manual.
Well, if what Ethel said about
that being the only rulebook is true,
no one's gonna play
that game ever again.
It's over.
I did what you asked.
I spread your gospel.
[Jughead] Ethel must've done it
before our rendezvous in the bunker.
Or maybe there was someone else
helping her.
- Um, excuse you?
- Where'd you get this?
It was in my locker.
Same with everyone else.
[Jughead] Either way, by next weekend,
almost every student at Riverdale High
would play Gryphons and Gargoyles.
And the real game was just beginning.
Soon they'll join us.
All of them, my King.