[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-What are you doing?
-What we did all summer.
[Moose] My dad is right over there.
Why?
He's the new RROTC instructor.
-Welcome, cadets.
-Excuse me, Major Mason.
Hope it's not too late to join.
Can I get another bartender in here?
Toby. Toby. I know him.
Listen, Andrews.
You are in freefall,
and I am not having it.
You broke the code.
Turn in your jackets and go.
[Toni] You serious, Jones?
I'm a Serpent by blood.
You can't take that away from me.
[Veronica] I think my mom may have
hired someone to shoot my father,
so she could profit
from the sale of his drug operation.
We're gonna destroy them
before my mom sells everything.
[Hermione] What did you do?
My buyer is coming, Veronica.
They are gonna want blood.
[Jughead] Riverdale is like Bizarro Town.
Where murder, mystery,
and candy drugs aren't the exception,
they're the norm.
And you forget, sometimes,
that people are still
just living their lives.
Doing things as ordinary
as getting married.
You don't want a big wedding?
We just finalized our divorces, Kevin.
And this is the second marriage
for both of us.
With everything that's going on
in Riverdale--
We just wanna go down to Town Hall
and keep it simple.
If I may.
We fully disagree.
But we're not the ones getting married,
so, we respect your decision,
as long as you let us throw you
an after-party at La Bonne Nuit.
Ah.
If there's no wedding reception,
the Gargoyle King has won.
Okay, but a small one.
Fabulous, I'll send out invites today.
-Marcus.
-Tom.
Cadet Keller, ladies.
-How are you all doing?
-We're good, thank you.
Actually, we've got some news.
Tom and I are finally tying the knot,
and these two are throwing us
an after-party downstairs.
You and Moose can be our first invites.
How about it?
I'll... check my calendar, Sierra.
What's his deal?
Marcus and I used to be good friends.
We did RROTC together,
but we just grew apart.
It's probably the jealousy.
Well...
Marcus always had a crush on me,
as you know.
-[chuckles]
-But I only had eyes for you.
Lucky me.
Mm.
Feels so good to sleep
in a real bed, doesn't it?
Far away from the rural horrors
of Tent City?
Well, I don't miss the cold or the mud,
that's true.
But...
I don't know.
I miss the gang, babe.
[cell phones beeping]
[Cheryl sighs]
Oh, my God, our SAT scores.
I pray mine are good enough
for Highsmith College.
Women of my family have gone there
for generations.
I don't intend to break Blossom tradition.
Much like Desert Hearts,
my score's not perfect, but it's close.
How'd you fare, Tee-Tee?
Flawless, as I've always known you to be.
[chuckles]
[Hermione] Since you two vigilantes
took it upon yourselves
to burn all the Fizzle Rocks
that I had already sold,
you are gonna come up with the money
to pay back what's owed.
-How do we do that?
-I'd start with the speakeasy's coffers.
We don't make nearly enough to pay off
whatever kingpin you're working with, Mom.
Well, then I suggest you get creative,
mija.
And quickly.
The buyer who has a reputation
for being dangerously unhinged
is on their way to Riverdale,
and looking to get paid back in full
for the drugs they are not getting.
Who is this buyer?
You don't need to know.
They're sending an intermediary.
How much money are we talking about,
Mrs. Lodge?
And suddenly, I'm in an episode of Ozark.
No, but you are in the big leagues now,
and it is time to sink or swim.
[Cheryl] Furthermore,
I've successfully balanced my duties
as captain of the River Vixens
and president of the student body,
whilst maintaining a 4.2 GPA,
perfect attendance,
and achieving an almost perfect SAT store.
For these reasons,
I'm an exemplary candidate
for Highsmith College.
Not to mention, I'm legacy.
You are, Ms. Blossom.
However, most recently,
Highsmith College's Board of Directors
have decided it's time
to diversify our student body
with women from outside the alumni pool.
This is a new initiative?
I'm afraid so.
But long overdue, don't you agree?
Oh. Absolutely.
I'm just imagining which board member
suddenly developed a conscience.
Hey. I need to ask you something. Hey.
-Will you be my date to my dad's wedding?
-Kevin--
It's a public event.
You haven't come out to your dad.
But maybe it's time.
I mean, how long have we been together?
-Since summer started.
-So, forever.
And I love a clandestine grope
as much as the next gay guy,
but we've never spent a night together.
-You don't think I want to?
-So do it. Just talk to your dad.
-Dad.
-Major Mason.
-Told you they were in here, sir.
-Cadet Mason, Cadet Keller.
The meeting with the Naval Academy
recruitment officer is about to start.
So, on the double.
Sorry, Kev. I can't.
[sighs]
[Josie] Hey, Sweet Pea.
Hope you don't mind me dropping by.
Always happy to see you, Josie.
Especially if this is a...
A booty call?
Wouldn't be our first one
since our summer fling ended.
Well, it's not.
Um...
I don't know if you've heard,
but my mom is getting married.
To Kevin's dad.
And I wanted to know
if you would be my date to the wedding.
As your boyfriend?
Does it have to be so official?
[chuckles]
Look, Josie...
I like you.
I'd be all in with you in a second, but...
But you sliding into my life
whenever you don't wanna be alone...
I'm not built that way.
Maybe that makes me needy, but I just...
I gotta get off
this merry-go-round with you.
[jazz music playing]
So, this is the infamous Maple Club.
And no surprise,
it's as cheap and callow as your efforts
to sabotage my admission
to your alma mater.
I spoke to the headmistress
at Highsmith College.
She enlightened me about a new policy
that seems designed specifically
to keep me from attending.
I can't think of anyone else
who would stoop so low, Mumzie.
Care to explain?
Oh, Cheryl.
The hallowed halls of Highsmith
shall not be polluted
by someone of your... alignment.
You are an aberration.
I'm so sure the alumni newsletter
would be thrilled
to profile a twice-widowed dominatrix
with a proclivity for poison.
With the financial gifts
I bestowed upon them over the years,
I doubt they would bat an eye.
Now, accept it, Cheryl.
This is the price of salt.
Your presence
shall not besmirch Highsmith.
[chuckles]
The charges against you are very serious.
Oh, well, what do you suggest?
I could request an injunction.
[chuckles] I think
I'd like to go straight to trial.
[both laughing]
Where are you going?
I am having a little snack
before having my other snack.
[laughs]
What is it?
"Fair Sierriana,
Friar Thomas,
congratulations on your upcoming nuptials.
If you wish to live
to see this blessed event,
you must reunite
with your Midnight Club to co--
To complete Ascension Night,
once and for all."
"Tell no one,
or your children will pay the price.
Best wishes...
the Gargoyle King."
Well, someone looks like
they could use an epaulet to cry on.
I'm not trying to carb-shame you,
but whatever's on your mind,
it's not worth it.
So, put down the Swizzler,
and tell me your tale of woe.
I could use the distraction.
Well...
there's this guy.
And we've been having problems.
Moose, you mean?
Please. I have eyes.
I saw you lounging together
at my pool party,
like a community theater production
of The Talented Mr. Ripley.
The Koose ship's been trouble
from the gay get-go.
Maybe it's time you move on.
I can't go back to Fox Forest.
Oh, sullen, tender-hearted Kevin.
I'm not talking about cruising.
I'm talking about Bumble.
Look.
I'm sure you can find a well-adjusted,
handsome, out-and-proud fella here.
That'd be nice.
But I like Moose a lot.
I just wish he'd be honest with his dad,
so we could date, you know, openly.
What's his hang-up?
Major Mason's not the biggest fan
of our persuasion.
It burns me that there are people
in this town that still believe
that being gay is anything less
than rapturous.
Maybe Moose would come out
if he liked me more.
No. It's not your fault, Kevin.
Your aesthetic may be firmly rooted
in the 1950s,
but you're a catch in any decade.
As for the object of your affection,
maybe he just needs
the subtlest of nudges.
A bulldozer wouldn't be enough.
Attention, students,
it's time for the daily announcements.
As Riverdale High's first openly lesbian
student body president,
I'm announcing the launch of a new club.
An LGBTQIA alliance.
With the mission to find and support
our queer and questioning students.
In that spirit,
this week's blind item will be on theme.
A certain oh-so-hunky,
all-American RROTC cadet is afraid
to come out of the closet.
Let's show him
that Riverdale High is welcoming,
so he and his Broadway-loving boyfriend
can finally PDA,
like the other sex-crazed couples
amongst us.
For lunch today,
we're having shepherd's pie. Thank you.
-[Moose] Did you put Cheryl up to that?
-What, her not-so-blind item?
Of course not.
I'm opposed to publicly outing people,
except conservative politicians.
Have people guessed it's you?
No.
I don't know, maybe.
Moose...
Putting aside what Cheryl did,
we've been together for a while now.
I can't keep playing Brokeback Riverdale
with someone who's in the closet.
Either you come out to your dad,
or, I'm sorry, but we're breaking up.
Either way, I respect your decision.
-What the hell were you thinking?
-Just now?
About the sweet revenge
I'll get on Mumzie.
Hopefully with help from you,
and your camera, shutterbug of my dreams.
-You just outed Moose.
-No, I didn't.
It was a blind item, Toni.
No one knows I was referring to him.
Moose's father could've heard
that announcement.
-Oh, my God. Is this our first fight?
-Cheryl, get some perspective.
Did you know that my uncle hated the fact
that I dated girls?
That's why the Serpents
were so important to me.
They were like my non-judgmental family.
Now I don't have them.
Toni, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize.
Of course you didn't.
Because you're too busy being Cheryl,
causing chaos,
regardless of the consequences.
Look, babe.
I get that you're mad at your mom,
and you're pissed that you're not going
to some college
that I could never get into or afford.
-If it's about money--
-Just stop and listen to me.
Highsmith College was your legacy.
The Serpents were mine.
Now they're not.
Toni, I'll...
I'll fix this.
What part?
All of it.
You are the most important person
in my life.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make all these things right.
But I may need your help.
Josie. Hey.
Archie, hey.
Am I interrupting?
I was just practicing.
There is a recruiter from Juilliard
holding local auditions,
and my slot's this afternoon.
Don't be nervous. You're gonna kill it.
[laughs] If I could even get there.
It's at Seaside,
and I just assumed
that Sweet Pea would give me a ride,
but I didn't even get a chance to ask him.
Sweet Pea?
-Wait, are you guys--?
-No.
I ended it,
so that I could focus on my music,
which is what I always do.
Stay focused.
So much so that I've pushed everyone away.
And I can't ask my mom for a ride,
she doesn't even know
that I have this audition.
Because if she knew,
and I didn't do well at it,
she'd start asking me
about my backup plans,
which I don't have.
Let me take you.
I got the jalopy.
Really?
Absolutely.
Just remember this moment,
when you're accepting
your Best New Artist Grammy.
Okay?
Okay.
[Reggie] What's up, Ronnie?
We're dead.
We're officially dead.
That or we're about
to have our kneecaps broken.
Courtesy of whoever this mystery buyer is.
Does that really happen?
I've combined my liquid funds
from Pop's and La Bonne Nuit.
We're not even a quarter of the way there.
Is robbing banks still a thing?
Although the thought of being Bonnie
to your Clyde is intriguing...
banks have round-the-clock
security guards with guns.
But if they're anything
like my dad's lame-ass security guards...
[sighs]
Holy crap, I'm a genius.
My dad keeps cash
in a safe at the dealership.
Enough to make up the difference.
I'm not gonna let you steal
from your own family.
That dealership is my legacy,
so, technically,
I'd borrow money from my future self.
And everything's insured,
so, my dad will get a sweet payout,
more than he deserves for all the shiners
he's given me over the years.
This is lunacy.
But it might be inspired lunacy.
-How would we get it all done?
-My dad's security guard
is only on duty at night after closing,
so, I'd hit the lot during the day,
probably lunchtime,
when my dad is usually at Pop's,
with a customer,
trying to close a sale.
You could wear a Gargoyle mask,
so as not to get recognized.
And I, of course, would come with you,
as we're in this mess together.
You can be my Baby Driver.
Just, please, don't scratch my car.
Okay?
So, we all received letters,
to finish Ascension Night.
-This was taped to my trailer.
-Mine came to the dealership.
Thought you caught the Gargoyle King, FP.
Tall Boy was using the game
as a cover to deal drugs,
but he wasn't the one setting up chalices
back when we were in high school.
We're not really taking this seriously,
are we?
We have to assume this is real,
if only for our kids' sake.
And then what?
We leave them home alone all night,
while we run around,
pretending to be teenagers?
May I remind you
what happened last Ascension Night?
Someone ended up dead.
We don't have any choice in the matter.
We all know why this is happening again,
and now.
Two members of the original Midnight Club
are daring to get married,
to be happy.
And the Gargoyle King,
whoever or whatever he is,
wants to destroy that.
He is a vicious and petty god.
And if we don't finish the game now,
the Gargoyle King is
never gonna leave us alone.
Maybe if we do this,
we catch the son of a bitch.
There's only one problem.
The letter says
we all have to participate.
I'll talk to Hiram.
All right, it's settled, then.
We finish the game we started.
[woman] Name?
Josephine McCoy.
All right, then.
Whenever you're ready.
[gunshots]
Go, go, go.
Oh, my God, Reggie.
-Were you shot?
-Yeah.
I got the money,
but there was security after all.
-Well, are you okay?
-Drive, drive.
-[Cheryl] Thanks for your help, Toni.
-Just remember your promise to me.
Don't worry, babe. I have a mega-plan,
and this is only step one.
Operation Fifty Shades of Blackmail
is underway.
What in God's name
are you jezebels doing here?
Whatever mad, sapphic caper you're on,
I won't have you jeopardize
my thriving business.
Step down from the Highsmith College Board
and revoke your ban on my admittance,
or I'll go public with these photos
of your sorry clientele.
I am far from ashamed of my work, Cheryl.
Need I remind you
that blackmail is far more illegal
than anything that goes on
at the Maple Club,
all of which is consensual.
[Toni] How will your clients feel,
once we publish their names and photos?
[Cheryl] Don't test us, Mumzie.
We know how to dominate, too.
[Archie] Did it come through?
-[Josie] Um...
-[Archie] What does it say?
"Unfortunately, we are...
unable to invite you
to callbacks this year."
I'm sorry, Josie.
I know I'm biased, Archie,
but I think I killed that audition.
I sang my heart out.
And it still wasn't enough.
Then they're crazy.
-They don't deserve you.
-I've given so much to this.
And all along, I've been saying,
"It's okay. It'll be worth it."
I've built up so many walls
to focus on this one thing,
and now...
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
And I'm alone.
Hey.
-You're not alone.
-I am.
I can't even get a date
to my mom's wedding.
-That speaks volumes.
-I'll do it.
What, be my date?
I've been alone these last few months.
Either literally...
or feeling like I'm from Mars,
and it sucks.
Yeah.
So, maybe I can help you
feel a little less alone.
Okay.
[Reggie] I can't believe I was shot.
Are you sure
you don't wanna go to a doctor, Reggie?
No, it's just a graze.
Besides, now I can say I've been shot.
Except you can't,
since we want everyone to believe
that the Gargoyle Gang robbed
your father's dealership.
Right, right.
Okay.
-Let's see how much money we just copped.
-And pray it's enough.
[grunts]
What?
A dye pack?
Oh, hell.
We're screwed.
[school bell ringing]
I did it. I told my dad.
What? You did? How'd it go?
He was quiet and weird at first,
but then okay, I think.
We went to Pop's after,
got chicken pot pie, which is a good sign.
I'm so proud of you, Moose.
That mean you'll be my date?
Yeah, and more importantly...
we should do it, spend the night together.
Question is, where?
Don't worry. I know the perfect spot,
where no one will interrupt us.
In a fortuitous turn of events,
Ms. Blossom,
Highsmith College's policy
not to admit legacy candidates
has been reconsidered,
so, we may proceed with our interview.
Respectfully, Headmistress Patricia,
I know you only perform a limited number
of one-on-ones.
With my qualifications,
legacy status or not,
I'm obviously a shoo-in.
I'd like to cede my time
to another
unquestionably worthy candidate.
Ms. Antoinette Topaz.
Future photojournalist,
and Nobel Peace Prize recipient.
It's a pleasure to meet you, headmistress.
Knock them dead, babe,
and remember, this is only step two.
Yes. Please, have a seat.
-Do you have your portfolio with you?
-[Toni] Yes, I do.
Whoever you are, please, be chill.
[The North Panics'
"Haven't You Heard?" playing]
Oh, great. More teenagers.
Here's your money,
or as much as we could get of it.
Veronica Lodge, I presume.
I can't believe your mom sent you out here
to sort out her mess.
I mean, I know she's cutthroat,
but, man, that's cold as ice.
Sorry, are we supposed to know you?
I'm Gladys Jones.
You might know my kid, Jughead.
-What?
-Seriously?
You're Jughead's mom?
Mrs. Jones,
if you could give us more time,
we could get you the rest of the money.
Just don't break our kneecaps.
I gotta say, I do admire the fact
that you two came here,
knowing you were short.
Shows you know how to take responsibility.
Look at the two of you.
[scoffs]
You remind me a bit of me and FP,
back in the day.
I'll tell you what.
I'm sticking around for a while.
So, I will take your money,
but I'm gonna have to charge you a fee,
because I'm gonna need
to get it laundered...
every which way.
Understood.
We'll figure out a payment plan
for the rest.
But in exchange,
you're gonna lend me those sweet wheels.
Not Bella.
Please, Mrs. Jones, Reggie loves that car.
I'll make sure
I take real good care of her.
Oh, wait, one more thing.
Just as a favor,
don't tell Jughead about our business.
I mean, if you do,
I'm gonna have to tell Hiram
about his missus going behind his back
for a cut,
and that'd be bad for all of us.
[Cheryl] Greetings, Moose.
What the hell, Cheryl? What do you want?
To apologize.
Outing you was wrong.
For so many reasons.
It's a personal decision
that I shouldn't have taken from you.
I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
And that's step three.
Bon appétit.
Cheryl.
I'm not saying what you did was right,
but it kind of turned out okay.
I'm out to my dad.
[chuckles]
And Kevin and I, we, uh...
We're finally gonna do it.
Tonight in some secret bunker.
Well, well, well, Moose.
In that case, I'd bring a fresh set
of sheets, if I were you.
A lot of people have had sex on that cot.
[Fred] Feels like we never left.
'Cause we never did.
[FP] The Gargoyle King wants us
to finish Ascension Night.
Better start by finding the chalices.
Then we flip for our fates,
and drink up, game over.
-You want us to drink poison?
-[Sierra] Not quite.
Penelope, did you bring them?
The antidote to cyanide.
Drink it now, you'll be inoculated
for the next several hours.
Oh, come on.
[all groaning]
[Keller] All right.
Let's get these chalices,
get this over with.
-Should we wait for the Lodges?
-We're already here, Sierra.
Friends, good to see you again.
I'm certain
not all of you feel the same way.
I sure as hell don't,
but we're here on a mission,
so, let's get after it.
[Donna Missal's "Thrills"
playing on speakers]
I know, candles. It's dumb.
No, I get it.
♪ You know the deal ♪
♪ Feels like a no stop
Head shot ♪
♪ Gas light
Low rise ♪
♪ Double time, overdose relapse, kill shit
My love is real, yeah ♪
Girls' bathroom is clear.
That's where I found the chalices before.
Check the trophy case?
Yeah, we did. Nothing.
We searched the student lounge,
the closet where we found Featherhead.
Second floor's clear.
-So is the cafeteria.
-And the library.
I don't understand.
The objective was simple.
Return to school, find the chalices,
finish the game.
What aren't we seeing?
Wait. Where's Penelope?
[Penelope screaming]
Penelope? What is it?
[Hermione] What the hell does it mean?
It's a prank, and we've been played.
Or...
it's just another iteration of the game...
and what the Gargoyle King wanted,
all along.
To distract us, and lure us away from--
-Our kids.
-[keypad beeping]
[cell phones ringing]
Hold on.
-Mom?
-Hey, Dad.
-Josie, where are you?
-Rehearsing with Archie. What's up?
Lock the doors.
Do not let anybody in the house.
It's locked, Dad. What's wrong?
[cell phones ringing]
-Crap, it's my dad.
-My mom's calling, too.
Think he knows about the dealership?
-Mom?
-What's up, Dad?
[cell phones ringing]
-It's my dad.
-It's my mom.
-Hi, Mom.
-Hello?
-Jughead.
-Where are you?
[cell phone ringing]
It's my hateful mother.
-Why are you calling, Night Hag?
-Just do what I say.
Keep your bow close.
-Josie's with Archie at Fred's.
-Veronica's with Reggie.
Kevin's not picking up.
Cheryl, you don't know
where the Keller boy is, do you?
It's funny.
Part of me thought
this was never gonna happen.
I'm glad it did.
[metal clanking nearby]
Betty, if that's you,
I reserved the bunker tonight.
Betty.
What the hell is this? Who are you guys?
What are you doing?
Say something.
No. Hey.
Let go of me.
-Oh, my God. No.
-Get your hands off me.
[Kevin] Oh, my God. Moose, no.
Oh, my God.
What do you want?
Please, just let us go.
-They want us to flip for our fate.
-We're not doing that.
We're not playing your sick game, okay?
If we don't, they'll kill us.
I'll go first.
-No, Kev--
-I'll go first.
Is this what you want?
Will this make you happy?
[panting]
[FP] Drop the weapons!
[police sirens wailing]
-Don't move.
-Dad.
-It's okay.
-Don't move.
They're from the RROTC?
What? Why?
Dad?
[FP] Let's cut to the bone, Mason.
Are you the Gargoyle King?
There was no poison in those chalices.
I was just...
scaring them.
Right.
Scaring them straight.
You set out to abduct
and terrorize your own kid.
How'd you talk your cadets into helping?
I made it a quest.
The Gargoyle King told them
their brothers needed help.
"When you are weak, I am weak."
The RROTC was the same way
when Tom Keller and I were in high school.
Back then,
us cadets did everything together.
And no one was closer than me
and my best friend, Tommy Keller.
Until I tried to kiss him.
Marcus.
When my parents found out
about my inclinations,
they sent me to the Sisters
to get help for my...
weakness of character.
That's where I first met the King,
and where I started playing
Gryphons and Gargoyles,
which I later learned Tommy played, too,
with his Midnight Club.
The Sisters cured me of impure thoughts.
I became strong,
as I have been all these years.
But then I heard Tom
and Sierra were getting married,
just as my own son, Moose,
told me he was seeing Tom's boy.
Who looks just like Tommy did...
when I...
You wanted to destroy
what you couldn't have.
The Sisters scared you
with the Gargoyle King,
so, you thought you'd do the same...
to Moose and Kevin.
Man, the Sisters did a number on you.
Tall Boy was using the costume
to sell drugs.
But Major Mason was using it to,
what, scare his kid?
We keep taking down Gargoyle Kings,
and they keep popping up again.
It's like playing Whack-a-Mole.
But the true Gargoyle King,
if there even is an Ur-King,
is still at large.
-[scoffs]
-[Jellybelly] Daddy?
-Jellybelly?
-What?
I'm sorry I was such a jerk last time.
That's all right, sweetheart. It's okay.
-Nice hat.
-[Jellybelly] You, too.
[Gladys] Hey, Jughead.
Hey, FP.
Hey.
What are you guys doing here?
I think what you meant to say is,
"Welcome home."
We're always happy to see you, Gladys.
Just, uh, wish you had called,
told us you were coming to visit.
Visit? No, me and JB,
we're here to stay a while.
[Gladys laughing]
In the end,
our folks got the wedding they wanted.
The four of us at Town Hall.
They said it didn't feel right,
having a party,
after everything.
So, what now?
Well, after everything
that Kevin and Moose just went through,
not getting into Juilliard doesn't seem
like such a big deal.
Honestly, I...
I don't know.
Just take it day by day.
That's what I'm doing, too.
The bummer is,
I was gonna suggest
we sing together, Josie.
So, why can't we?
♪ I always wanted
to see the lights of Broadway ♪
To hear the traffic roar ♪
♪ I always wanted to be a part ♪
♪ Of New York City's great big heart ♪
♪ And now I am ♪
♪ I couldn't ask for more ♪
♪ People like us
We get through the day ♪
♪ Surviving the city
Way better than most ♪
♪ We go through the motions
From nightcap to nightcap ♪
♪ Here but not here
With the heart of a ghost ♪
♪ People like us
We meet up some night ♪
♪ In a room full of strangers
Who call themselves friends ♪
♪ Feels like a dream
But it's too hard to tell ♪
♪ Where the dream begins
And the real world ends ♪
♪ [both] And where ♪
♪ Where do we belong? ♪
I'm glad it was too late
to cancel the cake.
It's beautiful.
You're beautiful.
I love you, Sierra.
I love you, Tommy.
[Moose] I can't stay, Kev.
I just...
I came to tell you that...
I'm, uh, moving to Glendale
to stay with my aunt.
Moose, your friends are here and I'm here,
and you can live with any of us.
Kevin.
Hey.
I can't live here.
At least not for a little while.
I'll miss you, Marmaduke.
I'll miss you, Kevin Keller.
It's so messed up, what Major Mason did.
It was the Sisters' conversion therapy.
It twisted his soul.
Well, I'm glad we got you
out of that hellhole when we did.
I'll never forget the day you saved me,
Tee-Tee.
And since you've done so much for me,
I wanted to do something for you.
Call it step four.
What's this?
[Cheryl] A gang, if you want it.
You said you were missing
having the Serpents as a family.
I found some other girls
who were looking for support,
or community,
or just good old-fashioned fisticuffs.
And I thought
maybe we could start a new family.
Cheryl, this is the most badass
and romantic thing you've ever done.
[clearing throat]
Uh... Do we have a name yet?
How about...
the Pretty Poisons?
Pretty by day, poison by night.
I love it.
-You said you have an update for me?
-Yeah.
But first...
You could've told us
that the secret buyer was Jughead's Mom.
Wait. Gladys showed up?
I assumed that she would've sent
one of her deputies up from Toledo.
Nope.
And about Toledo, Mom?
I've got news for you.
I don't think Gladys is leaving
anytime soon.
Everything's going how you said, Mom.
Dad's wrapped around my pinky.
You're his weakness, baby.
Which means we got the whole town, JB.
Your old man's the sheriff.
The mayor owes us serious cash.
Hell, even her daughter's
working for me now.
Oh, yeah.
We moved to the right place
at the right time.
I could feel it.
♪ Where ♪
♪ Where do we belong? ♪
Archie.
Can I kiss you?