- [narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
- Ben and I thought it was a game.
But it's not. It's so much more.
- He's real. The Gargoyle King.
- Dilton?
Ben. Hey.
Framing Archie for murder,
conspiring to keep him locked away?
You don't have a daughter anymore.
We start a version of the Farm.
You're actually buying this Farm crap
that a huckster named
Edgar Evernever is selling you.
[Alice] Oh, my God.
- Betty.
- I didn't kill anyone.
But I could've.
I have to take responsibility.
I can't put everyone through this again.
I'll take the deal.
Your Honor, I'm guilty.
[school bell ringing]
[Jughead] We've all felt it.
The first day of a new school year.
Butterflies in the stomach.
We've all looked around, and wondered,
where will I fit in here?
Who will I sit with at lunch?
Will I even make it till lunch?
Multiply that by a thousand,
and that's how Archie Andrews felt
as he was being processed
at the Leopold & Loeb
Juvenile Detention Center.
Andrews. Warden wants to see you.
Let's go.
It's Shakespeare. Know what it means?
No, sir.
Means you're alone
and have no one to blame but yourself.
I read your file.
Besides killing that
boy at Shadow Lake...
I'm told you have an affinity for music.
We have a music room.
No one uses it, but it's there.
I keep an orderly house, Mr. Andrews.
Respect that, and we'll
get on just fine.
- You understand?
- Yes, sir.
I just got off the phone with the warden
at juvenile hall.
He says Archie's been processed.
- He's okay.
- Oh, thank God.
Yeah. They got a line on those three thugs
that gave false testimony against him.
I'm friends with the sheriff
at Shadow County.
He found a campfire in the deep woods.
Archie's in jail,
and these cretins are basically camping.
Not for long. We'll make sure of that.
Meanwhile I'll keep the home
fires burning at Riverdale High
so everyone knows my Archiekins
will be back in time for Homecoming.
And everything will be
just as he left it.
Dr. Patel kept Betty overnight
for observation,
but it was just a precaution.
Did he say what caused the seizure?
They ran tests, but he suspects
it's just good old-fashioned stress.
Oh, Betty.
I was up all night with the twins.
- We were so worried about you.
- You were worried about me?
And Juniper and Dagwood?
Are they all right?
Okay, here we go again.
Juniper and Dagwood are napping.
They're fine.
Why wouldn't they be?
Um, because I saw you and Mom throw the
twins into a giant bonfire last night.
Right, that's enough.
The only thing burning last night
was the hibachi in the backyard.
- We made skewers with friends.
- From the Farm?
Yeah, as a matter of fact.
You must've had a hallucination
while you had the seizure.
It was so real.
Sweetheart.
[cell phone buzzing]
[Betty] My God.
- Dilton is dead?
- Yeah.
And Ben from the drive-in?
He's barely hanging on.
Doctors don't know when,
or if, he's even gonna wake up.
Sheriff Minetta asked me
to keep it hush-hush for the families,
but, Betty, what I saw was...
- What, Jug?
- It was like a ritual site.
Their lips were blue. There were chalices,
that were filled with poison or something.
Animal bones were in a circle.
The tree had markings on it.
There was a winged totem,
with a skull and branches.
Was it a murder
or a suicide pact gone wrong?
I have no idea. I saw Ben and Dilton.
Playing a weird game at Pop's.
Dilton was raving
about someone called the Gargoyle King.
I was also thinking that maybe you and
I could investigate this together.
For old times' sake. Or at least until
we catch a new lead with Archie's case.
I like that idea.
I'll try to see if Dr. Curdle can get us
into the coroner's office.
Have more romantic words
ever been spoken?
No.
[man] You bunk with Mad Dog.
[inmates shouting]
[jazz music playing on speakers]
Hey.
I'm Archie. You're Mad Dog, right?
[exhaling sharply]
How long you been in?
[music stops]
- Listen, since we're cellmates...
- Nice shoes.
I'd keep them tied real tight.
Mr. Weatherbee? As Archie's girlfriend,
and former running mate,
I wanted to let you know I'm stepping in
as interim student body president.
Sorry, someone else already petitioned
to be president.
- Just this morning.
- What? Who did?
Cheryl, what do you think you're doing,
trying to steal Archie's presidency?
Who would you have lead us
through these dark times?
Ethel Muggs? I saw the
poor girl earlier.
She was fuguing about a winged creature
- that was after her.
- Actually...
I thought I'd keep Archie's seat warm.
Why? When JFK was shot,
Jackie O. didn't become president.
Lyndon B. Johnson did.
And then he lead us into Vietnam.
I'm just saying.
Her man's in the big house, Cheryl.
Give her a break.
I get it. And I sympathize,
up to a point.
But let's be reals, Veronica.
I need this presidency
for college applications
a lot more than Archie.
You mind if I sit?
I'm Slash.
Who gave you that ink?
- Looks fresh.
- FP Jones did.
His son, Jughead, made me a Serpent.
Said I could hang out with you guys.
[Joaquin] You're no Serpent, Archie.
Joaquin.
What the hell are you doing in juvie?
Didn't you hear?
I came to town to help Fangs escape,
stuck around.
Got hauled in during Riot Night.
I know this guy, Slash.
He's Mr. Clean-Cut, All-American.
You're Jughead's pal, not a Serpent.
You have to earn our trust and
protection, with a test of loyalty.
See that Ghoulie?
I want you to go up to him...
and shiv him.
Don't worry about the guards.
We pay them to turn a blind eye.
Do that,
and then we'll have your back, huh?
You're kidding, right?
Not gonna happen, bro.
I don't need your protection that bad.
[inmate] Nice shoes.
[inmates whistling]
Dr. Curdle?
- Oh. You're not...
- I'm his son.
We spoke over the phone earlier.
I took over after my father passed away.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Do you have the money?
The toxicology report revealed
lethal levels of cyanide
in Mr. Doiley's blood.
I surmise the surviving boy
didn't drink enough to finish the job.
Dr. Curdle, if you had to guess,
murder or suicide?
Well, the body did show signs of stress.
Three symbols carved out on his back.
Runic, I'd say.
Mind if I get a shot of this?
What caused, uh... the blue lips?
The cyanide was mixed
into a sugary drink called Fresh-Aid.
Blueberry-flavored.
There's something dimly familiar
about this.
But you asked me before
if I thought this was murder,
or suicide.
I'm not sure what it is,
but whatever it is,
it's darker
than what happened to Jason Blossom,
or what the Black Hood did.
No, what we're looking
at here, I believe,
is the true face of evil.
[playing blues tune]
- What's up, guys?
- You don't remember us?
Should I? Have we met before?
We were at the drag race
the day you called the cops on us.
We're in because of you.
Ghoulies.
Crap.
Look, I don't want any trouble.
I'm sorry.
Neither do we. We just want your shoes.
What?
Don't touch his face.
Why are you sitting that way?
I'm just a little sore, Ronnie.
Sore from what?
Working out. There's an amazing gym.
Uh-huh.
And where are your shoes?
The warden took them when I got here,
with my other clothes.
- That makes no sense.
- Ronnie.
Talk to me about school.
What am I missing?
How's the speakeasy coming?
It's coming.
What's it like,
being president in my place?
Hi, I'm checking in on the status
of a friend of mine, Ben Button.
Oh. Wait, he's out of the ICU?
That's great.
Uh, what time are your visiting hours?
Uh, thank you.
[Betty sighs]
Hi.
I'm Evelyn. And you're Betty Cooper?
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
Not exactly. We almost met,
through your mom and sister.
- They're studying with my dad.
- Edgar Evernever.
Yeah. That's right.
Anyway, I go to school here now.
I wanted to say hi,
let you know I won't tell anyone
about what happened the other night.
- What are you talking about?
- Your seizure, of course.
Wait, sorry, you...? You were there?
Your mom invited us over for a cookout,
and to burn a few of her things.
How are you feeling?
Uh... [chuckles]
Um...
Uh, you know what, Evelyn? I have to go.
I have to visit a
friend in the hospital.
So...
Yeah, no worries. I totally understand.
- Dude, what are you doing?
- What we've done all summer.
I thought we'd sneak off
to the boiler room...
My dad is right over there.
Why?
He's the new RROTC instructor.
He's making me sign up.
If he's around school,
we have to take it easy.
Hey, Cadet Mason.
On time is late. Let's go. Room 302.
Talk to you later.
[school bell ringing]
[pop music playing on speakers]
Veronica.
That's right, you work here now.
Cherry phosphate and curly fries. Girls?
I don't work at Pop's, Cheryl. I own it.
And as of this moment,
you're no longer welcome.
You can't discriminate against someone
'cause they're better-looking.
Cheryl, you're acting like trash,
and I don't wanna get a citation.
[sighs]
Vixens, leave us be.
Now, then.
What are you mad about?
It can't be that I'm making a play
for student body president.
Actually, that's exactly why I'm mad.
I promised Archie that when he gets out,
I'll have everything in place, waiting.
That includes this stupid presidency.
Just a suggestion,
but maybe channel that rage
into something more productive,
like getting your boyfriend sprung.
There's an organization
called the Innocence Project.
Looked into it when I was accused
of Jay-Jay's murder.
Maybe check it out.
A little food for thought.
Speaking of food, cancel my order.
I'm going to TGI Thursdays.
[woman on PA] Dr. Matthews
to Pediatrics.
[EKG beeping]
Hi, Mrs. Button.
- We wanted to see how Ben was doing.
- How do you know my Ben?
Uh... From school. And he and I worked
at the Twilight Drive-In.
Oh.
How he's doing?
He's stabilized,
but he hasn't woken up yet.
Do you know what happened
in the woods, Mrs. Button?
No. Ben's always been a bit
of an odd duck, you could say.
Kept to himself. Especially after
his piano teacher was murdered.
But this summer, he
became friends with...
Dilton Doiley.
That's right.
It's like he became a different person.
Secretive, sneaking out at all hours.
Having these horrible nightmares.
Mrs. Button.
Know what this is, or how it got here?
Maybe that nice girl left it.
Someone else came to visit Ben?
Another friend from school.
I don't remember her name.
She wore a bow in her hair.
Jughead, Betty.
I don't care how Keller ran things
when he was sheriff.
I won't let a couple teenagers compromise
an active murder investigation.
If it's an active murder investigation,
start by letting
the rest of the town know.
Sheriff Minetta?
- What, Henderson?
- An Adventure Scout's parents called.
- Haven't seen him in two days.
- What?
We've got a missing kid. And he was
part of Dilton Doiley's troop.
- [Veronica] Madam Mayor.
- Wait, why are you not in school?
I'm on my way, but this couldn't wait.
I'm starting a chapter of the
Innocence Project here in Riverdale
and with a letter of support
from Town Hall,
I can cut through all
that silly red tape.
I can't get in this war
between you and your father.
But I'm not here as your daughter.
I'm here as a citizen.
One of your constituents
sits in juvenile detention,
wrongfully convicted,
and I intend to get him acquitted.
[Veronica sighs]
Your endorsement could help sway
a lot of dubious minds.
Please, Mom.
Fine.
- I'll have Gloria draft a letter.
- Wonderful.
Oh, and I'm also accepting donations.
[Jughead] Hi, Ethel.
- Does this look familiar to you?
- Where'd you get it?
Ben's hospital room.
- Why were you there?
- I don't have to tell you anything.
- You're not police.
- Ethel, wait.
We're trying to find out what happened
to Ben, Dilton, and the missing Scout.
- Is it the Gargoyle King?
- How do you know?
Dilton started to tell me,
but only got so far.
So, is it?
No. No.
It's the opposite.
I made that talisman
to... To protect Ben.
- How do you even know Ben?
- He's my boyfriend.
- I've never seen you two together.
- We started dating this summer.
- We spent all our time in the bunker.
- Bunker?
Never mind.
Ethel, just...
What bunker?
Dilton's.
In the woods.
Dilton Doiley has a secret bunker
in the woods?
It was our secret spot.
- And Dilton's, too.
- Can you at least tell us where it is?
I mean, I can't.
It's too hard to describe.
Then can you show us where it is?
Ethel, it's either us
or Sheriff Minetta.
Okay, fine.
But you have to keep it a secret.
- Sure.
- Of course.
And go at night, so nobody can see us.
Know where Fox Footbridge is?
I tried to warn you.
Yeah.
Apparently,
the Ghoulies really like sneakers.
You're a Serpent.
- Why didn't they look out for you?
- I wouldn't shiv a Ghoulie.
How come?
Because that's not who I am.
Maybe not yet.
But you will be soon.
When you got here, you
lost your humanity.
You're an animal in a cage now.
An animal does whatever he has to do
to live.
- To survive.
- What do you do, Mad Dog?
You're not a Ghoulie.
You're not a Serpent.
I doubt anyone in here messes with you.
You have stuff no other prisoner does.
Why?
You don't wanna know.
And trust me, you don't
wanna get tapped.
But take my advice this time.
Be an animal.
Before they kill you like one.
What is wrong with the two of you?
- Dad?
- What's going on?
- Sheriff Minetta called. Said...
- Called us both.
He caught you snooping around Ben's room
at the hospital.
Look, Dad,
something weird is going on here.
No one wants to talk about it.
But Dilton came to me for help.
You were there.
- I feel like I owe him something.
- You don't owe him anything.
- It's nothing to do with you.
- And Betty,
this is exactly
what Dr. Patel was talking about.
Keep it up, young lady,
you'll have another seizure.
Seizure?
Did you have a seizure and not tell me?
She most certainly did,
because you keep dragging her
into these murder investigations.
You are unbelievable, Mom.
- Hey, Betty.
- FP, can you please...?
Don't even think about it.
We're going home.
Everyone needs to cool off.
You didn't have to get me anything.
Nonsense. Reggie helped
me pick them out.
Go on, open it.
To replace your other pair.
Perfect for your triumphant strut
out of here
when the Innocence Project
gets your conviction overturned.
They're great, Ronnie. Thanks.
Sucks, you could've worn those kicks
to the pep rally.
[chuckles] Yeah.
- How are the Dogs doing?
- Coach is running our asses off.
Varsity squad will be tough
to beat this year,
especially with Moose
anchoring the O-Line.
Dude is a straight beast.
But we're missing our star running back.
Need you back on the field.
[Twenty One Pilots' "Jumpsuit" playing]
♪ I can't believe how much I hate ♪
♪ Pressures of a new place roll my way ♪
♪ Jumpsuit... ♪
- [inmate] Is he for real?
- Hey, Joaquin. It's your boy.
- Got a death wish, Archie, is that it?
- No, Joaquin.
I wanna live.
Look, guys, straight up.
Most of us are gonna be here
for a long time.
And I...
I don't wanna do it
living like an animal.
Shivving each other
in the freaking yard might be
what the guards, the warden,
and the world expects of us,
but screw them.
- Let's show them there's another way.
- What way is that?
If we weren't here,
we'd be in school, joining clubs,
- trying out for sports.
- Not me.
I dropped out in fourth grade,
to run drugs to support my Nana.
Then you haven't
known the triumphs and defeats,
the epic highs and lows
of high-school football.
But you will.
At least for one afternoon,
when all of us play a game.
One game.
To remind them that we are not animals.
That we're men.
Not Ghoulies versus Serpents.
No gangs. We'll mix it up,
for a clean, fair game.
Or we gut you like a fish,
and take your shoes again.
[Mad Dog] Kid's got a point.
We keep killing each other,
they're the ones who win.
I know all about that.
How about this?
MVP wins my new sneakers.
- All right.
- All right, man.
[inmates chattering]
How about that?
If that's some weird tea from the Farm,
I really don't want it.
It's chamomile, Betty. Calm down.
Listen, honey, I thought you would've
told Jughead about your seizure.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have assumed.
It's okay.
You really scared me.
- What happened to you.
- I'm fine, Mom.
I just want you to be safe.
I know.
And I am.
Good night.
[Jughead] So, what happened, exactly?
One minute I was fine,
the next I was hallucinating,
some truly insane stuff,
like out of a horror movie.
And then I woke up in the emergency
room, embarrassed, to be honest.
That's why I didn't say anything.
It's nothing.
Dr. Patel said it was just stress.
Great.
And I ask you to investigate
a double suicide-slash-murder.
Weirdly, being in the woods with you,
investigating something crazy,
is the least stressful,
most normal thing I can think of.
This kind of reminds me of, like,
when we first started dating, remember?
That's probably Ethel, right?
[grumbling]
Jug, do you see that?
- Yeah. I do.
- Okay.
Run.
[Jughead sighs]
Is that the thing we just saw?
If I had to hazard a guess... yeah.
Behold the Gargoyle King.
Who, luckily for us,
doesn't run very fast.
No, but really,
it was too tall to be Ethel, I think,
unless she was on stilts,
which is possible,
because she's not answering her phone.
Is there anything on Dilton's map?
What we should've checked
in the first place?
Uh, yeah. Right here.
This is where I found Ben and Dilton.
And this is the footbridge,
where Ethel wanted us to meet.
But this...
- What does that look like?
- I was researching runic symbols earlier.
That one didn't show up.
What if it's the drawing
for the hatch...?
- That leads to the bunker.
- If this map is halfway accurate,
I'd say that's right around the deadfall
in Fox Forest.
We can find this, Betty.
I think
this football game is a fantastic idea.
But is it safe?
It's fully sanctioned.
Everyone wants this.
The Ghoulies, the Serpents,
everyone wants to feel... free.
Ugh. I so wish I could be there,
cheering you on to victory.
Me, too.
And if ever
a group of guys needed a pep rally.
I've reconsidered your bid
for student council president.
Why, pray tell?
Because you were right.
Protecting Archie's presidency doesn't
really help him in any meaningful way.
- I'm glad you've come to your senses.
- However,
I know something
that would help bolster his spirits.
But I would need your help,
and the Vixens.
- Thanks, Delores. See you around.
- Sure.
[doorbells jingle]
- Hey, handsome...
- Hey, Kev.
Um, me and some of the guys
from the RROTC are having a chow-down.
But I'll see you at school tomorrow?
Moose, are you ashamed of me?
No, I just...
I'm with the guys.
I'll talk to you later.
- Will you play football with us, Mad Dog?
- Can't.
Warden says I got other business.
Who the hell are you to him?
Before this place...
[Mad Dog sighs]
I had a mom.
A little brother.
A girl, too.
Liz. [chuckles]
They used to come visit
me every Saturday.
One day the warden tells me
I can't see them anymore.
They've been banned.
It's for my own good, he said.
That was two years ago.
That's not right.
Next month,
they'll transfer me to a real prison,
where I'll spend the next 20 years.
You got a life after this.
A girl.
Don't let them take that away from you.
Let's go, Mad Dog.
Good luck with the game, Archie.
[Jughead grunting]
Wow.
Dilton really was a
hardcore survivalist.
I'll go first.
Good God.
It's like the inside
of a Philip K. Dick novel.
I think this is all...
that game they were playing.
Yeah, Gryphons & Gargoyles.
Looks like Ben and Dilton
were in pretty deep.
I wonder if Ethel was playing with them.
Jug.
Is it the thing
that came at us last night?
Yeah, the Gargoyle King?
He's also featured on this copper coin.
Betty.
Oh, God.
"Drink from the correct cup."
Blue lips, cyanide.
It was a challenge.
Part of that stupid
game they're playing.
Pick the chalice that's not poisoned,
and...
win, I guess?
So, it was suicide?
Maybe.
Or something even more insidious.
[screaming]
- Know how worried your folks are?
- Doesn't matter.
I'm supposed to hide,
until Master Doiley comes back.
Jeez.
Kid, haven't you heard?
Dilton's not coming back.
- That's a lie.
- [Betty] No. It's not.
Dilton is...
dead.
I'm sorry.
You played Gryphons & Gargoyles
with Dilton?
I was his apprentice. He was teaching me
so I could join the game.
With Ben Button,
and Ben's girlfriend Ethel Muggs?
Yes, but Princess Etheline isn't dating
Ben in real life, only in the game.
She warned me two enemies
might invade the bunker.
Okay, well, game's over.
All right?
I'm gonna get you back to your folks.
Then we need to pay another visit
to Princess Etheline.
[bell ringing]
[all shouting and cheering]
Down.
Set, hut.
[groans]
- Not so fun without the pads, huh?
- No, this is great.
Holy hell.
It's about to get a whole lot better.
[chuckles]
Who the hell is that?
That's my girl.
[rock music playing on speakers]
♪ [singing] The warden threw a party
In the county jail ♪
♪ The prison band was there
And they began to wail ♪
♪ The band was jumping
And the joint began to swing ♪
♪ You should've heard
The knocked-out jailbirds sing ♪
♪ Let's rock ♪
♪ Everybody, let's rock ♪
♪ Everybody in the whole cell block ♪
♪ Was dancing to the Jailhouse Rock ♪
♪ Number 47 said to number three ♪
♪ "You're the cutest jailbird
I ever did see ♪
♪ I sure would be delighted
With your company ♪
♪ Come on and do
The Jailhouse Rock with me" ♪
♪ Let's rock ♪
♪ Everybody, let's rock ♪
♪ Everybody in the whole cell block ♪
♪ Was dancing to the Jailhouse Rock ♪
♪ Spider Murphy
Played the tenor saxophone ♪
♪ Little Joe was blowing
On the slide trombone ♪
♪ The drummer boy from Illinois
Went crash, boom, bang ♪
♪ The whole rhythm section
Was the Purple Gang ♪
♪ Let's rock ♪
♪ Everybody, let's rock ♪
♪ Everybody in the whole cell block ♪
♪ Was dancing to the Jailhouse Rock ♪
Why are you here?
Warden Norton is a friend,
and a business associate.
He told me about this little game,
and invited me to come see it.
- And you had nothing better to do.
- As disrespectful as you're being,
I won't let you flush your life
down the drain for a boy, a criminal.
And I think you'll find that after today,
you won't be allowed to visit Archie.
I get it.
Warden Norton is in your pocket.
Everyone is in your pocket.
Except for me and Archie.
You won't keep us apart. But right now,
I need to cheer my boyfriend to victory,
so, excuse me.
♪ Was dancing to the Jailhouse Rock ♪
♪ Dancing to the Jailhouse Rock ♪
[all cheering]
Down. Set, hut.
- Stop the riot.
- [alarm buzzes]
Stop the riot.
Move.
Go, go.
It's an ambush. Everybody, run.
[all grunting and shouting]
Archie!
Let go of him!
Wait.
What's happening?
Where's Mad Dog? His stuff?
Oh, you didn't hear?
Mad Dog died in the riot.
The one you started.
No, that's impossible.
Mad Dog wasn't even there.
- It'll never end with him, will it?
- Daddy Dearest, you mean?
He's obsessed
with keeping me and Archie apart.
I can't even go visit him anymore.
Apparently he put my name
on a do-not-admit list.
Get a new name.
Before leaving on my iconic road trip
to California with Toni,
Reggie got us fake IDs,
to get into the Viper Room.
He'd hook you up, too.
You blew us off, Ethel.
And you knew where the missing Scout
was, and didn't say anything to anyone.
- Also, you and Ben aren't really dating.
- Yes, we are. We're in love.
No, Ethel, you were playing a game.
Role-playing.
That's what you don't get.
It was more real than you'll understand.
Ethel, we're trying to help you,
but you have to stop lying.
- I'm not lying.
- Okay.
Let's go to the sheriff's station.
You can put that truth on record
to Sheriff Minetta.
Look, if any of us talk to any grown-ups,
he's gonna get very, very angry.
Who, Ethel?
Look what happened to Dilton.
He tried to talk to you, then he...
[Betty] Ethel?
Ethel?
Oh, my God.
- She's having a seizure.
- Call an ambulance.
- Weatherbee!
- Ethel.
It's okay.
- Help is coming, okay?
- Yeah, hi. Uh...
We have a girl that's having a seizure,
at Riverdale High. Send an ambulance.
You've got ten minutes.
Hello, Archie.
My name is Monica Posh.
I'm with Riverdale's chapter
of the Innocence Project
I'll be working
to get you out of this place.
Welcome, Cadets, to the RROTC.
Excuse me, Major Mason?
My name's Kevin Keller.
Hope it's not too late to join.
Keller. You Tom Keller's boy?
- I am, sir.
- [Mason] Hell.
Tom and I were in the RROTC together,
back in the day.
Come on in, son.
Take a seat. We'll get started.
[man] Open it.
You caused quite the
commotion in my yard.
You sent three of my
men to the infirmary.
Where's Mad Dog, warden?
Captain Golightly said he died
in the riot,
when he wasn't even there.
What did you do to him?
Save that righteous anger, young man.
You're going to need it.
You impressed me today.
- Proved you have what it takes.
- What's happening?
You've been tapped.
You're gonna be my new Mad Dog.
Some of you know why we're here.
And some of us are sworn enemies.
But we made a vow in high school.
Now that the Scout is back,
safe and sound, thank God...
we can only assume
that he'll start talking,
and that whatever he says
might lead back to us.
To the secret that we buried,
all those years ago.
Why are you talking about this?
This hasn't been made public yet, Fred,
but Dilton Doiley and Ben Button...
were found in the woods with blue lips.
Dilton is dead.
Ben is in a coma.
Don't you keep Sheriff Minetta
on a short leash?
- Can't you just make this all go away?
- We control Minetta, yes.
- Jughead found the body.
- That's the concern.
We talked with Jughead and Betty,
told them to stop.
But you know how crazy our kids can be.
We made a pact
to never revisit that night.
Not to mention it,
not to even think about it.
- My vote is we stick to that.
- We might not have that luxury, Tom.
Not if it's happening again.
Not if it's our children.
All our children.
They're in danger.
[Betty] Mrs. Muggs said Ethel's resting.
It just doesn't make sense, Jug.
It can't be a coincidence,
but seizures aren't contagious.
So... what? What is it?
Sounds like another mystery
for us to solve.
If you're up for it.
I am.
And maybe it's the same one.
Maybe there's a connection
between the seizures
and whatever happened to Dilton, and...
Do you wanna check on Ben
while we're here?
Ben?
[Jughead] Ben.
Hey, what are you doing?
Come away from the window.
It's okay. Everything's okay.
I know.
I know it is.
I'm gonna be with Dilton now.
We both flipped the coin.
He was scared to ascend, but I'm not.
What about...?
What about your Princess Etheline, huh?
We'll be reunited.
In the Kingdom.
One day, all of us will.
It's all part of his plan.
- You'll see.
- Ben.
Soon.
- You'll fly, too.
- [Betty] Ben, no!
[glass breaking, car alarm wailing]