Previously on Riverdale...
I'm Cassidy.
We're gonna take what we want
and then we're gonna go.
If you tell me
you're going to Shadow mines...
I am.
Those guys would still be alive
if I wasn't in the picture.
Andrews, the warden wants to see you.
Killing that boy at Shadow Lake. You
have no one to blame but yourself.
The warden from that
juvie killed himself last night.
I saw you with Hiram Lodge.
You're testing his drugs out on patients.
Why?
I only answer to one authority, Betty.
Let's convince them to escape.
Let's give them the opposite of the
Gargoyle King, which is the Gryphon Queen.
The King is dead.
You're all free.
Betty, what are we going to do
with all these kids?
They have nowhere to go.
The bounty on your pal Archie
is why you got to cut him loose.
I'm not just gonna ditch Archie, Mom.
Your mom's right, Jug.
Wherever I go next,
it's got to be alone.
Arch, we'll get
you a ride to the border.
I know a guy up there
who can help.
Town's under quarantine.
Governor's orders.
No one in or out.
What hero's journey would be
complete without a self-imposed exile?
Witness Archie Andrews.
Just as Luke Skywalker
went to planet Dagobah,
so, too, has Archie been
in the Canadian hinterlands,
wondering what dark demons
he would have to conquer
before being able, finally, to go home.
And speaking of home,
since Riverdale's quarantine,
the crime rate in town had risen.
There had been, for instance,
a series of daring cat burglaries.
You make an extremely sexy
Robin Hood, T.T.
Stealing from the rich
to give to, well, us.
You're so crazy.
I love you.
It's been five weeks since we
were cut off from the rest of the world.
The quarantine's been lifted,
but the town still hasn't
gotten its pep back.
Blossom, Topaz, break it up.
Bite me, Moose.
It's one of the new school rules, Cheryl,
all physical contact
must be kept to a minimum.
Well, that doesn't make any sense.
There haven't been
any seizures for weeks,
and everything tested
has come back negative.
The RROTC doesn't make the rules, Toni.
No, you just enforce them like
the crypto-fascists you are.
Come on, T.T.
And though above ground,
Riverdale was a haunted shell
of its former self,
underground,
at Veronica's La Bonne Nuit,
life was beautiful.
Cheryl, Toni!
Welcome, ladies.
I've got your usual table waiting for you.
- Merci, madame.
- Enjoy.
What's the good word, Reginald?
The kegs are tapped out.
We've got more empty bottles than full.
Hell, even your mocktails
are selling out tonight.
It's nuts.
- What was that?
- No, not again.
Just go back to sleep, Jug.
Pray that that didn't wake up my mom.
He's coming.
The Gargoyle King, he's coming to kill me!
Hannah, hey, hey.
No, he's not, Hannah.
It was just a bad dream, okay?
That's all over, remember?
The Gargoyle King is dead.
The Gryphon Queen, she slayed him.
She saved us.
Exactly, Tyler.
Okay, but since we're up, can we play?
Please, Betty,
it really does make us feel better.
- Please, Betty.
- Please.
Okay, just one quick round
and then back to bed.
What is this?
Who does this belong to?
- Huh?
- They're Tyler's.
He's been taking them.
Tyler...
Where did you get
the Fizzle Rocks?
An unnamed Serpent
dealing Fizzle Rocks?
Are you sure this kid wasn't lying?
If it was a lie, Tyler came
up with it pretty quickly.
A Serpent dealing Hiram Lodge's
drugs like we're one of his gangs.
This is my fault.
I was gone for too long.
I left the Serpents high and dry.
I left you high and dry.
No, you were protecting Archie.
Yeah, and while I was busy
protecting the Red Paladin,
Hiram made a play for the
entire town and he got it.
Fizzle Rocks are everywhere.
Weatherbee's running Riverdale
High like it's a police state.
We don't even have
an elected sheriff yet.
Quarantine. Why would he
want the town quarantined?
It can't just be because he wants
to expand his candy business
and make more money, can it?
Hiram was paying the Sisters to test
out his drugs on the patients there.
I don't see how he could
possibly get away with that.
Attorney McCoy and I are just trying to get
Sister Woodhouse and the rest of her nuns
to rat him out, and we're close, I think.
Oh, God, could you imagine
Hiram Lodge finally paying for his crimes,
brought down by the testimony of nuns?
Well, maybe that means
Archie could come back home.
Wherever he is.
This is KDK 12 calling KDK 1.
Over.
This is KDK 1.
How are things looking in
your neck of the woods? Over.
Same as the last few weeks,
quiet and clear. Over.
Glad to hear it. Still thinking about
staying on for another rotation,
or are you ready to leave
the wilderness behind? Over.
I might sleep on it.
I'm still figuring things out.
I'm not sure if I'm ready to go back yet.
Copy that. Oh, we've been
getting some bear sightings.
So stay vigilant while you're
clearing the trails. Over.
Will do, ma'am.
Over and out.
Come on.
Shoot.
What the hell, man?
Veronica Lodge
hasn't paid what she owes.
Let go of me!
I'm sorry that this happened, Reggie.
With my father breathing down our necks,
I suppose it was only a matter of time.
Sorry.
Every time I make a beer run across
the border, I've been changing it up.
Never taking the same road twice.
He got lucky.
Daddy made it very clear
that if La Bonne Nuit was to continue
operating in a post-quarantine Riverdale,
I'd have to give him 10% of
my earnings for the privilege.
If you start paying him for protection now,
you'll never stop.
But there are ways to minimize that price.
5% feels fair.
And once Daddy reviews
these well-cooked books,
he'll be none the wiser.
Has anyone ever told you
you're a badass?
Hey, hey, Vegas.
It's okay. We'll go this way.
Come on.
Come on, Vegas.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
This is KDK 12 calling KDK 1.
KDK 12 to KDK 1.
Do you read me?
This is KDK 1.
We're receiving you. Over.
I need help.
I've been attacked.
By a grizzly.
I'm in bad shape.
How severe are
your injuries? Over.
- It's bad.
- Stay calm. Help is on the...
You're cutting out.
Apply pressure, and are you
able to dress your wound?
Hello? Hello?
Damn it!
It's okay, boy.
They said they're on their way.
We just gotta stay calm.
Good boy.
Good boy, Vegas.
I am exhausted, Betty.
We don't have the resources
to shelter these children.
But the farm does.
Mom, no.
Well, they can't stay here.
Can this please just wait
until after the trial?
The only reason they left the Sisters
is because I convinced them to trust me.
They've imprinted on me.
I'm their Gryphon Queen.
Fine.
But as their queen, they are
your responsibility, not mine.
So, let me get this straight.
Regardless of the fact that
the Sisters abused children
and tested Hiram Lodge's drugs on them,
which is why they're in jail,
awaiting trial,
their lawyer doesn't
want us to harass them?
It gets worse.
I told Sowerberry that we'd
give the Sisters immunity
if they agreed to testify against Hiram.
He informed me that the nuns
had taken a vow of silence.
So what if I testify?
You already admitted that you were
all on drugs while at the Sisters,
drugs that caused hallucinations.
I know what I saw.
I believe you, Betty.
But a jury won't.
I like to give people
the benefit of the doubt.
I like to believe they can change.
But you never do, Daddy.
If this is about the attack
on your delivery truck,
I only know what I've heard,
that someone sent the Gargoyle
Gang to apply pressure to you.
World's gotten scary
these last few weeks.
Well, I'm ready to face reality.
I need protection,
and you're the only person
who's offering it.
It's nothing to be ashamed of, mija.
15%, drop in the bucket.
And no gargoyles will mess
with your contraband again.
Unfortunately, business has been slow.
- Hmm.
- How does 5% sound?
Really?
Because Leo and Nico tell me
that your parking lot's
been packed every night.
Right, guys?
Well, well,
new coat, new capos, you're
walking tall these days.
Hope those nuns in jail
don't crack under pressure
and start talking about how
you were their candy man.
All right, I'll settle for 10%
but I need to see your books.
Naturally.
Josie's sounding incredible these days.
Only the best at La Bonne Nuit.
All right, Serpents,
it's come to my attention that one
of us has been dealing Fizzle Rocks.
Slinging dope is not
what Serpents do.
So from this moment on,
we're going clean.
There'll be no selling or doing drugs.
No crime of any kind will be tolerated.
Anyone that breaks the
Serpent code will be exiled.
Permanently.
I think it's pretty ridic
that you vanish for a month on
some vision quest with your bestie,
only to return and lecture us
about responsibility.
We got no money coming in, Jug.
I mean, how are we
supposed to eat, survive?
We'll figure it out and get
back to you, Fangs. All of you.
In the meantime,
"In unity, there is strength."
In unity, there is strength.
Go away!
I'm so, so sorry
this happened to you, Josie.
I'm paying someone
a lot of money to make sure
this exact sort of thing doesn't happen.
They were from your
father's gang, weren't they?
You know, whatever problems
you've got with him,
I can't be dragged into them, Veronica.
Either you get this mess
straightened out,
or La Bonne Nuit finds itself
a new headliner.
They helped me.
Gave me freedom,
gave me back my life.
At the farm, you won't be
the only ones doing chores.
Everybody's equal.
Um, Polly? Evelyn?
The hell's going on?
Mom called. She said that
you had your hands full.
Want a T-shirt?
Um, no, and neither do they.
Guys, don't take anything
from these two vampires, okay?
They're bribing you.
Betty doesn't know
what she's saying.
When I escaped the Sisters, the
farm became my salvation, my family.
Okay, as your Gryphon Queen,
I promise to protect you
and keep you safe.
And trust me, the farm is not safe.
Not safe? Did you tell them how
the Gargoyle King and his henchmen
broke into this house
and terrorized you and Mom?
What about these drugs we found here?
How can you be protecting
them if you're allowing them
to put these dangerous
chemicals into their bodies?
I didn't know. I don't know
how they're getting them.
They're too scared to tell
you because you're a Serpent.
But they told us.
A Serpent dealer named Fangs Fogarty.
If you were hard
up, you could've talked to me.
The quarantine happened, I needed money.
You were gone.
Well then, you could've talked to me.
And what do you need money for?
My mom's sick.
She's got treatments
that we can't pay for.
You're like a brother to me, Fangs.
We could've helped you.
I was ashamed.
So you started dealing Fizzle Rocks?
And where'd you get it, the Gargoyle Gang?
I'm out now?
The punishment for breaking
this code is immediate exile.
However, you'd had
a rougher year than most.
I'm willing to look
the other way just this once,
but this has to stay between us, okay?
- And if I catch you dealing drugs again...
- You won't.
I'm done.
Is that...
A Glamourge egg, worth more than the
GNP of most developing countries.
Why, yes, Kitty Cat, it is.
Okay, let's go.
Wait, T.T.
I'm feeling particularly brazen tonight.
Cassidy.
Good. You're awake.
Time to play.
This isn't real.
You guys are all dead.
You keep saying that but then how
are we here, talking with you?
I'm dreaming.
I must be, or I'm hallucinating
from the loss of blood.
Or we're here and this is real.
No. I went to juvie
after being framed for
your murder, Cassidy.
I found you three in the mines after
Sheriff Minetta gunned you down.
If what you say is true,
then we are dead.
And it sounds like
it's all your fault.
If you ever want to return to Eldervair,
you're gonna have to play and win.
Come on.
One round at least.
One round.
Any luck, Ms. Weiss?
I'm on the phone with Child
Services nonstop, Betty.
But...
But it's gonna be hard
getting the kids you're
housing adopted or fostered.
There's concern about the
emotional trauma they've suffered.
Yeah, well, the Sisters
really did a number on them.
Any luck getting the Sisters
to testify against Hiram Lodge?
They've taken a vow of silence.
It's part of their religion.
- Religion?
- Mmm-hmm.
Betty,
as a social worker, I've had dealings
with the Sisters over the years.
And there's something you need to know
about their affiliation with the church.
Josie was stalked, Daddy,
by those gargoyles of yours.
So tell me, if I'm paying you
10% for protection
why is my headliner getting harassed?
Because you had the audacity
to try to deceive me.
Cooking the books, that's
the move of a rank amateur.
Now, I want the full amount
that's owed me.
Oh, and your mother's
Glamourge egg that was stolen.
Come again?
One of your Serpent school
chums broke into our apartment
and stole your mother's bauble.
And based on
the calling card they left,
I'm guessing
it's probably Cheryl Blossom.
Anyway, get it back for me, won't you?
Why is this my responsibility?
Because you have
more to lose than me.
You need to fix this, Jughead.
If Cheryl took the egg,
why did you come to me?
Why didn't you just
go directly to her?
She's dodging my phone calls.
Besides, aren't you her king?
Since when are you
and your father aligned?
We're not. He's squeezing me,
he's squeezing my business.
Now, not only does he
have me paying him protection,
he's got me on this wild-goose chase
to get my mom's stolen egg back.
You're paying your father
protection money?
Against his very own
Gargoyle Gang.
What if you were to pay less money
not to be in business with him?
What are you suggesting?
Let the Serpents come work for you.
You get real protection
from your father's goons
and the Serpents get jobs with a
steady income. This is a win-win.
Get me that Glamourge egg back
and we have an accord.
It's your turn, Red.
"Defeat the Hooded Spectre of Death."
Go on.
The challenge reveals the weakness,
the weakness is
what keeps you from winning.
Give me your wallet!
I did it.
Now am I finished playing this game?
The Red Paladin returns.
Warden Norton?
Take a load off, my boy.
We're just getting started.
I'm not playing the game
with someone who died from it.
I didn't die.
I ascended to the Kingdom.
And what about Joaquin?
Did he ascend, too?
That was his reward
for stabbing me, wasn't it?
That was the card
Mr. DeSantos drew,
his do-or-die moment.
You know all about those,
don't you, Archie?
Did you have one yourself?
With the Black Hood?
Yes.
And I stopped him, but I'm
still trapped here in this hell.
Then that wasn't the moment,
the place and time
where it all went wrong.
Roll the dice
and you may find the path
that leads back to Eldervair.
We know your secret,
Sister Woodhouse.
The church disbanded the Sisters of
Quiet Mercy during the Vatican II
over allegations of cruel
and inhumane practices.
You and your sisters haven't
been nuns for more than 60 years.
Which means your vow of
silence won't hold up in court.
So here's a new deal.
Testify against Hiram Lodge
and I won't have you charged
with the following crimes,
child endangerment, illegal
drug testing, human trafficking.
Fine.
What do I need to do?
Swear in court that Hiram Lodge
gave you money and drugs
for illegal testing.
Then you'll have immunity.
Serpents, earlier today,
I brokered a deal.
I got us a paid gig.
From here on out, we'll be working
security detail for Veronica Lodge,
her speakeasy and her employees.
Long live the Serpents! Whoo!
Settle down.
I know it's good news for a change,
but I've also gathered us here
for less celebratory reasons.
Cheryl, Toni,
- come up here.
- Excuse me?
- What did we do?
- You broke into the Lodge apartment
and stole a Glamourge egg.
So what if we did?
Well, more than that,
you left your calling card,
attaching yourself,
and by extension,
all of the Serpents
to your crime.
I'm not afraid of Lodge.
What's he gonna do,
call the sheriff?
Oh, right, there is no sheriff.
Cheryl, that's not the point.
You broke the code.
Turn in your jackets and go.
Are you serious, Jones?
I'm a Serpent by blood.
You can't take that away from me.
You hypocrite.
You give your drug-dealing buddy
Fangs a pass but you crucify us?
And in case you were
wondering how we know,
- Fangs told Sweet Pea, who told me.
- Who told me.
If you're asking for our jackets,
shouldn't you be asking for his as well?
Jug.
You're right.
- Fangs, give me your jacket.
- Hey, what the hell, man?
It's okay, Sweet Pea.
Some leader you are.
Fangs.
Cheryl, Toni.
We'll go but we're
keeping our jackets.
Fine, but I need that egg back.
- Come again?
- You need to give me that damn egg
or Veronica won't give us
the protection contract.
Why the hell would I care?
I'm not a Serpent anymore.
Because I believe that you
still have honor, Cheryl.
And it's getting cold out.
And the rest of us don't get
to go back to Thistlehouse.
Well done, Torombolo.
Cost me a lot to get that ugly thing back.
So make sure you put it to good use.
Oh, don't you worry.
I shall.
And in the meantime, you and the
Serpents have your first assignment.
You ever hear of the Gargoyle Gang?
Tyler, what the
hell happened to you?
You lied to us.
What do you mean?
I would never.
You said he was dead,
but I saw him.
I saw the Gargoyle King.
Oh, my God.
What? Where?
Fox Forest.
He was there with other
gargoyles, his gang.
They beat me up.
The Gryphon Queen is a liar.
And if she lied about the
Gargoyle King being dead,
maybe she lied when
she says we're safe here.
No, I'm not.
You have to believe me.
The Sisters are going to
testify against the Man in Black
and then you will all be safe.
Where, Betty?
Where will we be safe?
It's your turn, Red Paladin.
Go on.
Pick your Quest Card.
What does it say?
"Kill the Gargoyle King."
Are you sure?
Read it again.
"Kill the Man in Black."
You have your marching orders.
Slay the dragon.
Good luck.
The Gargoyle King.
The Man in Black.
How many names do you have, Hiram?
I know why you've come.
Do you genuinely think killing
me will solve all your problems?
It's what I should have done that night.
In here. My do-or-die moment
before you had me arrested.
Yeah, it was awfully stupid
of you to come in here,
threaten me, tell me all your plans.
I mean, what was I supposed to do,
not have you arrested?
Put that down, Archie.
You're not gonna...
I don't understand.
What are you guys doing here?
I thought...
I thought it was over.
You're almost done.
Just one last round to play.
Have you been working
on any new songs, Arch?
I'd love to hear some of them.
Betty, I haven't played guitar in forever.
I'm not the same person anymore.
I don't wanna do this.
I don't wanna play with you guys.
You have to.
It's the only way back.
Back to what?
Eldervair.
Riverdale.
Innocence.
Come on, Arch.
Time to play.
Thanks for meeting
me at such short notice.
A lot of the freed patients
from the Sisters of Quiet Mercy
have been orphaned or disowned.
My mom and I have been housing
them but that is becoming
untenable.
So if any of you are willing
or able to take a few in,
just until the Sisters have testified
against Hiram and he's behind bars...
I could take, you know,
some of the boys in.
And with Archie gone, I have the room.
I've saved many children from that
particular circle of hell before
and I'm happy to do it again.
Nana and I will board some
of the girls at Thistlehouse.
And we have a pullout here.
I'll house a couple.
Thank you.
What about this deal with the Lodges?
It's with Veronica,
it's not with the Lodges.
She's still a Lodge, boy,
don't you ever forget it.
You know, as I recall, you
worked for the Lodges once.
Does trashing that drive-in
ring any bells?
I want you to be
a better king than me.
Make us players instead of pawns.
That's what I'm trying to do, Dad.
Put me in.
I'm tired of sitting on the sidelines.
I'm not made for it.
We gotta stop meeting like this.
Shut your mouth.
Trash the cargo, all of it.
I... I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
- Let's go! Come on.
- It's an ambush!
Get 'em!
I tried to tell you.
Pick him up.
I want you to go back to your Gargoyle King
or your Man in Black or Hiram Lodge,
and I want you to tell him
that Veronica Lodge is now
under the protection of the Serpents
and that Riverdale has not fallen.
Go.
Mom?
Where are they?
Where are the kids?
After that one was attacked,
I called Edgar and asked him for advice.
And he came and took them to the farm.
Edgar did?
You only missed him by like five minutes.
It's your turn, Archie.
You have to pick a Quest Card.
Is this the last level?
Sure feels like it, doesn't it?
You don't have to do this, son.
He's the one who got me into this trouble.
Not the Black Hood,
not the Gargoyle King, not Hiram Lodge.
Him. It's the only way.
You could forgive him.
It's too late.
You are not the villain you think you are.
I've hurt everyone.
There's always another path home, son.
Not for me.
If I ever want to go
back to Riverdale again,
I have to destroy that part of me.
It's weak, it's bad, it's stupid.
Just come home, Archie.
I can't, Dad.
I have to do this one thing first.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry for letting you down.
Archie, wait.
Fangs, my dad and I were talking.
We wanna give you
another shot at redemption.
- What are you thinking?
- We want you to go undercover.
Join the Gargoyle Gang.
We need a man on the inside of
Hiram Lodge's drug operation
so that we can take him down.
Are you in?
It'd be an honor.
Attorney McCoy, I was just reviewing
our questions for the Sisters.
Don't bother, Betty.
The Sisters are gone.
Gone? How?
An anonymous donor
posted their bail.
Hiram Lodge.
And they took off
who knows where.
But not before leaving a message.
We go to join thee.
Does that mean anything to you?
Oh, my God.
I think I know where they went.
Come on, kid.
Come on, wake up.
Wake up, kid!
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==