Previously on Riverdale:
Tall Boy? We know
you're working for Hiram.
Why would he want the town quarantined?
- Apparently there was a mass seizure.
- Seizures aren't contagious.
So, what?
There's nowhere he won't follow me.
It's over?
You will stoop to any level
to get me back in your clutches.
I just wanted some father-daughter time.
Claudius Blossom.
You may not be the Man in Black,
but his stink is on you.
Sheriff Minetta's body was found
in the marsh last night.
It was decapitated.
No, Tall Boy was just trying to escape.
It was an accident.
As far as anyone knows,
Tall Boy's been exiled.
Riverdale,
once a safe, decent, innocent place,
had become Noir Town,
like the setting
of a Raymond Chandler story,
filled with dames to kill for,
postmen who like to ring twice,
and more mobsters
than a Scorsese retrospective
at the Bijou.
We were a town of lost souls.
Each of us wrestling with demons.
Each of us with secrets
we were trying to keep.
Mine was on the large side.
Six-foot-five to be exact.
Explain it to me once more.
We drove him to the bus station
at gunpoint,
- got him on a bus out of town.
- He murdered Joaquin.
You thought putting him on a bus
was enough punishment?
- I don't buy it.
- I made a decision.
I'm sorry you don't agree, but he's gone.
I'll pretend
like I believe you idiots for now.
I got my hands full
finding Hiram's would-be assassin.
Next time you see me, have a better story.
I was covering up the death
of a wicked man.
But Tall Boy Petite wasn't
the only fresh corpse in Noir Town.
Claudius Blossom had taken the big sleep,
and my girlfriend, Betty Cooper,
had murder on the brain.
And murderers, in Betty's world,
needed to be brought to justice.
It's infuriating, Dad.
The Lodge Ledger is calling
Claudius Blossom's death a suicide,
- but I think he was murdered.
- But if he ingested cyanide--
But how did it get in his prison cell?
A gift from his former partner-in-crime
Penelope, I'm guessing?
Poison does suit her.
Subtle, elegant.
But if nobody else is asking questions
about Claudius' death,
why are you?
Because it's black and white,
and wrong, Dad.
Penelope's been killing people for years.
She's literally getting away with murder.
Daryl Doiley was poisoned with oleander,
which is something only the Blossoms grow.
Featherhead, poisoned.
The nuns, poisoned.
And now Claudius.
I just can't prove any of it.
It's like she's committed
the perfect murders.
You've already found the pattern,
murders disguised as suicides.
Who else has died by suicide
near Penelope?
Think now.
Clifford.
But he hung himself.
Perhaps.
I wonder, though,
if that's the whole story.
Who was there that night?
Penelope.
And Cheryl.
If there's a witness,
it's not a perfect murder.
Meanwhile, Archie Andrews
no longer felt hunted by Hiram Lodge,
but he was still haunted.
Trapped in that in-between place,
avoiding his destined face-to-face
with the Man in Black,
Archie struggled,
searching for a sense of purpose.
What's going on, son?
- Is it your breakup with Veronica?
- No, Dad, it's not...
I've been thinking.
Maybe college isn't for me.
Maybe I can work with you
in the construction company again.
Well, there's no shame in hard work,
son, but where's this coming from?
After the crap I've seen
these last few months,
I just wanna get out of my head,
work with my hands,
try and make peace with things.
If you're serious about it,
you better get your butt in gear.
Shift starts in about an hour.
The only thing
Archie knew for sure: he was angry.
And hitting things made it better.
Meal break, boys.
Andrews.
This is a union crew.
You need to take your mandatory break.
Stop working.
When I say stop, you stop.
Back off. I don't need a break.
You don't want to do this, kid.
I got you by about 100 pounds.
That's it.
I don't care if you are Fred's kid.
- You're off my crew!
- The hell I am!
With Hiram laid up
in the hospital clinging to life,
there was blood in the water,
and sharks were closing in
on the mobster's daughter, Veronica Lodge.
From my family to yours.
While I love a grand gesture, Elio,
- diamonds are a girl's best friend.
- These are for your father.
I heard he's still in the hospital,
and I wanted to come here personally
- to tell you I'm praying he pulls through.
- Well, to paraphrase Samuel Clemens,
reports of his death
have been greatly exaggerated.
The vultures are circling, Veronica.
They're eager to swoop in
on his territory.
Talking about yourself?
I'm offering some friendly advice.
Jobs like the hit on your father,
it's very rare they go unfinished.
Yes, we all had our problems.
The town was drowning in them.
A good-looking one was about
to walk through my door.
Nice hat, Bacall.
I've got a job for you, Jones.
I want you...
to find out who shot my father.
You'll get the other half
when you give me their name.
That is a big job.
Half the people in this town wanna
see your old man kick the maple barrel.
- No offense.
- None taken.
I'll give you your first suspect.
My mother. A few weeks ago,
I overheard my parents arguing.
It was right before the quarantine,
after I had my seizure.
No. I supported you.
- You swore that this wouldn't happen.
- What is going on?
My mother was berating my father.
Something about breaking a promise.
- What if you don't like what I find?
- I'm a big girl.
I can take it.
Well, then...
Consider me your Philip Marlowe.
I didn't mind playing detective,
especially for this price.
But if I'd known then and there
where this investigation would lead me,
I never would've taken the money.
- To what do I owe the pleasure?
- I'll just get right to it, Madam Mayor.
- You shoot your husband?
- Excuse me?
- I love my husband.
- Uh-huh. But did you shoot him?
I hear not all is well at The Pembrooke.
Records and witnesses will attest,
I was on the phone with Hiram
when he was shot,
picking up lunch at Pop's.
What were you and Hiram arguing about
when Veronica had a seizure?
Well, Mr. Jones, if you must know...
we fought
because I caught Hiram having an affair.
I had been suspicious for a while,
so, I had Sheriff Minetta follow him.
This was before he was butchered,
of course.
And he...
gave me these.
Now, I don't know who she is,
but they met regularly
at the Five Seasons.
But Hiram having another woman
is good motive to shoot him.
No, it isn't.
I simply asked him to end it, and he did.
I'm telling you this
because I have nothing to hide.
Keep those. I mean, who knows?
Maybe Hiram's mistress was angry
when he called it quits.
You do know how volatile blonds can be.
No. You're not going to the job site today
after you picked a fight yesterday.
I was trying to do my job.
It wasn't my fault. And then Vic--
Vic? Vic who has worked for me
for a very a long time?
- Who knows what he is doing?
- Fine. Whatever.
No. We're not done here, young man.
You wanna explain to me
how I found this in your bedroom?
You think you're the first kid
to take a drink in high school? No.
- This does not solve your problems.
- I'm out of here.
Fine. Take a walk. Clear your head.
While you're out there,
think about how you need to shape up!
We are gathered today
to mourn the passing of one of our own.
Betty.
Sweet, darling Betty.
You've come to pay your respects.
Well, Uncle Claudius was family, so...
Mourn with us, cousin.
Tragically, this ungrateful town never
welcomed Claudius to its bosom.
And I believe that is why
he committed the most cardinal of sins...
taking his own life.
Crocodile tears.
While I appreciate the company,
tell me,
what are you really doing here, Betty,
at our uncle's funeral?
I came to talk to you.
Cheryl, people connected to your mother
keep dying by poisoning,
or by strange suicides,
including your father.
My father...
hung himself in a barn, Betty.
He slipped a rope around his neck
and kicked a maple barrel out
from under him.
End of story.
Is everything okay?
Betty was being a gnat,
as usual, Tee-Tee.
- And I don't have any patience for it.
- Back off, Betty.
It's been a rough day.
Sweet Pea, Fangs.
Why bring me here? I'm on a case.
I heard the Gargoyle Gang is riled up.
They're looking for Tall Boy.
And as long as his body's down here,
it's a ticking time bomb.
Yeah, well,
it's too hot to move him right now.
Hey.
Let's not lose our heads.
Okay? Fangs,
I need you to stay here with Tall Boy.
And I need you to lock this place up.
I'm serious.
Sweet Pea,
you need to tail someone for me.
Nico, Leo.
We're in a crisis.
The mob underworld smells blood,
and we need to change the narrative.
Obscure the fact
that my father's down for the count,
and present a strong front.
- Too late.
- People are talking.
No one's seen the Man in Black.
No one's collecting the vig.
What? Why the hell not?
We should get out there
and start collecting, immediately.
Nico and I have been discussing options.
It might be in your family's best interest
to align with the Grandes.
You mean Elio's family?
- Not gonna happen.
- Your father took a bullet
two inches from his heart.
If we're not careful,
our next play could be our last.
I don't need you to mob-splain
what's best for my family.
Due respect, you're not being realistic.
Due respect, you're fired.
- Both of you.
- Seriously?
You're getting rid
of the only capos you have left?
The same two clowns who didn't
protect my dad from getting shot?
Yeah, no, we're good.
I consider you both inner circle.
Smithers, as my former doorman,
and Reggie,
as my jacked jack of all trades,
I asked you here
because I need people I can trust.
Our enemies are sensing weakness,
and we need to show strength.
Veronica, if I may...
There was a moment, back in the trenches,
when our numbers were greatly diminished.
We knew the enemy would storm
the barricade at any moment.
I collected the helmets from our dead,
and propped them atop our bayonets.
High enough so that they'd be visible
to our enemies and give them pause.
See, sometimes,
it's not what things are,
it's what they appear to be.
You've just given me an idea, Smithers.
But we're gonna need
your bus driver's cap.
So, who's this blond bombshell
that you're tracking?
Hiram's mistress.
He broke things off with her.
She may want revenge.
Concierge tipped me off about the floor,
but I wish they'd given me a room number.
Well, maybe there was no room number
to give.
- Thanks for coming with me, by the way.
- My pleasure.
My investigation is on hold
until I hear back from Dr. Curdle Junior.
Turns out,
there was no autopsy on Claudius.
Penelope had him cremated
before he could perform one.
I'm hoping there's something
in Clifford Blossom's autopsy report.
No one's home. Let's move on.
Would Bogart move on?
Let's just give it a try.
What kind of hotel room is unlocked?
And now apparently there's
a not-so-secret sex club in Riverdale.
Excuse me.
What is this place?
The Maple Club.
A safe place,
as long as you know the safe word.
You seen this woman? She come here?
You just scared off my client.
She doesn't work here,
but I see her around.
Try Room 311.
Laura, why did Mr. Arklight leave
in such a rush?
Why are you two here?
You know this is a private club. Get out.
You mean a brothel?
By the way, does the new sheriff know
there's a red light district in Riverdale?
My time is costly, children,
so, what do you want?
I knew you were an escort, Auntie,
but now you're exploiting other women?
These women aren't victims, Betty.
At The Maple Club,
it is the men who suffer.
We specialize in domination.
These ladies make enough
to start new lives.
Oh, please. You are only helping yourself.
And why shouldn't I?
No one else ever has.
When I was eight years old,
I was plucked
from the Sisters of Quiet Mercy
by the Blossom family.
You poisoned the Sisters
because they sold you to the Blossoms?
I didn't kill those nuns. And, anyway...
it was the so-called monsignor
who sold me,
- not the Sisters.
- Fine.
You didn't kill the fake nuns.
Did you kill Claudius?
- He committed suicide, so I was told.
- It's pretty convenient, don't you think?
Either way, I was right here
when the poor man died.
Ask any of my girls.
Fun fact of the day:
Penelope is the madam of a kink club.
Okay, her sob story
doesn't change the fact
that she's a stone-cold murderer.
Wanna check out Room 311?
I could use one of your bobby pins.
It's Curdle. Maybe he tracked down
Clifford's autopsy report.
And just like that,
you are back on the case.
- No rest for the wicked.
- Not in a wicked town.
See you later.
♪ Sooner or later
You're gonna be mine ♪
♪ Sooner or later you're gonna be fine ♪
♪ Baby, it's time... ♪
Reggie.
♪ I always get my man ♪
I think you've had enough, bud.
Let me get you a cab.
I'm a paying customer, Reggie.
- I'll leave when I'm ready to leave.
- Veronica's dealing with enough crap.
She doesn't need you making a scene.
Can I get another bartender
in here, please?
- Another bartender? Don't touch me.
- Let's go.
Hey, Toby. Toby.
It's okay. I know him.
He's our friend.
It's okay. I'll go.
- I'll go.
- I got him.
I got him. It's fine.
God.
Josie.
You can't tell Veronica about this.
Listen up, Andrews.
You are in free fall,
and I am not having it.
It's time for a literal, and metaphoric,
cold shower.
Wait. Wait, Josie, don't--
At the docks,
it was a classic con:
- Smoke and mirrors with a pretty girl.
- Collecting for Lodge.
- Where are Nico and Leo?
- No longer in our employ.
I'm Veronica.
I'm sure you know my father, Hiram Lodge.
He doesn't like to be kept waiting,
and neither do I.
See you next week.
Well played, Ms. Veronica.
Thank you, Smithers.
And you, too, Man in Black.
Apologies for the delay, Ms. Cooper,
but this one took some digging.
Clifford Blossom's wife requested
that there be no autopsy.
But my father was nothing
if not a curious man.
So, let me guess.
He performed one anyways?
What does it say?
That he died of asphyxiation by hanging?
There was bruising around the esophagus,
consistent with a hanging.
However...
there was also tetrodotoxin
in his bloodstream.
Puffer fish venom.
In Clifford's case,
the dose was almost certainly fatal.
So, you're saying Clifford
may not have died from hanging,
- but from being poisoned.
- I'm saying that
Clifford Blossom was already dead
when he hung himself.
And Betty Cooper thought, "Gotcha."
What's this?
Um, lemon, ginger, and cayenne.
Where is your dad?
He's at work.
I got canned on my first day,
so, I went to drown my sorrows.
Look, Archie.
I know we didn't talk much last year,
and I can't even attempt to guess
at the hell that you've been through.
And maybe all you can do now
is wallow in booze,
and pick fights.
But personally, I think you need
to channel your anger
into something constructive,
like music, maybe.
- Josie--
- Or...
if you're in the mood to hit things...
Kevin's dad boxes at the gym.
Either way, you've gotta deal
with your demons head-on.
I thought I did.
In the cabin, I thought I faced my demons.
And killed them.
And myself.
You're losing me.
You're right, Josie.
I gotta face this head-on.
And there's one person
I still haven't seen
since I've been back in Riverdale.
Archie, where are you going?
I'm going to face,
and kill, one last demon.
That's one thing
about being a crime boss:
You learn to never leave a paper trail.
But Hermione Lodge,
it seems, was out of practice.
What the hell is this, Mom?
I was entering today's take
into Daddy's ledger
when I noticed a shady collection
of invoices and receipts.
So, I dug a little deeper.
And Daddy's Fizzle Rocks empire?
You're a part of it, Mom.
No.
You ordered the quarantine.
You paid these invoices.
- It's your name in blood-red ink.
- No, Veronica.
I found out that your father
and Claudius were making drugs
in the new prison,
and at the Blossom Maple Factory,
so, I told him to shut it down.
I even helped him create a distraction,
so he could do it quickly and cleanly.
The quarantine.
It was a smoke screen.
But then, typical of your father,
he lied to me.
Instead of shutting it down,
he consolidated everything
into the prison. Believe me.
Veronica, I want no part of this.
We agree, then.
Let's end this nightmare.
Destroy the drugs,
and the means of production.
Burn it to the ground.
While Daddy can't lift a finger
to stop us.
Now, that is one option, yes.
Or we could sell it.
I already have a buyer lined up.
All-cash offer.
He's willing to take the drugs,
the lab, everything.
Shouldn't we get something in return
for all the pain he has caused us?
It's over, Auntie Blossom.
I know what you did.
I know what happened in the barn.
How you faked Clifford's hanging
and lied to the police.
And who is your witness? Cheryl?
Proof that you poisoned Clifford
with puffer fish venom.
You'll go to jail for this.
Won't be justice for everyone you killed,
but it's a good start.
You think you know what I've done,
but have you paused to consider why?
Because you're a serial killer,
a black widow.
The Red Dahlia, let's call you.
You poison people.
Not people, Betty.
Men.
I'm not admitting anything,
but they are the true poison.
Clifford killed my son.
Daryl was a Judas.
And Claudius...
I'm surprised
you're not thanking me for that.
Why would I thank you?
Because he caused your seizure.
He caused everyone's seizures.
Claudius was running
a Fizzle Rocks operation
from our once-distinguished maple factory,
and dumping the runoff
into Sweetwater River.
- Fizzle Rocks caused the seizures?
- No, Betty.
The runoff from the manufacturing
of the drug.
Not the drug itself.
But why did it only affect girls?
I am an herbalist, Betty,
not a medical doctor.
Tests on Sweetwater Reservoir
were ordered and faked.
But Claudius had every intention
of continuing
to poison the town with drugs,
so, it was fitting that poison be his end.
Just because someone is a horrible person
doesn't give you the right to kill them.
Doesn't it?
Isn't that what you did
with the poison that infected your home?
The imposter Chic?
Hal tells me things, too.
When you delivered Chic to the Black Hood,
you sent him to his death.
You're not so innocent, Betty.
And if you insist on turning me in,
I will gladly do the same to you.
And that is when Betty realized:
No one's innocent in Crime Town.
Certainly not
Hiram Lodge's mystery mistress.
What are you doing in my room?
That's a good question.
Here's another one.
Why's a water inspector got a gun?
I only wanna talk, Ms. Mulwray.
Who the hell are you?
How do you know my name?
It's the Glamourge Egg, right?
You shoot me, I'll drop it.
I've seen one of these before.
Hiram gives them as gifts.
Maybe in your case, payment.
And it costs more
than you'll make in a lifetime.
So, put it down before you break it.
Based on the things I found in your room,
here's what I know about you.
You're a health and sanitation inspector.
Must pay quite a bit
if you can afford the Five Seasons.
- Unless Hiram put you up.
- But I'm no kept woman.
I do a job, I get paid for it.
Report says you were sent
to investigate Riverdale's water supply.
Specifically,
Sweetwater River and Reservoir. Why?
Young women in town were having seizures.
I was sent in to help.
Brought in by Hiram Lodge.
He also make you write to Governor Dooley,
advising him
to support a town-wide quarantine?
You see, I'm confused,
because the letter says the water's dirty,
but the report says it's clean,
you either lied to the governor
or faked that report.
- Or both.
- You know what?
Break the egg if you want. I don't care.
Just get out of my room
before I call hotel security.
Why was Hiram faking
water test reports? What was he hiding?
What did any of this have to do
with who shot him?
Yeah.
I followed Hermione Lodge
like you asked. You better get out here.
Stay down, and keep quiet.
Is that...?
It can't be.
Sheriff Minetta's alive?
- Thought he was decapitated.
- Nope. From the sounds of it,
he and Hermione
have been having an affair for months.
- Wait, listen.
- There's too many people asking questions.
Which means,
our little outstanding problem,
you need to take care of tonight.
Now clear the decks.
Use your old sheriff's gun.
Then all signs will point to FP.
- They're talking about framing my dad.
- For what?
I have to figure it out and warn him.
Back in an eerily deserted
Riverdale General,
Archie Andrews was a man on a mission.
On a collision course
with his dark destiny.
After months of torment
at the hands of the Man in Black...
he was trying to bring a sorry chapter
in his life to a close...
the only way he knew how.
- I need to talk to you.
- There's something at the hospital.
No. You can't go there. It's a setup.
Hermione and Minetta-- He's alive.
They plotted together to kill Hiram Lodge.
- What?
- Yes.
They're going to finish the job tonight
and pin it on you.
- Minetta's alive?
- Dad, there is a lot you need to know.
I just got back from the coroner's office.
A week ago, the torso
of a Michael Minetta was found
without its head and hands.
But it wasn't Sheriff Minetta,
because I just saw him.
- He's very much alive.
- Oh, my.
- Someone must've made a grave mistake--
- Save it, Junior.
Who asked you to fake Minetta's death?
Hermione Lodge.
I saw Minetta and Hermione,
up at some secret love shack up north.
I heard them talking about setting you up.
She'll try to put Hiram's shooting on you.
You need to arrest them.
I can't do that.
Yeah, you can. You're the sheriff.
They've been trying to murder Hiram Lodge.
No.
No, they didn't.
I shot Hiram.
- What?
- Hermione came to me.
She wanted it done. And I...
I wanted revenge.
You think I forgot about Riot Night?
That son of a bitch came close
to getting you killed.
I've been biding my time,
waiting for the perfect opportunity.
If you and Hermione tried to kill Hiram,
why'd she appoint you sheriff?
Payment. It was my payment.
I was naive enough to think
the office of the sheriff would protect me
if Hermione got an itch
to double-cross me.
Guess I was wrong.
Guess it's lucky
that you have me in your corner.
I have a confession to make.
About Tall Boy.
There's a way
that I can solve both of our problems.
But we'll need Ms. Cooper's help.
I came here to end our story.
When we first met, I was a scared kid,
afraid that I could lose everything.
You took me under your wing,
taught me to use fear as a weapon.
And for a while, it worked.
But it also hurt people.
Of all the horrible things you've done,
you know what enrages me the most?
That after my father was shot
by the Black Hood,
and almost died in my arms,
you hired some stooge...
to take another shot at him, in our house.
Maybe it's time I balance the scales.
A shot for a shot.
FP. Alice.
- Hermione.
- What's going on here?
Perfect timing. We'll start the interview.
All right, FP, let's check the levels.
- What, I just start talking?
- Yeah.
Well, Madam Mayor,
I am pleased to announce
that we caught the man
who shot your husband.
You did?
- Who was it?
- Gerald Petite.
But you might know him as Tall Boy.
It seems that Hiram kept him alive
in a secret cabin in the north,
to carry out...
odd jobs for him.
Can you imagine that?
Tall Boy resisted arrest, got violent,
and unfortunately,
I was forced to discharge my sidearm.
He died on the way to the hospital.
Well, thank goodness it's over.
And so neatly, too.
You know,
I would love to interview you next.
Get your perspective as mayor,
and wife of the victim, of course.
That's a great idea, Alice.
It's important that the mayor and I both
go on the record about what happened.
Present a united front.
Don't you agree, Madam Mayor?
That we should be on the same page?
Yes.
I think we are.
I think my mom may have hired someone
to shoot my father,
so that she could make a profit
from the sale of his drug operation.
- Damn.
- I know.
So, we need to act fast.
Tonight we're gonna break into the prison,
find the drugs,
and destroy them, and the equipment,
before my mom sells everything.
Sounds a lot like the plot of Bad Boys II.
I'm in, Ronnie.
But why? If she's selling it--
I'll be damned
if my mom gets a payout for her crimes.
Archie? What happened?
- I gotta go.
- To meet Archie?
It's not what you think.
But can you handle our heist
on your own, Bad Boy?
Yeah.
- How is he?
- Alive, thanks to you.
But, Archie, what were you doing here?
I...
came looking for you.
Reggie may have told you
what happened at the speakeasy,
how I was acting like an ass.
I wanted to apologize. I wasn't myself.
- I haven't been for a while.
- I'm sorry, too.
That I ever thought for a second
that you shot him.
At some point, maybe I could have.
But I don't hate him anymore, Veronica.
He's awake.
And he wants see you.
And, Archie...
If you ever need a friend to talk to...
Archie Andrews.
Veronica told me what happened.
How I have you to thank for being alive.
We've been locked in battle for some time.
I never set out to be your enemy,
Mr. Lodge.
All I want is
to live in Riverdale in peace.
Well...
I see no reason for us to keep fighting.
So,
starting tonight...
I propose a truce.
You don't make a move against me,
and I won't make a move against you.
A life for a life.
- What are you gonna tell your mom and dad?
- I don't know.
Maybe the truth.
But probably not.
Meanwhile,
in case you'd forgotten,
Betty's encounter with Penelope
had shaken her worldview.
There was only one person
she could talk to about it.
Penelope's guilty.
I found proof that she poisoned Clifford.
My clever daughter.
What do you plan to do next?
I'm not sure.
I thought if I caught her,
I'd turn her in.
But hearing her talk,
seeing how she's living her life,
how she's been twisted...
I don't know, I feel almost feel...
Pity for her?
Penelope and I,
we're products of our environment,
raised by those
who taught us a twisted sense
of right from wrong.
Do you still believe that she's a monster
who deserves to be in here?
Maybe not every murderer is guilty.
And maybe not every victim is innocent.
Maybe it's not all black and white.
I wonder, Betty, if one day,
you'll ever be able to see me
in that same compassionate light.
Well, how you feeling, Red?
- Better.
- Good.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Setting me straight.
Sometimes we all need a little tough love.
I was thinking about your advice, too.
Doing something constructive.
- Would Mr. Keller talk to me about boxing?
- For sure he will.
And, uh, I was thinking,
maybe we could...
I don't know,
if you wanted to jam sometime, or...?
- Like the old days?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Let's do it.
But you're singing backup.
- Okay.
What the hell did you do?
I assume you're talking about the drugs.
Reggie and I burned them last night,
with the equipment.
But I told you I had a buyer lined up.
They paid in advance.
So, I saved you
from being a drug dealer, Mom.
- Might I suggest you offer them a refund?
- I can't, Veronica.
I used the cash
to pay off Governor Dooley.
To keep our names clean.
And now my buyer is coming,
and they are gonna want blood.
- You have no idea what you've just done.
- I know exactly what I did.
And I know what you did, Mom.
And I'm not the only one on your case.
You think you're really smart, don't you?
You have all the answers.
I know Hiram's mistress works
for the Sanitation Department
and doctored false water reports
for your husband.
I see.
Is that all?
No.
Not in the slightest.
Betty told me about the runoff
from the Fizzle Rocks manufactured
at the factory.
How it poisoned Sweetwater River,
gave everyone seizures.
That's why Hiram had
to doctor those reports.
To cover his ass.
It's also why he moved his drug lab
to the prison.
Away from the water supply.
Now, my guess is
that you were pissed about his drug lab
and what it was doing
to all the girls in the town.
Soon after, you hired my father
to shoot Hiram Lodge.
When that didn't work,
you tried to finish the job
in the hospital with Minetta
and a sheriff-issued pistol
so that you could pin it all on my dad.
Oh, and I also know why you did it.
Veronica.
You knew Hiram was responsible
for her seizure.
Very good, Mr. Jones.
But you forgot one thing.
Last year, Hiram hired Tall Boy
to take shots at me
during the mayoral debate,
nearly killing me.
So, that's what this was about? Revenge?
So that you could run off with Minetta?
Live a happy little life together?
You can't tell anyone about this.
Not Veronica, no one.
Because if I go down...
your father goes down.
And that's a promise.
So, I think...
we should agree...
to keep each other's secrets.
Don't you think?
So,
Hermione and I were deadlocked.
In a stalemate.
Much like Hiram and Archie.
And Betty and Penelope.
As for Minetta?
I didn't imagine there was much
to worry about.
Grab me a cigarette, will you?
Of course, Michael.
We gotta talk about what to do
with FP and his kid.
Your husband always had a simple way
of tying up loose ends.
He did, didn't he?
Perhaps, in Riverdale,
the best you could hope for wasn't to win,
but to draw, and pray not to lose.
Working late, I see.
I assume you're here to find out whodunit.
After my father woke up,
it was the first thing he asked me.
- I told him it was Tall Boy.
- Did he believe you?
I think so.
If it's good enough for my father,
it's good enough for me.
Second half of your payment.
You don't wanna know who really did it?
Forget it, Jughead.
It's Riverdale.