[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
He was there to kill me.
That's the real Archie Andrews.
[Veronica]
I don't own the diner. My father does.
And La Bonne Nuit, too.
Will you help me, Archie?
This time,
we can take down my father for good.
-Hell, yeah.
-I have someone who can help you.
A friend of mine from the Farm.
[Betty] Groups like the Farm prey
on emotionally vulnerable people.
You're actually buying this Farm crap.
[Alice] Edgar and I have a deep
understanding of one another.
Everyone in your life is here,
in this room.
Join us, and we can unpack
this obsession you have
with the Gargoyle King.
[Ethel] I've seen him, the Gargoyle King.
He's out there.
I need your help.
This game is literally killing people.
Ben and I thought it was just a game.
But it's not. It's so much more.
Were you playing G&G with Dilton?
He was teaching me how to play
so I could join the game.
[Jellybean] Ricky said that the Gospel's
where the Gargoyle King keeps
all his secrets.
[Betty] The Gospel that we found
and the proclamation was
to get me alone with my dad again.
[Jughead] Return of the Black Hood. Now
we have two serial killers running around.
Possibly working together.
[Jughead] It was the deadliest prom night
since Carrie's.
Riverdale High had been overrun
by the Black Hood,
my girlfriend's dad,
and the Gargoyle King,
true identity yet to be determined.
We needed answers, starting with...
So, how in the hell did Hal Cooper
fake his own death in a bus explosion?
Well, I re-examined the telltale hand
recovered from the bus.
See here?
The erratic incision at the wrist leads me
to think
this amputation was self-inflicted.
So, the Black Hood cut off his own hand
and left it behind
to convince everyone he died?
It's not an easy task.
There are eight bones in the human wrist.
Forget it, Hiram.
I will not endorse or support this.
We have drugs on our streets,
gangs at every corner.
Riverdale is broken,
about to slide off a cliff,
and the only way to save it is
to privatize it.
And by "privatize," you mean
you want to buy the town of Riverdale.
I'd like to put in a bid
to relieve our town of its debts
and assume its leadership.
So, yes, I plan to buy Riverdale,
with or without your support.
And Governor Dooley has already signed off
on this strategy, so...
My advice?
Clear out your office.
The deed, the contract I signed,
none of it matters.
It was all fake.
My dad still owns Pop's,
and the speakeasy,
and I'm a fool for ever trusting him.
And on top of everything he's done to me,
he's now planning
on buying the entire town.
Yeah, Ronnie, your dad sucks.
Wait a minute.
[chuckles] What about
all of the shady stuff
that goes down at the speakeasy?
If it's my dad's name on the deed,
can't he be prosecuted for it?
"Shady stuff," as in...?
Drinking without carding.
And-or illegal gambling, let's say?
Hiram did these things?
Well, technically, no.
Not exactly.
But if the property were under his name,
doesn't that make him liable?
I think I know someone
who might be able to help.
[EKG beeping]
[Mary] Ardelia and I went
to Sarah Florence together.
Now she's my friend at the FBI.
The FBI's had their eye
on Hiram Lodge for a long time.
He served less than a year
for embezzlement.
Whatever we can charge him with
in the future, it's gotta be gangbusters.
How about serving alcohol to minors,
and operating an illegal casino?
And doctoring books?
Aren't those crimes you committed?
My client can neither confirm
nor deny that statement.
Don't worry. We want your father, not you.
If none of this stuff will be enough
to get Hiram arrested, then what will?
Catch him red-handed.
We need to arrest Hiram committing a crime
in real time.
Understood, Agent Ardelia.
Let me see what I can do.
[Edgar] Betty.
Now that you're here,
your mother and sister have something
they'd like to tell you.
Go ahead, Alice.
[sighs]
Honey, when you were eight,
you spent some time in the hospital
after you fell off your bike
and got a concussion.
While you were there,
the doctors ran a bunch of tests, and...
they discovered...
What?
What, Mom?
They discovered that you have the MAOA
and the CDH13 genes,
which are commonly called...
The serial killer genes.
They tested the rest of us for it.
None of us have it. Not even Dad.
It's just you, Betty.
You have a predisposition to violence.
But now that you know you have it,
and you're here,
Edgar can help you heal.
How...?
If-- If this is true,
how can you help me?
Let's start by talking.
Just because you were born with a malady
doesn't mean it defines you.
Destiny...
it's a false notion.
You are destined to make a choice.
Give in to your proclivity, or fight it.
Tell me your fears.
Now...
begin.
I've always felt like there's
another person inside of me.
A person capable of doing dark,
terrible things.
And I don't know how to get rid of her.
The first step is confrontation.
[Shadow Betty] Hi, Betty.
Hello.
Who are you?
Take a closer look.
We know each other very, very well.
You're...
me.
I'm the shadows...
that you hide from our family and friends.
I'm all the dark deeds you did
in our youth...
and now.
Like what we did to our old cat, Caramel.
Caramel ran away.
I didn't do anything to her.
[chuckles] Oh, Betty.
We both know that we drowned Caramel.
What?
What about the time
we pushed Polly down the stairs?
Or do you not remember that, either?
No, that's...
That's not true.
Oh, but it is.
Here's what else is true.
I am not a part of you.
You are a part of me.
I am the real Elizabeth Cooper.
You are the illusion.
[groaning]
The first few sessions,
it's normal to feel disoriented.
What else did you feel?
I have this, um...
A stabbing pain in my forehead.
Your body's located your trauma.
That's step one.
Healing is painful.
But together,
we can discharge that pain forever.
This is just the beginning.
I thought the Farm would keep me safe
from the Black Hood.
But, bonus,
I'm also learning a bunch of fun,
terrifying facts about myself.
I had a session with Edgar,
and I still can't wrap my mind
around what happened.
Betty, don't let Edgar,
or these Farmies, get inside your head.
Well, he had these magnetic balls
on his desk
that were clicking and clacking.
Well, maybe he's using sound
to try and influence you.
Do you need me to get you out of there?
No.
I think I have an idea
for my next session with Edgar.
It's time I find out
what the Farm is about,
once and for all.
I need to find out the connection
between the Gargoyle King
and the Black Hood.
Oh, I had a thought about that.
The reason I went off alone during prom
was because someone dressed as a jester
gave me an envelope
from the Gargoyle King.
Okay, I got my quest.
"Follow the envelope."
Godspeed, my brave Hellcaster.
Bye. Be safe.
[school bell ringing]
Ah.
It's Louie, right?
Yeah, and?
Well, this is kind of a funny story,
but a jester gave my girlfriend
an envelope at prom,
so, I asked around.
Jester's name was Jerry.
Jerry told me that he got the envelope
from a druid named Loona.
Loona said that she got the envelope
from a centaur named...
Louie.
True or false?
Yeah, I gave it to Loona.
Okay. So, here's the 20-dollar question.
Mm.
Who'd you get the envelope from?
Some kid gave it to me.
He looked homeless.
A kid?
Was he around 13? Brown hair, brown eyes?
Thank you, Louie.
Can I join you guys?
Oh, of course, cousin.
[Fangs groans]
Fangs, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm still a little sore.
But the big pain is gone now.
What are you talking about?
Fangs had a minor procedure done.
What kind of procedure did you have?
It's a... purging
of all of the pain
that's been crushing us.
I can't wait for mine to be gone, too.
Hold on. Cheryl, you're in pain?
Like, physical pain?
Well, it's just part of Edgar's methods.
He transforms our emotional pain
into physical pain,
so it's easier to treat, and banish.
But me first, babe.
That's right. Tee-Tee's next in line.
For me, the tenderness in my back
only lasted a few days.
But it was so worth it.
[Kevin chuckles]
Oh, my God, Kevin.
That scar is not from a minor procedure.
That's from major surgery.
Don't ever do that again, Betty.
Kev...
[knocking on door]
-Ronnie.
-Archie.
I have a plan to catch my father,
to put him back behind bars
where he belongs,
and stop him from buying our town.
Okay. What is it?
It's gonna require
that we each play our parts flawlessly,
and you're up first.
[Hiram] Big change is coming to Riverdale.
Opportunities.
Riverfront.
Northside.
I'm gonna need some strong allies
I can trust.
Archie Andrews, what a surprise.
I heard you're trying to buy Riverdale,
Mr. Lodge.
My town. I can't let that happen.
It's all right, Archie.
It's a good thing for everyone.
You'll see.
I am sick of you thinking
you can control everyone,
take over everything.
You think you're unstoppable,
which is why I wanna kick your ass.
[all laughing]
If I win,
you walk away from Riverdale.
If you win,
the town's yours.
Win what?
A boxing match.
El Royale.
Or are you too weak, after being shot?
Everyone is saying that you've gone soft.
There is nothing soft about me,
and you know I don't lose.
We'll see about that.
[Veronica] Really, Daddy? A boxing match?
Archie challenged me to this fight
in the presence
of some business associates.
I couldn't look weak, Veronica.
-Well, you're not gonna win this.
-Says who?
Says me.
And all the odds-makers.
What? People are betting on this?
I've already gotten calls.
The underworld's abuzz,
asking if I'm taking bets
at La Bonne Nuit.
Obviously, I don't want any part of it.
Whoa, wait. You said no?
Mija, you could make some money off this.
Maybe.
I mean, I do still have that debt to you.
Yes, you do.
So, it's settled.  We'll run
all the betting through La Bonne Nuit.
I'll reach out to some friends.
Everyone will want a piece of the action.
It's a win-win.
And, Veronica, make no mistake,
I will win.
[Polly] I'm proud of you, Betty.
It takes courage to face your demons.
Did your darker half mention the time
you pushed me down the stairs?
Because I forgave you for that years ago.
JB?
Do you know where your pal Ricky is?
Is he in trouble?
Ricky's been working
for the Gargoyle King.
It's putting a lot of people's lives
in danger.
Ricky's in Fox Forest,
getting ready to ascend,
whatever that means.
Where? Do you know?
I need you to draw me a map. Right now.
Tell me, Betty.
Why have you chosen to return?
To see her again.
My other half.
I need to know what she wants.
[Shadow Betty] Did you miss me, Betty?
Don't worry.
Soon, the one will become many,
and the many, one.
And you can finally be your truest self.
And what is that?
My truest self?
You're a killer.
Just like Dad.
And it's time that you embrace that.
Come on, Ricky.
Where are you?
[Jughead] Ricky.
You... You shouldn't be here.
No.
What did you do?
Listen, kid. I'm taking you back
to civilization, all right?
I don't want to.
I've played this game.
I know it makes you do some crazy things.
But I need you alive,
because we're gonna end this together.
We answer to no one but our King.
"We"?
[Ricky] Kill him.
-Protect the princess.
-Princess?
[all shouting]
[Ethel] Hellcaster?
Princess Etheline?
Help me, Jughead Jones.
You're my only hope.
What are you doing down here?
Hiding from the Gargoyle King. I'm...
I'm terrified he's gonna kill me
for failing in my mission.
Mission? What mission?
Wait.
You were the one that told Ricky
to send that letter during prom?
[scoffs]
You led Betty right to the Gargoyle King
and the Black Hood?
I thought you quit G&G,
after Betty saved you
from the Sisters of Quiet Mercy.
She saved me from the Sisters' false King,
yes, but...
then I rejoined the true King
in the woods after...
When I came back to him,
he put me in charge of his Lost Boys.
That Lord of the Flies gang
that just chased me
through the woods with spears?
Ethel, you're playing G&--?
All right.
You're gonna tell me now,
right now, who the Gargoyle King is.
I can't.
I can't betray his trust.
Even when you just said
he's trying to kill you?
He's...
He's beautiful.
Despite it all,
I love him.
It's okay.
But you and the Lost Boys can't stay
in these woods.
You have to end this game.
Will you?
[Ethel sobs]
I asked you here because
I'm pulling off my biggest con yet,
and I need my best con man for the job.
Haven't we learned our lesson
about mixing business with pleasure?
Mm. The business is taking down my father.
So, are you in?
For old times' sake?
How could I resist?
[Kevin] What's this emergency, Betty?
Okay.
Edgar Evernever is hypnotizing us.
So?
Hypnotherapy is
a standard therapeutic practice
that people pay good money for.
And whatever Edgar is doing works.
-He took my pain away.
-I can't wait for him to take mine.
[Betty] But that's just it.
I think that he's purposely
inflicting pain on you during hypnosis.
Okay. Now you just sound cuckoo-pants.
Why would Edgar cause us pain,
just to take it away?
I don't know.
To have more power over you?
Edgar's our healer, Betty.
And do you have any proof to the contrary?
Right. Didn't think so.
Okay, bye.
I'll get you proof, Cheryl.
[Ethel] Stand down, Lost Boys.
The Hellcaster is on our side.
And he's come bearing good news.
Our quest is complete.
Where's Ricky?
He just took off.
He's probably reporting back
to the Gargoyle King or the Black Hood.
[sighs]
Jack? Where's Jack?
He went back to the bus
to get his carving knife.
We can't leave Jack behind.
He's the youngest.
Okay, I'll find him.
He's never gonna trust you on your own.
Then come on.
What is all this, Evelyn?
Is this one
of your dad-husband's treatments?
This is dialysis, Betty.
I was very unwell as a child.
My kidneys failed when I was little.
Hmm.
"Immuno..."
Wait, why are you on anti-rejection meds?
Which is what they give you
when you've had an organ transplant.
Not that it's any of your business,
but like I said, I was an ill child.
The scar on Kevin's back...
Fangs' treatment...
Oh, my God.
Edgar is...
butchering his disciples,
but it can't all be just for you.
You don't know anything.
[Ethel] Jack?
Jack?
Maybe he's on the bus.
Jack, are you here?
I can't find my knife.
Okay, I'll get you a new one.
But right now we have to go.
Why'd you bring the Hellcaster?
It's okay, you can trust him.
[screeching noise nearby]
Get down. Right now.
Shh.
Don't say another word.
[screeching]
[banging]
-Go, go, go.
-We have to go.
Go through the back door. Back door!
[Ethel] It won't budge.
Ethel, open the back door.
It won't budge.
-Ethel. Open the door.
-It won't budge.
Move. Move.
-We gotta go.
-Go. Go.
He's going to the front.
Stay back.
[Ethel] That's not gonna hold him.
We have to go.
[Mary] Archie?
Mom.
You're doing it? Tonight? Whatever it is
that you and Veronica have planned?
Yes.
But it's better you don't
know the specifics,
because I'm sure you're gonna try
and stop me.
After everything that Hiram has done
to you,
and to your dad, and to this town,
I wanna watch.
[man] Oh, yeah.
[chattering]
A grand on Hiram Lodge.
Good luck to you.
[Veronica] How are we looking?
Really, really illegal.
In case I haven't said it,
thank you for doing this, Reggie.
How you holding up?
By a gossamer thread.
However,
it's vital we keep up appearances.
[microphone feedback]
Speaking of,
it's showtime.
[crowd applauding]
[crowd cheering]
♪ [singing] Came into this world ♪
♪ Daddy's little girl ♪
♪ And Daddy made a soldier out of me ♪
♪ Daddy made me dance ♪
♪ And Daddy held my hand ♪
♪ And Daddy liked his whiskey
With his tea ♪
Touch them up.
Had this date a long time, you and I.
♪ Daddy made me fight ♪
♪ It wasn't always right ♪
♪ But he said
"Girl it's your Second Amendment" ♪
-Box.
-[bell dings]
♪ And we rode motorcycles ♪
♪ Blackjack, classic vinyl ♪
♪ Tough girl is what I had to be ♪
♪ He said
"Take care of your mother ♪
♪ Watch out for your sister" ♪
♪ That's when ♪
♪ Daddy looked at me ♪
Ref.
♪ With his gun
With his head held high ♪
♪ He told me not to cry
Oh, my daddy said, "Shoot" ♪
Is that how it's gonna be?
♪ Oh, my daddy said, "Shoot" ♪
Let's go.
♪ He said
"Take care of your mother ♪
♪ Watch out for your sister" ♪
♪ That's when Daddy looked at me ♪
♪ With his gun
With his head held high ♪
♪ He told me not to cry ♪
♪ Oh, my daddy said, "Shoot" ♪
♪ My daddy said, "Shoot" ♪
♪ My daddy warned me
About men like you ♪
♪ He said
"Baby girl, he's playing you ♪
♪ He's playing you ♪
♪ When trouble comes to town ♪
♪ And men like me come around" ♪
♪ Oh, my daddy said, "Shoot" ♪
It's the feds!
-What is the meaning of this?
-Are you the owner of this establishment?
Why, no.
That would be my father, Hiram Lodge.
Hmm. Happen to know
where I could find him?
Why, yes.
He's at the El Royale Boxing Club,
taking part
in an illegal underground boxing match.
Sheriff Jones is expecting you outside.
Ronnie, Ronnie. We've got a problem.
Some last-minute bets are coming in.
They all want odds
on Hiram killing Archie in the ring.
[bell dings]
[bell dinging]
This ends now.
[man] Yeah! That's right!
Just remember.
You asked for this.
Archie!
Daddy, stop.
I beat you.
I'm the better man.
No.
You lost.
I was just keeping you busy.
Hiram Lodge.
It is with great pleasure...
that I say, you're under arrest.
For what?
For conducting illegal activities
at your establishments,
El Royale Boxing Club,
and La Bonne Nuit speakeasy.
You betrayed me?
[Mary] Archie.
Are you okay?
Hey, hey.
Did we do it?
We got him.
My own daughter,
working with the feds.
[chuckles]
And for what?
An ex-boyfriend?
No. I did this for me, Daddy.
I found out you lied,
that you still held the deeds to Pop's,
and La Bonne Nuit,
and it made me very, very angry.
Consider it a lesson learned, mija.
Regardless,
all of your assets are being seized
by the government,
as we speak.
Your precious empire will be put up
for public auction.
In the meantime,
I'll leave you with this parting thought:
I won.
So, you and Veronica are
quite the dynamic duo.
Are you...?
I don't know.
Sometimes it feels like
we're gonna get back together,
but then...
Well, personally, I think you're endgame.
-Endgame?
-Oh, yeah.
But doesn't really matter what I think.
Maybe you should ask her what she thinks.
Excuse me, Mr. Jones,
but where are the Lost Boys?
We've assigned a deputy to them.
They'll be under our care,
until the Gargoyle King
and the Black Hood are caught.
[knocking on door]
Excuse me for a minute.
[FP sighs]
See? You're safe. It's okay, Ethel.
And we're going to find Ricky, too.
I promise.
Thank you.
You deserve a reward
for your bravery, Hellcaster.
I can tell you who he is.
The King.
Who?
But that's impossible.
[cell phone buzzing]
-Jug.
-Betty.
Are you ready
to hear the craziest thing ever?
Well, I think I might have you beat
on that one.
According to Ethel,
Jason Blossom is the Gargoyle King.
That's not possible, is it?
Normally, I would immediately say no.
But there's only one way to find out,
definitively.
A way that would make
Dr. Curdle Junior proud.
I'm gonna have to dig up Jason's body,
aren't I?
Call me afterwards.
Cheryl, the Farm is a front.
Kevin, Fangs?
Edgar took their kidneys.
There's a refrigerator,
filled to the brim with human organs.
The Farm...
is an organ farm.
Are you trying to get shipped off
to Shutter Island, you lunatic?
Oh, my God.
Is that a...?
Yes.
Cheryl, what if
this is why he keeps adopting kids?
For his human chop-shop.
Based on the price list I saw
in the infirmary,
it's lucrative as hell.
Infirmary.
If there's even a chance you're right,
Toni's procedure is today.
The nurses just took her away.
Okay. Go, go. Go get Toni.
I'll get Kevin and Fangs.
Are you nervous?
Don't be.
Get your hands off my girlfriend.
-Excuse me, you can't be in here.
-What's going on?
-They're charlatans.
-What?
Not another step.
Get up, Toni. Let's go.
But my treatment.
There's a chance Betty's cries
that the sky is falling are true.
Look at those instruments of torture.
Now, please, can we go?
There's a door I snuck Betty in.
Lead the way, my Monte Cristo.
Stop those girls.
Kev, Fangs.
I know that this sounds crazy,
and I'll explain later,
but Edgar's harvesting our organs.
We are all in danger.
You don't know what you're saying, Betty.
He's taking out the parts of us
that are diseased.
[Betty] Kev, Fangs...
Why don't we all go talk to Edgar,
clear this whole thing up?
Guys, guys, guys.
We don't have to do this.
We can all just go home.
Stop being a detractor, Betty.
[pop music playing]
[all grunting]
Hey, we need some help in here.
We're being attacked.
[screaming]
It's locked.
Over here.
We'll never outrun them.
Cheryl, come on.
Toni...
I love you.
This is your only chance at freedom.
No. Run!
Go!
[grunting and shouting]
♪ I know where your secrets hide ♪
[knock on door]
Archie, what's going on?
Ronnie, I wanted to tell you...
I needed to tell you...
Wait, before you say anything...
Is there someone else here?
[Reggie] Hey, Andrews.
Reggie was helping me
at La Bonne Nuit earlier tonight,
and he came to tell me...
[Reggie] I came to tell her
that I wanted to be with her,
no matter what.
And she said
she wanted to be with me, too.
Is that true?
That is...
what I said.
Right, well, uh...
Wait.
Just stay.
We should celebrate.
We did an amazing thing tonight.
No. No, I'm good. Um...
I'll see you guys at school.
Well...
You put up quite the fight, Betty.
And now you have left me with no choice.
I saw the truth, Mr. Evernever.
I know what you're doing here.
You don't know what you saw, Betty.
They're gonna come for me.
Jughead,
and his dad.
[Edgar] Nurse.
Can we please prepare Betty
for her procedure?
[Betty] Don't touch me!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[thud]
[panting]
[closing theme playing]