-[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-Thank you for agreeing to help me.
If I could go undercover, I would.
Have you ever experienced the loss
of a loved one?
My brother Jason.
[Edgar] Memories are often painful.
They don't have to be.
[Cheryl] I'm done being your mole.
You should stop going to the Farm
before Edgar catches onto you.
I'm still going to go.
Is the reason you're so obsessed
with the Farm
because they let you talk to Charles?
Yes, I see my son.
[Edgar] Tell me, what do you want to know?
Everything. Start from the beginning.
Ricky. You don't wanna do this.
If I don't do this, the Gargoyles,
they won't protect me.
[Archie] Jug, Mad Dog was right.
I saw Gargoyles coming in and out,
like they own the place.
[Jughead]
Must be where Kurtz is doing his cooking.
I'm ready to ascend. Are you?
Elio hooked me up with a house
on the Northside.
-So, what, you have to fight for him?
-Come on, you saw that place.
[FP] Terry, I'm getting close
to the clearing. I don't see any--
Poor Baby Teeth.
Brandon Morris was his real name.
We ID'd him from his prints.
First glance, very similar
to how you found Ben and Dilton,
but I don't know.
I need your help, son. Please.
Yeah, of course.
His blue lips are the same.
Markings on his back are the same, too.
But his missing teeth, that's the twist.
[sighs]
This might be a copycat killer.
It could be the same guy
that went after Ben and Dilton,
but they were willing participants.
Baby Teeth struggled.
Maybe the brutality
of his death was the message.
Like a warning.
That he's back,
and he's angry.
-The Gargoyle King.
-The real one.
You already know who I am, Betty.
No. I don't have a clue.
I've done a deep dive on the Internet,
and there's no record
of anyone named Edgar Evernever.
Many years ago...
I was a very different man.
My life was in tatters.
So, I left it behind...
and I walked in the desert to die.
Until I stumbled upon a tree
on a hill beside a farm.
I was in death's clutches.
And somehow,
I stumbled to the door of that farm,
and I knocked.
When I awoke, I was in a white room.
I was being tended to
by a kind, elderly farmer.
I asked her, "How can I repay you?"
So, she put me to work on her farm.
I plowed those fields,
and I sowed them with seed,
and I watched them grow
into something beautiful.
I felt reborn.
After that, I made it my sacred duty
to open my own farm...
where I could welcome lost souls
wandering out in the darkness.
It's a nice story,
but it doesn't explain
how you've convinced my mom
that she can see her dead son.
Here, we strive to create a safe place,
where wounded people can heal,
and become the best versions
of themselves.
But first, they must open themselves
to that process.
No, but really,
how does my mom see her dead son?
Do you have someone dress up like Charles?
All right, boys, bring it in.
-Know you're all pissed about Baby Teeth.
-Damn right.
And his killer will be caught.
I swear to you.
But in the meantime...
we honor our fallen brother.
How the hell do we do that?
I'm dedicating my next match
to Baby Teeth.
No one asked you, Mad Dog.
Why are you even here?
Because Baby Teeth was my brother, too.
Wait, Mad Dog, what match?
Did Elio already hook you up with one?
There's a boxing tournament this weekend,
called the Gilded Gloves.
I was gonna fight to win.
But now I'm gonna fight to win
and honor Baby Teeth.
[Veronica] How's your boxing career
these days, Archie?
Your pal Elio is organizing
a boxing event called the Gilded Gloves.
Brawny young men,
shirtless and in shorts. Go on.
[Archie] I was thinking, maybe you could
help get the El Royale Crew a spot
in the tournament.
The guys could use a win,
or at least a boost,
after what happened to Baby Teeth.
Let me see what I can do.
Good morning, my dear Riverdale High
constituents and comrades.
A lot of you have been asking
about the Farm's student advocacy group.
Well, here's the skinny.
Signup sheets are posted
throughout the school.
The club is open to all students.
Where the one become many,
and the many become one.
So, uncap those pens,
sharpen those pencils, and sign up.
A little birdie told me,
it's what all the cool kids are doing.
Invasion of the Body Snatchers continues.
So, let me get this straight.
The reason Cheryl is all-in on the Farm
is that she gets to see and talk to Jason?
Yeah.
My mom's entirely convinced
that she's seeing and talking to Charles.
Her long-lost son.
What if you prove that Charles was dead?
Your mom has lost touch with reality,
so, maybe the best way
to snap her out of her delusions
is with a harsh dose of truth.
Like proof that Charles is dead.
Anything that'll refute these fantasies
that Edgar Evernever is spinning.
[Betty] No. Unfortunately,
I only have a name. Charles Smith.
He was raised
in the Sisters of Quiet Mercy,
but they turned him out when he was 18.
Well, I appreciate you trying.
Betty, whatever the Farm did with Cheryl,
I'm holding you responsible.
How did my girlfriend become
Queen of the Farmies overnight?
It's Edgar.
He is a con artist.
He's somehow convinced my mom
and Cheryl...
[sighs] that they can...
talk to the dead.
Excuse me?
Cheryl thinks she's been talking to Jason.
She says she sees him.
But Jason's dead.
Everybody knows that Jason's dead.
True.
And there's proof that Jason's dead,
that he was murdered.
What are you talking about?
[sighs]
I'm gonna send you a video, Toni, of...
Clifford Blossom shooting Jason.
I kept a copy of it on my laptop.
Show it to Cheryl,
and hopefully it will be enough
to snap her back into reality.
[cell phone buzzing]
Oh, hold on. Will you give me a second?
I think this is my dad.
Hello?
[Elio] Veronica Lodge,
I don't suppose I need to tell you,
this is a men's steam room.
I came to talk business.
I wanna get in on the Gilded Gloves.
You don't know a thing about boxing.
[chuckles]
You'd be surprised by what I know
about hot, shirtless, muscular bruisers.
Starting with Archie Andrews.
If memory serves,
he almost beat your prizefighter,
Randy Ronson.
Archie's a bum.
And bums have no place in my tournament.
Now get the hell out of my steam room.
Fine.
But remember this.
Remember I tried to keep things civil.
[Curdle Jr.]
He suffered a myriad of traumas.
But our good friend here died
from loss of blood.
From the pulling of his teeth,
which occurred premortem.
There's one more ghoulish detail
I discovered during the autopsy.
There was something lodged in his throat.
What the hell is that?
[Jughead] A matchbook from the Maple Club.
I thought I'd seen the true face of evil.
But this...
Whoever did this...
isn't even human.
Any idea how one of your matchbooks
ended up in Baby Teeth's throat?
Well, they are complimentary
to all of our guests.
We don't recommend they ingest them.
I do recall this young man being here
a few nights ago.
He was here with some friends.
Ex-cons, but charming.
Anyway, this "Baby Teeth"
left the Maple Club
with a grin on his face,
and alive.
My girl Rosemary fulfilled his fantasy.
[glass breaking and women screaming]
What on Eve's earth?
[man growling]
All right, okay.
Hey.
I got him cuffed in the back
of my cruiser.
He's not going anywhere.
Anything else you can tell us about him?
Like his name, or where he's from?
Martin, but they all use an alias.
Did something seem different about him?
Yes.
Martin likes to take Fizzle Rocks
to enhance the experience.
But this was different.
The high hit him like a truck,
he started foaming at the mouth,
freaking out.
This was helpful.
If anything else comes up,
please, give me a call.
[Alice] And we're live in three, two, one.
This is Alice Smith,
and I'm here with Veronica Lodge,
promoter of the Southside's
El Royale Boxing Club.
Veronica, would you like to tell us
about your latest business venture?
Our athletic facility will help you
reach your fitness goals
in a fun, classic,
competitive environment.
Our trained staff features some
of the toughest fighters in the state,
including up-and-coming boxer
Archie Andrews.
Archie?
[Archie] Hi, I'm Archie Andrews,
owner, trainer, and fighter,
here at the El Royale Boxing Club.
Join now, and your first three
personal training sessions with me
are completely free.
I got one more thing to say.
A message for Randy Ronson.
This Friday night at the Gilded Gloves,
I want my rematch.
Me and you.
Let's settle this for good.
Strong words from a local hero.
Live from the Southside,
I'm Alice Smith, RIVW.
[Hal]
Your mother has thrown down the gauntlet.
She's filed for divorce.
Her lawyers issued the papers today,
but I haven't signed yet.
Has she started seeing someone?
Well, she does spend most of her time
at the Farm,
presumably with Edgar,
who's a con artist.
He's got her thinking
she's seeing Charles.
That's impossible. Charles is dead.
Yeah,
but I don't have physical proof of that.
I don't have a body, I don't have ashes.
You know,
you don't need a body or ashes, Betty.
Just a stone.
A piece of granite will do.
[Elio] I must admit, that was a bold move,
challenging Randy.
So, does this mean the El Royale boxers
will get to be part of the Gilded Gloves?
Yes.
Only thing is, your boy is gonna have
to move up a weight class.
Randy's fighting
in the middleweight division now.
Fine.
Great.
-I'm hosting at my gym.
-[chuckles]
Nice try.
We'll flip for the venue.
Heads for Archie's gym,
tails for your gym.
Heads.
We'll see you at the El Royale.
[FP] When he finally comes down, we'll
ask him where he got the Fizzle Rocks.
My bet is still Kurtz.
Wouldn't mind asking him if he knows
anything about Baby Teeth either.
I'll have forensics run a test
on the Fizzle Rocks he had on him.
[Cheryl] Why would you show this to me?
[Toni] Because you needed
to be reminded of the truth.
Cheryl, you're not talking to Jason
at the Farm.
The truth is all right there,
in this video.
Toni, this video is clearly fabricated.
With technology these days,
anything is possible.
Detractors can spin any story they want.
Cheryl, have...
you ever hugged Jason?
Yes. Of course.
Now enough of this third degree.
Betty?
Mom...
are you engaged to Edgar?
[sighs]
Edgar and I have a deep understanding
of one another.
That's what I thought.
I wanna show you something.
What is this, Betty?
I paid someone
to help me track down Charles' grave.
I'm so sorry, Mom,
but you haven't been talking to him
at the Farm.
Your son...
has been here, dead and buried,
for the last five years.
[sighs]
It's just so sad.
I know, Mom.
So sad that you won't let me be happy
at the Farm.
I don't know
when you're gonna give up, Betty.
You saw his gravestone.
I'm sorry, Betty.
But I spoke to my son this morning.
[breathing heavily]
I'm sorry, too, Mom.
[Alice gasps]
Bon appétit, champ.
You're making up for lost calories.
-Ronnie, I feel like Jughead.
-That's the idea, Archie.
[man] Randy Ronson, to the scale.
One hundred and fifty-nine pounds.
-[crowd cheering]
-Yeah.
Archie Andrews, to the scale.
One hundred and fifty-four pounds.
[crowd cheering]
Where am I? What did you do to me?
I chloroformed you.
Don't worry, Mom. You're safe.
Edgar always starts with questions,
so, I'll do the same.
Do you remember this?
It was your first day
at The Riverdale Register.
You were so excited.
And now I'm an on-air reporter for RIVW,
thanks to the Farm.
Eighth grade graduation.
You cried that day. Do you remember?
That's the past.
I'm someone else now.
No. No.
The past is...
part of who you are.
You're Alice Cooper.
You bought a house on Elm Street.
You painted our front door red.
I lived with a murderer in that house.
You raised me and Polly in it, too.
Bad things happen,
but you can't get rid of your past,
because then you'd lose
the good parts, too.
There's been so much pain.
I know, I know, but...
that's what makes us stronger.
Edgar doesn't see that.
You have to believe me.
Believe you?
Okay. So, tell me the truth, Betty.
Was that really Charles' grave?
So, how can I trust you? You lied to me.
You faked a gravestone.
Look, I love you. I love you, Betty.
But you're gonna have to let me go.
I'm sorry, Mom.
No...
I have to go to school, but, um,
I'll come back to check on you.
No, Betty.
This is your life.
Look at it.
And remember who you are.
Hey...
[Jughead] You locked your mom
in Dilton's bunker?
Yeah, it's the only place
where she'll be safe from the Farm, Jug.
And I've already made some headway
with the deprogramming.
Next I'm gonna listen
to her testimony tapes,
and see if there's anything I can use
to help me get my mom back.
[banging noise nearby]
What is that?
What the hell is going on?
Hey, did she take something?
Yeah. She took some G.
Get her to the infirmary.
[cell phone buzzes]
Hey, Dad.
Jug, I need your brain, boy.
I got another guy here on a nasty trip.
Can you meet me at the station?
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Okay.
[banging, grunting]
It's gotta be a bad batch.
One that causes Fizzle Rocks psychosis.
[grunting]
Or the Fizzle Rocks are being cut
with something.
Bath salts, maybe.
We need to catch whoever's dealing
this garbage before someone turns up dead.
Looks like our john is almost ready
to talk.
[gasps]
Evelyn?
What are you doing?
Toni...
you're detracting Cheryl
from her studies at the Farm...
but I'm not gonna let you ruin her.
Ruin her?
Bitch, I love her.
And she loves me.
The Farm is fulfilling Cheryl
in ways you can't even begin to imagine.
I find that hard to believe.
Have a blessed day.
Andrews.
Mad Dog, what are you doing here?
There's something you need
to know about Randy.
He's juicing.
He's taking steroids?
No.
Something new.
Powder. I saw Elio give it to him.
Made him crazy strong.
Elio's scared. He thinks I might win.
No, man, you're not listening to me.
I looked into Randy's eyes,
and it wasn't Randy anymore.
It was rage.
He'll kill you.
Unless you take something
to level the playing field.
-Here.
-No.
Dude...
I don't take that stuff.
When you see Randy in the ring...
you might want to.
Just in case.
Thirteen. What does it mean?
It's a good roll.
Sadly, your Elven army is no match
for the legions of Gargoyles
at your doorstep.
It's okay, JB.
You got further in this quest
than I did at your level.
Could we play another round?
You sure your parents won't mind
you staying out so long?
No, it's like I told you when we met.
They're busy.
Same with my parents.
[Jughead] What does it mean?
The G is for "Gargoyle," I think.
Which Gargoyle?
Is there anyone in particular?
This time it was a guy named Kurtz.
-Do you have any idea where Kurtz is now?
-How should I know?
Kurtz is the cook, and he's selling, too.
But we need the kingpin.
I'm gonna pay Hiram Lodge a visit.
Tell your mom I'll be home late.
Mom?
Mom, are you okay?
Betty.
Evelyn.
You wouldn't happen to know
where your mom is, would you?
Am I my mother's keeper?
She missed bed check last night,
but somebody did see you
visiting her room yesterday.
Hmm. Well, I'll let you know if I see her.
We have copies of those tapes...
Betty.
And copies of those copies.
Let me make something very clear.
You and your dad may have brainwashed
my mom.
But I see right through
your enlightened Farmie crap.
So, stop messing with me,
stop messing with my family,
and stop messing with my friends.
Better yet,
don't even think about coming near me,
or my mom, ever again.
Because if you do, Evelyn...
I will kill you.
And if you don't believe me, ask around.
People will tell you what I'm capable of.
Cheryl, are you going to a meeting
at the Farm?
Indeed, my love.
Do you think
these Louboutins are too flashy
for kombucha brewing?
Well...
how about if you didn't go?
Why wouldn't I? The Farm needs me tonight.
I need you tonight.
I need you in every way.
Mind...
body...
soul.
But, uh...
mostly body.
[Kiergy's "My Temptation" playing]
♪ My temptation ♪
♪ Pulls me under ♪
Tomorrow, when we fight, we fight for him.
For Baby Teeth.
[FP] He's the guy I collared at Pop's.
He finally woke up.
That's when I called you.
Hey.
You could've really hurt someone, pal.
Where'd you get the G?
From a guy named Kurtz?
[man] Yeah.
He wasn't my usual dealer.
-[phone buzzing]
-He was real aggressive,
trying to get me
to buy more than my usual.
He's still in Riverdale.
He's getting desperate, sounds like.
Hmm. It's Laura,
our lady friend from the Maple Club.
Hello.
[Alice on recording]
She's just so angry, Edgar.
[Edgar] Alice, Betty loves you.
She's a good person.
[Alice] It's just the two of us
in the house now, and the truth is...
I'm afraid of Betty.
Sometimes, the way she looks at me,
I think she's going to hurt me.
I think she wants to hurt me.
She's her father's daughter.
She has the same darkness in her
that I saw in him.
What happened?
Another crazy john?
[Laura] You told me to call
in case anything came up.
Well, some preppy rich kids were here,
rowdy and stirring up trouble.
On the same Rocks
that drove the other customer feral?
No. But they were here killing time,
before meeting a dealer in the lobby.
But I guess the guy never showed.
How'd you get rid of them?
One of the ruffians got a call.
Sounded like a supplier,
looking to reschedule.
He said something about a fight.
Left this in the trash.
That's Archie's gym.
One last chance to bust Kurtz.
What did you do to my mom?
What did you do
to make her say such horrible things
about me on those tapes?
Why are you trying to turn her against me?
Betty...
everything your mother said
on those tapes...
those were her own words.
And to be fair,
you have given Alice
some legitimate reasons to fear you.
You're not turning this around on me.
Not while you keep feeding her lies.
Telling her that Charles--
Charles is a wound. She needs to heal.
Charles is dead.
He's a ghost.
Your mother is on a journey.
And she is making tremendous progress
towards finding her truest self.
She could've done that at home,
with a therapist.
She didn't have to give away my money,
our house, everything.
Ah, you know, I think, Betty...
you and your mother
see the world quite differently.
You don't need us.
She does.
She needs to heal from the pain
that has been inflicted upon her.
And communing with Charles,
real or illusionary...
comforts her.
Fills her in a way
that no one in her life can, or does...
including you.
Now, I ask you,
why...
in your mind, is that a bad thing?
[metal clanging]
[footsteps approaching]
We're going somewhere.
[car door opening, closing]
It's okay, Mom.
Evelyn will make sure you get home safely.
Take care of her, Evelyn.
Please.
That's all we've ever wanted to do.
-[Archie] What is this for?
-It's for luck.
[both chuckle]
I'm pretty sure they're your size.
[giggling]
Thank you, Ronnie.
Thank you for believing in me.
No matter what happens...
I want you to know that...
I'm always in your corner.
-I should go. Still lots to do.
-Yup.
[sighs]
-Okay.
-Okay. Bye.
See you later.
[door opens then closes]
Flying a little close to the sun there,
aren't you?
We're friends now, Dad.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Friends.
[school bell ringing]
Tee-Tee.
Are you okay?
[sighs] Evelyn said...
I have to make a choice.
Jason...
or you.
Cheryl, Jason's a ghost.
I'm right here.
You love me.
[sobbing] I'm sorry, Toni.
I do love you.
But I've loved Jason my whole life.
Cheryl...
I'm not gonna let this happen.
There has to be a way
you can be with me...
and Jason.
[sighs]
There is.
If you're willing to open your mind to it.
[rock music playing]
[Alice] Betty won't admit it,
but I know she was deeply hurt by Hal.
We all were, but she took it the hardest.
-How'd it go?
-Great.
No one suspects anything.
Toni...
I'm not a monster...
-am I?
-No.
You're a daughter
who wants her mother back.
Just like I want my girlfriend back.
-There he is, Kurtz.
-Where?
[Jughead] In the hoodie.
He's walking towards the alley.
[police siren wailing]
-[Jughead] Hold it.
-[FP] Put your hands up.
Don't you move.
Get them up.
You and your drugs
are done for good, Kurtz.
Get up.
[crowd cheering]
[Josie] Are you nervous?
Not a bit.
[Josie] Is that a new robe?
And trunks.
Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe is Archie's
official sponsor. You like them?
I'm gonna end Andrews tonight. I got this.
You said that last time,
and he almost beat you.
-What the hell's in that?
-Little last-minute boost.
Dissolved some G into your water.
Now...
get in there and live up to your promise.
[opera music playing on speakers]
I'll admit, Betty,
I'm surprised you've asked me
to sign these divorce papers.
Well, that makes two of us.
[clears throat]
Why the change of heart?
I finally realized
that it's time to let Mom go.
She needs to heal
in whatever way she chooses.
Mm.
I wonder, Betty, if you would consider
doing me a favor, as well.
What kind of favor?
Oh, it's nothing much.
I just wanna come home.
Good boy, Arch. Stick and move.
Kid, get the hell out of there.
[bell rings]
[bell ringing]
You better stay off the ropes, kid.
Something's wrong.
Ronson's on some kind of crazy drug.
The ref needs to call the fight.
Hey, ref. Ronson looks like he wants
to chew off my fighter's face.
We want a disqualification.
Only way this match ends
is if you forfeit.
You wanna take the loss?
Screw you, Elio.
He's gonna have himself
a hell of a hangover,
but I need you to knock him out
in this round.
I don't know. I don't know.
The overhand right is there for you.
Once you see a crack in his armor,
you bring out the hacksaw, you understand?
-[ref] Seconds out.
-[bell rings]
Let's do it.
[bell rings]
[Mr. Keller] Good boy, Arch.
-Attaboy.
-[ref] One. Two.
Three. Four. Five.
-Six. Seven. Eight. Nine.
-[crowd] Archie. Archie. Archie...
Ten. It's over.
[bell rings]
Whoo!
Ronson.
We need a doctor.
Somebody call a doctor.
Ronson, wake up.
[FP] You hurt a lot of people, Kurtz.
What were you thinking?
Sell the bad batch, get out of town,
dodge a murder charge?
Why Baby Teeth?
Did the Gargoyle King demand a sacrifice?
Baby Teeth.
He was only the warm-up.
To what?
To the ultimate quest.
To one final game...
for you...
and your family...
Hellcaster.
It was demanded by the King.
Save the Little Princess.
Jellybean?
What the hell did you do? What did you do?
She's been summoned...
by the King.
[laughing]
I don't understand.
Why couldn't we just keep playing
in Pop's?
Because, Princess Jellybean...
he wanted to meet you.
Who did?