[narrator] Previously on Riverdale:
-[shouts] Kurtz!
-What the hell?
[growling]
I'm willing to sell the Whyte Wyrm to you
in exchange for Pop's Chock'lit Shoppe.
It's about Jason.
The Farm gave me back my brother.
Edgar Evernever decided he wants
to adopt the twins after he marries Mom.
That can't happen.
I wonder, Betty, if you would consider
doing me a favor, as well.
Your dad and a few other inmates
were being transported
to my father's prison,
and there was some kind of accident.
There were no survivors.
Mr. Jones, what happened here?
We don't know yet. We're working on it.
It's him.
He's back. The Black Hood.
Betty's dad was on that bus.
He was being transferred
to Hiram's prison.
He's out there, Mr. Jones.
No, no. Betty.
No one survived this crash.
I'm sorry.
You know that he's dead?
You're positive?
There were five inmates on that bus,
one driver, six in total, which is...
It's the number of heads we found.
DNA tests will confirm it,
if we can't piece everyone back together.
I'm sorry.
Betty, we should go.
He asked for my help with this transfer.
He wanted this, Veronica.
What if he planned this?
What if he escaped?
He could still be out there.
Archie?
Mom.
I would've picked you up from the airport,
but Dad took his truck,
-and I'm not sure the jalopy's your speed.
-That's fine. I took an Uber.
Have you had breakfast yet?
We can go to Pop's. My treat.
Can we do dinner instead? I was gonna head
to the gym before school starts.
Your dad mentioned
that you'd taken up boxing.
-Said you were pretty serious about it.
-I am, yeah.
That's not why you came, is it?
To talk me out of it?
Not at all. Things were slow in Chicago,
and I just wanted to spend some time
with my son, that's all.
Have you come to steal more babies?
No, I came to warn you
that Dad might be on the loose.
FP already called.
There were no survivors.
Dr. Curdle Junior hasn't
identified the bodies yet.
We don't know that.
This is what I mean
about letting go of your past.
Stop indulging in these morbid delusions
that your serial killer of a father
is somehow still alive.
Did you get a tattoo?
Yes.
Edgar asked me to get it.
I like to think of it
as an engagement ring.
[Jughead] How are you feeling?
You mean,
considering that Mom abandoned me?
[Jughead sighs]
She didn't abandon you.
Mom leaving town is probably
the most selfless thing she's ever done.
I've never lived anywhere without her.
Well, I'm glad you decided to stay.
Just no more playing G&G, okay?
Why is everyone so freaked out about it?
It's just pretend quests and costumes.
Who was in costume?
Well, Ricky had those ears,
and I had a crown...
and the Gargoyle King, of course.
Wait, you met the Gargoyle King?
Like, in person?
-What happened?
-He gave me and Ricky a quest.
You talked to him?
-What did he say?
-That I couldn't enter the Kingdom.
Not until I had the Gospel.
That was our next quest.
The Gospel.
-What's the Gospel?
-I don't know. We never found it.
But Ricky said that the Gospel's
where the Gargoyle King
keeps all his secrets.
Good morning, boys.
And good news, Archie.
I've got your fight application.
-What are you talking about?
-For the Regional Classic.
Nice. That's a hot tournament.
How'd you get him in?
I'm very persuasive when I need to be.
You'll be ready.
You just gotta get your mom or dad
to sign off on it
so we can make the deadline.
This is the perfect opportunity
to jumpstart your boxing career.
Hey, if you ever wanna add
another client to your roster,
-I'd love to have a manager like you.
-I'll think about it, Mad Dog.
Guys? Old Faithful just opened up
in the locker room.
I think a pipe burst.
I turned the water off,
but someone should go look at that.
I'll fix it.
Suddenly you're a plumber?
-Bring in a professional.
-Ronnie--
I've actually been meaning to talk to you.
As your manager,
this gym has charm to spare,
but it could use an update.
-A little sprucing up.
-With what money, Ronnie?
Mine.
I'd like to invest.
In you and your gym.
La Bonne Nuit has been doing
very well lately,
and I wouldn't mind
diversifying my portfolio
to include a property on the Southside.
[Betty] Can't be a coincidence.
He asked for the transfer,
and then his bus just burst into flames.
He planned it. He used me to escape.
And now he's out there.
Betty, I was with you.
I saw what was left of that bus.
-Nobody could've survived that.
-Yeah, but if he did--
If he did,
you've got me, you have the Serpents,
you have Archie
and his fight club buddies,
you have a veritable armada
to protect you.
Also, you can move back in
with my dad and I.
Been a lot quieter
since my mom's been gone.
Mm... I'm sorry that she left, Jug.
How's JB doing after all this?
Shockingly well.
And she's filled in some key blanks.
Apparently there's a Gospel
of the Gargoyle King out there somewhere.
Could be important.
My dad's been sweeping Junkyard Steve's.
Sorry to interrupt
your no doubt thrilling catch-up, chums,
but, as you know,
junior prom is this weekend.
The theme is Fire and Ice.
And naturally, Toni and I are campaigning
to be the most captivating prom queens
this school's ever seen.
So, it goes without saying,
vote Choni for co-monarchs,
because when you really think about it,
no other options make sense.
Prom is this weekend?
We still do things like that here?
I mean, apparently.
Jug...
will you go to prom with me?
Only for you, Betty Cooper.
Hey. Peanut butter and banana.
Thought you might be hungry,
ready for a break.
Definitely. Actually, Mom,
I wanted to ask you something.
There's a tournament this weekend
that I wanna box in. The Regional Classic.
I need you to sign my application
to let me compete.
-Archie...
-Let me guess. You don't want me to box.
[chuckles]
I didn't even want you to play football.
And boxing is so much more...
brutal.
I'm behind on everything else,
but I'm good at boxing.
-I was actually thinking about going pro.
-Going pro?
I know you've been dealing
with a lot lately.
-Mom--
-But I won't support you getting pummeled.
[man] Range is closing.
Please return your gear.
[cell phone ringing]
Dr. Curdle Junior?
[Curdle Jr.] Ms. Cooper, hello.
Have you identified the bodies?
The corpses were charred
beyond recognition,
but I was able
to work with one semi-intact hand,
and it matches your father.
DNA and fingerprints.
It's him, Ms. Cooper.
For good or ill, your father is dead.
[sobbing]
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, Dad, have you seen Jellybean?
[FP] I dropped her off at school.
Listen, I'm at Junkyard Steve's.
-You better get down here and see this.
-Okay. I'm on my way.
Since this is where Kurtz brought you,
and where he was killed
by the Gargoyle King,
me and my men have been doing a sweep
of the junkyard,
and it led us to this bus.
Looks like this is where Kurtz...
and some other Gargoyles were crashing.
The Gospel.
-[school bell ringing]
-Veronica.
Uh, my mom signed.
-I can enter the Regional Classic.
-And not a moment too soon.
We can submit it now
and get it in just under the deadline.
Awesome.
Are you sure about this?
I love seeing you back in the ring,
but if the tournament's too soon,
we can send Mad Dog.
You can keep training, and go next year.
No, I'm ready. It's just, um...
I was wondering...
-What are you doing for prom?
-Prom?
Yeah,
I thought maybe we could go together.
-As friends.
-[chuckles]
I would honestly love that.
Yeah?
Great.
-Great.
-[Toni] Prom tickets here.
Get your prom tickets here.
Uh, actually, we'll take two, please.
Well, well, well.
What was off is now back on again.
You owe me a cherry phosphate.
We're just going as friends.
-In fact, we'll be paying separately.
-Whatever.
Just remember to vote Choni
for prom queens, okay? Thanks. Bye.
Cheryl, what are you doing?
Campaigning for prom queen
is strictly forbidden.
Forbidden? What's up with that?
The Farm prohibits it,
because it goes against
our strictures of equality.
Remember, the one become many,
the many, one?
Easy for you to say, Evelyn.
Aren't you like 30?
How many proms have you been to?
This is a test.
You can either be queens for one night,
or you can live in the glory of the Farm
for all of eternity.
Which would you prefer?
Honestly? Both.
There's a lot of mythical stuff
in this Gospel, Betty.
The Gargoyles were thought
to be evil spirits
that lived in the clouds,
preying on people.
So,
the Gryphon Queen turned them to stone.
They fell from the Kingdom,
-and shattered when they hit the earth.
-Jug.
All this lore builds up the Gargoyle King
to be some kind of supernatural creature,
but this guy's just a serial killer.
Just like my dad.
The Black Hood was flesh and blood,
and so is the Gargoyle King.
Which means...
that he can die.
Betty, if you need a couple days,
you can take a break.
No.
I need to keep moving.
I just want this to end.
[cell phone beeps]
It's Dr. Curdle Junior.
He's got results
from Kurtz's autopsy for us.
Hey, Archie, can I talk to you for a sec?
Yeah. Sure. What's up?
I know you're upset with me
that I wouldn't
let you enter the tournament.
And believe it or not, I'm really happy
that you've found something that you love.
I do love it, Mom.
Well, listen.
I called a recruiter
from the Naval Academy,
old friend of mine,
and they have an amazing boxing program.
Even scholarships.
So, you could box, and get an education.
Will you at least talk to her?
[chuckles]
Sure, Mom. Of course.
Thanks.
Judging by the healing,
I'd say Mr. Kurtz got
these tattoos last month.
Yet again, the same symbols
that were carved into Ben,
Dilton, and Baby Teeth.
The Gospel says you need these markings
to ascend to the Kingdom.
Maybe these tattoos are Kurtz's way
of trying to slip his way in.
Jug, whoever gave him
these tattoos could be a new lead.
Thanks for coming all this way, Brooke.
I owe you one.
Happy to help, Mary.
Buy me a drink later, we'll call it even.
Done and done.
Brooke, this is my son, Archie.
-Hi.
-[Archie] Hi.
So, you guys go way back, huh?
We do. We met at Sarah Florence.
We were roommates freshman year.
So, your mom tells me you're interested
in boxing for the Naval Academy?
Uh, possibly.
Well, the Academy's
physical education program
requires all midshipmen
to participate in boxing,
so, you'll have plenty of competition.
And as a member of the boxing club,
you train with the best.
But the Academy also prepares you
for life outside the gym.
Over four years,
you get a great education,
a college degree, and a job.
In the military?
Upon graduation,
you serve five years active duty.
Then by the time I'm finished,
my prime boxing years might be behind me.
Yeah, but that's why you need
to find something real to fall back on.
And many of our boxers go on
to have professional careers.
Our program is extremely competitive.
I'd wanna see you in the ring first.
You can set up an exhibition match,
so Brooke can see what you can do.
Yeah. Yeah, I can ask Fangs.
Great, let's do this Friday evening.
We'll be there.
[tattoo needle buzzing]
[knocking]
Got IDs?
Gotta be 18 or over to get inked.
Actually, we were wondering if you, um...
recognized this.
Matter of fact, yeah.
Kid came in asking for those symbols
a few weeks back.
Did he mention why?
No, just showed me the design,
and paid cash,
just like the first guy.
Wait. There was a first guy?
About a year ago,
I gave that same tattoo
to a different dude.
Same symbols, also on his back.
Do you have a name?
Maybe a photo, by chance?
Never ask for names.
Normally I like to take photos
of my finished work,
but this guy would not
let a camera anywhere near him.
No photos, huh?
Sounds like someone that I know.
What did he look like?
Sandy hair, blue eyes...
Weirdly magnetic?
That's the guy.
Mm-hm.
Thanks.
Evelyn told me what you've
been doing, Sister Cheryl.
She said that you've been campaigning
for prom queen.
Brother Edgar,
think about what it would mean
if I were prom queen.
Standing on that stage,
a crown on my head,
I could use that platform
to spread the Farm's message.
Cheryl...
do you like being a member
of our community?
Yes, immensely.
That is good.
But...
standing with us
requires sacrifice.
Now, if you can't let something
as trivial as prom queen go...
we can't have you speaking
with your brother Jason any longer.
I understand, and I'm done campaigning.
Just...
please, don't take Jason away.
[woman] No question.
This is a unique and handsomely
maintained property, Ms. Lodge.
I have no doubt
your loan will be approved.
That's great. Thank you.
Veronica, tell me you're not selling--
Absolutely not, Pop.
I'm just looking to get a loan,
to help Archie and his boxing gym.
I thought you and Archie...
We're just friends, Pop.
Friends and business associates.
You're over.
By six pounds.
Sorry, but you're not fighting, kid.
No, no, no. Commissioner.
I'll cut down. I'll make the weight.
By Friday? Good luck with that.
Friday?
I thought the fight was on Saturday.
Last-minute change.
The fight's at four.
But I can't let you in at this weight.
I'll be there.
Minus six pounds.
Jug, the tattoo artist said
that a guy with blond hair and blue eyes
got a Gargoyle King tattoo,
about a year ago,
right around the time the Farm
moved to town,
and right before any
of this game stuff started to happen.
Add the fact
that my mom just got a tattoo,
per Mr. Evernever's request.
Okay.
But if the Gargoyle King is Edgar,
then how does that explain your mom
seeing him during Ascension Night
nearly two decades
before Edgar got to town?
Well, who says that the new Gargoyle King
is the same person as the old one?
My mom gave testimony to the Farm
about the Midnight Club.
Edgar could have taken on that persona.
I know that Edgar's
been messing with your family.
Think about it.
Edgar bought the Sisters of Quiet Mercy,
where the game originated.
Both he
and the Gargoyle King preach ascension.
Both of them have followers
that they manipulate.
And they're both really, really creepy.
There's one way to settle this.
And fast.
I don't know if this is a cry for help,
or if you need to seriously refine
your taste in athletic wear.
I gotta lose weight for this fight Friday.
Are you sure that's enough time?
I'll do it.
Can you give me a ride back here after?
I gotta focus in the car.
Focus on what?
Another fight.
My mom invited this recruiter
to come see me box.
Archie, that's insane.
You can't fight twice in the same day.
Just invite your mom and the recruiter
to the tournament.
That's the thing.
My mom didn't sign that waiver. I did.
I forged her signature.
She doesn't want me
to fight in this tournament.
So much so that she brought this recruiter
all the way from Annapolis, so--
So, you've gotta give her a good show.
I get it.
I'll make sure you get back here in time.
Many tribes, when their elders die,
would consume their bodies
to absorb the wisdom.
Very good question, Alice.
Now, who's next?
Me.
How about you admit
that you are the Gargoyle King?
Edgar, I am so sorry.
It's all right, Alice.
Clearly, whatever's on Betty's mind
must be very important.
Why don't you join us?
And we can unpack
this obsession you have
with the Gargoyle King.
I have a better idea.
Why don't you take off your shirt?
-Betty.
-I wanna see your tattoos.
I do have a tattoo.
On my wrist. It's an infinity symbol.
Just like many of us here.
I'm talking about the runic symbols
that would be on your back.
This is sublimation, Betty.
But...
I have nothing to hide.
Then prove it.
There.
Does that satisfy you, Betty?
[Survivor's "Eye of the Tiger" playing]
♪ Risin' up, back on the street ♪
♪ Did my time, took my chances ♪
♪ Went the distance
Now I'm back on my feet ♪
♪ Just a man and his will to survive ♪
♪ It's the eye of the tiger
It's the thrill of the fight ♪
♪ Risin' up to the challenge
Of our rival ♪
♪ And the last known survivor
Stalks his prey in the night ♪
♪ And he's watchin' us all
With the eye of the tiger ♪
[chuckles]
Just a hair under the limit.
Well done, Archie.
Now let's get you to bout number one.
[school bell ringing]
Don't worry about it.
Should be a relief that your mom's
not marrying a second serial killer.
If not Edgar, then who?
If we're gonna catch the Gargoyle King,
it'll be on his own terms.
-His gospel?
-Yes.
I think that there's a ritual in here
that will help invoke him.
Just listen to this.
"After the false prophet is sacrificed,
the shire will have a bacchanal
to celebrate the coronation
of the Gryphon Queen."
-Does that sound like any school event?
-Junior prom?
"Upon her crowning,
the Gryphon Queen will ensure
the King's arrival
by subjugating herself,
and declaring that the one true monarch
of Eldervair is the Gargoyle King."
I'm assuming I'm the Gryphon Queen?
Right. We just have to ensure
that you're crowned Prom Queen.
So, maybe we switch the prom theme
to something G&G-related.
Assuming the Gospel is, well, gospel,
he's going to show up.
He's not going to ignore his own rules,
right?
We need to ensure
that you're elected prom queen.
So, what if we do all that,
and the Gargoyle King
still doesn't materialize?
Then the prom is just another horrible
school event that we'll have to endure.
[sighs]
Who is the chair of the Prom Committee?
Hi, Cheryl.
We had an idea
that we wanted to run by you.
Now, we realize that our prom's theme,
Fire and Ice,
was decided months ago.
-But people don't know what that means.
-Right.
So, what if we specified the theme,
a little bit?
Maybe we call it something like,
The Renaissance?
Or Medieval Times?
Sure.
Whatever.
Cheryl,
did you hear anything we just said?
Yes.
For all I care, change the theme,
make everyone wear chain mail and corsets,
turn the photo booth into a pillory,
hand out turkey legs.
What does it matter if I won't be queen?
It was a great fight, Archie.
You almost had him.
One more round, and I would've.
I won't lose two fights in the same day.
What, that exhibition fight with Fangs?
No, Archie.
You are punch-drunk if you think
I'm gonna let you fight another match.
You look like you were hit by a truck.
You hobbled out of the ring,
dead on your feet--
I'm fine, Veronica.
I told my mom I'd be there.
I don't wanna disappoint her.
I'll get her
and the recruiter to reschedule.
You can't. She's leaving.
Then I'll get her to come back.
My persistence is stronger
than your uppercut.
I'll go first...
and smooth out any ruffled feathers.
Veronica, where's Archie?
Yeah, I'm going cold in here.
Ms. Andrews. Counselor Rivers, I presume.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting,
but Archie's not gonna be able to make it.
What? Why not?
He's feeling under the weather.
Since when? He was fine this morning.
We think it's food poisoning.
I'd love to reschedule.
I can fight.
I can still do this
-Are you out of your mind?
-I'm fine.
I'd like to show you what I got.
Fangs, you ready?
Yeah, let's do it.
-[Veronica] Archie.
-[Mary] Archie.
Serpents, Poisons,
we have a proposition for you.
The Pretty Poisons don't take orders
from you.
Please, Peaches,
we're talking about a Prom Night Truce.
So that we can all work together
to catch the Gargoyle King.
How does that sound?
The Poisons can get behind that.
During prom, groups of you
will be stationed at every entrance.
Once the announcement
for Prom Queen begins,
you guys are gonna bar anyone
from exiting the gym.
Whoever's cosplaying
as the Gargoyle King is gonna be there.
It's our one shot at nabbing him.
-Will he be in costume?
-Maybe.
Maybe not. At the minimum,
he'll have some sort of kingly signifier,
like a crown, or antlers, and the like.
He's gonna make his move
after Betty is crowned Prom Queen.
Let's end this nightmare.
Once and for all.
Nice and slow.
You took a fall there, kiddo.
That's what happens when you try
to fight two matches in one day
after starving yourself for a week.
[Archie sighs]
Where's Ronnie?
I asked Veronica to give us some space
so we can talk about
what's really going on with you.
[groans]
I shouldn't have double-booked.
You shouldn't have forged my signature
and lied to me.
Not to mention,
risking your health, Archie.
And to what end?
Mom, I wanna be a boxer.
You were so excited about the recruiter
that I wanted to give your way a shot.
But I don't wanna join the Navy.
I don't wanna go to college.
That's a losing battle for me.
I want to see how far
these fists can take me,
and I wanna fight.
And you're 17 years old.
You're thinking about tomorrow.
I'm thinking about the rest of your life.
Pop, I'm closing La Bonne Nuit early
for the night.
Most of my regulars will be at prom.
Veronica.
What?
What's going on, Pop?
A few months back...
I found something out.
Something I should've told you.
You're gonna wanna sit down for this.
[Tears for Fears'
"Head Over Heels" playing]
[chattering]
Well...
shall we, my lady?
Lead on, Hellcaster.
♪ And talk about the weather ♪
You two wanna vote for Prom Court?
-How's the turnout been?
-Lackluster.
Luckily, you're running unopposed.
Still, we don't want any... surprises.
So far so good.
I see the Serpents
and the Poisons are in place.
Now we just wait for the Gargoyle King
to make his move.
And you'll take him down.
I mean, imagine, Jug.
He may be in this gym right now.
Wanna dance while we look for him?
And before your coronation, Your Majesty?
Yes.
From the Back to School Dance
to the Junior Prom.
How much has changed.
Some things are still the same.
True.
Like my father.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Before I came here tonight...
Pop dropped a bombshell on me,
and I'm still reeling.
Apparently...
I don't own the diner.
My father does. And La Bonne Nuit, too.
But you bought it from your dad.
He tricked me.
He gave me a fake deed,
and kept the original.
All this year...
all this time...
I've been working for my father.
Everything I've made...
I put back into the business,
back into his pockets.
-Does he know that you know?
-No.
And I'm gonna act as though
nothing has changed.
I'm gonna do exactly what he would do,
manipulate him into digging his own grave.
That's our way through this mess.
"Our"?
I like hearing you say "our."
-It reminds me of--
-The old days?
Will you help me, Archie?
And this time,
we can take down my father for good?
Hell yeah.
I'm sorry you won't get
to be Prom Queen, babe.
I know how important it was to you.
It's okay, Tee-Tee.
Edgar gave me something better
than a Queenship.
Humility.
You can't mean that.
[sighs] No, you're right.
I can't and I don't.
And suddenly being a Farmie is making
a lot less sense to me.
Are you the Gryphon Queen?
This is for you.
Who sent this?
I got it from a druid,
who got it from a centaur,
who got it from someone else.
[Betty] "To Her Majesty the Gryphon Queen.
You've been summoned to the place
where the first Ascension Night was held.
Come alone.
Tell anyone,
and every reveler attending
the festival tonight will pay the price."
Good evening,
Riverdale Renaissance revelers.
At long last,
it's time to announce this year's court.
And the winner of Prom Queen...
is Betty Cooper.
[all cheering]
Is Betty here?
Hey, have either of you seen Betty?
Not gonna happen.
I did what you asked.
I came here alone.
What do you want?
Who are you?
[shouts]
[gasps]
Dad?
Why are you doing this?
[grunting and shouting]
Dad, you don't wanna do this.
Somebody, help me!
[screeching]
[grunting and shouting]
[screaming]
[banging on door]
[knocking on door]
[Jughead] Betty? It's Jug.
Jug.
Oh, God.
[sobbing]
-Did you see him? Did you see him?
-Who, the Gargoyle King?
No, the Black Hood.
The Black Hood is back, Jug.
It was a setup, Jug.
The Gospel that we found,
the Proclamation...
it was all to get me alone
with my dad again.
I can't believe none of us saw it coming.
The return of the Black Hood.
Now we have
two serial killers running around.
Possibly working together.
And both of them outsmarting us.
[sighs]
It's horrible, what happened at the dance.
I can't believe we were all in the gym
while that was going on.
I'm gonna stay in Riverdale
a little longer.
I don't want you alone
while your dad's away.
Okay.
That's great, Mom.
I'm gonna go for a run, if that's cool.
You're really committed to this,
aren't you, to boxing?
Well... I tried music, I tried football.
The world is such a scary place,
maybe it's not the worst thing
to know how to fight.
To be able to defend yourself.
Do you mean that?
If this is your path...
I wanna support it.
And you.
As long as you do it right.
I promise, Mom.
No more crash diets, or double-bookings.
Will you help me convince Dad?
[chuckles]
Mom.
-Betty, what are you doing here?
-Listen to me.
I was right.
Dad escaped.
He's back. I saw him.
No, they confirmed he's dead.
No, he survived.
He chased me during prom.
-He's killing people again.
-No, Betty. I left that all behind.
Mom, you have to deal with this.
Dad is back,
and I think he's coming here next.
What?
-Why would he come here?
-I told him about your engagement.
And how he plans to adopt the twins,
and he was really upset.
Why were you talking to that monster?
Because he fooled me.
What do we do?
[Edgar] You stay here.
Our walls are strong, Betty...
and our members stronger.
Let the Farm protect you, both of you.
Will you stay?
Yeah.