Previously on Riverdale...
Welcome to the Pit. Give us a show.
Hit me.
Warden Norton is in your pocket.
Everyone is in your pocket
except for me and Archie.
Where's Mad Dog? Captain
Golightly said he died.
So what did you do to him?
All three victims were playing
the game Gryphons and Gargoyles.
So you're admitting the
game killed Dilton and Ben?
You've clearly played G&G before,
and when you were my age, there
was another suspicious death
where the corpse had blue lips.
One of us was a murderer.
I saw a creature in the woods.
What if it's the same person
from the Midnight Club?
Swear to me that you won't play it.
I wanna be worthy, Ethel.
Could you please show me how?
Welcome to your first game.
This game, it's pure evil.
That book may be our
best shot of figuring out
what happened to Dilton and Ben.
We're gonna get the hell
out of here. We're escaping.
Count me in.
You are imprisoned in the
Gargoyle King's fortress.
Trapped in pens, you live in fear,
never knowing when
his legion of Gargoyles
will descend from the sky to feed.
But his guards are arrogant.
You've been able to observe
and study their movements,
and you've planned an escape.
Pit's down.
Baby Teeth got to the
breaker and cut the juice.
You're sure?
You're absolutely positive?
We can squeeze through those
wires at the top in that corner.
But it won't be long before they notice
and turn that fly fryer back on.
It's now or never, Archie.
Roll the dice to decide your fate.
Let's do it.
Now.
Remember. It's only a game.
It's not life or death...
They wouldn't...
Unless, of course, it is.
Your mission was
unsuccessful. Everyone dies.
Jug, you won't believe the
story my mom told me last night.
Jug, what are you doing?
Betty.
It's all making sense. All
of this is becoming clear.
The game, the Gargoyle King.
I'm on Level Three, but it's only
a matter of time until I ascend.
And I get to meet him.
So you've confirmed...
So my dad played G&G
in high school, huh?
- Of course, it makes so much sense.
- All of our parents did.
And they swore each other
to secrecy, but, Jug,
while they were playing, one of them
killed their principal back then,
Felix Featherhead, either
accidentally or on purpose,
but, he had blue lips.
Just like Ben and Dilton, which
is why all of this has to stop...
Betty, the fact that
our parents played G&G
just corroborates what
I've come to believe,
that we have been playing this
game for a lot longer than we know.
And off-board. Think about
it, the Hot Dog rescue,
what was that, if not a quest?
The Serpents, the
Ghoulies, what are they?
If not warring tribes, might as
well call us orcs and goblins.
Okay, you're not making any sense
and you're also not listening
to anything that I'm saying.
We have nine suspects that
are all real, tangible leads.
One of our parents could be a
murderer, so let's go investigate them.
You're not seeing the big picture.
"Eldervair," the realm
of Gryphons and Gargoyles
is an anagram for Riverdale.
The whole game is an
analog for Riverdale.
The game only exists in Riverdale.
That's why we couldn't
find it on the web.
Okay, well, that is a weird coincidence.
It's not a coincidence,
it's all connected.
It's all one big narrative that's
still being written and played.
Okay, you need to calm down,
Jug. Who's telling you this?
The game. The more I play,
the more familiar I become
with Eldervair and its rules,
the more I see the patterns.
The more I understand him or her,
and how we'll catch the Gargoyle King.
This game is their psychology.
It's their imagination.
It's how they view Riverdale.
My mom was right, this
game messes with your head.
No, no. This is the clarity
I needed, this is the truth.
G&G's myths, they are our stories.
They're our parents'
stories. Simple logic, Betty.
How do you catch a Game Master?
You become a Game Master
yourself. That's what I'm doing.
And in the end, when I
prove that I'm at his level,
I'll come face to face with him.
Fine. As long as you're safe down here,
that's one less thing for me to
worry about. So you keep playing.
I'm going to go figure this out,
starting with our nine suspects.
You really should go on a run
with me one of these morning, mija.
Nothing's more invigorating.
By the way,
did you hear what happened
at Leopold and Loeb?
Apparently, some
inmates tried to escape.
And I hear their ring leader
was, once again, Archie Andrews.
But no worries, the
guards caught them all
after shooting them with rubber bullets.
Of course, they'll be punished.
They might add an extra
year to Archie's sentence.
Huh.
My friend, Warden Norton
runs an awfully tight ship.
I know you're trying
to set me off right now,
but it won't work.
I'm getting Archie out,
one way or the other.
And then, you'll be the one rotting away
in the very prison your
blood money has built.
Yes.
Warden Norton, please.
Are you comfortable?
The idea to escape was all
mine. I told them to do it.
Why am I not surprised?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Let this serve as a reminder,
you can't fight your destiny.
No, please. No! Don't!
Hold up. You're telling
me that my mother
was a rule-breaking, anti-apartheid
activist in high school?
And that she and my dad
were together back then?
I don't buy it.
There's no way my old man
hung out and did, like, cosplay
with a group of lame-ass nerds.
Okay, it's true, Reggie.
And you want us to
find out what exactly?
My suspicion is that whoever
was running the game back then
is running it now.
Which is why we need to stop them
before things get any worse...
What, what are you trying to say?
That one of our parents
might be responsible
- for what happened to Dilton and Ben?
- Maybe.
And that's why you can't
tell them that you know
about their Midnight Club,
okay? You have to be careful
and subtle when you
ask them what they know.
This speakeasy is impressive, Veronica.
Impeccable taste and
a little elbow grease
go a long way, Elio.
But, from what I hear,
your Sweetwater Casino
will soon be giving the
Miragio a run for its money.
You know, if you added a
couple of slots, table games,
maybe some cocktails with actual liquor
you'd have quite the little gold
mine on your manicured hands.
Thank you for mansplaining
my business to me.
- But that's not why I asked you here.
- Right.
You wanted to talk Leopold and Loeb?
More than talk.
Archie's locked away in that hellhole,
and I haven't heard from him in weeks.
I've hit a dead end with
the Innocence Project.
However, I've heard rumors that
L&L has direct ties to the mob.
That's why I thought you, with
your connections, could help.
Tell you what, Veronica, I'll
talk to some of my dad's friends,
see what I can find out,
- but, if I scratch your back...
- I'm a Lodge. I know how this goes.
Just make it happen, and you'll
be appropriately recompensed.
Jones, we have a problem.
Your boys went off the deep-end
and got into the arsenal.
Oh, next time I'll get it.
What's going on here, fellas?
Toni and I were in her
tent having a rendezvous...
When this arrow shot right through it.
Three feet to the left and I'd
be missing an eye right now.
Yeah, well, we were practicing
our aim for the next quest.
We wanna go off-board,
take G&G to the real world.
- We heard other groups were doing it.
- Tough.
I'm the Game Master so I
decide when we go off-board.
You're the Serpent King, Jones.
Isn't that enough?
We're your foot-soldiers in life,
we gotta be the same in the game?
Down in the mud, taking all the risks?
Sweet Pea, we're not doing this again.
Cheryl, grab your bow, notch an arrow.
Jones, wait, what are you doing?
Come on. Fire.
He's not serious, is he?
Fire, Deadeye!
Whoa!
Sweet Pea, if you have
something to prove,
get against the tree.
What?
- Hell, no. You're crazy.
- No.
I'm Game Master, which means
it's my game and my rules.
You guys wanna go on a quest? You
want to prove you're bad-asses?
You're gonna get a chance.
But not until I say so.
Don't defy me again.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Elio, what's the good word?
I think I can get you
to your boy, Veronica.
You'll come as my date,
but dress incognito.
No problem. But, come
as your date to what?
It's better if you just see it.
So you're still screwing
around with this crap, huh, boy?
I guess the apple doesn't
fall too far from the tree.
The hell is that supposed to mean?
Means I know you played
G&G in high school, Dad.
And I know all about what
happened to your principal
- during the Ascension Party.
- How?
Betty. Which means
Alice spilled the beans.
Big time.
Yeah, well, whatever story
Betty's got in her head
about that night, you just remember
that's Alice's version, not mine.
So, tell me yours.
I've been through every
scenario about that night,
other people could have been sneaking
into the school same way we were.
Featherhead could have
had his own game going on.
Yeah, there are infinite possibilities.
But what's the most likely one?
I don't know. I don't know
who killed Featherhead.
I do. It was a Game Master.
Whoever planned Ascension Night.
Betty thinks it was someone from the
Midnight Club. But I'm not so sure.
I think it was someone
who's playing a much longer,
a much deeper game.
And whoever it was, I'm
going to get inside their mind
and then I'm going to catch them.
Don't you want that, Dad?
No, it's not that at all.
Well, this is nice. We
never get to do this.
Yeah, this is a blast.
So, uh, Mom, Mr. Keller,
Kevin and I were talking and we realized
that we don't really know
anything about how you two met.
Well, we were at Riverdale
High at the same time.
- So you were friends back then?
- More acquaintances.
We didn't run in the same circles.
Oh, so you didn't do any
extracurriculars together?
Not that I can recall.
Um, I was in Model UN
and Volunteers of America.
And I was in RROTC and
I was on the boxing team.
Did you guys ever play
Gryphons and Gargoyles?
Yeah.
I mean, I knew some kids that played
it, but I wasn't really into that stuff.
Yeah, it never really
appealed to me either.
Although, now that we're all together,
Josie, Kevin,
there's something we should discuss.
Elio, what is this place?
And why aren't we at the juvie?
It's a decommissioned Rec Center.
I didn't tell you beforehand because I
didn't want you calling in the cavalry.
At least not while I'm here.
My patience is wearing thin.
Easy, tigress, it's
just about show-time.
I'd recognize those abs anywhere.
- Archie?
- Relax.
I hear he always wins.
Archie?
Veronica.
Wait. I don't understand.
How are you here?
I know people who know people.
We only have about 20 minutes.
Oh, my God.
- What have they done to you?
- Ronnie.
I don't want to talk right now.
I have been pursuing legal options,
but it's dead-end after dead-end.
Which is why I'm thinking
an old-fashioned prison break
might be your best option.
Ronnie, nobody has ever broken
out of Leopold and Loeb before.
Fine. But we're not in
Leopold and Loeb right now.
The security Elio and I went
through to get in here was tight.
- So we'll need another entry point.
- You're serious about this?
Deadly. Why?
You have something in mind?
Look, it's a long shot.
But a couple weeks back, Warden
Norton had me hose down the pool
to get rid of the blood.
There's a drain, under the ring.
I have no idea where it leads or
if I can even squeeze through it.
Curse your broad shoulders.
But if there's even a chance...
Ronnie, I'm not sure
what I can do to help.
Nothing.
Let me do some research on the
place and see where the drain leads.
You just be ready when the time comes.
- When's your next fight?
- It's coming up. Fast.
Then that's when we're breaking you out.
Fellow Serpents,
I know all of you have been
eager to get back to Eldervair.
Well, cancel your plans.
We play tomorrow.
So they said nothing? Admitted nothing?
All they did was lie and act
like they didn't know about G&G.
Bury the lead, Kevin.
They also announced
they're getting married.
Oh, seriously? As what, a smokescreen?
I have no clue.
You think that was a crazy reaction?
This is what I got when I asked
my dad about that stupid game.
Why are our parents being so cagey
about something that
happened 25 years ago?
What aren't you telling us?
Guys, whatever this is, it has to wait.
What's wrong, Vee?
I saw Archie.
He's caught up in some
diabolical teen fight-club.
And I need to break him out of juvie
before he dies or kills somebody.
And you all have to help me.
Jug?
Betty.
What are you doing?
Getting ready for a party?
Yeah, we're about to start a
new quest. Do you want to join?
Even if I wanted to, I can't.
It's a long story but I'm helping
Veronica break Archie out of juvie
- and I'm hoping you can come with us.
- Wait. What?
You're breaking Archie out of juvie?
- I know it sounds insane.
- No.
Sounds perfect.
What? What do you mean?
Betty, this quest that I've been
working on, that we're about to start,
I thought I was finished, but it
lacked heart, it lacked humanity,
until you just gave
me the missing piece.
We'll make it a rescue mission,
to save their friend.
All Ethel ever talked
about was being worthy.
- What is more worthy than that?
- Jughead, this is not a game!
This is Archie's life and since
you refuse to recognize that,
I'm taking your bike.
This is quite the spread, Warden.
All this, after I tried to escape.
That makes me think
you're not rewarding me.
Hmm.
You're getting rid of me.
I'm afraid so.
Your final meal before your final fight.
You have powerful enemies, Archie.
I appreciate you being
honest with me, Warden.
But since this may be the
last meal that I ever eat,
can I ask you a question?
Go on.
How exactly did Hiram Lodge pin
Cassidy Bullock's murder on me?
Do you know?
It's as you imagine.
We paid Mr. Bullock's friends, the
ones that were with him that night,
$10,000 each to lie under oath.
And say that they saw
you pull the trigger.
That's how much your
life is worth, Andrews.
$30,000.
- Where are they now? Dead?
- They might as well be.
It's my understanding
that they're in hiding.
Some say, in Shadow Woods. But me,
I'd hide in the mines by Shadow Lake.
No chance of being found there.
One last question.
Does Hiram Lodge own you, too, Warden?
Has he always pulled the strings?
My soul belongs to no
mere mortal, Andrews.
Judgement of all men
belongs to he who resides
in the kingdom alone.
But he's watching us,
he's always watching.
Thank you all for coming.
I've gathered you all here
because the world is changing.
Strange, dark times have fallen upon us.
As you all know, Archie's
stuck behind bars.
His life is in danger.
The realm of Eldervair is in disorder,
afflicted by evil,
as its heart and soul, the Red Paladin
has been captured by the Mad Emperor
and twisted into a beast of war.
Before we get started, I
want to acknowledge that, yes,
we are flying by the
seat of our pants here,
but as much as possible,
we must follow the plan.
The slightest deviation, and
Archie could wind up dead.
We'll need a distraction
to disorient the guards and
hide Archie's play for the grate,
something we can sneak
into the location easily,
that won't arouse suspicion,
something we make ourselves.
As for the getaway route,
I want you positioned
for the pickup here, Bee.
If you stick to the woods,
their cars shouldn't
be able to follow you.
Just in case,
might I suggest we put
another precaution in place.
Joaquin,
something might go down.
If it does, just know that I
will come back for you guys.
Hey, Joaquin,
you with me?
Dude, what are you doing?
Our game begins with a Judas kiss.
I'm sorry, Archie. But the
Warden said that if I did this,
I'd finally ascend.
A dastardly act of betrayal.
A traitor has wounded the Paladin,
severely weakening his defenses.
With his life in peril, it's
now up to you, Dream Warriors,
to save the Red Paladin
and to restore peace
and order to the realm.
But be warned,
with every second that passes,
the Paladin's fate dims,
and with it, all hope
for peace in the realm.
Without further ado...
Let the game begin.
- Password?
- Contra.
Nice try.
That's what it was last time.
It changes every time.
- Hmm.
- What are your names?
Deadeye, you're at the entrance
of the Mad Emperor's dungeon,
but you've been blocked by a
bridge troll. How do you proceed?
I roll for an intimidation
spell, obviously.
What's my name?
What's your name?
I'm Monica Norton.
Perhaps you're familiar
with Warden Norton?
Of course.
Good. We understand each other then.
My fiance and I are here for the show.
We want to see blood.
The fighters' blood,
yours, I don't really care.
As long as it's red.
So if you need to call Warden
Norton to get me cleared...
Ah, that won't be necessary, miss.
Sorry for the delay.
Good job. You're inside.
Pantera, you're up.
Whoa, where are you going with that?
I'm supposed to put this
with the other refreshments.
If you don't mind, I
can just run this inside.
I think it's starting.
We're entering the Lion's Den.
The Paladin is being marched in
to meet his doom.
For he must face a
resurrected Hellhound.
Mad Dog!
I thought you were dead.
Where have you been?
It's me, Archie.
Care for a drink?
I just overheard some guards
betting heavily against Archie.
They say he's going down.
That other guy's huge. I'm
not sure Archie's got long.
Okay.
Get in position. Wait for my signal.
You've arrived at the
Mad Emperor's tunnel.
You found the entrance.
But, the Mad Emperor has placed a
Bano protection spell over the barrier.
Now that is super annoying.
Joaquin?
Kevin, what are you doing here?
We're breaking Archie out.
What are you doing here?
It doesn't matter. And
it's too late for Archie.
Where are you going?
Back to the Serpents?
No. No, no, no. I
joined a different gang.
- Who?
- You don't want to know, Kevin.
Just leave. You got to
get out of here. Right now.
- Wait...
- Go. Go!
Wait, Joaquin!
Come on. Hit me.
Right here. Do it.
I'm not fighting you, Mad
Dog. You're not my enemy.
But you got to listen to
me, there's a plan in place.
My girl is going to cause a commotion,
and I'm going to make a break
for the drain underneath the ring.
Come with me.
You'll never make it.
Not after getting shivved.
Yes, I can.
You're gonna need a head-start.
Deadeye Blossom, you're up.
- Betty, thank God.
- Kev, why isn't the grate opened?
There's a lock we didn't know about.
But look, Joaquin was just here,
and I have to go after him.
Well, I got this, but you can't go
after Joaquin. What about Archie?
I'll be back. I promise.
What is it, Game Master?
It's a curveball.
You're about to come
face-to-face with the Dark Dragon.
It's the most evil-tempered,
vile creature in the land.
With forked tongue and snarling black
slime, it reeks of rotting flesh.
Veronica, what do you
think you're doing here?
I can ask you the same, Daddy.
And I bet my answer's better than yours.
Whatever scheme you've
cooked up, it ends right now.
Sorry, Daddykins,
but this is going to hurt you
a lot more than it will me.
Ow!
Well played.
You've impaled the dragon
with your concealed dagger.
Mad Dog, let's go. Come on.
I won't get through that grate.
I tried. But you go.
I'll hold off the guards.
- Yeah, but you...
- Just go, Red! Don't look back.
- Warden, he's getting away.
- Guards! Stop him!
Find him.
We know where that pipe leads.
Find him right now!
Archie.
- Betty.
- Hi.
What took you so long?
I could ask you the same thing.
Are those clothes for me?
Oh, my God.
You're bleeding.
I got to put pressure
on it. Here, come here.
You freed the Paladin from the dungeon.
But you're not clear of
the Mad Emperor just yet.
What the hell are you
waiting for? Go after them!
In fact, the Emperor sends a
ruthless cavalry in pursuit.
Your noble steed is no match for
the cavalry's mighty stallions.
Do you continue on your path
or do you surrender and beg for mercy?
- Keep going!
- Never give up!
- Go! Go!
- Keep going!
You lean forward in your saddle
urging your horse to fly.
On all sides, the forest
becomes a blur of green,
but, a quick peek back
reveals the Emperor's nightmares
galloping at supernatural speed.
It's like hell itself is chasing
you and it's gaining ground.
One loose rock,
one cursed root will send you
toppling at this lethal speed.
But you force those
thoughts out of your mind.
You feel the battle-fury of
your forefathers rise within you,
an inextinguishable fire
pulsing through your veins.
You are the light
out-running the darkness.
Go around. It's on the other side.
You will escape, you will be victorious.
But then, you're barreling
towards the edge of a cliff,
you must stop.
What can we do for you, fellas?
Bravo!
Your deception gambit has paid off.
You've outsmarted the Emperor's cavalry.
Yeah!
Game Master.
Um, hello? What happened?
Did we save the Red Paladin?
I don't know. I made a
last-minute change to the quest.
I was hoping to have the ending or
the answer by the time I got this far.
What do you mean you don't know?
Game Master, where is the Red Paladin?
Where is he?
Where is the Red Paladin?
I... I don't know what
you're talking about.
Let him go, Warden Norton.
Let him go or I'll mace you.
Fall back.
Everyone, back to the center.
Is it over? Did he die?
There, you are all patched up.
Now don't make any sudden movements.
I won't. Thanks, Toni.
Who did that to you, Archie?
It was Joaquin. He stabbed me.
I think the Warden made him do it.
Guys, where the hell am I?
You're in Dilton Doiley's bunker.
The only people who know
it exists are in this room.
Right now, it's the safest place
for you in Riverdale. I promise.
Dilton Doiley has a bunker?
We'll catch you up to speed
once you're rested, okay?
Archie.
What is that on your hip?
Courtesy of Warden Norton,
to put me in my place after I
tried to escape the first time.
The Warden branded you and
ordered Joaquin to stab you?
Jug...
Can I have everyone's attention?
Since my father saw me,
I need to go do some damage
control on the home front.
But, someone needs to stay
with Archie at all times.
- Ronnie, I don't need anyone...
- Yes, you do.
You go ahead, Vee. Jughead and
I will take the first shift.
Excellent.
Now, equally important,
everyone in this room is part of a pact.
From this moment on, no one
knows where this bunker is.
No one was involved with that breakout,
and no one is aware of
Archie's whereabouts.
To the grave.
Capisce?
Are you out of your mind, Hiram?
Archie escaped from an
underground fight-club?
That you knew about?
I am being hounded by social workers.
The Innocence Project is
breathing down my neck!
I mean, for God's sake, I took
donations from Warden Norton.
Stop yelling. We can get
ahead of this. Contain it.
Oh, and finally, she arrives.
Do you have any idea the
kind of mess you've made?
Me? What about your husband?
Madre de Dios! You two are unbelievable.
This obsession that you both
have with Archie Andrews
is going to destroy us.
Where the hell are you going?
To try and contain the mess
that you and your daughter made.
I tried to find him, but it was no use.
- I had to double-back
and be the decoy. - Oh...
- Thanks, Pop.
- Welcome.
He's out there.
Joaquin is out there.
I still can't believe
we pulled off the escape.
Shh!
Sorry. My bad.
- It's a secret.
- Yeah.
Speaking of, are we
going to do this or not?
- I don't know, you guys.
- Come on, Josie.
Don't you want to find out what
our parents and Betty won't tell us?
I want to know the
truth. Wherever it leads.
We interrupt our Top Ten countdown
with an important news bulletin.
Convicted murderer,
Archibald Andrews has escaped
from the Leopold and Loeb
Juvenile Detention Center.
He is considered extremely dangerous.
The public is advised to remain indoors
and to report suspicious activity.
It is believed he will seek refuge
in his hometown of Riverdale.
He's finally asleep.
Jug, his burn mark...
You mean his brand?
Looks a lot like a runic symbol
from Gryphons and Gargoyles.
He said the Warden gave it to him.
The Warden also called
Archie a Red Paladin.
Does that mean the
Warden is playing G&G?
See, this is what I'm saying, Betty.
This game is so much bigger
than a couple of kids playing.
What if Warden Norton
is the Gargoyle King?
Jug,
before we dive back in,
I think you should go
home and get some rest.
How long has it been since you've slept?
Just get a couple of hours at least.
I'll take this watch.
Sleep well, Paladin.
I have a bad feeling your
trials are only beginning.
Sir, Mayor Lodge is here.
She'd like to have a word with you.
Tell her I'll be right out.
In the end, why did Warden Norton do it?
Was he afraid of retribution from the
authorities for his illegal activities?
Or was it that the game of G&G
he'd been playing was finally over,
and the Gargoyle King was
calling him home to ascend?
Either way, the result was the same.
Death by cyanide poisoning.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --