Previously on Mad Men...
This is over,
and not just this.
You should get some sleep.
How can I?
My wife's a big TV star.
Why didn't you tell us
Frank Gleason was dying?
Frank's going to be fine.
I wanted to make it clear.
Unless this works,
I'm against it.
Just saying the same thing.
So, how'd it go?
We went in together.
We won Chevy.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- ( horn blaring )
- Feel that torque?
It's like riding
a hard-on.
Come on, floor it.
My little girl's got
a heavier foot.
- ( men laughing )
- I'm going back.
Knock it off, Mikey.
Go on the shoulder.
I want to shoot this sign.
Put the gun away, Jack.
Jesus, what the hell
are you doing?
- ( horn blaring )
- ( tires screeching )
Sylvia: Arnie, you
should eat something.
How about some leftover veal
and some cold pasta?
Want a beer, honey?
Chicken salad or tuna?
Here come the judge.
What's the difference?
Eat it.
Who says we can't
hire more people?
Why don't you take a nap? Your
face looks like a bag of walnuts.
Everyone should take a rest.
It's an easy thing
to say, isn't it?
You're not thinking.
You're not writing.
Ted, calm down.
You need a nap, too.
Can you believe this crap?
Yes, I can.
Sorry I'm late.
You're sorry you're late?
You couldn't call?
He called.
I told you there's no news.
You did not make that clear.
You really didn't.
You just said "no news."
You didn't say Kenny called in.
- Pow.
- Damn it.
No one cares
that I almost got killed?
What did they say?
It's just like last time, no.
- What does that mean?
- It means they didn't like it.
Then they got drunk, they took
me for a joyride in the Impala.
Why can't we have the Impala?
What did they say?
They said they didn't like 'em.
It's your job to make
them like them.
- Are you not up to the task?
- Don.
What? We've given them seven
ways to go in six weeks.
We don't even get
to talk to them?
We have to depend
on this cripple?
You don't know
what he's up against.
I've got to sit down,
but I'm not gonna
if you're just gonna
continue to insult me.
Just sit down.
( sighs ) They gave me this
and I can't even
show it to you.
What is it?
They typed up their rejection?
It's worse.
They finally gave me
a calendar.
Three years
of monthly deadlines.
That's the rest
of '68, '69, and '70.
Best case scenario, six months
of strategy statements,
every one of them
backed up with copy tests.
And then, if and when
they land on something,
it's got to kick its way up
the ladder through all of GM
until it gets to God.
And then He's got to
run it past His wife.
So what happens now?
You take a swing at it
and they take a swing at me.
They want another packet
Tuesday morning.
- But they want me back on Sunday.
- For what?
I guarantee you
they're not going to church.
We cannot go on like this.
This is what Chevy
is paying us for.
It's not our clock,
it's theirs.
So what's another weekend?
Because they're
really paying us.
Mr. Chaough,
you have a phone call.
Take a message.
It's Nan.
It's about that matter.
Excuse me, Mr. Draper.
Get all the Chevy materials
back in my office.
- We're working the weekend.
- Yes, of course.
But I wanted to tell you
Dr. Rosen is on the phone.
- Do you want me to take a message?
- Yes.
- I'll find out what it's regarding.
- No.
I'll take it.
You know what, Don?
That's a great idea.
I'm gonna call my doctor.
I'm gonna get Kenny here fixed up.
I'm gonna get
everybody fixed up.
( door closes )
Arnold, how are you?
It's me.
( exhales ) Um...
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh, I bet you are,
because I wanted to let you know
that's what that would feel like.
I thought I misunderstood.
Oh, bullshit.
You have got to stop
loitering in my hallway.
Sylvia, I'm glad you called.
He saw all the cigarette
butts out there
and he thinks
I'm smoking again.
I want to see you.
I was in the kitchen
biting my nails
thinking,
"I just cleaned it up."
How many nights
are you out there?
I know you want to see me, too.
All I kept thinking
is he's gonna come in
and ask my why
there's no lipstick on them
and I'm gonna burst into tears
and tell him everything.
Then he's gonna murder me
and murder you.
- Are you afraid of him?
- No.
I'm afraid of you.
I don't think you understand.
Look, I'm too old
to say this was a mistake,
but I want you to try
and be happy.
About what?
That you got away with it.
When you start
something like this,
it takes a lot of convincing.
It's all about whether
or not the other person
has as much to lose as you do,
because you want to be able
to trust them when it's over.
And right now I'm wondering
how I ever trusted you.
I don't really have
a choice, do I,
because you've got me.
So if you ever really cared
about me at all, knock it off.
Don't cry.
Just listen to me.
I'm feeling a lot
of emotions, too.
I'm hanging up.
Please, just listen.
I just want to talk
to you about a few things.
You loved Megan once.
- Stop it.
- Nothing else gets through to you.
I'm going.
Don't make me hang up on you.
I'm hanging up.
( crashes )
- ( intercom buzzes )
- Dawn: Mr. Draper?
Mr. Draper?
I'm gonna go in there.
- Yes?
- Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm gonna...
I'm tired.
I'm just gonna take a nap.
You do that.
( sighs )
( coughing )
You girls should back away.
Does he have a fever?
You get your bedroll.
You stay in here,
you'll get everybody sick.
- You sleep in the cellar.
- Yes, ma'am.
If the fever doesn't break,
we'll call a doctor.
Better for you
than for everyone.
Aimée, did you leave
that plate in the lounge?
- ( intercom buzzes )
- Dawn: Mr. Draper?
- Yes, what is it?
Do you need some water?
No, I'm fine.
Bobby, go get your suitcase.
- That's mine.
- What about Gene's?
I'm not going
to pack his suitcase.
I already did it.
You just have to get it.
- Go get it, Geenie.
- ( door closes )
Go up there and get
Pinocchio and bring it down.
( sighs )
I have to do everything.
- Where's Daddy? We're ready to go.
- I'm taking you.
Were you sitting under the hair
dryer and just remembered that?
Where did you get that skirt?
I bought it.
You mean Megan
bought it for you.
- I earned it.
- On what street corner?
She pays me to babysit.
You're not a hired hand,
you're their sister.
Boys, let's go.
- ( knocks )
- ( door opens )
I'm sorry to bother you,
but Mr. Cutler
wants to see you.
It's been two and a half hours.
Do you want to rest some more?
No.
May I clean that up?
Please.
Put the Chevy materials
on the coffee table.
The funeral will be tomorrow.
Frank's family has asked
that in lieu of flowers
a donation be made to the
American Cancer Society.
Frank Gleason
was a great artist
and a great friend.
And he made our company whole.
I'm not gonna be able to work
with you through the weekend.
I apologize, but I'm afraid
this takes precedence.
I'll attend the funeral
if that's all right.
But I can still make myself
available for Chevy.
That's helpful.
I'm sorry for your loss.
He's a piece
that cannot be replaced.
The doctor's here
and I want you to see him.
- I don't know.
- No, he's gonna fix you up.
That's an order.
Can I see him, too?
I did it last time.
We're a team.
If he does it, I do it.
Age before beauty.
How old was he?
Older than you,
younger than me.
You either get used to it
or stop thinking about it.
Sorry about your friend.
Yeah, it's tragic.
I hope we don't lose
Ted for too long.
He doesn't know how
to deal with these things.
Do you feel anything?
'Cause I don't.
He said it takes a minute.
- Well, maybe I need another.
- I'm next.
Actually, Roger, I think
Don should go next. Don.
Pleasure to meet you.
Dr. Hecht.
Don Draper.
Where do you want me?
Anything in your medical history
you want to alert me to?
No, I'm just--
hell, I don't even know
what I'm doing here.
You're exhausted.
I'll need you to turn
around and drop your pants.
- This goes in the gluteus.
- What is it?
It's an energy serum.
Oh? What's in it?
It's proprietary.
But all you need to know
is it's a complex
vitamin superdose.
It's basically my own combination
of B vitamins and a mild stimulant.
You have a heart condition?
No. I thought you said it was mild.
What does it do?
Well, a lot of things.
But I think it'll give you
what Jim Cutler says you need.
24 to 72 hours
of uninterrupted creative
focus, energy, and confidence.
- Really?
- Really.
No one told you about this?
I've visited
some agencies lately.
- You've got a great outfit here.
- Thank you.
All anybody wants to know is what
are you gonna call this place?
Can you tug your drawers
down a little?
"SCDPCGC"?
That's a mouthful.
- Stan again.
- ( laughs )
What do you say, Don?
You think you can beat me?
I want another chance.
You changed course.
- Who's next?
- That'd be me.
- And I have a heart condition.
- Don't worry about it.
( panting )
( laughs )
Come on, let's go.
Best two out of three.
( echoing ) You can beat me any day.
Let me see the doctor first.
We'll do before and after.
( coughing )
Hey, kid.
Where you going?
Come in here.
( coughing )
Sit down.
Breathe deep.
( inhales )
Is that you?
No.
It's a chest cold. I've
seen plenty of consumption.
You don't have it.
Lay down here.
Your mama don't know
how to take care of nobody.
She ain't my mother.
( coughs )
Can I help you?
Do we know each other?
I'd like to think so.
Can I help you?
I meant from somewhere
other than from this moment.
I don't think so.
( loud clicking )
- ( men laughing )
- ( phones ringing )
( ringing, laughing increases )
( silent )
- Where's Ed?
- He said his heart stopped.
Roger took him to the hospital.
But they were both laughing.
The strategy is about some
kind of love transaction
between a parent and a child
involving the greatest
gift of all, a Chevy.
I was a child and she was a child
in this kingdom by the sea.
Four score and seven years ago,
this country had some
memorable happenings.
What I don't understand is
is it "Dad, I want this car"
or "Son, I bought
you this car"?
Great, that's two. We need 15
more and we can try another.
In what family is it "Son,
I bought you this car"?
- Good night, all.
- That guy's family.
Did you hear about
Frank Gleason?
( laughs ) Yeah, I guess
dreams do come true.
I think that's in poor taste.
Tell him, Peggy. Tell him
what a son of a bitch he was.
I liked him.
Before he was sick?
I hate how dying makes
saints out of people.
Well, he's obviously
in a better place.
Have a good weekend.
"Dad, I need the car.
I've got a date."
"Dad, everybody at school
has a car but me."
"Dad, I can only go
to college if I have a car."
- "Dad, I--"
- "Dad, I could be dying in Vietnam.
Don't you want me
to have a car?"
Damn it, Ginsberg.
I had another 80 of them.
I got nothing interesting to
say 'cause I'm not on drugs?
No, you just flushed
a toilet in my head.
"Son, I got a car
when I was your age."
"Son, they didn't have
cars when I was your age."
"Son, you can fly till you're
high as an elephant's eye."
- ( Stan chuckles )
- That's great.
What are you, class secretary?
I want to write stuff down
so it looks like I'm working.
Fine.
The child is the father
of the man.
Spectacular.
- ( intercom buzzes )
- Dawn: Mr. Draper.
Mr. Cosgrove is here
to see you.
Hello, Kenny.
How you feeling?
My foot's like new.
You think you'll have
new work on Monday?
I'll have 15 campaigns
for you by then,
but you have to get me in a room
so I can look them in the eye.
The timbre of my voice
is as important as the content.
I don't know whether
I'll be forceful or submissive,
but I must be there
in the flesh.
You understand that I have
no power whatsoever?
That's not true.
Not if they like you.
- ( feet tapping )
- Oh, they like me all right.
( tapping )
- I'm their favorite toy.
- That's your job.
It's my job to take them to
dinner at 80 miles an hour.
It's my job to stop
a mile from the restaurant
so they can have
five pounds of crab legs
and three bottles of beer apiece
and then go get prime rib.
It's my job to go hunting so
they can fire off their guns
an inch from my ear and laugh
when I get startled
because it's my job.
Where'd you learn that?
My mother.
No, my first girlfriend.
( tapping )
One doesn't like changing
so often, you know?
- I don't know.
- I'm not myself, you see?
I don't see.
And she comes
to the fork in the road
then she says to the Cheshire
Cat, "Which road do I take?"
I know this.
Where do you want to go?
- I don't know.
- Then it doesn't matter, does it?
- How's it going?
- What's going on?
I know you're all feeling
the darkness here today.
But there's no reason
to give in.
No matter what you've heard, this
process will not take years.
In my heart I know
we cannot be defeated
because there is an answer
that will open the door.
There is a way
around this system.
This is a test of our patience
and commitment.
One great idea
can win someone over.
Dear Lord, you're as
good as they say.
That was very inspiring.
Do you have any idea
what the idea is?
No.
But I'm not gonna stop looking.
( sighs ) I think we
should order dinner.
I don't think
I'll ever eat again.
Do what you have to.
( coughing )
- You're burning up.
- ( sniffles )
You have to eat something.
Sit up.
I can't, Miss Swenson.
Call me Aimée,
and yes, you can.
( coughing )
I've got it.
How many times do you do it?
I need six throws
for a reading.
What are you doing?
The I Ching.
Have you slept?
Crap, I missed
the funeral, didn't I?
- How was it?
- It was rough.
It was beautiful.
Who are you?
Her name is Wendy.
Wendy, this is Don.
Don. Ask a question.
- I'm supposed to be next.
- Are you done with mine?
You can just think of it.
You don't have to say it out loud.
Perfect.
Peggy, do you remember
when we had soup?
( chuckles ) Maybe.
Could you be more specific?
Carnegie Deli has great soup.
No, he's talking
about some account.
He asked me yesterday.
I don't think it exists.
- No, I didn't.
- I don't understand what you're asking.
We had an account at Sterling Cooper.
A soup account.
That must have been
before my time.
Can you go to the
archives and look for it?
I already looked.
Why are you asking her?
- 'Cause you think I'm incompetent?
- I did it!
I've got 666 ideas.
I'm wasting my Saturday
with lunatics.
- It's Saturday?
- Yes, it is.
Why don't you lay down
for a little while?
Because I've got it. I want
you to go to the archives.
Look in 1958 or '59 for soup.
You'll know it when you see it
and it's gonna crack
this thing wide open.
You see the mess you made?
Wendy:
That was fast.
What are you doing in here?
You said you were
going to get some ice
and we were going to have a
drink and watch the sun set.
I have some things to do.
Stop doing that.
( chuckles ) You are really
uptight, aren't you?
No, I'm just on a deadline.
Where'd you get that?
It was upstairs
in one of the offices.
You want to get it on?
Wendy, what are you doing here?
I'm here to make you
feel better.
I feel great,
but I'm on a deadline.
"Does someone love me?"
What?
That's what your question was.
Why would you say that?
That's everyone's question.
I want to hear your heart.
Oh.
I think it's broken.
You can hear that?
I can't hear anything.
I think it's broken.
You should go.
I'm in the middle of something.
( door opens )
( door closes )
( phone ringing, TV playing )
Megan:
Can you get that?
If it's Jeff Hunter,
I'll be right there.
- Draper's.
- Sally?
- When are you coming home?
- Is Megan there?
- I want to talk to him.
- It's my dad.
Where are you?
I'm still at work.
I have to leave.
I'm leaving right now.
I'm really sorry.
I'm not finished yet.
It-- I'm really close.
It's just the research
hasn't come in.
Don, I don't care.
What am I supposed to do?
I watched them last night
so you could work and now--
I'll be home in a little bit.
Well, I don't like
you working so hard.
You must be exhausted.
Actually, I've got
a second wind.
When's he coming home?
Sally, how would you like to earn
some boots to go with that skirt?
You're going to leave us
with her again?
I'm really sorry, sweetie,
but you know you'll have fun.
Don't make her feel bad.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see a play.
And Jeff my agent is going to
introduce me to some producers
so that maybe I can
be in their play.
Why do you want to do a play?
You're on TV every day.
Don't they know that?
Shit, you must be hungry.
Sally, would you put
a pot of water on the stove?
I'm gonna make
spaghetti in a minute.
I'm gonna wait for Dad.
We're not hungry.
Okay, but go make Gene
a peanut butter and jelly.
Come on, that thing's
twice the size of a real apple.
Step right up.
How about everybody takes one?
Do a real firing squad.
He's gonna look
just like Saint Sebastian.
Hold on a second.
One at a time.
Everybody'll get a chance.
You're pretentious,
you know that?
I love that.
I'm gonna do it.
Fine, but I'm gonna go first
because you're drunk.
In fact, I believe
I'm the only person
in the Time-Life Building
who's not out of his mind.
But you hate him.
I hate apples more.
Don't hit his eye.
Don't hit anything.
- ( grunts )
- Ah!
- Aw, crap.
- Who's next?
It's fine. It's fine.
I've done that before.
- Doesn't hurt at all.
- Let me see. Let me see.
You've gotta keep
pressure on it.
Honestly, Peggy,
I don't even feel it.
Come on, you've got
to wash this.
( Stan laughs )
( pen clatters )
( "Going Out of My Head"
plays in background )
( taps )
♪ ...each morning ♪
♪ You just walk past me ♪
♪ You don't even know
that I exist ♪
♪ Going out of my head
over you ♪
♪ Out of my head over you ♪
♪ Out of my head
day and night ♪
♪ Night and day and night,
wrong or right ♪
♪ I must think of a way ♪
♪ Into your heart ♪
♪ Oh, there's no reason why ♪
♪ My being shy ♪
♪ Should keep us apart... ♪
Hold still.
You got a great bedside manner.
What are you doing?
( kisses )
You're lucky
I don't like beards.
Women say that, but
they don't act like it.
You're like my brother.
You don't have a brother.
I want you to stop.
No, you don't.
I have a boyfriend.
No.
( sighs ) Come on.
I need this.
I know, I know.
You're in pain.
( sighs )
My cousin Robbie
was killed in action.
20 years old.
Had to join the fucking Navy.
That's awful.
What happened?
They don't tell you.
They just tell you
when it happened.
March 4th.
Three months ago.
( sighs )
That means my aunt sent
16 letters that he never saw.
You know they get mail
right up to the front lines?
That'd be a bad job, right?
Delivering mail into combat?
I'm so, so sorry to hear that.
I've had loss in my life.
You have to let
yourself feel it.
You can't dampen it
with drugs and sex.
It won't get you through.
Maybe we're different.
Why don't you go home?
( laughs ) 'Cause I can't
stand up right now.
That's from the shot.
You've got a great ass.
Thank you.
( clattering )
- Hello?
- Oh!
You startled me.
I didn't know anybody was home.
What are you doing?
Go back to sleep.
What are you doing here?
I'm visiting.
Didn't nobody tell you?
No.
Who are you?
I'm your grandma.
That's impossible.
Now, why is that impossible?
Okay, I know.
But I raised your daddy.
What are you doing here?
I was just looking
for a serving plate.
I was gonna make
your daddy's favorite.
You know, he loves
fried chicken.
I bet you do, too.
Ooh, you sure look like him.
No one said you were coming.
Well, I think I was supposed
to be a surprise for you.
And your daddy
said I could visit
and he gave me a key.
I thought nobody was home.
Come over here and give a hug
to your Grandma Ida.
Now don't you be rude to me.
Is that how you was raised
to speak to your betters?
No.
I'm gonna fix you some eggs.
And you're gonna sit down
and you're gonna eat 'em.
But first, you're gonna tell
me who else in the house.
How come you don't know?
I haven't talked to your daddy
in a long time.
And he want
to surprise me, too.
I've never heard of you.
Your daddy Mr. Donald
Draper or not?
You come over here
and give me some sugar.
Now I know you ain't
here all by yourself.
My little brothers are here.
Well, there's no need
to wake them.
Just be us.
Okay, let's go
and make you some eggs.
I bet you like them scrambled.
I can make them.
And burn yourself on the stove?
When you think
they're gonna be home?
I don't know.
When's the last time
you saw my dad?
Years ago.
I doubt he's changed.
He still handsome?
Yes.
Your mama still
a piece of work?
( laughs ) Yes.
Now what do they call you?
Sally.
_
( "Dream a Little Dream"
plays in background )
♪ Stars fading,
but I linger on, dear ♪
♪ Still craving your kiss ♪
♪ I'm longing
to linger... ♪
- Your fever broke.
- Ahem.
- Yes, Miss Swenson.
- Call me Amy.
It's not really Aimée. I just
liked the way it was spelled.
It's got two Es and an accent.
It's a nice name.
You are better.
♪ But in your dreams,
whatever they be... ♪
Do you like this?
I do.
Do you like girls?
You don't even know what
to do right now, do you?
But you like it.
Stop it.
You like my bosom.
I don't know.
Don't you want to know
what all the fuss is about?
No.
It's okay.
I'll do everything.
♪ But in your dreams,
whatever they be ♪
♪ Dream a little dream
of me. ♪
_
( rustling )
What are you looking for?
Now you stop asking questions
or I'm not gonna let you eat
in your nice living room.
Maybe I know where it is.
I'm just looking for some place
to hide my presents
I bought y'all.
My, that TV's in here good!
Who's she?
Is that little Bobby?
My, you have grown up big!
- Who are you?
- That's Grandma Ida.
We don't have a grandma.
You do now.
And you're gonna get
all the candy and toys
and good stuff
your grandma bought you
when you wake up
in the morning.
But right now,
you go back to sleep.
I'm not tired.
Now, Sally don't remember,
but I gave your daddy a watch,
gold watch.
And I got a new band for it
and I wanna fix it up
before he come back.
You seen it?
He has four watches.
I'll know it when I see it.
They're in the drawer
by his bed.
Are we allowed to watch TV?
I think she's lying.
Are we Negroes?
Will you put me through
to the police?
It's an emergency.
I'm at 783 Park Avenue
and there's a stranger
in our apartment.
What?
No, I'm 14.
My name is Sally Draper.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
These children
ought to be in bed
and they ain't
too well behaved.
Yes, sir. They played
a joke on both of us.
Uh-huh.
Good night.
Now why'd you do
something like that?
You hurt my feelings.
I'm gonna go out
and get some air.
When I come back,
you best be sleeping.
( door opens, closes )
( lock clicks )
( TV remote clicks )
( rapid clicking )
"This may be hard to believe,
but the history
can't be ignored.
The history should not
be ignored.
Look, I don't want to waste
your time, with..."
Peggy!
"I don't want you
to shut this door.
Just let me say a few things.
You and I both know--"
Did you want us?
Yes.
Get everyone.
No, wait.
Just listen.
I've got it.
Great.
Remember this work?
I've never seen it before.
Well, it says it all.
It really does.
Okay, I've got
this great message
and it has to do with what
holds people together.
What is that thing
that draws them?
It's a history.
And it may not even be
with that person, but it's...
it's like a...
well, it's bigger than that.
And that makes them buy a car?
If this strategy is successful,
it's way bigger than a car.
It's everything.
I keep thinking about the basic
principle of advertising.
There's entertainment
and you stick the ad
in the middle of the entertainment
like a little respite.
It's a bargain.
They're getting
the entertainment for free.
All they have to do
is listen to the message.
But what if they don't
take the bargain at all?
What if they're suddenly
bored of the entertainment?
What if they don't--
what if they turn off the TV?
- You gotta get your foot in the door.
- Exactly!
So, how do I do that?
Let's say I get her
face to face.
How do I capture
her imagination?
I have a sentence, maybe two.
Who's "her"?
Promise them everything. You know,
you're gonna change their life.
- You're gonna take away their pain.
- That's good.
Then you hit 'em
with the one-two punch.
What's the answer
to all of life's problems?
A Chevy.
No, it's not.
Then it's oatmeal?
No.
What have you been doing
the last three days?
Have you been working
on Chevy at all?
I gotta go.
You wanna get someone
in here who can draw?
No, I don't have time for art.
He's happy.
Now we can relax.
You think he'll care
if I nap in here?
Don? Wait.
( moaning )
I'm going home!
Okay, I'm gonna
change my shirt,
tell Megan I'm going out
for cigarettes,
then I'm gonna knock
on her door.
Sylvia, don't close
the door on me.
( sighs )
"When in the course
of human events--" no.
"You haven't heard
everything I have to say."
Don't shut the door on me.
All right, all right,
he's home.
Oh, thank God you're here.
What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
Some elderly Negro woman
held your children hostage
and robbed you blind.
- What?
- Betty.
She robbed a bunch
of places in the building
and she came in here.
Our back door was open.
She said she was your mother.
We think we caught her
boarding the IRT.
You'll need to come down
in the next 24 hours
and ID your things.
Because no one was here.
Because she's off on the
casting couch and you're--
what does he tell everybody,
that he's at work?
This is not the time or the
place for this conversation.
Ma'am, this could have
happened to anyone.
Anyone who lives
in this disgusting city
and leaves their
three children alone.
Do you know Henry's
running for office?
Sally, I'm really sorry.
I should have been
home earlier.
I want to go home.
( sighs )
Miss Swenson: You get your hands off me!
I don't need to be manhandled!
Mack: I know you've
been holding out on me.
You don't know anything.
I defy your accusations.
You peddle that ass
on the street.
You don't deserve a home.
You don't deserve me.
Yeah? I do fine
without you.
- And you owe me money, not the
other way around. - Get out.
'Cause I took
that boy's cherry.
$5, we'll call it even.
Is that true?
No.
You filthy, shameful,
disgusting, shameful,
horrible...
You're trash!
You are filth!
You know that you are!
After I gave you a home,
you go and do something
this disgraceful!
I know you're exhausted, but I could
feel the floor swimming, too,
when I came home to that.
I'm surprised
we didn't all faint.
( sighs )
I'm really sorry.
Sally seems so grown up,
but she's really still a kid.
( doors close )
( elevator bell rings )
- How are you?
- Busy.
( doors close )
( faint rattling )
( elevator bell rings )
You should talk to him.
Hello?
I just wanted to call
and tell you I'm okay.
I didn't have a heart attack.
I've just been working
too much.
I'm-- I'm so embarrassed.
I acted like
a stupid little kid.
No, you didn't.
And I'm sure she's fooled
plenty of adults, too.
She said she knew you.
I asked her everything I know
and she had an answer
for everything.
Then I realized I don't know
anything about you.
- ( intercom buzzes )
- Dawn: Mr. Chaough wants to see you.
You did everything right.
Try and forget about it.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Sally.
I left the door open.
It was my fault.
Okay. Bye.
( line clicks )
( door opens )
I need to talk to you.
Morning, fellas.
I'm fine.
Thank you for asking.
How could you bring
Frank's little girl here?
I let her tag along.
I kept an eye on her,
didn't I, Don?
Who?
Wendy.
Believe me, it's a lot better
than what could have happened
if I had let her loose in the
Village like she wanted.
Well, that's not
what her mother thinks.
What the hell went on
here this weekend?
Half of this work is gibberish.
"Chevy" is spelled wrong.
Look, I am going
to continue on Chevy
in my function
as creative director.
That is, evaluating
other people's work.
That's all I can do right now.
Call me around 1970
when they're ready
to make an ad.
What are you talking about?
I can't do this by myself.
I'm sorry, Ted.
But every time we get a car,
this place turns
into a whorehouse.
( "Words of Love" plays )
♪ Words of love,
so soft and tender ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ If you love her,
then you must send her ♪
♪ Somewhere where
she's never been before ♪
♪ Worn-out phrases
and longing gazes ♪
♪ Won't get you
where you want to go ♪
♪ No! ♪
♪ Words of love... ♪