>> [laughs]
HI, I'M KATIE.
WE SHOULD JUST, LIKE, DANCE IN,
LIKE, ONE BIG GROUP.
AND I'M FROM ROCK SPRINGS,
WYOMING.
THERE'S NOT MUCH OUT HERE
BESIDES MOUNTAINS AND WIDE-OPEN
SPACE, BUT MY FRIENDS AND I
FIND WAYS TO HAVE FUN.
DON'T DO ANYTHING SCARY!
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
BUT I'M STILL REALLY CLOSE WITH
BOTH OF THEM.
BUT THE PERSON I'M CLOSEST WITH
IS MY BOYFRIEND, JOEY.
JOEY AND I ARE ATTACHED AT
THE HIP, AND WE DO EVERYTHING
TOGETHER.
I HOPE IT STAYS LIKE THIS
FOREVER.
AND SINCE OUR FAMILIES GET ALONG
GREAT, MY MOM LET ME MOVE IN
WITH HIM, SO NOW JOEY AND I LIVE
WITH HIS MOM AND STEP-DAD
AND HIS LITTLE BROTHER AND
SISTER.
I'M ALMOST DONE WITH MY SENIOR
YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL.
I GET REALLY GOOD GRADES,
AND I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO GO
AWAY TO COLLEGE IN DENVER.
MY LONG-TERM PLAN IS TO GET
A MASTER'S DEGREE IN PSYCHOLOGY.
AND EVERYBODY IS GONNA CALL ME
DR. KATIE.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO PUT THAT ON HOLD
BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
I'M SIX MONTHS PREGNANT AND
NEARING THE END OF MY SENIOR
YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL.
BUT IT'S SUNDAY AND ONE OF
THE FIRST NICE SPRING DAYS OF
THE YEAR.
>> WHERE DO YOU WANT TO SIT?
>> JOEY'S BEEN SO SUPPORTIVE,
AND I LOVE GETTING TO SPEND TIME
WITH HIM.
WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHER FOR
A LONG TIME.
>> LIKE, 12 OR 13, PROBABLY.
>> MM-HMM.
YOU WORE, LIKE, SKINNY PANTS,
LIKE, SILVER JEANS.
>> [laughs]
>> AND THEY WERE, LIKE, GIRL
PANTS.
I WAS LIKE, "JOEY IS SO HOT."
[chuckles]
I NEVER KNEW YOU AS THE TYPE OF
GUY THAT WOULD, LIKE, WANT
A GIRLFRIEND.
>> 'CAUSE I'M NOT THE TYPE OF
GUY THAT NORMALLY WANTED
A GIRLFRIEND.
>> IT'S FUNNY, THOUGH, 'CAUSE,
LIKE, WE WOULD SLEEP IN THE SAME
BED, BUT I WOULD NEVER LET YOU
HAVE SEX WITH ME.
I JUST, LIKE, WANTED YOU TO BE
IN A RELATIONSHIP WITH ME BEFORE
I, LIKE--I DIDN'T WANT TO BE,
LIKE, SOME STUPID HO THAT, LIKE,
CAME TO YOUR HOUSE AND, LIKE,
JUST HAD SEX WITH YOU.
I WANTED YOU TO RESPECT ME.
>> I DID.
>> SO AROUND THE TIME THAT WE
GOT PREGNANT, BIRTH CONTROL WAS,
LIKE, NEVER A BIG DEAL, BECAUSE
IT WAS JUST, LIKE, YOU REACHED
OVER AND GRABBED A CONDOM,
AND IT WAS THAT--
>> SOMETIMES.
IF THEY WERE THERE, I USED THEM;
IF NOT, THEN WE JUST KIND OF DID
OUR THING.
>> I JUST WISH I WOULD'VE, LIKE,
REALIZED THAT BEFORE, LIKE, THAT
IT WAS, LIKE, NOT YOUR JOB;
IT WAS MY JOB.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK IT'S BOTH PEOPLE'S JOB,
BUT APPARENTLY I DIDN'T DO TOO
GOOD OF A JOB.
>> OUR FRIENDS WERE SHOCKED WHEN
THEY FOUND OUT WE WERE HAVING
A BABY.
THE DAY THAT I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT--I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW
YET, LIKE, THAT DAY THAT I
CALLED YOU ON THE PHONE.
WHEN I WAS CRYING, AND I WAS
LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN" AND ALL THAT STUFF.
AND YOU'RE LIKE, "WELL, HAVE YOU
TAKEN A TEST?"
AND I'M LIKE, "I HAVEN'T LOOKED
AT IT YET."
YOU'RE LIKE...
>> "WELL, CALL ME BACK."
>> "WELL, CALL ME BACK
WHEN YOU KNOW."
>> I REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU GUYS KNEW
SHE WAS PREGNANT.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE JUST PULLING
MY CHAIN, BRO.
>> [laughs]
>> "NO, SHE'S NOT.
DON'T LIE TO ME."
EVERYTHING'S CHANGED SO MUCH.
WE USED TO BE PARTY, PARTY,
PARTY, SLEEP, PARTY, YOU KNOW?
>> IT'S 'CAUSE HE MET ME,
AND I STRAIGHTENED HIM OUT.
>> MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS,
IF JOEY WAS, LIKE, HAPPY OR MAD
ABOUT IT, AND THEN WHEN
YOU TOLD ME HE WAS HAPPY,
LIKE--IT WAS KIND OF,
LIKE, A RELIEF.
AT LEAST YOU HAVE SOMEONE BESIDE
YOU, LIKE, HELPING YOU NOW.
>> THAT WAS MY BIGGEST FEAR THAT
JOEY WAS GONNA BE LIKE, "WELL,
I'M STILL A KID," YOU KNOW,
AND COMPLETELY BOOK IT OUT OF
MY LIFE.
BUT THEN WHEN I SAW, LIKE--AFTER
I WAS CRYING THE WHOLE TIME AND,
LIKE, FREAKING OUT, AND I SAW
THAT HE WAS, LIKE, STILL
THERE--AND THAT KIND OF JUST
MADE ME FEEL LIKE, "OKAY, I'M
PRETTY LUCKY, 'CAUSE THAT
DOESN'T HAPPEN."
LIKE, NORMALLY THE GUY IS
THE FIRST ONE TO RUN
IN THE OTHER DIRECTION.
BUT THAT'S THE FIRST TIME I EVER
TRUSTED A GUY, WAS AFTER THAT.
I KNOW I'M LUCKY TO HAVE JOEY,
AND I HOPE THINGS DON'T CHANGE
TOO MUCH ONCE THE BABY COMES,
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE MY BEST
FRIEND IS ABOUT TO HEAD OFF TO
COLLEGE WITHOUT ME.
>> I AM LEAVING, LIKE, NEXT
MONTH.
>> I FEEL DITCHED.
>> DO NOT FEEL DITCHED.
>> LIKE, I WANTED TO GO TO
DENVER WITH YOU.
I WANTED TO LIVE WITH MY BEST
FRIEND IN THE BEST CITY ON THIS
PART OF THE WORLD.
AND NOW, LIKE, I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> I WAS LIKE, "WE HAVE BEEN
PLANNING THIS SINCE DAY ONE."
>> IT WAS SO FRUSTRATING,
THOUGH, WHEN THE LADY FROM
THE ADMISSION OFFICE--
>> MM-HMM, I REMEMBER WHEN YOU
GOT ACCEPTED, AND YOU WERE
SO HAPPY.
>> YEAH, I TOLD HER--I WAS LIKE,
"I CAN'T COME."
AND SHE'S LIKE, "OH, WELL, ARE
YOU GOING SOMEWHERE ELSE?"
I WAS LIKE, "YEAH, I'M GOING TO
COMMUNITY COLLEGE."
[both laugh]
>> YOU'RE LIKE, "UGH."
>> AND I WAS ALL UPSET.
"I GOT PREGNANT, AND SO NOW I
JUST HAVE OTHER PRIORITIES IN
LIFE, AND I COULDN'T DO, LIKE,
UNIVERSITY AND BABY AND--
BUT I THINK YOU HAVE A FABULOUS,
FABULOUS SCHOOL.
IT'S A SCHOOL OF DREAMS."
>> YOU'RE LIKE, "IT WAS MY
DREAM."
>> YEAH.
>> SO AFTER YOU, LIKE, HAVE...
THE LITTLE ONE, ARE YOU GONNA,
LIKE, GO TO DENVER LIKE YOU
WANTED TO?
>> ME AND JOEY, LIKE, HAVE
TALKED ABOUT THAT,
MOVING IN TWO YEARS.
LIKE, HIM GETTING A JOB AND US
SAVING MONEY.
IT'LL STILL HAPPEN.
IT JUST WON'T BE THE SAME WAY
THAT I WANTED IT TO BE, LIKE--
>> YEAH.
>> THE WAY THAT I PLANNED
EVERYTHING TO BE.
EVEN THOUGH I LIVE AT JOEY'S,
I STILL GO TO SEE MY MOM A LOT.
TONIGHT SHE'S HAVING US OVER
FOR DINNER.
MY MOM WAS PRETTY DISAPPOINTED
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, BECAUSE MY EDUCATION
IS REALLY IMPORTANT TO HER.
>> IT'S GONNA BE A STRESSFUL
YEAR THAT--NOW, YOU GOT INTO
BOISE STATE.
YOU GOT INTO UTAH STATE, AND NOW
ALL THAT STUFF HAS TO BE PUT ON
THE BACK BURNER.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A BABY
INSTEAD OF GOING TO SCHOOL.
WELL, I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA DO
BOTH, BUT WHO'S GONNA WATCH
THE BABY?
>> THE BABY'S NOT GONNA BE
LIKE, "OKAY, I'M NOT GONNA CRY
WHILE YOU'RE ON THE COMPUTER
DOING YOUR HOMEWORK."
>> I KNOW.
>> NOT HAPPENING.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU DO IT WHEN
THE BABY'S ASLEEP.
>> THEY MIGHT STAY UP--
SLEEP FIVE OR TEN MINUTES.
>> THAT'S WHY JOEY GETS TO HOLD
THE BABY WHEN I DO MY HOMEWORK.
[laughs]
>> JOEY WILL BE AT WORK.
>> NOT IF I DO MY STUFF
AT NIGHT.
>> THEN IN THE MORNING TIME WHEN
IT'S FINALLY ASLEEP AND YOU'RE
TIRED, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
NOT SLEEP?
>> YOU THINK THINGS ARE GONNA BE
A LOT EASIER.
BEING A GROWN-UP'S NOT AS EASY
AS YOU THINK IT IS.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
MAKE IT SOUND LIKE IT'S SO
[bleep].
I KNOW IT'S GONNA BE [bleep].
>> OKAY, EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE
ROSES.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE TO WORK TO
GET ANYTHING.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA GET EVERYTHING
HANDED TO YOU.
THIS IS OUR REALITY.
I'M TRYING TO PREPARE YOU FOR
WHAT YOUR FUTURE HOLDS.
>> YOU COULD BE THE LEAST BIT
PROUD OF ME, THOUGH.
IT WOULDN'T HURT.
>> I AM PROUD OF YOU.
I SAY IT ALL THE TIME.
>> IT'D BE NICE IF YOU COULD
JUST, LIKE, SAY ONE NICE THING.
[crying]
>> I WISH MY MOM WOULD HAVE MORE
FAITH IN ME.
I WANT TO PROVE HER WRONG,
SO I'VE BEEN STUDYING REALLY
HARD DURING THE WEEK AND WORKING
AT A BABY SUPPLY STORE ON
THE WEEKENDS.
>> JOEY GOT HIS G.E.D., AND NOW
HE WORKS SIX DAYS A WEEK AT
A TRACTOR RENTAL SHOP,
BUT HE'S TRYING TO GET A JOB
WORKING AT THE MINES WHERE HE'LL
MAKE MUCH MORE MONEY.
[chime dings]
OUR BABY GIRL IS DUE IN
2 1/2 MONTHS, AND WE DECIDED TO
NAME HER MOLLI.
I REALLY WANT JOEY AND I TO GET
OUR OWN PLACE TO START OUR
FAMILY, BUT JOEY DOESN'T THINK
WE CAN AFFORD IT NOW AND WANTS
TO CONTINUE LIVING WITH
HIS PARENTS.
BUT THEY ALREADY HAVE TWO KIDS
AND NOT MUCH ROOM FOR A THIRD.
>> I GUESS MY QUESTION IS,
HOW LONG ARE YOU GUYS
STAYING HERE?
NOT THAT I'M TRYING TO KICK YOU
OUT WHEN YOU GET HERE, BUT I
JUST WANT TO KNOW WHAT--
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
>> I DON'T WANT, LIKE, TO BRING
THE BABY HOME HERE, BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT TO PUSH MY CHILD
ON YOU GUYS.
LIKE, I WANT TO BE ABLE TO TAKE
CARE OF MY KID.
>> THAT'S WHY I'M SAYING I WANT
TO SEE IF I CAN, YOU KNOW--
IF THAT JOB DOWN AT THE MINES
IS A GO OR NOT, BECAUSE IF IT
IS, THEN WE WON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT THEN, BECAUSE
THAT'S JUST A [bleep]-TON
OF MONEY.
>> SO, UH, YOU GET ONTO THE JOB
THERE, THEN YOU'RE SAYING YOU'RE
GOING TO BE FINANCIALLY STABLE?
AND WHERE IS IT THAT YOU GUYS
ARE LOOKING AT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IF YOU APPLY FOR INCOME-BASED
HOUSING, IT WOULD BE A GOOD
START, BECAUSE YOU NEED TO LEARN
HOW TO BUDGET YOUR MONEY.
>> IF YOU GUYS WANT AN
APARTMENT, YOU HAVE TO APPLY
FOR THAT.
YOU GOT TO GET YOUR PROCESS
STARTED.
>> THE THING THAT FRUSTRATES ME
IS, LIKE, WELL, WE'VE BOTH KNOWN
THAT WE'VE NEEDED TO HAVE
A HOUSE.
I KNOW I'LL BE FREAKING OUT IF
IT'S, LIKE, A MONTH BEFORE,
AND I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO SET UP A BABY ROOM YET.
WHILE WE'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE WE'RE GOING TO RAISE
OUR DAUGHTER...
[chime dings]
ALL OUR FRIENDS ARE HAVING FUN
AT THE END OF THEIR SENIOR YEAR.
BUT I DECIDED NOT TO LET THE
FACT THAT I'M ALMOST SEVEN
MONTHS PREGNANT STOP ME FROM
GOING TO THE SENIOR PROM.
MY FRIENDS AND I ARE MAKING IT
A GIRLS NIGHT, AND I'M EXCITED
TO HAVE A FUN NIGHT OUT...
>> HEY.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
>> IF I CAN FIND A DRESS
THAT FITS.
>> IT'S, LIKE, STUCK.
TAKE IT ALL THE WAY DOWN,
AND THEN GO ALL THE WAY UP.
HOW'S THAT FITTING, KATIE?
>> IT'S BETTER.
THERE'S NO ZIPPER, SO...
I FEEL FAT, BUT...
>> WHY?
YOU DON'T LOOK FAT.
>> I THINK IT LOOKS CUTE.
>> YEAH, I THOUGHT THAT ONE FIT.
>> ONE MORE.
>> MY BAD.
>> I SAY JUST GO WITH THAT ONE.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
>> ME TOO.
>> I THINK IT'S A WINNER.
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU GUYS STOKED
FOR GIRLS NIGHT?
>> HELL, YEAH.
[horn honks]
>> HAVE FUN!
>> BYE!
>> WHOO-HOO!
>> WHOO!
>> * WHOO, OOH, OOH
>> I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED FORWARD
TO MY SENIOR PROM.
[chime dings]
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT SO MANY
PEOPLE WOULD BE STARING AT ME
OR THAT MY FEET WOULD GET
SO SORE
OR THAT I WOULD GET TIRED
SO QUICKLY.
>> I'LL GET THE DOOR FOR YOU.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> I THINK THIS WAS JUST TOO
MUCH PARTY FOR ME AND THE BABY.
>> MM-MM!
>> HOW WAS IT BEING PREGNANT
AT PROM?
>> I JUST FELT LIKE EVERYBODY
WAS JUST, LIKE, STARING
AT MY STOMACH.
I KIND OF JUST WANT TO GO HOME
TO MY BOYFRIEND AND CUDDLE UP
IN MY COMFY P.J.s AND WATCH
A MOVIE.
>> YOU'RE GROWING UP SO FAST.
>> SO, KATIE...
>> NO.
>> IT'LL BE FUN.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S PAST MY
BEDTIME, AND I NEED TO GO HOME.
MY FEET HURT.
MY BACK HURTS.
MY HEAD HURTS.
I'M ALL SWEATY.
I FEEL LIKE A COW.
>> YOU DON'T--
>> YOU DON'T EVEN LOOK SWEATY.
>> YEAH.
>> I, LIKE, DON'T FEEL LIKE
IN PARTY MODE ANYMORE.
>> WRAP GLOW STICKS AROUND--
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT--
NO, I JUST...
I WISH I HAD THE ENERGY TO STAY
OUT WITH MY FRIENDS,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I KNOW THAT
I WON'T BE SEEING THEM AS MUCH
ONCE MOLLI COMES.
BUT I'M EXHAUSTED,
AND I NEED TO GO HOME.
SINCE JOEY IS STILL WAITING TO
HEAR IF THERE'S A JOB FOR HIM AT
THE MINES, AND MY DUE DATE IS
ONLY TWO MONTHS AWAY, WE DECIDED
TO TAKE HIS MOM'S ADVICE AND
START APPLYING FOR INCOME-BASED
HOUSING.
ARE YOU A CITIZEN BY BIRTH
OF THE UNITED STATES?
ARE YOU SURE?
>> I'M PRETTY SURE.
>> I THINK IT WILL BE BEST IF WE
PUT IT IN YOUR NAME.
SINCE YOU'RE PAYING THE BILLS,
YOU HAVE TO BE HEAD OF
HOUSEHOLD.
WE NEED TO JUST GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE THE BABY COMES, 'CAUSE
THEN WE CAN HAVE OUR OWN SPACE
AND OUR OWN FAMILY.
JUST US THREE.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT EVERYTHING,
BUT WHAT IF WE DON'T GET
ACCEPTED?
>> THEN WE'LL BE STILL ON
THE WAITING LIST AND CLIMBING
TOWARDS THE TOP.
LIKE, WE CAN'T BE ON THERE FOR
70 YEARS.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, THAT DON'T
MEAN IT'S GONNA GO RIGHT.
>> WELL, LET'S JUST ACT LIKE
THINGS ARE GONNA GO RIGHT
FOR ONCE.
I NEED TO KNOW THAT ONE THING--
>> I'M ALWAYS THE ONE THAT'S
SAYING IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
>> I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU RAIN ON
MY PARADE, SO...
>> I'M NOT RAINING ON YOUR
PARADE.
I'M A REALIST, KATIE.
>> WE'VE KIND OF GOTTEN THE
[bleep] END OF THE STICK LATELY.
I THINK SOME GOOD THINGS
ARE COMING.
IT'S STRESSING ME OUT THAT WE
HAVE SO LITTLE TIME LEFT...
[chime dings]
AND DON'T HAVE A PLACE TO LIVE.
AND JOEY BEING NEGATIVE
ISN'T HELPING.
>> ALL MY HARD WORK PAID OFF,
AND TODAY, I GRADUATED HIGH
SCHOOL ON TIME WITH MY CLASS.
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M PRETTY
STRESSED ABOUT FINDING A PLACE
TO LIVE, I MADE AN APPOINTMENT
WITH MY COLLEGE COUNSELOR TO
DISCUSS CONTINUING MY EDUCATION.
>> HAVE YOU DECIDED WHAT PROGRAM
YOU'RE GONNA DO?
>> I'M GONNA DO ONLINE
THE FIRST YEAR.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THEN I'M GOING TO ATTEND
CLASSES AT WESTERN
THE NEXT YEAR,
LIKE, SLOWLY TRANSITION INTO
CLASSES.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> WELL, I HAD MY TEN-YEAR PLAN,
LIKE, BEFORE I HAD GOTTEN
PREGNANT.
LIKE, I WAS GONNA GO TO A BIG
UNIVERSITY, AND I WAS GONNA DO,
LIKE, DRAMA AND EVERY SINGLE
CLUB THAT I COULD JOIN UP IN,
AND I WAS GONNA, LIKE, HAVE
THE BEST COLLEGE EXPERIENCE.
AND I WASN'T GONNA HAVE
A FAMILY.
I NEVER PLANNED ON EVEN HAVING
A KID OR GETTING MARRIED OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I'M LIKE, "I WANT TO BE SINGLE,"
AND THEN IT DIDN'T WORK OUT
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
[laughs]
I THINK THIS HAS GIVEN ME MORE
MOTIVATION, 'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE
TO JUST TAKE CARE OF MYSELF NOW.
>> RIGHT.
AND THEN YOU GOING TO COLLEGE IS
GOING TO BRING OUT HER
EXPECTATIONS OF WHAT SHE'S GONNA
DO IN LIFE TOO,
WHICH IS EXCELLENT.
>> YEAH, I WANT TO BE
A GOOD EXAMPLE.
OKAY, WELL, THANK YOU FOR
MEETING WITH ME.
I'M FEELING PRETTY GOOD ABOUT
MY PLANS TO START COMMUNITY
COLLEGE ONLINE IN THE FALL.
[chime dings]
I JUST HOPE I CAN STAY ON TRACK
ONCE MOLLI GETS HERE, BECAUSE
I REALLY WANT TO TRANSFER TO
A COLLEGE IN DENVER AFTER
TWO YEARS.
MY DUE DATE IS IN SEVEN WEEKS,
AND TODAY I HAVE A DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT.
I'M BUMMED JOEY CAN'T MAKE IT,
BUT HE HAS TO WORK.
>> SHE SITS IN A "V"
ALL THE TIME.
LIKE, HER BUTT IS OVER HERE--
>> WELL, THEY JUST THINK THEY'VE
GOT TO KIND OF CURL UP
IN THERE TOO.
AND SO THE HEAD IS DOWN,
AND THE BACK'S LYING RIGHT OVER
HERE, AND HER LITTLE BUTT'S
RIGHT HERE, SO YOU PROBABLY HAVE
LOTS OF FEET AND THE KNEES AND
THAT KIND OF THING
RIGHT OVER HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WHAT ARE
YOUR QUESTIONS?
>> UM...
WELL, I WAS NERVOUS ABOUT
THE I.V. AT THE HOSPITAL,
'CAUSE I'VE NEVER HAD ONE
BEFORE.
>> WE HOOK UP THE TUBING IF YOU
WANT AN EPIDURAL.
>> AT THIS POINT, I DON'T WANT
THE EPIDURAL.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH.
I WANT TO DO IT NATURALLY,
'CAUSE OF THE WAY THAT I SEE IT
AS WOMEN HAVE BEEN DOING IT
FOR CENTURIES.
I DON'T NEED DRUGS.
>> THAT'S TRUE. THAT'S TRUE.
WELL, YOU'VE NEVER HAD A BABY
BEFORE, SO YOU DON'T KNOW HOW
THIS IS GONNA GO.
YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE TO MAKE
ANY DECISION ABOUT THAT UNTIL
YOU'RE ACTUALLY INTO LABOR.
EVERYTHING LOOKS WONDERFUL
AT THIS POINT.
>> OKAY.
AWESOME.
WHEN HE'S NOT WORKING, JOEY'S
BEEN HANGING OUT WITH HIS
FRIENDS A LOT LATELY.
I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK HE'S
TRYING TO AVOID FOCUSING ON
FINDING A PLACE FOR US TO LIVE.
BUT I'M SETTING THAT ASIDE FOR
THE WEEKEND, BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO DENVER TO VISIT VERONICA.
HEY!
>> HI.
THIS IS MY ROOM.
>> OH, GOSH, AND YOU HAVE
A GREAT VIEW.
>> I KNOW. I LIKE IT.
AT NIGHT, I JUST SIT HERE AND
WATCH THE TRAFFIC GO BY.
>> I'D SIT HERE AND WATCH
MY NEIGHBORS.
YOU BETTER HAVE THE MOST AMAZING
TIME HERE, 'CAUSE I'M GONNA LIVE
VICARIOUSLY THROUGH YOU.
LIKE, YOU BETTER TELL ME--
>> YOU'RE JUST GONNA CALL ME.
"WHAT HAPPENED TO US TODAY?"
>> "WHAT DID WE DO TODAY?
HOW'S LIVING IN DENVER
FOR US TODAY?"
>> FOR US TODAY.
[upbeat music]
*
>> I LIKE IT HERE.
I LIKE THE FEELING
OF BEING HERE.
>> AFTER WESTERN, ARE YOU GONNA
COME HERE?
>> IT GIVES ME SOMETHING TO WORK
TOWARDS, IT FEELS LIKE.
WHEN I'M LIKE, "OH, I WANT TO BE
OUT OF ROCK SPRINGS" AND STUFF,
AND THEN I'LL BE LIKE, "WELL,
I'M WORKING TOWARDS THIS."
AND THEN I'LL PICTURE THIS.
>> WELL, JUST REMEMBER
THE COURTYARD WITH THE FLOWERS
AND THE PRETTY CHURCH BUILDING.
>> AND WE'LL ALWAYS END UP...
>> TOGETHER SOMEHOW.
>> TOGETHER IN THE END.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'LL BE REALLY ROMANTIC.
>> IT'LL BE A SUPER-CUTE HAPPY
ENDING.
>> [laughs]
LET'S HOPE.
HANGING OUT WITH VERONICA AND
SEEING HER COLLEGE LIFE REALLY
GOT ME TO THINKING ABOUT
MY OWN FUTURE.
I DO HOPE JOEY AND I WILL BE
ABLE TO MOVE OUR FAMILY TO
DENVER IN A COUPLE YEARS.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AT
HOUSES.
BUT FOR NOW, I'D BE CONTENT JUST
GETTING OUT OF HIS PARENTS'
HOUSE, INTO OUR OWN PLACE
BEFORE MOLLI COMES.
WELL, I'M HAPPY YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THESE WITH ME.
WE HAVEN'T LOOKED AT ANY
APARTMENTS TOGETHER YET.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK WE CAN
AFFORD?
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE, YOU'VE TOLD
ME ABOUT PLACES YOU'VE SEEN THAT
ARE, LIKE, $750, $800.
YOU KNOW, AND IT'S, LIKE,
I THINK THAT'S TOO MUCH.
>> I JUST DON'T THINK LIVING
WITH YOUR MOM IS A GOOD IDEA,
WITH A BABY.
>> I KNOW IT'S NOT THE BEST
IDEA, BUT IF IT'S WHAT WE HAVE
TO DO FOR A WHILE...
>> I WOULD LIKE TO BE
INDEPENDENT WITH YOU.
>> I KNOW.
YOU ACT LIKE I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL THE SAME.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE GONNA
SET UP A NURSERY, LIKE...
>> WE'LL MOVE ALL OF OUR [bleep]
OUT OF THE ROOM IT'S IN
RIGHT NOW, AND WE'LL
SET IT UP IN THERE.
>> DOES IT BOTHER YOU THAT
EVERYTHING'S IN A BOX STILL?
>> HECK YES.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S MY FAULT,
'CAUSE I'M NOT PREPARED.
I JUST WANT--
>> KATIE, YOU'RE [bleep] 17
YEARS OLD, AND YOU'RE HAVING
A BABY.
>> BUT STILL, I WANT EVERYTHING
TO BE PERFECT AND READY.
>> JUST BECAUSE THINGS AREN'T
GOING PERFECT RIGHT NOW AND JUST
BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T GOTTEN TO
AN APARTMENT YET OR GOT
A HOUSE YET DOESN'T MEAN
WE'RE [bleep].
DOESN'T MEAN MOLLI'S GONNA HAVE
A [bleep] LIFE.
IT DON'T MEAN NONE OF THAT,
AND YOU ACT LIKE IT DOES.
YOU ACT LIKE IT'S THE END OF
THE [bleep] WORLD.
>> [exhales]
I'M JUST OVER THIS.
CAN WE GO HOME?
[sullen guitar music]
*
>> JOEY'S ATTITUDE ABOUT GETTING
A PLACE IS REALLY BUMMING ME
OUT, BUT WITH MOLLI COMING
IN JUST A LITTLE OVER A MONTH,
I'M NOT GOING TO GIVE UP ON
FINDING SOMETHING WE CAN AFFORD.
HI, I WAS CALLING YOU ABOUT
THE APARTMENTS THAT YOU HAD
FOR RENT.
WHAT IS THE RENT?
>> IS THAT NEGOTIABLE, OR IS IT,
LIKE...
>> OKAY.
I CAN'T REALLY DO THAT.
THAT'S TOO EXPENSIVE,
SO THANK YOU.
I REALLY WISH JOEY WOULD HELP ME
OUT, BUT INSTEAD, HE JUST KEEPS
PULLING AWAY EVEN MORE.
WHEN HE GETS HOME FROM WORK,
HE BARELY ACKNOWLEDGES ME.
I KNOW HE DOESN'T WANT TO TALK
TO ME ABOUT FINDING A PLACE
ANYMORE, BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
THAT HE HAS TO IGNORE ME
ALTOGETHER.
>> HELLO?
>> HEY.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> NOT MUCH.
>> WELL, IT'S JUST, LIKE...
LIKE, HE'S ALWAYS AT WORK,
AND I SIT HERE BORED ALL DAY,
AND THEN HE COMES HOME
FROM WORK, AND HE DOESN'T EVEN,
LIKE, TALK TO ME OR WANT TO TALK
TO ME OR ASK ME HOW MY DAY IS
AT ALL, LIKE...
>> YEAH.
>> SO I'M PRETTY MUCH ALONE
ALL THE TIME, IT FEELS LIKE.
LIKE, I'M ALONE IN
A RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM, LIKE...
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN YOU SPEND ALL DAY ALONE,
YOU'RE KIND OF NEEDY FOR
ATTENTION.
>> IT'S REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE
BEING IGNORED BY JOEY, AND IF
THINGS ARE GOING TO CONTINUE
LIKE THIS, I'M NOT SURE HIS
PARENTS' HOUSE IS THE BEST PLACE
FOR ME TO BE STAYING.
HEY.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT?
>> I'M GOING TO MY DAD'S.
>> DO YOU REALLY HAVE TO GO,
LIKE, SERIOUSLY?
>> I TOLD YOU THREE DAYS AGO
I WAS GOING.
>> YOU GO OUT THERE ALL
THE TIME.
>> NO, I GO OUT THERE ONCE,
TWICE A MONTH.
>> YOU'VE GONE OUT THERE
QUITE A BIT, AND I NEVER GET ANY
TIME TO SPEND WITH YOU.
ALL I DO IS WAIT FOR YOU TO COME
HOME FROM WORK, AND YOU DON'T
TALK TO ME ABOUT THINGS.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU CAN GO, BUT DON'T EXPECT
ME TO BE HERE WHEN YOU GET BACK.
I'M SICK OF COMING SECOND.
I SHOULD BE FIRST.
>> THAT'S HOW IT'S GONNA BE?
>> I GUESS SO.
>> OKAY.
>> [sighs]
[dramatic music]
*
I CAN'T BELIEVE JOEY'S
TREATING ME LIKE THIS.
I DECIDED TO PACK UP SOME THINGS
AND GO STAY AT MY MOM'S HOUSE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> EVERYBODY COMES BEFORE ME,
IT FEELS LIKE, AND HE DOESN'T
SHOW ME ANY SORT OF AFFECTION OR
ATTENTION ANYMORE.
AND IT FEELS LIKE I'VE BEEN
DOING ALL THE WORK FOR
THE HOUSING.
I WANTED US TO GET OUT ON OUR
OWN SO WE COULD BE
OUR OWN FAMILY.
LIKE, IT WAS OUR RESPONSIBILITY.
>> I THINK THAT'S A GOOD
CONCEPT, THAT YOU WANT TO DO IT
ON YOUR OWN, BUT THE REALITY IS,
YOU NEED HELP.
AND I KNOW YOU WANT TO GET
A BABY ROOM READY,
AND YOU WANT...
>> YEAH.
>> IT'LL HAPPEN EVENTUALLY.
MAYBE NOT IN KATIE TIME,
BUT IT'LL HAPPEN.
>> I WISH THE WHOLE WORLD WORKED
ON KATIE TIME, THOUGH.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING
ON DOING?
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT I'M
GONNA DO.
>> YOU GUYS BETTER MAKE
A DECISION.
THIS DOESN'T JUST AFFECT YOU AND
JOEY ANYMORE.
THERE'S A BABY INVOLVED.
>> I KNOW.
AFTER A NIGHT APART, JOEY WANTED
TO MEET UP AND TALK.
>> I DON'T GET IT.
>> WHAT DON'T YOU GET?
AND I'LL TRY TO EXPLAIN IT
TO YOU.
>> I DON'T GET WHAT I'M DOING
SO [bleep] UP.
THAT'S WHAT I DON'T GET.
>> YOU COME HOME.
YOU HARDLY SAY HI TO ME.
YOU GO DOWNSTAIRS.
YOU SHOWER.
YOU COME BACK UPSTAIRS.
YOU EAT.
YOU SIT NEXT TO ME AND
DON'T SAY [bleep].
I DON'T EVEN GET A,
"HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
WHAT DID YOU DO TODAY?"
NOTHING.
IN THE SITUATION THAT WE'RE IN,
WHERE WOULD WE PUT THE BABY?
>> UH, WHERE YOU GONNA PUT IT
NOW, THE TRUNK OF YOUR CAR?
>> THERE'S AN EXTRA ROOM
IN MY MOM'S HOUSE.
MY MOM'S NOT GONNA LET ME AND
THE BABY LIVE ON THE STREET.
>> WELL, THEN YOU GOT IT ALL--
>> THAT'S JUST THE SITUATION
THAT I WANT TO BE IN.
>> WHY'D YOU GO?
>> I DON'T WANT TO FORCE
OUR FAMILY ON YOUR MOM.
>> JUST 'CAUSE WE'RE NOT OUT NOW
DON'T MEAN WE'RE NOT GONNA MOVE
OUT, AND IT DON'T MEAN WE'RE
GONNA BE THERE FOR FIVE
MORE YEARS.
>> I HAVE A HARD TIME TAKING
THINGS FROM OTHER PEOPLE WHEN
I DON'T DO ANYTHING.
AND I FEEL BAD, BECAUSE THEY'RE
SO--THEY DO EVERYTHING FOR US,
AND WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
GIVE TO THEM.
>> 'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT PARENTS
DO, KATIE.
>> THEY'RE NOT MY PARENTS!
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER!
YOU'RE MY GIRLFRIEND,
AND YOU'RE HAVING A KID WITH ME.
THAT KID IS THEIR GRANDCHILD.
THEY LOVE YOU TOO.
>> IT'D BE PERFECT IF WE CAN
GET OUR OWN HOUSE, AND IF YOU
WOULD START TREATING ME LIKE
A GIRLFRIEND.
>> I'M SORRY THAT I OBVIOUSLY
CAN'T DO THAT FOR YOU.
I'M SORRY THAT I MAKE YOU FEEL
LIKE SUCH A PIECE OF [bleep],
KATIE.
I'M SORRY THAT I [bleep] UP
YOUR LIFE.
[mellow instrumental music]
*
>> SINCE OUR FIGHT, JOEY AND I
HAVEN'T SEEN EACH OTHER.
OUR BABY IS DUE IN TEN DAYS,
AND INSTEAD OF GETTING HER ROOM
READY, WE'RE ARGUING OVER
TEXT MESSAGE.
THE TIMING COULDN'T BE WORSE,
BECAUSE THE NEXT MORNING,
SOMETHING FELT DIFFERENT.
>> DO YOU THINK YOUR WATER
BROKE?
>> MY MOM AND MY SISTER RUSHED
ME TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> ANY HEADACHE?
>> NO.
>> REALLY BAD PAIN RIGHT HERE?
>> OKAY.
>> ALL DOWN IN HERE.
>> WANT AN EPIDURAL FOR PAIN?
>> NO.
>> MAYBE?
>> WELL, YOU CAN CHANGE YOUR
MIND AT ANY TIME.
>> AT THE MOMENT, IT'S NO.
>> OKAY.
>> DID YOU TEXT JOEY?
>> YOU WANT ME TO?
DID THEY SAY--
>> WELL, LET'S WAIT AND SEE IF
YOUR WATER'S BROKEN.
>> I WAS LIKE, "UM, THE LADY
JUST SAID..."
>> OKAY, SO I'M GONNA ADMIT YOU
AND START AN I.V.
>> I'M NERVOUS ABOUT THIS.
CALL JOEY.
>> [sighs]
>> HELLO. IS THIS JOEY?
>> TELL HER THAT THEY'RE
ADMITTING ME.
TELL HIM TO GET HERE.
>> TEXT HER AND TELL HER THAT
I'M IN LABOR
AND TO COME HERE IF SHE CAN.
>> HELLO?
>> HEY, STARLA.
>> I'M GONNA CHECK YOU JUST TO
SEE WHERE WE'RE STARTING FROM.
OKAY, SO I WOULD SAY
WE'RE ABOUT 2.
IT'S ABOUT 80% THINNED OUT.
>> OW.
>> AND ABOUT A MINUS 1.
SORRY, SORRY.
BY ABOUT NOON OR SO, I REALLY
WANT YOU TO START BEING IN
LABOR, AND I WANT TO SEE SOME
CHANGES IN YOUR CERVIX THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> [quietly] JUST GET THERE.
>> DON'T, BLAKE.
>> I'M JUST KIDDING.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> [sighs]
>> WHEN JOEY SHOWED UP,
IT WAS PRETTY AWKWARD AT FIRST.
[sighs]
IT HURTS IN MY BACK.
BUT AS MY LABOR PROGRESSED,
HE DROPPED HIS ATTITUDE AND
STARTED BEING MORE SUPPORTIVE.
[moaning]
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY.
>> WELL, LITTLE MORE PRESSURE
THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
I'M GONNA CHECK YOU.
I'M GONNA SEE WHERE WE'RE
SITTING SINCE I'M OVER HERE AND
DRESSED FOR THE OCCASION.
>> YEAH, YOU LOOK REAL NICE.
>> SO IT'S--YOU'RE 3,
ABOUT 90% THINNED OUT,
BUT THE CERVIX IS ALL THE WAY
TO THE FRONT NOW, OKAY.
AND THE HEAD IS VERY LOW.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE FEELING
SO MUCH PRESSURE.
>> OKAY.
>> SO THAT'S GOOD.
YOU'RE HEADING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
THIS IS PERFECT.
>> USUALLY, A FIRST-TIME MOM
TAKES ABOUT A CENTIMETER
AN HOUR.
>> AND THIS IS WHERE SHE SAID
SHE WANTED--
>> WHERE SHE'LL START PUSHING.
>> [moans]
[sobbing]
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> YOU'RE FINE, KATIE.
>> [hushing]
>> PERFECT TIMING.
>> OW!
>> ALL RIGHT, GOOD.
YOU'RE ABOUT 8--
8 TO 9 CENTIMETERS.
[all cheering]
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'LL JUST CRAWL UP
IN HERE WITH YOU.
>> [moaning]
>> [groaning]
>> YOU'RE OKAY.
>> YOU'RE GETTING CLOSE, GIRL.
>> OW!
>> THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
>> IT HURTS.
>> I KNOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT THERE, KATIE.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
>> [moaning loudly]
>> GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
>> YOU'RE ALL RIGHT NOW, KATIE.
>> both: FIVE, SIX, SEVEN,
EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
>> [screams]
>> THERE SHE IS!
LOOK UP, KATIE.
OPEN YOUR EYES.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE'S YOUR
DAUGHTER.
[baby crying]
>> * I FOUND WHAT I NEED
* TO KNOW
* WAITING FOR SO LONG
* TO HAVE WHAT I'VE MISSED *
* ALL ALONG
[upbeat instrumental music]
*
[baby crying]
smooch!
[chime dings]
[baby sobbing]
>> MOMMY'S GONNA FEED YOU.
OH, YOU'RE PISSED.
>> PUT THIS IN HER MOUTH.
JUST HOLD ON.
>> YOU'RE OKAY.
IT'S TIME TO EAT, OKAY?
>> ON THE BELLY, REMEMBER.
[baby crying]
>> WELL...
>> IT'S OKAY, ANGEL.
>> WHAT'S IT FEEL LIKE, KATIE?
>> IT HURTS.
BUT IT'S WORTH IT...
>> THAT'S SO WEIRD.
>> 'CAUSE THEN SHE'LL BE
A PRETTY SMART BABY.
[gentle guitar music]
*
ONE GOOD THING ABOUT NOT HAVING
AN EPIDURAL IS, I DIDN'T HAVE TO
STAY IN THE HOSPITAL VERY LONG.
BY THE NEXT AFTERNOON,
WE WERE READY TO LEAVE.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS, BECAUSE OF
EVERYTHING GOING ON WITH ME
AND JOEY, I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHERE WE'RE GOING.
>> SO WHERE AM I TAKING YOU?
>> TO YOUR MOM'S HOUSE.
>> WHAT YOU MADE YOU DECIDE
THAT?
>> I JUST WANT TO BE A FAMILY,
AND WE BOTH NEED TO WORK
THINGS OUT.
SO WE MIGHT AS WELL DO IT
TOGETHER.
>> WE NEED TO WORK [bleep] OUT
BEFORE WE JUST BREAK UP.
>> WE NEED TO TRY TO BE
THE BEST FAMILY WE CAN BE
FOR HER, 'CAUSE I THINK SHE
DESERVES A FAMILY.
*
[chime dings]
>> female announcer: GET ANSWERS
TO YOUR SEX AND RELATIONSHIP
QUESTIONS AND TIPS ON HOW TO
TAKE CONTROL, AT:
>> [gasps]
OH, YEAH, IT'S COLD, HUH?
>> [suckling]
>> SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S GIVING YOU
KISSES.
[smooching]
>> YEAH.
SHE GIVES GOOD KISSES ALREADY.
>> [laughs]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> PUT HER IN THE CRADLE
NEXT TO OUR BED.
>> I WAS GONNA SWADDLE HER.
>> OH, YEAH.
THIS THING IS HUGE FOR HER.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> IT'S SO NICE TO HAVE MOLLI
HOME WITH US, AND JOEY EVEN
REARRANGED THE BASEMENT SO WE'D
HAVE A LITTLE MORE SPACE.
>> [crying]
>> ARE YOU HUNGRY?
IS THAT WHAT'S WRONG?
[shushing]
BUT IT'S STILL PRETTY CRAMPED,
AND JOEY'S BROTHER AND SISTER
ARE ALWAYS AROUND.
TODAY'S MY FIRST DAY OF ONLINE
COMMUNITY COLLEGE CLASSES.
BE CAREFUL.
BE GENTLE.
SHE'S NAPPING.
>> BE CAREFUL, DESHAUN.
BE CAREFUL ON HER HEAD.
DESHAUN, BE CAREFUL ON HER HEAD.
SHE HAS SOFT SPOTS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> MY HOMEWORK.
>> ARE YOU EVER GONNA GO TO
A REAL COLLEGE?
YOU NEED TO BE GETTING SOME
EDUCATION FROM REAL TEACHERS
AND NOT A COMPUTER.
>> I WAS GOING TO GO TO
A REAL COLLEGE.
>> IN DENVER?
>> YUP.
AND THEN I HAD MOLLI INSTEAD.
[shushing]
STUDYING WITH A BABY IN THIS
HOUSE IS NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
BUT A COUPLE WEEKS LATER,
WE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS.
JOEY GOT HIRED AT THE MINES.
SO NOW WE CAN GO LOOK AT
A PLACE WE CAN FINALLY AFFORD.
>> [sighs]
WANT TO CHECK OUT
THE KITCHEN, MOLLY?
YEAH, YOU WANT TO LOOK
AT THE KITCHEN.
>> WELL, WE COULD PUT HER CRIB
IN HERE.
>> I BET THE CRIB THAT WE HAVE
IS TOO BIG.
>> NOT REALLY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IF WE PUT IT THIS WAY.
>> WHAT, YOU MEAN THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, BUT IT'S GONNA BE
STICKING OUT.
>> WELL, I GUESS WE CAN ONLY
TELL BY THE--IF WE GET IT IN
HERE OR MEASURE IT OR WHATEVER.
>> THIS IS THE KITCHEN TABLE.
>> MM-HMM.
LOOK AT THE CLOSET SPACE.
THIS IS WHAT I NEED.
>> YEAH?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I THINK YOU NEED ABOUT FIVE
OF THOSE.
>> I LIKE IT SO FAR.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I LIKE IT.
>> I THINK EVERYTHING WOULD FIT
IN HERE TOO.
>> YUP.
>> IT'S PERFECT.
WE APPLIED FOR THE APARTMENT
AND A FEW DAYS LATER, FOUND OUT
WE GOT ACCEPTED.
>> MOLLI, I GOT YOU A SIPPY
STRAW.
>> SHE'S LIKE, "WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?"
>> WE'RE SITTING ON A TUPPERWARE
LOOKING AT A HOUSE FULL OF
[bleep].
>> NOW WE CAN BE A FAMILY.
>> YEAH.
I'M EXCITED.
I'M GLAD THAT WE'RE IN HERE.
[chime dings]
>> THE NEW HOUSE IS GREAT FOR
A COUPLE YEARS, BUT I STILL WANT
US TO MOVE ON TO BIGGER AND
BETTER THINGS AS A FAMILY.
BECAUSE JOEY IS NEW AT THE
MINES, HE HAS TO WORK THE NIGHT
SHIFT, WHICH MEANS HE SLEEPS FOR
MOST OF THE DAY WHILE I TAKE
CARE OF MOLLI BY MYSELF.
JOEY.
JOEY, YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR WORK.
[baby crying]
OKAY.
I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
>> SEE YOU IN THE MORNING, BABY.
>> BEING ON OUR OWN IS TURNING
OUT TO BE A LOT DIFFERENT
THAN I EXPECTED.
JOEY'S JOB IS SUPER GRUELING,
AND BEING ALONE ALL DAY SUCKS.
SO I'M GLAD OUR ARRANGEMENT IS
JUST TEMPORARY UNTIL WE CAN MAKE
OUR MOVE TO DENVER.
>> I'M HOME.
>> SHE'S LIKE, "WHY DO YOU
TORTURE ME?"
>> [hiccupping and crying]
>> WE'RE DONE. WE'RE DONE.
WE'RE DONE.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA TAKE
A SHOWER, OKAY?
>> JOEY HAS TONIGHT OFF,
SO MY MOM IS TAKING US OUT
TO DINNER SINCE SHE HASN'T SEEN
US IN A WHILE.
>> SO WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO
TODAY?
>> JUST SITTING AROUND PRETTY
MUCH, BEING BORED.
SO TWO YEARS FROM NOW,
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA SEE ME AGAIN.
>> WHY?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TWO YEARS
FROM NOW?
>> 'CAUSE WE'RE MOVING AWAY AND
NEVER COMING BACK.
>> OH, REALLY?
WHERE ARE YOU PLANNING ON MOVING
AWAY TO?
>> DENVER.
>> AND WHAT COAL MINE IS JOEY
GONNA WORK IN IN DENVER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I KNOW.
I WOULDN'T MAKE YOU LEAVE.
THAT WOULD BE IRRESPONSIBLE FOR
US TO MOVE.
>> WELL, AND I TOLD YOU, WHEN
THAT POINT COMES, IF YOU'RE
PISSED OFF 'CAUSE WE CAN'T GO TO
COLORADO, I NEVER SAID YOU
COULDN'T GO.
I JUST SAID I WASN'T GONNA GO
WITH YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA THROW AWAY ALL OF
THOSE BENEFITS AND THAT MUCH
MONEY FOR YOU TO GO COLLEGE WHEN
YOU DON'T NEED TO GO
TO COLLEGE.
>> I DO NEED TO GO.
>> I WOULD SAY I DON'T AGREE
THAT SHE DOESN'T NEED TO GO TO
COLLEGE, BUT--
>> I'M JUST SAYING, IF YOU WANT
TO STAY WITH ME AND RAISE MOLLI,
THEN YOU DON'T NEED TO GO
TO COLLEGE IF I HAVE THAT
HIGH PAY OF A JOB.
>> I NEED TOO, THOUGH.
NOT FOR MONEY, FOR MYSELF.
>> YEAH, BUT FOR MOLLI--
FOR MOLLI, I CAN'T QUIT MY JOB
AND GO TO DENVER SO YOU CAN GO
TO SCHOOL.
>> BUT YOU HAVE TO REALIZE,
IF YOU DO THAT, YOU'RE GONNA BE
A SINGLE PARENT KIND OF.
EVEN THOUGH JOEY'S HELPING,
YOU KNOW, SUPPORT YOU GUYS WHILE
YOU'RE DOWN THERE, YOU'RE GONNA
STILL BE DOING IT
ALL BY YOURSELF.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'RE SAYING,
"ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'LL GO TO
DENVER AND TAKE MOLLI.
THAT WAY I CAN GO TO
UNIVERSITY."
WELL, THAT'S JUST LIKE ME
SAYING...
>> YOU HAVE BOTH SACRIFICED
THINGS IN YOUR LIFE, BUT THAT'S
WHAT PARENTS DO.
AND YOU JUST STARTED.
YOU HAVE 18 MORE YEARS OF GIVING
THINGS UP.
[calm instrumental music]
*
[chime dings]
>> announcer: DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> AFTER DINNER WITH MY MOM AND
JOEY, I'M NERVOUS THAT DENVER
ISN'T GOING TO PLAY OUT THE WAY
THAT I HAD PLANNED.
EW, IT'S, LIKE, STUCK.
BUT I JUST CAN'T SEE MYSELF
STAYING HERE FOREVER AND
BECOMING A HOUSEWIFE.
[fire alarm beeping]
SORRY, MOLLI.
THAT'S LOUD.
SO WHEN I'M NOT COOKING,
CLEANING, OR TAKING CARE OF
MOLLI, I'M TRYING TO KEEP UP
WITH MY ONLINE COURSES.
AND TODAY I'M ACTUALLY GETTING
OUT TO SEE SOME OF MY FRIENDS.
HELLO, HELLO.
>> both: HEY!
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN
FOREVER.
>> [crying]
>> OH, MWAH, MWAH, MWAH.
>> HEY, BABY GIRL.
>> YOU JUST WANT TO TALK WITH
THE GIRLS, DON'T YOU?
>> SO HOW'S SCHOOL?
>> IT'S NOT REALLY, LIKE,
THE FUN PART OF SCHOOL.
IT'S LIKE, "OKAY, HERE'S YOUR
WORK; NOW DO IT."
>> both: YEAH.
>> AND MOLLI DOESN'T LIKE WHEN
MOM DOES HOMEWORK.
>> I KNOW.
PLUS, THERE'S ALWAYS, LIKE,
THE SCHOOL STUFF, LIKE,
THE DORM STUFF THAT YOU CAN
NEVER COME TO.
>> I DON'T GET, LIKE, THE HUMAN
INTERACTMENT.
>> IT'S GOT TO BE SO TIRING.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, TAKING CARE OF A BABY
ALL DAY.
>> AND WHEN THE HOUSE GETS
DIRTY, I HAVE TO CLEAN IT.
WHEN I--WHEN, LIKE, LAUNDRY HAS
TO BE DONE, I HAVE TO DO IT.
WHEN I'M HUNGRY, I HAVE TO MAKE
MY OWN FOOD.
IT JUST SUCKS BEING ALONE ALL
THE TIME, ULTIMATELY.
LIKE, I THOUGHT THAT, LIKE, WHEN
YOU HAVE A FAMILY, YOU ALWAYS
HAVE PEOPLE WITH YOU, BUT
THE REALITY IS, IS THAT YOU'RE
ALONE A LOT.
LIKE, I NEVER THOUGHT I WOULD BE
A MOM.
LIKE, I WANTED TO BE INDEPENDENT
FOREVER, FOR THE REST OF MY
LIFE.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THEN I HAD HER, AND IT
FEELS GOOD TO HAVE SOMEBODY
DEPEND ON YOU, BUT IT'S, LIKE,
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
I'M A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
PERSON THAN I PICTURED MYSELF
TO BE.
>> [crying]
>> SO I'M GONNA GO.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY, WELL...
WE'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU LATER.
[solemn instrumental music]
*
>> I DIDN'T THINK LIVING IN
A HOUSE ALL BY OURSELVES WAS
GONNA BE SO LONELY.
LIKE, I COULD GO DAYS WITHOUT
HAVING A CONVERSATION WITH
A REAL PERSON.
LIKE, I SIT THERE, AND I, LIKE,
BABY-TALK TO MOLLI ALL DAY,
AND THEN YOU COME HOME, AND WE,
LIKE, HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
A CONVERSATION, AND THEN YOU
FALL ASLEEP WHILE I'M TALKING TO
YOU, AND THEN YOU LEAVE FOR
WORK, AND I DON'T TALK
TO ANY OF MY FRIENDS.
>> MY DAY'S NOT MUCH MORE FUN
THAN YOURS, KATIE.
>> AND IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
I'M A PERSON ANYMORE AT ALL.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I JUST SIT AT
HOME, AND I CHANGE, FEED, BATHE.
AND THEN THE NEXT DAY:
CHANGE, FEED, BATHE.
I SOMETIMES FORGET TO EAT MYSELF
OR BATHE MYSELF OR DO ANYTHING
FOR MYSELF.
>> WELL, IT'S THE SAME WITH ME.
I FEEL LIKE I WORK, COME HOME,
CHANGE DIAPERS,
GET READY FOR WORK.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE I GAVE UP
EVERYTHING.
>> I GAVE UP STUFF TOO.
>> I KNOW. WE BOTH DID.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE
THIS HARD.
AND I SEE, LIKE, ALL OF MY
FRIENDS OFF PARTYING AND DOING
THEIR THING.
>> WHO DON'T HAVE BABIES.
>> IT JUST KIND OF--IT'S WEIRD
TO THINK ABOUT, LIKE, WHAT COULD
HAVE BEEN.
>> [crying]
>> I MOST DEFINITELY WANT TO GET
AN EDUCATION JUST TO PROVE TO MY
DAUGHTER THAT NO MATTER WHAT,
SHE CAN DO WHAT SHE WANTS TO DO
AND NOTHING CAN GET IN THE WAY
OF THAT.
IT'S VERY HARD TO FINISH SCHOOL
AND CONTINUE GOING WITH A BABY.
I AM ON HER SCHEDULE.
IF SHE'S CRYING AND I'M IN
THE MIDDLE OF AN EXAM, I HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO TAKE THIS
TIMED EXAM AND GET HER TO STOP
CRYING AT THE SAME TIME.
BEING ALONE A LOT WITH THIS BABY
IS HARD.
IT GETS REALLY LONELY.
HI, DAD.
I THINK I WAS A LITTLE BIT HARD
ON JOEY WHEN IT CAME TO
THE LIVING SITUATION.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING ON STUFF.
WE STILL FIGHT, BY ALL MEANS,
BUT IT'S NOT AS BAD AS BEFORE.
OH, NO, MY NOODLES STUCK
TOGETHER.
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> SPINACH AND TORTELLINI SALAD.
>> [chuckles]
>> JOEY WORKS HIS HARDEST TO
GIVE ME AND MOLLI WHATEVER
WE NEED.
>> [crying]
>> HE IS AN AMAZING DAD.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO?
[chuckles]
I WISH WE COULD SPEND MORE TIME
TOGETHER.
SET HER ON A PUMPKIN.
I WANT TO TAKE A PICTURE.
>> [crying]
>> OKAY, YOU CAN PICK HER
BACK UP.
AT THIS POINT, IF WE CAN MOVE TO
COLORADO, THAT WOULD BE IDEAL.
BUT IF JOEY CAN'T GET
TRANSFERRED, THEN WE CAN'T
AFFORD NOT TO HAVE THE GOOD JOB
THAT HE HAS RIGHT NOW.
SAY, "CHEESE, DAD."
I DON'T WANT TO BE STUCK IN
WYOMING FOREVER.
I KIND OF WANT TO EXPERIENCE
SOMETHING BIGGER AND BETTER.
I WENT STRAIGHT FROM BEING
A CHILD TO BEING AN ADULT.
>> I HAVE TO TIPTOE AROUND
MY SISTER.
I DON'T WANT HER TO FEEL
DEPRESSED OR SAD.
>> WHEN I GOT MY ABORTION,
I KNEW WHAT I WAS DOING IT FOR.
>> I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAD TO GO
THROUGH THAT.
AND I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAVE TO
STAY HERE AND WATCH HER HAVE
HER BABY, AND YOU CAN'T.
>> I'M LEAVING.
I DON'T WANT TO BE IN
THIS [bleep] HOUSE.