- Hi, I'm Felicia.
I'm 17, and I live in
Lewisville, Texas,
typical small-town USA.
I live at home with my
grandmother, mom,
and step-dad.
Oh, my god. Again?
I'm a senior this year,
and studying is my number one
priority.
There's a lot of pressure
from my mom to do well
because no one in my family
has ever graduated high school.
I'll be the first one.
'cause nobody's gone to the
12th grade, and that's why
I want to do it.
My life is hectic, but I still
find time to hang
with my girls.
Goodness, gracious.
I am starving.
And my boyfriend, Alex.
He works part-time as a barber
and dances in a crew with
his friends.
We've been together
for two years.
My mom isn't thrilled
that I spend so much time
with him.
- Felicia, what are you doing
in there?
- She always thinks we're
messing around and that
it's taking time away from
my studying.
- Open the damned door,
Felicia!
- Mom, go away!
But she doesn't have to guess
what goes on behind closed doors
anymore, because I'm pregnant.
[chime dings]
I'm just starting my senior year
of high school.
It's been an eventful summer.
After finding out I was
pregnant, I took night school
classes to keep me on track
to graduate with my friends.
And they're always asking me
about my pregnancy.
- So, Felicia, how did you
tell your mom?
- My period never came.
- You told her that you didn't
get your period?
- Well, yeah, I had told her.
I was like, "I still haven't
gotten it," 'cause she kept
asking me, "How come you haven't
gotten your period?"
she knows, like, I usually
have it on a set date.
She was like, "I'm gonna get
you a pregnancy test."
And then I just handed
the pregnancy test to her,
and she's like, "So you're
not pregnant?"
I was like, "No, Mom.
It says I'm pregnant."
[laughter]
- Yeah, I mean, yeah, 'cause
I took night school, and I
should graduate this year.
My friends are pretty
understanding.
I just wish my mom was too.
She really wants me to graduate
this year, since I'd be the
first in the family to finish
high school, but getting
pregnant wasn't exactly part
of her curriculum.
- Okay.
- I didn't believe it would
happen to me, but...
- It's not gonna stop me.
You know that's always been
my goal, to graduate
in this family.
- I know my mom's worried that
having a baby will prevent me
from graduating, but I think
I can handle it, especially
since Alex is here to
support me.
I convinced my mom to let him
live at our house during my
pregnancy.
She thinks Alex spends too much
time with his friends and isn't
mature enough to support me
once the baby comes.
But he's my first love,
and I know he'll be there.
- Do you remember when we
first met?
Do you remember?
- I remember the first time
Jasmine showed me you on
Myspace, and I was like,
"Well, he's mine."
I saw you, and I was like,
"He's mine."
- I had danced with that girl
Jessica.
- Yes, and you made me mad.
And then you came to me,
and I got happy.
- You think you're ready
to be a mom or what?
- I don't know.
I mean, I have to be ready.
It's gonna be different.
- It's already been different.
- I know, and it's gonna be
way different once she's
actually out of my stomach.
Both of my sisters had their
kids young, and I remember.
I was like, "I'm not--
that's not gonna be me."
- Yeah.
I honestly never even thought
I was gonna have kids
this young.
- Despite what my mom thinks,
I'm really glad Alex has stuck
by me since finding out I was
pregnant.
We definitely didn't think
it would happen to us
and neither did our friends.
- You would never expect
you to be pregnant.
It's shocking.
- I know, I saw myself
as a goody-goody too.
- So did y'all actually use
condoms?
- Honestly, we never used
a condom.
We used a condom, like,
twice ever in our whole
entire relationship.
- That's what's up.
But at least you're not running
away from it, like...
- Like, 'cause I lost it
to him, and I'm having his kid.
So I'm glad that it's him.
- But did you want a baby,
like...
- No, not at this time.
I definitely didn't want one
now.
I had, like, so much planned
for myself.
I'm a little worried.
Raising a baby and being the
first in my family to graduate
high school isn't going to be
easy.
[baby crying]
- It's a been a month since
I convinced my mom to let Alex
move in so he can be here for me
when I have the baby,
but we never get any privacy.
It looks so ugly all faded now.
Do yours fade?
- Nah.
That's 'cause you didn't
put no lotion or nothing.
- Close the door.
- Why?
- 'Cause of my mom.
- She doesn't even know about
your tattoo, huh?
- No.
She usually works most nights,
but when she's home, she's
always on our case.
- Felicia?
- Even though we're already
pregnant, my mom never wants us
to be behind closed doors.
[knocking at door]
- What are you doing in there?
- Mom!
Can you please go away?
- Ooh, I hate this.
Why you--you always close
the door!
- My older sister moved out
when she got pregnant at
a young age.
You never give us privacy.
- Damn.
Why she want to know what
we're doing in the restroom?
- So I feel like she understands
what I'm going through.
[phone beeps]
- Hello?
- Ciara?
- Yeah?
- You know how it is down over
here at Mom's.
There's, like, a lot of stress.
- Really?
- And there's just stress
'cause Mom, you know, when she
gets mad, she goes crazy,
and she's always screaming.
- I mean, I told you.
You always have--you know,
I always have my doors open.
- Mm-hmm.
It's nice of Ciara to offer us
a place to stay at her
apartment, but right now,
it's easier to have my mom
around to help us, even if
she's overbearing.
She set a curfew for Alex
to be back in the house,
which didn't go over well
because he works a lot
and stays out really late.
And it seems the more my mom
annoys Alex, the more time
he wants to spend elsewhere.
- What is wrong with your mom,
man?
She's been trippin' lately,
for reals.
She just comes in like nothing.
She doesn't even respect
nothing.
- She always says
'cause this is her house.
- It's just not working.
It's pissing me off.
- I know Alex is losing
his patience with my mom,
but my parents aren't happy
with his bad habits.
- When he goes all the time
and all the time, like,
see, he comes at 2:00
in the morning.
This is a problem for us.
We need to fix it too
because he lives in our home.
- He's gonna have to do
some changing.
He's got a rude awakening
coming too.
This all looks like fun and
games, but when it comes out--
[chuckles]--
life is going to change,
and it's gonna be--
it's gonna get tough.
- My parents have a good point.
Alex does have some growing up
to do.
I just hope living at my mom's
house doesn't push him away
for good.
Since he is out all the time
or at work, my mom's been the
one taking me to doctor's
appointments.
[monitor pulsing]
- 143 beats per minute.
And now the baby is looking
at you.
- Oh.
- Little baby!
- Oh, I see.
- That's cute.
So what are you gonna name her?
- Genesis.
That's a beautiful name.
We're all done.
Cute baby.
- It's so cute. Very cute.
That is beautiful.
- My mom can tell I'm upset
Alex isn't here for the
sonogram, so today, she's
going to talk to him about
his priorities.
- Yeah?
- Just out with one of
my friends.
- Yeah, you see?
- It's not like--
- I don't need to tell you
where I'm going.
That's the thing.
You get in my business.
You don't even know.
You're not my mom.
- You mom's just trippin'.
I'm just tired of it.
- You're running away always
when I want to talk to you.
- I'm not running away from
anything.
It's just you, basically.
I just can't stand it here,
so I'm just gonna go ahead
and leave.
- I don't need to face
anything.
- I know my mom can be
annoying, but I wish Alex
could try harder to get along
with her.
Once the baby is here,
we're gonna need her support.
Over the next week, things
between Alex and my mom
didn't get any better.
I hope they smooth things over
soon, since I plan on being
with Alex for a long time.
- So do you and Alex really
think y'all are, like,
gonna get married, like,
y'all are gonna work out?
- I don't know. I hope.
- Right, all you can do
is hope.
- Does he want to get married?
- Later in life, not now.
Like, if things go right.
- So if y'all don't work out,
what are you gonna do?
- If I didn't have Alex,
I would be, like,
financially dead.
I depend on him.
- That's crazy that he has
that much power.
- Like, literally, I--
every--I depend on him,
'cause he's my money.
- Wait, so, like, when you
graduate, right, are you gonna,
like, go to college?
- I want to open up my own
salon with Alex, since he's
a barber.
- Oh, that's cute.
- Yeah.
- So how are you and your girl?
- Just bad things have been
going on lately.
- Mm-hmm.
- Me and her mom started
getting into it crazy.
- Yeah.
- It's just not really tight,
man, 'cause it's nothing but
arguments and arguments,
fights.
I want to move out.
You know, I really want to move
out as soon as possible.
- Mm-hmm.
- When Alex got home from work,
he was still pretty annoyed
at my mom, and he doesn't think
things are going to get any
better.
- I've been wanting
to move out.
I already told you.
Either you come with me
or I go, 'cause I can't
stand it here.
I've been telling you that
for the past month.
- It's gonna be harder, though,
if we move out on our own.
- 'cause there's too much
stress in here.
- If we move to my sister's,
will you stick around more?
- We just need to move out.
It's not working.
I just think it's better,
you know?
Our relationship is gonna be
better now.
- I'm still on the fence about
leaving this house, but maybe
getting away from my mom will
bring Alex and I closer
together.
I know my mom is going to be
really surprised.
To avoid confrontation,
Alex rented a moving truck
that night so we could move our
stuff while my mom and step-dad
are out.
[objects rattling]
- Now that we're at my sister's
apartment, I'm still getting
used to the fact that my mom
won't be around to help with
the baby.
Where am I gonna put all
the baby stuff?
- Don't ask me.
It's your baby.
[laughter]
- Well, duh.
- I talked to Mom.
- About what?
- She was telling me that she
told you that she wanted you
to stay.
- It wasn't necessarily like
I had to leave, but I just
didn't want to deal with Alex
not getting along with Mom.
My mom was really surprised
and disappointed when she found
out Alex and I moved in with
my sister.
She wasted no time in letting me
know.
- Felicia!
- Hi.
- Well, I had to leave
sooner or later, Mom.
You have to...
Get through it.
- I hope so.
- It's hard for me to pretend
that I don't need my mom's help,
but right now, it's important
for me to be with Alex.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
- Bye.
- I didn't necessarily want
to leave, but I hope that Alex
will be happier to be out of
my mom's house.
- You have my word.
I'll be there.
All right, see you later.
- So far, he hasn't spent much
time at home.
Bye.
And even though we picked
Genesis as our little girl's
name, he missed another checkup.
I hope we can start spending
more time together now.
You're gonna wake up in the
morning and in the nighttime
when she's crying?
Or are you gonna make me
do all the work?
- We could take turns.
You could do it for a full week
and then--
- That'll never happen.
I think you'll get--
- No, trust me.
- You'll get frustrated
of her crying.
- Like, right now, right now,
you might be saying that,
but I bet you whatever
I'm gonna get attached to--
I'm gonna get attached to her.
- You gonna spend more time
at home?
Alex isn't too convincing
when he says he's going to be
here to help with the baby.
I hope he gets serious soon
about his commitment because
I've got a lot of schoolwork
to do.
I really want to keep up
with my studies, but being
pregnant is exhausting.
It's getting harder to focus
in class, and I barely have
the energy to do my homework.
- Hey, babe.
- I hate math.
- I would help you, but,
you know, I don't want to give
you the answers, because--
- Because they'll be wrong.
- No, because then--
Alex just got home from work,
and as usual, he's already
leaving again to be with his
friends.
- Ladies first.
Ladies first as always.
- I guess he'd rather
be elsewhere.
- Let's do this.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
- ♪ If you were me
♪ And I was you
♪ And we could see
♪ Completely through
- It's 2:30 in the morning,
and he's still not back.
- I'm really pissed at Alex
for staying out all night.
He doesn't seem to care that
I'm home alone now more often.
It really worries me.
Is this how it's going to be
when the baby comes?
Probably.
Because over the next few weeks,
Alex went out more and more.
He's always complaining that
we need to save money so we can
get our own place, but he's out
spending cash with his friends
almost every night.
Tonight when he comes home
from work, I plan to talk to him
about his commitment.
Before I was pregnant, Alex used
to treat me, like, so nice.
- Mm-hmm.
- He tells me, "I'm coming home
early."
he doesn't get home till, like,
2:00, 3:00 in the morning.
- Yeah, that's messed up.
[phone buzzing]
- Hello?
- At home.
- Yeah.
- I don't think so.
- You can't go.
- No!
- What time are you coming
home?
[buttons clicking]
- [laughs]
- Now I'm saying,
"You're so mean.
There you go again,
leaving me again."
No, he hasn't texted me.
I'm mad.
- 'Cause he knows you're right.
- This isn't the Alex I want
to have a baby with.
Because Alex stayed over at
his friend's house again,
our talk had to wait until
the next day.
- What are you doing?
- Homework.
- What kind of homework?
- English.
How was work?
[phone ringing]
- Hey, what are y'all doing?
Are you already coming or what?
Just call Felicia,
'cause I'm not gonna be here.
- What do you mean you're not
gonna be here?
- Yeah, I'm--I'm--
I'm going to my aunt's house
first, and one of my friends
might go get a tattoo, so...
- This is pretty much our last
weekend till the baby comes.
That's why I wanted to do
something with you.
- We could still do something
next weekend.
- Next weekend, she's probably
gonna be here.
- I don't like always to be,
like, right there.
You know, I also want
to have my space.
- So after she's born,
are you still gonna be
going out?
- I can't really answer that.
- Why not?
- Because I don't know.
- I don't want to be left alone
every weekend with her.
- It's just not the same
anymore.
It's just not.
- So what's different
about now?
- You are.
- How am I different?
- ♪ Go on, go on
[melancholy music]
♪ If you've nothing to say
- [sobs]
- ♪ Then I will be
♪ On my way
♪ Go on, go on
- What I thought would be
the last week of my pregnancy
really wasn't.
Even though I'm sure he'd rather
be with his friends, Alex came
with me to the doctor's office.
As if things weren't stressful
enough, I'm now four days past
my due date.
- How are y'all?
You're having contractions,
I hope?
- No.
- Um, so you're really
not dilated yet,
but we are kind of running
out of time.
It's really not safe to go on
with a pregnancy a great deal
longer.
The plan is to bring you into
the hospital tomorrow night
and to induce you on Thursday.
- All right.
- Doing good.
Won't be much longer.
- Even though it's after my due
date, I'm really nervous to be
induced.
- Stuff so I'm not bored,
baby stuff, and my stuff.
- I'm gonna take this for
my neck.
- My mom has to work the night
shift, so I was glad Alex was
able to take some time off
from work to be with me
at the hospital.
I hope he's prepared to help me
through this.
- We want you to get as much
rest as possible, so...
- ♪
- That's not gonna take effect
really fast, okay?
You'll start feeling those
cramps, and they'll just
progressively get worse.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- The pitocin is definitely
working because I'm starting
to feel contractions.
I can't believe I'm finally
in labor.
- Why are you crying? Huh?
- Alex doesn't seem to realize
how intense this is for me.
[belching]
- What's wrong, baby?
You scared?
Just relax.
- [vomiting]
[spits]
My labor has been really rough
so far.
But seeing my mom makes me feel
a little bit better.
- [sighs] Oh, my god.
The pain is getting worse
and worse, and I'm not sure
how much I can take.
[electronic beeping]
- May I help you?
- Can I get someone to see
if I can get an epidural now?
- Sticking it in.
- [sighs]
- Alex is not being supportive,
so I'm trying my best
to ignore him.
- I'm just gonna get everything
set up, Felicia, and then we'll
get you into position.
- After getting the epidural,
I can hardly feel anything.
- She's really close.
So with the next contraction,
we'll start pushing.
- It's almost time to push,
and I'm happy my family is here
for encouragement.
- It looks like you're having
a contraction.
So I want you to take
a big deep breath
and push hard on your bottom.
One, two, three, excellent.
- Yes, Felicia, yes.
- Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
Big deep breath,
and go again.
You can do it.
And go.
Okay, one, two, three,
four...
Good job.
We can already see some
black hair. Good job.
[electronic beep]
- May I help you?
- Yeah, if you want to call
Dr. Fleidner for delivery,
please?
- When the doctor came in,
I knew we were getting close.
- Okay, so they tell me
you can push.
- Push hard as you can.
You can do it.
- Go, go.
- Push hard as you can.
Excellent job. Excellent job.
Good job. Good job.
Excellent.
- I bet you can do it.
I want you--when you're ready,
take a deep breath and push
again.
- Ready? Big deep breath.
- Oh, here we go.
[people murmuring excitedly]
- Good job.
- I knew you could.
Excellent job, Felicia.
[cheering]
- Oh, my god.
- Good job! Good job!
- Good job!
[baby crying]
- Thank you, Jesus.
[laughter]
[baby wailing]
- I'm so happy that Genesis
is finally here.
She is so precious.
It even looked like she was
having an effect on Alex.
But it didn't take long
for him to slip back into
his old self.
- Don't go.
- You're gonna go home?
[baby fussing]
All right, babe.
I'll be back later. All right.
- I don't know, Mom.
- Alex didn't come back to
the hospital last night
and went straight into work
this morning.
I guess some things
never change.
I'm realizing just how much
I'm gonna need my mom's help.
- Hello!
How is my baby?
- Okay.
- Not you.
My baby.
- Where's Alex?
- He went to go to work,
to cut hair.
- Oh, yeah?
Man.
Always at the wrong time,
just cutting hair.
- Well, yeah.
Mom, I want to, like,
come back to your house,
'cause I'm gonna need help
with the baby.
- I want to, like, go
straight--after I get out
of the hospital tomorrow,
like, go straight to y'all's
house, 'cause I can't even
get up, really.
It hurts, and I'm not gonna have
anyone to help me at Ciara's,
'cause Alex works, so I'll be
by myself that whole time.
- Yeah, that's not good.
Well, I love you,
and I can't wait.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- You know, we love you, okay?
- I'm glad my mom is willing
to have us back at her house,
so I texted Alex, and I told him
the plan.
He wasn't happy, but it's the
right thing to do for the baby,
especially if he isn't going
to take any time off of work.
Sucks that you're not gonna be
there when she comes home
for the first time.
- Just gonna be for, like,
four or five hours, basically.
- I know, but...
But at least he agreed to drive
me home to my mom's house.
- Okay, everything's set to go.
You are discharged.
Baby is discharged.
So you're good to go.
- ♪ Turn the light low
♪ I want to go
♪ Below this
♪
♪ Or if you see
♪ Come follow me
♪ Outside
- Yeah.
- Huh?
- We just brought her home,
and he's already leaving.
I know he has to work to make
money for the baby, but I could
really use the support right
now, especially if I'm gonna
graduate on time.
- ♪ I want to be
- It's clear this was
the right choice,
'cause I will definitely
need my mom's help.
[baby crying]
- Oh, don't start.
You're fine.
It's been a week since coming
home from the hospital.
Between work and hanging out
with his friends, Alex has
barely been around to help me
with the baby, and I'm starting
to fall behind in my schoolwork.
Okay, hush.
I don't understand why
he's acting this way.
I thought he was ready
to be a dad.
At least my friends are anxious
to spend time with Genesis.
- I can't believe this thing
came out of your vagina.
[laughter]
- Pearl!
- I'm for real.
- Yeah, it felt so weird
when they pulled her out
'cause it just--my stomach
just went plop.
- That's nasty.
- It was weird.
- So uncomfortable.
- So, like, what's going on
with you and Alex right now?
Like, are you happy?
- I just don't like that he's
not ever home.
- Where is he?
- Out.
He doesn't like being home.
- [laughs]
- You don't got nothing to say?
- Is he there for you, like,
emotionally and mentally?
- I can't talk to him.
- So do you think that Alex
is gonna stick around?
- I don't know.
It just depends
on how things go, I guess.
- Are you happy with your
baby mama?
Will you--
[laughter]
- You know, like, once you know
a girl, at the moment of being
with her, right, you like it,
right?
But then after you start
living with her actually,
in her house, you know, or
something, everything changes.
You know what I mean?
Like, she's actually--
she's not actually how she
used to be.
It's, like, back then,
when she wasn't pregnant,
it was better than now.
[line ringing]
- I kept calling Alex, and he
wouldn't pick up his phone.
[line ringing]
Since we've been home from
the hospital, it feels like
I'm doing all the work.
[baby fussing]
[shushes]
I've got a lot of homework
I need to get done before
I head back to school.
Where's your Daddy at?
- Ahh...
- I can't believe I still
haven't heard from Alex.
[line ringing]
- Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice--
- [growls]
- Go first.
- During the past week,
my friends have been busy
shopping for prom dresses.
But I'm busy convincing them to
help me pick up baby supplies.
- What do you, like,
need from here?
- Well, I really need diapers.
- Is--does that mean the size?
Yeah.
[indistinct]
- 17 times 8?
Actually--
- That's not much.
[all gasp]
- The baby! Are you crazy?
- The one for her size
is the small, which is 200
diapers for $19.99.
- I say you get these.
- Yeah.
- Let's go look at strollers.
- Did you want the pink
or the green one?
- She said pink, right?
Yeah, the pink.
- How much is that?
- It's $29.99.
- That's a pretty good price.
- Oh, she looks so cute.
- I have to call Alex.
- Okeydokey.
- I do need a stroller
for Genesis, but I only have
money for diapers.
I wish Alex would put more money
into baby supplies instead of
spending it with his friends.
What took you so long?
- You want to see what I got?
- How much were they?
- I bought them for $80.
- I thought you weren't gonna
spend more than $70.
- It was just $10 more.
- $10 that could have been used
on the stroller.
Where do you think we'll be
in a year from now?
- You never know. I don't know.
- I don't want to be left alone
with Genesis.
[bulb syringe squeaks]
- It makes a fart sound.
- Alex is so immature.
I thought having a baby would
make him grow up.
Genesis has been by my side
from the moment she was born.
[phone ringing]
But today I need to leave her
so that I can go back to school.
Alex and my mom already left
for work, so my grandmother
is taking care of Genesis
while I'm away.
You gonna stay here and be
a good girl for Grandma?
It's already 8:30?
Oh, my god.
Bye, baby girl. Miss you.
Thank you for watching her.
I'll be back at 4:00.
Okay. Bye.
I'm anxious to go back
to school.
I need to figure out if
I'm still on track to graduate
this year.
I definitely missed a lot.
There's so much work
to catch up on.
And I can barely concentrate
in class.
All I can think about
is how much I miss my baby girl.
- Mamacita.
[gasps]
Look at who's coming!
Your mommy's coming!
Hi, mamacita.
Mini mommy.
[babbles in baby talk]
- I missed her all day.
It's all I could think about.
- Boring.
- I could have graduated
in 2 1/2 weeks, but since
the semester already started
and I'm behind, I have to make
up my hours before this year
is over.
Then I'll graduate, probably.
- Yeah.
- Yes?
- It is hard.
The pressure is still on
for me to graduate, and I know
I'm going to need Alex's help.
So that night, he agreed
to take care of Genesis
while I tried to study.
- What time is it right now?
- She's hungry?
- [shushing]
[shushing]
[laughs]
There, you see?
Crybaby.
- Are you done?
- No.
All right.
Alex was no help babysitting
tonight.
Gonna fail this test.
I've got a ton of homework
to do.
I'm so behind, and he doesn't
even care.
[baby fussing]
[liquid sloshing]
[sneezes]
[baby fussing]
[shushing]
Why am I the only one
who gets up at night
when Genesis starts crying?
- Alex's behavior sucks.
He needs to grow up and accept
his responsibilities.
There's no way I'll be able
to graduate high school without
his help, and my mom will be
devastated.
I waited for him to come home
that day after work, because
we really need to talk.
- What are y'all doing?
- Just hanging out.
Whenever you come home,
it's, like, sometimes I would
want some help with her,
and I really never get that.
- That's it?
- You act like it's
an easy job.
You act like I do nothing.
- I'd rather take care of her
and you go to work, so you can
see how I feel.
I just want you to.
I would rather, honestly,
take care of her.
- I'd rather work.
- Tell you what.
Let's switch then.
You'll see how it is.
But you're also gonna take care
of her and me, right?
And pay rent and pay for food?
And for diapers and everything?
- I'm just saying you don't
help with Genesis at all.
You come home, and I still
don't get no help.
She's still in my arms
the whole day, the whole night.
- You're not happy, are you?
- No.
Honestly, I know I used to bug
about you not being with me
all the time, but now that
I have Genesis, I could care
less if you're with me,
but this is your daughter.
- I know, in the future,
things do change, and me
and Alex do get better, and he
helps me to help her grow,
and I don't want her to see us
going through struggles.
Being a parent is frustrating.
There's a lot that you have to
give up.
It's like nothing's about me
anymore.
Everything is about her.
Genesis needs her father
to be there for her.
And I don't want her not having
a dad, not knowing who her
real dad is.
But I know things probably won't
end up being good between us.
I'm not a teenager anymore.
I'm a mom, and that's hard
to say, but I'm a mom now,
and my teenage life is pretty
much over.
- I want to be the first one
to graduate in my family
for my mom and for Genesis,
but literally, it's just--
it's not easy,
and having the baby has put me
a lot behind in my schoolwork.
If I could go back in time
before all this happened
and do it all over again,
I would, 'cause this is not
the life I planned for me.
- My mom made me move out.
I was not allowed to live
under her roof pregnant.
- Probably go and see you
at Huntsville.
You better be living with me.
- We're promoting Daniel's
education, and what about
the girl here?
- Push, push, push.
- Oh!
- I just don't want to feel
like I'm stuck with you.
- Well, you are.
- When are you gonna
wake the hell up?
You got a baby, sweetie.
[upbeat piano music]
♪
- ♪ Go these nine awful weeks
♪ Don't know how I'm gonna
♪ Get through it all
♪ I'm weak, but I'm
♪ Strong enough to see
♪ When it's all done ♪