Someone'Ős got to get
that pony tamed.
Hi, I'Őm Mackenzie.
I'Őm 16 and live
in Miami, Oklahoma.
When I'Őm not outside
riding horses,
you can find me
inside at the gym.
Competitive
cheerleading is my life.
[Girl]
Good one.
And since I'Őm planning
to cheer in college when
I graduate in two years,
I'Őm always trying to stick
the most dangerous stunts.
Until then, I live at home
with my mom, dad,
two sisters, and brother.
Touchdown!
I'Őm in the end zone!
Even though we'Őre
all super close,
it'Ős my boyfriend Josh
who really gets me.
Don'Őt throw it that hard.
He'Ős an adrenaline junkie too
and rides bulls.
But since he'Ős had
a few concussions,
he mainly rides
wild horses now,
but still competes
in all the local rodeos.
You go, boy.
We'Őre totally in love.
Although we'Őre both really
busy, we'Őre gonna have to start
spending more time
together soon,
because I'Őm pregnant.
My due date is four months away,
and even though there'Ős a lot
to plan for with the baby...
Look for seats down there.
Summer'Ős almost over,
and my friends
and I never miss a rodeo.
Look, your first rodeo.
[laughing]
Whoo!
[laughs]
Tomorrow?
I don'Őt want to watch it.
Does it scare you?
Yeah.
I don'Őt want a dead
baby'Ős daddy.
[laughs]
Mackenzie.
Josh.
Want to say thank you to...
[speaking indistinctly]
Yeah.
Josh, I think I kiss
Mackenzie more than you.
Mwah!
Fun, huh?
[laughing]
My friends were pretty shocked
to find out I was pregnant,
especially since I had
big goals this year
to win state in tumbling.
Although I need
to find a job soon,
I'Őm still determined to go
to as many practices as I can,
so I don'Őt fall too far behind.
Sorry, I caught.
Sorry.
No, you'Őre good.
That was good.
Hey, squad.
Whoo-hoo!
What'Ős up, Mackenzie?
You girls ready?
Come on, Cheyenne. Let'Ős go.
Kick it.
Let'Ős go. Push. Push.
Get there.
Yeah.
That'Őll work.
Handspring back.
Let'Ős go. Push. Push.
Stand up.
There you go.
Good job.
[Mackenzie]
Yay.
This is making me depressed.
Oh.
I feel so bad.
I just hope I can
do this stuff again.
I hope I can get
back into that body.
That was me
before I got pregnant.
[both laugh]
Awesome.
You guys want to corner up?
You should jump in soon.
So what'Ős the plan
after the baby comes?
Are you gonna be back
cheerleading?
Heck yeah, I am.
[laughs]
Have you thought about, like,
what that'Ős gonna be
like to have to cheer and--
I don'Őt care.
I'Őm gonna do it.
One way or another.
When is
your baby due?
October 9th.
October.
Okay.
[Matt]
But if you'Őre cheerleading,
who'Ős gonna watch the baby?
Yeah, cheer used to be your
number one priority
but not anymore.
It'Ős my number two.
[laughs]
And Josh is number three.
[laughter]
I still have not met Josh.
He'Ős busy with rodeos.
[Matt]
Is he a junior also?
He'Ős graduated.
Are you gonna try to cheer
for the high school, or...
Yeah.
I'Őll show you
I'Őm still flexible.
Seriously.
[Cody]
All the way up?
Yeah, see?
Yay!
Whoo!
O-S-U.
[laughter]
Josh has been really supportive
ever since we found out
I was pregnant
and has been trying to
win some money by competing
in more rodeos lately.
But since our baby
is coming in a few months,
I want to make
the most of the time
we have together.
If I'Őm just, like,
not far along at all?
Okay.
Well, that sucks.
[Mackenzie]
There'Ős the merry-go-round.
You'Őll not bawl
that hard.
Oh, hell, no.
That thing?
No.
You'Őre questioning my manhood,
man.
[laughs]
[Mackenzie]
I have to give
birth to your kid,
so I think you can
do this for me.
Hey, can she ride?
Yeah, she can ride.
Dang it, man.
You should'Őve helped me out.
You should'Őve said no.
[Mackenzie]
Come on.
Will you help me on it?
[laughs]
Okay, thank you.
Oh!
Oh, my gosh.
My water just broke.
No, it didn'Őt.
Just kidding.
This is when you put
your arms up and go, "Whoo!"
Are you serious?
Oh.
That'Ős a good way
to go into labor.
I hope I'Őm with you
when my water breaks.
When'Ős my due date, Josh?
It'Ős, like...
September 19th.
October 9th.
Oh.
You need to get it in gear.
Yeah, I plan on that.
You plan on that?
Yeah.
Okay, well, then,
what about your plans
with me in the future?
Well, we need to both
settle down and get jobs.
Man, it takes time.
I can'Őt just go out there
and apply for a job
and expect for
someone to call me back.
Okay, but we have to think
about the future.
You can'Őt leave me
to do this on my own,
because me, nor my family,
can support this baby.
Mine and your money together,
maybe.
But that'Ős the only way we'Őre
gonna come close to doing it,
is doing it together.
I wish Josh would help me
plan more for the baby.
We know we'Őre having a boy,
but that'Ős all we know,
and my family is worried
we'Őre not ready.
You know, my initial thought
was, "This is my baby sister."
You know, you'Őre so young.
You'Őre only 16.
And for you to take on
a responsibility like this,
it worries me.
Just don'Őt name the baby
something like Cowbell
or something like that.
Spur.
But Josh wants to name the kid,
like, Haybell.
[Mackenzie]
No, he said Buckshot.
Buckshot. Buckshot.
And if it was a girl,
her name was gonna be Doeshot.
Doeshot?
[both laugh]
[Mackenzie]
I'Őm not kidding.
Mackenzie.
Think about your kid'Ős life.
It'Ős a person.
Well, I like Gannon.
I like the name Gannon.
Just think about it,
'Őcause it'Ős important.
It really is.
[Mackenzie]
I know my sisters don'Őt think
I'Őm taking it seriously,
but I get there'Ős
a lot to figure out
before the baby comes.
Yeah,
money'Ős gonna be a big problem.
[Angie]
Exactly.
You'Őre not thinking
about things like that?
That baby'Ős gonna
change everything.
That'Ős why I wanted to wring
your neck when I found out
you were pregnant.
You remember that day?
I couldn'Őt talk.
Yeah.
[Angie]
I think--
Here'Ős where I get confused.
I mean, how did this happen?
Because he seemed so shy,
and he won'Őt
even hardly touch you
when he'Ős around us,
and all of a sudden,
you'Őre pregnant.
I don'Őt know.
I did not want to take
birth control
because I did not want
to gain weight.
[laughs]
I didn'Őt.
I was a cheerleader.
So now you'Őre gonna balloon.
You can'Őt even cheer now.
[Mackenzie]
I'Őm going to.
I know I'Őm going to.
It'Ős gonna be tough with a baby.
I mean, things are not gonna be
like what you thought
they were gonna be.
You know what I'Őm saying?
[Mackenzie]
Yeah.
[sighs]
[chime dings]
I'Őm due in just
three months,
so I'Őm calling around to all
the local job openings,
because our parents can'Őt
help us out with much money.
Good luck.
[Woman]
Hello?
Hey, I was wondering
if you had any openings.
Okay.
[line ringing]
Um, yes.
Do you know if you guys
have any openings?
Thank you.
Yes, I'Őm 16,
and I'Őm seven months pregnant.
Okay, bye.
[Man]
Bye.
There'Ős no more.
That'Ős it?
I'Őll be--
Yeah.
[Dr. Swan]
Okay, so we'Őre gonna
take a look.
There you go.
That'Ős a pretty cool view.
[Angie]
That'Ős a good one.
[Brad]
He'Ős so busy.
He'Ős hard to keep up with.
[Angie]
Oh, no.
He'Ős gonna be like Mackenzie.
Is he sucking his thumb?
[Dr. Swan]
He'Ős very close.
[Angie]
Look at his fists.
Kidneys look good.
[Angie]
Josh wants to make sure
it'Ős still a boy too.
[Dr. Swan]
Yeah.
That would be right
between the legs there.
[Angie]
There'Ős your boy, Josh.
No doubt.
Pick out names.
Pick out boy clothes.
[Angie]
There it is.
[heartbeat thudding]
Isn'Őt that cool?Yeah.
[Mackenzie]
Josh and I finally agreed
on naming the baby Gannon,
but my mom is worried,
because that'Ős basically
all we have figured out.
Dear heavenly Father,
thank you so much for this food,
and thank you
for Mackenzie and Josh,
and thank you for baby Gannon.
In your name, I pray.
Amen.
So reality setting in yet?
This is huge.
Yeah.
Like,
feeling Gannon move and stuff,
it makes it so much more real.
[Angie]
Yeah.
Where'Ős the baby gonna stay?
Well, clearly, we have no
money to move in together.
Well, I wouldn'Őt want you
to move in together
if you wasn'Őt married anyway.
Then how are we gonna--
If Josh wanted to stay here
and help take care of the baby,
he can just sleep
in the room with the baby,
and you can sleep in here,
and you guys can take turns.
So, Josh, since she has
to finish high school--
I mean, that'Ős just huge.
Yeah.
I really don'Őt want to take
that much time off
when the baby'Ős here.
So just a few weeks,
you'Őre thinking?
Do you have a plan on how
you'Őre gonna pay for day care?
'ŐCause right now,
neither one of you have jobs.
[huffs]
Are you gonna be able
to bring in money on that?
Yeah.
It all depends, like, what place
I get in and how I score.
But what happens when
you break something
or have another concussion?
That'Ős something else
to think about.
You'Őre right.
Josh.
[Mackenzie]
What if you become paralyzed?
You can'Őt rely on that,
because you'Őre risking your life
every time you get on 'Őem.
Hmm.
You have a baby that needs you.
♪♪
I know Josh doesn'Őt
want to give up rodeos,
but I'Őve had
to sacrifice a lot too.
[knock at door]
Hey.
See how good of shape I was in?
Yeah, you had a six-pack.
You think you can
still fit into it?
[Mackenzie]
I don'Őt know.
We can try.
[Kayleen]
Do it.
Oh.
Okay, now,
tuck your head in.
One, two, three.
Oh.
Oh!
[both laugh]
Oh, my gosh.
And now we have to do
the hair on my head.
[Kayleen]
Wait, I got to zip it up.
I can'Őt believe this thing
still goes on.
[Mackenzie]
I know.
[Kayleen]
Well, it'Ős only
your belly that'Ős--
[laughs]
Do I look good?
Oh, goodness.
Oh, my God.
[Angie]
Hey, Mack.
What?
Oh, my goodness.
[laughing]
So you are determined
to get back into that
right after the baby comes.
Yeah, with the six-pack
and no stretch marks.
Okay.
[Kayleen]
Good luck with that.
[chime dings]
[Mackenzie]
School starts in four weeks.
And since I'Őm having
a hard time finding a job,
me and my dad
are recycling cans
to bring in
a little extra money.
126 pounds, at 42 a pound--
A check for you.
[Brad]
All righty.
Let'Ős go.
[Mackenzie]
Every little bit helps,
but it'Ős definitely not
a permanent solution.
What was it?
$52?
[Mackenzie]
Two.
[Brad]
That'Ős the most we'Őve ever made.
So is this gonna be your
career now?
Is this what you
gonna do for money?
Yep.
I'Őm gonna make a living
off of this.
[laughs]
I just thought we'Őd
both have jobs, but...
[Brad]
Yeah.
I'Őve tried.
If you get a job right now,
though,
in a month,
you'Őre gonna have to take off.
[Mackenzie]
I know.
That'Ős why no one will hire me.
Yeah.
I just don'Őt know how
I'Őm gonna buy diapers.
Hey, Josh needs to buck up too.
It'Ős time to grow up,
'Őcause now you got
a baby to think about.
And I think you'Őre gonna
be able to survive,
but I think it'Ős gonna
be very tough.
So how long you had
this horse, Josh?
I'Őve had him
since he was one.
You broke him, didn'Őt you?
[Josh]
Yeah.
You gonna ride for a living
when the baby comes?
Yeah, it'Őd be nice.
But me and Mackenzie
were talking,
and she'Ős on me to give up
rodeo and Bronc riding.
Really?
[Josh]
Yeah, it'Ős too dangerous.
What do you think?
[Josh]
I don'Őt know.
I mean, like,
I know where she'Ős coming from.
She don'Őt want me
getting hurt 'Őcause of Gannon,
but, you know, there'Ős
a lot of good Bronc riders
that got babies on the way,
or they have babies.
You know, it'Ős not affecting how
they worked it out, you know?
But, you know, I'Őve done
this before I met her.
You know?
It'Ős part of your life.
[Josh]
Yeah, and I don'Őt think
there'Ős any way I can just quit.
You know what I mean?
That natural high.
Nothing like it.
[Josh]
Yep.
Well, I'Őm not one to get into
anybody'Ős business, but...
I wouldn'Őt do it.
Give up riding?
Nah.
Don'Őt take away
somebody'Ős rodeo.
[Josh]
Yeah.
[line ringing]
[hooves clomping]
[Mackenzie]
Even though I want
him to stop riding,
Josh has been bringing in
some money from rodeos.
And since I can'Őt find a job,
and the baby'Ős due
in two months,
we don'Őt have much choice.
Hello?
Hey, what are you doing?
Getting ready to go to a rodeo.
[Mackenzie]
Mm.
Be careful.
Love you.
Love you too.
[Mackenzie]
School starts
in a couple of weeks,
so I'Őm meeting up
with my friends,
because there'Ős
a lot of stuff I need.
Just looking at this
makes me sick.
Yeah, I know.
[Mackenzie]
I only want to take a month off
when Gannon is born
so I don'Őt fall too far behind.
Do you need any pencils?
These are $16?
Oh, no, no, no.
We don'Őt do that.
Oh, yeah.
20 stuff.
Are those 20?
Yeah, that'Ős more my...
[both laugh]
[Mackenzie]
This is not how I thought
I would start my junior year.
The summer'Ős flown by so fast.
I know. I can'Őt believe
it'Ős almost over.
Like, oh, my gosh.
I don'Őt even know
what I'Őm wearing.
Oh, I'Őm gonna look hot.
You'Őre gonna look
like a rock star.
Mackenzie, what are you wearing?
Um, I'Őm gonna look
like a rock star too.
[laughter]
So, Mackenzie,
how are you and Josh doing?
Good.
You guys are, like,
the cutest couple ever.
Like, your pictures on
Facebook--
I'Őm like, "Oh."
I mean, he can'Őt get a job.
Probably 'Őcause he'Ős
on the way to a rodeo.
And I don'Őt want to get mad
and be like,
"I hate you. You'Őre so lazy.
You'Őre not getting a job."
But I feel like
this whole situation
is very bad timing for getting
ready to have a baby.
Yeah.
[Mackenzie]
Josh and I planned tonight
to look at day care
options together,
but he'Ős late.
[phone chiming]
Hello?
[Becky]
Hey, Mackenzie?
Hi.
Um, Josh has been
in a car accident?
I'Őm at my house.
I will be up there
as soon as I can.
Okay.
[engine turning over]
When I got to the hospital,
Josh was in the ICU for neck
and head injuries.
His family told me his pickup
got hit by a truck.
Although he might need
surgery in a few weeks,
the doctors sent him
home for rest.
I never thought I'Őd
have to worry about
you getting hit by a semi.
I thought I'Őd have to worry
about you getting bucked off.
So you don'Őt know 100%
you'Őre having surgery?
[Josh]
Well, we'Őll see,
but I don'Őt know when.
But hopefully I'Őll be
able to ride again.
I say, because you have a son,
you'Őre not getting back on one.
Yeah, but there'Ős a lot
of Bronc riders,
a lot of bull riders out there,
that are in the same condition
as I am or even worse--
They didn'Őt get hit by a semi.
Yeah, no [bleep].
Okay, but do you understand
why I'Őm frustrated?
Because I'Őm having a baby.
I have no money.
You can'Őt work.
So pretty much,
day care'Ős out of the question.
Like, I have to wake up
and go to school.
What are you wanting me
to do with him?
I don'Őt know.
I mean, it'Ős hard for me
to think right now.
I'Őm having a baby,
and I have nowhere to put him.
I'Őm not dropping
out of high school.
And if that'Ős my only choice,
to drop out,
then I'Őm gonna be mad.
Like, you won'Őt say anything.
Because I don'Őt know.
You can at least say,
"It'Őll all work out.
"Things will be better."
But you just go, "Okay."
What?
Control my brain, what I do,
and if they do something,
it could [bleep] paralyze me.
Okay, you can stop
talking to me like that.
No, you just don'Őt get it.
You don'Őt.
You think everything'Ős gonna
be all right, but it'Ős not.
[sighs] Explain
Explain to me
what the doctor said.
I guess he has to have
surgery on his neck.
Oh, my gosh.
But they'Őre waiting
and putting it off.
So you'Őre afraid--
I'Őll have a newborn
with no help.
Well, that'Ős a possibility.
I wanted things to be better
than this when Gannon was born.
But the bottom line is,
there'Ős a baby coming
in a few weeks.
Actually, it could be any day.
I know.
And we can make the best of it,
or we can make the worst of it.
You know what I'Őm saying?
[Mackenzie]
There'Ős a lot to do
before Gannon comes,
and since money'Ős tight,
we'Őre setting up
my old baby crib.
See, I'Őm smart.
I left the screws in it.
[Mackenzie]
And today, my sisters are
throwing us a baby shower
so we can get things
in place for Gannon.
Okay, one, two, three.
[Mackenzie]
It means a lot to me
that Josh made it,
even though he'Ős
not feeling great.
Oh, my gosh.
Ah!
Look at them.
Aren'Őt they cute?
[Mackenzie]
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, look at this one.
Ah.
Cute.
Oh, my goodness.
Look.
Ah.
Oh, realtree.
That is adorable.
And it has a hat.
It'Ős realtree!
Although I'Őm still not sure
who will watch Gannon
when I go back to school,
I'Őm glad we got a lot
of what we need,
and our families have offered
to help out as much as they can.
Today is the first day
of my junior year.
[Angie]
Hey, Mackers, wake up.
Hello?
You can do this.
[Mackenzie]
I'Őm more uncomfortable
than ever,
but since I know I'Őll
have a lot of absences
after Gannon is born,
I can'Őt miss any days now.
Oh, goodness.
I can'Őt zip it.
[chime dings]
I used to be
the smallest girl in school,
but today,
I can'Őt hide from anyone.
I can handle all the whispers,
but going from
class to class all day
has made my feet swell up
so bad, I can barely walk.
Hey.
Oh, hi.
You tired?
Yeah.
I need to take these off ASAP.
[laughs]
[Whitney]
So how was school?
Were people nice to you?
They were just like,
"Oh, Mackenzie.
"Whoa."
[laughs]
Being back in school is
really wearing me out,
so I'Őm not sure I can
keep it up another month
until my due date.
[Whitney]
We'Őre giving you one week
until you pop.
I'Őm gonna pop tonight.
I mean, like...
My whole body'Ős swollen.
Even the baby'Ős swollen.
[Angie]
Mack, you need to go lay down,
put your feet up.
Yeah.
I feel like I'Őm gonna throw up.
I need to lay down.
Mom!
Hey, kiddo.
What'Ős wrong?
My stomach.
Okay, like, is it,
like, your back hurting
because you'Őre too big,
or is it contractions?
I don'Őt know.
Contractions, I think.
Okay, so do you want
to go to the doctor?
You think
we need to go in?
Yeah.
Okay, get your shoes on.
Did you call Josh?
Yeah, I texted him.
[Angie]
Okay.
You don'Őt have any bags packed.
They probably won'Őt keep me
anyways.
[Angie]
Okay.
Well, we'Őll try.
Come on.
Oh, it hurts.
[moaning]
Yeah.
[engine turning over]
Okay.
Okay, I think I need
to call the hospital
and tell them
we'Őre on our way, okay?
[Mackenzie]
Yeah.
So how you feeling,
Mackenzie?
Like crap.
Okay.
[Mackenzie]
Although my water
hasn'Őt broken yet,
the doctor confirmed
my labor has started
and admitted me.
Ow.
It keeps getting more pressure.
Ow!
It'Ős been seven hours.
I'Őm miserable.
[Angie]
Oh.
[Mackenzie]
And the doctor told me
that the baby is so big
that he can'Őt
come out naturally,
so they decided I should
have a C-section.
I'Őm pretty scared,
but having everyone here
makes it easier.
[Josh]
Give a thumbs-up.
You'Őre a happy daddy.
[Brad]
Don'Őt worry about it.
We got it.
[Angie]
Okay, thank you.
You'Őre gonna have a baby,
Mackey.
Can you believe
it'Ős finally here?
You can'Őt feel your butt?
[laughs]
That'Ős a good thing.
How you doing, Josh?
You feel pressure?
Yeah.
[Angie]
Hang on.
Ow!
[Nurse]
Can you take a deep breath in?
[Angie]
You okay?
[Nurse]
Deep breath in.
Ow!
Oh.
[Angie]
Oh, he'Ős gorgeous, Mackey!
[Man]
All right, it'Ős a boy.
Congratulations!
[Angie]
It is a boy!
[baby crying]
He'Ős beautiful, isn'Őt he, Josh?
♪ You might know ♪
♪ But if you don'’t ♪
♪ Then it'’s all right ♪
♪ You have a place inside ♪
♪ And you know that it'’s good ♪
♪ In your life ♪
♪ When your heart feels right ♪
Yay, Mackey.
You did it.
[laughter]
[Whitney]
Right now?
[Man]
Is he a football player
or a bullrider?
Bullrider.
For sure.
[chime dings]
[Angie]
Ain'Őt he cute?
He'Ős dandy.
It will get better.
You just got to get up
and walk around slow
when you can.
It hurts so bad.
I'Őm in a lot of pain
and can'Őt do much.
But if Josh takes it easy,
his doctor said it was okay
to take his neck brace off.
And after a few days,
I was feeling better,
and it was finally
time to go home.
[Angie]
Uh-oh.
Okay, you ready for this?
Whoo.
Yeah.
[Mackenzie]
Josh is going to stay over
to help with the baby.
And since it'Ős gonna take
some time for me to heal,
my mom is taking
this week off from work.
Yay, Gannon, you'Őre home.
Can you get him out of there,
Josh?
[Whitney]
Hey!
[laughs]
[Angie]
He needs a bigger one.
Oh, he'Ős gonna cry.
My boy.
[Angie]
Good job, Mackey.
[baby crying]
[Mackenzie]
You little...
I have a feeling he'Ős
gonna be fussy all night.
[baby crying]
Where'Ős a diaper?
[Mackenzie]
Is he poopy?
Yeah.
[Mackenzie]
He peed all over
his other onesie.
[Angie]
Ah.
Did you pee on your onesie?
[laughs]
Good night, guys.
I'Őm in the other room
if you need me.
[crickets chirping]
[baby crying]
[Mackenzie]
Gosh.
[groans]
Well, I just can'Őt
get him to latch on.
[baby crying]
Ugh.
I just fed him.
Shh.
That'Ős horrible.
Come smell this.
[baby crying]
and tips on how to take
control, at:
[baby crying]
[Mackenzie]
These past few weeks
have been exhausting,
especially since my mom
has had to go back to work.
What'Ős the matter?
Because money is tight,
Josh is at his house today,
figuring out what old rodeo gear
he can sell.
Since we can'Őt afford day care
when I go back
to school in a few days,
the plan is for Josh to watch
Gannon during the day,
and I'Őll get him at night.
Hey, you want to do
my homework for me?
You want to help me
with my homework?
I'Őm going back to school today,
and although Josh
still might need neck surgery,
he'Ős feeling better
and is able to watch Gannon.
Mackey, hi.
Hi, I missed you.
I missed you too.
How does it feel
being back at school?
Um, I miss my baby.
Oh.
Where is Gannon?
He'Ős at his dad'Ős.
You'Őre always so busy.
I never get to see you at all.
I know.
We went from
hanging out every day to--
Yeah.
But then again, you didn'Őt have
a baby on your side every time.
I know.
I have so much making up to do.
[Victoria]
Yeah.
And you don'Őt have any time
at home to do homework, huh?
[Mackenzie]
I know.
I'Őm learning how to live
on no sleep.
That'Ős fun.
No, not really.
Are you ready
for Tumbling Tuesday?
[Victoria]
Yeah.
I'Őll be starting out slow.
Yeah, you'Őre on my level now.
Ha-ha.
[laughs]
Oh, okay.
I'Őm losing it.
[Angie]
Oh, God.
Bye.
[Mackenzie]
Oh, gosh.
I'Őm excited to make
a total fool out of myself.
[Victoria]
You are not.
And what are you
gonna do with Gannon
while we'Őre tumbling?
I don'Őt know.
I'Őm just gonna sit him there,
and if he cries, I'Őll feed him.
Really?
Ew.
Whoo!
What is that?
[laughs]
Gannon, did you poop?
[Victoria]
Oh, that was bad.
[Mackenzie]
Ready to tumble?
[Victoria]
Oh, yeah.
Whoo!
[Matt]
Much better on the layout.
Hi.
Hey.
How are you?
[Mackenzie]
Good.
Who is this?
He'Ős gonna stunt.
He'Ős smiling.
[Matt]
That'Ős a smile?
That'Ős not a smile, Mackenzie.
[laughter]
All right, stretch out.
Let'Ős get started.
We need to stretch a lot.
Oh, my gosh.
[Matt]
This is gonna be rough.
Oh, my.
I bet that one
felt good.
[Mackenzie]
I can'Őt do this.
[Matt]
Okay, tossings.
Just if--
If you see blood, stop.
Wait.
Oh, god.
[Matt]
One, two.
Ah!
You'Őre slow on bottom.
Right over my nose.
Okay, you got this.
Give me a good jump.
One, two.
Oh, sorry!Mackey.
I did that.
[Victoria]
It'Ős different seeing her
not being able
to just throw
whatever she wanted.
Mm-hmm.
We got to hit one.
We do?
[Matt]
Yeah.
Okay.
Squeeze tight, okay?
One, two.
Bend your knees.
Ah!
Buck up, Mackey.
[Mackenzie]
Oh, my gosh, Matt.
I just embarrassed myself.
Oh, whatever.
[sighs]
I thought it would be easier,
but that hurt.
Well, I mean, you just got
to take it slow and get back in.
From the sounds of it,
probably ought
to call it a night.
[baby crying]
He'Ős mad.
[Matt]
It was kind of a short
practice, wasn'Őt it?
Yeah.
It'Ős going to be tough
to get back into tumbling,
but I know with Josh'Ős injury,
he'Ős missing riding too.
So tonight, Josh'Ős mom
is babysitting Gannon
so we can all go out
and see the rodeo.
Bye.
[Mackenzie]
Thanks for watching him.
[Announcer]
All right,
ladies and gentlemen...
[audience cheering]
[Victoria]
Do you miss it?
[Lane]
Does this look
dangerous to you?
[Mackenzie]
Yes.
[Lane]
Yeah, it looks dangerous.
Did you seriously
just say that?
[Victoria]
Where is he going?
He'Őll ask him
to ride a bull.
Man.
You'Őre asking
to ride?
I want to ask one, yeah.
Please don'Őt.
No way.
That'Ős not funny.
Tell him, "No."
[Lane]
Come on, man.
You can'Őt do this.
[Victoria]
You just got done
with all your...
[Lane]
Yeah,
you ain'Őt even released yet.
[Victoria]
Semi stuff that happened.
Think about it.
[horn honks]
Think about what you'Őre
doing right now, Josh.
It ain'Őt a good idea.
Yeah, I know.
That'Ős your problem.
[Victoria]
Like,
what if something does happen?
[Lane]
Yeah.
Think about you hitting
the ground over there, Josh.
Think about you taking a horn.
Please don'Őt do this, Josh.
Please.
Dude, I just think
it'Ős pointless
to come all this way,
and nothing [bleep] happen.
[Victoria]
That doesn'Őt me you have to,
though.
[bleep].
It'Ős not life or death, man.
Man, do not get on one tonight.
[Announcer]
Don'Őt go away.
This episode
of "16 and Pregnant"
continues right now.
[Mackenzie]
Josh, everyone'Ős leaving.
Let'Ős just go.
[Josh]
Yeah.
[Mackenzie]
I can'Őt believe Josh actually
wanted to ride tonight.
The thought of him getting back
into rodeos despite his injuries
is keeping me up all night
and really making me mad.
[line rings]
[Josh]
Hello?
Are you going to stop, Josh?
Do you think it'Ős gonna
make me like you more?
I mean, what--
Do you think it'Ős accomplishing
anything, other than hurting me?
I just want you to grow up,
and I just want you to stop,
and you won'Őt.
And you won'Őt,
and it'Ős gonna ruin us.
Seriously?
I'Őll be at your house soon.
How about you sacrifice riding
and rodeos for me and Gannon?
What?
It might not work out, Josh.
If your plan is to stay with me,
you can'Őt ride anymore.
What'Ős your plan?
Are you gonna quit?
Yeah.
[Josh]
It'Ős gonna be hard,
but I know Gannon comes first.
After all his concussions,
I would think he would realize
that he needs to stop
bull riding for the baby.
If someone would have told me
when I was little,
"You'Őre gonna be with a cowboy,
"and you'Őre gonna have
a baby with him at 16,"
I would have been like,
"No, no, I'Őm not.
"I'Őm gonna have fun
the rest of my life.
"I'Őm gonna cheer and be crazy
and hang out with my friends.
"That'Ős not gonna happen."
Mm, that was gross.
[laughter]
But now that I have a baby,
I don'Őt really get
much girl time anymore,
because my life revolves
around the baby.
It'Ős been tough,
but his mom and my mom
have been great to us,
so we'Őve both been really,
really lucky.
[Brad]
Put some clothes
on that boy.
[Mackenzie]
We'Őre getting ready
to give him a bath.
I don'Őt know what me and Josh
would have done by ourselves.
You know, we would still like
to have a baby
and still be able
to do our dreams.
[Brad]
Oh, cool.
[Angie]
Whoa.
You think you'Őre gonna
be able to do that again?
That was so cool.
But we'Őre kind of realizing
that we can'Őt just run off,
'Őcause we are a family,
and family does come first.
So you gonna watch him
while I tumble?
[Josh]
Yeah, that'Ős fine.
You better be safe.
I don'Őt want you
to break your neck.
[sighs]
[laughs]
[chime dings]