>> [gasping and laughing]
THERE YOU GO, KYARA.
>> I'M SAVON.
I LIVE IN MARIETTA, GEORGIA,
A SUBURB OUTSIDE OF ATLANTA,
WITH MY AUNT LADONNA AND COUSINS
KAHLEM AND PHILIP.
I'M A JUNIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL, AND
I'VE ALWAYS GOTTEN GOOD GRADES.
BUT PLAYING BASKETBALL
IS WHAT KEEPS ME FOCUSED,
AND I'M HOPING TO GO TO COLLEGE
ON A SPORTS SCHOLARSHIP.
MY DREAM FOR THE FUTURE IS
TO BECOME A SINGER/SONGWRITER...
* THEY WILL SAVE US
AND TO EVENTUALLY GET MARRIED
AND HAVE A FAMILY.
I MET MY BOYFRIEND, MAUWI,
ON THE BASKETBALL COURT,
AND WE HIT IT OFF RIGHT AWAY.
BUT WE WERE FRIENDS FOR A WHILE
BEFORE WE BECAME A COUPLE.
DON'T EMBARRASS YOURSELF NOW.
>> UGH.
>> OOH, YOU DID IT ANYWAYS.
HE JUST STARTED COLLEGE
AND IS VERY SUPPORTIVE OF ME
AND MY DREAMS.
WE HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP,
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY WITH HIM.
BUT BEFORE I STARTED DATING
MAUWI, I FELL FOR
THIS OTHER GUY, ELI.
AFTER WE HOOKED UP A COUPLE
TIMES, HE FORGOT ALL ABOUT ME.
HAVE A SEAT, SIR.
>> NO, GIVE ME A HUG.
>> NO, I DON'T WANT A HUG.
GET OFF ME.
NOW THAT I'M WITH MAUWI,
I WISH I COULD FORGET
ABOUT ELI TOO, BUT
THAT'S GOING TO BE IMPOSSIBLE,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT
WITH ELI'S BABY.
I'M REALLY GRATEFUL TO BE
LIVING WITH MY AUNT LADONNA.
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S DISAPPOINTED
ABOUT MY PREGNANCY,
I KNOW I CAN DEPEND ON HER
TO HELP ME THROUGH IT ALL.
IS THIS IT?
>> I MEAN, IT'S A LOT OF--
YOU GOT A LOT OF OPTIONS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "IS THIS IT?"
[both laugh]
>> IT'S TOO PAGES.
>> OH.
>> YOU REMEMBER THE DAY YOU
FOUND OUT YOU WAS PREGNANT?
>> YEAH.
THE FIRST THING THAT POPPED IN
MY HEAD WHEN I FOUND OUT,
I WAS LIKE,
"I'M NOT KEEPING IT."
'CAUSE I ALREADY KNEW IT WAS
ELI'S, SO I WAS LIKE,
"WHY KEEP IT?"
IT'S LIKE, "WHY HAVE A BABY BY A
GUY THAT DOESN'T EVEN LIKE ME?"
LIKE--[laughs]
LIKE, THIS IS--
>> I MEAN, HE'S CRAZY.
>> THAT'S JUST POINTLESS.
HE DOESN'T EVEN WANT ME, SO--
>> SO YOU DIDN'T HAVE
NO KIND OF ATTACHMENT?
>> NO.
I HAD SOME THOUGHTS ABOUT
ABORTION AT ONE POINT.
THEN I WAS LIKE, "THE MONEY."
>> I DON'T BELIEVE IN ABORTIONS,
BUT I THINK IT'S WORSE TO BRING
A CHILD INTO THE WORLD THAT YOU
CAN'T AFFORD TO FEED.
>> RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S ALL
GONNA WORK OUT, BUT...
I DON'T KNOW.
I KNOW--I JUST ADDED EXTRA
RESPONSIBILITY FOR MYSELF.
AND I WISH THAT I WOULD HAVE
GAVE MAUWI A CHANCE BEFORE I
TRIED TO BE REBELLIOUS AND DO
THE TOTAL OPPOSITE.
I WISH I WOULD HAVE JUST SAT
DOWN AND REALIZED THAT MAUWI WAS
THE RIGHT PERSON FOR ME TO BE
WITH INSTEAD OF TRYING
TO BE WITH SOMEBODY
WHO HAS NO INTEREST IN ME.
IT'S JUST HARD TO GET PAST
THE FACT THAT I'M ABOUT TO
HAVE A BABY.
LIKE, I STILL HAVEN'T
GOT OVER THAT.
I WASN'T SURE IF MAUWI AND I
WERE GONNA LAST ONCE I FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT WITH BABY EDEN.
I WAS SO DISAPPOINTED IN MYSELF
AND WAS SURE HE WOULD BREAK UP
WITH ME, ESPECIALLY BECAUSE
WE HADN'T HAD SEX YET.
AND I TOLD HIM I DIDN'T WANT TO
NOW THAT I WAS PREGNANT
WITH SOMEONE ELSE'S BABY.
BUT MAUWI SAID HE COULD WAIT,
AND WE DECIDED TO STAY TOGETHER.
I'M GLAD HE STUCK BY ME.
WELL, YOU CAN FEEL HICCUPS
RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
SEE?
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S LIKE--
[mimics hiccupping ]
LIKE, EVERY TWO SECONDS.
I'M LIKE, "OH, MY GOSH."
WHEN YOU FIRST MET ME,
WHAT WAS YOUR IMPRESSION LIKE?
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE CUTE.
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO JUST,
YOU KNOW, JUST STRAIGHT UP
AND JUST START TALKING TO YOU.
TRYING TO, YOU KNOW,
TAKE MY TIME WITH IT.
>> IT'S ALMOST BEEN,
LIKE, A YEAR.
I NEVER THOUGHT OF MYSELF
THIS YOUNG IN THIS POSITION.
LIKE, NOW I HAVE TO, LIKE,
PUT OFF COLLEGE.
I PUT OFF ALL THE OPPORTUNITIES
THAT I HAD, YOU KNOW, DEALING
WITH MUSIC AND BAND AND
BASKETBALL AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
LIKE, NONE OF THOSE
OPPORTUNITIES ARE OPEN.
>> OPEN, YEAH.
>> NO, I MISS PLAYING BASKETBALL
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, THE THRILL
LIKE, WHEN YOU MAKE A SHOT,
YOU LIKE, "OH, SNAP."
>> YOU REMEMBER WHEN YOU TOLD
ME, LIKE--LIKE, HOW YOU TOLD ME?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I DIDN'T REALLY
KNOW ANY OTHER WAY TO TELL YOU
OTHER THAN JUST COME OUT
AND BE 100% HONEST.
I MEAN, THE AWKWARD SILENCE
WAS JUST LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
>> HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO REACT
TO THAT, LIKE, "OH, YEAH."
I WON'T SAY IT TOOK AWAY
OPPORTUNITIES, BUT IT, LIKE,
IT TOOK US DOWN ANOTHER PATH
INSTEAD OF GOING DOWN THE PATH
THAT WE COULD HAVE WENT DOWN.
>> OR EASIER ROAD.
>> YEAH, EASIER PATH.
>> NOW I'M GONNA HAVE TO GO...
>> NOW IT'S LIKE, YEAH.
>> ALL THE WAY BACK AROUND--
>> EXACTLY.
NOW IT'S, LIKE, CRUNCH TIME.
AND, LIKE, LEAVING WASN'T
JUST AN OPTION.
IT WASN'T LIKE YOU CHEATED ON ME
OR YOU DID SOMETHING CRAZY.
ALL THIS HAPPENED
BEFORE WE WERE DATING.
SO I COULDN'T JUST UP AND LEAVE
JUST 'CAUSE YOU FOUND OUT
THAT YOU WERE PREGNANT.
>> RIGHT.
>> I ALREADY TOLD YOU, YOU KNOW,
I WANT TO HELP OUT AS MUCH AS
I POSSIBLY CAN OR WHATEVER.
WELL, YOU KNOW I STARTED SCHOOL
LAST WEEK.
>> OH.
>> SO SCHOOL, FOOTBALL.
YOU KNOW I HAVE TO DO
MY TRAINING.
AND I GOT TO WORK AT THE JOB
OR WHATEVER.
>> SO THAT'S A LOT.
>> I KNOW.
I'LL BE BACK, YOU KNOW, FOR JUST
ABOUT EVERY WEEKEND 'CAUSE I'M
GONNA HAVE MY CAR OR WHATEVER.
AND I'LL JUST--I'LL COME BACK
AND VISIT JUST ABOUT
EVERY WEEKEND.
>> IT WON'T BE--
I MEAN, I CAN HANDLE IT.
IT WON'T BE THAT BAD.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S AWKWARD BEING
PREGNANT WITH SOMEONE ELSE'S
BABY, I REALLY LIKE MAUWI
AND THINK WE'RE GONNA BE ABLE
TO GET THROUGH THIS.
[doorbell rings]
>> HEY THERE.
>> HEY.
OH, MY GOD.
>> SAVON.
>> YOU CAN HAVE THIS ONE RIGHT
HERE AND THEN MISMATCH 'EM.
>> I GUESS YOU GET STARTED ON
ONE FINGER.
I GOT YOU, SEE.
>> YOU START DOING THE OTHER
THEN.
>> WHAT Y'ALL THINK ABOUT IT?
>> WHAT I KNOW OF HIM
IS, YOU KNOW, AROUND SCHOOL,
HE WAS, LIKE, THE "LADIES MAN."
>> WELL, I DON'T--
I JUST DON'T LIKE HIM.
HE--
>> YEAH, I DON'T LIKE HIM.
HE TREATED YOU LIKE
YOU WAS JUST SOME TRASH.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND I DON'T LIKE THAT.
YOU DON'T DISRESPECT--
>> BUT THAT'S HOW
HE TREAT ALL GIRLS.
'CAUSE HE DON'T KNOW NO BETTER.
LIKE, HE HAS NO MORALS.
>> WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU'VE SEEN HIM?
>> THE LAST TIME I SEEN HIM--
OH, MY--THAT WAS A WHILE AGO.
>> HAS HE CALLED OR TEXT YOU?
>> NO, HE DON'T CALL.
HE DON'T TEXT.
HE DON'T CARE.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY TO YOU WHEN
YOU TOLD HIM YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> HE WAS BASICALLY LIKE,
"ABORTION."
AND I WAS LIKE, "YOU DON'T TELL
ME WHAT I CAN AND CANNOT DO."
HE'S A HORRIBLE PERSON.
LIKE, HE'S A LOSER.
HE DOES HAVE OTHER KIDS.
THAT HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING FOR.
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW HOW
I ENDED UP EVEN LIKING HIM.
LIKE, REALLY?
>> SO HE'S NOT LIKE, AN EX.
HE'S LIKE A "WHY?"
LIKE, "WHY DID I TALK TO YOU?"
>> YEAH.
[laughter]
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT WASN'T MAUWI'S?
WASN'T YOU DATING HIM, LIKE--
>> YEAH, I MEAN, BUT WE
WEREN'T--WE JUST STARTED DATING
PROBABLY, LIKE, TWO WEEKS BEFORE
I TOLD HIM, SO WE WEREN'T
INTIMATE OR NOTHING LIKE THAT.
BUT IT'S REALLY AWKWARD
FOR ME BEING PREGNANT
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE'S BABY.
HE CAN'T REALLY RELATE.
>> YOU TALK TO MAUWI ABOUT
HOW EVERYTHING WOULD BE
AFTER YOU HAVE THE BABY?
>> OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, WE TOUCHED BASE WITH IT,
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN, LIKE,
A SERIOUS, SERIOUS DISCUSSION.
WELL, I REALLY DON'T FEEL LIKE
OUR RELATIONSHIP'S GONNA CHANGE,
AND WE JUST HAVE TO DEAL WITH IT
THE BEST WAY.
[phone buzzes]
THE FURTHER ALONG I GET IN MY
PREGNANCY, THE HARDER IT IS
TO GET UP FOR SCHOOL
IN THE MORNINGS.
NOTHING FITS ANYMORE, SO GETTING
READY IS NOT FUN AT ALL.
SHOULD I WEAR THESE LEGGINGS
OR SHOULD I WEAR JEANS?
>> WHY DON'T YOU JUST WEAR
WHAT YOU GOT ON?
YOU ALWAYS WEAR SWEATPANTS.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
YOU DON'T HAVE
THAT MANY OPTIONS.
>> SO TODAY'S, LIKE,
MY LAST DAY.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
I'MA GO TALK TO MY GUIDANCE
COUNSELOR, YOU KNOW, ABOUT THOSE
ONLINE CLASSES AND STUFF.
SO I'LL JUST BE AT HOME ALL DAY
EATING, LIKE, NOODLES AND STUFF.
[both laugh]
>> WHAT'S UP, SAVON?
>> HEY.
>> OH, SAVON HERE?
>> both: YEAH.
>> HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> BORING.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> WELL, TODAY WAS MY LAST DAY,
SO I GET TO START
MY ONLINE CLASSES.
YEAH, 'CAUSE I'M SMART.
>> YEAH, HOW YOU GONNA DO ONLINE
COURSES WHEN THIS BABY BORN?
>> I MEAN--
>> YOU GONNA--
YOU DISCIPLINED ENOUGH?
>> YEAH, I'LL GET UP LIKE
REGULAR SCHOOL HOURS
AND WORK ONLINE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DON'T GET UP WHEN YOU
AT HOME AND DO ANYTHING.
>> I MEAN--
>> HOW YOU GONNA GET UP REGULAR
SCHOOL HOURS AND WORK?
>> NO MORE PARTYING FOR YOU.
>> I NEVER PARTIED.
>> THERE GOES YOUR PARTY TIME.
>> NO MORE HANGING OUT,
NONE OF THAT.
YOU HUNG ALL THAT UP.
>> I THINK I CAN--
I THINK I CAN DO IT.
>> BUT YOU SPENT TOO MUCH OF
YOUR TIME BULL[bleep].
>> SO I KNOW I NEED TO
PASS MY CLASSES AND GRADUATE
AND GET A JOB
AND THINGS THAT I NEED TO DO.
>> YOU GOT TO PUT ON
THE BIG GIRL PANTIES.
I'M NOT PLANNING ON BABYSITTING.
I'M NOT BUYING DIAPERS.
I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING.
I'M NOT TRANSPORTING
FROM DAY CARE BACK AND FORTH.
I MEAN, YOU--
WE IN THE SAME HOUSE.
I'LL HELP YOU FROM TIME TO TIME,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA
RAISE YOUR BABY.
YOU GOT TO REALLY STEP INTO
WOMANHOOD NOW.
>> I'M DUE IN FOUR WEEKS,
AND THINGS ARE MOVING QUICKLY.
WITHOUT MY AUNT'S HELP AND MAUWI
BEING AWAY AT SCHOOL,
I'M WORRIED THAT RAISING
THIS BABY IS GONNA BE HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT.
SEEING IT MAKES ME
110% MORE NERVOUS.
>> MAKES IT A LITTLE MORE REAL,
RIGHT?
>> I'M TRYING TO PREPARE FOR
EDEN AND STAY ON TOP OF MY
SCHOOLWORK, BUT I NEED TO
FIND A JOB TOO.
>> I MEAN, IF I WAS YOU GOING
IN TO A JOB, I WOULDN'T TELL 'EM
I'M PREGNANT.
'CAUSE TO MOST PEOPLE, IT'S
GONNA TELL THEM, OH, YOU GONNA
HAVE ISSUES WITH BABYSITTING.
IT'S TOO MUCH RESPONSIBILITY;
YOU WON'T BE RELIABLE.
SO I WOULDN'T BRING THAT UP
IN THE CONVERSATION AT ALL.
>> SHOULD I BUTTON IT?
>> YEAH.
I THINK YOU'LL GET BY
IF YOU KEEP YOUR COAT ON.
YOU JUST LOOK A LITTLE CHUNKY.
BUT YOU CAN'T REALLY TELL
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
YEAH, YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHTY, THEN. LET'S GO.
>> HI.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU GUYS WERE HIRING.
>> OKAY, I GOT TO
GET APPLICATION.
>> OKAY.
>> RIGHT?
>> HAVE YOU WORKED IN
RESTAURANTS BEFORE?
>> I HAVE NOT, BUT I DO HAVE A
LITTLE EXPERIENCE WITH WORKING.
>> OKAY.
>> HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
>> HI, I WAS TRYING TO SEE, YOU
KNOW, IF YOU GUYS WERE HIRING,
AND IF SO, I CAN FILL OUT
AN APPLICATION.
>> WHAT KIND OF A JOB
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
>> UM...
SOMETHING RELAXING.
>> PLAY ANY MUSICAL INSTRUMENT?
>> UM, I CURRENTLY PLAY, LIKE,
THE PIANO AND GUITAR AND DRUMS.
>> GUITAR. MM-HMM.
BUT I CAN GIVE YOU
AN APPLICATION TODAY.
YOU JUST FILL IT OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> OKAY.
[engine turns over]
>> HOW DID THE LAST SHOP FEEL?
>> UM, IT WAS A BETTER
ENVIRONMENT, LIKE, IT WAS MORE
OF A STORE THAT I WOULD BE INTO.
AND I'M JUST GONNA HOPE
FOR THE BEST, I GUESS.
>> GOOD YOU'RE TRYING, BUT I'M
NOT GONNA SIT THERE AND TELL YOU
I'M EXCITED.
I'LL BE HAPPY WHEN YOU GET ONE.
[laughs]
I'M JUST BEING HONEST.
THIS IS WHAT I'LL DO
WHEN YOU SAY, "AUNTIE,
I GOT A JOB."
I'LL DO THAT.
>> WITH SO MUCH ON MY MIND,
IT'S HARD TO CONCENTRATE.
AND I'M NOT GETTING MUCH
SCHOOLWORK DONE.
>> I WON'T SPILL.
>> NUH-UH.
I'M SCARED OF HEIGHTS.
I CAN'T SIT RIGHT HERE.
MM-MM.
NO.
I'VE BEEN PREGNANT FOR A YEAR.
I DON'T CARE WHAT NOBODY SAY.
I'VE BEEN PREGNANT FOREVER.
I DON'T SEE HOW PEOPLE GET
PREGNANT AND JUST HAVE, LIKE,
SIX, SEVEN KIDS.
THAT IS YOUR LIFE.
YOU IS OLD AND DRIED UP
AFTER THEM KIDS.
>> WELL, ARE YOU READY
SINCE IT'S SO CLOSE?
YOU DON'T HAVE
THAT MUCH TIME LEFT.
>> I MEAN, BASICALLY I JUST
GOT TO GET EVERYTHING TOGETHER
AND MENTALLY PREPARE MYSELF.
BUT THEN I'M JUST LIKE,
"I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING."
LIKE, I DON'T EVEN
HAVE AN OVERNIGHT BAG.
>> LIKE, I'M NOT READY FOR THIS.
>> [laughs]
LIKE, I'M JUST LIKE,
"I REALLY HOPE THIS BABY
DON'T COME TONIGHT,
'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE NOTHING."
SO WHENEVER MY AUNT IS LIKE,
YOU KNOW, I GUESS DRILLING ME
ABOUT WHAT I NEED TO DO,
IT MAKES ME REALIZE
THAT I'VE BEEN SITTING AROUND
NOT DOING WHAT I NEEDED TO DO.
>> HOW HAVE THINGS BEEN?
WITH YOU AND MAUWI?
>> WELL, HE JUST STARTED
BACK AT SCHOOL, SO WE ONLY
SEE EACH OTHER ON WEEKENDS,
BUT OTHER THAN THAT, I MEAN,
THINGS ARE GOOD.
I'M ABOUT TO SEE HIM
LATER TODAY.
>> SO HOW DO YOU THINK IT'S
GONNA BE LIKE AFTER THE BABY?
>> I MEAN, AFTER THE BABY,
BECAUSE I'LL BE ABLE TO MOVE
AROUND AND BE MORE OF MYSELF,
YOU KNOW.
THEN I THINK THINGS
WILL GO BACK TO NORMAL, BUT IT'S
NOT GONNA BE COMPLETELY NORMAL,
'CAUSE I HAVE A BABY.
I HATE SEX.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS.
[laughter]
>> DID YOU AND MAUWI
EVER HAVE SEX?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GONNA TAKE ME A WHILE TO
GET BACK AROUND TO IT, BECAUSE
I'VE HAD SUCH A HORRIBLE
EXPERIENCE WITH SEX.
FIRST OF ALL, WITH THE WRONG
PERSON, AND THEN YOU GET A BABY
OUT OF IT.
YOU JUST KIND OF LIKE, "THAT IS
THE LAST THING ON MY MIND.
I DO NOT CARE."
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, IF I NEVER HAVE SEX
AGAIN, I WOULDN'T CARE.
[both laugh]
I REALLY WOULDN'T.
>> YOU THINK MAUWI WOULD, LIKE,
FEEL LIKE YOU'RE BLAMING HIM OR
PUNISHING HIM FOR WHAT ELI DID?
>> YEAH.
IN SOME SENSE,
I FEEL LIKE HE COULD--
HE COULD TAKE IT THAT WAY.
BUT IT'LL BE A WHILE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND IF HE'S WILLING TO, LIKE,
WAIT THAT TIME,
THEN IT'S UP TO HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> MAUWI IS HOME THIS WEEKEND,
SO MY AUNT WANTS TO TALK TO US
ABOUT OUR PLAN
FOR WHEN EDEN GETS HERE.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WHAT'S GOOD, BRO?
>> both: HEY, MAUWI.
>> HOW Y'ALL DOING?
>> GOOD.
YOU WANT SOMETHING TO EAT?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, OKAY.
WE JUST ABOUT TO HAVE DINNER.
>> OF COURSE.
EVERY TIME YOU COME OVER HERE,
YOU'RE ALWAYS EATING SOMETHING.
>> SO?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT?
>> MY FOOD.
>> YOU CAN'T TALK.
>> YOUR FOOD.
DOESN'T EVEN MATTER.
>> HI, BIG BELLY.
>> OKAY.
>> SO, MAUWI, I REALLY
APPRECIATE YOU STEPPING UP
AND KIND OF HELPING OUT, WHICH--
I DON'T HAVE ANY EXPECTATIONS,
SINCE, YOU KNOW, BIOLOGICALLY,
YOU'RE NOT THE FATHER.
BUT HOW DO YOU SEE YOURSELF,
YOU KNOW, KIND OF--WHAT ROLE
DO YOU THINK YOU'LL HAVE
IN THE CHILD'S LIFE?
>> YEAH, I KIND OF
THOUGHT ABOUT IT, LIKE...
[clears throat]
I WAS REALLY GONNA
TAKE IT DAY-BY-DAY, BECAUSE
I KNOW THAT ONCE THE BABY HERE,
OF COURSE, WE GONNA EVENTUALLY
JOIN IT--LIKE, MAKE THAT BOND,
'CAUSE I'MA BE AROUND SO MUCH.
AND LIKE--
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE, FROM Y'ALL'S PERSPECTIVE,
LIKE, DO YOU THINK OUR
RELATIONSHIP IS GONNA CHANGE,
LIKE, WHEN THE BABY GETS HERE
OR HOW IS IT GONNA CHANGE?
>> I MEAN, I WOULD SAY IT SHOULD
DRAW Y'ALL CLOSER TOGETHER, BUT
I BELIEVE THE LEVEL OF STRESS
CAN EITHER MAKE OR BREAK YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> NOT HAVING THE BABY HERE,
YOU CAN SAY ONE THING, BUT WHEN
THAT BABY COMES, IT'S GONNA BE
A WHOLE NOTHER SITUATION.
SO I CAN SEE THAT YOU TRYING
TO GIVE YOUR ALL,
BUT YOUR PLATE IS FULL.
REALISTICALLY SPEAKING, DO YOU
REALLY THINK THAT YOU CAN HANDLE
WHAT'S ABOUT--'CAUSE YOU NEVER
RAISED YOUR OWN CHILD BEFORE.
>> THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
>> SIX MONTHS FROM NOW,
DO YOU GUYS HAVE A PLAN?
>> NO.
I CAN HONESTLY SAY WE DON'T HAVE
A--I MEAN, WE PROBABLY TALKED
ABOUT IT, BUT WE DON'T HAVE,
LIKE, A CONCRETE PLAN.
>> I MEAN, I BELIEVE THAT,
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS ARE LIVING
IN A FANTASY WORLD.
>> MAN, THAT'S FOR REAL.
>> AND IF YOU'RE NOT STRONG
ENOUGH, THEN I DON'T THINK--
I DON'T THINK
YOU GUYS WILL LAST.
>> I HOPE MY RELATIONSHIP WITH
MAUWI WILL STAY STRONG,
BUT FOR NOW,
HE'S AWAY AT SCHOOL AGAIN.
>> I GUESS WE GOT TO GET
EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH.
SINCE MY AUNT UNDERSTANDS I
PROBABLY WON'T GET A JOB UNTIL
AFTER I GIVE BIRTH, SHE'S
WILLING TO HELP ME OUT A LITTLE
UNTIL THEN.
>> I WONDER WHERE THEIR
BABY SHOWER DEPARTMENT--
OH, COME ON, PARTY SUPPLIES.
I'M GONNA LOAN YOU THIS MONEY.
I WANT MY MONEY BACK.
>> OKAY.
>> HERE YOU GO.
SO HOW ABOUT THIS BLUE?
THAT BLUE IS BETTER.
>> WHAT ABOUT YELLOW AND BLUE?
>> WHY YOU WANT TO DO YELLOW?
>> YELLOW'S A CUTE COLOR.
>> I JUST DON'T THINK YELLOW'S
A COLOR FOR A BOY.
>> YOU DON'T THINK SO?
>> NO.
I WOULD NEVER LIKE TO DATE A MAN
THAT GOT ON YELLOW.
NO.
YEAH, I THINK
WE'RE IN THE WRONG SECTION.
OH, MY GOD, SAVON.
WE HAVE TO DO THIS.
THIS'LL HELP YOUR BABY COME.
>> OH, LORD.
I DON'T KNOW.
I KIND OF GOT ACID REFLUX.
>> HERE.
>> DON'T HURT YOURSELF.
>> LET ME SEE IF
I CAN STILL HULA HOOP.
OH, NO.
[both laugh]
YOU GOT TO PUT IT
ABOVE THE BABY.
THERE YOU GO.
>> [grunts]
[both laugh]
I FEEL HANDICAPPED.
THIS NEVER USED TO BE THAT HARD.
>> LET ME SEE IF
I CAN STILL HULA HOOP.
>> [laughs]
>> I DID IT LONGER THAN YOU DID.
[upbeat pop music]
>> * HEY, HEY!
* HEY, HEY!
*
>> * LISTEN
>> SAY "WEENIES."
[laughter]
>> * LIKE A DOOR
* THAT'S HARD TO OPEN *
>> EVERYBODY GOT TO GRAB
AS MANY PIECES AS THEY THINK
SAVON BELLY IS.
DID YOU COUNT YOUR--
MINE COULD HAVE BEEN IT.
>> OH!
>> LET'S SEE.
>> YOU BIG.
>> ONE OFF.
>> IT'S TEN.
TEN GONNA BE--WHO GOT TEN?
SHE WON.
>> YOU SO BIG.
>> THE PRIZE IS...
>> WHAT IS THE PRIZE?
>> AN EXTRA CUP OF ICE.
[laughter]
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> DANG, DO THAT SUCK TO WIN.
[laughter]
>> I'M BEHIND ON ALL MY
ASSIGNMENTS, AND MY GRADES ARE
STARTING TO SUFFER.
I SHOULD TRY TO CATCH UP, BUT
MAUWI'S FINALLY HOME FOR THE
WEEKEND, SO I'D RATHER HANG OUT
WITH HIM.
>> YOU READY TO LOSE, THOUGH?
>> OKAY.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> CAN WE GET
A LITTLE KID'S BALL?
[laughs]
>> GET THE LITTLE THING
RIGHT THERE.
>> [laughs]
>> IT'S GONNA BE A LONG GAME.
>> [laughing]
>> UH! UH!
>> MAN!
>> GUTTER BALL.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I SUCK AT THIS.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> IT'S NOT OKAY.
YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
YOU MIGHT COME BACK.
>> OKAY. PROMISE?
>> YEAH, I PROMISE.
[chime dings]
>> OF COURSE I'M REALLY
ATTRACTED TO MAUWI, BUT BEING
PREGNANT WITH SOMEONE ELSE'S
BABY IS SO AWKWARD FOR ME
THAT I ALWAYS STOP THINGS
FROM GOING TOO FAR.
BUT LAST NIGHT, IT STARTED
TO CAUSE MORE TENSION.
AFTER THIS EXPERIENCE, I DON'T
EVEN WANT TO HAVE NO MORE KIDS.
>> I FEEL YOU.
>> I'M PUTTING ON
A CHASTITY BELT.
>> YOU'RE NOT TRYING TO HAVE SEX
OR NOTHING AFTER HE POPS OUT?
>> NOPE. NOPE.
>> EVER?
>> I'M TRAUMATIZED.
>> TRAUMATIZED.
>> AFTER HAVING A BABY, LIKE,
WITH SOMEBODY THAT YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW, I DON'T--
>> BUT I'M NOT HIM.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW ME.
IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT SCENARIO.
>> IT'S GONNA TAKE TIME FOR ME
TO GET OVER THAT.
>> MAN, THAT'S--THAT'S
EXTREMELY FRUSTRATING.
'CAUSE, LIKE, I'M IN COLLEGE.
I'M PLAYING FOOTBALL.
AND WHEN I GO OUT, OF COURSE,
FEMALES TRY TO HOOK UP WITH ME
AND DO STUFF WITH ME.
BUT IT'S LIKE,
"OH, I GOT A GIRLFRIEND.
I CAN'T DEAL.
I GOT A GIRL BACK HOME.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER, BUT I'M
GOING TO SEE MY GIRL.
EVERYTHING I WANT TO DO,
I'MA DO IT WITH HER."
I CAN'T SAY THAT.
>> OH.
I DON'T--[laughs]
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO BE
DISCUSSING STUFF LIKE THIS.
I NEED A DAMN CAR SEAT.
I MEAN, IT MIGHT BE FRUSTRATING
FOR YOU, BUT--
>> YEAH, IT'S FRUSTRATING
FOR ME.
>> YOU NOT PREGENET, SO--
>> I'M NOT WHAT?
>> YOU'RE NOT PREGENET.
>> I'M NOT PREGNANT?
>> I MEAN--
>> NOW, THAT SOUNDS PERSONAL.
'CAUSE NOBODY TOLD YOU
TO POP UP PREGNANT.
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE USE, YOU KNOW,
CONDOMS.
THEY DID INVENT THOSE TO
PREVENT STUFF LIKE THIS.
>> I MEAN, MY ORIGINAL PLAN
WAS TO WAIT TILL
I GOT MARRIED ANYWAYS.
>> UH...BUT YOU DIDN'T DO THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT'S MY THING.
>> [sighs]
>> SO, SAVON...
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU AND MAUWI
GOT INTO IT TODAY?
>> HE DID HAVE
A LITTLE ATTITUDE TODAY.
>> HE DID?
HOW Y'ALL RELATIONSHIP GONNA
WORK OUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S NOT LOOKING TOO GOOD
RIGHT NOW, HONESTLY.
>> HEY, I MEAN, YOU AND MAUWI
AIN'T NEVER EVEN BEEN INTIMATE,
RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
I'M MAKING SURE I'M, LIKE,
TRYING TO GET EVERYTHING BEFORE,
YOU KNOW, THE BABY GETS HERE AND
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING IS SETTLED.
SEX IS REALLY NOT--
>> SO WHY DO YOU HAVE
A BOYFRIEND?
>> I MEAN--
>> I MEAN, I'M JUST TRYING TO--
>> THIS WAS BEFORE I KNEW.
I MEAN, EVENTUALLY, IF YOU GET
WITH SOMEBODY AND YOU DON'T KNOW
YOU PREGNANT--
>> BUT YOU DIDN'T MAKE ELI
WAIT THAT LONG.
I MEAN, YOU HAD A CHAN--
YOU BECAME AN ANGEL
AFTER YOU GOT PREGNANT?
>> NO, I'M SAYING--
WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
WHEN I GOT WITH MAUWI,
THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED
THAT I WAS PREGNANT.
SO I--WE REALLY DIDN'T HAVE A
CHANCE TO EVEN BE INTIMATE.
>> WHAT YOU LIKE ABOUT MAUWI?
>> I MEAN, HE'S A GOOD PERSON,
LIKE, GENUINELY, LIKE, FROM THE
HEART, LIKE, WHENEVER HE DOES
SOMETHING, IT'S HONEST.
>> DO YOU WANT TO BE INTIMATE
WITH HIM?
>> EVENTUALLY.
BUT NOT AT THE MOMENT.
THE SITUATION IS ALREADY
COMPLICATED AND AWKWARD.
I'M PREGNANT, AND THERE'S
OTHER RESPONSIBILITIES
I GOT TO TAKE ON NOW.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA PICK A MAN--
CHOOSE A MAN OVER YOUR KIDS.
YOUR KIDS GONNA ALWAYS BE
THE NUMBER ONE PRIORITY.
YOUR FOCUS GOT TO BE ON YOURSELF
AND YOUR SON TO MAKE A BETTER
LIFE FOR HIM.
>> YEAH.
WELL, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
SO--
I'M DUE IN A WEEK, AND WE'RE
HAVING A CRAZY ICE STORM.
MAUWI AND I HAVEN'T TALKED
SINCE OUR ARGUMENT,
AND HE'S BACK AT SCHOOL.
MY AUNT'S OUT OF TOWN VISITING
A FRIEND, AND I'M AT HOME
WITH MY COUSIN PHILIP.
BUT WHILE I WAS TRYING TO
GET CAUGHT UP ON SCHOOLWORK,
I STARTED TO FEEL
SOME INTENSE CRAMPS.
[grunts]
MY BOOTY IS, LIKE,
REALLY HURTING.
>> ARE YOU GONNA CALL
YOUR BOYFRIEND?
>> I'M NOT CALLING ANYBODY
UNTIL THE BABY'S BORN.
>> YOU IN PAIN?
>> UH, YEAH, I MEAN,
IT WENT FROM JUST, LIKE,
A LITTLE PRESSURE TO, LIKE,
IT'S LIKE REALLY BAD, SHARP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BYE.
>> SO BASICALLY, MAMA CAN'T
GET IN THE STATE OF GEORGIA
RIGHT NOW.
SO SHE'S STUCK.
>> YEP.
WELL, I GUESS WE JUST WAIT.
BUT MY CONTRACTIONS GOT WORSE.
AND SINCE MY AUNT WAS STUCK OUT
OF TOWN AND IT WAS TOO DANGEROUS
TO TAKE A TAXI IN THE STORM, MY
COUSIN HAD TO CALL AN AMBULANCE
TO TAKE ME TO THE HOSPITAL.
WHEN I GOT TO THE HOSPITAL,
THINGS MOVED PRETTY QUICKLY.
THE DOCTOR SAID I WAS ALREADY
6 CENTIMETERS, SO I GOT
AN EPIDURAL RIGHT AWAY.
>> WELL, IT LOOK LIKE
TODAY IS THE DAY.
HOW YOU FEELING?
>> MY LEGS ARE COMPLETELY NUMB.
>> [laughs]
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> YOUR COUSIN?
>> BEFORE I KNEW IT,
IT WAS TIME TO PUSH.
>> PULL THOSE LEGS.
CHIN TO YOUR CHEST,
AND BEAR DOWN
LIKE YOU GOT TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
>> [gasps]
>> ONE MORE, HONEY.
ONE MORE.
ONE MORE JUST LIKE THAT.
GIVE 100%.
BEAR DOWN.
THERE YOU GO.
OH, THERE YOU GO.
>> [speaks indistinctly]
>> [sighs]
>> IT IS A BABY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> HE'S HERE.
[baby cries]
>> THERE HE IS.
[baby crying]
[sighs]
>> *GRACE FALLS DOWN *
* ON QUIET HEARTS
[sentimental music]
*
* JUST WHEN YOU THINK
* IT MIGHT FALL APART
[chime dings]
>> I'M EXHAUSTED BUT GLAD EDEN
IS HEALTHY AND DOING WELL.
THE ICE STORM HAS PASSED,
SO MY AUNT WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO GET HOME.
HEY.
>> HEY, SAVON.
I HEAR YOU WAS A TROUPER, GIRL.
I'M SORRY, I--
OH, BABY.
[stammering]
I'M PROUD OF MY NIECE.
YEAH.
SHE--SHE PAID ATTENTION.
WE DON'T MAKE UGLY BABIES.
>> YEAH, I TOLD HIM
THAT HE WAS BORN, LIKE,
30 MINUTES AFTER I HAD HIM.
>> OH.
WHAT'D HE SAY?
>> NOTHING.
>> OH, I'M PROBABLY NOT GONNA
CALL HIM TILL I GET HOME
AND GET SETTLED.
>> DAMN.
WHERE THE HELL YOU GET THESE
THREE-YEAR-OLD [bleep] HANDS
FROM?
BOY, YOUR HANDS ARE HUGE.
>> WE'RE FINALLY LEAVING THE
HOSPITAL, AND I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO GETTING HOME.
BUT I'M NERVOUS TO TAKE CARE OF
EDEN ON MY OWN.
>> GET THE BACKPACK.
I'LL GET IT.
HI.
>> WHAT'S UP, SAVON?
>> HEY.
I TEXTED MAUWI TO LET HIM KNOW
I HAD EDEN BUT THAT I WASN'T
READY FOR COMPANY YET.
I REALLY MISS HIM, BUT RIGHT
NOW, I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO BE A MOM.
[baby crying]
OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S SO MUCH PEE IN HERE.
ICK.
THAT IS NASTY.
OH, MY GOSH.
OH.
THAT--
[sighs]
HE JUST SQUIRTED CORN-LOOKING
POOP ALL OVER ME.
OH, MY GOSH.
OKAY.
LET'S TRY THIS ONE MORE TIME.
UH.
OKAY.
[liquid squishing]
THIS IS OUT OF CONTROL.
I DON'T--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
ARE YOU FINISHED
MAKING POO-POO EVERYWHERE?
[baby sneezes]
EWW.
[grunts]
[baby grunts]
[baby sneezes]
OKAY, WE GONNA GET YOU A
BLANKET, 'CAUSE THIS SNEEZING
IN MY FACE IS NOT OKAY.
[baby sneezes]
OKAY.
MAUWI'S BEEN CALLING TO SEE
HOW THINGS ARE GOING, AND I KNOW
I NEED TO TALK TO HIM SOON.
[phone ringing]
[wistful music]
**
I DO MISS HIM,
BUT THE REALITY THAT
HE'S NOT EDEN'S FATHER
IS REALLY HITTING ME.
[baby crying]
MAUWI TEXTED THAT HE'S AROUND
THIS WEEKEND.
SO I FINALLY INVITED HIM OVER.
>> WHAT'S UP?
[sighs]
WHAT'S UP?
>> THIS.
>> WHERE THE BABY AT?
HE ASLEEP?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW'S THE MOMMY LIFE
TREATING YOU?
>> GOOD, I GUESS.
>> SO WHAT'S GOING ON WITH US?
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE GROWING APART.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T LIKE THE PRESSURE
OF BEING IN A RELATIONSHIP.
SO--
>> SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM THEN?
>> I JUST DON'T HAVE ENERGY.
I DON'T HAVE THE TIME FOR
ANYTHING OUTSIDE OF TAKING CARE
OF EDEN AND GOING TO SCHOOL.
I MEAN, HONESTLY,
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO BE A MOM, SO...
>> I FEEL YOU.
>> TRYING TO BE A GIRLFRIEND
AT THE SAME TIME IS TOO MUCH
RIGHT NOW.
>> I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
AND I RESPECT YOU
FOR TELLING ME THAT...
AT THE LAST MINUTE.
>> I'M JUST COMING TO A
REALIZATION THAT I'M A MOM,
AND THAT KIND OF COMES FIRST.
>> OKAY.
BUT NOBODY ASKED YOU TO PUT YOUR
BOYFRIEND FIRST.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IF I WOULD HAVE HAD THE KID
BEFORE WE STARTED TO DATE, THEN
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN DIFFERENT.
BUT I CAN'T BALANCE THE TWO
RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY.
[baby crying]
SPEAKING OF YOUR CHILD,
I THINK HE'S CALLING FOR YOU.
YEAH.
GO FOCUS ON YOUR CHILD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
[baby crying]
[delicate music]
*
>> * YOU WERE THE ONE
* THAT I HELD
* I HELD
* IN MY HEART
* SO WELL
*
>> I FEEL LIKE AT ONE POINT,
WE WERE ON THE SAME PAGE,
AND NOW WE JUST GOING
IN DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I DIDN'T
HAVE A KID.
>> I JUST--
I JUST WONDER WHAT TOOK YOU SO
LONG TO COME TO THIS CONCLUSION
IN LIFE.
I DON'T LIKE,
YOU KNOW, WASTING TIME.
TIME IS VERY PRECIOUS,
SOMETHING YOU CAN'T GET BACK.
>> IF I WOULD HAVE KNOWN,
I WOULDN'T HAVE KEPT STRINGING
IT ON FOR SO LONG.
LIKE, OH, WE CAN WORK IT OUT.
MY MIND-SET
IS TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
I'M THINKING LIKE A MOTHER,
NOT AS A GIRLFRIEND.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING ELSE TO ACCEPT OR--
I DON'T HAVE NO CHOICE.
THE PROOF IS IN FRONT OF ME.
[delicate music continues]
*
>> * YOU WERE THE ONE
* THAT SHOWED
* TEACHING LIFE
* TO LIVE FOR
>> TEEN MOM JUST CAME.
YOU GO RIGHT HERE.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY.
SAY "HEY."
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
HOW ADORABLE ARE YOU?
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
>> UM...
NOTHING MUCH.
>> HOW ARE THINGS GOING
WITH MAUWI?
>> UM, THINGS ARE SUCKISH RIGHT
NOW, 'CAUSE WE JUST DECIDED
TO BE FRIENDS.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE TIME.
I CAN'T BE A FULL-TIME
GIRLFRIEND AND A FULL-TIME MOM.
IT'S TOO MUCH WITH SCHOOL
AND HAVING A BABY AND ALL THAT
OTHER, YOU KNOW, STUFF THAT
COMES ALONG WITH IT.
>> WAS IT HARD FOR YOU
TO MAKE THIS DECISION?
>> YEAH, BUT I FEEL LIKE
EVENTUALLY,
WE WOULD HAVE GROWN APART.
IF NOT NOW, IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN LATER ON, AND WE BOTH
WOULD BE LIKE, "WELL,
WE WASTED A LOT OF TIME,"
YOU KNOW, TRYING TO STRING
SOMETHING OUT THAT WE KNEW
WAS NOT GONNA WORK.
>> DOES IT MAKE YOU FEEL SAD,
OR DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GONNA BE LONELY?
>> I CAN'T FOCUS TOO MUCH ON IT.
I GOT OTHER THINGS ON MY MIND.
I FINALLY GOT A JOB,
AND MY FRIEND AGREED TO BABYSIT
A FEW NIGHTS A WEEK.
JUGGLING WORKING, SCHOOLWORK,
AND TAKING CARE OF EDEN
IS EXHAUSTING.
I'M MORE BEHIND IN SCHOOL
THAN EVER.
[baby cries]
BUT HAVING A BABY DOESN'T LEAVE
ME MUCH TIME TO CATCH UP,
MUCH LESS HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS.
COME ON, BABY,
IT'S TIME TO GO TO BED.
I'M TIRED.
CAN I GET SOME SLEEP?
YOU GONNA LET ME GO TO SLEEP
OR NO?
[baby whimpering]
[baby cries]
EDEN, WHAT'S WRONG?
[hums]
[baby cries]
>> * DAMN OUR LUCK
* THAT SENT US ASTRAY
[baby crying]
* YEAH, YEAH, YEAH
*
* WE WERE IN PARADISE
[baby crying]
[sweeping pop music]
*
[baby crying]
[sweeping music continues]
*
>> I MISS HANGING OUT WITH
MAUWI, AND I'VE BEEN FEELING
PRETTY LONELY.
I NEVER PICTURED HAVING A BABY
WOULD BE LIKE THIS.
>> SEE, THAT'S A PRETTY BABY.
SAVON, I JUST THINK THAT
YOU HAVE MORE FEELING THAT
YOU'RE NOT BEING HONEST ABOUT.
I THINK YOU'RE--YOU'RE NOT
RELEASING HOW YOU REALLY FEEL,
AND YOU SHOULD.
AND IF YOU'RE IN PAIN OR IF
YOU'RE DISAPPOINTED, YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T LIKE THE SITUATION,
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO TALK ABOUT
IT, 'CAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
YOU'RE GONNA MOVE PAST IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL,
THOUGH.
I DON'T FEEL ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T DESCRIBE.
I MEAN, THERE'S NOTHING.
>> I MEAN, ARE YOU DISAPPOINTED
IN YOURSELF?
ARE YOU DISAPPOINTED THAT EDEN
DON'T HAVE A FATHER?
>> MM, I THINK BOTH.
I HAD A DIFFERENT PLAN FOR IT.
>> I'M SURE YOU WANTED BETTER
FOR YOURSELF, BUT YOU CAN'T
BEAT YOURSELF UP ABOUT IT.
NOTHING IN LIFE GOES
ACCORDING TO PLAN.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M DISAPPOINTED
IN MY SITUATION,
I KNOW I HAVE TO ACCEPT IT
AND MOVE FORWARD.
I REACHED OUT TO MAUWI FOR THE
FIRST TIME SINCE WE BROKE UP,
AND WE'RE GONNA MEET.
I STILL CAN'T HANDLE BEING IN A
RELATIONSHIP, BUT IT'LL BE GOOD
TO SEE HIM AND HANG OUT LIKE WE
USED TO BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT.
AUNTIE.
DO YOU MIND WATCHING EDEN FOR
A LITTLE BIT WHILE I GO OUT?
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> TO GO MEET MAUWI.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> I'LL WATCH HIM
FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
THAT'S IT.
>> OKAY, HE'S ASLEEP RIGHT NOW,
AND I MADE HIM A BOTTLE
ON THE THING.
>> OKAY.
>> HMM.
>> SO HOW YOU LIKING THE JOB,
MAN?
>> IT'S FUN.
I'M EATING, LIKE, PIZZA
EVERY NIGHT NOW.
>> SO DID YOU EVER PICK THOSE--
THOSE GRADES UP?
>> I'M BEHIND SO MUCH.
BOY, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
IT'S PRETTY HARD DOING ONLINE
CLASSES RIGHT NOW, BECAUSE EDEN
WAKES UP SO OFTEN.
I HAVE TO GO IN THERE,
FEED HIM, WAIT FOR HIM
TO BURP, FEED HIM AGAIN.
I'M LIKE, "I HAVE THINGS TO DO,
OKAY?"
>> SO HE ALREADY GOT YOU
LOOKING LIKE A PUPPET,
AND HE CAN'T EVEN TALK YET.
>> YEP.
>> [laughs]
>> I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT
HOW EVERYTHING IS, LIKE,
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
LIKE, I MEAN, YOU STILL DOING
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO FOR THE MOST
PART, BUT FOR ME, IT'S LIKE--
LIKE, YOU CAN DO SPORT--YOU CAN
GO TO COLLEGE FOR SPORTS,
BUT IF I GO TO COLLEGE,
IT WON'T BE--
I MEAN, THAT'S GONNA BE
TOO TIME-CONSUMING FOR ME.
>> BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO DO IT,
YOU CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>> YEAH.
TO BE SUCCESSFUL IN THE THINGS
THAT I WANT TO DO,
LIKE BASKETBALL AND MUSIC,
I MEAN, IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
>> YOU'RE NOT A 40-YEAR-OLD
WOMAN.
LIKE, YOU'RE NOT EVEN 20 YET.
YOU STILL GOT MORE THAN ENOUGH
TIME TO MAKE THINGS HAPPEN.
>> IT WASN'T WHAT I HAD PLANNED
FOR MY LIFE.
BUT I JUST HAVE TO ROLL
WITH THE PUNCHES, REALLY.
JUST LIVE DAY-BY-DAY.
>> I FEEL YOU.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING
YOU CAN DO.
>> YEP.
I MEAN, IT'S NICE THAT WE STILL
CAN BE FRIENDS EVEN AFTER,
YOU KNOW, BREAKING UP.
BUT--
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'S LIFE.
MY BOYFRIEND IS ONE MONTH.
I FEED HIM EVERY DAY,
AND I CHANGE HIS DIAPER.
AND THAT'S MY BOYFRIEND.
THAT'S MY LIFE.
>> OUR FRIENDSHIP
IS NEVER GONNA END.
>> IS THAT RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I'M ALWAYS
GONNA BE AROUND.
YOU AIN'T GONNA HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO BE MY FRIEND,
WHETHER YOU LOVE ME OR HATE ME.
[geese honking]
>> OH, HELL NO.
I DON'T LIKE THIS [bleep].
>> THEY TRYING TO JUMP US.
>> IS THIS SAFE?
I'VE BEEN ATTACKED BY A DUCK,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT,
SO IT'S LIKE--
>> WANT ME TO SCARE THEM AWAY?
I DON'T TRUST DUCKS, THOUGH.
>> [laughs]
>> GET BACK.
>> I WOULD HAVE NEVER THOUGHT
I WOULD BE A TEEN MOM
BECAUSE OF THE WAY
THAT I WAS RAISED.
I WAS VERY DISAPPOINTED
IN MYSELF.
DON'T RUN UP ON THE WRONG ONE.
[laughs]
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
SO I'M BEING CAUTIOUS.
>> [laughs]
OH, OOH!
>> SIT BACK DOWN.
ACT LIKE THIS NEVER HAPPENED.
>> BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
I WAS FOCUSED IN SCHOOL.
I HAD GOOD GRADES.
I WAS ON THE BASKETBALL TEAM.
BUT I FEEL LIKE AFTER I GOT
PREGNANT, ALL THOSE THINGS
KIND OF WENT AWAY.
>> YOU HUNGRY, LITTLE MAN?
>> MY AUNT HAS HELPED ME A LOT.
SHE TOOK ME IN, SHE HELPED ME
RAISE EDEN THE BEST THAT I CAN.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT WHEN I HAD A
BABY, THAT THE FATHER WOULD BE
THERE AND IT WOULD BE
A COUPLE THING AND WE WOULD
RAISE THE CHILD TOGETHER.
THEN I REALIZED, YOU KNOW,
"I'M HAVING A BABY,
AND I'M BY MYSELF."
IT'S JUST ME.
EVERYTHING JUST KIND OF CAME TO
ME, HIT ME ALL AT ONCE.
EDEN'S FATHER
HAS NOT CAME BY ONCE
TO SEE HIS SON.
IT WAS HARD TO LET MAUWI GO
AS A BOYFRIEND,
BUT HE'S STILL A FRIEND.
I WANT TO START COLLEGE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
I JUST FEEL LIKE GETTING MY GED
WILL BE A BETTER OPTION FOR ME
TO HAVE MORE TIME FOR EDEN
AND PUT TOWARDS MY CAREER.
HI, EVERYBODY, I'M SAVON.
I'M GONNA BE SINGING
SOMETHING ORIGINAL.
I WANT A CAREER IN MUSIC,
WHETHER I'M A FAMOUS MUSICIAN
OR A MUSIC TEACHER.
I'M NOT REALLY SURE WHAT THE
FUTURE IS GONNA HOLD FOR ME.
HEY.
HEY, YOU GOT SOME BIG EYES, MAN.
BUT WHENEVER I GET DISCOURAGED
OR DISAPPOINTED IN SOMETHING,
I JUST LOOK AT EDEN AND KNOW
THAT AT THE END OF THE DAY, I
HAVE TO DO THE BEST THAT I CAN
TO PROVIDE FOR HIM
AND MAKE HIM HAPPY.
[chime dings]
>> ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT...
>> IF YOU WAIT FOR ME,
THEN I'LL KNOW FOR SURE THAT
YOU WANT TO BE WITH ME.
>> IF WE'RE PREGNANT, WHAT
HARM'S GONNA COME OUT OF IT?
>> WE'RE REMAINING...
[slow-motion] ABSTINENT.
[baby wailing]
>> [moans]
>> I THINK YOU CAN LAST
UNTIL WE'RE MARRIED.
[tires screeching]
thud!
>> YEAH.