>> MY NAME IS EBONY, AND I'M
A TEENAGE MILITARY BRAT
FROM COLORADO SPRINGS, COLORADO,
HOME OF THE AIR FORCE.
I'M A SENIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I SPEND ALL MY TIME
WITH MY FIANCE, JOSH.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
JUST OVER A YEAR.
DID I TELL YOU NOT TO EAT
MY OREOS?
I LIVE AT HOME WITH MY MOM.
SHE WORKS A LOT, SO I'VE LEARNED
TO TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
JOSH LIVES WITH HIS PARENTS,
AND HIS MOM IS A LITTLE MORE
HANDS-ON.
>> YOU WEREN'T AT SCHOOL.
YOU NEVER WENT TO SCHOOL
THAT DAY.
>> YEAH, AND I'VE ONLY MISSED,
MAYBE, AT TOPS, 50 CLASSES
THIS SEMESTER.
>> SO WE CAN'T WAIT TO GRADUATE
HIGH SCHOOL AND ESCAPE.
WE BOTH COME FROM MILITARY
FAMILIES, AND WE ALWAYS WANTED
TO FOLLOW IN THEIR FOOTSTEPS,
SO WE JOINED JUNIOR ROTC
AT OUR HIGH SCHOOL.
AW, YOU LOOK GOOD.
AFTER GRADUATION, WE'RE PLANNING
TO GET MARRIED,
JOIN THE AIR FORCE,
AND FLY AWAY TOGETHER.
BUT NOW ALL OF OUR PLANS ARE
UP IN THE AIR, BECAUSE...
I'M PREGNANT.
Captioning byCaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
MY MOM WAS PRETTY BUMMED
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT.
>> YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, I WAS A
LITTLE UPSET ABOUT NOT--YOU
KNOW, THE PROTECTION THING, AND
WE TALKED ABOUT CONDOMS AND...
>> MM-HMM.
>> IN FACT, I SAT YOU AND JOSH
DOWN RIGHT HERE AND SAID, "HEY,
USE PROTECTION.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
A GRANDMA YET."
AND LOOK, NOW I'M GONNA BE
A GRANDMA.
>> I THINK JOSH'S PARENTS WERE
A LITTLE BIT MORE UPSET ABOUT
IT, BECAUSE THEY WOULDN'T LET US
STAY IN THE SAME ROOM, EVEN
AFTER I WAS PREGNANT.
>> REALLY?
SO HOW DO THEY YOU THINK
YOU GOT PREGNANT?
IMMACULATE CONCEPTION?
>> [laughs]
>> SO HOW OLD WERE YOU THE FIRST
TIME WE STARTED TALKING ABOUT
SEX WITH YOU?
SERIOUSLY, JOSHUA.
YOU REMEMBER I HAD TO SIGN THOSE
PAPERS FOR THAT CLASS, AND YOU
CAME HOME AND EXPLAINED TO ME
HOW A BABY'S MADE?
>> YEAH, THE SEX ED CLASSES.
>> YOU MADE SURE THAT YOU KNEW
WHAT PRECAUTIONS TO TAKE AND
THAT YOU HAD THOSE PRECAUTIONS.
>> AND WE USED THEM.
[laughs]
>> THEN WHY ARE YOU GOING TO BE
A DADDY?
>> 'CAUSE--I DON'T KNOW.
>> IS HE UP TO THIS?
I MEAN...
>> I THINK HE'LL GROW UP AS SOON
AS HE HOLDS HER, BECAUSE YOU
KNOW HOW FATHERS AREN'T REALLY
FATHERS UNTIL THEY HOLD
THEIR BABY.
>> MAYBE.
>> ♪ I DON'T KNOW WHY
♪ THE WORLD IS SPINNING
♪ IN HER OWN WAY
♪ THINK I'LL CRY
♪ FROM ALL THESE IMAGES
>> DID YOU GET YOUR INVITE
TO THE BABY SHOWER?
>> YAY.
>> [laughs]
>> EBONY, YOU GOTTA GIVE OUT
A LIST OF THINGS YOU WANT,
BECAUSE IF NOT--ALL RIGHT.
>> AT SCHOOL, SOME KIDS ARE
EXCITED ABOUT MY PREGNANCY,
BUT OTHER KIDS JUST AREN'T
AS COOL WITH IT.
>> MY SISTER HAD HER KID BECAUSE
THEY DIDN'T USE A CONDOM.
I MEAN, I SAW HOW
IT RUINED HER LIFE.
I DON'T WANNA END UP LIKE THAT.
>> I KNOW SHE WASN'T A PLANNED
PREGNANCY, BUT I THINK THINGS
HAPPEN FOR A REASON, AND I'M
HAVING MY BABY BECAUSE I WANT
TO HAVE HER.
>> IF GIRLS HAVE ENOUGH RESPECT
FOR THEMSELVES--I'M NOT SAYING
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE RESPECT
FOR YOURSELF IF YOU'RE HAVING
SEX, BUT, YOU KNOW, JUST KEEP
YOUR LEGS CLOSED.
[laughter]
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING
IN ROTC TODAY?
>> NOT SURE.
>> OH.
>> LEFT!
LEFT!
LEFT, RIGHT!
>> ABOUT FACE!
PRESENT ARMS!
ORDER ARMS!
>> JUST SOUND OFF.
GIVE 'EM OPEN RANKS.
GIVE 'EM ATTENTION, OPEN RANKS,
OKAY?
EBONY, YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, JUST LOOK--
YOUR EYES ARE KIND OF WANDERING
ON ME, OKAY.
>> ROTC WAS SUPPOSED TO GIVE ME
A HEAD START ON JOINING
THE AIR FORCE.
[man shouting indistinctly]
BUT GETTING PREGNANT HAS MADE
IT HARD TO KEEP UP.
>> DOUBLE TIME!
HUT!
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, EBONY?
I KNOW YOU CAN'T DO THAT,
SO IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> A COUPLE MONTHS AGO,
MAYBE, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S OKAY.
YOU'RE BREATHING HARD JUST FROM
MARCHING.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
MY FRIENDS WERE SURPRISED WHEN
I GOT PREGNANT, BUT SO FAR,
THEY'RE SUPER SUPPORTIVE.
THEY'RE EVEN HELPING ME PLAN
FOR PROM.
ARE YOU GOING TO PROM THIS YEAR,
LAUREN?
>> UM...
>> ARE YOU ALLOWED TO GO
TO PROM?
>> I AM ALLOWED TO GO.
IF SOMEBODY ASKS ME AND THEY'RE
GONNA PAY FOR IT, OKAY, YEAH,
I'LL GO, BUT...
>> SINCE YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
ABLE TO DANCE, AM I GONNA BE
ABLE TO DANCE WITH PEOPLE?
>> YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED TO DANCE
WITH ANY GIRLS.
IF YOU WANNA DANCE WITH GUYS,
ALL FOR YOU DANCING WITH GUYS.
[laughter]
YES, IT'S IN APRIL.
THE BABY IS DUE IN MAY.
>> SHOULD CALL UP THE PEOPLE
WHO MAKE BLIMPS.
>> I'M GONNA BE, LIKE, THIS BIG.
I'LL BE THIS BIG.
YOU SEE THIS TABLE RIGHT HERE?
THIS IS HOW BIG I'M GONNA BE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT MY MOM SAID
ABOUT YOU?
SHE'S LIKE--NO OFFENSE, JOSH,
BUT SHE'S LIKE, "EBONY IS SO
BEAUTIFUL."
AND SHE'S LIKE, "THEN YOU HAVE
JOSH, AND HE'S JUST KIND OF
GOOFY-LOOKING."
I WAS LIKE, "MOM!"
[laughter]
'CAUSE YOU HAVE TO FACE IT,
JOSH.
YOU'RE KIND OF GOOFY-LOOKING.
>> [indistinct chatter]
>> AM I REALLY THAT
PATHETIC-LOOKING?
LIKE, IS IT SO HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT I'M WITH HER?
>> NO, HONESTLY I CAN'T PICTURE
EBONY WITH ANYBODY ELSE.
>> HEY, JOSH, ARE YOU GOING TO
SPEND THE NIGHT THIS EVENING,
OR ARE YOU ALLOWED?
>> I CAN ASK, THOUGH.
I CAN CALL MY MOM REAL QUICK
AND SEE.
BUT I GOT A QUESTION TO--
I WANTED TO KNOW IF I COULD
STAY THE NIGHT TONIGHT.
>> HI, CHRISTI.
YEAH, HE'S HERE.
[chime dings]
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE MY BABY'S
DADDY CAN'T STAY OVER WITHOUT
ASKING HIS MOMMY.
>> SO WHERE DO YOU WANT ME TO
TRY TO GET STATIONED?
>> HAWAII.
>> HAWAII?
DO YOU REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
THAT YOU ASKED ME TO MARRY YOU?
DO YOU REMEMBER?
>> A WHILE AGO.
>> SO WERE YOU NOT SERIOUS
ABOUT IT THEN?
>> NO, I WAS SERIOUS.
WE'RE ALREADY 17 AND HAVING
A KID.
THAT'S ALREADY A BIG STEP
RIGHT THERE.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE 17
AND MARRIED.
>> OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
WITH JOSH SECOND-GUESSING OUR
MARRIAGE PLANS NOW THAT I'M
PREGNANT, I'M STARTING TO WISH
THAT WE HAD BEEN MORE CAREFUL.
>> THE BIGGER I GET, THE MORE
OVERWHELMING SCHOOL IS.
MY SCHOOL COUNSELOR DOESN'T WANT
ME TO DROP OUT, SO SHE BROUGHT
ME IN TO TALK TO SOME OTHER
STUDENTS WHO HAVE BEEN THROUGH
THE SAME THING.
>> I WAS IN LABOR FOR, LIKE,
32 HOURS.
IT SUCKED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> 32 HOURS?
>> YEAH, SO I WENT AND GOT
AN EPIDURAL AFTER, LIKE,
THE FIRST 26.
LIKE, YOUR CONTRACTIONS GO
OFF THE CHART, THOUGH.
IT SUCKS.
IT HURTS.
[laughter]
>> GET READY.
>> THE FIRST NIGHT I BROUGHT HER
HOME, SHE CRIED THE WHOLE NIGHT.
AND I HADN'T SLEPT AT ALL
IN THE HOSPITAL.
IT WAS, LIKE, THE HARDEST THING
TO GO THROUGH, IS THE FIRST
NIGHT.
AND THEN YOU GET AROUND TWO
MONTHS, AND THEN THEY GET COLIC,
WHICH IS, LIKE, THE WORST THING
EVER, BECAUSE SHE CRIES,
AND NOTHING, NOTHING WILL HELP,
NOT ONE THING.
YOU'LL BE OKAY, THOUGH.
>> BUT HOW ABOUT THE REST OF YOU
GUYS, TRYING TO COME TO SCHOOL
AND BE A MOM AT THE SAME TIME?
>> UM, IT'S THE WHOLE HOMEWORK
THING.
>> THE HOMEWORK?
>> YEAH.
I'D COME HOME AND THEN TAKE CARE
OF HER, AND MY BOYFRIEND WOULD
GO, UM, HAVE FUN WITH HIS
FRIENDS, 'CAUSE HE WATCHED HER
ALL DAY, SO...
>> THESE GIRLS ARE FREAKING
ME OUT.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO
MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
>> GO!
GO, TEAM.
HALT!
WAIT FOR IT TO COME.
smack!
>> I WAS EXCITED TO COMPETE
ON THE DRILL TEAM THIS YEAR,
BUT NOW I'VE BEEN FORCED
TO SIT OUT.
>> YEAH, EBONY, YOU GOTTA GIVE
THEM A HAND.
>> I KNOW, YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE,
AMAZING.
I LOVED YOU GUYS.
>> I KNOW SHE WANTED TO DO THIS,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY, YOU KNOW,
NONE OF US CAN DELIVER A BABY
HERE, SO...
IN SPIRIT, SHE'S WITH YOU.
IN PHYSICAL, THOUGH, A COUPLE
OF MONTHS FROM NOW, SHE'S GONNA
BE SOMEWHERE ELSE, YOU KNOW,
AND THINGS LIKE THAT.
SO GIVE EBONY A HAND FOR--
[applause]
>> OKAY.
I'VE DREAMED OF JOINING
THE AIR FORCE MY WHOLE LIFE.
I HOPE I DON'T HAVE TO BAIL OUT
NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT.
WELL, I CAN GO INTO THE MILITARY
AFTER SIX MONTHS.
>> WELL, AFTER SIX MONTHS,
RIGHT, BUT YOU ARE NOT GONNA BE
WANTING TO LEAVE THAT BABY
AFTER SIX MONTHS.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> SO YOU JUST NEED TO MAKE
A PLAN AND STICK WITH IT
AND JUST SAY, "OKAY, THIS IS
TEMPORARY THAT I'M AWAY
FROM HER," YOU KNOW.
>> AND I WOULD MISS SO MUCH
IF SHE WAS...
>> YES.
>> AFTER SIX MONTHS, I'D MISS
HER FIRST STEPS AND HER FIRST
WORDS, AND--AH.
>> EXACTLY.
>> OH.
>> AND YOU'VE THOUGHT THIS
THROUGH?
>> YES, I DID.
SHE'S GONNA STAY
OVER AT JOSH'S HOUSE.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW HE'S GONNA
BE STATIONED HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, THAT WAS MY PLAN, SO...
>> BUT YOU DON'T ALWAYS GET
STATIONED WHERE YOU GO TO
TRAINING AT.
>> WELL, WHEREVER HE GETS
STATIONED AT.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THIS.
WE WILL TALK ABOUT THIS.
>> THIS IS SOMETHING WHERE YOU
REALLY NEED TO THINK ABOUT.
YOU CAN'T GO IN THE SERVICE
AND NOT KNOW, YOU KNOW,
WHERE YOUR BABY'S GONNA BE AT.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT?
>> WE'LL FIGURE THAT OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU WANNA
LOOK AT SOMETHING?
>> YES, I DO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IS JOINING THE AIR FORCE
REALISTIC WITH THE BABY
ON THE WAY?
I NEED SOME ANSWERS FROM SOMEONE
WHO KNOWS WHAT THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
[martial drumming and humming]
>> GONNA HAVE YOU GUYS BOTH
FILL THESE OUT.
READ THROUGH THEM.
AFTER YOU UNDERSTAND THEM,
GO AHEAD AND PRINT AND SIGN
AND DATE, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> WHAT I'D LIKE TO DO IS START
OFF WITH A PREQUALIFICATION
QUESTIONNAIRE JUST TO MAKE SURE
YOU GUYS ARE QUALIFIED.
YOU'RE CURRENTLY A HIGH SCHOOL
SENIOR?
>> YES.
>> MARITAL AND DEPENDENCY
STATUS?
ARE YOU SINGLE OR MARRIED?
>> UM, SINGLE.
>> OKAY, AND EXPECTING?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, AND HAVE YOU EVER USED,
POSSESSED, SOLD, OR TRANSPORTED
ANY ILLEGAL DRUGS, TO INCLUDE
MARIJUANA, EVEN IF ON AN
EXPERIMENTAL BASIS?
>> NO.
>> VERY GOOD.
>> HAVE YOU EVER BROKEN A BONE?
>> NO.
>> ANY PINS, SCREWS, OR PLATES
ANYWHERE IN YOUR BODY?
>> NO.
>> HAVE YOU EVER BEEN DIAGNOSED
WITH A MENTAL PROBLEM OR
DISORDER?
>> NO.
>> STRESS?
>> NOPE.
>> ADHD?
>> NO.
>> DEPRESSION?
>> NOPE.
>> HAVE YOU EVER ATTEMPTED
SUICIDE?
>> NOPE.
>> OKAY.
SO WHAT KIND OF QUESTIONS DO YOU
GUYS HAVE?
>> UM, WITH THE BABY, I KNOW YOU
HAVE TO WAIT...SIX MONTHS?
OR I'VE READ THAT YOU'VE HAD TO
WAIT SIX MONTHS BEFORE YOU GO
IN, SO, UM...
>> RIGHT, ACTUALLY YOU'D BE
IN NONPRIOR SERVICE, MEANING
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN IN THE AIR
FORCE BEFORE OR ANY BRANCH
OF THE MILITARY.
IT'D ACTUALLY BE DISQUALIFYING
FOR BOTH OF YOU GUYS TO JOIN
BECAUSE OF THE DEPENDENT
THAT YOU HAVE.
SO ONE OF YOU GUYS COULD JOIN,
BUT THE OTHER ONE WOULDN'T BE
ELIGIBLE TO JOIN, SO...
>> OH, I SEE.
>> YOU'RE JOINING THE AIR FORCE
TO SERVE YOUR COUNTRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I MEAN, THE SERVICE BEFORE SELF
AND EXCELLENCE AND ALL YOU DO AS
SOME OF OUR CORE VALUES, YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO EXPECT TO
DEPLOY, AND THAT PUTS A STRAIN
ON A FAMILY, AND SO IN ORDER
TO MINIMIZE THE STRAIN THAT IT
DOES PUT ON A FAMILY, THEY'VE
PUT THAT REGULATION IN PLACE.
OKAY?
YOU GUYS HAVE ANY QUESTIONS,
LET ME KNOW, OKAY?
BYE, THANKS AGAIN.
>> YEP.
>> YOU GUYS HAVE A GOOD DAY,
OKAY?
>> YOU TOO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
THINKING, BUT IT'S CLEAR NOW
THAT I'M NOT GOING INTO
THE AIR FORCE.
I KNEW HAVING A BABY MEANT
MAKING SACRIFICES, BUT I NEVER
EXPECTED MY CAREER WOULD END
BEFORE I EVEN FINISHED
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> I HAD TO GIVE UP MY AIR FORCE
DREAM SO THAT JOSH COULD HAVE
HIS, SO HE BETTER START TAKING
THINGS SERIOUSLY.
>> ♪ DO WHAT I WANT
♪ 'CAUSE I CAN
♪ AND IF I DON'T
♪ BECAUSE I WANNA
>> HOLA.
>> ♪ BE IGNORED BY THE STIFF
♪ AND THE BORED
♪ BECAUSE I'M GONNA
♪ SPIT AND RETRIEVE...
>> HELLO?
>> HEY, BABE.
>> WHERE YOU AT?
>> I'M AT THE PALMER PARK.
WE JUST DECORATED LYDELL'S CAR.
>> YOU REALLY DON'T NEED TO BE
GETTING CAUGHT SKIPPING.
AND YOU KNOW THAT.
[laughter]
[chime dings]
IF JOSH DOESN'T GRADUATE,
HE WON'T BE ELIGIBLE FOR
THE AIR FORCE, AND THEN WE'LL
BE A LITTLE FAMILY WITHOUT
A PLAN.
SO I'M TRYING TO HELP JOSH
CONCENTRATE ON HIS HOMEWORK.
>> CAN I HAVE A KISS?
>> NO.
JOSHUA, YOU HAVE HOMEWORK.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> JOSH.
>> WHAT?
>> STOP PLAYING WITH THE CAT.
>> ARE YOU MAD?
>> THAT MAKES ME EXTREMELY MAD.
[chime dings]
TODAY WE'RE GONNA GET AN
ULTRASOUND, IF JOSH CAN BORROW
THE CAR.
>> WHAT ARE THE RULES ABOUT
TAKING MY CAR, JOSHUA?
WHAT--JOSHUA, WHAT ARE THE RULES
ABOUT TAKING MY CAR?
DON'T ROLL YOUR EYES AT ME,
OR YOU'RE NOT TAKING IT.
WHAT ARE THE RULES ABOUT TAKING
MY VEHICLE?
I'M NOT KIDDING.
>> SPEED LIMIT.
UH...
>> NO SMOKING.
>> NO SMOKING, UH...
>> AND WHERE CAN YOU DRIVE IT?
>> TO JAY'S.
>> AND TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> THAT'S IT.
JAY'S, BACK, THE HOSPITAL,
THAT'S IT.
AND I'M CHECKING THE MILEAGE
BEFORE YOU TAKE MY VEHICLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M NOT KIDDING, JOSH.
>> SO YOU THINK IT'S A LITTLE
GIRL, HUH?
>> I'M HOPING IT'S STILL
A LITTLE GIRL.
[laughs]
'CAUSE WE GOT EVERYTHING PINK,
SO...
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OH.
>> LOOKS BEAUTIFUL.
>> THIS IS YOUR FIRST PREGNANCY?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, AND YOUR LAST MENSTRUAL
CYCLE?
>> JULY 23RD.
>> WERE YOU USING BIRTH CONTROL
WHEN YOU GOT PREGNANT?
>> NO.
>> WE'RE GONNA START WITH YOUR
WEIGHT REAL QUICK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
[chime dings]
WITH PROM JUST AROUND THE
CORNER, THIS IS THE WRONG TIME
FOR ME TO GAIN 40 POUNDS.
>> DO YOU, UM...
>> WHERE IS THE...
>> HI, GUYS, ARE YOU READY
TO TRY THESE ON?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET ME TAKE THESE
FOR YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> NO PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT, IF YOU GUYS JUST
WANNA FOLLOW ME.
>> OKAY.
I LOOK LIKE A MERMAID.
[laughing] LIKE A PURPLE
MERMAID.
>> MERMAIDS AREN'T, UM,
PREGNANT.
>> [laughing] MERMAIDS
AREN'T PREGNANT.
>> UH-UH.
OH, SEE, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
>> NO, IT DOESN'T.
>> IT'S ACTUALLY NOT--
IT'S NOT REAL TIGHT.
HEY, DON'T LOOK AT YOURSELF
SIDEWAYS; LOOK FRONTWAYS.
>> [laughs]
OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WHICH ONE ARE YOU
TRYING ON NEXT?
>> THE TENT--UGH.
>> WHY IS IT THE TENT?
>> YOU WILL SEE.
>> OKAY.
NICE.
SEE?
YES, THOSE COLORS LOOK
REALLY GOOD.
>> YOU KNOW WHY I DON'T LIKE IT?
BECAUSE I CAN GO LIKE THIS.
>> OKAY, BUT...
>> I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS IS MAKING ME SAD.
>> WHY?
'CAUSE--
TELL ME WHY.
>> JUST BECAUSE I CAN'T FIT
IN A DRESS.
>> WELL, EBONY.
>> [crying] NO.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE THAT LONG.
YOU'RE VERY PRETTY, VERY PRETTY.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT?
>> OKAY, LET'S--
DO YOU WANNA TAKE A BREAK?
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> FIRST THE AIR FORCE,
NOW THE PROM.
THIS PREGNANCY IS GETTING IN THE
WAY OF EVERYTHING.
[jets rumbling]
>> I'M A LITTLE WORRIED ABOUT MY
WATER BREAKING IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DANCE FLOOR.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU GONNA THINK PEOPLE
ARE GONNA, LIKE, LOOK AT YOU
WEIRD?
>> YEAH, BUT YOU LEARN TO DEAL
WITH IT.
>> I TRY TO STAY AWAY
FROM THE DRAMA.
>> JEEZ.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YEAH, FIVE MINUTES TO COME
OUT.
WE GOT FIVE MINUTES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M READY TO COME
OUT NOW.
>> THEN COME OUT.
>> [giggles]
>> [wolf whistle]
>> OH.
OH, PRETTY.
>> AW, ISN'T THAT SWEET?
>> OH.
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S TAKE A PICTURE,
AND THEN WE GOTTA GO.
>> OKAY.
>> RIGHT NOW.
>> I REALLY HAD NO IDEA HOW
STRESSED OUT I'D BE ABOUT THE
WHOLE PROM SITUATION.
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO TELL YOUR MAMA WE CANNOT
STOP BY HER WORK.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE, JOSHUA, WE--
>> OKAY, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
>> WE NEED TO GET BACK TO THE
[bleep] SPOT ON TIME.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
[horn honking]
>> THAT WAS NICE.
WHO JUST FARTED?
>> [laughing] JOSH.
>> HOLY [bleep].
WE WENT TO THE [bleep]
WRONG HOUSE.
SHE'S AT HER GRANDMA'S HOUSE.
>> WHERE'S HER GRANDMA LIVE?
>> WHERE'S YOUR GRANDMA LIVE?
>> OFF JET WING AND FOUNTAIN,
JOSHUA.
DAMN IT.
AND WE DIDN'T EVEN NEED TO DO
ALL OF THIS?
>> NO.
>> THAT'S [bleep] GREAT!
>> MAKE A RIGHT HERE.
>> WRONG [bleep] HOUSE.
>> I LIKE YOUR DRESS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IT'S PURDY.
>> WERE YOU SURPRISED?
>> NOPE.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
>> YEAH?
WHILE JOSH'S GOOFINESS CAN
ANNOY ME, SOMETIMES IT'S JUST
WHAT I NEED.
>> BEAUTIFUL, ALL RIGHT,
HERE WE GO, LOOKING THIS WAY.
GREAT SMILES.
PERFECT.
>> ♪ SHAKE, DROP IT
♪ THEN SHE STANDS UP STRAIGHT
♪ SPREAD IT LIKE IT'S
♪ LAND O' LAKES
♪ HANDSTANDS ALL IN MY FACE
♪ SO CLOSE THAT I CAN FEEL
♪ THE PLACE
♪ SHAKE IT BUT DON'T BREAK IT
♪ JUST MAKE SURE YOU SHAKE IT
♪ RIGHT, RIGHT
♪ SHAKE IT BUT DON'T BREAK IT
♪ JUST MAKE SURE YOU SHAKE IT
♪ RIGHT, RIGHT
♪ SHAKE IT BUT DON'T BREAK IT
[toilet flushes]
[sighs]
>> YOU READY, LADY?
>> AH, YEAH, SHE'S JUST--
>> SHE'S STRESSED?
>> NO, SHE'S JUST KICKING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> KICKING AWAY.
NOW'S NOT THE TIME TO KICK,
LITTLE GIRL.
>> ♪ OUR LOVE FLOATED
♪ OUT THE WINDOW
♪ OUR LOVE FLOATED
♪ OUT THE BACK DOOR
>> I COULD STAY LIKE THIS
FOREVER.
[chime dings]
MY FANTASY ALL HINGES
ON ONE THING: JOSH GRADUATING.
BUT THE NEXT DAY,
REALITY SET IN.
JOSH'S COUNSELOR CALLED HIM IN,
AND HIS DAD WAS THERE
WAITING FOR HIM.
>> YOU'VE BEEN MISSING A LOT OF
CLASS.
YOU HAVE 228 UNEXCUSED ABSENCES.
YOU'VE GOT 18 DAYS LEFT.
YOU HAVE TO BE IN EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF YOUR CLASSES.
YOU HAVE TO BRING EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF YOUR GRADES UP,
OR YOU WON'T GRADUATE.
DON'T GRADUATE, YOU DON'T GET
IN THE MILITARY.
YOU CAN'T DO WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO.
>> YOU HAD 200 UNEXCUSED
ABSENCES!
200, JOSHUA!
HOW DO YOU HAVE 200 UNEXCUSED
ABSENCES?
WHY?
>> BECAUSE I'M STRESSED!
>> BECAUSE WE STOPPED HELPING
YOU!
>> YOU STILL KEEP ME LOCKED UP
IN THIS HOUSE EVERY DAY!
>> YOU STAY FOR THE NEXT SIX
WEEKS, AND YOU HAVE THE SUPPORT
OF YOUR FAMILY, OR THERE'S
THE DOOR, BECAUSE WE HAVE DONE
EVERYTHING AND GIVEN YOU
EVERYTHING AND EVERY
OPPORTUNITY, AND ALL YOU DO
IS THROW IT IN OUR FACE!
>> I DO NOT THROW IT IN YOUR
FACE!
WELL, FINE, I'M GETTING MY
STUFF, AND I'LL LEAVE.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT HE WANTED.
IT'S NOT WHAT HE WANTED.
I KNOW.
HE JUST REALLY--
[crying] HE REALLY DOES CARE
ABOUT YOU GUYS.
[clattering]
>> JOSHUA!
STOP THROWING THINGS AROUND!
>> HEY, I JUST GOT KICKED OUT
OF MY HOUSE, AND ME AND EBONY
ARE WALKING TO HER HOUSE
RIGHT NOW.
WE NEED A RIDE.
WHAT IS SHE DOING?
>> GET YOUR HAPPY ASS BACK TO
THE HOUSE.
>> NO.
>> GET YOUR [bleep].
WE'LL TAKE YOU.
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA WALK YOUR
PREGNANT GIRLFRIEND FIVE MILES.
>> I'M GETTING A RIDE RIGHT
NOW.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M GETTING A RIDE RIGHT NOW.
NO, I GOT A RIDE RIGHT NOW.
>> WITH WHO?
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M GETTING A RIDE.
>> SO YOU'RE GONNA STAND OUT
HERE WITH EBONY WHEN IT'S
20 DEGREES OUT--
>> SHE'S FINE.
SHE'S FINE.
>> YEAH, THAT'S ABOUT THE MOST
RESPONSIBLE THING YOU'VE DONE--
[yelling indistinctly]
>> WHATEVER.
>> I'VE ALWAYS STUCK BY JOSH,
BUT NOW THAT OUR LITTLE FAMILY
IS OUT IN THE COLD,
I'M WONDERING WHY I SACRIFICED
SO MUCH TO GET HERE.
COME ON.
JOSH NEEDS A PLACE TO CRASH NOW
THAT HE CAN'T STAY AT HIS
PARENTS' HOUSE.
JOSHUA, GET UP.
>> I AM UP.
>> EVEN FURTHER UP.
SINCE I CAN'T GO INTO THE AIR
FORCE, OUR PLAN IS FOR JOSH
TO ENLIST AND TAKE CARE OF ME
AND THE BABY, WHICH MEANS
FOR NOW, I'M STUCK TAKING CARE
OF HIM.
CAN YOU MAKE SOME BISCUITS
FOR ME, JOSH?
>> HEY.
>> WATCH OUT.
>> MY AREA IS--
>> NO, NOT CRESCENTS.
>> CROISSANTS.
>> I SAID BISCUITS.
I DID NOT SAY THEM.
I SAID NONE OF THEM.
I SAID BISCUITS.
HMM.
HEY, MADRE.
>> HEY.
NOW, JOSH, DID YOUR FAMILY
CALL YOU?
>> NO, BET YOU THEY'LL CALL ME
TOMORROW, THOUGH.
OW.
>> YOU JUST GONNA STAY HERE?
YOU GONNA ATTEMPT TO CALL THEM,
OR ARE YOU JUST GONNA...
>> GONNA LET THEM CHILLAX FOR
A LITTLE BIT, AND THEN THEY'LL
PROBABLY CALL ME, AND...
I'LL JUST STAY HERE
AND JUST GO TO SCHOOL.
[chime dings]
>> JOSH'S PARENTS DIDN'T CHILLAX
FOR LONG BEFORE CALLING US OVER
TO WORK THINGS OUT.
>> YOU GUYS ARE LIVING
IN A FANTASY WORLD, AND ALL
WE'RE TRYING TO DO
IS GET THROUGH TO YOU.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO LIVE
IN A FANTASY WORLD.
I'M TRYING TO GROW UP AND FIGURE
THINGS OUT.
I MEAN, YEAH, I'M GONNA NEED
HELP FROM YOU GUYS.
I'M NOT SAYING I'M--
I DON'T WANT YOU GUYS OUT OF MY
LIFE AT ALL, BUT I DO NEED TO
GROW UP, AND I DO NEED TO LEARN
SOME THINGS, AND I'M GONNA
EITHER SINK OR SWIM.
>> YOU GUYS WANTED TO DO THESE
THINGS AND LEARN LIFE AS IT
CAME, BUT YOU HAVE A BABY,
AND THAT'S WHERE THE MATH
DOESN'T COME UP.
IF YOU CAN'T--
THE BABY CAN'T GO HUNGRY.
THE BABY CAN'T GO WITHOUT
CHANGING ITS DIAPERS, 'CAUSE
THAT'S WHAT YOUR TOMORROWS
ARE ALL ABOUT NOW.
AND YOU GOT--YOU GUYS HAVE GOT
TO BE SCARED TO DEATH.
I CAN'T UNDERSTAND HOW YOU
WOULDN'T BE.
I WAS.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND THE
SIGNIFICANCE OF IT.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE I KNOW
WHERE YOU ARE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE MOVING OUT, RIGHT?
THIS DECISION CAN'T
WAIT ANYMORE.
I'M TIRED OF WAITING.
WE DON'T WANT YOU GUYS TO MOVE
OUT.
>> OKAY, AND--OKAY, 'CAUSE I
DON'T WANNA MOVE OUT.
I DON'T WANNA MOVE OUT AT ALL.
THAT'S MY DECISION.
I DON'T WANNA MOVE OUT, BUT...
SHE'S PRETTY DARN CLOSE,
SO I'M GONNA STAY WITH HER
AT HER HOUSE...
>> AND THAT'S FINE.
>> UNTIL THEN, AND THEN SWITCH
OFF.
>> OKAY, DON'T RUB MY STOMACH.
IT HURTS.
THANKS.
[sighs]
I CAN'T WAIT TO HAVE MY BABY.
I WANT HER OUT SO BAD,
I'VE STARTED LOOKING FOR SIGNS.
[bell dings]
WHEN THE BALLOON FINALLY SINKS,
SHE'LL COME OUT.
IT'S BEEN FLOATING THE ENTIRE
TIME UNTIL RECENTLY, AND IT
JUST--WELL, IT SANK TODAY.
UNUSUAL.
VERY UNUSUAL.
>> YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
>> IT'S JUST FLOATING THERE.
>> I THINK, YEAH, I THINK YOU'RE
JUST--
I THINK YOU'RE JUST ANXIOUS.
SHE'S GONNA COME OUT WHEN SHE'S
DAMN WELL READY.
IF IT FALLS TO THE GROUND
AND YOU SUDDENLY GO INTO
LABOR...
>> [laughs]
>> I WILL KISS YOUR BIG TOE.
>> GOOD.
[laughs]
IT'S A DEAL.
IT'S A PINKY SWEAR.
I'VE BEEN HAVING CONTRACTIONS,
LIKE, CONSTANTLY EVERY FIVE
MINUTES.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> I'M IN PAIN.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> TIRED.
>> DO YOU THINK SHE'S GOING
INTO LABOR, OCEAN?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DO?
>> YEAH, DUDE, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
THE BABY.
>> EXPLAIN WHAT YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH.
>> PAIN, THAT'S WHAT I'M GOING
>> PAIN?
>> YEAH.
>> A LOT OF PAIN?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU READY?
>> THEY SAY PAIN WILL
MAKE YOU STRONGER.
PAIN SUCKS [bleep].
'CAUSE I WILL KICK THEIR ASS.
>> WE'RE ALMOST THERE RIGHT NOW.
>> JOSHUA, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
KISS MY BIG TOE.
>> ♪ IT'S FOUR IN THE MORNING
♪ CAN'T SEE STRAIGHT
>> TEN, NINE, EIGHT, SEVEN, SIX,
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
COME ON, GIRL.
GO, GO, GO.
>> PUSH!
PUSH, COME ON, PUSH.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
COME ON, BABY, PUSH.
COME ON, COME ON.
OKAY, ONE MORE TIME.
PUSH, PUSH!
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> OH!
>> DO YOU WANT HER TO GO THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> THERE YOU GO.
LOOK AT HER.
LOOK HOW CUTE SHE IS.
OH.
>> ♪ FREE TO ROAM
♪ MAKE A HOME IN MY HEAD
>> HEY.
HEY.
[smooch]
>> OH.
>> [smooch]
>> HOLDING HER, JOSH LOOKS LIKE
A DAD ALREADY.
I HOPE HE CAN ACT LIKE ONE TOO.
>> OH, MY GOD, LOOK HOW TINY
SHE LOOKS IN THERE.
>> HOLD ON, I CAN'T LOOK UP
RIGHT NOW.
>> JOSH, YOU DON'T HAVE
TIME FOR GAMES.
YOU HAVE A BABY NOW.
[laughter]
I'M JUST TELLING YOU, 'CAUSE
WHEN YOU LEAST EXPECT IT,
THEY'LL DO IT, 'CAUSE IT
HAPPENED TO AUNTIE DAWN.
>> WHAT?
>> THE CAT GOT IN THE CRIB
WITH SARAH, BECAUSE THEY SMELL
THE MILK ON THEIR BREATH.
>> OH.
>> THEY DON'T--THEY'RE NOT
TRYING TO HURT THE BABY.
THEY JUST DO, BECAUSE THEY
SMOTHER THEM, 'CAUSE THEY'RE
TRYING TO GET THE MILK.
>> HEY, JOSHUA.
>> WHAT?
>> BABE, CAN YOU GET ME SOME
SOCKS, PLEASE?
>> NO.
SOCKS FOR WHO?
YOU OR JOCELYN?
>> FOR HER.
[baby crying]
>> [mock crying]
>> THOSE ARE TOO BIG.
[baby crying]
TOO BIG.
CAN YOU GET THE LITTLE SOCKS,
LIKE, THE WHITE ONES THAT HAVE
THE FUZZ ON THEM?
[baby crying]
>> JOSHUA!
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A--
>> HEY, JOSH.
JOSH.
>> WHAT?
>> GUESS WHAT.
>> CHICKEN BUTT.
>> YOU SHOULD--YOU'RE A DAD NOW,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I WOULD SAY SO.
>> SHOULDN'T BE ACTING
LIKE A FIVE-YEAR-OLD.
[baby cooing]
BABY GIRL, BABY GIRL.
JOSH HAS TO FOCUS ON GRADUATING
HIGH SCHOOL.
AND WITH MY MOM AT WORK,
I'VE BEEN LEFT ALONE A LOT
WITH JOCELYN.
YEAH, ARE YOU HUNGRY?
I BETTER GET USED TO IT,
BECAUSE JOSH WILL BE TAKING OFF
TO THE AIR FORCE IN A COUPLE
MONTHS.
>> NICE, ISN'T THAT?
SHE CAME OUT LOOKING
LIKE A WHITE GIRL.
>> WITH BLACK PEOPLE HAIR.
>> YEAH.
SHE JUST SEEMS SO PEACEFUL NOW,
NO CARES OR NOTHING.
SHE JUST DREAMS, POOPS,
AND EATS.
WOULDN'T THAT BE GREAT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> JUST TO EAT, POOP, AND DREAM.
[chime dings]
>> I WAS WORRIED THAT WAS GONNA
BE HIS GAME PLAN.
BUT FOR NOW, IT LOOKS LIKE JOSH
IS GONNA SCRAPE BY AND GRADUATE.
I, ON THE OTHER HAND, AM HAVING
A HARDER TIME PULLING IT ALL
TOGETHER.
YEAH, IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD
CHANGING A DIAPER IN THE SCHOOL
PARKING LOT, JUST A TINY BIT.
>> I BET YOU NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D
BE DOING THAT AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE YEAR, DID YOU?
>> NOPE, SURE DIDN'T.
GROSS.
I'M WORRIED I'M MISSING TOO MUCH
SCHOOL TO GRADUATE, SO I'M
MEETING WITH MY SCHOOL
COUNSELOR.
>> YOU ONLY NEED, WHAT, 5.6
TO GRADUATE.
IF YOU'RE WITHIN ONE OR TWO
CREDITS, YOU CAN STILL WALK.
YOU CAN STILL GRADUATE,
GO THROUGH THE CEREMONY.
BUT YOU SHOULD BE FINE TO
GRADUATE AND EVERYTHING,
JUST AS LONG AS YOU GET THOSE
OTHER TWO CREDITS DONE.
>> OKAY.
>> MY QUESTION IS, YOU JUST
SAID YOU HAVE TO FINISH TWO
BEFORE GRADUATION.
>> YES.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA DO THAT
PRIOR TO GRADUATION SO THAT
YOU CAN WALK ACROSS THE STAGE?
THAT'S MY QUESTION.
>> I MEAN, I, IF I GET THEM AT
NIGHTTIME, THEN...
SHE'D BE FINE.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE'D BE FINE BEING WATCHED
BY JOSH.
>> WE NEED TO DISCUSS THIS,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, JOSH NEEDS
TO GRADUATE...
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND YOU NEED TO GRADUATE.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, SO IT'S JUST--
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO WATCH HER,
BUT HE STILL NEEDS TO GET HIS
WORK DONE.
>> HE CAN.
I CAN WATCH JOCELYN WHILE HE'S
AT SCHOOL, AND WHEN HE GETS OUT
AT THREE, HE'LL COME HOME AND
WATCH HER SO I CAN TAKE MY
CLASSES.
WE'LL MAKE A TRADE-OFF.
MM-HMM.
[Beethoven's Fur Elise]
♪
SO WHILE JOSH IS AT SCHOOL,
I'M KEEPING UP MY PART OF THE
PLAN BY TAKING CARE OF JOCELYN.
[yawning]
IT'S THREE O'CLOCK, AND I'M
READY FOR JOSH TO COME HOME
AND HELP.
[humming Beethoven's Fur Elise]
♪
BUT SO FAR, JOSH ISN'T KEEPING
UP WITH HIS SIDE OF THE DEAL.
MY PLAN TO GRADUATE DEPENDED
ON JOSH BEING SUPPORTIVE...
AND GETTING HOME ON TIME.
>> HOW'S IT GOING?
>> GREAT, YOU'RE A LITTLE LATE.
THIS IS NOT WORKING FOR ME,
'CAUSE DOING THIS THREE DAYS
A WEEK AND YOU NOT--YOU BARELY
MAKING IT HOME ON TIME IS MAKING
ME LATE FOR MY CLASSES.
THIS IS A LOT OF WORK.
THIS IS A LOT OF STRESS, AND...
>> WELL, WE COULD JUST NOT GO,
AND WE CAN GO HANG OUT WITH
LYDELL AND SHEDORI.
THEY'RE ACROSS THE STREET
WAITING FOR US IMPATIENTLY.
>> UH-HUH.
>> ♪ SO TIRED OF THIS
♪ HEAVY LOAD
♪ I'VE BEEN CARRYING
♪ FOR SO LONG
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT WANTS
♪ WITH ME
♪ OH, LORD, PLEASE LET ME BE
>> ALL HE REALLY WANTS TO DO
IS WHAT PISSES ME OFF, IS THAT
HE WANTS TO GO OUT WITH
HIS FRIENDS.
>> GUYS ARE RETARDED.
GUYS DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT YOU
CARRIED THE BABY.
YOU HAD TO GO FROM BEING YOUR
CUTE LITTLE PETITE SELF
TO SHAMU.
>> [laughs]
ALL THAT FREAKIN' WEIGHT.
EXACTLY.
NOW I JUST HAVE THE HUGE BOOBS
AND LEAKING FLUIDS.
>> AND EMOTIONS
UP THE YING-YANG.
>> YES, EXACTLY, I DON'T HAVE
THE EMOTIONAL CONTROL,
AND HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
I FEEL LIKE ALL THE STRESS
HAS BEEN PUT ON ME,
AND I'M JUST--
I'M A LITTLE MAD ABOUT IT.
>> YOU CAN'T JUST BE THE PERFECT
LITTLE HOUSEWIFE THAT TAKES CARE
OF THE BABY ALL THE TIME,
YOU KNOW?
>> [crying] LIKE, I'M JUST THE
ONE THAT GREW UP TOO FAST.
LIKE, I NEEDED TO.
AND I WANT HIM TO GROW UP TOO.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT HIM TO DO?
>> I KIND OF JUST WANT HIM TO
GET IT THROUGH HIS HEAD THAT I'M
NOT HAVING SUCH AN EASY TIME.
LIKE, HE DOES STEP UP WITH HER.
HE ALSO NEEDS TO BE THERE
FOR ME, SO...
[baby cooing]
[baby crying]
>> OH, WHAT?
>> HEY.
HEY, HEY.
JOCELYN, HEY.
YOU BE QUIET.
JOSHUA, CAN YOU PLEASE TAKE OUT
THE TRASH?
>> YES.
>> YOU'RE NOT DOING
ANYTHING ELSE.
CAN YOU PLEASE--
>> I'M SLEEPING, IF YOU HAVEN'T
NOTICED.
IF YOU STOP YELLING AT ME,
I'LL GO GET THE--
>> PLEASE TAKE OUT THE TRASH.
>> THINGS ARE OBVIOUSLY NOT
GOING TO GET BETTER BY
THEMSELVES.
>> SO WHY, EXACTLY, ARE YOUMAD?
>> I JUST NEED YOU TO CARE
SOME MORE.
>> ANYTHING I DO--I WANNA
GO OUT; I WANNA DO SOMETHING--
YOU GET MAD.
>> NO, JOSHUA, IT IS OKAY
TO GO OUT SOMETIMES.
IT REALLY IS.
BUT RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT
THE SAME.
IT'S NOT THE SAME GOING OUT.
YOU'RE HER FATHER, AND YOU NEED
TO ACT LIKE IT.
>> I DO ACT LIKE I'M HER FATHER.
WHAT THE [bleep] ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
AND I GOT SO MUCH [bleep]
THAT I NEED TO DO SO I COULD
PROVIDE FOR YOU AND JOCELYN.
I'M HERE ALL THE TIME,
NEXT TO YOU ALL THE TIME.
YOU WANT ME BY YOUR SIDE...
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> 24-7.
>> YOU'RE NOT MENTALLY THERE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT, LIKE,
THERETHERE.
YOU'RE PARTIALLY THERE.
>> HOW AM I PARTIALLY THERE?
>> YOU'RE JUST PARTIALLY THERE.
I MEAN...
NOT--I MEAN, YOUR HEAD'S
SOMEWHERE ELSE HALF THE TIME.
>> I'M SAYING I'M 18 YEARS OLD.
YOU'RE 17 YEARS OLD.
AND WE GOT A BABY.
I GOTTA--I'VE BEEN TRYING--
I'VE BEEN WORKING MY ASS OFF
JUST TO GRADUATE, AND THEN I
GOT TO WORRY ABOUT ENLISTING
INTO THE AIR FORCE, SO I'M NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO SEE YOU GUYS
THAT MUCH AT ALL.
SACRIFICES.
>> ♪ I'LL KEEP
♪ A LIGHT ON
>> SHE REALLY LOVES THAT SWING.
>> THE HARDEST THING ABOUT
THE FUTURE IS GONNA BE THE FACT
THAT WE'RE GONNA BE ON OUR OWN.
LIKE, WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE
OUR PARENTS ANYMORE.
AND WE'RE JUST GONNA BE OUT IN
THE OCEAN BY OURSELVES,
OUT IN THE BIG WIDE WORLD
ALL BY OURSELVES.
[chuckles]
>> YOU LOOKING AROUND?
LOOKING AT EVERYBODY?
CHECKING OUT ALL THE SALES?
>> I'M MORE SELF-RELIANT
THAN JOSH IS.
I'M OKAY WITH BEING THE ADULT
IN THE RELATIONSHIP.
>> MOMMY AND DADDY.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE GIVEN UP
A LOT MORE THAN JOSH HAS.
>> WOULD THE CLASS OF 2009
PLEASE RISE?
[crowd cheering]
>> WHOO!
I MEAN, I HAD TO SACRIFICE
GRADUATING, AND I SACRIFICED
GOING INTO THE AIR FORCE
AND, ACTUALLY, BEING A TEENAGER.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'LL FULLY
GROW UP, BUT I KNOW THAT HE'LL
GROW UP SOMEWHAT.
BUT I DON'T THINK HE'LL EVER
LOSE THE CHILD.
I THINK HE'LL ALWAYS BE CHILDISH
IN SOME WAY.
[smooch]
WHEN I THINK ABOUT JOSH LEAVING
FOR THE AIR FORCE, IT'S HARD
FOR ME TO BE APART FROM HIM
FOR VERY LONG, BUT IT'S BETTER
FOR THE BABY'S FUTURE SO THAT
WE CAN HAVE--WE CAN ACTUALLY
START OUR LIVES TOGETHER.
GETTING PREGNANT HAS CHANGED
MY VIEW OF LIFE.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT
SOMEBODY ELSE BEFORE YOU THINK
ABOUT YOURSELF.