>> HI, I'M JENELLE,
AND I'M FROM OAK ISLAND,
NORTH CAROLINA,
WHERE THE SURF IS GOOD
AND THE FISHING IS EVEN BETTER.
IT'S SUMMER, SO I SPEND
ALL MY TIME AT THE BEACH
OR OUT PARTYING, SINCE I'M NOT
IN SCHOOL.
>> YOU WANT TO JUST RUN OUT
EVERY NIGHT.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
[chime dings]
>> MY MOM AND I FIGHT A LOT
ABOUT HOW MUCH I GO OUT
AND ESPECIALLY ABOUT MY
BOYFRIEND, ANDREW.
>> WHAT HIS PLAN?
TO JUST COME AROUND ONCE IN
A WHILE AND HANG OUT HERE
AND SMOKE HIS CIGARETTES?
>> WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR THREE YEARS.
>> I REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME
I MET YOU.
I DIDN'T SAY NOTHING TO YOU.
I JUST WENT UP AND GRABBED YOU
AND KISSED YOU.
>> AND MY FRIENDS THINK
HE'S BAD NEWS, BECAUSE DESPITE
HAVING BEEN A MODEL, HE
CURRENTLY HAS NO JOB, NO CAR,
AND HE LIVES WITH HIS PARENTS
FOUR HOURS AWAY.
>> I HAD MY CARS.
I HAD MY MONEY.
I HAD--YOU KNOW, I HAD
TWO APARTMENTS IN NEW YORK.
>> AND, UH, NOW YOU LIVE
WITH YOUR PARENTS.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT EVERYONE BETTER GET USED
TO HIM, SINCE WE'RE IN IT
FOREVER NOW, BECAUSE I'M
PREGNANT.
EIGHT MONTHS ALONG,
MY PREGNANCY IS NOT EXACTLY
A SECRET, BUT FOR A WHILE,
IT WAS.
I DID NOT WANT TO TELL MY MOM.
>> REMEMBER, I KEPT SAYING TO
YOU, "ARE YOU PREGNANT?"
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT, REMEMBER?
BECAUSE YOU KNEW.
>> YEAH, I KNEW I KNEW.
I JUST DIDN'T TELL YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> I JUST FIGURED I WOULD--
YOU WOULD FIND OUT BY YOURSELF.
>> WELL, I FOUND OUT ALL RIGHT
THE DAY I WALKED IN,
AND YOU WERE TAKING A BATH,
AND I WALKED IN ON YOU,
AND I SAID--I LOOKED AT YOU
AND SAID, "JENELLE,
YOU'RE PREGNANT."
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU CAUGHT ME
OFF GUARD.
>> AND YOU GO, "NO, I'M NOT."
I SAID, "WELL, I'M BUYING
A PREGNANCY TEST,"
AND MADE YOU TAKE THEM.
IT WAS VERY UPSETTING.
I WAS VERY UPSET, BUT--
>> CAN'T DO NOTHING ABOUT
IT NOW.
EVEN THOUGH THE SHOCK VALUE
HAS WORN OFF, IT'S STILL
THE TOPIC OF EVERY CONVERSATION,
ESPECIALLY WHEN MY FRIENDS
ARE OVER.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU GIRLS THINK
ABOUT JENELLE BEING PREGNANT?
>> I WAS SHOCKED AT FIRST.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
JENELLE'S PREGNANT."
SHE'S REALLY PREGNANT.
SHE IS REALLY PREGNANT."
LIKE, NO, NOT JENELLE.
>> BECAUSE I SEEMED--
I SEEMED SO INNOCENT.
[laughter]
>> NO.
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> BUT DON'T YOU THINK THAT
SHE'S A LITTLE YOUNG?
>> THE WAY I SEE IT, IF YOU'RE
RESPONSIBLE ENOUGH TO HAVE SEX,
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE ENOUGH
TO CARRY A BABY.
>> THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
>> NOW SHE HAS TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> THAT'S THE CHOICE SHE MADE.
[chime dings]
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO GET
PREGNANT, BUT TRY EXPLAINING
THAT TO MY MOM.
THERE'S BEEN SO MUCH TO GET USED
TO SINCE I'VE BEEN PREGNANT.
I FIGURED I'D BE OUT PARTYING
EVERY NIGHT OF MY SUMMER
VACATION, BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D SPEND IT DECORATING
A BABY'S ROOM.
>> GONNA BE SO SMALL AND CUTE.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE DRESSING UP
A DOLL EVERY DAY.
DID YOU EVER DO THAT WHEN
YOU WERE LITTLE?
>> YEAH.
IT'S THE REAL THING NOW.
SO YOU'RE EXCITED TO BE
HAVING A BABY?
>> I MEAN, AT FIRST, I WASN'T.
>> WAS THERE EVER, LIKE,
ANY DOUBT IN YOUR MIND THAT YOU
WEREN'T GONNA KEEP IT OR...
>> NO, I DEFINITELY WAS
GONNA KEEP IT NO MATTER WHAT,
BUT MY MOM ALWAYS REMINDED ME,
"YOU KNOW THERE'S ABORTION.
YOU KNOW THERE'S ADOPTION."
AND I WAS LIKE, "I DON'T CARE.
I DON'T CARE."
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
LIKE, ABOUT SCHOOL AND, LIKE--
>> I'M GONNA COMPLETE SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW, ME AND THE BABY
ARE GONNA LIVE HERE.
AND THEN WHATEVER COLLEGE I DO
GO TO, I'M GOING TO TAKE IT
ONLINE.
BECAUSE I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO GO TO WORK AND GO TO SCHOOL
AT THE SAME TIME AND DO
ALL THAT.
>> DO YOU THINK--IF Y'ALL CAN,
LIKE, JUST WORK THROUGH THE
DRAMA WITH YOUR MOM AND ANDREW,
DO YOU THINK SHE'LL EVER BE
SUPPORTIVE OF YOU GUYS, LIKE,
EVER?
>> SHE--SHE'LL, LIKE, NEVER GIVE
HIM A CHANCE, I DON'T THINK.
SHE NEVER TRIES TO,
AND I DON'T THINK SHE EVER WILL.
ANDREW WILL BE VISITING SOON,
AND I KNOW I SHOULD STAY AND
TALK ABOUT IT WITH MY MOM,
BUT MY FRIENDS WANT TO GO
TO THE BEACH, AND NOTHING
GETS IN THE WAY OF THAT.
[lively rock music]
* *
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
I SPENT EVERY SUMMER SURFING.
BUT NOW I SPEND MY BEACH TIME
CLOSER TO THE SHORE.
LAUREN ASKED ME THE OTHER DAY,
SHE SAID, "SURFING WHILE
PREGNANT," SHE'S LIKE,
"YOU WANT TO TRY IT?"
I WAS LIKE, "I CAN'T LAY DOWN"
>> MY COUSIN WAS YOUR AGE
WHEN SHE GOT PREGNANT TOO,
AND SHE DIDN'T REALLY TAKE IT
AS WELL AS YOU ARE.
LIKE, SHE STILL WENT OUT
AND WENT TO THE CLUBS WHILE
SHE WAS PREGNANT,
LIKE, STUPID STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> I STILL GO OUT AND HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS, BUT I DON'T
TAKE IT TO--I TAKE IT TO
A CERTAIN EXTENT.
I'LL GO TO PARTIES AND STUFF,
BUT I WON'T DRINK.
>> MOST GIRLS WOULD JUST, LIKE,
GO OUT AND BE LIKE, "HEY, MOM,
YOU WANT TO WATCH MY KID?"
>> YEAH.
>> BUT YOU'RE GONNA STAY HOME
WITH YOUR KID AND, LIKE,
TAKE CARE OF HIM AND STUFF.
>> I'LL WATCH A MOVIE WITH HIM
OTHER THAN JUST GO OUT.
>> I CANNOT WAIT TILL SHE HAS
THIS BABY.
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT'S SO GREAT
ABOUT ME?
I FEEL LIKE I'M GOING TO BE
A GOOD MOM.
ONCE HE GETS OLD ENOUGH,
I'LL DEFINITELY BRING HIM
TO THE BEACH.
HE'S GONNA HAVE SO MUCH FUN.
ALL RIGHT, YOU READY?
>> YEAH.
>> I CAN SPEND THE WHOLE DAY
AT THE BEACH, BUT I STILL
HAVEN'T TOLD MY MOM ANDREW'S
ON HIS WAY OVER.
SO I BETTER TELL HER.
>> THIS IS HOW IT IS.
I MAKE THE RULES.
WHEN ANDREW COMES HERE,
I NEED TO TALK TO HIS MOTHER
AND SAY, "LOOK, YOU KNOW,
HE MAY COME, BUT HE MUST LEAVE
AT THIS TIME."
IT'S NOT NO FIVE-DAY HOLIDAY
HOTEL HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU DON'T PAY RENT.
>> YOU ALWAYS OVEREXAGGERATE.
YOU TALK ABOUT HOW MUCH FOOD
ANDREW EATS FROM US WHEN HE'S
HERE, HOW MUCH HE [bleep] USES
THE SHOWER WHEN HE'S HERE.
>> IF HE CAN PULL UP AND START,
YOU KNOW, HELPING YOU OUT
WITH THINGS FOR THIS BABY,
THEN MAYBE THINGS COULD CHANGE.
>> WELL, WHAT DOES HE THINK?
THIS BABY--HE'S NOT GONNA COME
LIVE HERE.
YOU KNOW, ALL WE WANT IS
WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T HAVE TO LIKE
ANDREW, BUT IF HE, YOU KNOW,
SHOWED YOU MORE SUPPORT...
>> WELL, GUESS WHAT, MOM.
NEWS FLASH:
JUST 'CAUSE HE CAN'T SUPPORT ME
FINANCIALLY, HE COULD SUPPORT ME
MENTALLY, MOM.
>> DO YOU KNOW--
>> IT'S WHO I'M HAPPY WITH,
AND I'M HAPPY WITH HIM.
>> MENTALLY ISN'T GONNA
PUT FOOD ON THE TABLE.
MENTALLY ISN'T GONNA
FEED THE BABY.
>> WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER
BECAUSE--
>> MENTALLY ISN'T GONNA BUY
THE DIAPERS.
>> BUT THE THING IS, I'M SAYING
IT DOESN'T MATTER, BECAUSE
NO MATTER WHAT YOU GUYS SAY,
IF YOU GET ME PISSED OFF,
I'LL GET MORE PISSED OFF,
AND SOONER OR LATER, I'LL JUST
LEAVE, AND I'LL LEAVE WITH HIM,
NEVER COME BACK.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT--
>> SO EITHER YOU ACCEPT HIM NOW,
OR LATER IN THE LONG RUN,
YOU'RE GONNA REGRET IT.
[chime dings]
ANDREW'S A PART OF MY FAMILY
NOW, AND MY MOM'S GONNA
HAVE TO GET USED TO IT,
WHETHER SHE LIKES IT OR NOT.
>> I GOT MY MOM TO AGREE
TO LET ANDREW VISIT, BUT HE
KNOWS HE'S NOT EXACTLY WELCOME
AT MY HOUSE.
SO ANDREW MADE SURE TO ARRIVE
WHEN MY MOM WAS AWAY AT WORK.
>> SEE, WHEN YOU'RE NOT HERE,
I DO EVERYTHING FOR MYSELF
'CAUSE I HAVE TO.
>> I'M GONNA BE MR. MOM.
ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
THE EMERGENCY ROOM, HOW MANY
PEOPLE IS GONNA BE THERE OR
WHATEVER, AFTER THE--YOU KNOW.
>> IN THE DELIVERY ROOM?
YOU AND MY MOM.
>> I'M JUST SAYING--
I MEAN, YOUR MOM, MM-MM.
IT'S GONNA BE JUST WILD.
I'LL BE LIKE, "OKAY, HONEY,
PUSH, PUSH."
"SHUT UP, ANDREW.
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH."
I'LL BE LIKE, "OH, SH..."
>> [laughs]
I HOPE NOT.
IS THAT BURNING IN THERE?
'CAUSE I SMELL SOMETHING.
>> YEP, THEY'RE BURNED.
[car horn honking]
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, LET'S GO.
MY MOM WILL BE HOME FROM WORK
SOON, SO TO AVOID UNNECESSARY
DRAMA, IT'S TIME TO GET OUT
OF THE HOUSE.
OH, THAT SUCKS.
>> WHY DIDN'T HER MOM LIKE YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> 'CAUSE SHE FOUND OUT YOU
DRANK A LOT.
>> GOING THROUGH MY LITTLE
PARTY STAGE AND ALL THAT.
>> YEAH, LOWLIFE.
>> YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
>> HE'S A ALCOHOLIC.
>> YEAH, I REALLY AM.
I'M A LOWLIFE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A LICENSE.
>> WOW, REALLY.
>> BUT HOW DID YOU GET PREGNANT?
WERE YOU ON BIRTH CONTROL,
OR DID YOU NOT USE A CONDOM?
>> WELL, ME AND ANDREW,
WE GOT IN AN ARGUMENT, SO WE
STOPPED TALKING FOR A COUPLE
DAYS, SO WHEN WE STOPPED
TALKING, I STOPPED TAKING
BIRTH CONTROL, AND THEN, YOU
KNOW, OF COURSE, WE GOT BACK
TOGETHER, AND WE DIDN'T USE
A CONDOM.
>> SO, LIKE, YOU WERE JUST
COMPLETELY UNPROTECTED?
>> YEAH, COMPLETELY.
>> YEP.
>> WERE YOU JUST NOT THINKING
ABOUT EVERYTHING YOU LEARNED
IN SEX ED?
WERE YOU THINKING THAT
ONE TIME WON'T HURT?
>> I MEAN, ME AND ANDREW DONE IT
OTHER TIMES BEFORE, BEFORE I GOT
ON BIRTH CONTROL, AND I DIDN'T
GET PREGNANT, SO I THOUGHT,
YOU KNOW, WHY WOULD IT CHANGE
NOW, THAT I WOULD JUST SUDDENLY
GET PREGNANT?
BUT I DID.
>> YEAH.
>> [sighs]
ANDREW LIVING SO FAR AWAY AND
BEING UNEMPLOYED HAS REALLY PUT
A STRAIN ON OUR RELATIONSHIP,
SO WE GOT TO FIGURE OUT HOW
WE'RE GONNA MAKE THIS WORK.
I KNOW YOU WOULD COME HERE
MORE OFTEN...
>> IF YOUR MOM WASN'T SUCH
A BITCH.
>> IF MY MOM WOULD LET YOU.
>> SHE SITS HERE, AND SHE
COMPLAINS THAT I CAN'T SUPPORT
THE CHILD.
>> YEAH, BUT CAN YOU SEE
WHERE SHE'S COMING FROM?
>> HONEY, I EVEN WENT TO
MCDONALD'S, AND I WAS
OVERQUALIFIED.
THAT'S KIND OF SAD, HONEY.
I MEAN, THERE'S NO JOBS.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING, YOU KNOW?
THE ECONOMY SUCKS RIGHT NOW
FROM THE DEPRESSION.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, SHE NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND, LOOK, MY LIFE
WAS STRAIGHT.
I DID HAVE A CAR.
SHE THINKS THAT I LIVED WITH
MY PARENTS ALL MY LIFE, BUT,
YOU KNOW, HERE'S THE THING,
THOUGH.
I'M GONNA BE HONEST WITH YOU.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU AND I AREN'T
GOING TO, YOU KNOW, LIKE,
SPLIT UP ANY TIME SOON.
WE'RE NEVER GONNA SPLIT UP,
YOU KNOW?
AFTER YOU GET FINISHED WITH
SCHOOL AND YOU TURN 18,
WE'RE GONNA GET MARRIED
OR SOMETHING.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA WORK OUT.
>> I HOPE IT DOES.
I WOULD REALLY LIKE YOU TO BE
HERE WHEN, LIKE...
>> NO, I'M NOT GONNA BE HERE--
>> WHEN MY WATER BREAKS, THOUGH.
>> I MEAN, THE THING IS--
>> I'LL CONVINCE MY MOM.
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
>> I'LL DO THAT.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> BUT CONVINCING MY MOM
IS MUCH EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
I WISH YOU'D JUST GIVE HIM
A CHANCE.
>> WHAT'S HIS PLAN NOW?
WHAT'S HE GONNA DO WHEN
HE HAS TO PAY CHILD SUPPORT?
I WISH THAT--
>> YEAH, YOU CAN'T STAND HIM.
I KNOW WHAT YOU WERE ABOUT
TO SAY.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF HE HAD A JOB AND WAS TRYING
TO MAKE MORE OF AN EFFORT TO
STAND BEHIND YOU AND THIS BABY,
THEN IT WOULD BE--
I'D BE OKAY WITH IT.
>> HE WANTS TO GET MARRIED.
BUT--
>> OH, MY GOD.
DON'T DO THAT.
>> HERE, PUT THOSE IN THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
THAT WOULD BE THE WORST MISTAKE,
TO DO THAT, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU DON'T WANT TO--YOU'RE NOT
DOING THAT, RIGHT?
>> I NEED TO GET A NAPKIN.
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> OBVIOUSLY, MY MOM IS NEVER
GONNA ACCEPT ANDREW.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> THE WEEKEND FLEW BY,
AND ANDREW'S DAD IS HERE
TO PICK HIM UP.
[car horn beeps]
IS THAT MY DAD?
>> YEP, HE'S WAITING OUTSIDE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
>> ANDREW MANAGED TO AVOID
MY MOM THE WHOLE TIME HE'S BEEN
HERE, BUT NOW SHE HAS SOMETHING
TO SAY.
>> BARNEY, BARNEY.
THIS ISN'T THE HOLIDAY HOTEL.
IT'S OUR HOUSE, AND HE NEEDS
TO RESPECT MY RULES.
ANDREW, I'VE KNOWN YOU
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
>> YEAH, I'VE KNOWN YOU TOO.
>> SINCE JENELLE'S BEEN WITH
YOU, THERE'S BEEN MAJOR,
MAJOR TROUBLE, AND NOW YOU
GOT HER PREGNANT.
YOU SAY A LOT OF LIES.
A LOT OF DRAMA'S BEEN GOING ON
SINCE YOU TWO MET.
THIS IS MY CHILD HERE
AND MY GRANDCHILD.
THINGS HAVE GOT TO CHANGE.
YOU GOT TO STEP UP MORE.
>> YEAH, YOU NEED TO MAN UP,
START BEING MORE RESPONSIBLE.
>> I LOOKED FOR A JOB, MAN.
>> BUT, ANDREW, SHE'S BEEN
PREGNANT EIGHT MONTHS, AND YOU
COULD HAVE GOT A JOB ANYWHERE,
AT MCDONALD'S.
>> I WAS EVEN OVERQUALIFIED
FOR MCDONALD'S.
MY DAD WAS THERE.
>> EVERYTHING THE BABY HAS
IS FROM ME.
ALL THE EXPENSE HAS BEEN
ON MY SHOULDERS.
>> WHAT?
DO YOU HAVE TO BE A [bleep]
MILLIONAIRE JUST TO [bleep]
CALM DOWN AND MAKE HER [bleep]
BE HAPPY?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T APPRECIATE YOU,
YOU KNOW, IN MY 16-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER'S BED HAVING SEX
IN MY HOUSE...
>> MOM, MOM.
>> WHETHER SHE'S KNOCKED UP
OR NOT.
>> GUESS WHAT.
NOTHING ELSE WORSE CAN HAPPEN,
MOM.
>> ANDREW'S VISIT MADE IT CLEAR
HE HAS NO PLANS TO MOVE CLOSER
OR GET A JOB.
MAYBE MY MOM WAS RIGHT.
IF I HAD A BABY LATER ON
IN LIFE, I WOULD HAVE MORE
MONEY, AND I CAN EVEN BUY
STUFF TODAY IF I WANTED TO.
>> DID YOU THINK THAT IT WAS
GONNA BE DIFFERENT?
LIKE, YOU AND ANDREW WERE
GOING TO BE DIFFERENT?
>> I THOUGHT ANDREW WAS GONNA
LIVE DOWN HERE WITH ME.
I THOUGHT HE WAS GONNA
HAVE A JOB.
SUPPORT ME AND THE BABY.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA MOVE--
BE MOVED OUT BY NOW AND HAVE
A CAR.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT
WAS GONNA HAPPEN,
BUT NONE OF IT EVER HAPPENED.
>> YEAH.
>> ANDREW REALLY NEEDS TO START
GROWING UP AND GETTING IT
TOGETHER, 'CAUSE THIS BABY
IS COMING SOON.
>> THESE LITTLE BUBBLES,
THAT'S ALL THE UMBILICAL CORD.
THERE'S A LITTLE HAND.
THERE'S A LITTLE FOOT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, MISS JENELLE,
WE'RE GONNA TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOME SIGNS OF LABOR THAT YOU
NEED TO LOOK OUT FOR, OKAY?
CONTRACTIONS, ANY BRIGHT RED
VAGINAL BLEEDING, ANYTHING LIKE
THAT, YOU NEED TO GO STRAIGHT
TO THE HOSPITAL,
BECAUSE PRETTY MUCH AT NEXT
WEEK, 38 WEEKS, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN REALLY GO INTO LABOR
ANYTIME.
WHY DON'T YOU SIT UP
SO YOU CAN GET OFF YOUR BACK?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THERE WE GO.
SO IS THE BABY'S DADDY BEING
SUPPORTIVE?
>> NOT REALLY, BECAUSE I THOUGHT
HE WOULD STEP UP WHEN HE FOUND
OUT I WAS PREGNANT.
HE ACTS LIKE HE'S A LITTLE KID,
AND IT'S, LIKE--IT'S STUPID.
>> THAT'S UNFORTUNATE,
BUT ONCE AGAIN, YOU'RE--
GOT YOUR MOM, WHO'S REALLY
SUPPORTIVE, AND HOPEFULLY,
HE'LL COME AROUND.
>> IT SUCKS THAT ANDREW ISN'T
SHOWING UP FOR THIS, BUT I'M
READY TO DO IT, WITH OR WITHOUT
HIM.
WITH THE BABY DUE AT ANY MOMENT,
IT'S TIME FOR MY SHOWER.
AND I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
ALL OF MY FRIENDS.
I'M GLAD I'LL BE GIVING BIRTH
OVER SUMMER VACATION 'CAUSE I'M
PSYCHED TO GET BACK TO SCHOOL
AFTER HE'S BORN.
>> OH, HOW CUTE.
>> THE LAST TIME THAT I SEEN
JENELLE WAS AT SCHOOL, AND SHE
WAS, LIKE, SKINNY.
>> KELLY'S, LIKE, GOING HOME.
>> YOUR STOMACH DOESN'T LOOK
THAT BAD IN THAT DRESS.
>> NO, IT'S BIG.
>> MAKE THE TEXT AND FORWARD IT
TO EVERYBODY, LIKE, WHEN YOU'RE
GETTING READY TO GO INTO LABOR.
>> EVERYBODY CAN COME
BUT ANDREW.
[laughter]
>> YOU'RE SO MEAN.
>> READY FOR CAKE?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU
FOR COMING.
ARE YOU LEAVING TOO?
EVEN THOUGH HE WAS THE BUTT
OF MY MOM'S JOKES, ANDREW KNEW
TODAY WAS MY BABY SHOWER,
AND HE DIDN'T EVEN BOTHER
TO CALL, SO I'M GOING OUT WITH
MY FRIENDS TO BLOW OFF SOME
STEAM AND GET HIM OFF MY MIND.
>> I REALLY WISH YOU'D STAY HOME
AND REST.
>> YOU'RE SO ANNOYING.
"YOU NEED YOUR REST.
YOU NEED TO GO TO SLEEP."
DA-DA, DA-DA, DA-DA.
I KNOW.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR IT AGAIN.
I REALLY DON'T.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
>> WHAT, MOM?
>> I THINK SINCE I DID ALL
THE WORK TODAY, SINCE IT'S YOUR
SHOWER, YOU COULD STAY HOME
AND HELP ME CLEAN UP.
>> I'M NOT CLEANING IT TODAY.
I'M WAY TOO TIRED TODAY.
>> GOT TO STOP BEING SO SELFISH.
YOU CAN FORFEIT ONE NIGHT
TO STAY HOME AND HELP ME.
>> MOM, OH, MY GOD.
TOMORROW, I WILL CLEAN
THE HOUSE.
I AM GOING, WHETHER YOU
LIKE IT OR NOT.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN WHEN THIS BABY COMES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHATEVER, MOM.
>> WELL, YOU'RE NOT GONNA DO
THIS WHEN THE BABY COMES,
JUST WALK OUT THE DOOR.
>> I'M GOING--
>> I'M JUST TELLING YOU.
>> OKAY, I'M DONE TALKING.
>> FINE.
>> I WISH MY MOM COULD JUST
UNDERSTAND THAT JUST BECAUSE
I'M PREGNANT DOESN'T MEAN
I HAVE TO STOP GOING OUT.
IT'S ON.
WHAT DRESS DO YOU WANT TO WEAR?
I WAS HAVING A GOOD TIME WITH
MY FRIENDS, BUT ANDREW STILL
HADN'T CALLED, SO I CAVED IN
AND TEXTED HIM.
HE'S PROBABLY GOING TO BE
PISSED, BECAUSE HE HATES WHEN
I GO OUT WITH MY FRIENDS.
>> WHY HAVEN'T YOU CALLED ME
ALL DAY?
>> I'M WITH MY TWO GIRLFRIENDS.
>> HE'S PISSED.
>> YOU KNOW HOW [bleep]-UP
YOU JUST SOUNDED?
>> THAT IS SO SCREWED UP.
YOU DON'T NEED HIM.
>> ANDREW, I'M NOT GROWN ENOUGH
TO HAVE A CHILD?
YOU HAVE NO JOB, AND YOU GOT
YOUR LICENSE TAKEN AWAY,
AND YOU'RE AN ALCOHOLIC.
WHO'S THE ONE THAT ISN'T
GROWN UP, ANDREW?
[chime dings]
>> I'M PREPARED TO DEAL WITH
ONE SCREAMING BABY BUT NOT TWO.
>> AFTER THE WAY ANDREW TALKED
TO ME LAST NIGHT, MY FRIENDS GOT
EVEN MORE CONCERNED ABOUT OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
>> USUALLY, I DON'T GET IN
PEOPLE'S RELATIONSHIPS, 'CAUSE
I KNOW I HATED IT WHEN PEOPLE
GOT IN MINE, BUT THE [bleep]
HE SAID TO YOU, IT WAS JUST...
>> UNNECESSARY.
>> LIKE, YOU DON'T SAY THAT
TO SOMEBODY THAT'S ABOUT TO
HAVE YOUR BABY.
>> HOW MUCH--LIKE, HOW MUCH
LONGER ARE YOU GONNA
KEEP LETTING IT GO?
'CAUSE HE HAD YOU SO UPSET.
LIKE, I REALLY THOUGHT YOU WERE
ABOUT TO JUST BREAK DOWN.
>> I'M GONNA SEE HOW
THINGS WORK.
IF HE DOESN'T STEP UP,
THEN I WILL LEAVE HIM,
'CAUSE I'M NOT GONNA SIT THERE
AND TAKE THIS.
>> DO YOU REALLY WANT YOUR BABY
TO BE AROUND SOMEBODY WHO'S
GOING TO TALK TO YOU LIKE A DOG?
LIKE, DO YOU WANT THAT?
LIKE, Y'ALL'S MAIN CONCERN RIGHT
NOW IS THAT BABY, AND, LIKE,
HOW IS HE SUPPOSED TO SUPPORT
THAT BABY WITH NO JOB,
NO CAR, OR ANYTHING?
>> THESE ARE GOOD QUESTIONS,
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE TIME TO ANSWER
THEM, BECAUSE TWO WEEKS LATER,
MY WATER BROKE EARLY.
>> I GOT A PEN.
>> I HAVE ONE.
>> I'M STILL PISSED AT ANDREW,
BUT I WANTED HIM HERE,
SO I TEXTED HIM.
>> AND HERE JENELLE IS,
IN LABOR, TEXTING ON HER
CELL PHONE.
[laughs]
>> EVEN THOUGH WE HADN'T TALKED
SINCE OUR BIG FIGHT...
>> HI, GUYS.
>> HE CAME.
>> OKAY, WE'RE JUST GONNA HAVE
YOU KIND OF TURN YOUR LEGS OVER.
>> ALL THE GIRLS ARE HERE.
>> HEY.
>> OKAY.
>> ONCE I GET STUFF SET UP
BACK HERE, EVERYTHING'S
GONNA BE STERILE.
>> [breathing heavily]
BEFORE I KNEW IT, IT WAS TIME
TO PUSH.
[chime dings]
>> COME ON, LET'S GO.
>> RIGHT DOWN YOUR BODY.
>> PUSH, PUSH, JENELLE.
PUSH, PUSH.
>> [gasps]
>> YOU'RE OKAY.
LET IT GO.
TAKE ANOTHER BREATH.
>> [gasps]
>> PUSH DOWN HARD.
>> AND AFTER 12 HOURS IN
LABOR...
>> * HELD ON AS TIGHTLY *
* AS YOU HELD ON ME *
* HELD ON AS TIGHTLY *
>> HEY, BUD.
HELLO AGAIN.
HERE, HOLD HIM.
[baby fusses]
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE CAME OUT
OF ME.
>> YEAH, I CREATED THAT.
WE CREATED THAT, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T THINK I'M SLEEPING
TONIGHT IF HE'S STAYING IN HERE.
THERE'S NO WAY.
>> WHY?
>> YOU KNOW, I'M JUST
GONNA STAY UP.
SEE, HE GETS TO GO HOME
WITH YOU.
I--HE CAN'T GO HOME WITH ME.
I'M GONNA CHERISH EVERY SINGLE
MOMENT I HAVE WITH HIM.
YOU KNOW?
>> IT'S NICE TO SEE ANDREW
ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT OUR BABY.
I HOPE IT LASTS.
AFTER STAYING UP ALL NIGHT,
ANDREW AND MY PARENTS LEFT
TO GET SOME REST, SO MY FRIENDS
CAME OVER TO KEEP ME COMPANY.
>> I WANT TO SEE HIM.
>> MORNING.
>> LADIES.
>> OH!
>> OH, MY GOD, HOW PRETTY.
>> OH.
>> DOESN'T HE LOOK JUST LIKE ME?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THE LIPS, THE FACE.
>> both: EVERYTHING.
>> WANT HIM, MOMMY?
>> YEAH.
[baby coos]
>> all: OH!
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> HE SAYS, "I WANT MY MOMMY."
>> OH.
>> IT'S LIKE HE'S NOT EVEN REAL.
>> I KNOW.
>> OH, LOOK AT HIM.
>> OH!
>> OH-HO-HO-HO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> IT'S WEIRD.
>> HUH?
>> I SAID, "IT'S WEIRD."
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU THINK STUFF WILL
CHANGE BETWEEN YOU AND ANDREW
NOW THAT YOU'VE HAD HIM?
>> I HOPE.
[baby fusses]
>> UH-OH.
>> DID YOU HEAR THAT?
>> YEP, [bleep].
>> THAT DON'T SOUND GOOD.
THERE YOU GO, MAMA.
THERE YOU GO.
>> DID YOU TAKE A POOPIE?
>> I'LL HELP YOU ON THE PEE-PEE
ONES.
THE [bleep] ONES,
YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
>> BEFORE WE CAN LEAVE THE
HOSPITAL, I HAD TO TAKE A CRASH
COURSE IN MOTHERHOOD.
>> THIS IS A LEARNING CURVE
FOR HIM AND FOR YOU,
JUST LIKE YOU'RE GONNA TEACH HIM
HOW TO TALK AND YOU'RE GONNA
TEACH HIM HOW TO WALK.
YOU'RE GONNA TEACH HIM HOW
TO EAT.
TO SLEEP.
WHICH SIDE DO YOU WANT
TO TRY ON FIRST?
>> UM, I'LL TRY ON THIS SIDE.
>> OKAY.
>> STARTING WITH
BREASTFEEDING...
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT.
PERFECT.
WHAT A NATURAL.
>> DIAPER CHANGES...
>> AND GO AHEAD AND TAKE
THAT ONE OFF.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HURT HIM.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA HURT HIM.
THEY DON'T LIKE THEIR DIAPERS
CHANGED.
THEY FUSS WHEN YOU CHANGE
THEIR DIAPER.
THAT'S JUST NORMAL, OKAY?
>> [giggles]
AND TO BURP IT.
>> OH, I THINK YOU JUST DID
A LITTLE POOP IN HIS PANTS.
>> ONCE THE BABY WAS BORN,
I THOUGHT THINGS WOULD GET
BETTER WITH MY MOM AND ANDREW,
BUT NOW THEY JUST IGNORE
EACH OTHER.
>> I THREW ALL THIS IN THERE
FOR YOU, IN THE BAG.
>> OH, DID YOU BRING
MY LIP RING?
>> YEAH, IT'S IN THERE.
SEE, RIGHT THERE?
>> HE AGGRAVATES ME, BUT YOU--
>> I KNOW, BUT, MOM, WHEN HE
DOES NOT SAY ONE WORD TO YOU,
LIKE, HE DOESN'T EVEN SAY
ANY WORDS TO YOU, AND YOU'RE
LIKE, "OH, WELL, HE AGGRAVATES
ME EITHER WAY."
I WANT YOU TO STOP ARGUING.
RIGHT NOW, ALL I NEED IS
SUPPORT FROM BOTH OF YOU GUYS,
NOT YOU GUYS BOTH FIGHTING.
>> I GIVE YOU MY WORD.
I WON'T SAY NOTHING ELSE.
HE'LL BE LONG GONE VERY SHORTLY.
>> DESPITE HER PREDICTION,
MY MOM AGREED TO GIVE ME
AND ANDREW SOME SPACE
SO WE COULD TALK.
>> WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
WE'VE BEEN THROUGH, YOU KNOW,
FIGHTS, EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WE WENT THROUGH STRONG FIGHTS
WHERE WE DON'T TALK TO EACH
OTHER.
YOU KNOW, JUST FORGET ABOUT
ALL THAT.
I THINK THOSE DAYS ARE
OVER WITH.
HERE'S THE PLAN.
HERE'S WHAT--YOU KNOW, YOU AND I
EVEN PLANNED IT, OKAY?
WHEN I MOVE, YOU KNOW,
AND GET ME A JOB, I'M GOING TO
SAVE MONEY TO GET A CAR.
AND YOU'RE GONNA--AS SOON AS YOU
GRADUATE FROM SCHOOL, YOU'RE
GONNA MOVE IN WITH ME.
WE TALKED ABOUT GETTING MARRIED,
AND YOU AGREED TO IT, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I'M, LIKE, AGREEING TO THIS,
BUT I'M JUST SAYING, YOU BETTER
NOT [bleep] IT UP, BECAUSE ONCE
YOU DO, I WILL BE GONE.
>> I DON'T THINK I EVER WILL
[bleep] IT UP.
>> OKAY.
>> I SERIOUSLY WON'T.
I WON'T MESS IT UP.
>> I DON'T EVEN WANT TO HEAR IT.
I JUST WANT TO SEE IT, ANDREW,
BECAUSE I WAS HEARING THAT
FOR FOREVER NOW.
>> YOU TRY TO BE IN MY SHOES,
SEE HOW DAMN EASY IT IS.
I'M HERE, 100%, RIGHT NOW,
EMOTIONALLY, BUT YOU KNOW,
FINANCIALLY, NO, I CAN'T DO IT
RIGHT NOW.
I'M SORRY, BUT DAMN IT
IF I CAN'T LOVE HIM.
>> I REALLY DO WANT
TO BELIEVE HIM.
>> THE NEXT DAY, ANDREW WAITED
FOR MY MOM TO LEAVE, AND THEN
HE SAID HIS GOOD-BYES.
IT REALLY SUCKS HE LIVES
FOUR HOURS AWAY.
>> HONEY, I REALLY DO GOT TO GO.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE, THOUGH.
BUT THEN AGAIN, I'LL SEE YOU
NOT THIS WEEKEND BUT
NEXT WEEKEND.
COME HERE.
LOVE YOU, LITTLE MAN.
YEAH, YOU LOOK AT ME.
I'LL BE BACK TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
OKAY?
I'LL CALL YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
BYE-BYE, LITTLE ONE.
>> COME ON, JACE,
YOU HANDSOME LITTLE BOY.
JACE, YOU READY TO ROLL?
>> BEFORE I KNEW IT,
IT WAS TIME TO TAKE JACE HOME
AND TRY TO DO THIS FOR REAL.
>> WHERE IS THIS GOING TO?
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> IT'LL TIGHTEN UP WHEN THEY--
IT WON'T GO ANYWHERE.
>> EVEN THOUGH ANDREW IS NOT
BY MY SIDE, I HAVE MY MOM,
HER BOYFRIEND, AND MY FRIEND
AMBER TO HELP ME WITH JACE'S
FIRST DAY HOME.
>> HE LIKES IT HERE.
[laughs]
>> HE'S HERE FIVE MINUTES,
AND HE LIKES IT HERE.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
>> HE'S LIKE, "PAPA, SAY HELLO."
[Jace gurgles]
>> [laughs]
I THINK YOU'RE POOPING.
>> I THINK HE'S DONE.
[Jace cries]
>> MY FIRST WEEK HOME WITH JACE
IS A LOT HARDER THAN I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE.
WHAT DO YOU KEEP KICKING ME FOR?
I HAVE NO TIME TO MYSELF,
AND ANDREW HASN'T CALLED ONCE,
MUCH LESS MADE A PLAN TO COME
VISIT.
AH.
>> [sneezes]
>> WHY DO YOU KEEP SQUIRMING?
>> [cries]
>> HEY, STOP, STOP.
[Jace fussing]
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THINGS ARE GETTING
EVEN HARDER.
JACE ISN'T SLEEPING AT NIGHT,
AND NEITHER IS ANYONE ELSE.
>> YOU HAVE TO MAKE BOTTLES.
>> SO MY MOM IS STARTING TO TAKE
THE LEAD, SINCE WATCHING JACE
IS JUST TOO MUCH FOR ME.
[Jace cries]
>> THE BABY NEEDS A BOTTLE.
YOU GONNA TAKE HIM?
>> I NEVER THOUGHT I CAN GO
THIS LONG WITHOUT SLEEP.
ISN'T THE BABY GOING TO
DAY CARE WHILE I GO TO SCHOOL?
>> HE STARTS THIS COMING WEEK.
>> I CAN'T WAIT FOR THAT.
>> IT'S WEEK THREE, AND
I FINALLY HEARD FROM ANDREW.
BUT WHAT HE HAD TO SAY MADE ME
EVEN MORE ANGRY.
LAST NIGHT, I GOT A CALL FROM
ANDREW SAYING THAT HE WENT TO
JAIL FOR A D.U.I. CHARGE.
>> I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
YOU CAN'T BE WITH THIS GUY
WHO'S A DRINKER.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, MOM.
>> AND YOU KNOW, HE HASN'T DONE
ANYTHING FOR THE BABY,
AND I DON'T THINK HE'S CAPABLE.
AND I THINK THAT YOU BETTER
START, YOU KNOW, PUTTING HIM
BEHIND YOU, AND BABY'S FATHER OR
NOT, LIKE I TOLD YOU, I SAID,
YOU KNOW, HE'S JUST THE SPERM
DONOR, REALLY, BECAUSE YOU NEED
TO JUST THINK OF YOURSELF NOW
AND THE BABY.
I JUST DON'T THINK HE'S
THE PERSON FOR YOU.
>> LIKE, I WANT HIM DOWN HERE
FOR THE BABY, BUT I MEAN,
IF HE'S GOING TO DRINK,
I DON'T WANT HIM DOWN HERE.
>> YOU KNOW, I TOLD YOU A LONG
TIME AGO TO MAKE A LIST.
MAKE A LIST, ALL OF ANDREW'S
GOOD POINTS AND ALL HIS BAD
POINTS.
YOU BETTER DECIDE, YOU KNOW?
[chime dings]
>> IT'S HARD TO MAKE THE CASE
THAT ANDREW'S PROS OUTWEIGH
HIS CONS.
NOW ADD CALLING DRUNK
THE DAY HE GOT OUT OF JAIL.
IT'S A NO-BRAINER.
I WAS LIKE, "ANDREW."
I HAD TO SAY "ANDREW," LIKE,
TEN TIMES FOR HIM TO SAY,
"WHAT?"
>> AND HE'D BE LIKE--
HE WAS TALKING LIKE THAT.
>> UH-HUH.
I WAS LIKE, "YOU JUST GOT
OUT OF JAIL?"
I WAS LIKE, "AND YOU DON'T CARE
NO MORE."
HE WAS LIKE, "NO."
>> IF HE'S DRINKING AGAIN
ALREADY SINCE HE'S OUT OF JAIL,
I MEAN, HE AIN'T GONNA STOP.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I TOLD HIM.
>> HE HAS A PROBLEM.
I WOULD NOT WANT AN ALCOHOLIC
AROUND MY BABY.
IF IT WAS ME, I WOULD NOT WANT
IT AROUND IT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> 'CAUSE HE JUST TREATS YOU
LIKE DIRT, AND, LIKE, HOW DO
YOU KNOW THAT HE'S NOT GONNA
DO THE SAME WITH THE BABY?
>> YEAH.
I'M GOING TO CALL ANDREW.
[line ringing]
HEY.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP,
BEAUTIFUL GIRL?
>> ANDREW, AFTER YOU DRANK
LAST NIGHT WAS THE LAST STRAW
FOR ME.
>> EVERY TIME I TRY TALKING
TO YOU ABOUT YOU DRINKING
AND BEING AN ALCOHOLIC,
YOU DON'T CARE.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T
LISTEN TO NO ONE.
EVEN SEVEN DAYS IN JAIL,
AND YOU GET OUT, AND YOU START
DRINKING AGAIN.
WHAT KIND OF [bleep] IS THAT,
ANDREW?
>> SENDS YOU A BULL[bleep]
LETTER.
>> HOW CAN YOU CARE FOR THE BABY
IF YOU DON'T CARE FOR ME?
YOU GOT TO CARE FOR THE PERSON
THAT'S HOLDING THE BABY, ANDREW.
>> DO YOU WANT TO BE WITH ME?
DO YOU NOT WANT TO BE WITH ME?
>> WELL, EVER SINCE YOU'VE BEEN
GOING TO JAIL, AND EVER SINCE
YOU CANNOT STOP DRINKING,
MY FEELINGS HAVE ALSO DROPPED
FOR YOU.
>> WELL, DON'T CALL YOU ANYMORE.
>> DON'T CALL YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, OH, TRUST ME,
I WON'T CALL YOU AGAIN.
IT'S BASICALLY OVER.
BYE.
>> REALLY?
FINE.
>> TOTALLY SHOULD HAVE LEFT HIM
A LONG TIME AGO.
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> HE'S A [bleep].
>> OH, WELL.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D HAVE TO
RAISE THIS BABY ALONE,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I'M GOING TO BE DOING.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> I'M GOING OUT.
ALTHOUGH MY MOM DOESN'T WANT ME
GOING OUT TONIGHT, I'M LEAVING
JACE WITH HER SO I CAN BLOW OFF
SOME STEAM WITH MY FRIENDS.
[laughter]
YAY.
MY MOM DOESN'T UNDERSTAND WHY
I WANT TO GO OUT, BUT I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHAT THE PROBLEM IS.
JACE DOESN'T NEED ME.
HE'S GOT MY MOM.
[alarm clock beeping]
AFTER BEING OUT ALL NIGHT,
GETTING UP IN THE MORNING
IS TOUGH, BUT I'M EXCITED
SCHOOL IS STARTING AGAIN.
>> COME ON.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
HA, I THINK YOU'RE DONE.
>> MY MOM'S TAKING CARE OF JACE
AND GETTING HIM TO DAY CARE.
>> HERE WE GO BYE-BYE.
>> AND I CAN FINALLY FOCUS
ON MY SOCIAL LIFE.
IT'S GREAT TO BE BACK IN SCHOOL
WITH PEOPLE MY OWN AGE AND AWAY
FROM ALL MY DUTIES AS A MOM.
[school bell rings]
AND WHAT'S COOL ABOUT DAY CARE
IS THAT I HAVE TIME TO HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS AFTER SCHOOL
BEFORE MY MOM COMES HOME
WITH JACE.
>> WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU SAW ANDREW?
>> OH.
LAST TIME I SEEN ANDREW
WAS WHEN THE BABY WAS BORN.
THAT'S IT.
>> THAT DAY?
OR DID YOU SEE HIM, LIKE, AFTER?
>> THE DAY HE LEFT, WHICH WAS,
LIKE, TWO DAYS AFTER
HE WAS BORN.
>> IS HE STILL TRYING TO HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU?
>> NO.
AND HE HASN'T EVEN TRIED
TO SEE JACE.
[cell phone rings]
MY MOM.
HELLO?
I'M GETTING READY.
>> YOU NEED TO MAKE BABY
BOTTLES.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YES.
MAKE SURE YOU DO IT.
DON'T FORGET.
>> I WILL.
>> MAKE AT LEAST THREE.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
AFTER WORKING ALL DAY, MY MOM
WAS NOT IN THE MOOD TO WATCH
JACE TONIGHT, BUT MY FRIENDS ARE
THROWING A PARTY AT TORI'S,
AND I'M GOING.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> GOING OVER TORI'S.
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT GOING OVER--
>> I JUST SAID I'M GOING OVER
TORI'S, AND YOU SAID,
"FINE, THEN I'LL WATCH HIM.
DON'T THINK YOU'RE GOING OUT
FRIDAY."
>> THIS IS, LIKE, RIDICULOUS.
YOU'RE GOING OVER THERE
EVERY DAY.
I DON'T WANT YOU OVER THERE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT YOU
OVER THERE, JENELLE.
YOU KNOW, WHAT DO YOU GIRLS
THINK?
THIS--THIS IS A DOG?
YOU THINK THIS KID'S A DOG?
>> NO, WE DON'T--
WE KNOW IT'S NOT A DOG.
>> JENELLE, WHY IS IT YOU CAN'T
EVEN STAY HOME?
THIS STUFF ABOUT GOING OUT EVERY
NIGHT HAS GOT TO STOP.
>> I'M NOT GONNA GO OUT
EVERY NIGHT.
I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
>> YOU'VE BEEN GOING OUT EVERY
NIGHT THIS WEEK.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO RAISE IT,
SAY IT, AND THEN WE'LL FIND
A GOOD FAMILY WHO WILL RAISE IT.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
IS IT TOO MUCH WORK FOR YOU,
JENELLE?
IS THE RESPONSIBILITY TOO GREAT
FOR YOU, JENELLE, TO GIVE UP
YOUR FREEDOM?
IS IT?
JENELLE?
>> CAN YOU LEAVE ME ALONE?
OR I WILL LEAVE TONIGHT,
AND YOU WILL NEVER SEE ME
AGAIN, 'CAUSE I WILL LEAVE
AT THE SIGN OF BULL[bleep].
>> I'VE STOOD BY YOU FOR THESE
NINE MONTHS, BOUGHT YOU
EVERYTHING, GAVE YOU BABY
SHOWERS AND EVERYTHING,
AND WHEN I SAY TO YOU THAT YOU
SHOULD STAY HOME WITH THIS BABY,
THEN YOU NEED TO STAY HOME.
I'VE BEEN DOING--
>> ALL RIGHT, SO ARE YOU
GONNA WATCH HIM?
AM I TAKING HIM WITH ME?
'CAUSE I'M ABOUT TO LEAVE
RIGHT NOW.
>> TAKE HIM, AND WHEN HE GOES
SICK IN THE HOSPITAL--
>> HE'S NOT GONNA GO SICK.
HE'LL BE--
>> TAKE HIM, TAKE HIM!
>> HE'LL BE [bleep] FINE.
>> I KNEW THIS WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE YOU WERE
BEFORE YOU WERE PREGNANT.
>> SHE'S GOT TO BE RESPONSIBLE.
>> SHE'S NOT RESPONSIBLE!
>> I KNOW SHE'S NOT,
BUT SHE HAS TO START, UH,
BEING RESPONSIBLE.
>> I ALREADY HAD TO GIVE UP
MY BOYFRIEND.
[chime dings]
MY MOM IS CRAZY IF SHE THINKS
I'LL GIVE UP MY FRIENDS TOO.
>> THERE'S BEEN ZERO CONTACT
WITH ANDREW, AND BEING A SINGLE
MOM IS REALLY DEPRESSING.
SO I'VE BEEN GOING OUT WITH
MY FRIENDS A LOT.
MY MOM HAS BEEN WATCHING JACE
MORE THAN I DO, AND SHE'S NOT
TOO HAPPY ABOUT THAT.
>> YOU HAD THIS BABY, CORRECT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, WHO TAKES CARE
OF THE BABY?
ME.
>> YOU TAKE THAT WHOLE
RESPONSIBILITY, YOU KNOW--
>> YOU ARE NOT HERE.
>> CAN YOU--
>> YOU'RE NOT HERE, JENELLE.
DO YOU GET UP IN THE MORNING
AND TAKE CARE OF THE BABY...
>> MOM, WELL, GUESS WHAT.
>> AND GET HIM DRESSED
AND MAKE HIS BOTTLES?
>> GUESS WHAT.
>> WHAT?
NO, YOU'RE NOT HERE
HALF THE TIME.
>> CAN YOU LISTEN TO ME?
IF YOU DON'T SHUT UP,
I'M GOING TO WALK AWAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
GONNA BE TAKING OFF IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT AND NOT
COMING BACK.
>> MOM, DO YOU REALLY THINK
I WOULD TAKE OFF IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT AND LEAVE HIM
IN THE BED?
>> YEAH.
>> WHATEVER, MOM.
>> YOU HAVEN'T BEEN TAKING CARE
OF THIS BABY SINCE IT'S BORN.
[bleep]DAMN IT, STAY HOME
AND TAKE CARE OF THE KID.
YOU FEEL LIKE THIS BABY IS
LIKE A DOG OR A CAT
THAT LAYS ON THE COUCH.
"OH, I'M LEAVING."
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT
I FEEL LIKE?
>> "I'M LEAVING."
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT--
AND YOU KNOW--
>> "I'M GOING WITH ALL
THESE BOYS."
>> CAN YOU SHUT UP AND LISTEN?
>> "I'M GOING PARTYING."
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I FEEL LIKE?
I DON'T EVEN FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE MY MOM NO MORE.
AND I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO FOLLOW
ALL THESE RULES JUST TO LIVE
IN YOUR HOUSE.
WELL, GUESS WHAT.
WHEN I'M 18, I'M OUT.
>> YOU'RE OUT.
>> AND WHEN JACE COMES WITH ME,
YOU WILL NEVER SEE ME OR HIM
AGAIN.
>> THIS IS MY GRANDSON,
AND IT'LL BE A COLD DAY IN HELL
BEFORE YOU WALK AWAY AND NOT
HAVE SOMEBODY TAKE CARE OF
THIS BABY PROPERLY.
DO THE RIGHT THING FOR
THIS BABY.
>> DON'T EVEN TALK TO ME.
I DON'T EVEN WANT--
JUST GET OUT OF MY FACE.
I DON'T--
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
GET THE [bleep] OUT OF MY FACE.
>> I HAVE NOTHING MORE TO SAY
TO YOU.
I'M WAITING FOR YOU TO TURN 18.
YOU'RE OUT OF MY HOUSE.
>> YEP.
>> YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I GO THROUGH.
I'M SO STRESSED OUT.
>> YEAH, AND YOU THINK THAT
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
A NERVOUS BREAKDOWN.
>> YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT THIS LITTLE [bleep]
OF A DAUGHTER, YOU, WHO TAKES
OFF ALL THE TIME, AND I GOT
A GRANDSON BABY WHO I'M TAKING
CARE OF AND WORKING
A 40-HOUR JOB.
AND YOU, AND ALL YOU DO IS PARTY
YOUR ASS AROUND TOWN.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
AFTER OUR BIG FIGHT,
LAUREN AND AMBER STOPPED BY.
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN GOING OUT
SO MUCH WITH MY OTHER FRIENDS,
I HADN'T SEEN MUCH OF THEM
LATELY.
>> JENELLE.
>> I JUST HIT HER IN THE FACE
WITH THE UMBRELLA.
>> WITH THE UMBRELLA?
OKAY, LET ME SHOW YOU
THE BABY'S ROOM.
I'M HAPPY YOU GUYS STOPPED BY,
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN
YOU GUYS IN A WHILE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T WAIT TILL JACE
GETS OLD ENOUGH TO SAY "MOMMY."
>> I KNOW.
MY MOM GOES, "NO, HE'LL SAY
MAY-MAY FIRST, BECAUSE YOU'RE
NEVER AROUND."
>> MAY-MAY.
>> IS IT GETTING MORE EASIER FOR
YOU TO TAKE CARE OF HIM OR...
>> I LOVE TAKING CARE OF HIM.
LIKE, IT MIGHT NOT SEEM LIKE
I'M HERE A LOT, BUT I DO LOVE
TAKING CARE OF HIM.
AND I MEAN, I JUST MAKE TIME
FOR MYSELF.
AND THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN DOING,
MAKING TIME FOR MYSELF.
I MEAN, I MIGHT HAVE MADE--
>> BUT A LITTLE TOO MUCH TIME.
>> I KNOW, A LITTLE TOO MUCH.
MY MOM GOES, "OH, WELL, LAUREN
AND AMBER THINK THAT YOU'RE NOT
DOING GOOD AT ALL, AND THEY
THINK THAT YOU SHOULD STRAIGHTEN
YOURSELF UP AND DA-DA, DA-DA."
>> I MEAN, I DO THINK
YOU SHOULD STRAIGHTEN UP.
>> YEAH, I DO.
>> I SAID--HONESTLY, I SAID,
"I HAVE NOT TALKED TO THEM
FOR A WHILE.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON."
>> [sighs]
WE THINK THAT, YOU KNOW,
YOU WERE JUST GOING OUT,
PARTY, PARTY, PARTY.
PEOPLE AROUND THE COUNTY HAVE
TOLD US, BECAUSE EVERYBODY'S
SAYING, "OH, WELL, SHE'S
A [bleep] MOM, AND SHE DOESN'T
DO THIS FOR HER KID."
I THINK YOU NEED TO PROVE IT
TO THEM THAT YOU ARE A GOOD MOM
AND THAT YOU CAN DO IT
AND NOT JUST THAT YOU'RE NOT
A PARTY-PARTY GIRL.
DON'T GO OUT AS MUCH AS YOU'VE
BEEN DOING OR STAY GONE JUST
BECAUSE YOU AND YOUR MOM GET
IN AN ARGUMENT.
LIKE, COME HOME AND PROVE TO HER
THAT, "MOM, I WANT TO BE HERE
FOR JACE."
>> MM-HMM.
>> PEOPLE REALLY NEED TO KNOW
THAT YOU REALLY ARE TRYING.
>> YEAH.
[chime dings]
>> MY FRIENDS MAY HAVE A POINT,
BUT THEY JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW HARD THIS IS FOR ME.
>> I'VE STAYED HOME THE PAST
COUPLE OF NIGHTS, SO MY MOM AND
I ARE GETTING ALONG BETTER.
>> GOT HIM?
>> YEAH, I GOT HIM.
COOL--OW, OW, OW.
[groans]
DOES THIS COME OFF YOU, JACE?
OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS,
IT STARTED TO BECOME CLEAR
HOW BIG THIS RESPONSIBILITY IS.
GOD.
[Jace crying]
I NEVER THOUGHT MOTHERHOOD
WAS GOING TO BE THIS HARD,
AND I NEVER KNEW HOW MUCH
I WAS GOING TO MISS JUST BEING
A REGULAR TEEN.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT JACE?
HAS ANYTHING GOT A LOT EASIER?
>> IT'S JUST THE PART FROM WHERE
THEY'RE BORN UP TO ABOUT
A YEAR OLD IS THE HARDEST PART.
THEY NEED YOU EVERY SECOND,
ALL THE TIME.
AND LIKE, IF THEY START CRYING
AND IF YOU ALREADY CHANGED
THEIR DIAPER AND ALREADY FED
THEM, THEY WANT TO BE HELD
ALL THE TIME.
THEY'RE CLINGY.
IMAGINE BEING IN PRISON.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S LIKE,
BEING IN PRISON.
MY MOM, EVEN THOUGH WE DON'T
GET ALONG AND STUFF, YOU KNOW,
IF IT WASN'T FOR HER, I DON'T
THINK I'D BE ABLE TO DO IT.
I REALLY DON'T.
>> SHE HAS HELPED YOU OUT A LOT.
>> YEAH, I WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO DO IT.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT RIGHT NOW.
I WOULD NOT.
I WOULD BE CONSTANTLY MAKING
BOTTLES CONSTANTLY.
>> YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO GO OUT...
>> OH, NO.
>> AND GET AWAY FROM ANYTHING.
>> NEVER.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU'RE STILL
A KID, THOUGH, LIKE, YOURSELF.
>> I KNOW, AND THEN EVERYONE'S
LIKE, "OH, YOU'RE A MOM.
YOU'RE SUCH A HORRIBLE MOM
BECAUSE YOU GO OUT AND PARTY
AND DA-DA, DA-DA, DA."
I MAKE TIME FOR MYSELF.
I THINK ONCE I MATURE MORE,
I'LL GROW UP, AND I WON'T WANT
TO PARTY AS MUCH.
>> YOU HAVING A KID MADE ME
THINK A LOT, LIKE, A LOT.
>> SERIOUSLY, DON'T GET PREGNANT
UNTIL YOU ACTUALLY GET MARRIED,
GET A CAR, GET A JOB,
AND HAVE A STABLE HOUSE.
BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T,
IT'S HARD.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE DOING
EVERYTHING BACKWARDS IN LIFE.
AFTER THESE COUPLE OF MONTHS,
I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT BEING A MOM, AND I'M
STARTING TO REALIZE THAT
I'M NOT READY.
>> YOU LIKE THE JUMPING CHAIR.
LET'S GO IN THE JUMPING CHAIR.
WHAT YOU DOING, JACE?
>> HEY, JACE.
ANYWAYS, I WANT TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT MY DECISION.
I WANT YOU TO HELP ME RAISE HIM
WHILE I GET MYSELF ESTABLISHED.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO TAKE
CARE OF HIM NO MATTER WHAT
BECAUSE IT'S NOT HIS FAULT
HE'S BORN.
I'M GOING TO DO THAT AS LONG
AS THERE'S NOT DRAMA GOING ON,
OKAY?
>> OKAY, MOM.
>> I NEED YOU TO STEP UP
AND BE A RESPONSIBLE GIRL.
>> I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU
THAT EVEN THOUGH YOU BITCH AT ME
ALL THE TIME AND STUFF, I KNOW
THAT I COULDN'T DO THIS WITHOUT
YOU, SO...
>> WELL, I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT,
JENELLE, BECAUSE...
YOU KNOW, I KNOW WE DON'T GET
ALONG, BUT, JENELLE, YOU GOT TO
COME TO A POINT--WE GOT TO COME
TO A MIDDLE HERE FOR THIS CHILD.
YOU GOT TO SPEND A LITTLE MORE
TIME WITH HIM, I THINK,
AND I THINK THAT, YOU KNOW,
YOU HAVE TO START TAKING
A LITTLE MORE RESPONSIBILITY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, THIS IS
WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M FINISHING HIGH SCHOOL
IN JANUARY.
I'M GETTING A JOB.
>> THAT'S A GOOD PLAN,
AND I'LL SUPPORT YOU ON THAT,
AS LONG AS, YOU KNOW, YOU KEEP
YOURSELF TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, WHEN ALL PUSH COMES
TO SHOVE, YOU KNOW, JENELLE,
IT'S NOT ABOUT MATERIAL THINGS.
IT'S ALL ABOUT FAMILY.
THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO
TAKE CARE OF THE BABY.
HE NEEDS HIS DIAPER CHANGED.
[sniffles]
>> AS HARD AS IT IS FOR ME
TO ACCEPT IT, MY MOM IS THE
RIGHT PERSON TO LOOK AFTER JACE
RIGHT NOW.
EVEN THOUGH ME AND MY MOM FIGHT,
I KNOW SHE STANDS BY ME,
AND SHE'S GONNA BE THERE
NO MATTER WHAT.
I THOUGHT THAT BEING A MOTHER
WOULD BE, YOU KNOW, FAIRLY EASY.
I DIDN'T--I JUST LOOKED AT THE--
I LOOKED AT THE FUTURE, WHERE
HE SLEPT ALL THROUGH THE NIGHT
AND TAKING HIM OUT TO PARKS
AND HAVING A GOOD TIME WITH HIM.
BUT I DIDN'T LOOK AT THE PART
WHERE YOU CONSTANTLY HAVE
TO WAKE UP IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE NIGHT.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE TAKING CARE
OF, LIKE, TWO OF YOU.
ANDREW'S NOT THE PERSON THAT
I WOULD WANT TO HAVE A BABY WITH
NOW THAT I LOOK BACK ON IT,
BECAUSE HE'S JUST--HE HASN'T
CONTRIBUTED TO ANY OF--
ANYTHING, NOTHING.
I JUST WISH I WOULD HAVE WAITED
SO I COULD HAVE BEEN A MOM
THAT CAN GIVE HIM EVERYTHING
HE WANTS.
[chime dings]
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com