>> HI, MY NAME IS AMBER,
AND I'M JUST YOUR TYPICAL TEEN
FROM ANDERSON, INDIANA.
MY BEST FRIEND, KAYLA, AND I
ENTERTAIN OURSELVES THE BEST
WE CAN IN THIS SMALL TOWN.
MY BOYFRIEND, GARY, AND I HAVE
BEEN TOGETHER FOR THREE YEARS.
[chime dings]
HE'S A CERTIFIED NURSING
ASSISTANT, AND HE SPENDS HIS
SPARE TIME PLAYING VIDEO GAMES.
[chime dings]
SO HOW DID I MEET GARY?
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
YOU SEE, GARY GRADUATED HIGH
SCHOOL WITH MY OLDER BROTHER
SHAWN, WHO'S IN IRAQ NOW.
ONE DAY WHEN I WAS IN TENTH
GRADE, GARY CALLED THE HOUSE
LOOKING FOR SHAWN,
AND GUESS WHO ANSWERED.
HELLO?
>> IS SHAWN HOME?
>> NOPE.
HE'S OUT SHOOTIN' SQUIRRELS.
[gunshot]
>> AMBER?
>> GARY?
[chimes ringing]
[knocking at door]
>> AMBER, WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO?
>> IT'S GARY.
>> WHAT DOES HE WANT?
>> MOM, DAD, AND MY BROTHER WERE
NOT TOO HAPPY WHEN I STARTED
DATING GARY.
>> YOU'RE STILL A LITTLE BABY
TO ME, AMBER.
>> SO YOU CAN IMAGINE THE
REACTION WHEN I LAID THIS ONE
ON THEM.
I'M PREGNANT.
>> * I'VE GOT A SECRET *
>> A BABY IS COMING OUT OF MY
FREAKING [bleep], DUDE.
>> IT'S YOUR FAULT.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WE ALL KNOW WHY I'M PREGNANT.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE YOU DON'T LIKE
CONDOMS.
AND I WAS TOO STUPID TO MAKE
YOU PUT ONE ON.
>> I NEVER SAID I DIDN'T LIKE
CONDOMS.
>> WE MAY NOT HAVE PLANNED ON
HAVING A BABY, BUT WE'RE
DEFINITELY KEEPING HER.
SO WE DECIDED TO MOVE IN
TOGETHER.
>> * HELLO, HELLO
* HELLO, HELLO, HELLO
>> NO, GET YOUR FEET
OFF THE COUCH.
I JUST WASHED THOSE.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE AN ALIEN.
>> MY BEST FRIENDS ARE TAKING IT
PRETTY WELL.
I MIGHT NOT HAVE TIME TO GO TO
THE MALL AND DO MY NAILS, BUT WE
STILL HAVE LOTS TO TALK ABOUT.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA DECORATE
THE BABY'S ROOM?
>> AND WE'RE GONNA MAKE, LIKE,
A BIG COLLAGE AND HANG IT ABOVE
THE BABY CARRIAGE.
IT'S CALLED A CARRIAGE, RIGHT?
>> SURE.
>> WHAT'S IT CALLED?
>> CRIB?
>> CRIB.
THAT THING.
[chime dings]
YOU NEED TO KNOW THAT I NEVER
THOUGHT I'D BE HERE RIGHT NOW
TALKING ABOUT A CRIB.
I DIDN'T EVEN WANT KIDS.
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT, I WAS
A REBEL AT SCHOOL.
I DRESSED DIFFERENT THAN THE
CHEERLEADERS, AND I WAS A TOTAL
PARTY GIRL.
BUT THAT LIFE IS ANCIENT
HISTORY.
OH, LOOK AT THAT ONE.
OH, THAT'S SO CUTE.
MOST KIDS MY AGE ARE SHOPPING
FOR BACK-TO-SCHOOL STUFF, BUT
I'M IN THE BABY SECTION SHOPPING
FOR BABY STUFF WITH GARY IN
TOW BITCHING ABOUT MONEY.
>> HOW MUCH ARE THESE?
FIVE BUCKS?
AFTER THE BABY SHOWER, WE CAN
ALWAYS COME BACK.
>> MONEY IS TIGHT, BUT AS LONG
AS WE'RE CAREFUL ABOUT WHAT WE
SPEND, WE'LL BE FINE.
>> YOU A SENIOR?
>> I WAS A SENIOR LAST YEAR,
BUT I'M PREGNANT.
>> OH.
WELL, I GUESS IT HAPPENS.
>> YEAH.
BUT NICE SEEING YOU.
>> YEAH, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HOPE EVERYTHING IS GOOD.
>> OKAY, GOOD LUCK.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU TOO.
>> DID YOU SEE THE LOOK
SHE GAVE ME?
DESPITE MY MOM NOT LIKING GARY,
SHE DECIDED TO COME WITH US TO
HEAR THE BABY'S HEARTBEAT.
I HOPE GARY DOESN'T SAY
SOMETHING STUPID.
[chime dings]
>> TOO LATE.
>> "MOST"?
>> AT LEAST I'M WITH THE GUY
WHO I LOST MY VIRGINITY WITH.
>> SEE, MY UNDERSTANDING--
YOU'RE STILL A VIRGIN.
>> I WAS.
>> IT WAS A MIRACLE BABY.
>> WE HAVEN'T BEEN HAVING SEX
FOR THREE YEARS.
>> BEEN MAKING LOVE.
IT WAS MAKING LOVE.
>> WHATEVER, MAKING LOVE, GARY.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE CALL IT.
>> HI, AMBER.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> SHOULD WE CHECK YOUR BELLY?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, LET'S DO THAT.
EXCUSE ME.
OKAY, LET'S HEAR THIS BABY HERE.
>> SHE'S MOVING AROUND.
>> SHE IS.
WHERE IS SHE GOING?
>> SHE MOVES AROUND A LOT.
[heartbeat pulsing]
>> THERE'S YOUR BABY.
>> I'VE HEARD IT A COUPLE TIMES.
>> IT'S IN THE 140s.
THAT'S KIND OF THE AVERAGE.
>> OKAY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> WANT A TISSUE OR A NAPKIN?
>> DON'T WORRY.
IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
>> OH, WOW, LOOKS GOOD.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ENJOY YOUR MEAL, AND I WILL
BE BACK TO CHECK ON YOU.
>> both: THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE PREGNANT
DON'T MEAN YOU CAN EAT, LIKE,
ALL THIS.
>> I AM NOT EATING ANYTHING
COMPLETELY BAD.
I'M EATING A GRILLED CHICKEN
SANDWICH, A SALAD, AND SOME
[bleep] CHEESE FRIES.
IT'S FINE.
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO GET SICK.
>> HI, AMBER.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
GOSH, I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
FOREVER.
HOW YOU DOING?
>> JUST BEING PREGNANT.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW TILL YOU CAME
IN THE DOOR.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER MET YOU
BEFORE.
>> I WAS GOING OUT WITH HIM
WHEN I WORKED HERE.
>> YOU WERE?
YOU BEEN SEEING HIM THAT LONG?
>> LIKE, 2 1/2 YEARS.
>> WOW.
WERE YOU GUYS TALKING ABOUT
GETTING MARRIED?
>> UH, YEAH.
I MEAN, I WOULD LOVE TO MARRY
HER, 'CAUSE I LOVE HER WITH ALL
MY HEART.
IT'S A LOT TO DO WITH HER
FAMILY.
I MEAN, I'M PRETTY SURE HER DAD
WOULDN'T CARE.
BUT HER MOM, I'M NOT SURE YET.
>> YEAH.
WELL, ONCE THE BABY COMES,
THAT WILL HELP.
IT'S GOOD SEEING YOU GUYS.
TAKE CARE.
BUH-BYE.
>> HEY, YOU THINK YOUR MOM WILL
GET ALONG WITH MY FAMILY?
>> YEAH, IF YOUR MOM TONES IT
DOWN A BIT.
>> SHE'S PRETTY RAMBUNCTIOUS.
>> I AIN'T FEELING GOOD NOW.
>> * ARE YOU FEELING
* ALL RIGHT?
>> [retching]
>> GRAB THESE TOO.
>> WE FOUND A CRIB AT A GARAGE
SALE FOR $15.
>> I NEED A FLATHEAD
SCREWDRIVER.
>> WE DON'T HAVE ONE, BUT I'VE
GOT A BUTTER KNIFE.
SINCE WE'RE SCRAPING FOR CASH,
WE NEED ALL THE HELP WE CAN
GET IF WE'RE GONNA MAKE THIS
WORK.
OH, MY GOD.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> SWEETIE.
>> THANK YOU.
YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
YOU WANT TO WASH YOUR HANDS
FROM TOUCHING THAT OLD CRIB?
>> IT'S SO WEIRD.
THAT CRIB BEING UP LIKE THAT
IS LIKE--I MEAN, IT'S JUST WEIRD
SEEING THE CRIB.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> HEY, BABY.
>> ARE YOU FREAKING SERIOUS?
DID YOU JUST BUY THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW MUCH WAS IT?
>> IT WAS, LIKE, A COUPLE
HUNDRED DOLLARS.
>> WHAT'S A COUPLE HUNDRED?
>> LIKE, $500.
>> $500 IS NOT A COUPLE HUNDRED.
A COUPLE MEANS $200.
THAT'S MONEY WE COULD BE SAVING
UP FOR THE BABY.
>> I GOT MONEY.
>> NO, YOU DON'T HAVE MONEY.
>> I'M WORKING OVERTIME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHATEVER, GARY.
>> WANT TO PLAY?
>> NO.
I DON'T WANT TO PLAY.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
BABY, DON'T BE MAD.
[chime dings]
[dog barking]
>> WHY?
>> PAY THE BILLS?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW IF I SHOULD BE
TELLING YOU THIS, BUT HE JUST
BOUGHT HIM A BRAND-NEW
PLAYSTATION 3.
IT WAS $500.
>> WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW, MOM.
>> HE'S GOT HIS PRIORITIES ALL
SCREWED UP, THEN.
HE WORKS HARD FOR HIS MONEY,
BUT, YOU KNOW, HE'S THE ONE THAT
GOT HIMSELF INTO THIS MESS.
YOU BOTH DID.
[phone ringing]
HEY, DAD.
ARE YOU GONNA COME TO THE
BARBECUE?
>> MM.
I'M SURE MOM TALKED TO YOU.
>> NO, HE'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
HE'S UPSTAIRS.
>> I SHOULDN'T HAVE TOLD HER.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL--
>> YEAH, THAT WOULD BE GOOD.
BYE, DADDY.
>> BYE.
>> YOUR FAMILY [bleep] PISSES ME
OFF, FOR REAL.
>> WHY, BECAUSE THEY CARE
ABOUT ME?
>> WHY DID YOU TELL YOUR MOM
ABOUT THE PS3?
YOU SAID YOU WOULDN'T.
IT MAKES ME LOOK LIKE AN ASS
WHEN I WORKED OVERTIME--
>> BECAUSE YOU ARE AN ASS FOR
DOING IT.
>> THERE'S MONEY IN THE BANK.
>> NO, THERE IS NOT.
>> LIKE, $5.
[bleep] MONEY.
STUPID MONEY.
I HATE MONEY.
>> WHY ARE YOU SO MAD IF YOU
DID IT?
>> BECAUSE OF YOUR MOM NEEDS TO
SHUT HER [bleep] MOUTH.
>> YOU WON'T SAY THAT TO HER
FACE.
>> WHAT DOES SHE CALL ME, AN
INBRED PIECE OF [bleep]?
>> IF MY KID WAS 17 AND SHE GOT
PREGNANT--
>> I DON'T CARE.
SHE CAN STILL--SHE CAN STILL--
SHE CAN GO SOMEWHERE.
>> I AM A TEENAGER.
YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU DO UNDERSTAND.
>> I DO UNDERSTAND.
I'M HAVING A DAUGHTER.
>> IT HURTS ME THAT YOU DID
THAT.
YOU DON'T CARE.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME.
IT'S LIKE, EVER SINCE WE'VE
BEEN TOGETHER, IT'S LIKE HE'S
CHANGED.
IT'S LIKE, GETTING OLDER,
IT'S LIKE HE'S TURNING MORE
INTO AN ASS[bleep].
>> OH, I CAN FEEL IT BURNING.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE THAT, YOU
KNOW, KNOCKED HER UP, SO...
>> I SAID, "IF YOU KEEP ON
ACTING LIKE THIS, I'M NOT GONNA
BE WITH YOU."
THE GOOD THING ABOUT LIVING
RIGHT NEAR MY MOM IS, I ALWAYS
HAVE A PLACE TO GO WHEN THINGS
GET TOUGH.
>> WE'RE GONNA GET A STROLLER.
I NEED TO BUY, YOU KNOW, ALL
THIS STUFF FOR THE BABY.
>> EVERYTHING IS EXPENSIVE.
BABIES AREN'T CHEAP, MAN.
>> THE BABY'S NOT EVEN HERE.
YOU KNOW, I'M BROKE.
>> SO THIS IS YOUR ROOM?
>> I LOVE THIS ROOM.
BEING IN THIS ROOM MAKES ME
REALIZE HOW MUCH MY LIFE HAS
CHANGED IN THESE LAST FEW
MONTHS.
I WISH I COULD JUST, LIKE, GO
BACK.
>> HAVE YOU HEARD FROM YOUR
BROTHER?
>> I WAS TEXTING HIM.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO CALL DURING
THE COOKOUT.
IT KIND OF SUCKS.
IT'S LIKE, THE TIME WHERE I NEED
HIM HERE THE MOST, HE'S GONE.
'CAUSE HE'S, LIKE, THE CLOSEST
PERSON TO ME, YOU KNOW.
>> WHEN DOES HE GET TO COME
HOME?
>> THEY WERE TRYING TO GET HIM
HOME NOVEMBER 1ST, BUT I HOPE
HE'S HERE BEFORE THE BABY IS
BORN, YOU KNOW?
[chime dings]
SHAWN'S BEEN AWAY FOR SEVEN
MONTHS, SO HE'S NEVER SEEN ME
WITH MY BIG BELLY.
IF I COULD HAVE ANY WISH IN THE
WORLD, IT WOULD BE THAT HE'D
BE ABLE TO LEAVE IRAQ AND COME
HOME IN TIME FOR THE BIRTH.
>> HEY.
I GOT MY HAIR CUT.
>> MY MOM'S GONNA BE HERE SOON,
AND I'M NOT READY.
>> OKAY, WELL, GET READY.
>> IT'S FOURTH OF JULY WEEKEND,
AND THE FAMILIES ARE ABOUT TO
MEET FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> WE'RE HERE. WE'RE HERE.
WE'RE HERE.
>> LOOK HOW BIG THAT THING IS.
>> FEEL IT.
FEEL HOW HARD IT IS.
YOU GUYS ARE ALL CRAMMED ON THE
LITTLE COUCH.
>> I HOPE EVERYONE GETS ALONG,
ESPECIALLY OUR MOMS.
HI, MOMMY.
>> SHE HAD TOLD YOU ABOUT
THE PS3.
I TOLD HER THAT THE REASON I WAS
GETTING IT IS 'CAUSE THEY
WEREN'T MAKING THEM NO MORE.
BUT THEN I WENT OUT AND I
WORKED, LIKE,
A MILLION HOURS OVERTIME.
>> I KNOW, GARY, BUT THE BABY IS
FIRST.
ACTUALLY, AMBER AND THE BABY IS
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> GARY, YOU GOT SOMETHING TO
PUT UNDER THIS ONE?
IT'S HOT.
>> YEAH.
>> HI.
>> THREE PLATES OF FOOD.
>> MOM.
HEY, TONYA, IS IT--THIS IS MY--
YEAH, THERE'S MORE.
THIS IS MY MOTHER, CAROL.
THAT'S TONYA.
THAT'S AMBER'S MOTHER.
>> WELL, I THINK I ACTUALLY SEEN
YOU WHEN THEY WERE LOOKING AT
THE CAR THE OTHER DAY.
>> OH.
I WENT THROUGH THE SHOCK THING.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT WAS LIKE,
"OKAY."
>> WHAT?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THAT'S THE FIRST TIME YOU MET
HIS MOM?
>> I'VE SEEN HER BEFORE.
>> YOU'VE SEEN HER?
YOU'VE JUST SEEN HER?
MY POOR LITTLE AMBER.
WHAT HAVE THEY DONE TO HER?
[laughs]
>> AMBER, IS YOUR MOM GONNA COME
IN AND JOIN US?
>> THEY'RE ALL EATING OUT THERE.
>> OH.
[chime dings]
>> WELL, IF THINGS WEREN'T WEIRD
ALREADY, THIS COOKOUT CERTAINLY
DIDN'T HELP.
JUST WHEN I WAS ABOUT TO HIT
ROCK BOTTOM...
MY BROTHER'S TRYING TO CALL, SO
I'M GOING OUTSIDE SO I CAN TRY
TO GET RECEPTION.
BUBBY.
HELLO?
BUBBY?
>> OH, MY GOD.
I MISS YOU SO MUCH.
>> [crying] NOTHING.
>> SHE'S CRYING.
>> SHE'S HAVING A COOKOUT.
SHE'S GOT THE FAMILY OVER.
>> YEAH, EXCEPT FOR YOU.
>> I NEED YOU HERE RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU'RE THE
CLOSEST PERSON TO ME IN THIS
FAMILY, AND I'M GOING THROUGH
ALL THIS [bleep].
AND I JUST NEED YOU RIGHT NOW.
MOM TOLD ME THAT SHE TOLD YOU
IT WAS A GIRL.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> all: WE LOVE YOU.
>> LATER, MAN.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU, SHAWN.
>> BYE, SHAWN.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> BYE.
>> GIVE ME YOUR FOOT.
>> NO.
>> NO, LET GO OF ME.
>> PUT YOUR FOOT OVER HERE.
SEE, THANK YOU.
YOUR FEET SMELL GOOD.
>> I CAN NEVER STAY MAD AT HIM
FOR THAT LONG.
[chime dings]
DESPITE ALL THE MESSES HE MAKES,
HE'S MY MAN.
[line ringing]
>> YEAH, I HAD A QUESTION.
I JUST FOUND OUT I'M HAVING
A BABY, AND I PURCHASED THE
METAL GEAR SOLID 80-GIG VALUE
PACK FOR THE PS3.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND I WAS WANTING TO KNOW
WHAT YOUR RETURN POLICY IS
ON THOSE.
[chime dings]
>> * IT'S OUR LIFE *
[bell rings]
>> FALL IS HERE, AND WHILE MOST
KIDS ARE FIGURING OUT THEIR
CLASS SCHEDULE, GARY AND I ARE
AT THE LIBRARY RESEARCHING BABY
NAMES.
>> HEATHER, GRACE, JUDITH,
GLORIA, RACHEL, ANNA OR ANNIE,
BARBARA, LINDA, JENNIFER, RUTH.
>> ARIANNA?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE, "ARIANNA, COME HERE."
YOU LIKE KUMADA?
>> NO, HONEY.
>> AMELIA?
>> MM-MM.
I GOT ONE.
NUMBER ONE: LEAH.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> YEAH.
WHO ALL DID YOU INVITE TO THE
BABY SHOWER?
>> EVERYBODY, BUT KAYLA CAN'T
COME.
SHE'S OUT OF TOWN.
>> DOES YOUR MOM STILL HATE ME?
>> "HATE" IS A STRONG WORD,
BUT YEAH.
OH, YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
I LOVE YOU.
>> WHATEVER HAPPENED DID.
>> YEAH.
YOU AND MY MOM WERE THINKING
THE SAME EXACT THING OR
SOMETHING.
"DADDY IS A ROCK STAR."
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> IT'S A LITTLE PHOTO THING.
>> FOR HER DRESSER.
I'M GONNA BUY HER A DRESSER AND
A COUPLE OTHER THINGS.
>> THE DADDY GUIDE.
I DON'T NEED NO DADDY GUIDE.
>> YEAH, NO KIDDING.
>> I HOPE THIS TENSION BETWEEN
OUR FAMILIES DOESN'T LAST
FOREVER.
EVEN THOUGH BEING PREGNANT KEPT
US AWAY FROM THE BIG GAME,
GARY AND I ARE SPENDING
QUALITY TIME WITH OUR FRIENDS AT
HOME.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO EAT ALL
THAT.
YOU NEED TO SAVE ROOM FOR
DESSERT.
>> I AM FRICKING STARVING.
GIVE ME MY DAMN FOOD.
[laughter]
WE'RE HAPPY, AND LIFE IS GOOD.
[thoughtful guitar music]
*
>> WHAT CAN I HELP YOU WITH
TODAY?
>> ANYTHING SPECIAL OR...
>> WELL, I'M GONNA PROPOSE.
>> REALLY?
>> IF EVERYTHING GOES SMOOTH,
YEAH.
>> OH.
>> SHE LIKES PINK SAPPHIRE
STUFF.
>> MM-HMM, THE PINK SAPPHIRES?
>> THE HEART ONE, I THINK.
>> THE HEART ONE?
>> THAT'S HER STYLE.
>> IT'S GOT A LOT OF
BLING-BLING.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> THAT'S $21.40.
>> UH, 90 DAYS WITH A RECEIPT.
>> RIGHT.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
>> THANK YOU FOR HOLDING THIS
WEEKEND OPEN FOR ME.
I WANT TO TAKE YOU SOMEWHERE
SPECIAL, GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE
FOR A WHILE.
>> I THINK SHE'LL HAVE TO.
AND WITH THAT, WE HIT THE ROAD
FOR ONE LAST ROMANTIC
WEEKEND IN THE COUNTRY.
[cheerful music]
*
OH, THAT'S SO PRETTY.
>> IT IS BEAUTIFUL OUT HERE.
[goat bleats]
>> PUMPKINS.
HI.
>> HI, I'M LINDA, THE INNKEEPER.
LET ME SHOW YOU YOUR ROOM.
WE'LL GET YOU ALL COMFY COZY.
THEN YOU CAN BE ON YOUR OWN.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
DUDE, YOUR FEET STINK LIKE POO.
>> THEY DO NOT, GARY.
>> HEY...
>> NO, GARY.
SO WE'RE JUST GONNA CHILL
OVER HERE?
>> IS THAT COMFY?
>> YEAH.
AND IT'S SPRINGY.
SIT.
>> OH, UM--
>> SIT.
>> I'M NOT THROUGH.
HOLD ON.
>> SIT.
>> THERE WAS SOMETHING I WAS
GONNA ASK YOU.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULD
MARRY ME.
>> NO.
YOU DID NOT.
YEAH.
BABY.
I HOPE IT FITS ME.
MY FINGERS ARE SWOLLEN.
>> IT'LL FIT.
>> [laughs]
>> I MEAN, I WANT TO ASK YOUR
DAD BEFORE WE ACTUALLY, YOU
KNOW, GET MARRIED, BUT I WAS
WONDERING IF YOU WANT
TO MARRY ME.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I KNOW WE FIGHT, BUT
EVERYBODY DOES.
I KNOW WITH US HAVING A BABY AND
EVERYTHING, WE NEED TO HAVE
A COMPLETE FAMILY.
I WANT TO BE THERE FOR BOTH OF
YOU GUYS.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH, HON.
>> I LOVE YOU.
I AM THE HAPPIEST GIRL IN THE
WHOLE WORLD.
I JUST HOPE MY FAMILY DOESN'T
GET IN THE WAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE SOMETHING
TO TELL YOU.
WE WENT TO A BED-AND-BREAKFAST.
IT WAS SO NICE.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> WELL, WE WENT OUT ON THE
PORCH, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
HE GOT IN FRONT OF ME AND
KNEELED DOWN AND ASKED ME TO
MARRY HIM.
>> OH, YES.
YAY!
>> GARY'S MOM WAS NOT THE ONE
WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT.
>> WHERE YOU AT, AMBER?
>> I JUST HOPE MY MOM TAKES IT
WELL.
HE PROPOSED TO ME.
>> WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> MOMMY.
>> THIS YEAR, NO
TRICK-OR-TREATING FOR US.
BUT LEAH DRESSED UP AS
A PUMPKIN.
>> IT LOOKS ADORABLE.
>> AND EVEN OUR MIDWIFE GOT INTO
THE SPIRIT.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
>> [laughs]
>> HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
WE WANT YOU TO GET DELIVERED BY
40 WEEKS.
>> OKAY.
>> SO THAT'S LESS THAN TWO
WEEKS.
IF YOU DON'T GO INTO YOUR LABOR
NATURALLY BY YOUR DUE DATE, THEN
WE WOULD WANT TO INDUCE YOU...
>> OKAY.
>> SO THAT YOUR BABY DOESN'T GET
TOO BIG, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> DID YOU THINK ABOUT PAIN
MANAGEMENT DURING LABOR?
>> YES.
AN EPIDURAL.
>> THE THING WITH THE EPIDURAL
IS, GET IT ONLY IF YOU NEED IT.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, DON'T HAVE IT BE, LIKE,
YOUR FIRST THING.
EVEN THOUGH YOU HAVE AN
EPIDURAL, WHEN YOU PUSH, MOST OF
THE TIME, I TRY TO DO A LOT OF
DIFFERENT POSITIONS.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THE BAR IS,
THE SQUATTING BAR?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU CAN SIT ON THE EDGE OF
THE BED, KIND OF LEAN OVER THAT
BAR, AND SQUAT, KIND OF LIKE
YOU'RE SITTING ON THE TOILET,
TO PUSH.
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE, WELL, PUSHING
A BABY OUT IS A LOT LIKE
PUSHING A POOP OUT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
OKAY.
[knocking at door]
MY DUE DATE CAME AND WENT.
BUT I HAD TO WAIT FIVE MORE DAYS
BEFORE BEING INDUCED.
>> HEY, BABE, THIS IS IT.
WE'RE COMING HOME WITH A LITTLE
BABY GIRL.
>> I AM SO READY TO HAVE THIS
BABY.
GOD, I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU
GUYS.
>> HEY, SHAWN.
>> * BABY
* WE'RE GONNA HAVE A BABY *
>> [laughs]
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> SO HOW YOU FEELING?
>> UM, I'VE BEEN PUKING ALL DAY
LONG.
>> I KNOW.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> BUT HOW COME YOU CAN THROW UP
AND THEN EAT TACO BELL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T GET IT...
>> AT ALL.
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
>> UH-HUH.
I FEEL IT.
>> I'M SORRY, AMBER.
NOW WE HAVE THE PITOCIN.
OKAY, IT'S GONNA HOOK RIGHT INTO
YOUR OTHER IV FLUID.
AND THIS WILL HELP INDUCE THE
LABOR.
>> LIQUID LABOR.
>> ONCE THIS REALLY HITS YOUR
SYSTEM, YOU'LL START TO FEEL
MORE CONTRACTIONS, AND THEY'LL
GET A LITTLE BIT MORE INTENSE.
OKAY?
>> [breathing heavily]
>> JUST KEEP BREATHING LIKE SHE
SAID.
>> I KEEP HAVING CONTRACTIONS.
>> TRY TO TAKE SOME NICE, SLOW
BREATHS.
I KNOW IT HURTS.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE REALIZED
IT WAS GONNA BE THAT HARD.
>> HER CONTRACTIONS ARE GETTING
BIGGER AND LONGER.
>> THEY'RE GONNA GET A LOT
BIGGER.
>> I NEED SOMETHING.
THE PAIN IS--
[sobbing]
>> OKAY, I HAVE TO CHECK YOU
FIRST.
>> I CAN'T.
PLEASE STOP.
>> OKAY, AMBER, TAKE A NICE BIG,
DEEP BREATH.
>> JUST KEEP BREATHING.
>> OW, PLEASE STOP.
STOP.
>> AMBER, YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
YOU'RE 100% THINNED OUT.
>> AM I READY FOR EPIDURAL?
>> YOU ARE READY FOR AN
EPIDURAL.
>> YAY.
[laughter]
>> THEY JUST GAVE HER THE
EPIDURAL.
>> IS SHE DOING BETTER?
>> IT'S A GOOD EPIDURAL IN THAT
IT'S HELPING YOUR PAIN, BUT YOU
CAN STILL MOVE.
>> AM I HAVING A CONTRACTION?
I FEEL THE TIGHTNESS.
>> YEAH.
MUCH BETTER, HUH?
>> I CAN TELL YOU LOVE HER
A LOT.
>> YEAH.
EVEN THOUGH WE FIGHT AND SAY
THINGS, I STILL LOVE HER.
>> YEAH, EVERYBODY'S GONNA FIGHT
AND ARGUE.
>> YEAH, YEAH, TOTALLY.
>> SHE'S FEELING SOME PRESSURE
IN HER BUTT.
>> IS THAT A GOOD THING?
>> THAT'S A VERY GOOD THING.
I THINK THAT WE CAN HAVE HER
START PUSHING, AND WE CAN KIND
OF GET READY FOR THIS DELIVERY.
OKAY?
OKAY, I WANT YOU TO PUT YOUR
HANDS RIGHT HERE.
OKAY, TAKE IN A BIG DEEP BREATH.
PUSH DOWN HARD INTO YOUR BOTTOM.
HOLD IT TO THE COUNT OF TEN.
>> OKAY, LET'S SEE.
>> BABY, PUSH.
>> PUSH, PUSH.
>> PUSH HARD.
>> REALLY, REALLY HARD.
>> OH.
>> YOU'RE DOING PERFECT.
>> IS THE HEAD SHOWING?
>> NOT YET.
>> I MEAN, IT'S IN THERE.
>> [laughing] IT'S IN THERE.
>> TAKE THE SHEET AND PULL ON IT
NOW WHEN YOU PUSH.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
OKAY, TAKE A COUPLE BIG DEEP
BREATHS AND REST IN BETWEEN.
AND PUSH.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
PUSH REALLY HARD INTO YOUR
BOTTOM, AND COME RIGHT BACK
AT IT--KEEP GOING.
PUSH HARD.
PUSH REALLY, REALLY HARD.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
>> IT'S NOT DOING ANYTHING.
>> IT IS.
IT IS.
LET'S CHANGE POSITION
A LITTLE BIT.
OKAY?
THAT'S A GIRL, JUST LIKE THAT.
GOOD JOB.
>> [sobbing]
IS HER HEAD--
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> KEEP GOING.
KEEP GOING. KEEP GOING.
>> SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT,
NINE, TEN.
>> AND PUSH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IS IT--OH, PLEASE.
>> THERE IT IS.
>> EVERY PUSH COUNTS.
>> DO YOU WANT TO TOUCH HER?
>> NO. NO.
>> CAN GARY TOUCH HER?
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
>> [laughs]
>> THIS IS A LOT OF WORK,
ISN'T IT, AMBER?
IT'S A TON OF WORK.
I KNOW IT.
OH.
>> I KNOW.
>> I REALLY DON'T THINK YOU NEED
A C-SECTION.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE WEAK.
>> OH, I CAN'T--
>> SHE'S COMING--
>> I'M REALLY, REALLY WEAK.
>> I CAN'T PUSH.
>> LET YOUR BODY JUST DO ITS OWN
THING FOR A FEW MINUTES.
>> I'M TRYING.
I'M TRYING.
>> OKAY, I'M JUST GONNA CHECK
AND SEE IF THE BABY'S MOVED DOWN
ANY MORE SINCE--OKAY?
HONESTLY, THE BABY IS REALLY
RIGHT THERE.
I REALLY THINK YOU COULD PUSH
THIS BABY OUT.
YOU WANT TO TRY IT?
>> SURE.
>> OKAY.
IS EVERYBODY READY?
>> YEAH, WE'RE READY.
>> OKAY, YOU GOT A CONTRACTION?
PUSH DOWN HARD INTO YOUR
BOTTOM.
GOOD JOB.
KEEP GOING.
PUSH.
COME ON.
YOU'RE MOVING THAT BABY.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
PUSH.
GIVE ME THAT BABY.
LET'S SEE.
OKAY, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD,
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
>> OH, WOW.
>> AGAIN, AGAIN.
BIG BREATH, AND PUSH, PUSH HARD.
BEAUTIFUL.
HERE COMES THE HEAD.
>> THERE'S A BUNCH OF BLACK
HAIR.
>> RIGHT NOW?
>> GIVE ME A HUGE PUSH.
COME ON, PUSH.
[mellow guitar strumming]
*
[baby crying]
>> OH, LISTEN TO HER.
>> I'M GONNA SET HER RIGHT HERE.
[baby crying]
>> IT'S A GIRL.
>> SHE'S SO PRETTY.
SHE LOOKS LIKE YOU.
>> YOU DID GREAT.
>> OH, SHE'S SO PRETTY.
[baby crying]
>> AH, YOU CAN DO IT.
>> DOES SHE COME WITH ANY
INSTRUCTIONS?
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
IT'S A GIRL. IT'S A GIRL.
>> AW, SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> PRECIOUS.
>> LOOKS LIKE SHE GOT GARY'S
FACE.
>> WHY, 'CAUSE IT'S FAT?
>> YEAH.
>> WHILE OTHER KIDS ARE STUDYING
FOR THEIR FINALS, GARY AND I
ENROLLED IN BABY 101.
>> EW.
>> IS IT POO?
>> UGH.
HONEY, THAT'S, LIKE, WAY TOO
LOOSE.
>> PATTY CAKE, PATTY CAKE.
BAKE ME A CAKE AS FAST AS YOU
CAN.
ROLL IT UP, ROLL IT UP,
THROW IT IN THE PAN.
>> BABY.
BEFORE WE KNEW IT, IT WAS TIME
TO TAKE BABY LEAH HOME.
>> NO HEAVY LIFTING.
THAT INCLUDES LAUNDRY BASKETS
AND STUFF LIKE THAT, AND EVEN
PUSHING A VACUUM.
>> CAN SHE LOAD THE DISHWASHER?
>> SHUT UP, GARY.
>> JUST NOTHING HEAVY.
WE SUGGEST, DURING THESE FOUR TO
SIX WEEKS, NO SEX WHATSOEVER.
OKAY?
IF YOU NOTICE, LIKE, YOU MIGHT
BE A LITTLE MORE TEARFUL NOW
THAN YOU WERE BEFORE--CRYING AT
STUPID COMMERCIALS--
OKAY, THE WEEPINESS IS OKAY.
>> HELLO?
>> OKAY.
>> IT'S YOUR BROTHER.
>> [gasps]
TOMORROW AFTERNOON?
>> YEAH, OKAY.
WE'LL TELL HER THAT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M GONNA CRY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BYE.
>> WHO IS THAT?
>> HER BROTHER.
HE'S BEEN IN IRAQ FOR A WHILE.
>> CALM DOWN.
>> [laughs]
>> IS THIS PART OF IT?
>> YEAH.
>> MY BROTHER, SHAWN, WAS
FINALLY COMING HOME FROM IRAQ.
HE WASN'T TOO HAPPY ABOUT GARY
AND ME HOOKING UP.
BUT NOW THAT THERE'S A NIECE IN
THE PICTURE, I'M HOPING HE'LL BE
OKAY WITH EVERYTHING.
ALL RIGHT, SHE'S BUNDLED UP.
SHE'S READY TO GO OUTSIDE.
>> SHE LOOKS FAKE NOW.
>> SHE LOOKS SO CUTE.
LOOK AT YOU.
OOH--OH.
I KNEW DELIVERING MY BABY WOULD
HURT, BUT I NEVER IMAGINED I'D
BE IN THIS MUCH PAIN.
THEY DO NOT TEACH YOU THIS IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
IT SMELLS SO GOOD IN HERE.
>> HI, MOM.
>> HI.
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS A SCHOOL
NIGHT, THANK GOD KAYLA CAME OVER
TO GIVE US A HAND.
>> ALL YOUR LAUNDRY IS CLEAN.
AND I WASHED YOUR SHEETS
FOR YOU.
I WASHED THE BOTTLES, ALL OF
THEM.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> I'LL LET YOU GUYS DO YOUR
MOM AND DAD THING.
>> BYE.
OKAY, PUT HER IN.
>> HERE, BABY.
HERE WE GO.
>> EVERYTHING IS SO SOFT ON HER.
I HOPE SHE'S COMFY.
[sweet lullaby music]
*
LOOK AT OUR LITTLE GIRL.
>> I LOVE YOU, BABY.
>> NO MORE.
>> LEAH WANTS A BROTHER.
[baby crying]
>> OH, GOODNESS.
DADDY'S MAKING YOU SOMETHING.
DON'T WORRY.
[baby crying]
GARY.
>> YEAH, PORTWOOD?
>> HURRY.
>> I AM.
>> HI.
>> I LOVE HER.
>> THE WHOLE FAMILY GATHERED IN
ANTICIPATION OF MY BROTHER'S
ARRIVAL.
AS YOU KNOW, SHAWN WAS NOT HAPPY
ABOUT ME AND GARY BEING
TOGETHER, AND I WAS SCARED
HE'D MAKE A SCENE.
BUT TO MY SURPRISE, HE SET THE
PAST ASIDE AND ACTED LIKE
A COMPLETE GENTLEMEN.
>> HEY, SIS.
>> I'M SO SORE.
OH, GOD.
OH, MWAH!
>> HI, MOM.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU DO LOOK DIFFERENT.
>> WHAT'S UP, MAN?
>> GARY.
>> WHAT'S UP, DUDE?
>> GOT A LITTLE MEAT
ON YOUR BONES.
>> [laughs]
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
>> SHE'S CUTE.
OH, MY GOD.
>> TOTALLY.
[chime dings]
>> BUT THE JOY OF A NEW BABY
AND THE JOY OF SEEING MY BROTHER
SOON FADED AS REALITY SET IN.
I REALLY NEED THAT DRESSER TO BE
DONE SOMETIME SOON SO I CAN
ACTUALLY PUT ALL THESE CLOTHES
IN HER DRESSER.
WHAT THE HELL?
THERE'S A DIAPER ON THE FLOOR.
NOTE TO SELF--OR TO YOU
ACTUALLY--LIKE, IF YOU FILL UP
A TRASH THING, LIKE, BRING IT
DOWNSTAIRS.
>> I'VE BEEN BUSY WORKING.
THEN I COME HOME AND TAKE
CARE OF A BABY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
CRY ME A RIVER, GARY.
EVEN WITH GARY PICKING UP EXTRA
SHIFTS, MONEY WAS STILL TIGHT,
AS WE HAD ALL SORTS OF NEW
EXPENSES: FORMULA, DIAPERS,
CLOTHES, AND TOYS.
ADD THAT TO CONSTANT CLEANING
AND LACK OF SLEEP, I FOUND
MYSELF ON THE VERGE
OF LOSING IT.
[baby crying]
>> WHAT?
WHAT?
>> WE NEED TO GET TO SLEEP.
>> YOU NEED TO GET TO SLEEP?
I DIDN'T GET NO SLEEP LAST
NIGHT.
>> HOW MANY HOURS OF SLEEP DID
YOU GET?
>> FOUR.
>> OKAY, NOW, LISTEN.
I DO THAT FOUR DAYS IN A [bleep]
ROW.
>> WHEN I WORK 40 HOURS IN THE
WEEKEND AND ALL YOU DO IS STAY
HOME AND TAKE CARE OF THE LITTLE
ONE, WHICH I WOULD RATHER DO.
>> YOU GET MORE SLEEP THAN I DO
WORKING THOSE 40 HOURS.
>> AND YOU COULD BE SLEEPING
RIGHT NOW, BUT YOU WANT TO
ARGUE.
>> I CAN'T GO TO SLEEP RIGHT
NOW.
YOU GOT THE LIGHT ON.
YOU'RE OVER HERE POUNDING ON
THE BABY.
SHE'S CRYING.
>> ARE YOU CRYING?
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO WATCH HER,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
I'LL DO IT ALL.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT WANTING, GARY.
IT'S ABOUT NEEDING TO GET SLEEP
SO I CAN MAKE IT THROUGH THE
[bleep] WEEKEND.
>> OKAY, MY MOM WILL WATCH HER--
>> WHY DOES YOUR MOM NEED TO
WATCH HER WHEN SHE HAS
A FREAKING FATHER TO WATCH HER?
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE COMPLAINING
ABOUT WATCHING HER, AMBER.
>> I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
YOU ARE SO LUCKY RIGHT NOW
YOU'RE HOLDING THE BABY.
>> WHY, YOU GONNA HIT ME?
NIGHT, LEAH.
>> THINGS MELLOWED OUT, AND
GARY AND I SETTLED INTO
A COMFORTABLE ROUTINE.
GARY.
BUT AS SOON AS I STARTED
GETTING SOME REST...
SHE'S BREATHING HEAVY RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN HEAR IT.
SOMETHING WAS GOING ON WITH OUR
BABY'S BREATHING.
>> [labored breathing]
[wheezing]
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M WORRIED
ABOUT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YEAH, WE NEED TO GET AN
APPOINTMENT FOR OUR DAUGHTER.
SHE'S HAVING BREATHING PROBLEMS.
LIKE, SHE STOPS BREATHING.
AND SHE KIND OF GASPS FOR AIR
SOMETIMES.
DO YOU KNOW HOW THE PROCEDURE
WORKS?
>> WELL, THEY TOLD ME THAT THERE
MIGHT BE A NOSEBLEED.
SO THIS KIND OF WORRIES US.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY?
THANK YOU.
>> AND WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE THEM
STICK IT UP HER NOSE.
YOU KNOW, I WORRY ABOUT HER.
>> SO LEAH'S SEEING A SPECIALIST
IN INDIANAPOLIS TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S WRONG.
>> HI.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HEY.
HOW'S LEAH DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> SLEEPING.
>> YEAH, SO WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
TODAY IS A PROCEDURE
CALLED FLEXIBLE BRONCHOSCOPY.
IT TAKES ABOUT FIVE, TEN MINUTES
TO FINISH THE PROCEDURE.
PREPARING IT WILL TAKE MORE
TIME.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> SO THIS IS THE FLEXIBLE
BRONCHOSCOPE THAT WE'RE
GONNA USE.
AND IT'S A VERY SMALL SCOPE.
IT'S VERY FLEXIBLE, SO IT
SHOULDN'T HURT HER.
AND WE COULD MOVE IT UP AND
DOWN.
AND IT HAS A CAMERA AND A LIGHT
AT THE END OF IT.
AND WE COULD SEE THE PICTURE
HERE ON THESE TWO SCREEN,
AND WE WILL RECORD IT.
>> SHE'S OKAY, HONEY.
RIGHT HERE.
>> THAT THING WAS THICK.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> THEY SAID IT WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE, LIKE, TINY.
LIKE, THAT'S BIGGER THAN HER
NOSTRIL.
>> 13 MINUTES ALREADY.
>> WE'RE DONE WITH LEAH.
YOU GUYS WANT TO COME ON BACK?
>> OH.
>> SHE'S FINE.
COME ON BACK.
>> HER LITTLE NOSE IS RED.
>> LET ME SHOW YOU WHAT I FOUND.
SO THIS IS HER VOICE BOX HERE.
THIS STRUCTURE CALLED THE
EPIGLOTTIS,
IT'S LIKE CARTILAGE.
IN HER CASE,
IT'S VERY SOFT STILL.
IT GOES DOWN AND COVER
MOST OF HER AIRWAY.
EVERY TIME SHE TAKE A BREATH,
IT MAKE IT SMALLER.
SO IT BECOME LIKE A WHISTLE.
AND THAT'S WHY SHE'S LIKE...
[wheezing]
WITH TIME, IT WILL GO AWAY.
BUT--SO YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH, YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> RELIEF FLOODED IN WITH THE
GOOD NEWS.
BUT I GOT TO TELL YOU, THIS
PARENTING THING IS NOT EASY.
THEN AGAIN, NOBODY SAID
IT WOULD BE.
DADDY GONNA SING TO US.
[calming guitar playing]
*
>> * EVERY CONSTELLATION
* IN MY HEART
>> [laughs]
>> * DANCING ON A RIVER
* ALL NIGHT
>> SMILE, GIRL.
>> * I WOULD CLIMB THROUGH...
>> WHAT A LONG ROAD THIS HAS
BEEN.
NEVER IN A MILLION YEARS
COULD I HAVE FORESEEN
WHAT HAVING A BABY
WOULD REALLY BE LIKE.
IT'S JUST WEIRD SEEING THE CRIB.
MY WHOLE LIFE HAS CHANGED
NOW THAT I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR
THIS CHILD.
I NEED YOU HERE RIGHT NOW.
WHILE GARY AND I HAVE OUR
DISAGREEMENTS...
$500 IS NOT A COUPLE HUNDRED.
A COUPLE MEANS $200.
AND BEING PARENTS
IS A CHALLENGE...
YOU DON'T CARE.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME.
WE DO OUR BEST TO SPREAD
THE LOVE.
>> I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULD
MARRY ME.
>> GIVE ME A HUGE PUSH.
>> AND GARY NEVER CEASES TO
SURPRISE ME WITH HIS RANDOM ACTS
OF SWEETNESS.
>> * DON'T STICK *
* YOUR TONGUE AT ME
[laughter]
>> NO ONE SAID BEING A TEEN MOM
WAS GOING TO BE EASY.
[chime dings]
AHEAD LIE MANY UNANSWERED
QUESTIONS, LIKE WILL GARY AND
I ACTUALLY GET MARRIED?
WILL WE HAVE MORE KIDS?
WILL WE EVER BE ABLE TO MAKE
ENDS MEET OR BUY OUR OWN HOME?
AM I JUST TOO YOUNG TO HANDLE
ALL OF THIS?
IT'S HARD TO TELL.
AS LONG AS THERE'S A HAPPY
FAMILY BEHIND HER, SHE SHOULD BE
A GOOD PERSON WHEN SHE GROWS
OLDER, YOU KNOW.
I THINK WE'RE DOING PRETTY GOOD
SO FAR.
SO WE'LL SEE HOW THE FUTURE
TURNS OUT.
>> * I WOULD DO ANYTHING
* FOR HER
AND THAT'S IT.
[laughs]
>> I SAT YOU DOWN RIGHT HERE
AND SAID, "USE PROTECTION.
I DON'T WANT TO BE A GRANDMA
YET."
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND LOOK.
NOW I'M GONNA BE A GRANDMA.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO THE PROM?
>> I'M GONNA BE, LIKE,
THIS BIG.
[laughter]
I CAN'T FIT IN A DRESS.
>> IF HE HAD KEPT IT IN HIS
PANTS, IT WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
THIS WAY.
>> PUSH, PUSH.
DON'T GIVE UP.
PUSH.
>> FATHERS AREN'T REALLY FATHERS
UNTIL THEY HOLD THEIR BABY.
>> MAYBE.
>> YOU'RE HER FATHER,
AND YOU NEED TO ACT LIKE IT.
I'M JUST THE ONE THAT
GREW UP TOO FAST,
AND I WANT HIM TO GROW UP TOO.
[upbeat piano music]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA *
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
* BUT I'M WEAK, BUT I'M *
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE