>> WHOO!
I'M ALEAH.
LET'S GO.
I'M 18 AND LIVE JUST OUTSIDE
ST. LOUIS, MISSOURI.
I'M REALLY CLOSE TO MY MOM AND
MY STEPDAD.
ADAM.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> BUT WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES, I WAS REALLY
UPSET, SO I STARTED TO ACT OUT.
AFTER GETTING INTO A BAD FIGHT
WITH ANOTHER GIRL, I ENDED UP IN
JUVENILE DETENTION, WHICH IS
WHERE I MET MY BOYFRIEND OF TWO
YEARS, SHAWN.
>> DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN WE FIRST
MET EACH OTHER?
>> I DO.
>> AND I WINKED AT YOU.
[laughs]
I FELT WEIRD DATING SOMEONE WHO
HAD A KID, BUT I FELL IN LOVE
WITH SHAWN AND HIS SON NOAH TOO.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
SINCE HIS MOM ISN'T AROUND,
I'VE BEEN HELPING RAISE HIM,
AND I'M ENROLLED IN COLLEGE TO
BE A MEDICAL ASSISTANT.
I ALSO HAVE TO REMEMBER TO STAY
ON TOP OF MY DIABETES BY
MONITORING MY BLOOD SUGAR AND
USING AN INSULIN PUMP.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT THAT I
TAKE MY CONDITION SERIOUSLY
SINCE IT'S ALSO AFFECTING
SOMEONE ELSE, BECAUSE I'M
PREGNANT.
IN TWO MONTHS I'LL BE HAVING
OUR DAUGHTER PEYTON.
>> THAT'S GIRL PARTS.
>> [laughs]
WHEN SHAWN AND I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, I WANTED TO STAY AT MY
MOM'S.
>> I GOT YOU GUYS SOME CLOTHES
FOR THE BABY.
>> OH, THAT IS REALLY CUTE.
BUT SHAWN'S WORK IS OVER AN HOUR
AWAY, SO WE DECIDED TO
COMPROMISE AND LIVE WITH HIS
FAMILY, SO HE CAN PICK UP AS
MANY SHIFTS AS POSSIBLE.
>> JUST SO YOU KNOW, I'M ALSO
WILLING TO WORK THIRD SHIFT.
>> OKAY, SHAWN.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
GOT TO MAKE MONEY SOMEHOW.
>> SHAWN HAS PROBLEMS SAVING
MONEY BECAUSE OF SPEEDING
TICKETS AND COURT FINES.
I HOPE HE'S DONE BEING RECKLESS,
BECAUSE I REALLY WANT TO GET OUR
OWN PLACE.
[laughter]
>> OUR HOUSE IS GONNA BE ON A
REAL STRICT DIET HERE SOON.
YOU KNOW WITH HER DIABETES
SHE CAN'T HAVE REGULAR SYRUP.
>> HAS YOUR DIABETES BEEN GOING
UP AND DOWN LIKE IT WAS BEFORE
OR...
>> I HAVE, LIKE, TIMES WHERE IT
WILL BE GOOD, YOU KNOW, AND THEN
IT SEEMS LIKE MY BODY JUST NEEDS
MORE INSULIN, SO MY BLOOD SUGARS
ARE, LIKE, ALWAYS HIGH.
>> COULD IT, LIKE, GENETICALLY
GO TO THE BABY, THE TYPE THAT
YOU HAVE?
>> NOT AS FAR AS GENETICALLY,
BUT IF MY BLOOD SUGARS WERE
SUPER-UNCONTROLLED, SHE WOULD
HAVE A HIGH CHANCE OFF BECOMING
DIABETIC HERSELF.
DO YOU WANT TO GO PLAY, BOO?
ALL RIGHT, GOOD JOB EATING YOUR
BREAKFAST.
>> WHAT'S GONNA BE THE PLAN WITH
PEYTON?
LIKE, THE DAY THAT SHE COMES
HOME, ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO,
LIKE, STAY HERE?
>> WE HAVE, WHAT, EIGHT WEEKS
LEFT TILL SHE'S HERE?
>> THAT EIGHT WEEKS IS FLYING
BY.
>> I'M TAKING EVERY DAY OF THESE
EIGHT WEEKS TO TRY AND WORK AT
THE PLASTICS FACTORY AND HOPING
I CAN TAKE EVERY LAST DOLLAR I
HAVE AND PUT IT TOWARD THE PLACE
FOR NOW.
>> MY GREATEST FEAR FOR YOU GUYS
IS TO THINK YOU HAVE TO MOVE
OUT.
I DON'T WANT YOU GUYS TO RUSH
INTO ANYTHING AND PUT YOURSELF
IN DEBT.
YOU'RE AT THE AGE TO WHERE I
WAS.
I'M NOT GONNA SAY IT'S GONNA BE
EASY, BECAUSE AT 19 YEARS OLD
WITH TWO KIDS...CAN BE ROUGH.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA FEEL WHEN YOU
GO BACK TO SCHOOL,
AND WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO IF
IT--
>> I--I REALLY DON'T--DON'T WANT
TO PUT HER IN DAY CARE.
BUT, I MEAN, I HATE TO PUT THE
RESPONSIBILITY ON YOU GUYS--
>> THAT'S MY JOB.
I SIT AT HOME, AND I BABYSIT.
THAT'S PART OF BEING A GRANDMA.
>> I KNOW.
>> IF YOU GUYS CAN'T DO IT,
STAY HERE AND GET ON YOUR FEET.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHERE YOU'RE
COMING FROM.
BUT HOPEFULLY, WE'LL HAVE OUR
OWN PLACE BY THEN.
I'M REALLY HOPING SO.
IT JUST DOESN'T SEEM THAT WAY,
BECAUSE EVERY TIME WE TRY TO
SAVE MONEY, IT GETS BLOWN.
>> AND THAT'S WHAT I'M WORRIED
ABOUT.
>> EVERYTHING IS GONNA CHANGE
WHEN THE BABY COMES, SO WE'RE
SPENDING SOME TIME WITH OUR
FRIENDS WHILE WE STILL CAN.
HEY, GUYS.
YOU GUYS READY TO GO HAVE A
CONCERT IN THE CORN?
>> [together] YEAH.
>> THIS IS KIND OF, LIKE, YOUR
LAST DAY OUT, YOUR LAST FUN
TIME--
>> RIGHT, WE'RE TRYING OUR BEST
TO, LIKE, GO OUT NOW BEFORE
WE'RE TIED DOWN TO THE HOUSE ALL
DAY WITH A NEWBORN.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT HAVING
TWO KIDS AT YOUR AGE?
LIKE, DID YOU EVER PICTURE--
>> NO, NEVER.
REMEMBER WHEN ME AND SHAWN
TOLD YOU GUYS WE WERE PREGNANT?
>> WELL, I THINK YOU SHOWED ME
THE TEST.
>> YES, I TOOK IT AT YOUR HOUSE.
>> AND YOU SHOWED ME THE
PREGNANCY TEST, AND YOU WERE
LIKE, "WHAT IS THIS?"
AND I'M LIKE, "WHAT IS IT?"
AND WE KIND OF LOOKED AT IT FOR
A SECOND.
>> I DIDN'T EVEN GET OFF THE
TOILET.
I JUST SAT ON THE TOILET AND
CRIED.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY?
WHEN YOU TEXTED ME AND TOLD ME,
I WAS SITTING ON THE JOHN.
[laughter]
>> DID YOU USE ANY KIND OF
PROTECTION, ANY BIRTH CONTROL?
>> I WAS ON DEPO WHENEVER WE
WERE FIRST TOGETHER, AND THEN I
GOT OFF OF DEPO AND STILL NEVER
HAD ANY PERIODS FOR MONTHS.
BUT THAT TEST SURE DIDN'T LIE
NOW, DID IT?
>> WHAT THOUGHT RAN THROUGH YOUR
MIND WHEN YOU FIRST, LIKE,
ACTUALLY KNEW?
>> HOW AM I GONNA HAVE A
THREE-YEAR-OLD AND A NEWBORN
BABY?
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA NOW?
>> NO.
[laughs]
>> I'M PRETTY SURE WHENEVER I
FOUND OUT ALEAH WAS PREGNANT,
I DIDN'T HAVE SEX FOR, LIKE, A
MONTH.
[laughter]
[rock music]
**
>> UGH.
[laughs]
THIS HAYRIDE IS GONNA MAKE ME GO
INTO LABOR.
[laughs]
>> * FEEL FREE TO
* GO AND TAKE A RIDE
*THIS AMERICAN DREAM *
>> SHE WAS DANCING A MINUTE AGO.
SHE SAID, "I'M READY TO PARTY."
**
*YOU START A PARTY *
* THE MIDDLE OF THE STREET
*SAY WHAT YOU WANT TO SAY *
* BE WHAT YOU WANT TO BE
*WHOA, OH-OH-OH, OH-OH-OH *
>> WHOO!
>> HAVING NOAH IN MY LIFE REALLY
MADE ME REALIZE HOW HARD IT IS
TO RAISE A CHILD.
>> HERE.
BRUSH 'EM GOOD.
>> AND NOW IT'S GOING TO BE
TWICE AS HARD WHEN PEYTON
ARRIVES.
>> GET YOUR BACK TEETH.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO GET DRESSED.
HOLD YOUR TOWEL UP.
>> COME HERE, BABY.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET IN BED.
>> HOLD ON.
BEFORE HE LAYS DOWN, CAN I HAVE
A HUG AND KISS?
GIVE ME A HUG.
>> DADDY.
>> WHAT?
>> GIVE ME A KISS.
YOU DON'T GET NO CARTOONS
TONIGHT, BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T
LISTEN TO DADDY LAST NIGHT,
OKAY?
BUT IF YOU DO GOOD TONIGHT AND
YOU GO TO BED LIKE A BIG BOY,
YOU CAN GET CARTOONS TOMORROW.
DOES THAT SOUND FAIR?
NO?
WELL, THAT'S THE WAY IT WORKS,
DUDE.
GIVE ME A HIGH FIVE.
GIVE DADDY A HUG AND KISS.
YES, YOU DID, BUT OKAY.
>> ANYTHING TO STAY OUT OF BED A
LITTLE LONGER.
KISS.
GOOD NIGHT.
I LOVE YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING,
OKAY?
>> GOOD NIGHT.
I LOVE YOU.
>> HI.
BECAUSE OF MY DIABETES, I'M
MEETING WITH A LABOR COACH TO
HELP ME DEAL WITH MY HIGH-RISK
PREGNANCY.
>> YOU KNOW THAT THE RISK WITH
DIABETES DURING PREGNANCY AND
DELIVERY ARE FEW BUT PRETTY
SERIOUS, RIGHT?
>> HONESTLY, WHENEVER YOU GET
PREGNANT AS A TEENAGER,
YOU DON'T THINK, YOU KNOW, "OH,
I HAVE ALL THESE HEALTH ISSUES
TO DEAL WITH."
YOU THINK OF, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
"HOW AM I GONNA FINISH SCHOOL?
HOW AM I GONNA PROVIDE FOR THIS
BABY?"
YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHERE MY MIND
WAS WHENEVER I GOT PREGNANT.
WHAT HAVE YOUR DOCTORS GONE OVER
WITH YOU SO FAR?
>> I HAVE REALLY ROLLER-COASTER
BLOOD SUGARS.
WHEN I FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT,
I WENT TO THE HOSPITAL, AND THE
DOCTOR TOLD ME, "YOU HAVE, LIKE,
A 50-50 CHANCE OF EVEN CARRYING
THIS BABY."
>> YEAH.
>> HE WAS LIKE, "YOU'RE PROBABLY
JUST GONNA HAVE A MISCARRIAGE,
TO BE HONEST."
>> AND ANOTHER RISK WITH TYPE 1
DIABETES IS A PREMATURE BABY
THAT MIGHT NEED TO BE DELIVERED
BECAUSE OF COMPLICATIONS WITH
THE BLOOD SUGARS.
>> RIGHT.
>> OKAY, SO THE ULTIMATE RISK
IS, OF COURSE, DELIVERING A
STILLBORN BABY.
>> RIGHT.
>> THAT STILLBORN DELIVERY IS--
IS HARD.
IT'S HARD TO THINK ABOUT.
IT'S HARD TO TALK ABOUT WITH
PEOPLE, BUT IT'S A REALITY.
>> I THINK THAT I WOULD JUST
FEEL SO BAD IF SOMETHING WOULD
BE WRONG WITH HER.
IT JUST SEEMS LIKE EVEN THOUGH
I'M TAKING GOOD CARE OF MYSELF,
ALL OF THESE THINGS ARE OUT OF
MY CONTROL.
LIKE, I'VE TRIED MY BEST TO TAKE
CONTROL OF MY DIABETES, BUT
ALL OF THESE THINGS ARE STILL,
LIKE, STACKING UP AGAINST ME.
>> SO YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
ARE YOU EXCITED YET?
>> KIND OF, BUT THEN, LIKE, THE
FURTHER ALONG I GET, THE MORE
NERVOUS I GET.
AND THEN WE WON'T HAVE TO WORRY
SO MUCH.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S THE BIGGEST FEAR FOR
ME, THAT SHE'LL COME EARLY.
WHENEVER YOU TOLD ME THAT YOU
WERE PREGNANT, I HAD THE SAME
FEELING AS I DID THE DAY THAT
THEY TOLD ME THAT YOU HAD
DIABETES.
WE WERE BOTH TRYING TO ABSORB
IT AND FREAKING OUT ALL AT THE
SAME TIME.
I JUST FELT LIKE, "NOW
EVERYTHING CHANGES,
AND YOU'VE GOT TO REALLY TAKE
CARE OF YOURSELF NOW."
>> I MEAN, THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
I WORRY ABOUT ALL THE TIME, YOU
KNOW.
EVERY TIME MY BLOOD SUGAR IS
HIGH, I, LIKE, FREAK OUT, AND
HONESTLY, I CRY, BECAUSE THERE'S
A WHOLE LOT OF THINGS THAT COULD
GO WRONG, AND NOW THAT I'M
PREGNANT, ANY TIME IT'S, LIKE,
OVER 150, THERE'S, LIKE,
IMMEDIATE CONSEQUENCES FOR IT.
I JUST--I WANT TO GIVE HER THE
BEST SHOT THAT I CAN.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> EVEN WITH MANAGING MY
DIABETES, I NEED TO KEEP UP WITH
SCHOOL SINCE I'M GOING TO TAKE
TWO MONTHS OFF WHEN PEYTON
ARRIVES, AND I DON'T WANT TO
FALL BEHIND.
SO WOULD YOU SET THAT UP X OVER
20 EQUALS 40 OVER 100?
>> EXACTLY, EXACTLY.
>> WITH EVERYTHING ELSE ON MY
PLATE, THE CHAOS AT SHAWN'S
HOUSE CAN BE OVERWHELMING.
>> DEVIN DID IT.
>> YOU DID IT.
>> I DIDN'T
I SWEAR.
>> NIGHT-NIGHTTIME.
GOOD NIGHT.
I LOVE YOU.
I REALLY WANT TO GET OUR OWN
PLACE, BUT SHAWN CAME HOME WITH
ANOTHER SPEEDING TICKET.
AND I HAD--STICK SHIFTS ARE
REALLY EASY TO SPEED IN.
>> YOU MAKE ME SO MAD.
YOU NEED TO SLOW DOWN.
AND WE NEED TO BE MORE CAREFUL
ABOUT REALLY WRITING DOWN HOW
MUCH MONEY NEEDS TO BE PAID.
>> I'M DEFINITELY REALIZING IT'S
NOT WORTH THE SPEEDING.
>> [sighs]
AS FAR AS THE NOISE LEVEL IN
THIS HOUSE BEING AN
ALL-THE-TIME THING, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT YOU
WOULD WANT TO HAVE A BABY AROUND
ALL OF THE TIME.
HOW REALISTIC IS IT FOR US TO
GET OUR OWN PLACE BEFORE PEYTON
GETS HERE?
>> IF I DO GET MY 40 HOURS AT
THE PLASTIC FACTORY, I'LL BRING
HOME, LIKE, 200 A WEEK IF THE
WORK STAYS STEADY.
I DIDN'T GET WORK LAST WEEK, SO
I'VE GOT NO MONEY COMING IN THIS
WEEK.
AS OF NOW, I'M NOT MAKING MUCH
FOR NEXT WEEK EITHER.
IT'S STARTING TO LOOK MORE AND
MORE LIKE IT'S GONNA BE
IMPOSSIBLE TO GET A PLACE IN
TIME,
AND I APOLOGIZE.
>> I'M DUE IN A MONTH, AND SINCE
WE'RE TIGHT ON MONEY, I'M REALLY
GLAD MY MOM IS THROWING US A
BABY SHOWER.
>> OKAY, YOU ALL ARE GONNA TAKE
THESE BALLOONS AND PUT THEM
UNDER YOUR SHIRT LIKE YOU'RE
PREGNANT LIKE ALEAH.
>> YOU WANT TO BELLY BUMP?
YOU DON'T WANT THIS?
YEAH, YOU RIP THAT OPEN.
>> WHOO.
WE GOT OURSELVES A CAR SEAT
AND A STROLLER.
"I'M FOLLOWING HIM IN MOMMY'S
FOOTSTEPS."
THE BEGINNING OF PEYTON'S
COLLEGE FUND.
>> OH, BOY.
>> SINCE THE SHOWER WAS NEAR MY
MOM'S, WE DECIDED TO STAY WITH
HER THAT NIGHT.
YOU GONNA GO NIGHT-NIGHT LIKE A
BIG BOY?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, HERE'S YOUR
SPONGEBOB.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING,
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> IS THAT IT?
>> YEP.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE TO
START WITH ALL OF THIS STUFF.
>> YEAH, I WAS THINKING THE SAME
THING.
[device chimes]
WHAT'S THAT SAYING?
>> DON'T JUST MUTE IT.
>> [laughs]
CHECK MY BLOOD SUGAR.
>> WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU
CHECKED YOUR BLOOD?
>> LAST TIME I CHECKED IT WAS
BEFORE WE STARTED REALLY
CLEANING UP FOR THE BABY SHOWER.
>> I FIGURED YOU'D CHECKED IT
WHEN WE GOT HERE.
>> IT'S 285.
>> UH-OH.
YOUR BLOOD SUGAR HAS BEEN JACKED
THE PAST COUPLE DAYS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
>> YOU'RE EITHER SUPER HIGH OR
SUPER LOW.
>> THIS IS NOT GOOD STUFF
AT ALL.
I'M NOT VERY HAPPY ABOUT IT.
LIKE, A NORMAL DIABETIC'S BLOOD
SUGAR SHOULD BE 80 TO 180.
WITH NUMBERS LIKE THESE,
THINGS AREN'T LOOKING VERY GOOD
FOR HER.
IT JUST SUCKS.
>> GONNA BE OKAY.
IT'S ALL GONNA BE OKAY.
>> BUT THAT NIGHT THINGS GOT
WORSE, AND MY DOCTOR TOLD ME TO
GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
MY MOM HAD TO GO TO WORK, SO
SHAWN IS STAYING WITH NOAH WHILE
I GO TO THE E.R. TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
THEY STARTED ME ON AN I.V. TO
HELP REGULATE MY BLOOD SUGAR
LEVELS, BUT I'M REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT PEYTON.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> TIRED.
I KIND OF BAWLED MY EYES OUT A
LITTLE BIT.
I DON'T KNOW.
THE DOCTOR SAID THAT THE MAIN
REASON WHY HE REALLY WANTS TO
GET MY BLOOD SUGARS UNDER
CONTROL IS BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
WANT TO CHANCE AT STILLBIRTH.
>> HE SAID THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> SHAWN TOOK NOAH TO HIS MOM'S
HOUSE SO HE COULD COME BE WITH
ME AT THE HOSPITAL.
MY BLOOD SUGAR LEVELS ARE STILL
OUT OF CONTROL, SO AFTER A
COUPLE OF TESTS, THE DOCTORS
DECIDED TO DELIVER PEYTON THREE
WEEKS EARLY.
>> HEY.
>> IT'S ABOUT TIME.
>> HI, HONEY.
>> NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> WHAT'S UP, BOSS?
PRETTY MAMA.
>> HI.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> I'M FEELING LIKE I'M HAVING
CONTRACTIONS.
>> HOW FAR APART ARE THEY?
>> LIKE, A MINUTE.
>> THAT CAN GO ON A LONG TIME,
THOUGH.
>> I'M STARTING TO GET REALLY
IMPATIENT.
LET'S GET IT GOING, MAN.
LET'S GET THOSE FORCEPS UP.
OH, MY GOSH.
[groans]
>> YOU WANT SOME OF MY TISSUE
WITH IT?
>> I AM IN SO MUCH PAIN.
I THINK I MIGHT THROW UP.
>> ALEAH'S WATER JUST BROKE.
WHOO-WHOO.
AND THERE'S THE EXPECTED DADDY.
>> TIRED EXPECTED DADDY.
>> ARE YOU EXCITED, THOUGH?
>> YEAH.
>> [sobbing]
OH.
FINALLY, IT WAS TIME TO START
PUSHING.
[groaning]
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT...
[baby crying]
>> * HOLD ONTO HOPE LOVE
* I SEARCHED HIGH AND LOW
* FOR YOU
*FOR YOU *
* EACH DAY GETS CLOSER
*SO HOLD ON STRONGER TO ME *
>> HI, MAMA.
>> CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR
BEAUTIFUL LITTLE GIRL.
WELL, HELLO THERE, BEAUTIFUL.
[baby crying]
>> I FEEL GOOD.
>> I'M HAPPY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> SHE IS SO CUTE.
>> *YEAH, OH *
>> AFTER THE DELIVERY, WE
THOUGHT WE WERE IN THE CLEAR,
BUT THE DOCTORS NOTICED SHE WAS
HAVING TROUBLE BREATHING, SO
THEY RUSHED HER TO INTENSIVE
CARE.
MY PREGNANCY, THERE WAS
JUST ALWAYS SOMETHING GOING ON.
SHE WAS IN RISK OF A STILLBIRTH,
AND I JUST COULDN'T WAIT TO HAVE
HER SO THAT I COULD QUIT
WORRYING ABOUT STUFF LIKE THAT,
BUT...
YEAH.
I JUST WANT HER HERE.
>> IN INTENSIVE CARE, THEY FOUND
OUT PEYTON IS SUFFERING FROM LOW
BLOOD SUGAR, SO THEY PUT HER ON
AN I.V. TO HELP STABILIZE HER.
PEYTON'S BLOOD SUGAR KEEPS
DROPPING.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE THAT SUGAR
COMING FROM ME ANYMORE, SO SHE'S
BOTTOMING OUT.
>> SO THEY ENDED UP HAVING TO
STICK THE I.V. IN HER
TO GIVE HER SOME SUGAR.
>> YEAH.
APPARENTLY, IT'S REALLY COMMON
IN, LIKE, ALL DIABETIC WOMEN.
>> HEY, WE HAVE NORMAL FOOD.
>> OH, YOU'RE THE BEST.
MY VAGINA HURTS.
>> I COULD IMAGINE.
>> I FELT HER HEAD PASS MY PUBIC
BONE.
I FELT HER SHOULDERS COME OUT.
I FELT EVERYTHING.
>> THAT SOUNDS TERRIBLE.
>> IT WAS TERRIBLE.
>> DUDE, THAT WAS THE LOUDEST
SCREAM I'VE EVER HEARD IN MY
LIFE.
>> [laughs]
>> AND I TOLD THEM--I WAS LIKE,
"I HAVE TO POOP.
I REALLY HAVE TO POOP.
LIKE, GET ME A BEDPAN.
I'M GONNA GO ALL OVER THIS BED."
[laughter]
AND SHE WAS LIKE, "NO, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO POOP.
THAT'S THE BABY'S HEAD.
IT'S PUSHING ON YOUR RECTUM.
IT MAKES YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
REALLY HAVE TO POOP."
AND THEN SHE CHECKED ME, AND SHE
WAS LIKE, "YEAH, YOU'RE READY TO
GO.
LET'S GET YOU READY TO START
PUSHING."
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU THOUGHT YOUR BABY WAS
POOP.
THAT'S KIND OF FUNNY.
>> WHEN I GO POOP AND I'M
PUSHING FOR 30 MINUTES, I
USUALLY JUST GET UP, SO...
[laughter]
>> WE STAYED WITH PEYTON FOR A
EXTRA DAYS IN THE HOSPITAL,
AND WE WERE SO HAPPY WHEN WE
WERE TOLD EVERYTHING HAD
STABILIZED.
PEYTON'S GONNA GO HOME TODAY.
>> TODAY'S THE DAY.
>> *OH, I WISH YOU COULD SEE *
* WHAT YOU ARE
*TO ME *
>> IT FEELS SO GOOD TO BE OUT OF
THE HOSPITAL.
ME NEITHER.
>> HERE SHE COMES.
>> OOH, WOW.
>> YOU NEED ME TO HOLD HER?
>> I GOT HER. I GOT HER.
>> SIT IN THE CORNER.
SIT IN PAPA'S SEAT.
>> AND I WANT TO HOLD HER...
>> THANK YOU, CHEYENNE.
>> I WANT TO HOLD HER.
>> ISN'T SHE PRETTY?
I LOVE THIS LITTLE GIRL.
THIS IS MY PRINCESS.
[baby crying]
>> HEY.
HEY, PSST.
>> COME FOR A SEC.
HI, BABY GIRL.
>> I AM SO GLAD TO BE HOME.
WATCHING YOUR BABY BE IN THE
I.C.U. IS DEFINITELY ONE OF THE
HARDEST THINGS I'VE EVER BEEN
THROUGH BEFORE.
I JUST FELT LIKE I'M SUPPOSED TO
PROTECT HER FROM ALL THAT STUFF,
YOU KNOW.
I'M GLAD SHE'S DOING MUCH BETTER
NOW.
>> IS THAT GOING TO CAUSE PEYTON
EVENTUALLY TO HAVE DIABETES?
>> OF COURSE THAT'S MY BIGGEST
FEAR, IS HER HAVING DIABETES,
BUT THE DOCTOR SAID WE'RE CLEAR
FOR NOW.
AND THEY'LL TEST FOR IT WHEN
SHE'S OLDER, OF COURSE, LIKE
THEY DO FOR EVERYBODY.
BUT SHE'S HEALTHY, AND I'M
HEALTHY.
>> THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
>> YEAH.
[baby cooing]
>> BECAUSE IT'S SO CRAMPED AT
SHAWN'S, IT'S BEEN CHALLENGING
LIVING HERE, SO HE'S BEEN
WORKING EVERY NIGHT AT THE
FACTORY SO WE CAN SAVE UP FOR
OUR OWN PLACE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> NOW DO YOU WANT SOME?
>> AFTER YOU GO POTTY AGAIN,
I BETTER NOT CATCH YOU BACK UP
OUT OF THAT BED.
GO NIGHT-NIGHT.
READY TO TAKE A BATH?
[baby crying]
THIS WOULD BE EASIER IF DADDY
WAS HERE.
YEAH.
HUH?
YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET CORNER TIME.
GET IN YOUR BED.
GO NIGHT-NIGHT.
[baby crying]
OH, OHH.
OH.
>> DON'T MAKE ME DO SOME NINJA.
WAH!
>> GO.
GO LAY DOWN.
[baby crying]
>> [grunting]
>> AFTER THIS...
>> OH, I'M HURT.
>> JOSH AND KEVIN, KNOCK IT
OFF, DUDE.
>> HE'S DOING IT.
>> NOAH'S SLEEPING, AND SO IS
PEYTON.
>> ALEAH, I'LL GET THEM.
STOP, AND I'M NOT JOKING.
>> WAH!
>> YEAH, MAMA FEELS LIKE SHE'S
ABOUT TO SNAP OUT HERE.
AND YOU CAN'T SLEEP, AND NOAH
CAN'T SLEEP.
I COULD TEAR SOMEBODY'S HEAD OFF
RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
>> HELLO.
>> HERE TO LOOK AT THE
TOWNHOUSE, RIGHT?
>> YES.
SINCE THINGS ARE SO CRAZY AT
SHAWN'S, AND WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO
SAVE SOME MONEY, HIS MOM IS
WATCHING NOAH TODAY WHILE WE
LOOK AT APARTMENTS.
>> THERE'S TWO BEDROOMS,
1 1/2 BATHS.
>> THERE'S SOME PRETTY
DECENT-SIZED ROOMS.
>> THERE'S A HALF BATH,
WASHER AND DRIER HOOKUPS
IN THE UTILITY ROOM.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> NEW DISHWASHER.
THAT'S BRAND-NEW.
DO YOU CHARGE A DEPOSIT?
>> YEAH, THE DEPOSIT IS THE SAME
AS THE RENT, 550 RENT, 550
DEPOSIT.
>> OKAY.
[exhales]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> IT'S DECENT.
>> AS FAR AS THE LOCATION GOES,
THIS PLACE IS PERFECT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MAMA?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
I THINK THAT IF WE GOT OUR OWN
PLACE, IT WOULD HELP WITH SO
MANY DIFFERENT THINGS.
LET'S START A BUDGET.
ELECTRIC...
I'LL PUT 160.
OUR PHONE BILL...
>> $50 A MONTH.
>> CAR INSURANCE.
MINE'S 100.
>> MINE'S 60.
>> AM I MISSING SOMETHING?
>> YEAH, THE SPEEDING TICKETS.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU OWE TO THE
COURTS FOR YOUR SPEEDING
TICKETS?
>> SO I CALLED ALL THE COURTS,
AND I FIGURED THE TOTAL AMOUNT
THAT I OWE THEM, AND THIS I WHAT
I CAME UP WITH, EXCEPT IN
HILLSBORO, I HAVE THE SAME
CHARGE AGAIN, SO IT'S VIRTUALLY
GONNA BE THE SAME EXACT FINE
PLUS A $135 CLASS ON TOP OF IT.
>> 2,500.
I'M NOT INITIATING WHY THAT IS
SO RIDICULOUSLY HIGH FOR SOME
SPEEDING TICKETS.
>> WELL, HONESTLY,
I DIDN'T PAY MY SPEEDING TICKETS
IN TIME, SO THAT DOUBLES THE
FINE.
>> THIS DEFINITELY SLOWS DOWN
THE PROCESS OF GETTING OUR OWN
PLACE.
I'M JUST TRYING--REALLY TRYING
MY HARDEST NOT TO GET MAD ABOUT
IT.
>> SHAWN.
>> I CAN'T LET GO OF THESE
SPEEDING TICKETS, SHAWN.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE IF YOU WOULD STAY ON
TOP OF YOUR COURTS, YOU
WOULDN'T HAVE ALL OF THE FINES
THAT YOU HAVE.
I MEAN, IS THAT A LIE?
>> YOU'RE TELLING ME?
I'VE BEEN PISSED OFF.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MONEY I HAD IN
MY WALLET AND AIN'T NONE OF IT
MINE?
[baby crying]
>> [coughs]
IT'S NOT THAT BIG OF A DEAL.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE MOVING OUT
TOMORROW.
>> BUT THE MONEY IS RIDICULOUS.
>> IT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA HAVE MONEY
PROBLEMS PROBABLY THE REST OF
YOUR LIFE.
I MEAN, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I HAVE NOT HEARD YOU TWO ARGUE
UNTIL THIS DAMN MONEY CAME INTO
POSITION.
MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY.
>> I'M NOT GONNA SIT HERE AND GO
AGAINST YOU AND YOUR MOM.
I'M NOT DOING THAT.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
>> FORGET YOU.
I'M TRYING TO GET YOU GUYS TO
COMPROMISE, BECAUSE IT'S CRAZY
STUFF THAT'S OVER MONEY.
>> AND HOW MANY PEOPLE HAVE I
TOLD THIS AS MUCH MONEY AS I
SPEND IN TRAFFIC TICKETS, I
COULD HAVE BOUGHT A NEW CAR
WITH, SOMETHING NICER THAN I
HAVE?
YOU DON'T THINK I KNOW THIS
[bleep].
I DON'T NEED A SECOND MAMA.
I NEED A GIRLFRIEND, A MOTHER OF
MY CHILDREN, NOT OF ME.
>> EXACTLY, A MOTHER OF YOUR
CHILDREN.
THIS MONEY COULD HAVE BEEN SPENT
ON OUR KIDS.
SO YOU'RE GONNA SIT THERE AND
TELL ME THAT YOU WEREN'T MAD
WHENEVER YOU FOUND OUT THAT
DOLLAR AMOUNT?
>> BUT I DIDN'T TAKE IT OUT ON
YOU.
>> YOU DIDN'T TAKE IT OUT ON ME,
'CAUSE I DIDN'T GET THE
MOTHER[bleep] TICKETS.
SORRY, THAT'S THE WAY THE COOKIE
CRUMBLES.
>> I'M TIRED OF GOING IN
CIRCLES.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T THINK I CAN LIVE HERE
ANYMORE.
I'M LEAVING.
>> BYE.
PEYTON'S STAYING HERE.
>> NO, SHE'S NOT.
>> YES, SHE IS.
YOU BETTER GO AND FIND YOU
SOMETHING TO DO AND COOL YOUR
[bleep] HEAD.
I'M KEEPING MY DAUGHTER.
SHE'S NOT GOING NOWHERE.
>> SHE CAME OUT OF MY VAGINA--
>> YEAH, AND GUESS WHO PUT HER
IN THERE.
THIS GUY.
>> WE'RE NOT GONNA DO THIS,
OKAY?
YOU CANNOT JUST WALK OUT AND
EXPECT TO LEAVE AND TAKE HIS KID
AWAY FROM HIM.
>> SHE'S BREAST-FED, THOUGH.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU BOTTLE-FEED HER ALL THE
TIME.
YOU DON'T EVEN BREAST-FEED HALF
THE TIME.
>> YES, I DO.
>> MOM, I GOT THIS.
>> NO, BECAUSE THIS AIN'T GONNA
TURN INTO NO [bleep]
FREE-FOR-ALL BECAUSE OVER
SOMETHING STUPID.
>> AIN'T GONNA [bleep] BEG HER
TO STAY.
>> I GUESS YOU CAN KEEP HER FOR
TONIGHT, BUT I BETTER GET HER
BACK TOMORROW.
UGH.
ME AND SHAWN GOT INTO IT.
SO I STARTED PACKING MINE AND
PEYTON'S STUFF, AND HE WAS LIKE,
"I HOPE YOU DON'T THINK YOU'RE
TAKING PEYTON."
AND I SAID, "I HOPE YOU DON'T
THINK YOU'RE KEEPING HER."
>> EVEN THOUGH MY MOM SAYS I
SHOULD TAKE PEYTON WITH ME,
I'M TOO EXHAUSTED TO CONTINUE
FIGHTING ABOUT IT.
HI, MOM.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> UGH.
IT STARTED OFF ABOUT MONEY,
WHICH ALTOGETHER, IT'S 2,500
IN COURT FEES.
>> WOW, $2,500.
THAT'S PRETTY SIGNIFICANT.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG,
AND YOU DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY,
$2,500 IS NOT A PETTY THING TO
ARGUE ABOUT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
AND THEN I HAVE, LIKE, A LOT ON
MY PLATE.
LIKE, I'M TRYING TO TAKE CARE OF
A NEWBORN, BUT I'M ALSO TRYING
TO MAKE NOAH NOT FEEL LEFT OUT,
YOU KNOW, TO WHERE PEYTON IS
MORE IMPORTANT THAN HIM.
ALEAH, THAT HOUSE AND ALL THAT,
YOU KNOW, ALL THAT CONSTANT
PEOPLE AND IN AND OUT...
[sighs]
YOU NEED TO GET OUT OF THAT
SITUATION, 'CAUSE...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST--I'M JUST TRYING TO
FIGURE ALL THIS OUT, YOU KNOW.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW YOU'RE WELCOME
TO COME BACK HERE.
>> WE CAN'T, BECAUSE SHAWN'S
WORK IS BY HIS PARENTS.
>> I KNOW.
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO KEEP ALL
OF OUR FAMILY TOGETHER.
>> IF YOU WANT MY SUGGESTION ON
WHAT YOU SHOULD DO, JUST RELAX
AND SEE HOW YOU'RE FEELING
TOMORROW, 'CAUSE YOU NEVER WANT
TO MAKE A SNAP DECISION WHENEVER
YOU'RE ANGRY.
>> I THINK THAT MY PLAN IS GONNA
BE, I'M GONNA GO UP
THERE TOMORROW,
AND IF HE SEEMS LIKE HE'S OPEN
TO TALKING, THEN I GUESS WE'LL
TALK.
I JUST WANT EVERYTHING TO WORK
OUT, BUT...
[sighs]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GONNA DO
WITH MYSELF TONIGHT.
I LITERALLY THINK THAT WAS,
LIKE, THE HARDEST DECISION OF MY
LIFE TO LET HER STAY THERE ALL
NIGHT.
>> * ON
*ON THIS NIGHT *
*I WILL BIDE MY TIME *
**
HOW WAS SHE?
>> SHE WAS GOOD.
SHE ATE, LIKE, TWO HOURS AGO.
>> HELLO, MAMA'S PRETTY GIRL.
MOMMY MISSED YOU.
YES, I DID.
YOU SMELL SO GOOD.
I WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> WE SHOULD GO TO MY CAR.
IT'S MORE PRIVATE.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU DON'T MIND WATCHING HER
FOR A MINUTE, OF COURSE?
I FEEL BAD FOR BEING SO HARSH
AND SO MEAN ABOUT THE MONEY
SITUATION, BUT I WAS JUST MAD
THAT IT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT JUST ONE OR TWO
SPEEDING TICKETS THAT YOU HAVE.
IT'S A HANDFUL.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY FOR
HAVING A LEAD FOOT AND NOT
KNOWING HOW TO SLOW DOWN.
>> BUT ALSO, YOU WERE KIND OF
SELFISH AND A DOUCHE BAG,
ENDED UP COSTING MY FAMILY A
LOT OF MONEY.
>> I'M SORRY.
SO YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
ABLE TO FORGIVE ME AND COME
BACK?
>> I GUESS SO.
I WANT US TO BE TOGETHER AND BE
A FAMILY, BUT I JUST WANT TO
MAKE IT VERY CLEAR THAT IF YOU
GET ANOTHER SPEEDING TICKET, WE
ARE DONE.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> THERE YOU GO.
GET HER BACK.
THANK YOU.
IT'S BEEN A WEEK SINCE OUR
FIGHT, AND I'M TRYING TO MAKE IT
WORK AT SHAWN'S MOM'S HOUSE.
SHAWN PICKED UP EXTRA SHIFTS
SINCE WE NEED THE MONEY TO PAY
OFF ALL HIS DEBT, BUT THAT
NIGHT, SHAWN CALLED ME WITH
SOME BAD NEWS.
HE GOT PULLED OVER AND GOT
ANOTHER SPEEDING TICKET.
I'M FURIOUS.
DID YOU KNOW THAT YOUR SON GOT A
SPEEDING TICKET TODAY?
>> YEAH, I JUST WANTED TO KNOW.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHY I'M GOING TO
MY MOM'S.
>> REALLY?
>> AND IT'S NOT BETWEEN ME AND
YOU.
>> BECAUSE THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
[baby crying]
>> [speaking baby talk]
ALL THIS CRAZINESS.
THAT'S NOT MY CALL, BUD.
I'M SORRY.
I LOVE YOU.
BYE, BABY.
[line trilling]
>> YEAH.
>> ONCE AGAIN, HERE GOES MORE OF
OUR KIDS' MONEY GOING TOWARDS
THE COURT.
THE SAME THING HAPPENS EVERY
TIME.
IT'S ALL THE SAME CYCLE OVER AND
OVER AND OVER, AND I'M OVER IT.
>> SHAWN HAS TO--HE'S GOT TO
GROW UP.
>> COP CLOCKED HIM AT 69 IN A
50.
YOU KNOW HOW EXPENSIVE THAT
TICKET IS GONNA BE?
>> HE'S GONNA HAVE TO GO GET A
LAWYER AND HAVE IT REDUCED DOWN.
>> WITH THE MONEY THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO GO TOWARDS OUR KIDS,
HE HAS TO GO GET A LAWYER.
>> THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU
HAVE KIDS AT YOUR AGE.
YOU GUYS ARE GONNA HAVE
PROBLEMS, TEENAGE PROBLEMS WHEN
YOU'RE TRYING TO BE IN AN ADULT
SITUATION.
>> I'M STARTING TO REALIZE HOW
STUPID I AM.
>> YEAH, AND I DON'T WANT YOU TO
SPLIT UP WITH SHAWN, BECAUSE I
THINK THAT THE NATURAL PARENTS
SHOULD TRY AND TRY AGAIN.
AND I LOVE NOAH TOO, YOU KNOW,
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD GO
BACK TO THAT HOUSE.
>> YEAH.
I'M STILL REALLY MAD, AND I
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO, BUT
SHAWN'S COMING OVER TODAY TO SEE
PEYTON.
[knocks]
HI, NO-NO.
CAN I HAVE A HUG?
I FEEL LIKE I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
IN FOREVER.
>> ME AND DADDY CAME HERE.
>> YEAH, YOU AND DADDY CAME
HERE.
I THINK THAT THERE'S A COUPLE
THINGS THAT ME AND YOU NEED TO
TALK ABOUT.
>> AND I DON'T WANT TO ARGUE.
HI.
HI, REIANNIE.
>> I'M SURE WHENEVER YOU CALLED
ME, YOU KNEW MY REACTION WOULD
BE THAT I WOULD GET MAD.
>> I CAN'T BLAME YOU.
I FEEL LIKE A DUMBASS JUST AS
MUCH AS YOU LOOK AT ME LIKE I'M
A DUMBASS.
>> HONESTLY, IT'S NOT OKAY THAT
YOU GOT A SPEEDING TICKET, BUT
I WANT TO GET OVER IT,
BECAUSE I THINK THAT OUR FAMILY
IS MORE IMPORTANT
AND TRY TO MY BEST TO MOVE ON
FROM IT AND
JUST GRIT MY TEETH AND WATCH YOU
PAY IT, I GUESS.
>> WHY YOU SQUIRMING, MAMA?
WHAT ARE YOU KICKING AT?
>> SO HERE'S THE PLAN.
I'M GONNA LIVE HERE WITH PEYTON.
>> I DON'T LIKE BEING AWAY FROM
YOU OR HER.
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT HER TO BE
RAISED WITHOUT YOU.
AND I DON'T LIKE SPENDING TIME
AWAY FROM YOU EITHER.
AND I'M ABOUT TO START SCHOOL
TOO.
WILL YOU COME HERE AND WATCH THE
KIDS THE DAYS THAT I HAVE
SCHOOL?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD, AND IT'S
NOT WHAT EITHER OF US WANTED,
BUT I THINK THAT THIS EVENT
KIND OF PUT A FIRE UNDER OUR
ASS TO GET OUR OWN PLACE.
AND EVEN IF WE'RE NOT HAPPY,
WE AREN'T ALLOWED TO JUST THROW
IN THE TOWEL ANYMORE,
BECAUSE WE HAVE KIDS.
>> *DON'T TELL ME THE TRUTH *
* TELL ME THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN *
*THERE'S BEEN A MISTAKE *
* THERE'S BEEN A MISUNDERSTAND *
>> WHEN I PICTURED MY LIFE AFTER
I HAD PEYTON, THIS IS NOT HOW I
PICTURED IT AT ALL.
SHAWN AND I ARE STILL TOGETHER.
I THINK THAT WE'RE BOTH TRYING
TO MAKE THINGS WORK FOR THE
KIDS.
[baby crying]
DON'T YOU START WITH ME.
I WISH THAT THINGS WERE EASIER
FOR US TO BE TOGETHER AND EASIER
FOR US TO BE HAPPY.
I WANT US TO BE ABLE TO PUT ALL
OF OUR MONEY AND ALL OF OUR
RESOURCES INTO FINDING OUR
OWN PLACE AND TO DOING
THINGS WITH OUR KIDS,
BUT INSTEAD, THEY'RE GOING
TO COURTS.
I THINK MY GREATEST CHALLENGE IS
GOING TO BE FINDING THE TIME TO
FINISH SCHOOL AND TAKE CARE OF
BOTH KIDS.
IT'S A LOT, AND WHEN I THOUGHT
ABOUT MYSELF GOING TO COLLEGE,
I FIGURED I'D BE LIVING ON
CAMPUS, I WOULD BE
PARTY-HOPPING, BUT I DON'T
REALLY HAVE THAT OPPORTUNITY
ANYMORE.
I LOVE YOU.
I FEEL LIKE MY KIDS DESERVE
SO MUCH MORE THAN I CAN GIVE
THEM, AND THAT HURTS.
I--I DEFINITELY WANT BETTER FOR
THEM.
I WISH I WOULD HAVE WAITED
UNTIL I HAD THINGS TOGETHER.
[chime dings]
>> *I'M NOT AFRAID *
* TEARING YOUR HEART
*INTO PIECES *
*
>> I JUST HOPE THAT HE HAS
ENOUGH TIME WITH HER, THE TIME
THAT HE WANTS, THE TIME THAT HE
NEEDS.
>> JUST SO WE CLEAR, NO
VISITATION WHEN THERE'S NO
ADULTS HERE.
>> IT'S BEEN HARD MIXING OUR
DIFFERENT SCHEDULES AND GETTING
HIM TIME TO SPEND WITH LAYLA.
>> AND THAT'S PISSING ME OFF AND
IRRITATING ME.
>> WHAT YOU WANT TO DO IS
REMEMBER YOUR IRRITATION IS
SITTING IN MY HOUSE.