[up-tempo percussive music]
*
>> HI, MY NAME IS FARRAH.
I LIVE IN COUNCIL BLUFFS, IOWA,
SMACK IN THE MIDWEST.
BUT I'M ANYTHING BUT
A SMALL-TOWN GIRL.
I HAVE BIG, BIG DREAMS, AND
I PLAN ON MAKING THEM HAPPEN.
RIGHT NOW, I'M A SENIOR
AT THOMAS JEFFERSON HIGH SCHOOL.
AND I'M A CHEERLEADER.
GONNA HAVE TO FALL ON THE GROUND
AND GET BACK UP.
TYLER IS MY BEST FRIEND...
>> AND SO IS ZABRINA.
>> I'M SUPER BUSY ALL THE TIME,
JUGGLING WORK, SCHOOL,
AND CHEER.
>> all: LOUDER! LOUDER!
DON'T BE SHY!
STAND AND GIVE YOUR BATTLE CRY!
>> THE ONLY PROBLEM IS,
I CRASHED MY CAR, SO I HAVE TO
RELY ON MY MOM, DAD, AND SISTER
TO DRIVE ME AROUND.
ARE YOU GUYS LEAVING?
I'M SERIOUSLY STILL ON MY WAY.
BECAUSE I'M A CHEERLEADER,
I HAVE TO STAY IN SHAPE,
WHICH IS FINE BECAUSE I LOVE
WORKING OUT.
EVEN THOUGH RIGHT NOW I'M STILL
A SIZE 2, I WON'T BE FOR LONG
BECAUSE I AM PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
SO I HAVEN'T TOLD THE BABY'S
DAD I'M PREGNANT.
I BROKE UP WITH HIM BECAUSE HE'S
WAY TOO JEALOUS AND IMMATURE,
BUT IT HASN'T QUITE
GOTTEN THROUGH TO HIM.
OH, NOW HE'S CALLING ME.
HELLO.
>> FARRAH.
>> YES?
>> NO, I'M BUSY ALL TODAY.
>> BECAUSE I HAVE WORK, AND THEN
I'M GOING TO THE HAUNTED HOUSE
WITH THE GIRLS TONIGHT.
>> ZABRINA AND, LIKE,
THE CHEER GIRL--
>> TYLER.
>> NO.
CAN YOU HOLD ON--
CAN YOU HOLD ON ONE SECOND?
>> OKAY, BYE.
WHILE MY PARENTS HAVE
ACCEPTED THAT I'M PREGNANT,
THEY ARE DEFINITELY NOT HAPPY
WITH MY EX TRYING TO CONTACT ME.
>> TONIGHT WHEN YOU'RE AT THE
GAME, YOU CAN TALK TO YOUR
FRIENDS AND HAVE A GOOD TIME,
BUT I DON'T WANT YOU HAVING
ANYTHING TO DO WITH HIM.
>> WELL, HE SHOULDN'T BE THERE.
>> NO, HE SHOULDN'T.
BUT IF HE'S CALLING YOU AND
HARASSING YOU--
>> WELL, I DON'T TALK TO HIM
OR HIS, LIKE, FRIENDS.
>> IF HE CALLS YOU, JUST GET HIS
NUMBER BLOCKED AND STAY AWAY
FROM HIM.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO GET
A NUMBER BLOCKED, SO...
>> WELL, WE'LL CALL UP THE PHONE
COMPANY AND HAVE THEM BLOCK IT.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> SEE YOU LATER, DEBRA.
>> LOVE YOU.
SEE YOU LATER TONIGHT.
[upbeat percussive music]
*
>> [together] JACKETS!
GO, ORANGE! GO, RED!
BEAT THE LYNX TONIGHT!
>> WHEN I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, I TOLD A COUPLE OF MY
CLOSEST FRIENDS AND TOLD THEM
NOT TO TELL ANYONE.
BUT NOW PEOPLE ARE TALKING,
AND IT SEEMS LIKE THE WHOLE
SCHOOL KNOWS.
FIVE MISSED CALLS?
AND IT LOOKS LIKE THE WORD JUST
GOT OUT TO THE BABY'S DADDY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA SAY
TO HIM?
>> I'M GONNA JUST SAY NO.
THAT'S WHAT ME AND MY MOM
TALKED ABOUT.
THAT'S WHAT, LIKE, WE'VE TALKED
ABOUT.
>> EVERYBODY AT EVERY SCHOOL
IS SAYING RUMORS.
>> NONE OF THE GIRLS KNOW
BESIDES YOU AND COURTNEY, SO--
>> YOU'RE THAT POPULAR, FARRAH.
>> I WOULD HOPE THAT IF ONE OF
YOUR FRIENDS JUST WANTS TO KNOW
AND GET IN ON INFORMATION,
THAT YOU WOULD JUST BE LIKE,
"WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO ASK
FARRAH YOURSELF," OR, "I'M NOT
GONNA TALK ABOUT IT."
[upbeat rock music]
*
AT THE GAME, I WAS WORRIED
EVERYONE WAS GOSSIPING.
MAYBE I'M JUST BEING PARANOID.
BUT NOW IT'S TIME TO TELL
MY CLOSEST FRIENDS SO
I'M IN CONTROL OF WHO KNOWS.
HELLO.
>> HELLO, PRINCESS.
>> I WANTED TO SHARE SOMETHING
'CAUSE, LIKE, I REALLY TRUST YOU
CERTAIN PEOPLE, AND I WOULD HOPE
THAT YOU WOULD, LIKE, RESPECT
EVERYTHING, LIKE, I SAY TO YOU.
AND ZABRINA ALREADY KNOWS
AND TYLER.
I AM PREGNANT.
AND IT'S GONNA BE FIVE MONTHS
BY THE END OF NEXT MONTH.
YOU GUYS DON'T LOOK SURPRISED.
>> THAT'S 'CAUSE, LIKE,
WE ALL KNEW.
>> THE CHEERLEADERS KNOW.
>> KYLA SAID TO ME ONE DAY
ABOUT IT--SHE'S LIKE, "DO YOU
KNOW FARRAH'S PREGNANT?"
I WAS LIKE, "WHO DID YOU HEAR
THIS FROM?"
>> ZABRINA, YOU SHOULD NOT TELL
ANYONE ELSE.
[chime dings]
I THOUGHT MY SECRET WAS SAFE
WITH ZABRINA, BUT OBVIOUSLY NOT.
>> FARRAH!
>> COMING.
AND NOW MY PARENTS WANT TO
TALK ABOUT EVERYTHING THAT'S
GOING ON.
>> EVEN IF PEOPLE ARE GOSSIPING
OR SAYING THINGS THAT ARE NOT
RIGHT, YOU REMEMBER THAT YOU
HAVE TO WALK WITH INTEGRITY.
>> YOU KNOW, RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE
IN THE EARLY PART OF YOUR
PREGNANCY, AND, YOU KNOW,
IT'S KIND OF STILL NOVEL AND
EVERYTHING, BUT THERE'S
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> YOU KNOW, LOOKING AT WHAT'S
BEST FOR THE CHILD AND HOW MUCH
TIME IT TAKES TO HAVE A BABY,
YOU KNOW...
>> MM-HMM.
>> IT MIGHT BE THE MOST LOVING
THING IS TO PUT THE CHILD UP FOR
ADOPTION.
HAVING A CHILD IS NOT LIKE
HAVING A PUPPY.
>> I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE
THAT HARD ONCE YOU LOOK
AT EVERYTHING AND GET
EVERYTHING TOGETHER AND
KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> BELIEVE ME, FARRAH,
IT'S EXHAUSTING.
[chime dings]
>> FOUR MONTHS AGO, MY BIGGEST
WORRY WAS WHAT I WAS GOING TO
WEAR TO PROM, AND NOW I HAVE
THE MOST IMPORTANT DECISION
OF MY LIFE TO MAKE.
>> MY EX FINALLY GOT THE PICTURE
WHEN I GOT A NEW PHONE AND I
DIDN'T GIVE HIM THE NEW NUMBER.
NOW I FEEL LIKE MORE THAN EVER
I KNOW WHAT I WANT.
IT'S TIME TO TELL MY MOM WHAT
I'M THINKING.
>> IT'S NOT EASY TO HAVE A CHILD
BY YOURSELF, LET ALONE BE
A TEENAGER, LET ALONE NOT HAVING
A DEGREE, NOT HAVING A GOOD JOB,
YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, IT'S AMAZING HOW MANY
PEOPLE HAVE ASKED ABOUT YOUR
BABY.
>> MOM, IF OTHER PEOPLE WHO
IT'S NOT PART OF THEM WANT TO
HAVE IT, WHY WOULDN'T YOU WANT
TO HAVE IT?
>> BABY, I'M JUST THINKING
ABOUT YOU.
>> [laughs] I JUST THINK--
OKAY.
>> SO WHAT DID YOU DECIDE ABOUT
YOUR BABY?
>> WE'RE FOR SURE KEEPING IT.
>> WE'RE KEEPING THE BABY, HUH?
>> YEAH.
SO IT'S DECIDED.
I'M GOING TO BE A SINGLE MOM.
BUT KEEPING THE BABY DOESN'T
MEAN MY PROBLEMS AT SCHOOL HAVE
GONE AWAY.
I FEEL LIKE I'M THE CENTER
OF AWKWARD STARES.
[girl laughs]
>> WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT?
I'M ABOUT READY TO REDIRECT
SOMEONE'S MOUTH.
EVEN THE CHEERLEADERS ARE ACTING
STRANGE.
THANK GOD FOR TYLER.
HE DIDN'T JUDGE ME AT ALL.
>> I'M JUST GONNA DO THE REGULAR
TANNING WHILE YOU'RE SPRAYING.
THAT WAY WE'RE DONE AT THE
SAME TIME.
>> IS IT OKAY IF I SIT IN HIS
ROOM WHILE HE TANS--WITH HIM.
IS THAT OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
[Tyler chuckles]
>> GIRLS ARE DRAMA.
IF YOU'RE NOT TELLING THE
PEOPLE, THEN APPARENTLY THEN
THAT IS YOUR BUSINESS,
NOT THEIRS.
>> IT WAS ZABRINA TALKING ABOUT
ME BEHIND MY BACK,
CAUSING [bleep]
WITH ME AND THE OTHER GIRLS.
IF YOU'RE GONNA ACT LIKE THAT,
THAT'S NOT A TRUE FRIEND.
>> AND YOU KNOW THEY JUDGE YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE A SINGLE MOM.
LIKE--
>> THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE LEADERS,
AND THEY'RE JUST NOTHING.
>> CHEER "LEADERS."
NOT CHEER "FOLLOWERS."
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT WHAT THEY
THINK ABOUT ME.
I DON'T EVEN CARE.
WHO CARES?
>> SO WHEN ARE WE GONNA DO THE
SENIOR PICTURE?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW BECAUSE
I DON'T HOW I'M GONNA BE AFTER
I'M PREGNANT.
SO IS IT GONNA TAKE, LIKE,
A MONTH FOR ME TO BE OKAY OR--
>> SO AFTER YOU HAVE THE BABY,
YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA BE ALL
PUFFED UP.
>> NO, I PLAN ON NOT BEING
THAT PUFFED UP, AND I PLAN
ON WORKING OUT.
>> WELL, YOU MAY PLAN ON IT,
BUT THAT'S NOT THE WAY IT GOES.
>> [laughs]
WELL, WE'LL BE SURPRISED,
WON'T WE, MOM?
I NEED TO LEAVE.
I WENT OUT FOR PIZZA WITH THE
TEAM, BUT THEY WERE STILL ACTING
REALLY WEIRD.
HELLO, HELLO.
HOW ARE YOU, LADIES?
[silence]
ARE YOU GUYS HUNGRY AT ALL?
OKAY, JUST IGNORE ME.
HEY, TY, WILL YOU, LIKE, SIT
AT THE SAME TABLE AS ME?
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TABLE
YOU WERE SITTING AT, SO...
>> I THINK MY FRIENDSHIP WITH
ZABRINA MIGHT BE OVER FOR GOOD.
THESE ARE SUPPOSED TO BE MY BEST
FRIENDS, BUT I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR HIGH SCHOOL OR THE CHEER
TEAM IF THIS IS HOW THEY'RE
GOING TO TREAT ME.
I QUIT.
>> AS MY BELLY CONTINUED TO
GROW, SO DID THE GOSSIP
AROUND HIGH SCHOOL, AND IT
QUICKLY BECAME UNBEARABLE.
SO MY MOM AND I DECIDED I SHOULD
STOP ATTENDING THOMAS JEFFERSON
AND FINISH MY REMAINING CREDITS
AT THE LOCAL COLLEGE.
>> SO WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR
ARE CLASSES THAT SHE CAN TAKE
WITHOUT HAVING TO COME, MAYBE,
TO CLASS, BUT DO SOMETHING
ONLINE.
>> ONE THING STUDENTS DON'T
UNDERSTAND: YOU HAVE TO BE VERY
DISCIPLINED, 'CAUSE COMING TO
CLASS, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
MOTIVATED TO COME, BUT HERE,
THERE'S NOBODY, YOU KNOW,
ACTUALLY MAKING YOU TURN IN
THE HOMEWORK.
YOU HAVE TO TURN IT IN YOURSELF.
>> WELL, WE ALL HAVE TO BE
GROWN-UP SOMETIMES.
>> I MEAN, WORKING, BEING
A MOTHER, BEING A STUDENT ALL AT
ONCE, IT'S A LOT TO TAKE ON.
[chime dings]
>> IT IS A LOT TO TAKE ON, BUT
LUCKILY, I HAVE MY MOM TO HELP
ME DEAL WITH EVERYTHING.
I FOUND OUT I'M HAVING A GIRL,
AND I'M GOING
TO NAME HER SOPHIA.
AND TODAY WE GET TO HEAR
HER HEARTBEAT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO LET'S LISTEN
HERE.
[soft rumbling]
>> THAT'D BE MY STOMACH OR
SOMETHING.
[rumbling grows louder]
WHAT IS THAT?
>> THAT'S THE BABY.
>> MONSTER BABY IN THERE.
[all laugh]
>> I'M JUST GONNA FEEL DOWN HERE
REAL QUICK.
>> OKAY.
>> THE HEAD IS RIGHT OVER HERE.
>> THE HEAD'S OVER HERE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, HOW COULD YOU HEAR
THE HEART OVER THERE?
>> 'CAUSE THE HEART'S IN THE
CHEST, NOT IN THE HEAD.
[both laugh]
ARE YOU GONNA BE IN THERE WHEN
SHE DELIVERS?
>> YOU KNOW, I--
>> HAVE YOU TALKED ABOUT
THAT YET?
>> I AM NOT REAL GOOD IN MEDICAL
SITUATIONS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> I PLAN ON NOT BREAST-FEEDING.
>> OKAY.
>> I PREFER NOT TO DO THAT.
I WOULD SAY, GOSH, IF YOU COULD
NURSE FOR A WEEK, TWO WEEKS,
AS LONG AS YOU COULD, I THINK
IT'S DEFINITELY GONNA BENEFIT
THE BABY.
IT'LL HELP PROTECT THEM AGAINST
COLD VIRUSES, BACTERIA,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
SO IT KEEPS THEM HEALTHIER.
IT'S GONNA BE MORE NATURAL
THAN YOU THINK IT IS.
>> I'M JUST WONDERING, WHAT
HAPPENS TO YOUR BOOBS IF YOU
BREAST-FEED?
>> NOTHING.
>> ALL I KNOW IS...
>> BEING PREGNANT--
>> WOMEN THAT HAVE HAD A LOT
OF BABIES, THEIR BOOBS SEEM TO
GET BIGGER AND SAGGIER.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> YEAH, DOESN'T IT MAKE YOUR
BOOBS MORE SAGGIER IF YOU
BREAST-FEED?
>> NO.
PREGNANCY WOULD DO THAT TO YOU.
>> ON THE WAY OUT OF THE
DOCTOR'S OFFICE, I GOT ASKED OUT
ON A DATE FOR TONIGHT, BUT I'M
SUPPOSED TO GO OUT TO DINNER
WITH MY PARENTS.
>> FARRAH...
>> OKAY, SO THERE'S THIS GUY
ROBERTO WHO WORKS WITH ME.
I THINK HE'S KIND OF CUTE,
SO I GAVE HIM MY NEW NUMBER.
[phone ringing]
HELLO?
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT. LATER.
>> WHAT TIME DID YOU WANT TO GO
TO DINNER?
LIKE AROUND 7:00?
>> PROBABLY MORE LIKE 8:00.
>> AND THEN I'M GONNA JUST GET
ICE CREAM WITH HIM REALLY QUICK,
AND THEN I'LL JUST COME HOME.
>> WELL, ALL I GOT TO SAY IS,
EXPLAIN TO HIM THAT YOU LIKE HIM
AS A GOOD FRIEND.
>> WELL, I'M NOT EVEN
GONNA SAY THAT.
I SHOULDN'T EVEN HAVE TO--
I'M NOT EVEN GONNA GO THERE.
"I LIKE YOU AS A GOOD FRIEND."
>> NO.
>> MOM, IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TO
GO THERE.
>> BUT HERE'S THE DEAL.
>> [laughs]
>> YOU LET HIM KNOW THAT YOU'RE
SIX MONTHS PREGNANT--
>> HE DOES KNOW THAT, MOM.
>> YEAH, WELL, YOU JUST...
>> EVERYONE AT WORK KNOWS THAT.
>> KIND OF REPEAT THAT TO HIM.
SAY, "HELLO, I AM SIX MONTHS
PREGNANT.
I AM NOT LOOKING FOR ANY KIND OF
A RELATIONSHIP AT ANY POINT
HERE."
[mellow rock music]
*
>> I SERIOUSLY LOVE THIS
PICTURE.
>> I DO TO. I LOVE YOUR HAIR.
>> IT WAS, LIKE, REALLY BLONDER
THEN.
>> WHAT ARE YOU UP TO TONIGHT?
>> SOME BOY THAT I WORK WITH,
WE PLAN ON GETTING SOME
ICE CREAM OR SOMETHING MAYBE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M NOT LOOKING FOR ANYTHING,
OBVIOUSLY.
MY MOM IS LIKE--YOU KNOW, LIKE,
EVEN ABOUT GUYS, SHE'S JUST
LIKE, "YOU DON'T NEED TO HAVE
THAT IN YOUR LIFE.
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH."
WELL, LIKE, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT
GONNA, LIKE, CUT MYSELF OFF
FROM DATING.
LIKE, I USED TO GO OUT ON DATES
ALL THE TIME.
I KNOW MY PRIORITIES.
IT'S JUST LIKE WHEN I WANT TO
HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF FREE TIME,
I WANT TO GO OUT.
>> YEAH.
[mid-tempo rock music]
*
>> AND HERE'S TO THE
NEW BEGINNING,
THE NEW COLLEGE STUDENT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU HAVE A DATE THIS EVENING?
>> WELL, MAYBE, POSSIBLY,
WITH THIS KID I WORK WITH.
SO I'M GONNA SEE--LIKE, WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO GO, LIKE, AROUND
9:30 OR 10:00, WHICH IS,
LIKE, COMING UP SOON HERE.
I WAS JUST TEXTING HIM,
AND HE HASN'T TEXTED ME BACK.
>> IT'S, LIKE, ABOUT 9:45 NOW.
>> HERE'S WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO...
WE'RE GOING TO TOAST
TO THE END OF MAY.
>> AND HE HASN'T TEXTED ME BACK
YET, SO...
>> BABY, BABY.
>> WHAT DOES THAT SHOW YOU?
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TO SAY.
>> WELL, LIKE, I MISS JUST
GOING OUT, SO...
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE ROBERTO
BLEW ME OFF.
MAYBE DATING ISN'T SUCH A GOOD
IDEA.
MY MOM AND SISTER ARE TAKING ME
TO VISIT THE HOSPITAL WHERE
I'LL BE DELIVERING MY BABY.
>> SO THIS WHAT OUR LABOR ROOMS
LOOK LIKE.
AND THIS ROOM HERE IS ACTUALLY
SET UP FOR DELIVERY.
ALL OF THE EQUIPMENT THAT WE
NEED FOR A DELIVERY IS IN
THE ROOM.
>> THIS IS REALLY NICE.
>> IT IS REALLY NICE.
>> SO WHO WILL BE HERE WITH YOU
DURING LABOR, INSIDE THE ROOM,
TO SUPPORT YOU?
>> ARE YOU GONNA BE IN THE ROOM,
ASHLEY, OR NO?
>> I CAN'T TAKE BLOOD.
BLOOD MAKES ME PASS OUT.
>> ME TOO.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE NEEDS THE
STRESS OF ME BEING ON THE FLOOR,
LIKE, KNOCKED OUT--
>> YOU GUYS COULD JUST TURN
AROUND AND LOOK AT THE WALL.
>> HONESTLY, SOMETIMES PEOPLE
KIND OF GET CAUGHT UP IN THE
MOMENT, AND THEY DON'T PAY A LOT
OF ATTENTION TO THE BLOOD AND
THE STUFF THAT'S GOING ON, SO...
BUT, I MEAN, YOU'LL KNOW HOW...
>> I PROBABLY WILL.
>> IT WORKS FOR YOU WHEN YOU
GET HERE.
>> OH, I DEFINITELY KNOW.
I WILL NOT BE LOOKING AT IT.
>> THEN MY OTHER QUESTION WAS,
LIKE, ABOUT INDUCING.
LIKE, WHAT DOES THAT--
LIKE, WHEN WOULD YOU DO THAT?
>> IT HAS TO BE YOUR DUE DATE.
IT CAN'T BE BEFORE YOUR
DUE DATE.
SO AS LONG AS...
>> YEAH, THOSE ARE THE DAYS.
>> YOU'RE DUE ON THOSE DAYS,
THEY WILL HAVE YOU COME IN.
>> FARRAH, DO WE HAVE TO GO
THROUGH ALL THIS?
>> YEAH, CAN WE NOT GO THROUGH
ALL THIS?
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THIS.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE
TO BE INDUCED.
THE BABY'S GONNA SHOOT OUT THERE
LIKE A DAMN BANANA IN A BANANA
PEEL.
AND YOU JUST THINK THEY'RE GONNA
HANDLE THIS.
I DO NOT HAVE TO ASK ALL THESE
GROTESQUE QUESTIONS.
>> WE CAN TALK ABOUT THIS
PRIVATELY IF IT'S MAKING THEM
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> I HAVE TO KNOW.
I WAS HOPING FOR MORE SUPPORT
FROM MY FAMILY.
I'M SCARED I'M GOING TO HAVE
TO DO THIS BY MYSELF.
[mid-tempo rock music]
*
>> OKAY.
>> IT'S SO COLD.
>> GOT TO SET THIS SOMEWHERE
WHERE IT CAN DRY.
>> MOM, DO NOT BEND IT.
WITH MY DUE DATE GETTING CLOSER,
EVERYONE IS GETTING MORE AND
MORE EXCITED.
IT'S TIME FOR THE BABY SHOWER.
HELLO, EVERYONE.
>> I LOVE THEM.
>> SHOES.
THESE ARE CUTE.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S HANDMADE OR
ANYTHING, BUT IT'S REALLY CUTE.
GETTING ALL THESE BABY ITEMS
REMINDED ME THAT IN JUST A SHORT
TIME, I'M GOING TO BE A MOM.
MOM!
>> WHAT?
>> I THINK MY WATER JUST BROKE.
>> ALL RIGHT, JUST BE CALM.
LET'S GO SEE.
LET'S SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE, AND THAT'S WHAT IT SMELLS
LIKE, SO...
[chuckles]
>> [scoffs]
>> ARE YOU HAVING SOME PAIN?
>> NOT REALLY. NOT RIGHT NOW.
>> NOT YET?
LET'S GET YOUR COAT.
YOU WANT SOME SOCKS?
>> YEAH, I'LL GET SOME SOCKS.
AND GRAB MY BAG.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU READY?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S WALK REAL
SLOW AND REAL CAREFUL.
>> OKAY, MOM, HOLD ON.
MY DAD'S OUT OF TOWN FOR WORK,
AND MY SISTER IS REALLY SICK,
SO SHE CAN'T COME.
I THINK MY MOM IS NERVOUS THAT
SHE'LL HAVE TO HELP ME
BY HERSELF.
>> YEAH.
>> MICHAEL?
>> YEAH?
>> DID YOU GET MY TEXT MESSAGE?
>> OH, WELL, WE'RE AT THE
HOSPITAL, AND FARRAH'S HAVING--
GOING TO BE HAVING THE BABY.
SO HER WATER BROKE, SO WE'RE
MOVING ON HERE.
>> OKAY. BYE.
>> BYE.
>> MOM, WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
JUST KEEP IT TOGETHER.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
[sniffles]
WELL, IT MAKES ME CRY IF YOU
CRY RIGHT NOW, MOM.
OBVIOUSLY, I DO NOT NEED TO BE
DOING THAT.
[sighs]
THE CONTRACTIONS ARE QUICKER,
AND THE PAIN IS BECOMING
UNBEARABLE.
THIS IS INTENSE.
[inhales]
[exhales]
>> [speaking indistinctly]
YOU'VE BEEN DOING REALLY GOOD,
BABY.
I'M VERY PROUD OF YOU.
>> SHE IS NOT LIKING THIS PART.
>> SHE'S--WE HAVE TO TALK TO
HER, KEEP HER OCCUPIED.
>> I AM IN SO MUCH PAIN;
IT'S TIME FOR THE EPIDURAL.
>> OKAY, I'M JUST GONNA HAVE YOU
KIND OF TURN YOUR LEGS OVER,
FACING ME.
OKAY.
I'M GONNA DROP THIS SIDE RAIL
DOWN.
>> OH.
I WANT TO BE REALLY STILL.
>> MM-HMM, YOU'RE DOING FINE.
YOU'RE DOING JUST FINE.
>> SO I'M JUST PUSHING
ON YOUR BACK--
>> THAT HURTS.
>> IT'S OKAY, YOU'RE--
>> IT IS OKAY?
>> IT'S JUST MY HANDS--
>> SHE'S JUST TRYING TO FIND OUT
WHAT TO DO FOR YOU, THAT'S ALL,
BABY.
>> ONCE I GET STUFF SET UP BACK
HERE, EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE
STERILE.
I'M NOT GONNA WANT YOU TO PUT
YOUR HANDS BACK HERE, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
CAN YOU GRAB ME HARDER,
PLEASE?
AM I IN THE PROPER--
>> YOU'RE NOT MOVING AT ALL.
YOU'RE GOOD.
JUST GONNA GET NICE AND CENTERED
IN THE BED.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'LL HELP THE MEDICINE GET
IN THERE FASTER, BABY.
>> TAKE THIS ARM UP, AND JUST
KIND OF TIP OVER.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO ROLL OVER
VERY FAR.
OKAY?
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> AND THEN ROLL BACK FOR ME,
SO YOU'RE JUST TIPPED A LITTLE.
PERFECT.
OKAY?
>> WONDER WHO THAT IS.
>> WELL, HELLO.
YOU MADE IT.
>> YES, I DID.
>> I'M VERY EXCITED.
>> THE EPIDURAL WORKING OKAY?
>> YEAH.
I THINK I WAS LOSING MY MIND
EARLIER.
>> NO, NO, NOT AT ALL.
I ALWAYS TELL PEOPLE, "IF I HAD
A BOWLING BALL COMING THROUGH
MY PELVIS, I'D WANT ALL THE PAIN
MEDICINE I COULD GET," SO...
>> [laughs]
>> I'M JUST TRYING NOT TO THINK
OF IT LIKE THAT.
>> AS YOU TAKE THE BABY OUT...
>> UH-HUH?
>> I'M, YOU KNOW, NOT REAL GOOD
WITH THESE KIND OF THINGS, BUT--
>> SHE'S SUPPOSED TO TAKE
A PICTURE.
>> I'M TRYING TO HELP WITH
EVERYTHING.
>> WELL, I'M GONNA MAKE HER CUT
THE CORD.
>> OH, NO. I CAN'T.
I'LL FAINT DEAD AWAY.
>> [laughs]
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M GONNA GO
PUT MY WORK CLOTHES ON.
>> OKAY.
NOW THAT MY DOCTOR HAS
ARRIVED AND MY CONTRACTIONS ARE
COMING FASTER, IT'S TIME TO
START PUSHING.
>> THE BETTER SHAPE YOU'RE IN
WHEN YOU COME IN IN LABOR
IS ALWAYS A GOOD THING
'CAUSE THIS IS A LOT OF WORK.
>> THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT
LABOR, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> HELLO?
>> SO LET'S GO AHEAD AND BRING
YOUR LEGS UP AND OUT,
LIKE A FROG.
>> I NEED TO PICK IT UP?
>> YEP.
>> OH, MY GOD.
EXCUSE THE LEGS AND EVERYTHING.
>> BIG DEEP BREATH IN.
AND BIG--TRY TO PUSH DOWN INTO
YOUR BOTTOM AS HARD AS YOU CAN.
BIG BREATH IN, AND PUSH DOWN
INTO YOUR BOTTOM AS HARD
AS YOU CAN.
ALMOST HOLD YOUR BREATH AND
KIND OF CHIN INTO YOUR CHEST--
>> HOLD ON. I JUST GOT TO--
I GOT TO GET TO THIS MIND-SET.
>> DON'T THINK ABOUT ANYTHING
ELSE EXCEPT JUST KIND OF
PUSHING, OKAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GONNA HELP, REALLY.
>> READY? BIG BREATH IN.
AND PUSH RIGHT DOWN INTO
YOUR BOTTOM.
>> HOLD THE AIR. HOLD THE AIR.
TWO. KEEP IT UP.
KEEP IT UP. KEEP IT UP.
>> SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
>> LET IT OUT.
COME RIGHT BACK ON IT AGAIN.
>> RIGHT BACK AT IT, AND PUSH
RIGHT DOWN INTO YOUR BOTTOM.
>> TWO. HARDER.
>> FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN.
>> EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
LET IT OUT.
>> I JUST KIND OF FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA PUKE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> TWO, THREE, FOUR.
HARDER.
FIVE, SIX.
I CAN SEE A LITTLE BIT OF HAIR.
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
>> I'M GLAD I WORKED OUT AS MUCH
AS I DID.
THAT'S ALL I'VE GOT TO SAY.
>> BIG BREATH IN.
>> LET YOUR LEGS FALL OPEN.
>> IS THIS IT?
>> YEP, JUST LIKE THAT'S FINE.
READY? BIG BREATH IN.
AND PUSH.
>> TWO, THREE.
KEEP IT UP.
FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN...
>> GOOD JOB. GOOD JOB.
>> NINE, TEN.
OKAY, WE'RE GONNA BREAK THE BED
DOWN.
>> I'M SO SORRY EVERYONE HAS
TO LOOK AT MY CROTCH RIGHT NOW.
I AM SO SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> MODESTY TENDS TO GO RIGHT OUT
THE WINDOW AT THIS POINT.
>> OKAY, WELL, I'M...
>> OKAY, SO LET'S CONCENTRATE
ON THE PUSHING.
NOW, IF YOU CAN PUSH LIKE YOU
DID LAST TIME, WE MAY HAVE
THE BABY THIS CONTRACTION OR
NEXT ONE.
>> PUSH AS HARD AS YOU CAN
RIGHT DOWN INTO YOUR BOTTOM.
>> HARDER.
FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN...
>> GOOD JOB.
>> EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
COME RIGHT BACK ON IT AGAIN NOW.
>> RIGHT BACK AT IT.
>> TWO, THREE, FOUR.
HERE'S THE BABY'S HEAD.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
GOOD JOB.
>> NOW LOOK DOWN HERE.
LOOK DOWN HERE. LOOK.
>> I'M LOOKING.
>> SEE, HERE SHE COMES.
HERE SHE COMES.
>> GOOD FOR HER.
>> HELLO, SWEETHEART.
[baby cries]
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> OH, HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>> AND DEFINITELY A SOPHIA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, MOM?
>> I LOVE HER. LET'S--
SHE HAS SOMETHING ON HER FACE,
THOUGH.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO GET THAT OFF.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A LITTLE VERNIX.
>> OH, SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> WELL, GRANDMA, YOU'VE BEEN
TAKING PICTURES.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
>> WHAT SHOULD I DO?
>> WHAT I WANT YOU TO DO IS,
I WANT YOU TO CUT RIGHT HERE.
GO AHEAD.
NOW, IT'S GONNA BE TOUGH.
THERE YOU GO. YOU DID IT.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> WE'RE GOING TO TAKE HER OVER
THIS WAY.
>> LOVE YA.
SHE IS SO PRETTY.
I JUST THINK SHE'S PRETTY.
I HAVE NEVER HELD A BABY
BEFORE SO YOU NEED TO HELP ME.
>> SHE KNOWS HER MAMA.
SEE, SHE'S ALL HAPPY.
WHEN THEY BLOW BUBBLES LIKE
THAT, THAT'S GOOD.
>> [softly] BABY.
>> ISN'T THAT WEIRD HOW THEY
KNOW THEIR MAMA RIGHT AWAY?
>> [kissing sounds]
BECAUSE SHE KNOWS I LOVE HER.
MM.
[kissing sounds]
[chime dings]
>> MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY ARRIVED
EARLY TO MEET BABY SOPHIA.
>> GRANDMA. GRANDPA.
>> HELLO, BABY.
>> HELLO.
COME SEE SOPHIA.
>> SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
MM.
>> HELLO.
>> FARRAH.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
MY GRANDPARENTS JUST GOT BACK
IN TOWN.
>> HI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> ISN'T SHE BEAUTIFUL?
>> OHH.
>> HELLO.
I LOOK LIKE CRAP.
I WAS IN BED, AND MY WATER
BROKE WHILE I WAS SLEEPING.
I WAS SO SHOCKED.
LIKE, I WAS LIKE, "WHAT?"
I THOUGHT I PEED MY PANTS.
[laughter]
YEAH, IT WAS REALLY SCARY.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHERE'S ASHLEY?
>> SHE'S AT HOME, SICK.
SHE WASN'T EVEN HERE.
>> REALLY?
>> THIS MOTHER'S DAY,
I'M GONNA BE A MOM.
>> I KNOW. I WAS THINKING THAT.
I WAS LIKE, "I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TEXT HER AND SAY 'HAPPY
MOTHER'S DAY.'"
>> I KNOW.
ISN'T THAT CRAZY?
TAKING CARE OF SOPHIA IS GOING
TO BE A LOT MORE WORK THAN I'D
EVER IMAGINED.
THEY DON'T TEACH ANY OF THIS
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
THANK GOD MY MOM IS GOING TO BE
ABLE TO HELP ME OUT.
GOOD JOB, BABY.
>> PAT HER BACK.
>> SHE'S GONNA BURP, LIKE,
RIGHT ON ME.
[giggles]
>> YOU CAN PUT HER, LIKE,
IN THE SINK.
>> DO YOU WANT YOUR LITTLE
THINGY?
NO, YOU DON'T.
BECAUSE MY DAD WAS WORKING
OUT OF TOWN, HE WAS THE
LAST TO SHOW UP.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> ALL RIGHT. THANK YOU.
>> YOU BET.
>> FROM MY LITTLE BABY,
MY FIRST GRANDDAUGHTER.
>> AH, WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> WELL, LOOK WHO HAS THE BABY.
>> I FINALLY GOT THE BABY.
[Sophia whimpers]
>> YEAH...
>> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> IT'S A MIRACLE.
BEFORE I KNEW IT, IT WAS TIME
TO TAKE SOPHIA HOME.
>> SOPHIA, WELCOME TO YOUR HOME.
>> I'M GONNA JUST CHANGE HER
AND EVERYTHING HERE.
>> YOU'RE GONNA PUT HER
ON THE TABLE?
>> WELL, WHY CAN'T I?
>> WELL, THE TABLE'S HARD.
SHE'S USED TO SOMETHING NICE
AND SOFT.
>> YEAH. OKAY.
OHH.
GET YOUR PANT LEG ON.
YEAH.
[Sophia crying softly]
>> FARRAH, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
WATCH IT 'CAUSE WHEN SHE GETS
A LITTLE OLDER AND STARTS
ROLLING, YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE
HER LAY LIKE THAT.
>> IT'S PROBABLY NOT A GOOD
IDEA.
>> JUST THINK, YOU'RE GETTING
AN EDUCATION THERE.
>> GIVE ME, GIVE ME, GIVE ME.
>> SHE'S A HUNGRY LITTLE BABY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY SHE JUST
BURPED ALL THAT UP, THOUGH.
I WAS SO EXCITED WHEN WE GOT
SOPHIA HOME, BUT I HAD NO IDEA
IT WAS GOING TO BE THIS MUCH
WORK.
MY MOM WAS RIGHT.
IT'S EXHAUSTING.
[Sophia fussing]
OVER THE PAST THREE DAYS,
EVERYTHING'S BEEN ABOUT SOPHIA.
I'M STARTING TO WONDER IF I'M
EVER GOING TO GET ANY SLEEP
AT ALL.
>> ARE YOU RUBBING HER FEET?
>> WELL, I WAS, BUT THEN SHE
SEEMED FINE, AND I DIDN'T WANT
TO MAKE HER COLD.
[Sophia crying]
>> OH, MY GOD, NOW YOU'RE GONNA
PUT HANDCUFFS ON THE BABY.
>> MOM, THEY HAD THESE AT--
>> SHE'S GOT TO LEARN TO WORK
HER--HER ARMS AND HER HANDS.
>> I DON'T WANT HER SCRATCHING,
MOM; THAT'S BAD.
>> WELL, HERE'S A NEWS FLASH:
I NEVER, EVER DID THAT TO YOU,
AND LOOK AT YOU; YOU'RE OKAY.
>> MY MOM IS STARTING TO GET ON
MY NERVES.
SHE'S BECOMING A CONTROL FREAK.
AND THEN WHEN THE SUN GOES DOWN,
SHE DISAPPEARS, AND IT'S ALL ME
TAKING CARE OF SOPHIA.
[Sophia crying]
[softly] YOU'RE OKAY.
SOPHIA...
[softly] SO PRETTY.
[Sophia crying]
SOPHIA KEPT ME UP ALL NIGHT,
AND I'M EXHAUSTED.
WELL, I KNOW THIS SOUNDS
A LITTLE BIT...
[laughs] NEEDY.
BUT, LIKE, HOW MUCH WOULD YOU
HELP A LITTLE BIT?
>> "HELP A LITTLE BIT"?
>> WELL, HOW MUCH WOULD YOU,
LIKE, IF I NEEDED SOMETHING
AT NIGHT...
[laughs]
>> PROBABLY NOT TOO MUCH.
>> NOT TOO MUCH.
YEAH.
>> NO, 'CAUSE I NEED MY SLEEP.
>> YEAH.
[chime dings]
WHEN I THOUGHT ABOUT PULLING AN
ALL-NIGHTER FOR MY SENIOR YEAR,
I WAS THINKING PARTIES, PROM,
OR CRAMMING FOR FINALS.
BUT NOW IT MEANS SOMETHING
TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
>> I'M SPENDING MORE AND MORE
TIME HOME ALONE TAKING CARE OF
SOPHIA, AND I'M STARTING TO GET
MORE OF A HANDLE ON THIS WHOLE
MOTHERING THING.
ALL RIGHTY TIGHTY.
YOU'RE GONNA DOZE OFF.
MAYBE I SHOULD BURP YOU
ONE MORE TIME.
TRAPPED IN THIS HOUSE WITHOUT
A CAR, I'M STARTING TO GO
STIR-CRAZY.
THANK GOD SOME OF MY FRIENDS
ARE VISITING.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO SEE
FRIENDS A LOT OR HAVE YOU BEEN--
>> WELL, ACTUALLY, LIKE, 'CAUSE
I CAN'T--REALLY COME, LIKE,
OUT OF THE HOUSE--
I DON'T HAVE A CAR RIGHT NOW
AND WHATEVER, SO...
>> THEY COME TO YOU.
>> SO, YEAH, THE FRIENDS COME
TO YOU.
>> I'M STUCK IN MY HOUSE
BY MYSELF AND DON'T GET TO
SEE FRIENDS, NO.
I'M HOPING IT WILL ALL BE
GOOD BY, LIKE, SIX MONTHS.
[all laugh]
THAT'S AS LONG AS I'M GONNA HOLD
OUT TILL.
I'M GONNA HAVE A HARD TIME
AFTER THAT.
IT WAS REALLY NICE TO SEE MY
FRIENDS, BUT WHEN THEY STARTED
GETTING READY TO GO OUT,
I REALIZED HOW MUCH MY LIFE
HAS CHANGED.
>> ARE YOU READY
TO GO OUT, THOUGH?
I SERIOUSLY--
>> NO, I'M NOT READY TO GO OUT.
I'M GONNA CHILL AT HOME.
>> YOUR MOM COULD WATCH HER.
>> WELL, I--
>> JUST FOR, LIKE, TWO HOURS.
>> YEAH.
YEAH, YOU'VE BEEN HOME ALL DAY.
JUST--
>> YEAH, NOW I WANT TO SLEEP.
YOU GUYS CAN HAVE A FUN NIGHT
AND TELL ME HOW IT GOES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TEXT YOU.
WE'LL TEXT YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BYE.
>> IT WAS A FUN TIME WITH THE
GIRLS, AND THEY'RE GONNA GO OUT
TONIGHT.
>> WHO WITH?
>> THE GIRLS.
>> OH, THEY ARE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU HAVE TO BUCKLE DOWN
TOMORROW AND GET ALL YOUR
HOMEWORK DONE.
>> YEAH.
I PLAN ON GETTING IT DONE.
WITH JUST MY MOM AND I IN THE
HOUSE, I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO DO
SOMETHING TO HAVE A LITTLE MORE
FREEDOM.
BEFORE I GO BACK TO WORK,
WHENEVER I DECIDE AND GET
EVERYTHING SITUATION--SITUATED
WITH MY DOCTORS AND STUFF,
I SERIOUSLY THINK WE SHOULD
LOOK AT CARS.
>> WE'LL DEAL WITH IT LATER WHEN
WE HAVE MORE RESOURCES TO DEAL
WITH IT, 'CAUSE YOUR INSURANCE
RATE'S GONNA BE THROUGH THE
ROOF.
>> WELL, LIKE, I PLAN ON
CONTRIBUTING TO THE CAR AND
EVERYTHING.
LIKE, I PLAN ON MAKING
MORE MONEY.
>> RIGHT NOW, YOU'RE ACTUALLY
NOT WORKING AT ALL.
SO WE GOT TO GET YOU BACK TO
WORK.
WE GOT TO GET YOU TO 18.
RIGHT NOW, YOU CANNOT AFFORD IT.
THERE'S NOTHING TO GET UPSET
ABOUT.
I KNOW ONE THING, FARRAH:
GOD'LL MAKE A WAY.
>> THAT IS SERIOUSLY JUST
PISSING ME OFF.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN YOU JUST BE
PISSED OFF.
I'M NOT GONNA DEAL WITH THAT.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO HAVE LOGIC
AND REASON, AND I'M NOT GONNA
DEAL WITH ANYTHING THAT'S NOT
THAT.
[chime dings]
>> MY MOM IS TRYING TO CONTROL
EVERYTHING THAT I DO.
I CAN'T TAKE MUCH MORE OF THIS.
>> I WAS LIKE, "WHAT STINKS,
SOPHIA?" AND GUESS WHAT?
YOU POO-POOED.
UGH, YOU POO-POOED WAY TOO MUCH.
READY?
MY SISTER AND I DON'T HANG OUT
OFTEN, BUT NO ONE KNOWS BETTER
THAN SHE DOES HOW DIFFICULT
MY MOM CAN BE.
I NEED TO, LIKE, FIND
A DIFFERENT SITUATION, LIKE, BE
MORE INDEPENDENT ON MY OWN.
AND I'M TRYING TO GET A CAR
SO THAT I DON'T NEED TO RELY
ON HER TO TAKE ME PLACES
'CAUSE IT'S LIKE--IT SEEMS LIKE
SHE DOESN'T WANT ME TO HAVE--
LIKE, SHE DOESN'T WANT ME
TO GET DIFFERENT THINGS SO
I CAN HAVE MY OWN SPACE MORE.
>> IF YOU LOOK HARD ENOUGH,
YOU CAN FIND A CAR THAT'S, LIKE,
YOU KNOW, $4,000 OR $5,000,
'CAUSE IF YOU'RE JUST STUCK ON
A MONTHLY PAYMENT, THEN YOU'RE
GONNA BE, LIKE--BE BROKE, AND
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DEPEND ON
MOM TO, LIKE...
>> AND THAT'S WHAT I DON'T WANT.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, MOM NEEDS TO JUST
SEPARATE HERSELF A LITTLE BIT
MORE FROM ME.
I THINK OUR SITUATION WOULD BE
BETTER.
DESPITE MY MOM'S RESERVATIONS,
SHE AGREED TO GO LOOK AT CARS
WITH ME.
>> WE'LL KEEP--WE'LL KEEP BABY
HAPPY.
I WILL SING TO HER.
>> LOVE YOU. SEE YOU LATER.
>> LOVE YOU, BABE.
>> GRANDPA WANTS US TO GO TO THE
FORD DEALER.
>> NO.
>> AND GRANDPA WAS TALKING ABOUT
FORD FOCUSES.
>> I HATE FORD FOCUSES.
>> I LIKE FORD FOCUSES, MOM.
IT'S A CUTE CAR I WOULD DRIVE.
>> YEAH, WELL, WE'RE NOT GONNA
GET THAT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE DUMB.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
NOW, WHAT YOU NEED
TO DO IS GO IN--
>> MOM, SHUT UP.
>> I'M NOT GONNA SIT HERE AND BE
DISRESPECTED BY YOU.
YOU'RE COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL.
>> NOPE. YOU ARE.
>> YOU CAN'T UNDERSTAND
ANYTHING.
>> NO, MOM, YOU CAN'T.
THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE SO MANY
PROBLEMS.
>> ALL RIGHT, FARRAH, I'M GONNA
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW...
>> DON'T TALK TO ME ANYMORE.
>> I HAVE HAD ENOUGH
OF YOUR BELLIGERENT...
>> NO, I DON'T CARE.
>> ANTI-CHRIST ATTITUDE.
>> NO, THAT'S WHAT YOU ARE.
>> NOW, I MEAN IT.
>> OH, OKAY, MOM.
WELL, I TRY TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING, AND YOU DON'T LISTEN.
>> YES, BECAUSE YOU'RE WRONG.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> AND I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU
THE RIGHT THING.
>> OH, UM, TOO BAD BECAUSE--
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
>> I'M TELLING YOU
EXACTLY WHAT I SAID.
>> NOW I MEAN IT!
YOU KNOW SO MUCH; THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE ALWAYS IN SUCH TROUBLE,
FARRAH.
>> I'M NOT IN ANY TROUBLE.
>> YEAH, RIGHT.
>> I'M ONLY IN TROUBLE
BECAUSE OF YOU.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HAVING
A BEAUTIFUL SITUATION RIGHT
NOW, HUH, FARRAH?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I HAVE TO DEAL
WITH YOU; YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, SORRY, IT MUST SUCK
TO BE IN MY LIFE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
PITY POOH.
>> YEP, 'CAUSE I'M SO SICK
OF YOU.
YOU AND ME ARE NOT WE, MOM.
TWO DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
>> HELLO?
>> HI, GRANDMA, CAN YOU PICK ME
UP AT THE BANK?
>> NO, NO. NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> BECAUSE I'M NOT HAVING
ANY MORE TO DO WITH MY MOM.
>> NO. NO, SHE'S NOT.
NO, SHE'S NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING.
>> YEAH.
SHUT THE [bleep] UP, MOM.
>> NO.
[engine turns]
>> WELL, I'LL TELL YOU ABOUT
YOUR MOTHER.
SHE THINKS SHE'S GOT TO BE
IN TOTAL CONTROL OF EVERYTHING.
SHE'S GONNA MAKE ALL THE
DECISIONS.
SHE'S GONNA DO--
>> WELL, SHE DOESN'T NEED TO
MAKE ANY MORE DAMN DECISIONS
FOR ME.
>> YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT
A BITE OF SOMETHING, LOVE?
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M MISERABLE,
MY GRANDPA AND I DECIDED TO
STICK WITH THE PLAN FOR THE DAY.
I NEED A CAR 'CAUSE I HAVE TO
GET TO COLLEGE AND I HAVE TO GET
TO WORK AND I HAVE TO TAKE CARE
OF SOPHIA, LIKE DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENTS AND STUFF, SO...
>> IN OTHER WORDS, IT'S BECOME
PART OF LIFE.
>> YEAH, AND I DON'T NEED TO BE
DEPENDING ON MY MOM.
>> GO IN AND HAVE A SEAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
COULD I JUST, LIKE,
TEST-DRIVE IT, LIKE,
AROUND HERE?
>> SURE, YOU BET YA.
>> OKAY.
>> JUST GO IN BETWEEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AND WE'LL JUST GO THIS WAY.
[mellow acoustic guitar music]
*
>> NOTHING ABOUT BEING A TEEN
MOM IS EASY, AND I KNOW I HAVE
A LOT TO LEARN.
MY MOM AND I, IT SEEMS LIKE WE
HAVE TO FIGHT EACH OTHER.
LIKE, WHEN I WANT TO BE
INDEPENDENT ABOUT SOMETHING,
IT MIGHT BE HARD FOR MY MOM TO
DEAL WITH THAT.
>> IT'S BEEN HARD FOR ME BECAUSE
I ONLY WANTED THE BEST FOR YOU.
>> MM-HMM.
>> PRETTY SOON, IT'LL BE
A WHOLE YEAR...
>> I KNOW.
>> SINCE YOU FOUND OUT YOU WERE
PREGNANT, AND YOU'VE HAD SOPHIA.
>> I KNOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT ALL
THE CHANGES?
>> I DON'T KNOW; IT'S BEEN
A HARD YEAR BUT A GOOD YEAR.
I'M FORTUNATE, LIKE, MY FAMILY'S
BEHIND ME EVEN THOUGH, LIKE,
WE'RE NOT THE GREATEST FAMILY
EVER, BUT WE STILL HAVE LOVE.
HEAD.
THE HEART.
>> LOOK AT THAT: 2,200.
>> I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT TO
FIND THE RIGHT MALE FIGURE
TO BE IN YOUR BABY'S LIFE.
>> I HAVE A KID?
>> DO YOU?
>> [laughs] YEAH.
SHE'S GOOD.
OH, MY GOD, I MISS SOPHIA NOW
THAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FUTURE
HAS FOR ME AND SOPHIA, BUT
EVERYTHING THAT I WENT THROUGH,
I WOULD NOT TAKE ANY OF
THAT BACK.
SHE'S MADE ME A BETTER PERSON.
LOOK HOW CUTE YOU ARE.
I'M CHANGING.
I WANT, YOU KNOW, MORE
INDEPENDENCE.
I NEED TO LEARN THINGS FOR
MYSELF.
I WANT TO BE THE MOM THAT WILL
TEACH HER TO LOVE THE RIGHT WAY,
TEACH HER TO KNOW WHAT'S A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP AND A BAD
RELATIONSHIP.
I WANT TO TEACH HER ALL THE
RIGHT THINGS THAT WILL HELP HER
OUT IN HER LIFE, SO WHEN I'M NOT
AROUND, SHE'LL KNOW BETTER.
PEACE OUT.
[chime dings]
[soft rock music]
*
>> A BABY IS COMING OUT OF MY
FREAKING [bleep], DUDE.
>> WE TOOK MOST OF THE
PRECAUTIONS.
>> DID YOU JUST BUY THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW MUCH WAS IT?
>> HE'S GOT HIS PRIORITIES
ALL SCREWED UP.
>> WHY DID YOU TELL YOUR MOM
ABOUT THE PS3?
YOU SAID YOU WOULDN'T.
>> I AM A TEENAGER.
YOU DON'T CARE.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME.
[cries]
>> GIVE ME A HUGE PUSH.
KEEP GOING. PUSH--
>> DOES SHE COME WITH ANY
INSTRUCTIONS?
>> I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
YOU ARE SO LUCKY RIGHT NOW
YOU'RE HOLDING THE BABY.
>> WHY? ARE YOU GONNA HIT ME?
[upbeat piano music]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA *
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
* I'M WEAK, BUT I'M *
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE