>> I WAS REALLY AWKWARD
IN SIXTH GRADE.
[laughter]
I'M KARLEY.
I'M 17 AND LIVE IN TOOELE, UTAH,
RIGHT OUTSIDE OF SALT LAKE CITY.
I LIVE AT HOME WITH MY MOM,
DAD, YOUNGER SISTER,
BROTHER, AND OUR FOUR DOGS.
THEY'RE EXCITED TO SEE US.
I MET MY BOYFRIEND TONY
IN HIGH SCHOOL TWO YEARS AGO,
AND I'M SINCE I'M A STRAIGHT "A"
STUDENT AND HE'S ALWAYS
STRUGGLED WITH HIS HOMEWORK,
I DECIDED TO TUTOR HIM,
AND WE HIT IT OFF.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> BUT UNFORTUNATELY,
TONY'S A LITTLE UNPREDICTABLE,
AND HE ENDED UP DROPPING OUT
OF HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE ANY SKIN
LEFT.
WHAT MORE DO YOU NEED?
>> SMOKE AND DEMON FACES.
>> HM.
AND EVERYTHING JUST BECAME
TWICE AS COMPLICATED
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT
WITH TWINS.
WHEN TONY AND I FOUND OUT
WE WERE HAVING TWINS,
WE DECIDED TO GET MARRIED
RIGHT AWAY SO WE COULD BE
A FAMILY.
I SWITCHED TO HOMESCHOOLING
SO I CAN STILL GRADUATE
THIS YEAR.
TONY FOUND FULL-TIME WORK
AS A MECHANIC AND MOVED
INTO MY PARENTS' HOUSE
TO BE WITH ME.
BUT HE'S HAD A HARD TIME
ADJUSTING TO LIVING IN SOMEONE
ELSE'S HOUSE.
HE REALLY WANTS US TO GET
OUR OWN PLACE ONCE THE BABIES
ARE HERE SO WE CAN RAISE OUR
FAMILY IN OUR OWN HOME.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
A LITTLE LOPSIDED, KARLEY.
>> I KNOW.
>> I THINK THE BIG TWIN
IS RIGHT THERE.
>> THE BIG ONE IS GONNA
BE AMARIAH.
AND THE OTHER ONE
IS GONNA BE AMAYAH.
>> I THINK TONY'S STILL HOPING
ONE OF THEM IS A BOY.
>> YEP, I THINK SO.
>> OH, HE WON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH TWO LITTLE GIRLS.
>> HE'LL GET USED TO IT.
WHEN THEY COME OUT,
HE'LL SEE.
>> [laughs]
>> [chortles]
>> I REMEMBER WHEN YOU TOLD ME,
I WAS IN SHOCK.
I WASN'T UPSET WITH YOU.
JUST MORE JUST DISAPPOINTED,
YOU KNOW?
WE WERE GETTING EXCITED ABOUT
PUTTING IN FOR SCHOLARSHIPS,
AND YOUR GRADES ARE SO GOOD.
AND, YOU KNOW, I WANTED YOU
TO GO TO THE UNIVERSITY
OF UTAH.
[laughs]
>> EVERY TIME, LIKE, I GET MAIL
FROM COLLEGES, YOU ALWAYS,
LIKE, TEAR UP.
>> [laughs]
I CAN'T HELP IT.
IT'S JUST A REMINDER OF WHAT
I WANTED YOU TO DO.
AND WHEN YOU FOUND OUT
THEY WERE TWINS, I JUST KNEW
HOW HARD IT WAS GONNA BE FOR
YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHAT'S YOUR BIGGEST WORRY?
>> THAT I'M NOT GONNA BE
GOOD ENOUGH FOR THEM.
>> WELL, THE ODDS ARE AGAINST
YOU A LITTLE BIT.
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE NOT
OLD ENOUGH TO REALIZE WHAT
A COMMITMENT IT IS.
I'M SO SCARED IT'S GONNA BE
SO HARD FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I LIKE HAVING YOU LIVE
HERE.
>> DO YOU LIKE TONY LIVING HERE?
>> YOU KNOW, I DO.
BUT I KNOW THAT HE'S WORRIED
ABOUT NOT BEING ABLE
TO BE A FATHER WHILE HE'S HERE,
THAT I MIGHT MAYBE GET INVOLVED
TOO MUCH.
SO I FEEL LIKE I'VE HAD
TO REALLY HOLD MY TONGUE
AROUND HIM.
'CAUSE I REALLY DON'T WANT HIM
TO FEEL LIKE I'M INTRUDING.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T THINK HE LIKES
THE ADVICE FROM ANYONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
>> YEAH.
BUT YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY AND HAVE HIM
RESENT ME.
SO...
>> YEAH.
WITH SIX PEOPLE LIVING
UNDER ONE ROOF, TONY HATES
THAT HE NEVER HAS ANY PRIVACY
AND CAN'T DO WHAT HE WANTS
WHEN HE WANTS TO.
SO WHEN HE'S HOME FROM WORK,
WE TRY AND GET OUT AS MUCH
AS WE CAN.
ARE YOU FREEZING?
>> NO, IT FEELS REALLY GOOD
OUT HERE.
>> ARE YOUR LEGS COLD?
>> NO.
>> [chortles]
OH.
>> SUCKS THAT I HAVE
TO GO TO WORK IN THIS, THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
IT WAS PRETTY WEIRD WHEN WE
FOUND OUT WE WERE HAVING TWINS,
HUH?
>> IT DID KIND OF SUCK
'CAUSE I THOUGHT YOU WERE
LYING AT FIRST 'CAUSE WE
WERE FIGHTING, AND...
I THOUGHT YOU WERE JUST SAYING
IT SO THAT I WOULD STAY
WITH YOU.
AND THEN AFTER YOU SHOWED ME
THE TESTS, I KNEW THAT YOU
WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO RAISE
HIM ON YOUR OWN, SO...
IN A WAY, IT'S BROUGHT OUT
A LOT OF GOOD.
>> YEAH.
>> WE GOT TO GET MARRIED FASTER.
IT'S MADE ME GROW UP MORE,
GET A JOB.
>> YEAH, BUT IT'S ALSO BEEN
HARD.
LIKE, I WOULD NEVER SUGGEST IT
TO ANYONE ELSE OR THINK
THIS IS HOW MY LIFE WAS GONNA
TURN OUT.
>> YEAH, IT'S WEIRD, 'CAUSE
WE'RE, LIKE, REALLY DIFFERENT.
I MEAN, YOU USED TO GO TO CHURCH
AND...
>> [laughs]
>> BELIEVED IN ALL THE GOOD
THINGS, AND I DIDN'T
AND BELIEVED IN ALL
THE BAD THINGS.
>> I WAS GOOD STUDENT AND--
>> I NEVER WENT TO SCHOOL.
>> I DID YOUR HOMEWORK FOR YOU.
>> IT'S OKAY.
IT WORKS OUT GOOD.
BUT IT'S GONNA BE MORE STRESSFUL
NOW THAT WE'RE HAVING TWO.
>> YEAH.
DOUBLE THE DIAPERS.
DOUBLE THE WIPES.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET
ANY SLEEP.
>> YEAH, I'M JUST GLAD
THAT EVERYBODY IS HELPING US.
BUT THEN AGAIN, IF I START
SAVING UP, WE CAN BE LIVING
SOMEWHERE NICE AND NOT
IN OUR PARENTS' HOUSE.
>> MAYBE.
SINCE I SWITCHED TO
HOMESCHOOLING, I BARELY GET
TO SEE MY FRIENDS ANYMORE.
>> KARLEY!
>> I THINK BECCA'S HAVING...
[laughing] A PROBLEM.
>> BECCA.
CAN SHE NOT GET OUT?
>> BRYTANNI, YOUR DAMN CAR.
[laughter]
>> WHOO, OKAY.
>> AH, IT'S SO NICE
HANGING OUT WITH YOU AGAIN.
>> I KNOW.
I MISS GOING TO SCHOOL.
>> REALLY?
WHY?
>> I GET SO BORED.
>> IT'S WEIRD THAT YOU'RE NOT
THERE.
LIKE, I USUALLY HAVE SO MANY
CLASSES WITH YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE SHOULD ALL GO ON A SENIOR
TRIP.
THAT WOULD BE FUN.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE CAN
LEAVE HER BABY THAT LONG.
>> THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
I WOULD LOVE TO.
>> NICE TRY, THOUGH.
>> BUT IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
>> YEAH.
ARE YOU UPSET THAT YOU DON'T
GET TO, LIKE, GRADUATE
AND WALK WITH US?
>> WELL, I CAN WALK IF I WANT.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> both: YOU SHOULD.
>> I JUST HAVEN'T DECIDED.
>> YOU SHOULD WALK WITH US.
>> I'M GOING TO.
>> ARE YOU STILL PLANNING
ON BEING A TEACHER?
>> UM, I'M STILL GONNA GO
TO COLLEGE, BUT I'M GONNA HAVE
TO, LIKE, DO IT ONLINE
OR, LIKE, GO TO NIGHT CLASSES.
>> HOW SOON ARE YOU GONNA DO
THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
PROBABLY, LIKE, IN A YEAR.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S REALLY SAD.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO ARE YOU EXCITED
TO BE A MOM?
>> I'M EXCITED NOT TO BE
PREGNANT ANYMORE.
>> YEAH.
>> I HATE BEING PREGNANT.
>> IS IT REALLY HARD?
>> EVERYONE SAYS YOU'RE, LIKE,
A HEATER.
>> YEAH, I'M ALWAYS HOT.
>> WELL, NOT YOU, A HEATER,
BUT PREGNANT PEOPLE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY.
I'M JUST, LIKE, SURPRISED
THAT YOU WEREN'T SAFER,
'CAUSE--I DON'T KNOW.
DID YOU REALLY NOT THINK
THAT YOU WERE GONNA GET
PREGNANT IF YOU WEREN'T,
LIKE, USING PROTECTION OR--
>> YEAH ,I GUESS I FIGURED
WE DIDN'T USE PROTECTION
BEFORE MULTIPLE TIMES,
SO NOTHING HAPPENED.
>> YEAH.
>> SO...
>> I KEEP LOOKING AT YOUR RING.
IT'S SO PRETTY.
>> THANKS.
>> IS YOUR RELATIONSHIP, LIKE,
DIFFERENT SINCE YOU'VE BEEN
MARRIED OR IS IT JUST--
>> YEAH, IT'S, LIKE, HARDER.
>> IT IS?
>> YEAH, BEFORE WE DIDN'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT STUFF,
AND WE JUST...
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> FOCUSED ON HAVING FUN.
AND NOW WE HAVE TO, LIKE, WORRY
ABOUT RESPONSIBILITIES TOGETHER.
>> YEAH.
>> WAS HE OKAY WITH YOU GUYS
MOVING TO YOUR HOUSE OR--
>> NO.
BUT HE WANTED TO BE WITH ME,
SO HE DID.
>> both: THAT'S GOOD.
>> YEAH.
BUT TONY WANTS TO GET OUT
AS SOON AS WE CAN,
'CAUSE OBVIOUSLY WHEN YOU THINK
OF HAVING KIDS, YOU HAVE
YOUR OWN PLACE AND EVERYTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> AND IT DOES KIND OF SUCK,
LIKE, HAVING TO LIVE
WITH MY PARENTS.
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO, LIKE,
RAISE KIDS AT MY MOM'S HOUSE.
SO WE'LL SEE.
I DON'T KNOW.
BECAUSE TONY AND I ARE THINKING
ABOUT MOVING OUT ONCE THE BABIES
COME...
MY MOM WANTS TO TALK IT ALL
OVER.
>> OH.
[sighs]
HOW ARE YOU FEELING TODAY,
KARLEY?
>> EXHAUSTED.
>> I CAN TELL.
[chuckles]
SOUNDS LIKE YOU JUST RAN
A MARATHON.
>> I KNOW; IT FEELS LIKE
I JUST RAN A MARATHON.
[laughs]
>> I KNOW IT'S NOT IDEAL FOR YOU
TO BE HERE,
ESPECIALLY YOU, TONY.
I THINK IT'S HARDER FOR YOU
TO BE HERE.
LIKE, YOU'RE ALWAYS ASKING ME,
"CAN I HAVE"--YOU'LL GO TO THE
REFRIGERATOR AND SAY,
"CAN I HAVE THIS OR CAN
I HAVE THAT?"
I'M LIKE, IT'S YOUR HOUSE.
I WANT YOU TO FEEL COMFORTABLE
WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
AND YOU KNOW YOU GUYS ARE
WELCOME TO STAY AS LONG AS IT
TAKES.
>> MM-HMM.
>> BUT WE WANT TO BE OUT
BEFORE THEY'RE AT LEAST SIX
MONTHS.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT'S POSSIBLE
RIGHT NOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE GONNA SEE HOW THINGS GO.
>> YEAH.
TRUTH BE TOLD, I WOULD REALLY
LIKE TO SEE YOU GUYS STAY
AT LEAST A YEAR BECAUSE I WANT
TO MAKE SURE YOU GUYS ARE OKAY,
YOU KNOW, THAT YOU CAN
FINANCIALLY HANDLE BEING ON--
>> BUT, I MEAN, LIKE,
MY PLAN, FINANCIAL-WISE,
JUST, I'M NOT GONNA WORRY
ABOUT THAT STUFF,
'CAUSE I'LL WORRY ABOUT THAT
WHEN THAT COMES.
I'M JUST NOT A WORRIED PERSON.
LIKE, I DON'T REALLY--
>> I DO THE WORRYING FOR HIM.
>> I DON'T REALLY WORRY.
LIKE, I JUST GO AS IT COMES.
>> YEAH.
WELL, I DON'T WANT TO GET
INTO AN ARGUMENT ABOUT IT...
[chortles]
BUT I JUST WORRY ABOUT YOU
BEING OUT ON YOUR OWN
WITH TWO KIDS.
AND IT MIGHT NOT MAKE
FISCAL SENSE TO DO THAT,
YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, I KNOW I'M WORRIED
ABOUT MONEY TOO.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT.
LIKE, WE HAVE TO SEE HOW THINGS
PLAY OUT BEFORE WE CAN DO
ANYTHING.
>> MM-HMM.
>> EVEN THOUGH TONY'S NOT
WORRIED ABOUT MONEY,
HE AGREED TO MEET WITH
A REALTOR SO WE COULD FIND OUT
EXACTLY HOW MUCH WE'D NEED
TO GET OUR OWN PLACE.
>> HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
CAN I GET YOU A GLASS
OF WATER OR SOMETHING?
>> NO, I'M OKAY.
THANK YOU, THOUGH.
>> OKAY, SO ON THE PHONE,
YOU HAD SAID THAT YOU'RE LOOKING
AT POSSIBLY GETTING A RENTAL?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, DO YOU HAVE AN IDEA
OF HOW MUCH YOU WANT
TO SPEND ON A PLACE?
>> I GUESS AS CHEAP AS POSSIBLE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> YEAH, THAT IS ALWAYS HELPFUL,
HUH?
>> LET'S SEE.
HE MAKES ABOUT ANYWHERE
FROM, LIKE, $900 TO $1,100
A MONTH.
>> OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, SO FOR A TWO-BEDROOM
IN TOOELE, IT WOULD COST
ANYWHERE FROM $600
TO ABOUT $800 A MONTH.
AND SOME OF THOSE, THEY ALSO
REQUIRED A SECURITY DEPOSIT.
SO WHEN YOU MOVE INTO THE PLACE,
YOU HAVE TO HAVE BOTH OF THAT.
AND SO IT'S A LITTLE COSTLY
UPFRONT.
>> YEAH, I DON'T REALLY STRESS
ABOUT IT.
I JUST--
>> YOU GO TO WORK.
[laughs]
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, I'M GONNA BE THE ONE
WORRYING ABOUT IT.
>> RIGHT.
SO $1,450, $1,470.
THAT'S JUST A ROUGH ESTIMATE
RIGHT THERE JUST TO GET YOU IN.
SO YOU SEE IF YOU CAN SET
ASIDE THAT AMOUNT OF MONEY
TO MAKE THAT HAPPEN IN THE
SITUATION THAT YOU ARE.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S A BIG STEP FOR YOU GUYS,
FOR SURE.
IT'S SOMETHING TO STRIVE FOR.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY
TO SAVE UP ALL THIS MONEY
WHILE ALSO GETTING READY
FOR THE TWINS.
BUT AT LEAST WE'LL GET A LOT
OF WHAT WE NEED TODAY
AT OUR BABY SHOWER.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR LEG?
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> [laughing]
[laughter]
>> NO, THAT'S SO SAD.
[laughs]
THANK YOU.
>> DO YOU GET SICK AT ALL?
>> UM, YEAH.
I GET, LIKE, SICK TO MY STOMACH,
AND I GET, LIKE, HOT.
LIKE, RIGHT NOW I'M REALLY HOT.
AND IT GETS LIKE--I WALK UP
THE STAIRS, AND I'M, LIKE,
GASPING FOR AIR.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I KNOW.
>> OKAY, EVERYBODY.
I'M GONNA HAVE KARLEY OPEN
THE GIFTS, SINCE WE'RE ALL
JUST IN THE SAME AREA.
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT LITTLE
BLANKET.
FEEL HOW SOFT IT IS.
>> NICE.
>> [chuckles]
>> HOLD THEM UP, TONY.
>> [laughs]
>> OH, THAT IS SO CUTE.
>> AW.
>> [chuckling]
THOSE ARE CUTE.
>> IT'S SO CUTE.
>> AW.
>> all: AW.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> [laughing]
IT SAYS "MOMMY'S LITTLE DEER"
ON IT.
AW.
[laughing]
THAT IS TOO CUTE.
I LIKE THIS.
[laughter]
"I LOVE MY MOM."
>> THERE'S PROBABLY NOT GONNA
BE ONE THING THAT SAYS
"I LOVE DAD."
>> PROBABLY NOT.
[chuckles]
IT WAS GOOD TO SEE EVERYONE.
IT WAS GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WHERE ARE WE?
OH.
THESE BALLOONS GONNA STAY ON?
I HOPE SO.
>> YOU WANT THEM TO?
[horses whinnying]
[dog barking]
>> OKAY, YOU NEED TO TRY NOT
TO BE STRESSED, 'CAUSE IT MAKES
THE BLOOD PRESSURE WORSE.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> BUT OF COURSE YOU'RE STRESSED
ABOUT IT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU WANT TO TRY TO GET AS
CLOSE TO FULL TERM AS WE CAN
HERE.
WE MAY OR MAY NOT GET TO FULL
TERM.
GO AHEAD AND LAY ON BACK.
>> I'M DUE IN JUST SIX WEEKS,
AND MY MOM TOOK ME TO MY
DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT TODAY
BECAUSE TONY HAD PLANS
TO GET SOME WORK DONE
ON HIS TATTOOS.
>> THAT HURTS.
>> I KNOW.
>> [laughs]
>> SO WHY'D YOU GET
"FAMILY FIRST"?
WHAT DOES IT MEAN TO YOU?
>> I HAVE TWO LITTLE GIRLS
ON THE WAY, SO...
>> OH, YOU'RE HAVING TWINS?
>> YEAH.
>> WOW.
YOU FREAKING OUT ABOUT THAT?
>> IT IS OVERWHELMING,
'CAUSE, LIKE, I'M STILL YOUNG.
I'M ONLY 17, SO...
STRESSFUL.
[tattoo gun buzzing]
[ultrasound whirring]
>> THIS IS THE STUPIDEST
THING I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> WHAT?
>> "SOME BUNNY LOVES ME"?
>> I THINK IT'S CUTE.
>> I'M JUST JOKING.
>> [chortles]
SO WHEN THE BABIES FIRST COME
HOME, ARE YOU GONNA TAKE OFF
WORK?
>> YEAH, I'LL TAKE OFF AS MUCH
TIME AS I CAN.
>> YEAH, AND I KNOW MY MOM
HAS TIME.
SHE'S GONNA TAKE OFF, TOO,
WHICH WILL BE GOOD,
ESPECIALLY IF I HAVE TO GET
A C-SECTION, YOU KNOW?
I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO BE
GETTING UP A LOT AND DOING
EVERYTHING FOR THEM, SO...
>> IT WILL BE HARD
FOR THE FIRST COUPLE OF MONTHS.
>> YEAH.
BUT DO YOU THINK, WITH THE JOB
YOU HAVE NOW,
THAT YOU'LL BE ABLE TO MAKE
ENOUGH MONEY FOR US TO MOVE OUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IF YOU HAVE A JOB,
THEN, YEAH.
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY I'M NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO GET A JOB
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO LEAVE
THEM WITH DAYCARE OR WHATEVER
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
'CAUSE IF THEY'RE GONNA NEED
THEIR MOM, THEN,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH, BUT THAT JUST MEANS
IT'S, LIKE, A LONGER PROCESS
OF US MOVING OUT.
>> I KNOW, BUT...
I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
TO SAY TO YOU.
>> WELL, THAT KIND OF REALLY
PISSES ME OFF.
I GUESS I JUST WANT TO BE
OUT OF HERE FAST, 'CAUSE I WANT
TO--I DON'T WANT TO RAISE
MY KIDS AROUND YOUR PARENTS.
I WANT TO RAISE MY KIDS
ON MY OWN.
>> I KNOW, BUT--
>> AND I'M NOT COMFORTABLE HERE.
AND I DON'T EVEN WANT TO BE HERE
RIGHT NOW, BUT I AM.
>> YEAH, WELL, I AM SORRY
THAT YOU FEEL THAT WAY.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO GET OUT,
TOO, BUT--
>> THEN YOU HAVE TO WORK
IN ORDER TO DO THAT.
>> YEAH, WELL,
WHEN THE GIRLS COME,
WE CAN SEE HOW THINGS GO,
AND THEN WE'LL SEE.
BUT LOOK AT IT THIS WAY.
IF I GET A JOB RIGHT AWAY,
THEY'RE GONNA BE RAISING OUR
KIDS.
EVERYONE IS.
YOUR GRANDPARENTS, YOUR MOM,
MY MOM.
LIKE, AT LEAST HERE,
THEY WOULD HAVE MORE GUIDANCE
FROM US.
SO I DON'T THINK YOU REALIZE
THAT.
>> AND I DON'T THINK YOU REALIZE
HOW UNHAPPY I AM HERE.
>> WE HAD TO SET ASIDE OUR
DISCUSSION ABOUT MOVING OUT
BECAUSE I WOKE UP IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT WITH HORRIBLE PAIN.
TONY RUSHED ME TO THE HOSPITAL.
WHEN I GOT THERE,
THE DOCTOR SAID I WAS GOING
INTO LABOR AND THAT ONE
OF THE BABIES WAS SITTING
BREACH AND CAUSING THE PAIN
DOWN MY BACK.
IT'S BEEN THREE HOURS,
AND THE BABY STILL ISN'T
TURNING, AND THE PAIN KEEPS
GETTING WORSE.
MY BACK HURTS SO BAD.
>> WANT ME TO RUB IT?
>> NO.
>> NO, DON'T TOUCH IT?
>> OKAY.
>> I'M SCARED NOW.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
ONCE YOU HAVE THAT EPIDURAL,
YOU'LL BE PERFECT.
>> DOES EPIDURAL HURT?
>> I'M NOT GONNA LIE TO YOU.
IT'S A LITTLE UNCOMFORTABLE.
BUT ONCE THE EPIDURAL GOES IN,
YOU WON'T BE CARING ABOUT
NOTHING.
>> [chortles]
>> I MEAN, NOT UP HERE,
BUT, LIKE, YOUR BODY.
YOUR BACK PAIN WILL IMMEDIATELY
GO AWAY, SWEETIE.
>> SOUNDS SO GOOD.
>> OKAY?
>> A COUPLE HOURS LATER,
THE BABY STILL WASN'T TURNED,
SO THE DOCTOR DECIDED TO DO
A C-SECTION.
[baby screaming]
>> * IF YOU LOOK AROUND
* THIS IS WHERE
* YOUR ARE RIGHT NOW
>> OH, MY GOSH.
SHE'S SO SMALL.
>> * THINGS YOU'VE NEVER *
* SEEN BEFORE
>> HOW DO YOU SPELL AMARIAH?
>> A-M-A-R-I-A-H.
>> AND WHAT'S THIS ONE?
>> AMAYAH.
A-M-A-Y-A-H.
>> * WONDERFUL
* BEAUTIFUL
* TAKE IT ALL IN
>> WELL, AREN'T YOU JUST SO
CUTE?
>> * IF YOU LOOK AROUND
>> HELLO.
>> * THINGS YOU'VE NEVER *
* SEEN BEFORE
>> I'M FEELING BETTER AFTER
MY SURGERY, BUT SINCE THE BABIES
WERE BORN A COUPLE WEEKS EARLY,
THEY NEED TO SPEND SOME TIME
IN THE NICU SO THEY CAN GET
A LITTLE BIGGER BEFORE WE TAKE
THEM HOME.
IT'S WEIRD TO THINK THAT THESE
GUYS WERE JUST INSIDE OF ME.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YEAH, IT'S WEIRD, ISN'T IT?
>> IT'S WEIRD.
HI.
HEY, BABE.
>> SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH ALL THIS ROOM NOW
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO SHARE.
>> OH, YOU'RE TIRED, HUH?
LOOK AT THOSE BIG EYES.
OH.
YOU JUST WANT TO GO BACK
TO SLEEP, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> OH.
>> [chortling] YEAH.
[train horn blowing]
>> AFTER STAYING AT THE HOSPITAL
WITH THE BABIES FOR A FEW DAYS,
THEY WERE FINALLY BIG ENOUGH
TO COME HOME.
BABE...
[baby crying]
DO YOU WANT TO COME GRAB HER?
[dogs barking]
HEY.
[baby screaming]
OH, GOD.
MOM.
UGH.
IT'S, LIKE, AN HOUR PAST
WHEN SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO EAT.
BRI, NO, GET AWAY FROM...
[dog barking]
[baby farts]
OH, MY GOSH.
[baby wailing]
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
THANK YOU, MOM.
[baby wailing]
>> SUCKS THAT I HAVE TO GO
TO WORK.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, I THINK--
[baby spits up]
OH, MY GOODNESS.
EVEN THOUGH I HAVE MY
FAMILY'S HELP, I'M WORRIED
THAT TAKING CARE OF TWO BABIES
ALL DAY WHILE TONY'S AT WORK
IS GONNA BE A LOT FOR ME TO
HANDLE.
YOU GUYS ARE A LOT OF WORK.
[baby screaming]
>> WHILE TONY'S BEEN TAKING ON
MORE SHIFTS TO MAKE EXTRA MONEY,
I'VE BEEN KEEPING UP WITH
HOMESCHOOLING SO I CAN STAY
ON TRACK TO GRADUATE THIS YEAR.
THIS ONE TAKES TWO HOURS?
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA BE QUIET
FOR TWO HOURS?
PROBABLY NOT, HUH?
[chuckles]
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN EASY,
'CAUSE TAKING CARE OF TWO AT
ONCE IS REALLY TOUGH.
SO IT'S A RELIEF WHEN MY MOM
GETS HOME FROM WORK
SO SHE CAN HELP ME.
[baby cooing]
>> OKAY.
IT'S FUNNY.
I THOUGHT I WOULDN'T REMEMBER
HOW TO TAKE CARE OF BABIES.
AND IT'S, LIKE, TWO.
DOUBLE.
>> DOUBLE THE FUN.
>> YEAH.
HAS THIS BEEN HARDER
THAN YOU THOUGHT IT WOULD BE?
>> YEAH, IT'S A LITTLE HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
IT'S STILL, LIKE, FUN,
BUT AT TIMES, IT'S JUST
OVERWHELMING.
> >I THINK YOU'RE DOING
A PRETTY GOOD JOB, THOUGH.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE HAD
TO MAKE A LOT OF SACRIFICES?
>> WELL, YEAH.
I CAN'T, LIKE, GO TO SCHOOL.
CAN'T WORK OR, LIKE,
GO DO WHATEVER I WANT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HARD TO, LIKE, PUT
ALL MY WANTS AND NEEDS ASIDE,
BUT...
IT DIDN'T TAKE VERY LONG AT ALL
FOR ME TO REALIZE, LIKE, THEY'RE
ALL THAT MATTER--LIKE, THEY'RE
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING,
YOU KNOW?
>> THAT'S GOOD.
I'M GLAD.
BUT I THINK IT'S GOOD THAT
YOU GUYS ARE LIVING WITH US
'CAUSE HOPEFULLY YOU CAN SAVE
SOME MONEY AND BE SMART
WITH IT AND SAVE IT
FOR WHEN YOU DO MOVE OUT.
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE I'D REALLY LIKE
TO SEE YOU GUYS BE INDEPENDENT,
TOO, YOU KNOW, BUT...
>> YEAH.
[baby squealing]
EVEN THOUGH TONY WORKS ALL
THE TIME, IT'S NICE THAT
HE'S WILLING TO HELP ME OUT
WITH THE BABIES AT NIGHT.
[baby squealing]
I THINK HE REALIZES HOW MUCH
WORK THEY ARE, 'CAUSE HE HASN'T
BROUGHT UP MOVING OUT
SINCE BEFORE THEY WERE BORN.
OH, MY GOSH, I AM SO TIRED.
[yawns]
[baby crying]
>> SO I'M THINKING ABOUT
BUYING A TRUCK.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> YEAH.
I'LL SHOW YOU A PICTURE.
>> HOW MANY PEOPLE DOES
THIS CAR SEAT?
>> THREE PEOPLE.
>> HOW MUCH IS IT?
>> $1,000.
>> [laughs]
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU WANT ME
TO SAY.
WHAT'S THE POINT OF BUYING A
TRUCK THAT YOU CAN ONLY USE
FOR YOURSELF?
DON'T YOU THINK IT'D BE
BENEFICIAL TO SAVE UP FOR
ANOTHER CAR THAT COULD BE
A FAMILY CAR?
>> NO.
>> SO THIS CAR BASICALLY IS MORE
SOMETHING YOU WANT
THAN SOMETHING WE NEED.
>> GUESS SO.
I WANT SOMETHING,
THEN I SET MY MIND TO THAT.
YOU ALREADY KNOW THAT.
>> I KNOW.
I GUESS THAT'S JUST THE ANNOYING
PART TO ME.
BECAUSE I CAN'T JUST GO OUT
AND SPEND A BUNCH OF MONEY
ON SOMETHING I WANT.
I'VE GIVEN UP BASICALLY
EVERYTHING AND--
>> WELL, SO HAVE I.
>> JUST WHENEVER I DO ANYTHING,
I ALWAYS TAKE INTO CONSIDERATION
OUR FAMILY, OUR BABIES.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M NOT
PUTTING THEM FIRST.
I GO TO WORK EVERY DAY
FOR THEM.
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME I DID
SOMETHING FOR MYSELF?
>> TONY, I DON'T DO ANYTHING
FOR MYSELF, SO DON'T MAKE
IT SOUND LIKE I DO.
>> I'M NOT SAYING YOU DO.
>> IT'S JUST,
THERE'S OTHER THINGS WE COULD
SPENDING MONEY ON, SO...
>> IF I'M THE ONE MAKING THE
MONEY, WHY CAN'T I GO
BUY SOMETHING THAT I WANT?
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY I CAN'T
MAKE MONEY.
I'M SORRY I HAVE TO STAY HOME
ALL DAY AND TAKE CARE OF THEM.
IF YOU WANT TO QUIT YOUR JOB
AND TAKE CARE OF THEM
AND LET ME TO GO WORK, FINE.
AND THEN I CAN TELL YOU,
"OH, I MAKE THE MONEY.
YOU CAN'T DO THIS,
YOU CAN'T DO THAT."
THAT'S NOT HOW A RELATIONSHIP
WORKS.
SURE, YOU MAKE THE MONEY,
BUT IT'S BOTH OF OUR MONEY.
AND I DON'T APPRECIATE YOU
THROWING THAT IN MY FACE
ALL THE TIME, THAT I DON'T MAKE
MONEY.
I CAN'T.
I'M NOT IN A POSITION WHERE
I CAN GO OUT AND WORK RIGHT NOW.
[sniffs]
I'M NOT IN A POSITION WHERE
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
THAT'S WHY IT'S KIND OF
ANNOYING, 'CAUSE YOU CAN GO
AND DO THESE THINGS FOR
YOURSELF, BUT I CAN'T DO
ANYTHING.
I'VE GIVEN UP EVERYTHING,
AND I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
[train horn blowing]
>> I HOPE I GOT THROUGH TO TONY
THAT BUYING A TRUCK IS A REALLY
BAD IDEA FOR OUR FAMILY RIGHT
NOW.
HE'S GOT THE DAY OFF,
SO HE'S SPENDING IT
WITH HIS STEPDAD.
AND I ASKED MY MOM TO BABYSIT
'CAUSE I HAVEN'T SEEN MY FRIENDS
SINCE BEFORE THE BABIES WERE
BORN.
I STILL DON'T REMEMBER WHOSE
DRINK IS WHOSE, BUT--
>> I CAN.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> OH, YOU WERE RIGHT.
THAT IS MINE.
>> YEAH.
SO HAS IT BEEN TIRING
TAKING CARE OF TWO BABIES?
>> YEAH, IT'S HARD.
IT'S A LOT HARDER THAN I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE.
LIKE, IT'S FUN.
WELL, IT'S NOT ALWAYS FUN.
BUT IT'S REWARDING,
BUT IT KIND OF SUCKS TOO.
>> THAT SUCKS.
>> SO HOW ARE THINGS WITH TONY?
>> WELL, HE'S WANTING TO GET
A TRUCK, AND HE'S, LIKE,
REALLY INTO IT,
AND IT'S KIND OF ANNOYING
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT HIM
TO GET ONE.
>> THAT DOES NOT SOUND
PRACTICAL.
>> SO HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF SHE SPENT 850 BUCKS
ON SOMETHING THAT YOU DIDN'T
WANT HER TO GET?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I WOULDN'T LIKE IT.
>> SO WHY DO YOU WANT TO GET
A TRUCK?
>> SO I CAN HAVE FUN, LIKE...
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN IT STARTS TO SNOW MORE
AND RAINS A LOT MORE,
I COULD GO OUT,
GO MUDDING.
>> [chuckles]
>> MAKES SENSE TO ME.
>> CAN YOU GUYS AFFORD
A TRUCK RIGHT NOW?
>> NO.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE A FAMILY CAR
AT ALL.
LIKE, IT'S SOMETHING FOR HIM.
>> AND SINCE YOU'RE MARRIED,
THEN IT'S A PARTNER THING.
>> MM-HMM.
WHAT HE DOES,
IT DOESN'T JUST AFFECT ME.
IT AFFECTS, LIKE, THREE OF US,
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> AND IT ALSO AFFECTS, LIKE,
EVERYONE ELSE, 'CAUSE IF WE
DON'T HAVE MONEY TO BUY STUFF,
I HAVE TO ASK MY MOM
OR HE HAS TO ASK HIS MOM,
SO IT AFFECTS A LOT MORE PEOPLE
THAN JUST HIM.
>> IT'S ONLY A THREE-SEATER,
BUT, I MEAN, I'M ALWAYS DOING
EVERYTHING FOR EVERYBODY ELSE,
SO THIS TRUCK'S MORE FOR ME
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
>> DON'T TELL KARLEY THAT.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
>> IF YOU'RE TRYING TO GET
AN APARTMENT, SAVING UP
WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN A BAD IDEA.
>> IF YOU COULD DO ANY ONE THING
FOR YOURSELF, WOULD YOU BUY
YOURSELF A TRUCK?
>> [chuckling] NO.
AND THAT'S THE THING.
LIKE, I DON'T WANT TO ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, IT'S JUST NOT
A PRIORITY ANYMORE.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, YOURSELF IN GENERAL
IS NOT A PRIORITY?
>> YEAH, LIKE, DOING THE BASICS,
LIKE, TAKING CARE OF MYSELF,
LIKE, EATING AND SHOWERING
AND STUFF--
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
>> I THINK THAT COMES WITH
BEING A MOM, THOUGH.
I THINK ONCE YOU HAVE YOUR KIDS,
YOU'RE MORE FOCUSED ON MAKING
THEM HAPPY RATHER THAN YOURSELF.
>> EXACTLY.
>> WHERE'S TONY AT?
>> I'M NOT SURE WHERE HE IS.
MAYBE I SHOULD CALL HIM.
[line trilling]
>> THERE'S $820.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO ALL THAT'S
FILLED OUT AND IT'S GOOD TO GO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OTHER THAN THAT,
APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
>> SEE YOU.
[line trilling]
>> I'M SORRY.
THE NUMBER...
>> [chortles]
WELL, THIS ISN'T A GOOD SIGN.
[ignition clicking]
[engine turning over]
>> OH, MY GOSH.
DON'T LAUGH.
>> NOT A GOOD START.
[gas pedal squeaking]
>> SHOULD I HOLD IT DOWN LONGER?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
[engine turning over]
[ignition clicking]
PUMP IT.
[engine slowly turning over]
>> [bleep].
[engine turning over]
[engine revving]
THERE WE GO.
>> KARLEY'S GONNA BE SO PISSED.
>> IS ANYTHING EVEN COMING OUT
OF THE BOTTLE?
>> YEAH, SHE'S GETTING SOME.
>> [laughs]
>> MAYBE YOU SHOULD CHECK.
>> HERE, LET ME LOOK.
>> NOT GONNA SUCK ON IT.
THAT WOULD BE WEIRD.
AND FORMULA TASTES LIKE CRAP,
SO...
>> NO, IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
LET ME GO GET HER A DIFFERENT
NIBBLE.
>> DANO, YOU'VE BEEN STARVING
HER THIS WHOLE TIME.
>> I HAVE NOT.
SHE'S HAD SOME FOOD.
>> SO GUESS WHAT I DID.
I BOUGHT THE TRUCK.
>> [bleep], ARE YOU JOKING?
THAT'S AWFUL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU SPENT MONEY
ON A TRUCK.
>> BUCKLE UP, BABY.
>> LIKE, I HAVE NEVER BEEN
SO HURT AND SO DISAPPOINTED
AND SO PISSED OFF BEFORE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WENT
AND SPENT ALL OUR MONEY
ON A TRUCK WHEN YOU KNEW
HOW I FELT ABOUT IT.
I GUESS I JUST EXPECTED MORE
OF YOU.
>> RIGHT.
>> LIKE, I DON'T DESERVE
TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP
WHERE I HAVE TO WONDER
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE THERE
FOR ME OR NOT.
>> YOU HAVE TO WONDER IF I'M
GONNA BE THERE FOR YOU OR NOT?
>> NOW I DO, YES.
>> 'CAUSE I'VE DONE NOTHING
TO SHOW YOU THAT I'M GONNA BE
THERE FOR YOU?
>> YOU HAVE UP UNTIL NOW.
>> I DIDN'T MARRY YOU.
I DIDN'T GET A JOB.
>> TONY, YOU HAVE UP UNTIL NOW.
>> [sighs]
QUIT YELLING.
[sniffs]
'CAUSE THAT'S GONNA PISS ME OFF
REAL QUICK.
>> I DON'T CARE, TONY.
I'M NOT GONNA--
>> I [bleep] CARE!
>> I'M NOT GONNA TIPTOE
AROUND YOU.
>> I'M DONE TALKING ABOUT IT.
[sniffs]
YOU'RE ALREADY STARTING TO YELL.
>> IT'S BECAUSE IT'S ANNOYING
TO REALIZE THAT YOU DON'T EVEN
CARE.
IT'S REALLY FRUSTRATING
TO REALIZE THAT YOU DISRESPECTED
THE PERSON WHO TAKES CARE
OF YOUR CHILDREN,
WHO HAD TO GIVE UP EVERYTHING
FOR THESE CHILDREN.
YOU DON'T EVEN CARE.
>> SO WHAT CAN YOU DEPEND ON ME
FOR, NOTHING?
THEN WHY THE [bleep]
AM I STILL HERE?
WHY THE [bleep] AM I STILL
WORKING?
WHY ARE WE STILL MARRIED?
TELL ME, WHY AM I STILL HERE?
IF I'M NOT GONNA CARE ABOUT YOU,
WHY AM I STILL HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DON'T
CARE ABOUT ME, HONESTLY.
>> RIGHT, I DON'T GIVE A
[bleep].
END OF STORY.
[sniffs]
>> IT'S NOT FAIR TO ME, TONY.
>> I'M [bleep] LEAVING.
HERE, TAKE AMARIAH.
>> LEAVE YOUR CARD ON THE TABLE.
THEY NEED FOOD.
>> KISS MY ASS.
[door slams]
>> * DO YOU REMEMBER
>> [sobbing]
>> I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO TONY
SINCE HE LEFT AND SPENT LAST
NIGHT AT HIS MOM'S HOUSE.
>> I REALLY JUST WISH THAT
TONY WOULD HAVE THOUGHT ABOUT
THE CONSEQUENCES OF WHAT
IT WAS GONNA DO TO YOUR FAMILY
WHEN HE BOUGHT THAT TRUCK.
YOU KNOW?
>> I KNOW.
>> I DON'T THINK A LOT OF
TEENAGERS THINK THAT WAY.
I THINK THEY JUST THINK
ABOUT THEMSELVES AND WHAT
FEELS GOOD TO THEM
AT THE TIME.
>> YEAH, THAT'S--THAT'S TRUE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO MOVE OUT FOR A LONG TIME.
>> YEAH.
I TRY NOT TO LET YOUR FIGHTS
BOTHER ME, BUT THEY DO.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S UNDERSTANDABLE.
BUT THEY GOT TO LEARN
ON THEIR OWN.
YOU KNOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAKES ME FEEL GUILTY 'CAUSE
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A BURDEN.
AND MAKES ME FEEL BAD.
>> I GUESS, JUST THINKING AHEAD,
THAT YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
WHY I'M FRUSTRATED,
'CAUSE HE REALLY HASN'T HAD
TO SPEND ANY OF HIS PAYCHECK
TOWARD THESE GUYS.
AND DAD AND I HAD DIFFERENT
PLANS FOR THIS STAGE OF OUR
LIFE, AND IT DIDN'T INCLUDE
HELPING TEENAGERS RAISE
THEIR BABIES.
NOT THAT WE WON'T HELP YOU,
AND WE'RE GLAD TO DO IT.
IT'S JUST, IT WASN'T WHAT I
ENVISIONED FOR YOU, YOU KNOW?
>> I KNOW.
I REALLY DO APPRECIATE WHAT
YOU'RE DOING FOR US.
>> AND I KNOW YOU DO.
IT'S NOT YOU.
BUT I THINK WHAT WOULD MAKE IT
EASIER IS IF TONY WOULD BE
MORE REALISTIC ABOUT WHAT
THINGS COST AND REALISTIC
ABOUT HOW MUCH RESPONSIBILITY
THIS ALL IS.
>> IT REALLY BOTHERS ME
THAT TONY'S SELFISHNESS IS NOW
HURTING MY ENTIRE FAMILY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I DON'T LIKE LIVING HERE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, TONY?
PART OF ME WOULD LIKE YOU GUYS
TO MOVE OUT.
>> OKAY, MOM.
LET IT GO.
>> NO.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU REALLY
KNOW HOW MUCH WE REALLY DO.
>> I'LL START PAYING YOU
$300 A MONTH.
>> TONY, I DON'T EXPECT
YOU TO PAY.
I WOULD REALLY LIKE SOME
GRATEFULNESS.
>> COULD YOU COME DOWN HERE,
MOM, INSTEAD OF...
>> I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
THIS CONVERSATION.
>> WELL, THIS WAY IT KIND OF
GIVES US AN IDEA--
>> I'M NOT GONNA MAKE YOU PAY
RENT.
>> WELL, IF IT'S A BIG DEAL--
>> NO, IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
IT'S JUST THAT A LITTLE BIT
OF GRAT--A LITTLE BIT
OF GRATEFULNESS.
>> DO I NOT SHOW APPRECIATION?
>> NOT LAST NIGHT, YOU DIDN'T.
>> WHEN I [bleep] WORK MY ASS
OFF EVERY [bleep] DAY.
I GO TO WORK EVERY [bleep]--
>> I DO TOO!
>> SERIOUSLY, GUYS, STOP.
I CAN'T DEAL WITH IT.
>> SEE, YOUR MOM'S [bleep]
CRAZY.
I'M LEAVING.
>> I--TONY, I WORK EVERY--
>> SHUT THE [bleep] UP, SYNDEE.
YOU'RE [bleep] CRAZY.
>> TONY, DON'T SIT THERE
AND TALK TO HER LIKE THAT.
>> IT'S FINE.
I CAN TAKE IT.
IT'S FINE.
>> GIVE ME AMAYAH,
GO WHEREVER YOU FREAKING PLEASE,
BUT YOU'RE NOT GONNA--
>> I'M [bleep] LEAVING.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> YEAH, CLEARLY--
>> I GO TO WORK EVERY [bleep]
DAY...
>> I DO TOO.
>> I [bleep] WORK MY ASS OFF.
AND THEN I COME HOME AND I GET
TO, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S COMING
TO ME?
>> I DIDN'T SAY IT LIKE THAT.
>> SHUT THE [bleep] UP.
>> GET OUT.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TALK TO HER
LIKE THAT.
>> [bleep] YOU.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> [bleep] I HATE THIS, TONY!
I HATE THIS!
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT ANYMORE!
[bleep]! AH!
[squealing wildly]
I CAN'T BREATHE!
[squealing]
[sobbing]
HE WON'T LISTEN.
>> * AND I TRIED EVERY DAY
* TO BE THE BEST I CAN
* UNTIL THE DAY YOU CAME ALONG
* THEN I SPENT SOME TIME
* WORRYING WHO I AM
* AND IF I COULD
* BE GOOD ENOUGH
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 & PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
[ambling guitar music]
*
[baby crying]
[door opens]
>> HEY.
[baby cooing]
[sighs]
I THINK THE REASON WHY
I LASHED OUT IS 'CAUSE
SHE TOLD ME THAT I WAS
UNAPPRECIATIVE.
>> YEAH, WELL,
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY
SHE FEELS LIKE YOU'RE NOT?
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE WHEN YOU TALK
ABOUT HOW YOU HATE IT HERE,
SHE FEELS UNAPPRECIATIVE
'CAUSE SHE BENDS OVER BACKWARDS.
AND SHE CARES A LOT ABOUT US,
AND SHE IS REALLY WORRIED.
WHICH, I DON'T BLAME HER.
I WOULD BE, TOO, IF I WAS HER.
>> LIKE I SAID, I DON'T KNOW.
I LIVE MY LIFE DAY BY DAY.
I STILL DO.
I JUST...
DO WHAT I NEED TO DO THAT DAY.
>> OKAY, BUT I'VE ALREADY MADE
IT CLEAR, NOW THAT WE'RE PARENTS
AND EVERYTHING, WE HAVE THIS
RESPONSIBILITY TOGETHER.
YOU NEED TO DO WHAT'S BEST
FOR EVERYONE,
BECAUSE IT'S A LOT OF STRESS
AND EVERYTHING,
AND IT'S REALLY FRUSTRATING.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I...
I'M SORRY.
WHEN I LEFT, I WAS JUST
THINKING I HAVE TO GROW UP.
AND I REALIZE THAT THE TRUCK
CAUSES A LOT OF FIGHTS
BETWEEN US, SO I GUESS
I'VE JUST BEEN THINKING ABOUT
SELLING IT SO THAT WE HAVE
MORE MONEY TO MOVE OUT.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU ARE FINALLY TAKING
EVERYONE INTO CONSIDERATION.
[baby coos]
MAKES ME HAPPY.
>> YEAH.
>> IF I COULD GO BACK,
I WOULD GO ON BIRTH CONTROL
AND EVERYTHING.
LIKE, THE HARDEST PART IS,
NOT ONLY DO I HAVE TO
CONSTANTLY TAKE THE BABIES
INTO CONSIDERATION.
I HAVE TO CONSTANTLY TAKE TONY
INTO CONSIDERATION,
WHAT HE WANTS.
AND IT'S HARD.
IT'S A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITY.
AND IT FRUSTRATES ME,
I SHOULD SAY, BECAUSE SINCE
WE BECAME PARENTS,
I'VE GROWN UP,
BUT HE HASN'T GROWN UP.
AND I TELL HIM,
LIKE, IT'S A LOT MORE SERIOUS
NOW.
WE HAVE ALL THIS RESPONSIBILITY
TOGETHER.
BUT HE JUST DOESN'T UNDERSTAND.
SO I HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
HE'S STILL A TEENAGER,
AND EVEN THOUGH I'VE MATURED,
HE HASN'T.
>> * WHEN YOU
* ARRIVED
* A PROMISE
* WAS DELIVERED
* I WAITED FOR YOU
* DREAMING
* AWAY ALL THE WHILE
[baby crying]
>> SINCE I'VE HAD THE BABIES,
IT'S MADE ME REALIZE, LIKE,
ALL THAT I'M MISSING OUT ON.
LIKE, I DON'T GET TO GO
TO COLLEGE AND STAY IN A DORM.
I DON'T GET TO GO TO SCHOOL
EVERY DAY AND GO AND HAVE FUN
WITH MY FRIENDS.
NOW I HAVE TO, LIKE, DEPEND
ON EVERYONE FOR OTHER STUFF,
WHICH I DIDN'T WANT TO DO
WHEN I HAD KIDS.
I WANTED TO BE ABLE TO DO IT
ON MY OWN.
BUT WITHOUT MY FAMILY,
I DON'T KNOW WHERE WE WOULD BE.
>> DOES SHE NEED HERS,
OR IS SHE GOOD?
>> OH, NO.
SHE ALREADY POOPED.
I ALREADY CHANGED HERS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WILL HAPPEN
IF WE HAVE TO STAY HERE
FOR, LIKE, ANOTHER YEAR.
I REALLY DON'T.
BUT I DON'T BLAME ANYONE ELSE
BUT MYSELF.
[baby crying]
I MEAN, IT REALLY IS
MY OWN FAULT.
[chime dings]
>> EVERY TIME WE GET TWO STEPS
AHEAD, WE GET FOUR STEPS BACK.
>> I HAVE WARRANTS IN TWO
COUNTIES.
>> YOU CAN GO TO JAIL.
>> YOU DON'T THINK I KNOW THIS
[bleep]?
I DON'T NEED A SECOND MOM.
I NEED A GIRLFRIEND!
[baby crying]
>> WE ARE DONE.
I COULD TEAR SOMEBODY'S
HEAD OFF RIGHT NOW, YOU KNOW.
[sirens blaring]