[laughter]
[chime dings]
>> HI, I'M DEVON.
>> [shrieking]
>> I'M 16 YEARS OLD,
AND I'M FROM RICHMOND, VIRGINIA.
I HAVE TONS OF FRIENDS,
AND I ALWAYS SPEAK MY MIND.
YOU ARE ACTING
LIKE YOU ARE FIVE.
LIKE, GROW UP.
PEOPLE TELL ME
I'M MATURE FOR MY AGE,
WHICH IS PROBABLY WHY
I FELL FOR MY BOYFRIEND, COLIN.
>> I'VE ALREADY FINISHED SCHOOL.
>> HE'S FOUR YEARS OLDER THAN ME
AND IN THE ARMY.
WHEN WE MET A YEAR AGO,
HE HAD JUST RETURNEFROM IRAQ.
COLIN AND I HANG OUT A LOT.
[belches]
EXCUSE ME.
[laughs]
BUT I'M STILL FOCUSED ON SCHOOL
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT TO START
MY SENIOR YEAR.
I LIVE WITH MY OLDER BROTHER,
MY TWO SISTERS, MY MOM...
>> I MEAN, YOU WERE SPOILED
'CAUSE YOU WERE THE BABY.
>> AND OUR FOUR DOGS.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
BUT THEY STILL GET ALONG,
SO MY DAD STAYS AT OUR HOUSE
WHEN HE'S IN TOWN.
>> SO IN A MONTH,
WHAT TEST ARE YOU TAKING?
>> MATH.
AND MY SISTER JANE
IS A TEEN MOM,
SO HER ONE-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER
STAYS WITH US TOO.
>> OH.
>> YEAH.
EVEN THOUGH SPACE IS TIGHT,
MY MOM ALSO LET COLIN
MOVE IN WITH US
AFTER WE STARTED DATING
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T GET ALONG
WITH HIS PARENTS.
WITH ALL THESE PEOPLE,
THINGS CAN GET PRETTY CROWDED
AROUND HERE, BUT WE'LL NEED
TO MAKE ROOM FOR ONE MORE
BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
[rooster crows]
COLIN, WAKE UP.
>> I'M SLEEPING.
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE LAUGHING.
PEEKABOO!
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S A LOT
OF PEOPLE AT MY MOM'S,
IT'S GOOD PRACTICE TO HAVE
MY NIECE KAYLEE AROUND...
LOOK, WHO'S HAND IS THAT?
SEEING AS I'M DUE
IN THREE MONTHS.
AND LUCKILY, COLIN GETS ALONG
WITH MY FAMILY,
ALTHOUGH IT WASN'T EASY
AT FIRST.
IN THE BEGINNING, WE WENT FROM
SNEAKING YOU INTO THE HOUSE.
MY MOM DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE STAYING THERE.
>> AND THEN, ONE DAY
YOUR MOM JUST WALKED IN,
AND I WAS SLEEPING IN THE BED.
>> AND THEN, AFTER THAT,
YOU STARTED LIVING THERE.
>> AND THEN SHE WAS LIKE,
"I DON'T CARE."
>> I MEAN, SHE DID CARE.
>> SHE CARED, BUT, LIKE--
>> SHE JUST DIDN'T WANT ME
TO GET PREGNANT, BUT...
>> YEAH.
>> IT DIDN'T WORK TOO WELL.
>> FIRST TIME I MET YOU
WAS THAT BONFIRE.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE CUTE.
I DIDN'T EVER THINK I WAS GONNA
HAVE A BABY WITH YOU.
I HAVE A THING FOR MEN
IN UNIFORM.
>> YEAH, I CAME BACK FROM IRAQ,
AND, AT FIRST, YOU KNOW,
I WASN'T REALLY LOOKING
FOR A RELATIONSHIP.
>> MM-HMM.
>> BUT THEN,
I LIKED BEING WITH YOU, SO...
WE ACTUALLY STARTED DATING IN--
>> both: SEPTEMBER.
>> AND HERE, A YEAR LATER--
>> THEN I FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT IN MAY.
I GUESS NOBODY'S PREPARED
FOR A BABY, BUT WE DID IT.
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR IT.
JUST SOMETHING WE GOT TO DO.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GREAT THAT COLIN
WANTS TO SUPPORT ME AND THE BABY
EVEN THOUGH IT MIGHT BE TOUGH
TO MAKE ENDS MEET.
[chime dings]
COLIN HAS TWO JOBS.
HE WORKS FULL TIME
AT A WAREHOUSE,
AND EVER SINCE HE GOT BACK
FROM IRAQ, HE'S STILL PART
OF THE ARMY RESERVES,
WHICH MEANS HE HAS
TO REPORT FOR DUTY ONCE A MONTH.
>> TEN HUT!
>> SO SINCE HE'S
BRINGING IN THE MONEY,
I CAN FOCUS ON FINISHING SCHOOL,
WHICH IS GOOD BECAUSE I START
MY SENIOR YEAR IN A MONTH.
ALL MY FRIENDS WERE REALLY
SHOCKED WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
ESPECIALLY SINCE
I DIDN'T EVEN FIND OUT
TILL I WAS FIVE MONTHS ALONG.
>> I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU GOT FIVE MONTHS
AND DIDN'T GET SICKNESS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DIDN'T FEEL ANYTHING.
THAT'S HALF YOUR PREGNANCY.
>> I MEAN, I HAD NOTHING.
>> I COULD KIND OF TELL
THAT YOU WERE GETTING
A LITTLE BIGGER TOO.
>> I NEVER--I DIDN'T.
>> I JUST THOUGHT
SHE WAS GETTING FAT.
>> IT WAS JUST HER TUMMY.
>> WHEN DID YOU SWITCH
TO YOUR NUVARING?
>> UM, ABOUT THE TIME
I GOT PREGNANT.
FOR REAL.
>> SO YOU MUST HAVE GOT PREGNANT
IN BETWEEN, FROM SWITCHING
FROM THE PILL TO NUVARING?
THAT'S CRAZY.
>> WERE YOU SCARED
WHEN YOU FOUND OUT?
>> I MEAN, I WAS, LIKE, CRYING,
LIKE, HYSTERICALLY,
LIKE, SHAKING.
>> WHY?
>> I WAS LIKE, "DANG IT,
MY PARTNER IN CRIME IS GONE."
>> WHAT DID YOUR MOM SAY?
>> "WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO,
DEVON?
WHAT NOW?"
>> MM-HMM.
>> SO HOW DO YOU THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE FOR YOU?
>> HARD, 'CAUSE I KNOW
I'LL WANT TO GO OUT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I NEVER SEE YOU MISS A PARTY.
>> YEAH, BACK IN THE DAY.
>> YOU WOULDN'T MISS ONE.
>> NOW I'M TOO TIRED TO GO OUT.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU'VE KIND OF,
LIKE, GIVEN YOUR LIFE UP.
>> I FEEL IT TOO, GIRL.
I'M ALREADY SCARED.
>> YOU SHOULD BE SCARED!
THIS IS SCARY.
I'M SCARED.
>> I'M SCARED FOR YOU.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO BE
"US" ANYMORE.
>> IT'S STARTING TO SINK IN
THAT EVERYTHING'S GONNA CHANGE.
LUCKILY, I'LL HAVE
MY FAMILY'S SUPPORT.
>> [screams]
>> THERE'S ALREADY EIGHT OF US
IN THE HOUSE,
AND SOON THERE'LL BE NINE.
>> HOW LONG YOU GONNA BE?
>> ALL RIGHT.
GUESS I'M GOING UPSTAIRS.
>> IT'S GONNA BE TIGHT,
BUT AT LEAST I'LL HAVE
LOTS OF HELP,
AND I'LL HAVE MY SISTER JANE
TO GO TO FOR ADVICE.
SHE HAD A KID AT 17
AND IS NOW A SINGLE MOM.
THAT'S FUN.
>> SO I KNOW HOW HARD IT IS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT,
LIKE, THE LIVING SITUATION
WITH ALL THESE BABIES
GONNA BE IN ONE ROOF?
>> I'M JUST GLAD THAT I HAVE,
LIKE, SOMEBODY ELSE HELPING ME.
LIKE, I'M NOT BY MYSELF.
LIKE, I GOT YOU, MOM, AND COLIN.
>> IT'S CRAMPED IN THIS HOUSE.
>> JUST SO MUCH STRESS
RIGHT NOW.
I JUST HAVE TO THINK ABOUT,
GOD, I'M NOT EVEN DONE
WITH SCHOOL YET.
>> EVEN THE LITTLEST THINGS
AREN'T EASY ANYMORE.
GOING TO SCHOOL AFTER BEING
UP ALL NIGHT, AND THEN TRY
TO STAY AWAKE THROUGH CLASS,
AND THEN COME HOME
AND DO IT ALL OVER AGAIN.
I MEAN, IT'S ALL HARD.
>> I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS
WE'LL FIGURE ALL THAT OUT
WHEN IT COMES OUT.
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
JUGGLE SCHOOL WITH A BABY,
AND I'M STILL DEALING
WITH MY MOM'S DISAPPOINTMENT.
>> HONESTLY,
IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING.
>> RUDE.
>> THAT'S NOT RUDE.
IT'S HONEST.
SINCE YOUR OLDER SISTER
GOT PREGNANT,
I DIDN'T WANT THAT FOR YOU.
YOU THINK, "IT HAPPENED ONCE."
>> I MEAN, AT LEAST I, LIKE,
TRIED TO BE ON BIRTH CONTROL--
>> YEAH, I KNOW THAT.
>> AND TRIED TO BE
RESPONSIBLE ABOUT IT.
JUST GOT TO FINISH SCHOOL
AND GO TO COLLEGE.
>> IT'S JUST GONNA BE HARD.
DO WE HAVE CHILD CARE
ARRANGEMENTS?
HAVE YOU EVEN THOUGHT OF THAT?
>> I MEAN, NOT YET.
>> I JUST WORRY ABOUT
WHEN REALITY HITS.
>> OH, IT ALREADY HAS.
TRUST ME.
>> NO, IT HASN'T.
I'LL HELP AS MUCH AS I CAN,
DEVON, BUT I'M NOT GONNA RAISE
THIS CHILD.
>> [bleep].
>> I KNOW IT'S HARD.
>> 'CAUSE I'M GONNA MISS OUT
ON EVERYTHING.
>> MY MOM HAS MADE ME REALIZE
HOW HARD THINGS ARE GONNA BE,
AND EVEN THOUGH COLIN MAKES
ENOUGH MONEY FOR NOW, WE STILL
HAVE A LOT TO FIGURE OUT.
WE HAVE ABOUT, WHAT,
THREE MONTHS?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M GONNA STOCK UP
ON DIAPERS AND WIPES.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO DISAPPOINT
YOU GUYS BECAUSE I WANT
TO BE ABLE TO, YOU KNOW,
BUY THE THINGS FOR THE BABY
AND EVERYTHING AND PAY THE BILLS
WITHOUT TROUBLE INSTEAD
OF LIVING PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK,
BE ABLE TO SAVE MORE MONEY
FOR THE BABY, SO...
>> I MEAN, I DO WANT TO FINISH
SCHOOL AND GO TO COLLEGE
AND WORK IN THE MEDICAL FIELD.
I MEAN, I THINK
IT WOULD BE GOOD.
AS LONG AS WE'RE SUPPORTING
EACH OTHER.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THE BABY.
I JUST WANT TO GIVE HIM, LIKE,
A GOOD LIFE, AND HE WON'T HAVE
TO, LIKE, STRUGGLE.
COLIN IS GOING ON RESERVE DUTY
FOR A FEW DAYS.
>> [whispers] IT'S 5:30.
>> IT SUCKS FOR HIM TO BE AWAY,
BUT IT'S BETTER
THAN HIM SERVING FULL-TIME.
WHILE COLIN'S GONE,
I NEED TO START FOCUSING
ON SCHOOL, AND TODAY,
I START MY SENIOR YEAR.
I REALLY WANT TO GRADUATE,
BUT I'M SEVEN MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND THIS IS MY FIRST DAY
AT SCHOOL WITH A BIG BELLY.
>> DROP YOU OFF ON THIS SIDE?
>> CAN I GO THIS WAY?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, BABY,
YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
>> YEAH, I'LL BE FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
YOU HAVE A GOOD DAY, OKAY?
[chime dings]
>> SCHOOL WAS REALLY HARD.
THE HALLWAYS ARE SO CROWDED.
EVERYBODY STARES AT ME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
I'M GONNA DEAL WITH THIS
FOR THE NEXT FEW MONTHS.
I'M JUST IRRITATED.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> 'CAUSE FRICKING SCHOOL.
I STARTED CRYING BECAUSE
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THERE,
AND I WAS FRUSTRATED,
AND, LIKE, MY FEET JUST HURT.
LIKE, IT'S JUST SO MUCH,
AND I'M REALLY TIRED.
I JUST FEEL LIKE PEOPLE JUST,
LIKE, TREAT ME DIFFERENT
NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT.
>> HOW DO THEY TREAT YOU
DIFFERENT?
ARE THEY, LIKE, MEAN TO YOU?
>> I MEAN, THEY'RE NOT MEAN.
I MEAN, I CAN HEAR PEOPLE TALK
ABOUT ME, LIKE, "LOOK AT HER."
>> YOU DO?
>> LIKE, PEOPLE ALWAYS
STARE AT ME
LIKE THEY'VE NEVER SEEN
A PREGNANT PERSON BEFORE.
I'M JUST FED UP
WITH THE PEOPLE THERE.
I HATE IT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> COLIN'S BACK FROM DUTY.
WHERE'S THAT GONNA GO?
>> MAYBE THE CLOSET.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> GOOD LUCK.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE HIM HOME,
BUT OUR STUFF IS REALLY
STARTING TO PILE UP.
>> WE GOT TO FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT
'CAUSE THIS SUCKS.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF SPACE.
I MEAN, WHEN HE COMES,
WHERE'S ALL HIS STUFF GONNA GO?
>> MM-MM-MM.
I GUESS RIGHT NOW WE'RE GONNA
DEAL WITH WHAT WE HAVE.
I'M NOT COMPLAINING.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD LIVING HERE.
COULD BE WORSE.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T MIND
STAYING HERE.
I'D JUST LIKE TO HAVE KIND OF
MORE SPACE THAN WHAT WE GOT.
>> HONESTLY, I'M NOT EVEN
STRESSING TO GET OUT OF HERE.
I MEAN, IT'S FREE.
>> WHAT, DO YOU JUST WANT
TO STAY HERE INSTEAD OF
GETTING OUR OWN PLACE?
'CAUSE I--
>> I MEAN, I'M NOT TRYING
TO CONVINCE YOU TO STAY HERE,
BUT IF YOU DON'T
HAVE THE MONEY TO MOVE OUT,
WHY WOULD YOU WANT, LIKE--
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO MOVE OUT?
>> WELL, I KNOW YOU LIKE
BEING CLOSE TO YOUR FAMILY
AND EVERYTHING.
I JUST LIKE HAVING MY PRIVACY,
YOU KNOW?
ESPECIALLY NOW THAT WE'RE
GONNA HAVE LANDON.
I MEAN, I'M A LITTLE OLDER
THAN YOU, SO I'M, LIKE,
PAST THAT STAGE OF WANTING TO
STAY AT HOME WITH MOMMY, SO...
>> I'M JUST SAYING I JUST WANT
TO BE ON MY FEET, AND I WANT
TO MAKE SURE I'M READY
BEFORE I JUMP INTO ANYTHING.
>> I JUST WANT TO BE ABLE TO
PULL INTO MY OWN DRIVEWAY--
>> I JUST WANT TO--
DON'T WANT TO BE BROKE.
>> GO TO MY OWN ROOM.
WHEN I HAVE THE MONEY TO GET
A HOUSE, I'M GONNA GET A HOUSE.
>> WELL, WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
THEN WE'LL GO.
>> JUST HOPEFULLY THAT'S,
YOU KNOW, NOT TOO FAR AWAY.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHY COLIN
WANTS TO MOVE OUT,
BUT I REALLY DON'T THINK
WE CAN AFFORD IT ON OUR OWN.
>> I'M DUE IN A MONTH,
AND COLIN IS STILL DEAD SET
ON BUYING A HOUSE.
>> THIS IS THE ONE I LIKE.
IT'S GOT THREE BEDROOMS.
>> BUT I DON'T THINK WE CAN
MAKE IT WORK.
HOPEFULLY MY MOM CAN REASON
WITH HIM.
HOLA.
>> HEY.
>> WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT MOVING OUT.
WE WANTED YOUR OPINION.
>> OH, YEAH?
WHERE ARE YOU MOVING TO?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
>> I JUST WANT TO HAVE
MY OWN HOUSE.
>> I MEAN, DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN BUY A HOUSE?
>> I NEED TO FIND OUT HOW MUCH
I CAN AFFORD,
LIKE, BASED ON MY INCOME.
>> WHEN YOU BUY A HOUSE, YOU'RE
RESPONSIBLE FOR EVERYTHING.
IT'S A LOT OF EXPENSE.
>> AND THEN WE STRUGGLE
AND NOT HAVE ANYTHING.
MAYBE WE CAN FURTHER THINGS
WHEN LANDON GETS HERE.
>> TAKE OUT TIME
TO THINK ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
AFTER TALKING TO MY MOM,
COLIN AND I STARTED GETTING
OUR ROOM READY FOR THE BABY.
>> WE NEED TO GO THROUGH
THIS STUFF.
>> BUT SPACE IS TIGHT.
[bleep] SO UNORGANIZED,
IT'S NOT EVEN FUNNY.
AND WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
EVEN MORE STUFF TO FIT IN
BECAUSE MY BABY SHOWER
IS TOMORROW.
[cheers and applause]
>> HOW PRETTY.
>> OKAY, CAN I GET
EVERYBODY'S ATTENTION?
THE BELLY GAME.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE THIS YARN
AND CUT HOW BIG AROUND
YOU THINK DEVON IS.
>> I DON'T THINK WE'RE GONNA
HAVE ENOUGH YARN
FOR MY STOMACH--
[laughter]
'CAUSE THAT WOULD BE LONG.
>> WHOOPS.
>> all: AWW.
>> AH, HEART BREAKER.
>> OOH, BREAST PADS.
>> GONNA NEED THOSE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU WANT TO SIT DOWN?
>> OKAY.
>> ARE YOU GONNA HAVE
A NATURAL BIRTH?
[laughter]
>> WOULD YOU?
>> I'M NOT PREGNANT.
IT DON'T MATTER
WHAT I'M GONNA [bleep] HAVE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO FEEL A THING.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE WHEN I GET
A LITTLE PAPER CUT.
I FREAK OUT.
>> I FREAK OUT TOO.
>> ARE YOU SCARED?
>> I MEAN, I'M NERVOUS,
BUT WHAT CAN I DO?
>> SO AS FAR AS, LIKE,
BABY STUFF GOES, LIKE,
WHO'S GONNA BUY WHAT?
LIKE, DIAPERS AND STUFF.
>> HIM.
[laughter]
I MEAN, HE'S THE ONE
WITH THE JOB RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T WORK RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> COLIN'S BEEN WORKING
AT THE WAREHOUSE JOB FULL-TIME.
>> BYE, SWEETHEART.
I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
AND I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO FOCUS ON SCHOOL,
BUT IT'S BEEN A STRUGGLE.
I DIDN'T FEEL WELL DURING CLASS
TODAY AND HAD TO GO HOME EARLY.
>> SO HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> I GOT SICK.
I WAS JUST SITTING IN CLASS
AND FELT HOT ALL OF A SUDDEN,
AND SO I JUST GOT UP, WENT
TO THE BATHROOM, AND THREW UP.
I DON'T WANT TO DEAL
WITH SCHOOL RIGHT NOW.
>> HOW DO PEOPLE REACT
TO YOU BEING PREGNANT?
>> HORRIBLY.
I MEAN, I UNDERSTAND I GOT TO GO
TO SCHOOL, BUT I THINK
I'M MIGHT JUST GET MY G.E.D.
I THINK I CAN DO IT AT HOME
A LITTLE BETTER THAN GOING.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO GRADUATE?
>> I MEAN, I DO, BUT...
I JUST CAN'T GO A WHOLE YEAR
DOING THIS.
I'M BUMMED NOT TO GRADUATE
WITH MY FRIENDS, BUT I FEEL
LIKE THIS IS THE ONLY WAY
I CAN GET MY DEGREE.
TONIGHT IS HOMECOMING.
SINCE SCHOOL'S BEEN SO HARD,
I WASN'T SURE
THAT I WANTED TO GO,
BUT I TOLD MY FRIEND JESSICA
THAT I'D HELP HER GET READY.
>> HEY.
>> HEY, GIRL.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> HOW'S SCHOOL?
LIKE, ARE YOUR GRADES STILL--
WHAT?
NO!
>> YEAH.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE GONNA
WALK WITH US.
>> I WANT TO,
BUT IT'S JUST SO MUCH.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
DO YOU FEEL YOU'RE, LIKE,
MISSING OUT ON--
>> I MEAN, I KNOW I'M MISSING
OUT ON BEING THERE, BUT JUST
WITH A BABY, IT'S DIFFERENT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
SO ARE YOU GONNA GO
TO HOMECOMING?
>> NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> 'CAUSE I COULDN'T FIND
A DRESS THAT FITS,
AND MY FEET SWELL UP TOO MUCH.
DEFINITELY DON'T WANT TO GO.
>> WELL, YOU COULD COME--
>> TAKE PICTURES.
>> TAKE PICTURES WITH ALL OF US.
>> MAN, THAT DEPRESSES ME.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I FEEL TOO FAT.
>> WELL...
>> BOO-HOO.
GO GET READY.
I WANT TO SEE YOUR DRESS.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> TA-DA.
>> OH, THAT'S CUTE.
>> YOU LIKE IT?
I'M EXCITED.
>> ARE THESE YOUR SHOES,
I GUESS?
>> YEAH, AREN'T THEY CUTE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> SASSY.
>> BREAK MY ANKLE.
>> I PROBABLY WILL.
[laughter]
I WISH YOU WERE GOING.
>> YEAH.
I KNOW YOU GOT TO GO,
SO I'M NOT GONNA HOLD YOU UP.
>> YEAH.
BUT HOW DO I LOOK?
>> AW, YOU LOOK CUTE.
>> CUTE?
>> GOD, I CAN'T WAIT
TO HAVE MY BODY BACK.
>> [laughs]
>> WHILE I'M STARTING MY G.E.D.,
COLIN IS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW WE CAN AFFORD OUR OWN PLACE.
AND TODAY HE MET
WITH THE ARMY RECRUITER.
>> I GOT ALL THIS STUFF
AND THEN SOME.
THIS IS GONNA STICK WITH ME
FOR MY REST OF THE CAREER
IN THE MILITARY.
>> WHICH IS?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YOUR CAREER.
LIKE, RE-SIGNING?
>> I MEAN, ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
>> TIME WILL TELL WHAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW, JUST--
THEY PAY FOR THE HOUSE,
THEY PAY FOR EVERYTHING, SO...
IF I WAS ACTIVE DUTY, WE
WOULDN'T STRUGGLE.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
IF THERE'S A WAR STILL GOING,
I DON'T WANT TO GET DEPLOYED.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GET DEPLOYED
AND MISS OUT.
IT SUCKS TO MOVE AWAY
FROM YOUR FAMILY, BUT, YOU KNOW,
YOU DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GO AWAY.
[chime dings]
EVEN THOUGH RE-ENLISTING
WOULD BRING IN MORE MONEY,
THERE'S NO POINT IN HAVING
OUR OWN PLACE IF COLIN IS GONE.
>> COLIN, WAKE UP.
I'M, LIKE, LEAKING.
[groans]
I FEEL LIKE I'M HAVING,
LIKE, CONTRACTIONS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO MY MOM.
MA, I FEEL LIKE I'M HAVING
CONTRACTIONS FOR REAL.
>> WELL, I HOPE THIS IS IT.
>> ME TOO.
>> YEAH, IT HURTS.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE READY AS ANYBODY'LL
EVER BE TO PUSH A BABY
OUT THEIR CROTCH.
>> DON'T HAVE THAT BABY
UNTIL I GET IN THERE.
>> WHEN WE GOT THERE, THE DOCTOR
CONFIRMED THAT I WAS IN LABOR,
AND THEY ADMITTED ME.
>> HI, BUDDY.
>> WELL, HI.
>> HOW MANY CENTIMETERS
ARE YOU DILATED?
>> I THINK THREE, BUT THEY'RE
GONNA START PITOCIN...
[speaking indistinctly]
>> THEY'RE GONNA START WHAT?
>> PITOCIN.
>> YOU'LL BE FINE.
>> [moans]
I JUST WANT TO TURN OVER.
I'M SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
[moans]
[crying]
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT IS IT?
[bleep].
AFTER NINE HOURS IN LABOR,
I DECIDED TO GET AN EPIDURAL
TO HELP WITH THE PAIN.
[machinery beeps]
AFTER 12 HOURS OF LABOR,
IT WAS FINALLY TIME TO PUSH.
>> PUSH HARD.
ONE AND PUSH.
THERE YOU GO.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> [moans]
[baby cries]
>> OHH, WELL, HELLO, EVERYBODY.
>> ♪ WAKE UP HAPPY
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE LYING
♪ BY MY SIDE
♪ AND I KNOW THAT EVERYTHING
♪ EVERYTHING WILL BE ALL RIGHT
♪ WILL BE ALL RIGHT
>> [cries]
>> AFTER TWO DAYS
IN THE HOSPITAL,
IT'S FINALLY TIME
TO BRING LANDON HOME.
BUT I'M STILL REALLY SORE
AFTER THE BIRTH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> COLIN, JUST GO.
I'M IN PAIN.
DRIVE SLOW OVER THESE.
IT HURTS.
[moans]
>> SORRY.
>> MOTHER [bleep].
I CAN'T HELP THE ROAD, BABE.
>> THIS CAR RIDE'S
[bleep] HELLACIOUS.
I FEEL LIKE MY INSIDES
ARE GONNA [bleep] FALL OUT.
ALL THIS PAIN FOR YOU.
>> HOME, SWEET, HOME.
WELCOME HOME, BABY LANDON.
>> [sneezes twice]
>> BLESS YOU! BLESS YOU!
>> WHOO!
SO ARE YOU READY FOR ALL THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> LOOK AT HIM YAWNING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE LANDON HOME,
BUT COLIN HAS TO GO BACK
TO HIS WAREHOUSE JOB TOMORROW.
HE'S PICKING UP EXTRA SHIFTS
TO SAVE MONEY, SO I'M NOT SURE
IF I CAN RELY ON HIM
FOR HELP DURING THE NIGHT.
WHAT TIME DO YOU HAVE TO BE
TO WORK TOMORROW?
>> I GOT TO LEAVE
AT, LIKE, 6:00.
>> SO YOU HAVE TO WAKE UP
AT LEAST ONCE TONIGHT.
IS HIS DIAPER WET?
YES.
>> [cries]
[farts]
>> YOU GOT GAS?
>> [farts]
>> CHILD, IF YOU POOP ON ME,
IT'S NOT GONNA BE GOOD.
>> [grunts]
>> OKAY.
GOOD NIGHT.
LOVE YOU.
>> [cries]
>> AW, YOU JUST POKED ME
IN THE EYE.
>> [cries]
[cries]
[alarm buzzes]
>> OKAY.
>> WHILE COLIN'S AT WORK,
I'M IN THE HOUSE ALL DAY
WITH THE BABY.
>> [cries]
>> I'M TRYING TO KEEP UP WITH
MY G.E.D. SINCE I'M PLANNING
TO TAKE IT IN A FEW MONTHS,
BUT IT'S BEEN REALLY HARD.
HERE I AM DOING THIS FOR YOU,
AND YOU'RE MAKING IT SO HARD
TO CONCENTRATE.
MY MOM AND SISTERS HELP ME
WHENEVER THEY CAN.
>> [snores]
>> HE'S SNORING.
YEAH, TIP HIS HEAD BACK
A LITTLE BIT,
AND IT'LL STOP.
>> AND THEN COLIN PITCHES IN
WHEN HE'S HOME FROM WORK.
I WOULD'VE BEEN DONE BY NOW.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
>> LOOK, HE'S ALL SMILES.
DO YOU SEE THAT?
>> WE'VE BEEN SO BUSY
THAT WE HAVEN'T EVEN HAD TIME
TO TALK ABOUT MOVING OUT.
I'M GLAD TO HAVE THE SUPPORT,
BUT NOW THAT LANDON'S HERE,
SPACE IS EVEN TIGHTER.
IT'D BE NICE IF I COULD, LIKE,
USE MY CHANGING TABLE
AS A CHANGING TABLE
AND NOT A DAMN STORAGE SPACE.
YOU WANT TO CALL ALEXUS?
[phone ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING
ALL DAY?
>> SITTING HERE LIKE ALWAYS.
>> WELL, I'M DOWN
TO HANG OUT WHENEVER.
>> I KNOW.
HOPEFULLY I'LL BE DONE
WITH SCHOOL SOON, THOUGH.
>> WHAT ELSE DO YOU HAVE
TO FINISH?
>> YOU KNOW I'M GETTING
MY G.E.D.
LIKE, I HAVE WORK TO DO NOW,
AND, LIKE, I HAVEN'T EVEN
DONE IT.
>> YEAH, YOU SHOULD PROBABLY
GET ON THAT.
>> GOING CRAZY IN THIS HOUSE.
BEING HERE, JUST SO CRAMPED,
LIKE--
>> YOU NEED TO GET OUT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> [squeals]
>> KAYLEE, GET--NO.
>> COME HERE, KAYLEE.
KAYLEE.
>> WITH ALL THE HOURS
COLIN'S BEEN WORKING
TO SAVE MONEY, IT'S BEEN
EVEN MORE ANNOYING TO COME HOME
TO A CROWDED HOUSE.
SO TIRED OF CLEANING UP
AFTER OTHER PEOPLE.
JUST TOO MANY PEOPLE
IN THE HOUSE.
[chime dings]
THIS HOUSE WAS SMALL
WHEN THERE WERE EIGHT OF US.
NOW THAT THERE'S ANOTHER PERSON,
AND WITH ALL THE DIAPERS,
CLOTHES, AND BABY STUFF,
I'M STARTING TO FEEL LIKE
THE WALLS ARE CAVING IN ON ME.
WE NEED TO GET OUT OF HERE.
IT'S TOO CROWDED.
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH ROOM
FOR EVERYTHING WE HAVE.
>> YEAH, I JUST WANT SPACE.
>> EVEN IF IT IS A TWO-BEDROOM
HOUSE, THAT'S ENOUGH FOR US,
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
CLEANING UP AFTER OTHER PEOPLE,
AND US SHARING A ROOM WITH HIM,
IT'S LIKE--
IT'S JUST A LOT.
I THINK WE SHOULD SEE
WHAT WE CAN AFFORD.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THE DOWNSIDE IS, IT'S, LIKE,
MY WHOLE PAYCHECK'S GONNA GO
TO THE HOUSE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THEN WE DON'T--
WE WON'T HAVE NO MONEY
TO DO ANYTHING ELSE.
>> NOW THAT COLIN AND I
BOTH WANT TO GET OUR OWN HOUSE,
HE STARTED LOOKING INTO
HOW WE CAN AFFORD IT.
>> HELLO?
>> I'M TRYING TO SCHEDULE A,
YOU KNOW, APPOINTMENT TOMORROW
TO GO LOOK AT A HOUSE
OR SOMETHING.
>> I'M KIND OF WANTING
TO GET SOMEWHERE SOON.
>> WHILE COLIN
IS DOING RESEARCH,
I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW
WE'RE GONNA MANAGE ON OUR OWN.
>> YOU READY, BOOKERS?
>> DO YOU NEED HELP?
>> I GOT HIM.
>> [cries]
>> DON'T CRY.
>> SO IS THIS WHOLE MOTHERHOOD
THING EVERYTHING YOU EXPECTED?
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO EXPECT,
REALLY.
I MEAN, I DID 'CAUSE OF YOU,
BUT--
>> YOU THINK HANDLING KAYLEE
AS SHE WAS GROWING UP
HELPED ANY?
>> MM-HMM.
YOU WERE MY PRACTICE BABY.
>> YOU LOOK CRAZY.
>> BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WOULD BE SO HARD JUST
TO GET UP AND GO OUT, BUT,
I MEAN, I WANT TO START COLLEGE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
HOW I'M GONNA DO IT, LIKE...
>> I MEAN, IT'S NOT EASY.
IT TAKES A LOT OF WORK.
AT LEAST YOU'LL HAVE COLIN,
SO...
>> YEAH.
I JUST, LIKE, WANT TO
GET OUT OF THE HOUSE
AND GET OUR OWN SPACE.
>> TCH. YEAH.
>> I'M JUST TIRED OF THE MESS,
LIKE, CLEANING UP AFTER PEOPLE.
>> SO HAVE Y'ALL, LIKE,
LOOKED AT ANY KIND OF HOUSES
OR ANYTHING?
>> NO, RIGHT NOW WE'RE, LIKE,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT HIS
PRICE RANGE WOULD BE FOR, LIKE,
HOUSE PAYMENTS, SO...
IT'S GONNA SUCK, BUT...
GOT TO DO IT.
WE'RE JUST TRYING TO FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT.
COLIN AND I ARE MEETING
WITH A BROKER TODAY TO FIND OUT
IF WE CAN EVEN AFFORD
OUR OWN PLACE.
DOES HE NEED A HAT?
IS IT COLD?
>> NO.
>> WELL, WELCOME HERE TONIGHT.
WE GOT SOME GOOD NEWS FOR YOU.
>> GOOD.
>> SO, COLIN,
WE TALKED LAST NIGHT.
JUST WANTED TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT YOUR CREDIT IS GOOD.
WE'RE ABLE TO WORK WITH THAT.
WE GOT YOU PRE-APPROVED
FOR A LOAN, AND THE LOAN AMOUNT
IS UP TO ABOUT $127,000.
>> YEAH, I CAN WORK WITH THAT.
>> YOU CAN DO THAT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY, WELL, THE BANK
SAYS YOU CAN TOO.
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T, YOU KNOW,
CHANGE JOBS OR NOTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> DON'T LOSE YOUR JOB
AND DON'T SPEND ANY MONEY.
>> GREAT.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO HELPING
YOU FIND THE RIGHT HOUSE.
>> SINCE WE HAVE A BUDGET NOW,
COLIN AND I CAN START
LOOKING AT HOUSES.
>> WE GOT TO BE THERE SOON.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M COMING.
>> YOU READY?
BUCKLED UP?
>> YES, DAD.
>> ME, PERSONALLY, I WANT SOME
LAND, LIKE, MORE THAN AN ACRE,
BUT WE'LL SEE.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD. GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> YOU EXCITED?
>> YEAH.
>> COME ON IN.
THIS IS THE EATING
AND KITCHEN AREA.
>> YOU LIKE IT?
OH, I LIKE THIS.
>> CENTRAL HEATING THERE.
>> THIS IS, LIKE, PERFECT.
>> I CAN DEAL WITH THIS.
>> I'M IN LOVE WITH THIS HOUSE
SO FAR.
OH, WOW, THIS HOUSE IS BIG.
>> 1,500 SQUARE FEET.
>> OH, WOW.
>> YEAH.
>> SO HOW MUCH IS THIS HOUSE?
>> IT'S A LITTLE BIT OUTSIDE
YOUR PRICE RANGE.
IT'S $139,000.
YOUR PRICE MAX IS $125,000,
SO...
>> I MEAN, I JUST DON'T WANT
TO JUMP INTO ANYTHING TOO SOON.
>> I KNOW, YOU WANT TO GAUGE--
>> I WILL LOOK AROUND,
BUT THIS IS, LIKE--
THIS IS WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
>> YEAH, THIS IS PERFECT.
NOW THAT WE'RE LOOKING,
I'M GETTING EXCITED
ABOUT OUR OWN PLACE.
HERE, COLIN.
WITH ALL THE PRESSURE OF TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHERE TO LIVE,
I HAVEN'T SEEN MY FRIENDS
IN A WHILE.
[all screaming]
OH, MY GOD, I THINK
I ALMOST JUST BROKE THE TABLE.
>> WHOO, I JUST ABOUT FELL.
>> YOU JUST ALMOST BROKE
THE TABLE?
>> YEAH.
>> SO HOW WAS THAT FOR YOU?
>> A WORKOUT.
BUT IT FELT GOOD
'CAUSE I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING
WHILE I WAS PREGNANT.
>> FELT GOOD TO GET OUT
THE HOUSE AND EVERYTHING?
>> BABY-FREE.
>> I BET.
HAVE A BREAK.
>> YES.
>> OW.
>> COLIN AND I,
WE STARTED LOOKING AT HOUSES.
>> YAY!
>> OH, THAT'S EXCITING.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU'RE, LIKE,
GROWING UP REALLY FAST.
>> YOU GOT TO WITH A BABY.
>> I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
>> YEAH, I'M REALLY EXCITED.
>> I'M EXCITED TO GET A HOUSE
AND DECORATE.
>> WELL, JUST DON'T RUSH THINGS.
>> I'M NOT.
GIRL, IF YOU SAW THE SPACE THAT
I HAVE IN MY HOUSE, YOU'D KNOW
WHY I NEED TO GET OUT.
IT'S AWFUL.
SPEAKING OF BABIES,
I THINK MINE'S BEEN
WITH COLIN LONG ENOUGH, SO...
I THINK IT'S TIME TO GO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> READY?
>> YEAH.
>> NOW THAT WE'RE GETTING READY
TO MOVE, COLIN'S BEEN WORKING
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE
TO SAVE MONEY.
MY LITTLE MAN.
HELLO.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
>> NOT SO GOOD.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I GOT LAID OFF.
>> REALLY?
WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I MEAN, IT SUCKS BECAUSE
WE WERE DOING EVERYTHING
ON OUR OWN
AND BUYING EVERYTHING
AND NOT DEPENDING
ON ANYBODY ELSE,
ABOUT TO GET OUR OWN HOUSE,
LIKE...
>> DID NOT WANT THIS TO HAPPEN
AT ALL.
>> BABY, NOBODY WANTS
TO LOSE THEIR JOB.
>> LIKE, BEFORE HE WAS BORN,
THIS WAS, LIKE, ONE OF MY
BIGGEST FEARS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE NOT FAILING.
YOU'RE DOING THE BEST YOU CAN,
BUT--
>> THIS SLOWED EVERYTHING DOWN.
DADDY'S SORRY, THOUGH.
HE'S GONNA DO WHATEVER HE CAN.
>> female announcer: DON'T
GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> COLIN'S BEEN JOB HUNTING
FOR THE PAST TWO WEEKS,
BUT HE STILL HASN'T
FOUND ANYTHING.
RE-ENLISTING FULL-TIME
IS AN OPTION, BUT FOR NOW,
HE'S LOOKING CLOSE TO HOME.
WE'RE GOING TO MEET WITH OUR
REALTOR TO SEE WHAT THIS MEANS
FOR OUR MOVING PLANS.
>> NOW WE GOT TO TELL HIM
THAT I LOST MY JOB.
HE'S GONNA BE LIKE, "YOU READY
TO FILL OUT A CONTRACT?"
AND THEN THAT'S PROBABLY
WHEN I'M GONNA BE LIKE,
"WELL, HERE'S THE CATCH."
>> LIKE, IT JUST SUCKS.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE
WE TOOK ONE STEP FORWARD,
AND NOW WE'RE TAKING--
HAVE TO TAKE ANOTHER ONE BACK.
>> WELL--
IT SUCKS.
>> YEAH.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HELLO.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO
FIRST TIME LOOKING AT HOUSES.
>> YES.
>> SO WHAT WOULD YOUR CONCERNS
BE AS FAR AS WRITING AN OFFER?
>> I WANT TO MOVE NOW, BUT...
>> MM-HMM.
>> COLIN LOST HIS JOB.
>> DID YOU REALLY?
>> YEAH, A COUPLE DAYS
AFTER WE TALKED WITH YOU,
I GOT LAID OFF.
>> I'M SO SORRY TO HEAR THAT.
>> YEAH.
IT SUCKS.
>> YEAH, I'M SORRY, MAN.
JUST TO BE FRANK WITH YOU GUYS,
THE FACT THAT YOU
DON'T HAVE A JOB--
YOU CAN'T SEARCH FOR HOUSES.
>> YEAH.
>> NOW, IF I GOT A NEW JOB,
DON'T YOU HAVE TO HAVE--
>> TWO MONTHS.
>> TWO MONTHS WITH A JOB?
>> MM-HMM.
AND UNDERSTAND, YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS GO THROUGH THINGS,
ESPECIALLY AS YOUNG AS YOU ARE,
BUT MY THING IS, I DON'T WANT
TO WASTE YOUR TIME.
LIKE, I DON'T WANT TO SELL YOU
ON A DREAM, AND YOU CAN'T--
>> MM.
>> IT'S NOT FAIR FOR ME
TO DO THAT TO YOU.
>> YEAH.
COLIN'S BEEN OUT JOB HUNTING
EVERY DAY WHILE I'VE BEEN
AT HOME WITH THE BABY.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S TRYING HIS
BEST, THINGS HAVE NOT TURNED OUT
THE WAY I THOUGHT THEY WOULD.
LIKE A TRAIN WRECK
COMING THROUGH THE DAMN DOOR.
SO HOW DID JOB HUNTING GO?
>> UH, STILL NO JOB.
>> WHERE DID YOU APPLY TO?
>> I APPLIED FOR
A COUPLE WAREHOUSE JOBS
AND A SECURITY JOB.
WHAT DID YOU DO ALL DAY?
>> NOTHING.
JUST SAT HERE AND WATCHED HIM.
YOU NEED, LIKE, A STABLE JOB.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
I'M EVEN CONSIDERING
GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> I THINK THEY HAVE
A FIRE SCIENCE PROGRAM,
AND I WAS THINKING ABOUT
DOING THAT TO BE A FIREFIGHTER.
>> CAN WE GET A HOUSE
IF YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL?
>> NO.
>> OKAY, THEN.
I'D RATHER YOU FIND A JOB.
>> WHAT IF I WENT TO SCHOOL
AND GOT A JOB?
>> THEN YOU'D NEVER BE HOME.
AND THEN I WOULD HAVE TO DO
EVERYTHING BY MYSELF.
WELL, YOU JUST NEED
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT YOU WANT,
AND YOU NEED TO DO IT QUICK.
>> WELL, I'M NOT TELLING YOU
THAT YOU HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO QUICK.
>> COLIN, I HAVE TO STAY HOME.
I HAVE TO WATCH THE BABY.
I HAVE TO GO TO SCHOOL.
I HAVE TO FINISH HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU'RE DONE WITH HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU NEED TO--
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT NEEDS TO GO
OUT THERE AND MAKE THE MONEY
FOR RIGHT NOW UNTIL I CAN.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS DEPLOYMENTS
I CAN GO ON.
>> AND WHAT IS THAT HELPING?
>> I COULD GO TO AFGHANISTAN.
YOU GET MONEY, GOOD MONEY.
>> YEAH.
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT TO
RELOCATE, BUT IT'S AN OPTION.
>> WHEN COLIN LOST HIS JOB,
I MEAN, I WAS DISAPPOINTED
'CAUSE WE WERE READY
TO HAVE MORE SPACE FOR LANDON.
BUT THINGS HAPPEN.
HE LOST IT.
>> APPLYING TO JOBS ALL DAY
GETS FRUSTRATING.
>> YEAH.
SO WE'RE JUST KIND OF TRYING TO
PICK BACK UP THE PIECES AND,
LIKE, GET FINANCIALLY STABLE,
GET A HOUSE, AND JUST KIND OF GO
BACK TO WHERE WE WANTED TO,
LIKE, IN THE BEGINNING.
IT'S NOT FUN HAVING A KID AND
LIVING AT YOUR PARENT'S HOUSE.
>> IF WE MOVE THE BED
LIKE YOUR DAD SAID,
DO YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
>> NOT REALLY.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WOULD DO
WITHOUT COLIN.
>> [babbling]
>> HE'S ALWAYS THERE FOR ME
AND FOR HIM.
I MEAN, IT SUCKS KNOWING
THAT COLIN COULD GO ACTIVE DUTY.
>> WE NEED TO DO SOMETHING
BIGGER AND BETTER.
>> I MEAN, IT'S NOT SOMETHING
THAT I WANT.
YOU'RE ALWAYS GONNA
MAKE SACRIFICES
WHEN YOU'RE A TEEN MOM.
I'M MISSING OUT ON PROM.
LIKE, I'M MISSING OUT ON SENIOR
YEAR, GRADUATING WITH MY CLASS,
SO I'M GETTING MY G.E.D.
TO GO TO COLLEGE FOR MY SON,
AND THAT'S ALL.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE, LIKE,
MOVING SO FAST 'CAUSE, LIKE,
YOU'RE SO YOUNG, AND YOU, LIKE,
ALREADY HAVE YOUR LITTLE FAMILY.
>> YEAH, IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN.
TRUST ME.
>> MY BIGGEST WORRY IS, LIKE,
WHAT I'M GONNA WEAR TO PROM
OR HOW TAN I'M GONNA BE.
>> JUST HAVING TO GROW UP.
I JUST MISS, LIKE, BEING ABLE
TO JUST BE A TEENAGER.
IT'S DEFINITELY HARD.
[chime dings]
>> MY FIANCE PASSED AWAY.
WHAT'S THE POINT FOR GOD
LETTING YOU FIND SOMEBODY
AND THEN JUST TAKE THEM?
>> IT'S THE LAST THING Y'ALL
GOT LEFT OF HIM.
>> HE LOOKS JUST LIKE HIM.
[baby coos]
HE DOESN'T GET TO HOLD HIM.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
>> I KNOW.