>> OH, THANK YOU.
HEY, MY NAME IS MACI.
I'M 16.
I LIVE IN CHATTANOOGA,
TENNESSEE, AND I'M A TOTAL
OVERACHIEVER.
I GET GOOD GRADES,
I PLAY SOFTBALL,
AND I'M EVEN ON
THE CHEERLEADING SQUAD.
BUT DON'T LET THAT FOOL YOU.
I DO HAVE A WILD SIDE.
I'M ALL ABOUT DIRT BIKES.
MY BOYFRIEND, RYAN,
STARTED CHASING ME
WHEN I WAS A SOPHOMORE.
I WASN'T INTO HIM AT FIRST
BECAUSE HE RIDES FOUR-WHEELERS,
WHICH, TO ME, ARE NOT COOL.
BUT EVENTUALLY,
HE SWEPT ME OFF MY FEET.
HE EVEN PUT A RING ON MY FINGER.
[cheering]
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE PSYCHED
FOR SENIOR YEAR,
BUT I'M GRADUATING EARLY
AND MOVING IN WITH RYAN
BECAUSE...
I'M PREGNANT.
>> * MAKE IT RIGHT
* MAKE IT PERFECT
>> OKAY, HEY.
>> HEY.
WHAT YOU DOING?
>> NOTHING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> MY HIGH SCHOOL FRIENDS
STILL LIVE AT HOME
WITH THEIR PARENTS,
SO THEY THINK IT'S REALLY COOL
I HAVE MY OWN PLACE.
I BOUGHT THAT COUCH
WITH MY OWN MONEY.
>> DID YOU REALLY?
>> YES.
I SAVED UP MY
$7-AN-HOUR PAYCHECKS.
>> LET'S GO SEE BENTLEY'S ROOM.
>> OKAY, BENTLEY'S ROOM.
IT'S VERY MESSY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
THESE ARE ALL OF HIS CLOTHES?
>> YES, HE HAS A MILLION.
>> OH, LOOK AT HIS CRIB.
>> LOOK AT HIS LITTLE ONESIES
THAT ARE, LIKE, HARD-CORE.
>> WE'RE HAVING A BOY,
AND WE'RE GONNA NAME HIM
BENTLEY.
>> MACI, HOW DID YOU TELL
YOUR MOM YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> THROUGH A TEXT MESSAGE.
[laughter]
>> THAT'S AWFUL.
>> I WOULD HAVE JUST, LIKE,
NEVER TOLD MY PARENTS.
>> LIKE, "MOM, I GOT"--
[laughter]
"JUST A LITTLE BLOATED."
>> DID YOU JUST, LIKE, SAY--
WHAT DID YOU SAY,
"I'M PREGNANT"?
>> I WAS SITTING IN CLASS,
AND I SAID, "HI, MOM."
SHE SAID, "HI."
I SAID, "I HAVE TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING."
TOOK A FEW DEEP BREATHS,
AND THEN I TEXTED,
"I'M PREGNANT" TO HER.
AND SHE SAID,
"WELL, IF YOU'RE JOKING,
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
IF YOU'RE FOR REAL,
WE ARE NOT HAVING THIS
CONVERSATION VIA TEXT MESSAGE."
YEAH, AND THEN WHEN I GOT HOME,
MY DAD AND MY MOM WERE SITTING
AT THE KITCHEN TABLE
WAITING ON ME.
>> WERE YOU CRYING?
>> RIGHT WHEN I WALKED IN,
I WASN'T CRYING,
BUT MY MOM GOT UP FROM THE TABLE
AND HUGGED ME, AND THEN WE,
LIKE, BOTH STARTED CRYING.
AND THEN IT WAS AWFUL.
IT WAS SAD.
>> YOU NEVER CRY.
>> I KNOW.
>> NEVER.
>> MACI, IT'S OKAY.
>> IT'S GREAT TO HAVE SUCH
A SUPPORTIVE GROUP OF FRIENDS.
I HOPE THINGS GO SMOOTHLY
WITH MY NEW EXPANDED FAMILY.
JUST DON'T--I SEE YOUR DAD
JUST BEING TOO OUTGOING
FOR MY DAD.
>> PROBABLY.
>> THEY WON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
>> CARS.
>> I GUESS.
>> I MEAN, THERE'S SOMETHING
GOING ON HERE.
>> SHE SAID, "I'M PREGNANT."
[laughter]
I LOOKED AT THE CALENDAR
TO SEE IF IT WAS APRIL FOOLS,
AND IT WASN'T.
>> YOU CAN IMAGINE
HOW SHOCKED OUR PARENTS WERE
WHEN THEY FIRST FOUND OUT,
BUT MY DAD DIDN'T KILL RYAN,
AND THEY ARE TRYING
TO BE SUPPORTIVE.
>> FOR SOME REASON,
WE GOT TALKING ABOUT THE WHOLE
EPIDURAL THING, AND I WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, I DON'T THINK I'M GONNA
DO IT WITH THE EPIDURAL."
SHE GOES,
"HA, KEEP AN OPEN MIND."
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT IT,
RYAN?
DO YOU WANT HER TO GET
AN EPIDURAL?
>> YEAH, GET THE SPINAL TAP.
>> WHY?
>> [laughs] SPINAL TAP.
>> HOW ARE YOU GOING TO DO
IN THE OPERATING ROOM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU'LL PROBABLY BE
THE COLOR OF YOUR SHIRT.
THEY'LL PROBABLY NEED TO GIVE
YOU SOME DRUGS.
>> I KNOW.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BE,
LIKE, TENDING TO YOU
WHILE I'M GIVING BIRTH.
[laughter]
I HAVE A LOT TO HANDLE
AT ONLY 16.
RYAN WORKS THE NIGHT SHIFT
AS A DIESEL MECHANIC,
AND I HELP MAKE ENDS MEET
WORKING PART-TIME WITH MY DAD.
THIS IS NOT HOW I PICTURED
MY SENIOR YEAR.
>> * HOW DOES IT FEEL
* TO NEVER DISCOVER
* THAT YOU AND I...
>> SO YOU'RE COMING TO
THE BABY SHOWER SUNDAY?
>> YOU DO NOT NEED
ANY MORE STUFF.
>> YES, I DO.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
HALF THE STUFF I NEED.
>> YOU'VE GOT MORE THAN ENOUGH
TO FILL UP HIS ROOM.
>> WELL, OKAY.
DON'T YOU HAVE MORE STUFF
THAN WHAT'S IN YOUR ROOM?
>> I GUESS, BUT--
>> OKAY.
IT SEEMS LIKE EVERY TIME
I BRING UP SOMETHING
BABY-RELATED, RYAN'S NOT
INTERESTED IN TALKING ABOUT IT.
I'M TELLING YOU.
HE'S GONNA RIDE DIRT BIKES.
>> WHATEVER.
>> 'CAUSE BENTLEY'S NOT RIDING
FOUR-WHEELERS.
>> RYAN, HE'LL BE A BABY.
>> SO?
>> ARE YOU GONNA READ
TO BENTLEY?
>> OH, HELL, NO.
>> WHY?
WHAT IF HE WANTS YOU TO?
>> THEN I GUESS I WILL.
>> WELL, YOU'LL BE WORKING
AT NIGHT.
>> [chuckles]
>> WHAT TIME DO YOU GET OFF?
>> 4:30.
>> IS THAT WHAT TIME
YOU GET OFF EVERY NIGHT?
>> WELL, SOMETIMES YOU GET HOME
AT 5:30, AND SOMETIMES YOU GET
HOME AT 5:00, AND SOMETIMES
YOU GET HOME AT 4:30,
AND SOMETIMES YOU GET HOME
AT, LIKE, 6:00.
WILL YOU GET TO WORK IN THE DAY
WHEN BENTLEY COMES?
>> I DOUBT IT.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE JUST NOT
GONNA LET ME CHANGE.
>> WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT
GONNA LET ME.
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I ASKED YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY.
"BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT GONNA
LET ME" IS A GOOD ENOUGH REASON.
>> WHY ARE YOU BEING MEAN?
>> WELL, 'CAUSE--
[scoffs]
[mellow instrumental music]
*
>> RYAN'S ATTITUDE SUCKS.
>> RYAN WAS ALL ABOUT MARRYING
ME WHEN HE FIRST ASKED,
BUT HE HASN'T SHOWN MUCH
ENTHUSIASM SINCE THEN.
WERE YOUR PARENTS EXCITED
WHEN Y'ALL WENT AND BOUGHT
MY RING THAT DAY?
YOUR DAD WANTED YOU TO GIVE IT
TO ME RIGHT THEN.
>> MY DAD'S SO DUMB.
>> CAN WE TAKE A MIRROR PIC?
>> NO.
>> YES.
>> WHY ARE WE ALWAYS--
>> WE NEVER TAKE PICTURES.
DON'T SAY THAT.
>> WE DON'T?
WE JUST TOOK, LIKE, 50.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
>> YOU LOOK UNHAPPY.
>> WELL, HONEY.
>> LOOK HAPPY.
>> MACI.
>> ONE MORE.
[sizzling]
[laughter]
>> IT IS GONNA BE WILD SEEING
RYAN CARRYING A BABY AROUND.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO CHANGE A DIAPER.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU NEED TO GO TO THAT CLASS
THEY GOT AT THE HOSPITAL, RYAN.
>> THEY DO GOT THEM CLASSES.
>> REALLY?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I MIGHT GO TO THAT ONE.
>> YOU DO NEED TO GO TO
A CLASS ABOUT--
>> WELL, YOU BETTER GO.
I MEAN, TWO WEEKS.
>> DO YOU EVEN KNOW HOW
TO HOLD A BABY?
>> NO.
I'VE NEVER HELD A KID
IN MY LIFE.
>> REMEMBER, LET YOUR ARM
FALL WITH THE EGG.
EASY.
>> Y'ALL ARE MAKING ME
NERVOUS NOW.
>> CATCHING A BASEBALL, RYAN.
[laughter]
>> IT'S TOO HARD.
FLIPPED IT OVER HERE.
>> EXACTLY WHAT WE TOLD YOU
NOT TO DO.
>> YOU GOT EGG SOUP NOW.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO STAY OUT
PARTYING WITH RYAN'S FRIENDS,
BUT IT'S A SCHOOL NIGHT,
AND SINCE MY DUE DATE
WAS ON A COLLISION COURSE WITH
GRADUATION, I TRANSFERRED
TO AN ACCELERATED SCHOOL.
>> * A POCKETFUL OF LOVE
* QUARTERS IN A HIGH SCHOOL
* I TOLD YOU, I TOLD YOU
* THERE'S NOTHING *
* TO BE SAD FOR
>> AT THIS POINT,
I CARE A LOT LESS ABOUT
WHAT PEOPLE THINK OF ME,
BUT I KNOW MY BELLY
IS A BIG DISTRACTION
FOR THE OTHER KIDS.
>> BENTLEY CADENCE.
YEP.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
RYAN FOUND IT IN A BABY BOOK.
>> IS THERE ANYTHING PHYSICALLY
YOU CAN'T DO
THAT YOU USED TO BE?
>> EVERYTHING.
UM, NO.
I PLAYED SOFTBALL
AND VOLLEYBALL AT MY OLD
HIGH SCHOOL, BUT I COULDN'T
PLAY THIS YEAR BECAUSE OF THIS.
MY BACK FEELS LIKE
IT'S CUT IN HALF.
IT HURTS SO BAD.
>> YOU SHOULD MAKE YOUR FIANCE
GIVE YOU A BACK RUB
BEFORE YOU GO TO BED.
>> WELL, HE WORKS SECOND SHIFT,
SO HE GOES TO WORK FROM, LIKE,
5:00 IN THE AFTERNOON
TILL 5:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> OH.
THAT SUCKS.
>> YEAH, IT DOES SUCK.
>> SO DID YOU EVER, LIKE, THINK
ABOUT, "NO, I DON'T WANT THIS;
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS BECAUSE
I'M YOUNG AND I'M NOT SURE
WHAT I'M GONNA DO"?
>> NO.
>> OR YOU JUST PUT UP WITH IT
AND JUST WENT THROUGH IT.
>> JUST PUT UP WITH IT.
I MEAN--I MEAN,
EVERY OPTION CROSSES YOUR MIND,
BUT I NEVER CONSIDERED IT.
I WAS JUST LIKE, "MIGHT AS WELL
MAKE THE BEST OF IT,"
AND SO THAT'S WHAT I'VE DONE.
>> OH, MY GOD, WHAT IS THAT?
[gasps]
>> THE ATTENTION IS NICE,
BUT IT IS DEFINITELY NOT
THE DAY'S ASSIGNMENT.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO BE DOING?
TODAY IS MY BABY SHOWER.
HEY, GUYS.
AND I'M PICKING UP MY FRIENDS
FROM MY OLD SCHOOL.
JUST COMING TO TALK
TO MY OLD FRIENDS.
>> HOW'S IT GOING, MACI?
>> IT'S GOING.
>> TOUCH HIM.
>> YOU CAN TOUCH HIM
IF YOU WANT.
YOU CAN KISS HIM ONCE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO CATCH IT.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO CATCH IT.
>> CATCH THE PREGNANCY.
>> MOTORCYCLES...
[laughter]
>> YES.
[squealing laughter]
>> * DARLING, PLEASE
* DON'T MIND *
* SHE SAID ON OUR LAST NIGHT
>> I HAVE BEEN WANTING
ONE OF THESE.
>> LET ME SEE.
>> * BE THE FIRST TO GO
* WHEN I LEAVE YOU, OH
>> CUPCAKE BREAK.
[laughter]
>> THIS STUFF IS ALL SO COOL,
BUT BENTLEY'S SWEETEST GIFT
OF ALL CAME FROM MY MOM AND DAD.
>> YOU'RE NOT RIDING THAT THING.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I SAID.
>> ISN'T IT CUTE?
I'M REALLY GRATEFUL
THAT I HAVE SUCH COOL PARENTS.
I DEFINITELY DO NOT PLAN TO BE
A HARD-ASS ON BENTLEY.
I DON'T CARE WHAT BENTLEY DOES.
HE CAN PLAY THE FLUTE
IF HE WANTS TO.
HE CAN PLAY CHESS,
JUST AS LONG AS HE'S GOOD
AT WHAT HE DOES.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, I'M GONNA LET HIM DO
WHATEVER HE WANTS.
HE'S GONNA LIKE THIS STUFF
OBVIOUSLY,
UNLESS HE'S, LIKE, CHICKEN.
>> * CLOSE THE DOOR
* ON THE RATS
* THE BIRDS ARE SINGING
* THEIR BLISS
>> MY DUE DATE IS COMING UP
FAST, SO RYAN IS TAKING ME
FOR MY FINAL DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT.
[bell dings]
>> OH, DO I HAVE A FLAT TIRE?
GET OUT THERE AND CHECK.
>> OH, NO, I'M NOT GETTING OUT.
>> NO, PLEASE.
>> RYAN, NO, JUST GO, PLEASE.
WE'RE ALREADY LATE.
JUST GO.
>> I'M NOT GONNA GO
UNTIL YOU LOOK.
>> GOD, YOU'RE SUCH A PAIN.
RYAN, IT'S NOT EASY FOR ME TO,
LIKE, GET IN AND OUT.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT IMPOSSIBLE,
EITHER.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> IF IT'S FLAT WHEN WE GET TO
THE DAMN THING...
>> WHAT?
>> * IT'S NOT TOO LATE *
* FOR A SECOND TAKE
>> I KNOW RYAN IS DREADING
THIS BABY, BUT WOULD IT KILL HIM
TO PRETEND TO BE SUPPORTIVE?
[heartbeat pulses on sonogram]
>> SOUNDS HEALTHY.
OKAY.
SLIDE ALL THE WAY TO THE EDGE.
THAT SHOULD BE GOOD.
PUTTING COLD JELLY
AND A LOT OF PRESSURE, OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> LET YOUR KNEES FALL OPEN.
ALL RIGHT, YOU ARE ABOUT
1 1/2 CENTIMETERS DILATED.
SO THE BABY CAN COME
AT ANY TIME.
>> RYAN, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS ANYWAYS?
>> WELL, TYPICALLY YOU GET
TO 10 CENTIMETERS FOR THE HEAD
TO COME OUT, OKAY?
SO YOU'RE LOOKING AT ABOUT
THIS BIG.
IMAGINE THE SIZE
OF A BABY'S HEAD.
>> IT HAS TO GET THAT BIG?
>> IT HAS TO GET THIS BIG.
>> WHAT IF IT'S NOT THAT BIG?
>> RIGHT NOW, THE CERVIX IS
ABOUT HERE NOW.
AND IT'S GOING TO GET TO BE--
>> ENOUGH FOR A BABY'S HEAD.
>> SO WE DON'T HAVE, LIKE,
THAT MUCH TIME LEFT.
>> [laughs]
>> WELL, YOU STILL HAVE TIME.
I MEAN, SHE'S STARTING.
SHE'S IN THAT EARLY STAGE.
SO I'LL SEE YOU NEXT WEEK
OR SOONER.
>> OKAY.
>> THANK YOU.
EXCITED?
>> PUMPED.
>> LAST WEEK, I WAS AT ZERO.
>> I KNOW.
>> OKAY, CHANGING.
[chime dings]
THERE'S NO GOING BACK NOW.
BENTLEY IS ON HIS WAY,
WHETHER WE'RE READY OR NOT.
>> RYAN'S PARENTS ARE COOL,
BUT I'M STILL GETTING USED
TO THE IDEA OF BEING 16
AND HAVING IN-LAWS.
RYAN'S THE FIRST BOYFRIEND
I EVER HAD.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
RYAN WAS YOUR FIRST BOYFRIEND?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, HE RUINED YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT I CAN'T BELIEVE?
I'M STILL--I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY LET HIM IN THE HOUSE.
>> HE WAS 19 THEN.
>> HE'S DRESSED IN BLACK
ALL THE TIME, AND HE HAS
THOSE THINGS IN HIS EARS.
WHAT DID YOUR DAD HONESTLY SAY?
AND DON'T LIE.
TELL US RIGHT NOW WHAT HE SAID.
HE SAID, "WHO IS THAT PUNK?"
>> NO.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> WELL, NO.
I MEAN, HE ALWAYS HAD ME HOME
WHEN I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HOME.
>> REALLY?
>> HE WASN'T DISRESPECTFUL.
>> YOU'RE FIVE YEARS
OLDER THAN ME.
I MEAN, I WAS 17,
AND YOU WERE 22, SO...
>> BUT WE WEREN'T DOING
THE HOKEYPOKEY.
[laughter]
WE WERE FRIENDS.
>> I THINK WE WERE
MORE THAN FRIENDS.
>> HEY, DIDN'T YOUR MOM
TALK TO YOU ABOUT--
[laughter]
SERIOUSLY.
>> WELL, 'CAUSE--
OH, THAT'S AWKWARD.
>> YEAH, BUT SERIOUSLY.
>> SHE DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH TIME
FROM WHEN THE HOKEYPOKEY STARTED
TO WHEN BENTLEY WAS CREATED.
>> SHE NEEDED TO START SOONER.
[laughter]
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
>> YEAH, WE HAVEN'T TALKED
TO YOU FOREVER.
>> WE AIN'T TALKED TO YOU,
YEAH, FOREVER.
I MEAN, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> YOU ALREADY ASKED
THAT QUESTION, AND HE SAID,
"DON'T GO THERE NOW, MOM."
>> YEAH, YEAH.
IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
[aggressive rock music]
*
>> THERE'S ONLY SO MUCH
PRECAUTION I CAN TAKE NOW.
BUT WHAT CAN I SAY?
WHEN DADDY WANTS TO RIDE QUADS,
WE RIDE QUADS.
[engine roars]
>> YEAH.
YEAH, I THINK SHE'S TIRED
OF BUMPING AROUND.
>> I MEAN, I'VE BEEN DOING IT
FOR NINE MONTHS, BUT I GUESS
WHEN I HIT THE EIGHTH-MONTH
THING, I JUST GOT TO QUIT.
[tires squeal]
[tense string music]
*
>> I MEAN, I WOULD--I WOULD
TAKE HER HOME AND--
>> RIGHT NOW, I JUST WANT THIS.
>> GIVING BIRTH TO MY BABY
WAS THE HARDEST THING
I'VE EVER DONE.
I KICKED AND SCREAMED
THROUGH OVER 30 HOURS
OF NONSTOP PAIN,
UNTIL FINALLY...
[Bentley cries]
>> AWW.
>> HE'S GORGEOUS.
[bell tolls]
[gentle acoustic music]
*
>> * REST YOUR SOUL NOW
* 'CAUSE MUSIC *
* SAVES YOUR LIFE
*
* AND REST YOUR SOUL NOW
* 'CAUSE MUSIC *
* SAVES YOUR LIFE
*
[Bentley cries]
>> HI.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> * 'CAUSE MUSIC *
* SAVES YOUR LIFE
[Bentley screams]
[music box tinkling]
>> MM-HMM.
>> THINGS HAVEN'T BEEN THIS GOOD
SINCE BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT.
I JUST HOPE IT LASTS.
[glass shatters]
[thunder crashes]
[upbeat music]
*
>> RYAN IS SO EXCITED
TO BE A FATHER
THAT HE RAN OUT AND GOT
A HUGE TATTOO OF BENTLEY'S NAME.
IT LOOKS GOOD.
[chime dings]
BUT WAIT.
I'M GETTING AHEAD OF MYSELF.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN LEFT
THE HOSPITAL YET.
[peaceful piano music]
*
>> SO Y'ALL CAN PACK
YOUR STUFF UP AND GO NOW?
>> I GUESS.
>> HOW'S HE DOING?
>> FINE.
HE'S REAL CRANKY IN THE MORNING.
HE GETS ON MY NERVES.
>> SOUNDS LIKE YOU AND YOUR
BOYFRIEND THERE NOW, HUH?
>> WHAT?
[slow guitar music]
*
[electronic beep]
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> COULD YOU TELL THE NURSE
THAT WE'RE READY TO LEAVE?
>> COME ON UP.
>> THANK YOU.
*
[Bentley fussing]
SHH.
YOU DON'T LIKE THIS, DO YOU?
I ALWAYS SAID WE WOULD JUST KNOW
WHAT TO DO WHEN BENTLEY CAME,
BUT NOW I'M NOT SO SURE.
>> I GUESS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT MEANS I GOT TO START
DOING STUFF FOR MYSELF.
>> IS HE ALLOWED TO DRINK
THIS WHOLE THING IF HE WANTS IT?
>> HOW MANY IS IN THAT WHOLE--
ALL OF IT--
HOW MANY MILLILITERS?
>> 40.
>> I WOULDN'T GIVE HIM
MORE THAN 30.
HE'LL GET SICK.
>> IS THIS WHAT YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS GONNA BE LIKE?
>> UH-HUH.
>> IT IS?
IS IT WHAT YOU THOUGHT
IT WAS GONNA BE LIKE?
>> NO, I FIGURED HE'D COME OUT
WALKING AND RIDING.
[lively music]
>> I WAS WORRIED RYAN WOULD
EXPECT BENTLEY TO CHANGE
HIS OWN DIAPERS TOO,
BUT SO FAR, SO GOOD.
OKAY, NOW KEEP IT ON THERE
UNTIL--
>> ARE WE AFRAID WE'RE GONNA
GET PEED ON?
>> UH, YEAH, 'CAUSE, LIKE,
I HAVE ALREADY GOT PEED ON.
>> I'M GONNA STAND BACK.
>> WELL, YOU NEED TO DO THIS.
HERE, YOU HOLD HIS FEET
TOGETHER.
>> OKAY, OKAY, COME HERE.
GIVE ME THAT.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA HURT HIM.
YOU JUST PULL THEM TOGETHER.
YOU GOT TO HOLD THEM THERE,
'CAUSE HE'LL COME OUT
OF YOUR HANDS.
YOU KNOW,
WE PUT IT ON BACKWARDS.
>> MAN...
YOU SURE YOU PUT IT ON
BACKWARDS?
>> YEAH.
[alarm ringing]
IT'S NOT PERFECT,
BUT WE'RE DOING THE BEST WE CAN.
RYAN EVEN SWITCHED
TO THE DAY SHIFT,
SO HE LEAVES
EARLY IN THE MORNING,
AND BENTLEY IS ALL MINE.
[music box plays lullaby]
*
[suspenseful electronic music]
I'M GOING STIR-CRAZY
JUST TAKING CARE OF BENTLEY
WEEK AFTER WEEK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW MUCH
I MISS MY OLD LIFE:
HANGING OUT WITH FRIENDS,
RIDING DIRT BIKES,
AND CHEERLEADING.
BUT THOSE DAYS ARE GONE.
MY HIGH SCHOOL YEARS
ARE OFFICIALLY OVER.
ARE YOU READY?
>> I'M SO READY.
>> MACI DESHANE...
[cheers and applause]
>> THANK YOU.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
BENTLEY.
HE'S RUINING 'EM.
>> HE'S NOT RUINING 'EM.
HE'S UNCOMFORTABLE IN THIS
OLD, STINKY SWEATER.
[rock music]
*
[camera shutter clicks]
>> I'M THRILLED TO SEE
MY FRIENDS, BUT IT'S HARDER
TO KEEP UP WITH THEM
NOW THAT WE HAVE A BABY.
>> THEY ONLY HAVE
THE DIAPER-CHANGE PLACES
IN THE WOMEN'S RESTROOM.
>> OH, DOES THAT MEAN
I GOT TO GO DO IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I'M NOT GOING IN THERE.
>> IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG FOR
RYAN TO FIND A WAY TO MAKE ME
CHANGE BENTLEY'S DIAPER.
THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE
A CHANGING TABLE IN HERE.
ARE YOU JOKING ME?
SERIOUSLY?
WHAT KIND OF RESTAURANT
DOES THAT?
PLEASE DON'T PEE ON ME,
OKAY, BUDDY?
>> I'VE DECIDED TO...
*
>> ARE YOU ALL COMING
TO CHRISTINA'S WITH US?
>> WE CAN'T.
BENTLEY'S BEDTIME.
>> YOU'RE GONNA MISS OUT.
>> STORY OF MY LIFE.
THANKS FOR COMING.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS.
>> BYE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> SEE YOU.
>> BYE, RYAN.
>> BYE.
[Bentley crying]
>> WHILE MY FRIENDS STAY OUT
TO CELEBRATE,
I HAVE TO TAKE BENTLEY HOME.
AND SOMETIMES IT FEELS LIKE
I'M TAKING CARE OF TWO BABIES.
RYAN'S TATTOO IS SWEET,
BUT I HOPE HE REALIZES
THAT BEING A FATHER
IS MORE THAN HAVING YOUR BABY'S
NAME TATTOOED ON YOUR BODY.
I DON'T KNOW IF I WANT
TO SHOW THIS TO YOU.
>> LET ME SEE IT.
>> YOU MIGHT TAKE IT FROM ME.
>> HERE, COME HERE.
>> THIS IS WELL DESERVED.
>> WELL DESERVED?
>> YEAH, I WENT 12 YEARS IN
SCHOOL, AND ONE OF THOSE YEARS,
I WAS PREGNANT.
I EARNED THIS.
$100, $200, $300,
$400, $500, $600,
$700, $800, PLUS $500.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> AND IT'S ALL MINE.
>> I'LL TAKE IT FROM YOU.
>> NO, YOU WON'T.
>> YOU DON'T THINK SO?
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
HIDE IT GOOD, THEN.
>> PUT IT IN BENTLEY'S DIAPER.
YOU NEVER OPEN THOSE.
>> HE NEVER HAD MONEY IN THERE.
>> EVEN WITH CASH INCENTIVE,
I'M WORRIED THAT RYAN WON'T DO
HIS FAIR SHARE.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN CALLED
AN OVERACHIEVER.
SINCE I GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL
EARLY, I ENROLLED IN CHATTANOOGA
STATE AND STARTED COLLEGE.
I KNOW IT WILL BE A LOT
TO JUGGLE, BUT I'M NOT GONNA
LET HAVING A BABY SLOW ME DOWN.
>> ARE WE GONNA ASK YOU
TO DO A LOT?
YES, WE ARE.
THIS ISN'T HIGH SCHOOL.
IF YOU CHOOSE NOT TO DO
THE HOMEWORK, YOUR RED WAGON.
I'M NOT DRAGGING IT AROUND.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHERE
THE BUSINESS OFFICE IS?
EXCUSE ME.
CAN YOU TELL ME
WHERE THE BUSINESS OFFICE IS?
>> WELL, LET ME TELL YOU
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT THE DAY CARE.
WE HAVE--UM, SIX WEEKS TO
TWO YEARS IS $650.
WE HAVE--TWO YEARS IS $550.
AND THREE YEARS AND UP IS $500.
WE DO HAVE A WAITING LIST.
>> $650 A MONTH?
THAT'S MORE THAN MY RENT.
DROP, ONE, TWO.
POP, THREE, FOUR.
AS IF COLLEGE WASN'T ENOUGH,
I'M ALSO MAKING TIME
TO JOIN A DANCE TEAM
WITH MY FRIENDS.
GUESS I SHOULD HAVE GOT IN SHAPE
BEFORE I TRIED THIS.
I JUST HAD A KID SIX WEEKS AGO.
AND TO HELP PAY FOR IT ALL,
I'M STILL WORKING PART-TIME
AT MY DAD'S SHOP.
>> THEY'RE GONNA NEED THAT
PINK COPY.
YOU NEED TO GO AND MAKE
A FOLDER FOR THAT.
>> OKAY, SHOULD I PUT "PAID"
AND STUFF UP HERE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> TO KEEP UP MY HECTIC NEW
SCHEDULE, I HAVE TO RELY
ON A TON OF FREE DAY CARE
FROM MY MOM.
OH, HE'S GETTING SLEEPY.
>> SO YOU DON'T THINK RYAN WILL
COME BY TO PICK HIM UP TONIGHT?
>> I MEAN, DOES HE EVER?
>> WELL, YOU GOT A LOT OF STUFF
GOING ON; HE NEEDS TO--
>> WHY DON'T YOU TEXT HIM?
>> YOU WANT ME TO TEXT HIM?
>> YEAH, HIS MOM--
>> NO, 'CAUSE THEN I'LL BE
THE WITCHY MOTHER-IN-LAW.
>> SO?
>> [laughs]
>> HE'S NOT GONNA LISTEN TO ME.
[train whistle blows]
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OKAY.
RYAN AND I ARE NOT TALKING
MUCH AT ALL.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN MENTIONED ANY
WEDDING PLANS IN OVER A MONTH,
BUT HE STILL MANAGES
TO GET IN QUALITY TIME
WITH HIS FRIENDS.
>> YOU TALK TO THAT
BIG GIRL YET?
[laughter]
HUH?
>> ARE YOU GONNA MARRY HER?
>> PROBABLY DID--SCRATCH.
>> SHE WEIGHS, LIKE, 250, 230.
>> SHE'S GOT A CUTE FACE,
THOUGH.
[laughter]
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE
THE NAGGING WIFE
AND CRAMP RYAN'S STYLE,
BUT TAKING CARE OF BENTLEY
ON MY OWN IS STARTING
TO GET TO ME.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU FIRST.
>> SO AS OF RIGHT NOW,
YOU WAKE UP,
TAKE BENTLEY TO OOLTEWAH,
DRIVE ALL THE WAY
TO CHATT STATE,
GO TO WORK.
>> YEAH, EXCEPT FOR ON MONDAYS
AND THURSDAYS, WHEN I GO
FROM WORK TO DANCE
AND THEN GO PICK UP BENTLEY.
>> WAIT, FOR WHAT?
>> BUT RYAN COULD KEEP BENTLEY
WHILE MACI WAS AT DANCE.
>> HE SEES BENTLEY
APPROXIMATELY...
>> LIKE, WHEN DOES HE
LAY EYES ON BENTLEY?
>> HMM.
UM...
ABOUT 9:30 OR 10:00, I'D SAY.
>> PROBABLY.
>> GOOD.
>> * SAID YOU'D NEVER *
* GIVE UP ON ME
* BUT YOU COULD HAVE
* SHOWED YOUR FAITH
>> I HAVE A TON OF HOMEWORK,
AND I'VE HAD BENTLEY WITH ME
ALL AFTERNOON.
SO I'M REALLY HOPING
RYAN WILL TAKE HIS TURN TONIGHT.
>> GONNA CHANGE HIS DIAPER?
>> BUT IT'S ALWAYS MY TURN.
>> IT'S YOUR TURN.
>> PLEASE LET ME STUDY.
THANKS.
MACI, THAT'S YOURS.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
>> CAN YOU JUST HOLD HIM TILL
I GET DONE WITH MY HOMEWORK?
HURRY.
>> JUST GO CHANGE HIM, MACI.
>> GUESS I'LL GO CHANGE
HIS DIAPER.
>> IT'S YOUR TURN.
>> OH, YEAH.
I DO IT 50 TIMES.
YOU DO IT ONCE, RIGHT?
>> IT'S STILL YOUR TURN.
>> FOR THE LOVE OF GOD,
I GOT TO FINISH MY HOMEWORK
SO I CAN GO TO SLEEP.
>> HE'S NOT TIRED, THOUGH.
>> RYAN, SERIOUSLY.
>> HE'S NOT.
>> HERE.
>> GOOD NIGHT.
[Bentley crying]
>> [coughs]
YOU KNOW, IF YOU PICK HIM UP...
>> I'VE TRIED.
>> AND JUST HOLD HIM.
YOU DIDN'T TRY HARD ENOUGH.
GOSH.
>> SHUT UP.
>> HERE, YOU CAN FEED HIM.
>> NO, YOU GET HIM.
>> BENTLEY, LAY HERE AND CRY
REALLY LOUD.
[Bentley bawls]
[muted sobbing]
>> [bleep], MACI, [bleep] DAMN.
>> I'M MAKING A BOTTLE.
CALM DOWN, SERIOUSLY.
HOLD HIM, AND HE WILL STOP
CRYING.
>> GO MAKE THE BOTTLE, PLEASE.
QUIT MOVING YOUR MOUTH
AND GO MAKE IT.
>> I'M GONNA LEAVE HIM HERE
IF YOU SAY ONE MORE THING.
>> NO, I'LL LEAVE, PERIOD.
>> THEN LEAVE!
GOD.
COME ON, LET'S GO EAT.
GET AWAY FROM YOUR MEAN OLD DAD.
[sighs]
GOODNESS.
[dramatic music]
*
>> RYAN AND I HAVE NOT
BEEN GETTING ALONG,
BUT WE'RE ON OUR WAY
TO HIS PARENTS' HOUSE,
SO WE'LL HAVE TO PUT ON
A HAPPY FACE.
>> HEY.
HEY, WHAT IS THIS?
MOM?
>> HUH?
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> IT'S, LIKE, SAUSAGE
AND CREAM CHEESE AND STUFFING.
>> WOW, YOU SOUND BAD, BABY.
>> I FEEL LIKE CRAP.
>> HEY, HAVE YOU GUYS THOUGHT
ANY MORE ABOUT THE DATE?
>> NOT YET.
[chime dings]
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE PLANNING
OUR WEDDING, BUT I CAN'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT MARRYING RYAN
IF HE NEVER WANTS TO SPEND TIME
WITH ME AND BENTLEY.
>> SOMETIMES I THINK YOU'RE
TRYING TO RUN AWAY FROM IT ALL.
HOW ARE YOUR FRIENDS
WITH IT--ALL OF THIS?
YOU KNOW, ARE THEY, LIKE,
YOU KNOW, "LET'S GO OUT,
COME ON"?
>> [mumbles] I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU TELL THEM?
>> I GO OUT WITH THEM SOMETIMES.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT IT?
DOES IT UPSET YOU?
>> YEAH, BUT--
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY?
>> NOTHING.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I JUST FIGURED IF THAT'S WHAT
HE WANTS TO DO INSTEAD OF
BE WITH ME OR BENTLEY, THEN...
>> OH-HO, MAN.
>> HE CAN DO THAT.
>> I KIND OF FEEL THAT
YOU AND BENTLEY NEED
A LITTLE MORE TIME TOGETHER.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT,
IT'S GONNA BE OCTOBER,
AND HE'S GONNA BE ONE.
AND I TOLD YOU, YOU CAN'T--
YOU KNOW, WHEN IT'S GONE,
IT'S GONE FOREVER.
YOU CAN'T GO BACK.
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS
NOT ONE THING,
NOT--NOT HIM CRAWLING,
TALKING, NOTHING.
NOTHING.
[microwave beeping]
[rustling]
>> [groans]
>> YOU'RE GOING BOWLING?
WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME
I'M GOING?
WHAT--WHAT YOU SAY GOES, HUH?
>> RYAN AND I AREN'T EVEN TRYING
TO MAKE IT WORK ANYMORE.
>> MACI, ARE YOU COOKING
SOMETHING?
>> WHAT?
>> WAFFLES?
>> NO.
WELL, YEAH, I MADE THAT
FOR YOU IF YOU WANTED THEM.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE I CAN'T DO
ANYTHING RIGHT SOMETIMES.
AND THINGS AT OUR APARTMENT
HAVE GONE DOWNHILL.
I'M LEAVING BENTLEY WITH MY MOM
SO I CAN GET ADVICE
FROM MY FRIENDS.
BUT ALL THEY CAN THINK ABOUT IS
NEXT WEEK'S DANCE COMPETITION.
>> I'M SO EXCITED.
IT'S YOUR FIRST COMPETITION.
>> MAYBE.
>> MAYBE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS TALKING TO MY MOM
ABOUT NOT DOING IT ANYMORE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY?
>> I HAVE TO PAY FOR IT
ALL BY MYSELF.
MY MOM OR DAD, LIKE,
THEY'RE NOT HELPING ME
PAY FOR IT.
I WANT TO DO IT,
BUT I FEEL LIKE I'M NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO ENJOY IT,
BECAUSE THE WHOLE TIME I'M
DOING IT, I'M, LIKE--
>> JUST STRESSED OUT.
>> "WHERE'S BENTLEY?
WHAT TIME DO I HAVE TO
PICK HIM UP?"
>> YEAH, WHO'S GONNA WATCH--
>> IT SUCKS JUST BECAUSE,
LIKE, IT WAS SOMETHING FUN
THAT YOU COULD DO, LIKE,
JUST FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THEN IT TURNS OUT
YOU CAN'T EVEN DO THAT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHERE'S, LIKE--
OH, HE'S AT WORK.
RYAN'S AT WORK, LIKE,
WHEN YOU'RE AT WORK AND SCHOOL
AND DANCE AND EVERYTHING.
>> LIKE, I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
I CAN DROP BENTLEY OFF
IN THE MORNING.
THEN I LEAVE AND GO TO SCHOOL.
WHEN I GET OUT OF SCHOOL,
BEFORE I GO TO WORK EVERY SINGLE
DAY, I GO AND SEE BENTLEY
FOR, LIKE, 30 MINUTES.
RYAN CAN GO TO WORK ALL DAY
LONG, THEN GO WORK OUT AND THEN
GO EAT WITH HIS FRIENDS
AFTER HE WORKS OUT
AND THEN COME HOME,
AND IT'S 10:00,
AND HE'S READY TO GO TO SLEEP,
AND I'M, LIKE,
"OH, YOU HAVE A SON
THAT HASN'T SEEN YOU ALL DAY."
>> YEAH.
I JUST DON'T THINK HE WAS, LIKE,
READY TO HAVE A KID YET.
>> AND I WASN'T READY EITHER,
BUT I GREW UP BECAUSE I HAD TO.
[door clicks open]
HELLO.
>> HEY.
>> THOUGHT YOU HAD
DANCE PRACTICE TODAY.
>> I HAVE NEWS.
I QUIT THE DANCE TEAM.
>> OH, THAT SUCKS.
WHY?
>> I HAVE MORE PRIORITIES
THAT ARE MORE IMPORTANT
THAN DANCE, LIKE, FOR ONE,
TAKING CARE OF BENTLEY
ON MONDAYS AND THURSDAY NIGHTS
SO THAT MY MOM DOESN'T HAVE HIM
FOR AN ENTIRE DAY.
AND HE'S NOT MY MOM'S CHILD.
HE'S MY CHILD.
NUMBER TWO, IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
I COULD SPEND THAT MONEY
ON SOMETHING ELSE
THAT IS MORE IMPORTANT.
I MEAN, DON'T YOU THINK
IT MAKES SENSE?
>> I GUESS SO.
NOW YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO.
>> ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I HAVE PLENTY TO DO,
UNLIKE RYAN, WHO HAS TIME
TO CALL UP HIS FRIENDS
AND PLAN ANOTHER NIGHT OUT.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO EAT
AND SING KARAOKE WITH US?
ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT?
>> I'M GOING TO EAT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO TONIGHT?
>> SIT AT HOME WITH BENTLEY.
WELL?
>> "WELL" WHAT?
>> NOTHING.
>> * HMM
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I SHOULD,
LIKE, START TELLING HIM
HE NEEDS TO STAY HOME.
I FEEL LIKE I WANT
TO MAKE HIM HAPPY, SO IF HE
WANTS TO BE HAPPY GOING OUT,
THEN I'LL TAKE THE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR BOTH OF US
JUST SO HE DOESN'T HAVE TO.
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, DO YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA IF
I CAME HOME FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
[Bentley fussing]
[crying]
*
>> * IT'S LATE *
* BUT I DON'T WANT TO SLEEP *
[Bentley coos]
>> RYAN AND I ARE BARELY
SPEAKING SINCE OUR FIGHT.
[chime dings]
HE PICKED UP THE ENGAGEMENT RING
I LEFT ON THE COFFEE TABLE,
AND HE HASN'T MENTIONED IT
SINCE.
>> [grunts]
>> SIX.
SIX.
LET'S SEE IF YOUR--
MOVES WHEN YOU DO THAT.
OH, WOW, THAT'S FLYING, RYAN.
YOU GUYS DOING OKAY?
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE REALLY NOT, SERIOUSLY?
>> WOW.
ARE YOU--ARE YOU STAYING THERE
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE OF BENTLEY?
>> UH, YEAH. YEAH.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON WHY.
>> [scoffs]
I KNOW YOU STILL CARE ABOUT HER.
THAT'S WHY YOU--
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE UPSET.
IF YOU DIDN'T CARE,
YOU WOULDN'T BE UPSET, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU WANT TO WORK IT OUT?
>> YEAH, BUT, I MEAN...
>> OKAY.
WELL, THEN YOU JUST CAN'T
GIVE UP, RYAN EDWARDS.
[grunts]
OH, YOU BETTER HELP ME.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BREAK UP
WITH RYAN, BUT I NEED TO KNOW
THAT HE REALLY WANTS TO BE HERE.
>> I-I'M--I'M DONE ARGUING.
I MEAN, IT'S--
IT'S WEARING ME OUT.
IT'S WEARING ME OUT
COMING HOME EVERY DAY
AND KNOWING THAT IT'S GONNA
SUCK AS BAD AS IT DOES AT WORK
WHEN I COME HOME.
I KNOW IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY,
BUT I MEAN, STILL, I SHOULD
AT LEAST WANT TO COME HOME.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES I CAN'T
EVEN ASK YOU A QUESTION
WITHOUT YOU GETTING MAD.
[Bentley cries]
>> IT'S--I, LIKE, RESENT YOU
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE I TAKE ON
MORE RESPONSIBILITY THAN YOU DO.
YOU HATE THIS LIFE.
YOU HATE IT.
THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> I MEAN, WHAT RESPONSIBILITY
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE
THAT I DON'T?
>> RYAN, HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO BEG YOU
ON THE WEEKENDS OR WHENEVER
YOU'RE FREE TO DO--
TO FEED BENTLEY?
YOU DON'T OFFER.
I HAVE TO ASK YOU.
I ENJOY THIS RESPONSIBILITY,
AND TO YOU, IT'S A HASSLE.
>> MACI, THE ONLY THING
THAT MAKES IT LOOK LIKE
A HASSLE IS YOU.
I DON'T ENJOY BEING HERE
WITH YOU.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
WHEN I'M WITH HIM BY MYSELF,
I'M FINE.
>> I MEAN, WERE YOU NEVER HAPPY?
>> I WAS HAPPY BEFORE.
>> OKAY, WHEN?
>> I DON'T--I DON'T REMEMBER
HOW LONG AGO.
IT WAS A WHILE AGO.
>> WELL, IT DIDN'T CHANGE
UNTIL I GOT PREGNANT.
I MEAN, I DON'T THINK IF WE
WERE IN THIS SITUATION
WE WOULD BE THIS UNHAPPY
RIGHT NOW.
>> NO, IF WE DIDN'T HAVE A KID,
WE WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
>> OKAY, WELL, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO STAY HERE BECAUSE YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU HAVE TO.
>> YEAH, I'M TRYING
BECAUSE WE HAVE A KID.
THAT'S WHY I TRY.
>> WELL, IF WE'VE ONLY BEEN
TRYING BECAUSE OF HIM,
IT'S TIME TO GIVE IT UP.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE GOOD FOR HIM
IF WE'RE TOGETHER
AND WE HATE EACH OTHER.
THAT DOESN'T SHOW HIM
ANYTHING GOOD.
SO WHAT?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
[solemn music]
*
[tattoo machine buzzes]
>> GETTING PREGNANT AT 16
MADE MY--MINE AND RYAN'S
RELATIONSHIP VERY DIFFICULT.
SINCE I GOT PREGNANT AT 16,
IT'S MADE A LOT OF THINGS
VERY, VERY, VERY HARD.
FOR BENTLEY'S SAKE,
WE BOTH WANT TO WORK THIS OUT
AND DO THE BEST WE CAN FOR HIM.
WE HAVE TO MAKE IT WORK
UNTIL EITHER IT DOES WORK OUT
LIKE WE HOPE
OR WE JUST REALIZE THAT IT--WE--
WE JUST DON'T BELONG TOGETHER.
>> I'M HUNGRY NOW.
>> BE PATIENT, BOY.
>> CAN WE ORDER PIZZA?
>> NO.
>> PLEASE?
>> RYAN.
>> I WANT PIZZA.
>> YOU CAN ORDER PIZZA.
I'M MAKING ME FOOD.
>> THAT IS FOOD.
>> I MEAN, HEALTHY FOOD.
HEY.
OH.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT WAS SO MEAN, BENTLEY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THAT WASN'T EVEN COOL.
WHO GETS UP WITH YOU
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
>> YEAH, HE SAY,
"I KNOW WHO LOVES ME."
>> HEY.
>> MM, YOU WERE THINKING
ABOUT IT.
>> IT'S BEEN A LOT HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE,
STAYING WITH HIM.
AND I'M SURE HE THINKS
THE SAME THING.
BUT WE'RE GONNA SEE
HOW THINGS GO,
AND MAYBE THIS SUMMER,
WE'LL HAVE OUR BEACH WEDDING
THAT WE WANT, AND MAYBE NOT.
OKAY, ARE YOU READY?
ARE YOU READY?
ONE, TWO, FREE!
>> LOOK, BENTLEY.
>> LOOK AT IT.
HERE.
>> OH, THEY DON'T REACH.
>> VROOM, VROOM.
[chime dings]
WHO KNOWS?
TODAY IT'S GOOD.
TOMORROW IT MIGHT FALL APART
AGAIN.
WE'RE JUST WORKING ON IT,
AND WE'LL SEE WHAT THE FUTURE
HAS IN STORE FOR US.
>> BEAT THE LYNX TONIGHT!
>> I AM PREGNANT.
YEAH, I JUST WANT THE OTHER
GIRLS TO RESPECT HOW I AM
DEALING WITH THIS SITUATION.
>> THE MOST LOVING THING
IS TO PUT THE CHILD
UP FOR ADOPTION.
>> I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE
THAT HARD.
I THINK MY WATER JUST BROKE!
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH.
>> SIX, SEVEN.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
HAVING A BEAUTIFUL SITUATION
RIGHT NOW, HUH, FARRAH?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I HAVE TO DEAL
WITH YOU--YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH!
[upbeat piano music]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA *
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
* I'M WEAK, BUT *
* I'M STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE... *