>> HEY, I'M KAYLA.
I'M 17, AND I LIVE
IN CENTRE, ALABAMA,
A TINY TOWN IN THE HEART
OF THE DEEP SOUTH.
ALL MY LIFE, I'VE BEEN
PRETTY SPOILED BY MY PARENTS,
BUT I'M FULL OF SOUTHERN CHARM,
WHICH COMES IN HANDY WHEN
I COMPETE IN BEAUTY PAGEANTS.
DON'T GET ME WRONG;
JUST BECAUSE I'M GIRLY
DOESN'T MEAN I DON'T KNOW HOW
TO GET MY HANDS DIRTY.
I RIDE HORSES AND GO HUNTING
WITH MY BOYFRIEND, J.R.,
ALL THE TIME.
OH, GOOD JOB.
YOU WOULD HAVE KILLED HIM.
J.R.'S ALREADY GRADUATED
HIGH SCHOOL.
WE'VE ONLY BEEN TOGETHER
FOR SIX MONTHS,
BUT I DEFINITELY THINK
HE'S THE ONE.
AND ONE DAY, HE MIGHT BE
LUCKY ENOUGH TO WALK ME
DOWN THE AISLE.
BUT FOR NOW, I'M GOING
TO ENJOY MY SENIOR YEAR
WITH MY FRIENDS,
AND I'M REALLY EXCITED
FOR PROM AND SPRING BREAK.
BUT MY DAYS OF BEING
A CAREFREE SOUTHERN BELLE
MIGHT BE NUMBERED,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
I ALWAYS GREW UP THINKING
I HAD TO BE THE PERFECT
PAGEANT QUEEN WITH BRAINS,
BEAUTY, AND GOOD VALUES.
SO WHEN I FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT,
I WAS REALLY SCARED
EVERYONE WOULD JUDGE ME.
WHEN I FIRST FOUND OUT,
I WAS SO SCARED.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT MY PARENTS WOULD THINK.
>> WERE YOU SCARED PEOPLE WERE
GOING TO BE, LIKE, CALLING YOU
"TRASHY" AND ALL THAT
BEHIND YOUR BACK?
>> I MEAN, PEOPLE PUT LABELS
ON EVERYTHING.
>> HOW DID YOU TELL J.R.?
>> I PULLED UP IN HIS DRIVEWAY
AND WAS, LIKE, BLOWING
ON THE HORN.
AND HE OPENED THE DOOR,
AND I HELD UP THE TEST.
AND HE HAD THE LOOK
SOMEBODY JUST SLAPPED HIM
IN THE FACE.
HE WAS LIKE--
ADVICE TO YOU TWO: ALWAYS WEAR
A RAINCOAT.
[laughter]
WAS SHE, LIKE, MAD?
>> WELL, I MEAN,
I KNOW SHE'S UPSET,
AND SHE'S SCARED FOR ME
'CAUSE OF SCHOOL AND EVERYTHING.
BUT SHE'S TAKEN IT REALLY WELL.
>> I KNOW.
LIKE, THEY'VE BEEN REALLY
SUPPORTIVE, AND SO HAVE
J.R.'S PARENTS.
LIKE, I WAS SCARED FOR THEM
TO KNOW, 'CAUSE I FIGURED
THEY'D THINK I WAS, LIKE,
A SKANK OR SOMETHING.
J.R. WAS RAISED
REALLY TRADITIONALLY,
AND NOW THAT I'M SHOWING,
I KNOW HE FEELS UNCOMFORTABLE
BEING OUT IN PUBLIC
WITH ME SO PREGNANT
AND US NOT MARRIED.
>> UM, YEAH, THEY SHOULD KNOW.
I MEAN...
IT'S NOT EXACTLY INVISIBLE.
I WONDER
WHAT EVERYBODY'S THINKING.
>> THERE'S NO HIDING IT ANYMORE.
IT'S REALLY SURPRISED ME,
HOW SUPPORTIVE AND LOVING
MY PARENTS HAVE BEEN.
BUT DEEP DOWN, I KNOW
IT'S BEEN DIFFICULT FOR THEM.
I MEAN, I WAS SCARED
TO TELL YOU, BECAUSE I FIGURED,
YOU KNOW, YOU'D BE DISAPPOINTED
IN ME.
AND I DECIDED TO TELL MOM FIRST,
BECAUSE--I DON'T KNOW.
I FIGURED IT'D BE EASIER.
>> I STAYED STRONG
IN FRONT OF YOU.
AND THEN, UM...
BUT WHENEVER YOU WERE GONE,
I WOULD CRY.
AND DADDY KEPT ASKING ME
WHAT WAS WRONG, AND I TOLD HIM
THAT--I JUST KEPT TELLING HIM
I HAD PROBLEMS AT WORK.
HE'S LIKE, "WHAT IS WRONG
WITH YOU?
AND WHAT IS GOING ON?"
AND I SAID, "WELL, IT'S KAYLA."
AND I DIDN'T HAVE TO TELL HIM;
HE GUESSED.
HE SAID, "SHE'S PREGNANT."
AND I SAID, "YEAH."
>> WELL, THE TIMING IS OFF
ON IT.
I MEAN, IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
SEVERAL YEARS ON DOWN THE ROAD.
I WAS IN SHOCK TO START WITH.
AND WHEN I REALLY FOUND OUT
IT'S SO, I KIND OF WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT WE WERE GOING TO DO
ABOUT YOUR SCHOOLING,
'CAUSE WE'D ALREADY PLANNED
YOUR SCHOOL AND COLLEGE.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO WORK
AROUND IT.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS WORRIED
ABOUT, IS, I DIDN'T WANT Y'ALL
TO BE UPSET, AND I DIDN'T WANT
Y'ALL TO THINK LESS OF ME.
>> WELL, WE NEVER THOUGHT LESS
OF YOU, BECAUSE YOU'RE
OUR DAUGHTER, AND WE KNOW
THAT YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON
AND THAT YOU HAVE A GOOD HEART.
AND THIS DOESN'T MAKE YOU
ANY LESS OF A PERSON, KAYLA.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND I WAS NEVER DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU.
THE HURT THAT I FELT
WAS BECAUSE OF ALL THE THINGS
THAT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
GO THROUGH FROM HERE ON OUT.
IT'S REALLY GOING TO BE HARD
ON YOU.
>> I WAS GOING TO GO AWAY
TO COLLEGE
AND STUDY TO BE A NURSE,
BUT NOW THAT ISN'T GOING
TO HAPPEN.
J.R. WANTS US TO MOVE IN
TOGETHER ONCE THE BABY'S BORN,
BUT RIGHT NOW, HE LIVES
WITH HIS PARENTS
AND DOESN'T MAKE ENOUGH MONEY
AT HIS MECHANIC JOB.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
AND EVEN THOUGH I KNOW
HE'S THE ONE FOR ME,
IT'S HARD IMAGINING
MOVING AWAY FROM MY MOM.
>> GET YOU DIRTY.
>> [laughs]
>> LOVE YOU.
>> AND NOW THAT WE FOUND OUT
WE'RE HAVING A BABY BOY,
WE HAVE TO MAKE A PLAN.
SO I RECKON YOU'RE EXCITED
ABOUT HAVING A LITTLE BOY.
>> I'M REALLY THRILLED
ABOUT HAVING A BOY
TO CARRY ON THE FAMILY NAME.
>> I REALLY THOUGHT
HE WAS GOING TO BE A GIRL.
>> I KNOWED HE WASN'T GOING
TO BE A LITTLE GIRL.
I TOLD YOU THE WHOLE TIME
HE WAS GOING TO BE
A LITTLE BOY.
>> YOU DIDN'T KNOW.
>> YEAH, I KNEW.
A DADDY'S INSTINCT.
I KNEW IT.
>> SO IS RYLAN
THE OFFICIAL NAME?
>> I RECKON SO.
>> I LIKE RYLAN JASON
THE BEST, SO--
>> ME TOO.
>> IT SOUNDS BETTER
THAN ANY OTHER NAMES.
>> I JUST HOPE IT DON'T ACT
ANYTHING LIKE YOU.
MAYBE HE'LL LOOK LIKE YOU
AND ACT LIKE ME,
SO HE'LL BE SWEET.
>> DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF, NOW.
>> ME AND DADDY WAS TALKING
ABOUT GETTING HIM ON HORSES
AND STUFF.
>> SO DOES THAT MEAN
YOU'RE SCARED?
>> IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT
TO CALL IT.
>> I HOPE J.R. ISN'T ALWAYS
THIS STUBBORN.
AND EVEN THOUGH I DON'T WANT
THINGS TO MOVE TOO FAST,
TODAY WE'RE GOING TO LOOK
AT A HOUSE NEARBY
THAT HIS PARENTS OWN.
WE CAN MOVE INTO IT
IF WE GET MARRIED.
>> THIS WAS MY GRANDMOTHER
AND GRANDDADDY'S.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO USE IT.
>> THE LIVING ROOM LOOKS GOOD
TO ME.
>> IT NEEDS A LITTLE WORK.
KITCHEN AND DINING ROOM.
IT'S GOT BRAND-NEW CABINETS
AND APPLIANCES IN IT, SO WE
DON'T HAVE TO EVEN BUY THEM.
>> IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT IT'S GETTING CLOSER
TO TIME FOR US TO MOVE OUT
ON OUR OWN AND STUFF.
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT IT TOO,
ALL THOSE BILLS
AND NOT LIVING AT HOME.
>> I MEAN, I GUESS
IT WILL BE DIFFERENT
ONCE IT'S JUST ME AND YOU
AND RYLAN LIVING HERE
BY OURSELVES.
>> YEAH.
I THOUGHT GETTING PREGNANT
IN HIGH SCHOOL WAS SCARY,
BUT TAKING ON THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF A HOUSEHOLD AND A BABY
IS TERRIFYING.
>> RIGHT NOW, MY PLANS
TO GO AWAY TO COLLEGE
ARE ON HOLD, BUT I PLAN
TO GRADUATE HIGH SCHOOL
AND GO TO A LOCAL COLLEGE.
THERE'S ALWAYS BEEN
PREGNANT GIRLS AT MY SCHOOL,
BUT I NEVER IMAGINED
I WOULD BE ONE OF THEM.
BEING A PREGNANT TEENAGER
DEFINITELY ISN'T IN ANY
PAGEANT HANDBOOK.
>> LOOK WHAT CAME IN THE MAIL,
MATERNITY PANTS.
>> OH, I'M SO SCARED.
OH, THEY SEEM SO BIG.
>> THEY LOOK A LITTLE DIFFERENT
THAN THOSE SIZE FOURS, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO TRY THEM ON
FOR ME?
I WANT TO SEE
WHAT THEY LOOK LIKE ON YOU.
>> [laughs]
>> NOW, THOSE ARE A LITTLE BIG,
AREN'T THEY?
>> NO.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
THOSE, YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO WEAR FOR A WHILE.
SO ARE YOU, LIKE, "I HOPE
I NEVER WEAR THESE"?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE THINKING?
>> YEAH.
IS MY LEGS REALLY GOING TO BE
THAT BIG?
LIKE, ARE THEY REALLY GOING
TO JUST BE--
>> I MEAN, YOU'RE GOING
TO GAIN WEIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET
A LOT BIGGER
THAN WHAT YOU ARE RIGHT NOW.
>> I WAS HOPING I WAS JUST GOING
TO GAIN BELLY, NOT GAIN
ALL THAT.
>> [laughs]
>> I HOPE RYLAN DOESN'T
TAKE AFTER J.R. AND NOT LIKE
HORSES, BECAUSE I LOVE RIDING,
AND I WANT TO BE ABLE TO DO IT
WITH MY SON.
>> SO HAVE YOU TALKED
TO THE DOCTOR ABOUT HOW MUCH
LONGER YOU'LL BE ABLE TO RIDE?
>> SHE DIDN'T REALLY SAY.
SHE JUST SAID SHE RODE
UP TO--SHE WAS, LIKE, 38 WEEKS.
SO IT SHOULDN'T BE ANY PROBLEM
JUST AS LONG AS I DON'T TROT
OR RUN.
>> WELL, MAKE SURE.
>> WE PROBABLY WON'T GET
TO RIDE MUCH
AFTER RYLAN GETS HERE.
>> YOU CAN RIDE SOME.
IT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH
WITH GOING TO SCHOOL
AND STUFF, BUT I THINK
WE CAN RIDE.
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO MAKE
SOME TIME.
>> I HOPE RYLAN DON'T
TAKE AFTER J.R. AND NOT LIKE
HORSES.
>> OH, YOU'LL GET J.R. RIDING.
IT JUST TAKES SOME TIME.
>> I HOPE.
THE WEEKS ARE GOING BY
FASTER AND FASTER, AND I'M
ALREADY SIX MONTHS PREGNANT.
>> OKAY.
>> HE'S LIKE, "I JUST WANT
TO BE LEFT ALONE."
>> HE'S GOT THE SWEETEST
LITTLE PUG NOSE
AND THAT LITTLE TOP BIT
THAT JUST POKES OUT.
I THINK HE'S TRYING TO SUCK
HIS FINGER OR SOMETHING.
LOOK.
>> BUT EVEN THOUGH OUR PARENTS
HAVE ACCEPTED WE'RE HAVING
A BABY, WE'RE GOING TO NEED
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO
WHEN HE GETS HERE.
>> KAYLA, I FEEL LIKE
YOU HAVE HAD PART OF
YOUR CHILDHOOD PRETTY MUCH
TAKEN AWAY FROM YOU.
I JUST HOPE THAT YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY HARD FEELINGS TOWARD J.R.
ABOUT, YOU KNOW, YOUR PREGNANCY
AND MISSING OUT ON A LOT
OF YOUR SENIOR YEAR,
BECAUSE IT'S A SPECIAL TIME
FOR YOU, AND J.R. GOT
TO EXPERIENCE ALL THAT.
>> I MEAN, IN EVERY SITUATION,
I TRY TO, YOU KNOW,
MAKE THE BEST OUT OF IT.
>> I STILL FEEL GUILTY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I THINK WHAT WE HAVE
IS MORE SPECIAL
THAN A LOT OF THINGS
THAT YOU CAN DO
IN YOUR SENIOR YEAR.
YOU CAN'T TURN BACK TIME.
>> SO IF Y'ALL DON'T
GET MARRIED BEFORE THE BABY
COMES, WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
BECAUSE I FEEL REAL STRONG
ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
NOT MOVING IN TOGETHER
UNTIL YOU'RE MARRIED,
AND I KNOW YOUR DAD, J.R.,
FEELS THE SAME WAY.
>> YOU KNOW, I SORT OF HATE IT
THAT HE'S GOING TO BE BORN
AND WE'RE NOT MARRIED.
BUT WHEN THAT BABY GETS HERE,
I'M NOT SPENDING A NIGHT
AWAY FROM HIM.
>> IT JUST MAKES ME FEEL LIKE
THAT'S TAKING THE GIFT
OF MARRIAGE AWAY
WHEN YOU'RE, YOU KNOW,
ALREADY TOGETHER AT NIGHT.
AND I DON'T BLAME YOU ONE BIT,
BUT THAT'S JUST MY FEELINGS
ABOUT IT.
>> I ALREADY LOVE THIS CHILD
MORE THAN ANYTHING
IN THIS WORLD, AND I WANT
TO ALWAYS BE THERE FOR IT
AND DO WHAT'S BEST FOR IT.
>> YOUR MOM WAS KIND OF WORRIED
ABOUT US STAYING TOGETHER
AFTER THE BABY'S BORN
AND US NOT BEING MARRIED.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, SHE KNOWS THAT I'M NOT
GOING TO SPEND A NIGHT AWAY
FROM MY BABY.
SO, I MEAN, SHE'S JUST
CONCERNED, LIKE ANY MOTHER IS.
I'M SURE YOUR MOM HAS
THE SAME FEELINGS.
I MEAN, I STILL WANT
TO GET MARRIED, BUT, YOU KNOW,
THAT STILL JUST DEPENDS
ON HOW EVERYTHING ELSE
WORKS OUT.
>> J.R. REALLY WANTS ME, HIM,
AND RYLAN ALL UNDER
THE SAME ROOF, BUT I'M NOT SURE
I'M READY FOR THAT.
>> EVEN THOUGH I HAVE A TON
ON MY PLATE, I'M TRYING MY BEST
TO DO EVERYTHING I DID
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
INCLUDING MY PAGEANTS.
UM, HEY.
I WAS WANTING TO KNOW
ABOUT THE PAGEANT, WHERE IT SAYS
THE CONTESTANTS CANNOT HAVE
ANY CHILDREN.
I HAD THOUGHT ABOUT MAYBE
SIGNING UP NEXT YEAR,
BUT I WAS WANTING TO KNOW
WHY THAT WAS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OKAY, WELL, I'M SORRY.
>> BYE.
>> BEING A TEEN MOM MAY MEAN
I HAVE TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO SOME THINGS, BUT I'M NOT
GOING TO MISS OUT ON GRADUATION,
SO MY MOM AND J.R.'S MOM
ARE HELPING ME FIGURE OUT
HOW I CAN FINISH SCHOOL.
>> HOPEFULLY, KAYLA WILL ONLY
HAVE TO MISS, WHAT,
TWO WEEKS, MAYBE, OF SCHOOL?
>> WE'RE HOPING.
I'M GOING TO TAKE OFF
FROM WORK THE FIRST WEEK
AND STAY HOME WITH KAYLA
TILL SHE GETS FEELING
A LITTLE BIT MORE COMFORTABLE.
>> MY SISTER, JENNIFER,
SAYS SHE WOULD LOVE TO KEEP HIM
SOME OF HER DAYS OFF.
>> THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
>> AND I CAN PROBABLY TAKE
A WEEK OF MY VACATION.
SO I DON'T THINK IT'S GOING
TO BE THAT BAD OF AN ISSUE.
OF COURSE, I HOPE
THE POSTPARTUM DEPRESSION--
>> MOM WAS TELLING ME
ABOUT THAT, AND I'VE NEVER
HEARD ABOUT IT,
AND IT SOUNDS SCARY.
SHE WAS TELLING ME, LIKE,
SOME MOMS GO CRAZY AND STUFF.
LIKE, THEY CAN'T STAND
TO HEAR THEM CRY
AND ALL THIS KIND OF STUFF.
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD,
THAT'S SCARY.
HOW CAN ANYBODY FEEL LIKE THAT?"
>> IT'S AN UNCONTROLLABLE
FEELING.
WITH MY DEPRESSION WAS--
MY MOTHER, EVERY TIME
SHE WOULD LEAVE, I WOULD CRY.
SO I'D CALL HER AT 10:00
AT NIGHT, YOU KNOW,
AND JUST BEG HER TO PLEASE COME
AND SLEEP ON THE SOFA.
[laughter]
SO FOR ABOUT THE FIRST
TWO WEEKS, SHE PRETTY MUCH
LIVED WITH US.
>> I'LL PROBABLY BE LIKE PAM.
I'LL PROBABLY CRY EVERY TIME
YOU LEAVE.
[laughter]
>> YOU CRY
EVERY TIME I LEAVE NOW.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[laughter]
>> MY MOM'S SO SUPPORTIVE.
I CAN'T IMAGINE NOT LIVING
UNDER THE SAME ROOF AS HER
ONCE I HAVE A BABY.
I'M SURE J.R. WILL UNDERSTAND,
ESPECIALLY SINCE HE'S GOT
A GIRLFRIEND WHO GOES HUNTING
WITH HIM.
>> HOW'S YOUR OUTFIT WORKING
FOR YOU?
>> IT'S A LITTLE SNUG HERE.
OH, MY GOSH.
>> NEED SOME HELP?
>> I CAN'T SUCK IN.
OOH.
[laughs]
MY BELLY GETS IN THE WAY
OF MY KNEES.
>> THERE YOU GO.
KEEP SWINGING.
TWIST.
>> OKAY, I'M GOOD.
[gunshot]
OKAY.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT
BRINGING HIM HUNTING WITH ME.
>> WHEN ARE YOU GOING
TO BUY HIM HIS FIRST GUN?
>> I WOULD SORT OF LIKE
TO GET HIM ONE
BEFORE HE'S BORN.
>> WHEN HE'S BORN?
>> YEAH, I MAY WAIT.
>> I WANT HIM TO LIKE TO HUNT
AND EVERYTHING TOO,
AND I HOPE HE'S, LIKE,
REALLY ACTIVE IN SPORTS.
AND I HOPE HE LOVES HORSES,
LIKE ME, AND RIDES,
UNLIKE YOU, STUBBORN BUTT.
IT MAKES ME SAD TO--LIKE,
THE FACT THAT I'M HAVING
TO GROW UP, SOMETIMES.
I CAN'T IMAGINE NOT LIVING
IN A HOUSE WITH MY MOM
AND HER NOT BEING THERE
EVERY DAY.
>> YOU GOT TO GROW UP SOMETIMES.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND LEAVE YOUR MAMA.
>> YOUR MOM AIN'T GONNA ALWAYS
BE THERE.
HOPEFULLY, YOU CAN DEPEND
ON ME.
>> GOING HUNTING WAS FUN
EVEN THOUGH IT WAS
PRETTY UNSUCCESSFUL.
BUT IT UPSET ME THAT J.R. DIDN'T
TRY TO UNDERSTAND MY FEARS
ABOUT MOVING OUT.
I'VE ALREADY HAD TO SACRIFICE
MY PAGEANTS AND COLLEGE,
AND I'M NOT SURE I'M READY
TO GIVE UP MY MOM TOO.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT MOVING OUT?
I MEAN, YOU'VE LIVED HERE
SINCE YOU WERE BORN.
>> I'M NERVOUS.
SOMETIMES I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO MOVE OUT, BUT...
I MEAN, I'VE GOT TO SOMETIME.
>> WHAT ABOUT SCHOOL?
YOU'RE DISAPPOINTED
ABOUT NOT BEING ABLE TO GO
TO COLLEGE, RIGHT?
>> GADSDEN STATE COMMUNITY
COLLEGE IS A BIG STEP DOWN
FROM WHAT I WANTED.
LIKE, ALL MY CLOSEST FRIENDS,
THEY'RE GOING TO U.A.B.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO MISS
YOUR FRIENDS WHEN THEY'RE GONE
AWAY TO COLLEGE?
IT'S OKAY.
GADSDEN STATE'S A WONDERFUL
COLLEGE.
I MEAN, YOU CAN GET A JOB
IN NURSING, JUST LIKE
YOU HAD PLANNED ON
AND YOU HAD HOPED FOR.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE
NEW FRIENDS.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, J.R. KNOWS I'M
DISAPPOINTED ABOUT NOT
BEING ABLE TO GO TO COLLEGE,
BUT I CAN'T REALLY TALK
TO HIM ABOUT IT,
'CAUSE HE GETS ILL.
>> YOU NEED TO BE ABLE
TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT IT,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU GO INTO A MARRIAGE,
IT'S MORE THAN JUST
TWO PEOPLE LIVING TOGETHER.
HE'S GOING TO BE
YOUR BEST FRIEND, YOU KNOW.
YOU NEED TO BE ABLE TO TALK
TO HIM ABOUT ANYTHING.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S JUST BETTER NOT TO TALK
ABOUT IT.
I MEAN--
>> WELL, IF IT'S SOMETHING
THAT BOTHERS YOU, IT'S NOT
BETTER NOT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
IT'S BETTER JUST TO GET IT
OFF YOUR CHEST.
>> MY MOM'S RIGHT.
IF J.R. AND I ARE GOING
TO MAKE THINGS WORK,
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TELL HIM
HOW I FEEL.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO START BEING
MORE HONEST WITH J.R.,
I CAN'T HELP BUT GET EXCITED
WHEN THE WORD "MARRIAGE"
COMES UP.
>> WHAT IF J.R. ASKS YOU
TO MARRY HIM, LIKE,
OUT OF THE BLUE?
YOU'RE LIKE, "WHAT?
REALLY? WHAT?"
>> I CAN'T, LIKE, IMAGINE IT.
BUT I'M JUST AN EMOTIONAL
PERSON.
I'LL PROBABLY BAWL MY EYES OUT.
I'LL PROBABLY--
>> AW!
IS IT GOING TO BE EASY
FOR HIM TO GET A RING?
>> PROBABLY NOT.
LIKE, HE DON'T REALLY MAKE
THAT MUCH, AND WHAT MONEY
HE DOES SAVE UP
GOES TOWARDS BILLS.
I DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE EASY.
OKAY, LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
MM!
>> SINCE MY PREGNANCY
HAS TAKEN ME OUT
OF THE PAGEANT CIRCUIT,
MY MOM ARRANGED A SPECIAL
PHOTO SHOOT FOR ME.
>> THAT IS SO PRETTY.
>> OH, WOW.
>> J.R. SHOWED UP AFTER WORK
FOR SOME COUPLE SHOTS.
>> HEY, HEY.
OKAY.
LET'S HAVE J.R.--LET'S HAVE
KAYLA--I'LL LET YOU TAKE
JUST A COUPLE OF STEPS FORWARD,
AND THEN, J.R., I'LL LET YOU
SLIDE IN BEHIND HER.
BEAUTIFUL.
MAYBE BRING YOUR HEAD FORWARD
JUST--PERFECT.
YAY.
NOW GIVE HER A SWEET LITTLE KISS
ON THE FOREHEAD BECAUSE SHE--
AW.
HOT MAMA.
MAYBE HOLD HIS HANDS.
>> THIS PAST YEAR HAS BEEN
THE GREATEST YEAR OF MY LIFE.
I LOVE YOU, YOUR MOM, YOUR DAD,
YOUR WHOLE FAMILY.
AND YOU'VE MADE ME HAPPIER
THAN ANYBODY COULD HAVE
EVER BEEN
IN THEIR WHOLE ENTIRE LIFE.
I LOVE YOU AND OUR BABY
MORE THAN ANYTHING
IN THIS WORLD.
AND I WANT TO SPEND THE REST
OF MY LIFE WITH YOU.
KAYLA...
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
>> I COULDN'T TALK.
I'M SPEECHLESS.
BUT YES, JUST IN CASE
YOU DIDN'T HEAR IT.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
I'VE ONLY CRIED FOR A WEEK.
>> I LOVE YOU, BABY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW J.R. AND I STILL
HAVE THINGS TO FIGURE OUT,
BUT I CAN'T HELP BUT BE EXCITED
ABOUT THIS RING.
HEY.
>> HI.
>> WELL...
>> OH!
THAT'S PRECIOUS.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> THE DIAMONDS GO, LIKE,
ALL THE WAY UNDER IT.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> BIG DIAMONDS.
>> OH, WOW.
DOES IT FEEL ANY DIFFERENT NOW,
BEING ENGAGED AND HAVING
A BABY ON THE WAY,
THAN IT DID BEFORE?
>> YEAH.
LIKE, NOW IT'S NOT LIKE
"ME AND MY BABY DADDY."
IT'S "ME AND MY FIANCE."
I WAS SUPER SURPRISED.
IT'S SCARY.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M EXCITED TO BE ENGAGED,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO MOVE
TOO FAST.
I HAVE NO IDEA HOW
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE MONEY
TO MOVE OUT,
TAKE CARE OF RYLAN,
AND PAY FOR A WEDDING.
BUT MY WORRIES WILL HAVE TO
WAIT, BECAUSE LATER THAT NIGHT,
I STARTED FEELING
SOME CONTRACTIONS,
AND MY DUE DATE
ISN'T FOR ANOTHER FIVE WEEKS.
MOM.
>> WHAT IS IT?
WHAT?
>> I THINK I'M HAVING
CONTRACTIONS.
WILL YOU COME TIME 'EM?
>> ARE YOU SURE
IT'S CONTRACTIONS?
>> IT HURTS PRETTY BAD.
>> OKAY.
ARE YOU HURTING NOW?
>> YEAH, I THINK I MIGHT
HAVE ONE NOW.
>> WELL, YOU GOT TO TELL ME
WHEN YOU'RE HURTING, NOW,
SO I CAN TIME 'EM.
>> WELL--
LIKE, EARLIER, I HAD, LIKE,
SOME BLOODY-LOOKING--
LIKE, I MEAN, IT WAS KIND OF
PINKISH.
AND, LIKE, THEY WERE HURTING
PRETTY--A LOT, REALLY SEVERE.
I THINK I'M HAVING ANOTHER ONE.
I'M ABOUT TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM.
MOM, I'M, LIKE, BLEEDING, LIKE,
REALLY BAD.
>> HOW BAD ARE YOU BLEEDING?
>> LIKE, IT'S BAD--LIKE, WORSE.
IT'S NOT PINK ANYMORE.
IT'S RED.
>> OKAY, WE'RE GOING
TO THE HOSPITAL NOW.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO GO
INTO LABOR
FOR ANOTHER FIVE WEEKS,
AND I'M REALLY NERVOUS
SOMETHING IS WRONG.
WHEN I GOT TO THE HOSPITAL,
J.R. WAS THERE WAITING.
I WAS ALREADY
SEVEN CENTIMETERS DILATED.
THE NURSES RUSHED ME
INTO A DELIVERY ROOM.
THE PAIN KEPT GETTING WORSE
AND WORSE.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, IT WAS TIME
TO PUSH.
EVEN THOUGH I WAS TERRIFIED
SOMETHING WOULD BE WRONG
BECAUSE RYLAN WAS PREMATURE,
HE CAME OUT WITH ALL TEN FINGERS
AND TOES AND SEEMED PERFECT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I MADE IT
THROUGH ALL THAT,
AND NOW I'M A MOM.
>> I'M SO HAPPY
EVERYTHING IS OKAY WITH RYLAN,
EVEN THOUGH HE IS
FIVE WEEKS PREMATURE.
>> HE LOOKS A LOT LIKE
HIS DADDY.
>> HE'S GOT MOMMY'S
LITTLE NOSE, THOUGH.
>> WE SHOULD HAVE BROUGHT--
>> WHAT DID THEY SAY?
>> YOU KNOW I NEED YOU
TO HOLD THE CAMERA.
"I'M GOING TO GO SEE
MY GRANNER."
[Rylan crying]
>> HE'S GOT THE DEATH GRIP
ON MY FINGER.
THE NURSES TOLD ME THAT BECAUSE
RYLAN IS PREMATURE,
HE MIGHT HAVE A HARD TIME
LATCHING ON.
SO FOR NOW, I'M PUMPING
BREAST MILK AND FEEDING HIM
WITH A BOTTLE.
BUT I'M GOING TO KEEP TRYING,
BECAUSE I WANT TO BOND
WITH MY BABY.
THAT WAS A LITTLE SUCK.
I'M TELLING YOU,
HE'S NOT LATCHING ON.
HERE.
MOM, WILL YOU PULL DOWN
HIS BOTTOM LIP?
THEY SAID IT'S ALSO GOOD, LIKE,
IF HE'S NOT LATCHING ON
AND YOU GOT HIM SKIN TO SKIN
LIKE THIS.
AT LEAST HE KNOWS THAT THAT'S
WHERE IT COMES FROM.
AFTER SCHOOL GOT OUT,
MY FRIENDS ALL SHOWED UP
TO SEE RYLAN.
>> OH!
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GET AN EXTRA MONTH
TO GET READY FOR PROM.
[laughter]
>> AFTER MY FRIENDS LEFT,
I WAS EXHAUSTED AND WAS READY
TO GET SOME SLEEP.
>> SEE YA.
[Rylan crying]
>> BUT SLEEP ISN'T REALLY
AN OPTION WITH A NEWBORN.
>> TODAY WE FINALLY GET
TO TAKE MY BABY BOY HOME,
AND I'M SO HAPPY
BUT SCARED OF HAVING TO DO
EVERYTHING BY MYSELF
WITHOUT THE NURSES' HELP.
>> OKAY, RYLAN,
WE'RE ON OUR WAY HOME!
KAYLA, IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
NO TIME AGO WHEN WE WERE
TRAVELING THIS SAME ROAD
TO TAKE YOU HOME.
>> WE AT HOME, BIG MAN.
>> HOME, SWEET HOME.
>> LOOK, RYLAN.
HERE'S YOUR ROOM.
>> SHOW HIM HIS LITTLE BED.
YOU CAN LAY HIM IN IT?
>> THANK GOODNESS MY MOM HAS
EXPERIENCE WITH BABIES
AND IS HAPPY TO HELP.
>> I HOPE HE LEARNS TO LATCH ON.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
>> SINCE RYLAN IS NOT
LATCHING ON, I'M ALREADY
SPENDING A LOT OF TIME
ATTACHED TO THIS PUMP.
I REALLY HOPE HE GETS THE HANG
OF BREAST-FEEDING SOON.
>> WHAT Y'ALL DOING?
>> WE WAS TRYING TO GET HIM
TO EAT.
>> HE DIDN'T EAT MUCH, DID HE?
>> YOU'VE ALREADY FALLEN
IN LOVE WITH HIM, HAVEN'T YOU?
>> NOW THAT I GOT HIM,
I JUST DON'T WANT TO LEAVE HIM.
I CAN'T HELP BUT LOVE HIM.
>> YOU'RE GOING BACK TO WORK,
J.R.?
>> YEAH, I GOT TO.
I CAN'T AFFORD TO MISS
ANY MORE WORK.
>> ARE YOU TAKING OFF
NEXT WEEK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE NEED TO DO?
>> YEAH, YOU NEED TO TAKE OFF.
>> YOU THINK I NEED
TO BE HERE ALL WEEK NEXT WEEK?
>> YEAH.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO,
BE HERE BY MYSELF?
>> WHY ARE YOU SCARED, KAYLA,
TO BE HERE BY YOURSELF?
>> BECAUSE I'VE, LIKE,
NEVER DONE THIS BY MYSELF.
>> BUT YOU ARE DOING
AN EXCELLENT JOB.
>> OH, WELL, BUT WITH HIM
BEING LITTLE, I DON'T WANT
TO REALLY TAKE HIM OUT
OF THE HOUSE MUCH.
>> YOU THINK THAT'S GOING
TO BE HARD, GOING BACK
AND FORTH BETWEEN HERE
AND DOWN TO PAM AND GLENN'S?
>> WE HAVEN'T, LIKE,
REALLY DISCUSSED IT,
BUT IS IT OKAY
IF J.R. STAYS WITH US?
>> YEAH, HE CAN STAY
AS LONG AS HE STAYS
IN THE OTHER ROOM
AND Y'ALL DON'T GET UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND VISIT EACH OTHER'S BEDROOMS
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> NO, WE DON'T WANT
NO MORE KIDS.
>> NO MORE BABIES.
>> J.R.'S FAMILY WAS FINE
WITH THAT PLAN TOO,
BUT WHILE HE GETS TO SLEEP
SOUNDLY IN THE OTHER ROOM,
I HAVE TO GET UP ALL NIGHT
WITH THE BABY.
[Rylan crying]
>> OKAY, RYLAN.
SLEEP WITH MOMMY
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
[Rylan crying]
LET MOMMY GET YOU A BOTTLE.
SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
>> I'M GOING TO WORK.
>> OKAY.
IT'S BEEN A WEEK, AND RYLAN'S
STILL NOT LATCHING ON.
SO I'M STILL PUMPING
AND FEEDING HIM WITH A BOTTLE.
I LOVE BEING A MOM,
BUT IT'S HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
HOW MUCH DID HE EAT?
WHY DON'T YOU GO GET
MY PUMPER THINGS
AND SOME BOTTLES?
>> THERE'S ONLY THREE OF THESE.
THE OTHER ONES ARE IN THE SINK.
THESE WERE IN THE SINK TOO.
>> DID YOU WASH THEM OUT?
I LOVE BEING A MOM,
BUT J.R. DOESN'T GET
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
WITH J.R. WORKING
AND BOTH OF US EXHAUSTED
TRYING TO TAKE CARE
OF THIS BABY,
EVEN THE SIMPLEST THINGS
CAN SEEM IMPOSSIBLY HARD.
EVEN THOUGH I SAID I WOULD ONLY
TAKE TWO WEEKS OFF FROM SCHOOL,
I'M NOT READY TO LEAVE RYLAN
AND GO BACK.
>> COME WITH ME, BIG BOY.
>> I'M TIRED.
>> YOU GOING TO TRY TO GET
A GOOD NIGHT'S REST TONIGHT?
>> I'LL TRY.
I'LL PROBABLY BE UP ANYWAY,
'CAUSE I HAVE TO CHECK
AND MAKE SURE HE'S BREATHING
EVERY NOW AND THEN
WHEN HE'S BEING TOO QUIET.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO RELAX
ABOUT ALL THAT.
>> I CAN'T.
>> ARE YOU STILL PLANNING
ON GOING BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> I'D LIKE TO GET BACK
PRETTY SOON, BUT HIM BEING
PREEMIE, I DON'T REALLY
WANT HIM TO BE
WITH ANYBODY ELSE.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO GO BACK
TO SCHOOL AND FINISH.
YOU'VE ONLY GOT A FEW MONTHS.
>> BUT I JUST WANT TO DO
WHAT'S BEST FOR HIM.
I TRUST MYSELF BETTER
THAN SOMEBODY THAT HASN'T HAD
A SMALL BABY IN A WHILE.
BEFORE I HAD THE BABY,
MY TOP PRIORITY WAS TO GRADUATE.
BUT BEING A MOM DOESN'T LEAVE
MUCH ROOM FOR ANYTHING ELSE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE A MONTH
HAS ALREADY PASSED.
I HAVEN'T GONE BACK TO SCHOOL,
BUT MY FRIENDS HAVE BEEN
VISITING.
HEY.
>> HEY, SUNSHINE.
WHEN DO YOU THINK YOU'LL BE
COMING BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> YOU GET A SIX-WEEK
MATERNITY LEAVE,
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> 'CAUSE I KEEP LOOKING
AT HER, AND WE'RE LIKE,
"WHERE'S KAYLA?"
KAYLA'S NOT HERE.
KAYLA'S NOT GOING TO BE HERE
TODAY.
>> RIGHT NOW, I GOT
THE NEW MOMMY THING GOING ON.
SAY, "I LOVE IT."
SAY, "I'M ALL THAT MATTERS
RIGHT NOW."
YEAH.
SINCE I'VE BEEN SPENDING
SO MUCH TIME AT HOME,
I'VE DECIDED I WANT
TO TAKE RYLAN RIDING.
J.R. THINKS IT'S A BAD IDEA,
BUT I WANT MY SON GROWING UP
KNOWING HOW TO RIDE.
>> HOW YOU GOING TO HOLD ON
TO HIM AND RIDE THAT HORSE
AT THE SAME TIME?
>> THIS IS HOLDING ON TO HIM.
>> HOW YOU GOING TO KEEP
HIS HEAD FROM--
>> I CAN--
ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> EASY.
>> OKAY.
>> BE A GOOD GIRL.
YOU GOT MY LITTLE SON ON THERE.
YOU BE A GOOD HORSE, OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT, READY?
>> YEAH.
COME ON.
>> GOT HER?
>> NOPE.
NO.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
HANG ON.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M GETTING ILL.
JUST STOP FOR A MINUTE.
>> WELL, GIVE ME RYLAN
AND JUST GET OFF.
>> HERE'S HIS PACI.
I GOT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, BEAUTIFUL.
>> EVER SINCE HE WENT BACK
TO WORK, J.R. AND I HAVE NOT HAD
MUCH TIME TO COMMUNICATE.
BUT HE'S BEEN SPENDING
HIS WEEKENDS
FIXING UP THE HOUSE FOR US,
SO I KNOW WE'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TALK SOON.
BUT I WANT TO MOVE
INTO THIS HOUSE
SOMEDAY REALLY SOON.
COME HERE, BABY BOY.
>> I MEAN, I THINK
IT'S REALLY NICE,
AND IT'LL BE A GREAT LITTLE
HOUSE FOR ME AND--
ME, YOU, AND RYLAN.
BUT I THINK THERE'S MORE--
LIKE, MORE STUFF WE NEED
TO TALK ABOUT.
WE NEED TO START TALKING
ABOUT HOW OUR FUTURE'S
GOING TO BE AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S OBVIOUS
THERE'S LOTS TO DISCUSS,
SO WE DECIDED TO GO BACK
TO MY HOUSE AND PUT THE BABY
TO BED BEFORE WE TRY
TO FIGURE THINGS OUT.
I DON'T THINK YOU REALIZE
HOW TOUGH IT IS GOING TO BE,
RAISING THE BABY.
>> I DON'T WANT US TO HAVE TO
DEPEND ON OUR PARENTS FOREVER
EITHER.
>> WELL, WE'RE NOT,
BUT WE'RE LUCKY TO HAVE
THE SUPPORT WE HAVE.
>> OH, I KNOW.
BUT IT AIN'T THEIR JOB
TO SUPPORT US AND TAKE CARE
OF US AND OUR BABY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S OUR JOB.
I WOULD LIKE TO MOVE.
>> YEAH, BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO BE SUPERMOM ALL BY MYSELF.
>> I FEEL BAD, BECAUSE THEY'RE
DOING IT IN MY PLACE,
WHEREAS I SHOULD BE DOING IT.
>> SO IS IT A PRIDE THING?
>> IT'S NOT PRIDE, BUT I WANT
TO SUPPORT MY FAMILY.
I KNOW OUR PARENTS ARE GOING
TO HELP US EVERY WHICH WAY
POSSIBLE, BUT I JUST DON'T
WANT THAT FOREVER.
>> WELL, I MEAN,
I'M NOT MOVING.
THAT'S JUST IT.
I HAVE TO DO WHAT I THINK
IS BEST FOR ME AND THE BABY,
REGARDLESS OF WHAT IT MEANS
FOR J.R. AND I.
WE'RE JUST NOT READY
TO DO THIS ON OUR OWN.
>> WITH J.R. AND I'S PLANS
TO MOVE IN TOGETHER ON HOLD,
I'M TRYING TO GET BACK
INTO THE SWING OF MY OLD LIFE.
BUT EVEN THOUGH I DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE RYLAN
WITH ANYONE BUT ME...
>> KAYLA!
>> MY BOYFRIEND.
NEXT WEEK, I HAVE TO GO
TO SCHOOL IF I WANT TO GRADUATE
ON TIME.
>> HOW'S THINGS BEEN?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M GOING
TO SCHOOL NEXT WEEK.
>> YOU ARE?
>> LIKE, I MISS EVERYBODY.
I MISS HAVING, LIKE,
A SOCIAL LIFE.
BUT, LIKE, I DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE HIM.
>> HE WANTS TO BE CLOSER
TO HIS GIRLFRIEND.
SEE?
SEE, RUBBING HIS EYES
EVERY TIME.
>> SO WHAT ARE Y'ALL'S PLANS
FOR PROM?
I DIDN'T KNOW IF, LIKE,
Y'ALL STILL WANTED ME
TO COME ALONG FOR PROM
OR WHATEVER, 'CAUSE I HAVEN'T
TALKED TO ANY--I MEAN,
I REALLY HAVEN'T TALKED
TO ANYBODY.
>> I WASN'T REALLY SURE ABOUT,
LIKE, IF YOU WOULD WANT TO DO
A LOT OF PARTYING
AND A LOT OF GOING OUT
AND ALL THAT
NOW THAT RYLAN'S HERE.
>> WHEN I FIRST GOT PREGNANT,
I WAS LIKE, "I'M GOING TO MAKE
THE BEST OF THIS.
I'M GOING TO TRY TO DO
EVERYTHING THAT I WOULD HAVE
NORMALLY DONE BEFORE,
BECAUSE IT IS MY SENIOR YEAR."
AND, LIKE, I STILL WANT
TO DO EVERYTHING.
>> I MEAN, THERE'S A LOT
THAT YOU CAN'T DO
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A BABY,
BUT THEN THERE'S STILL A LOT
THAT YOU CAN STILL BE PART OF.
IT'S JUST LIMITED.
>> YEAH.
IT'S OBVIOUS MY FRIENDS AND I
HAVE GROWN APART,
AND I'M NOT SURE HOW TO GET BACK
TO HOW THINGS USED TO BE.
[alarm beeping]
TODAY IS MY FIRST DAY BACK
AT SCHOOL, AND SINCE MY MOM
IS WORKING, I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO LEAVE RYLAN
WITH J.R.'S MOM.
[Rylan cries]
NO, NO.
>> DON'T FORGET THE PACI.
SHE'LL NEED THAT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> CALL ME AND LET ME KNOW
HOW YOU'RE DOING, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
I KNEW IT WAS GOING TO BE HARD
TO LEAVE HIM, BUT I HAD NO IDEA
IT WAS GOING TO BE THIS HARD.
>> HEY, SWEETHEART.
SAY, "BYE, MOM."
>> BEING BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL
WAS WEIRD.
IT MADE ME REALIZE HOW MUCH
BEING A MOM HAS CHANGED ME.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO LET
MY WHOLE YOUTH SLIP AWAY.
SO I'VE BEEN THINKING LATELY.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVEN'T REALLY
TALKED ABOUT THE WEDDING.
I'VE BEEN KIND OF RELIEVED,
'CAUSE I'M NOT READY
TO MOVE OUT.
WHY RUSH IT WHEN NOTHING'S
REALLY GOING TO CHANGE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I MEAN, I JUST THOUGHT
I'D BE GOOD FOR RYLAN.
>> I KNOW.
YOU GOT TO HAVE
YOUR SENIOR YEAR,
BUT I HAD TO MISS OUT
ON A LOT OF STUFF,
LIKE ME MOVING OFF
WITH ALL MY FRIENDS
AND GOING TO COLLEGE.
>> IF YOU THINK IT'S SOMETHING
THAT I DONE
THAT YOU'RE MISSING OUT ON,
IT'S NOT.
>> BUT I DIDN'T HAVE
THAT CHOICE.
>> I WANT TO BE YOUR HUSBAND,
AND I WANT TO PROVIDE
FOR YOU AND RYLAN,
AND I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
DEPEND ON YOUR MOM AND DAD
FOREVER.
IT MAKES ME FEEL LOW SOMETIMES
FOR YOUR MOM TO HAVE TO GO
BUY HIM FORMULA OR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, I WANT TO FEEL LIKE
I'M PROVIDING FOR YOU AND HIM.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
>> IF I WOULDN'T HAVE HAD
RYLAN, WOULD YOU STILL WANT
TO MARRY ME?
>> OF COURSE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO FEEL,
ON MY WEDDING DAY,
THAT I'M JUST GETTING MARRIED
BECAUSE WE HAD A BABY.
>> I WANT TO MARRY YOU
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU
AND I WANT TO SPEND THE REST
OF MY LIFE WITH YOU.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO PUT IT OFF
AND JUST KEEP PUTTING IT OFF
AND OFF AND OFF.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SCARED OF,
IS THAT YOU'RE DOING IT
'CAUSE YOU'RE SCARED
OF BEING WITH ME.
>> NO, I MEAN, I THINK
OUR RELATIONSHIP STILL NEEDS
SOME WORK, BUT IT'S NOTHING
CLOSE TO ME NOT WANTING
TO BE WITH YOU.
I DON'T THINK THAT ME AND J.R.
WERE READY TO BECOME PARENTS.
WE STILL NEEDED SOME MORE TIME
FOR OUR RELATIONSHIP TO GROW.
AND I'M GLAD THAT I TOLD J.R.
THAT I WASN'T READY
TO GET MARRIED RIGHT NOW,
BECAUSE MARRIAGE IS NOT
SOMETHING I'M READY
TO RUSH INTO.
HEY!
>> HEY, BABY DOLL.
>> MY MOM HELPS ME SO MUCH,
AND RIGHT NOW, I COULD NOT
IMAGINE DOING ANY OF IT
WITHOUT HER.
WHEN I HAD UNPROTECTED SEX,
I REALLY WISH I WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT IT THROUGH MORE,
BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH I HAD
ALL THE LOVE AND SUPPORT
IN THE WORLD,
THE EMOTIONAL STRUGGLE
THAT YOU HAVE TO GO THROUGH
ALONG WITH BEING PREGNANT
IS REALLY, REALLY HARD.
AND I JUST WANT TO SLOW DOWN
MY LIFE A LITTLE BIT.
I WANT TO FINISH OUT
MY SENIOR YEAR AND GRADUATE
AND ENJOY THE SUMMER
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, SEE
WHERE THE REST GOES.
Captioning byCaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY
TO TAKE CARE OF A BABY
WITH A CONTROLLER IN YOUR HAND.
>> IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
YOU GUYS CAN'T BE KIDS ANYMORE.
>> I THINK ONCE THE BABY COMES,
NATHAN'S GONNA SPLIT.
>> YOU NEED TO LAY OFF THE VIDEO
GAMES AND CHANGE MORE DIAPERS.
YOUR LIVING OFF OF MY DAD'S
PAYCHECK DOESN'T REALLY
THRILL ME.
>> WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT