>> STAY STILL.
>> YOU'RE MAKING MY NOSE ITCH.
[chime dings]
HI, I'M TAYLOR.
AND I'M FROM CINCINNATI, OHIO.
KAYLEE, THEY'RE BROKEN.
I'M 15 YEARS OLD NOW,
BUT ONE DAY, I WANT TO GO
TO COLLEGE AND BECOME A NURSE.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM,
AND WE'RE REALLY CLOSE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT WAS HYSTERICAL.
>> IT'S BEEN THAT WAY SINCE
MY DAD LEFT WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE TOO MANY
MEMORIES WITH HIM.
MY OLDER SISTER LIVES DOWN
THE STREET WITH HER FAMILY,
AND WE SPEND AS MUCH TIME
TOGETHER AS POSSIBLE.
>> BINGO!
>> BUT THEN I MET MY BOYFRIEND,
NATHAN, AT A ROLLER-SKATING
PARTY, AND WE BECAME
INSEPARABLE.
NATHAN AND I BOTH LOVE SPORTS
AND HANGING OUT WITH OUR
FRIENDS.
THAT WAS FUN.
WE SHOULD DO THAT AGAIN
NEXT WEEKEND.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S A YEAR OLDER
THAN ME, WE STILL GO
TO THE SAME SCHOOL TOGETHER.
NATHAN GREW UP WITHOUT A DAD TOO
BUT IS CLOSE WITH HIS MOM,
MISSY.
>> [chuckles]
>> YEAH.
>> MY MOM THINKS WE'RE TOO YOUNG
TO BE IN A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP,
BUT SHE'S GONNA HAVE TO GET
OVER IT, BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
YOU READY FOR THIS?
THIS IS MICHAEL JORDAN
RIGHT HERE.
OH!
IT'S SUMMERTIME, SO NATHAN
AND I HAVE BEEN ABLE TO HANG OUT
A LOT MORE LATELY.
"MY GIRLFRIEND BEAT ME
IN BASKETBALL."
WE ONLY LIVE A FEW BLOCKS AWAY
FROM EACH OTHER, WHICH IS A GOOD
THING, BECAUSE NEITHER ONE OF US
IS OLD ENOUGH TO DRIVE YET.
WHAT DID WE DO WHEN WE FIRST
STARTED DATING, LIKE...
>> SKATING RINK.
WENT OUT DANCING OR SOMETHING.
>> YEAH, WE WERE DANCING.
YOU WERE DOING SOME WEIRD MOVE,
AND ME AND LEXI HAD NEVER SEEN
IT BEFORE.
WE WERE LIKE, "OH, MY GOODNESS,
THAT'S SO COOL."
YOU WERE JUST, LIKE,
ON THE GROUND AND, LIKE,
VIBRATING.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS WEIRD.
>> AND LOOK WHAT ALL THAT
GOT US INTO.
>> YEAH.
>> HAVING A BABY NOW.
LET'S MAKE THE BABY SHOOT IT.
>> NO.
>> POP IT OFF YOUR BELLY.
>> YOU WANT TO GO FOR A WALK?
>> I GUESS.
>> THIS SUMMER HAS BEEN, LIKE,
BEEN KIND OF BORING, THOUGH,
JUST 'CAUSE WE CAN'T--
>> 'CAUSE NOW THAT
YOU'RE PREGNANT, LIKE,
YOU CAN'T DO MUCH.
I COULD, BUT I CHOOSE
TO STAY HOME WITH YOU.
>> THINGS HAVE DEFINITELY
CHANGED SINCE I GOT PREGNANT,
BUT I'M GLAD NATHAN IS STICKING
BY ME.
AND NOW THAT I'M SHOWING,
IT'S ALL MY FRIENDS WANT
TO TALK ABOUT.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO WHEN YOU
FOUND OUT YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> UH...
I TOOK THE PREGNANCY TEST,
AND THEN IT SAID POSITIVE,
AND THEN I CALLED NATHAN
AND TOLD HIM.
HE WAS LIKE, "WHOA,
I'M GONNA BE A DAD.
LET'S GO SHOPPING.
LET'S TELL MY MOM."
I WAS LIKE, "NO!
DON'T TELL ANYBODY.
KEEP IT A SECRET."
I WAS KIND OF, LIKE, IN AWE,
LIKE, JUST STRUCK BY IT.
LIKE...[gasps]
"I HAVE TO TELL MY MOM."
I WAS LIKE, "NO, NO, NO,
I CAN FAKE IT FOR A WHILE."
SO I THOUGHT OF PUTTING, LIKE,
FOOD COLORING ON, LIKE,
TAMPONS OR SOMETHING,
SO SHE WOULD THINK THAT I WAS,
LIKE, HAVING MY PERIOD.
I WAS THINKING UP A LOT
OF CRAZY THINGS.
>> SO I'M GUESSING YOUR MOM
WASN'T REALLY HAPPY ABOUT IT.
>> NO, SHE WASN'T HAPPY AT ALL.
IN FACT, MY MOM WAS REALLY UPSET
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, BECAUSE BEFORE SHE
HAD ME, SHE GOT PREGNANT AT 17
BUT CHOSE ADOPTION.
I WANT ME SOME COCOA PUFFS.
AND NOW SHE'S CONCERNED THAT
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO HANDLE
A BABY EITHER.
>> THIS IS A BIG BOWL.
>> THAT'S A TROUGH.
THAT'S NOT A BOWL.
>> WHAT'S A TROUGH?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE A BOWL TO ME.
>> I WORRY ABOUT YOU.
I WORRY ABOUT THE FINANCIAL PART
OF IT.
I WORRY ABOUT YOU GUYS
GOING TO SCHOOL, TAKING CARE
OF KIDS, BEING SO YOUNG.
YOU KNOW, I WAS 17 WHEN I GAVE
A CHILD UP FOR ADOPTION.
I KNEW THAT I COULDN'T TAKE CARE
OF A CHILD AT A YOUNG AGE.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU
GIVE THE CHILD UP FOR ADOPTION.
I JUST--
>> SHE'S GOT THAT LOOK.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S THERE EVERY TIME.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT SHE'S THINKING.
>> SHE PUTS THAT WALL UP.
>> YOU'RE MAKING ME MAD.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO HAVE TO STRUGGLE.
YOU SEE WHAT I GO THROUGH
AS A SINGLE MOM.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE IDEA
OF ADOPTION.
>> I JUST CAN'T STAND THE IDEA
OF, LIKE, HOW MY DAD LEFT,
AND I WOULDN'T WANT TO DO THAT
TO MY CHILD.
>> YOU SAY NOW THAT YOU'RE GONNA
BE WITH HER, BUT YOU ALL GROW
UP, AND YOUR FEELINGS CHANGE.
THEN THAT RESENTMENT STARTS
COMING IN, AND THEN YOU ALL
START FIGHTING, AND THEN
YOU BREAK UP.
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT ABOUT
YOU ANYMORE.
IT'S ABOUT THE LITTLE BABY.
>> I KNOW IT'S ABOUT THE BABY,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
CHOOSE ADOPTION.
WE'RE HAVING A GIRL,
AND I WANT HER TO GROW UP WITH
ME AND NATHAN AS HER PARENTS.
>> I LIKE THIS ONE.
>> SO I NEED TO MAKE SURE NATHAN
REALLY WILL BE THERE FOR US.
I WAS A HUGE DADDY'S GIRL,
AND THEN, LIKE, HE QUIT, LIKE,
BEING THERE.
HE WOULD JUST PROMISE THINGS,
AND IT WOULD JUST BREAK MY HEART
WHEN HE WOULDN'T DO IT,
'CAUSE I LOVED MY DAD SO MUCH,
AND, LIKE, I DON'T WANT HER
TO BE LIKE ME TOWARDS MY DAD.
>> WELL, I COULDN'T STAND
ANOTHER IDEA OF SOMEONE ELSE
BEING CALLED "DAD" BY MY KID,
AND I DON'T BELIEVE IN ADOPTION,
ABORTION.
I BELIEVE IN THE BABY BEING WITH
THEIR BLOOD PARENTS.
I'D GIVE HER WHAT ALL SHE WANTS,
'CAUSE SHE'S DADDY'S LITTLE
GIRL.
>> [laughs]
>> SPOIL HER ROTTEN.
SHE ONLY KICKS WHEN I TOUCH HER.
>> I'M RELIEVED NATHAN AGREES
AND WANTS TO KEEP THE BABY.
I'M SCARED TO TELL MY MOM,
BUT I'M GLAD AT LEAST NATHAN'S
MOM SUPPORTS US.
>> I'M NOT FOR ADOPTION
BECAUSE I THINK FAMILIES SHOULD
STICK TOGETHER.
THE BABY DOES NEED BOTH
ITS PARENTS IN ITS LIFE.
AND IT WILL BE HARD,
I MEAN, 'CAUSE YOU GUYS
WILL GET STRESSED.
>> JUST GOT TO FIGURE IT OUT.
>> JUST TALKING ABOUT IT WITHOUT
GETTING IN A FIGHT, I THINK,
IT HELPED ALREADY.
>> HAVE FUN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WATCH YOUR FEET.
>> OH...GIVE ME YOUR HANDS.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME FALL.
YOU'RE MAKING ME NERVOUS.
[laughs]
I CAN'T REMEMBER HOW TO SKATE,
'CAUSE I HAVEN'T SKATED
IN FOREVER.
I FEEL LIKE A LITTLE KID.
WHOA!
THINGS WITH ME AND NATHAN
HAVE BEEN REALLY GOOD,
AND I THINK WE'LL MAKE IT
TOGETHER AS PARENTS.
>> I LOVE YOU.
[laughter]
NOW THAT I'M DEFINITELY
KEEPING THE BABY, I NEED
TO TELL MY MOM.
I JUST HOPE SHE UNDERSTANDS
HOW I FEEL.
I GUESS I JUST FEEL I CAN DO IT.
EVEN THOUGH I RESENT THAT
I CAN'T DO SOME OF THE THINGS
I'D RATHER BE DOING AS
A TEENAGER, I THINK THE BETTER
OPTION IS TO KEEP HER.
>> YOU'RE JUST SO YOUNG.
YOU DON'T REALIZE--
HOW ARE YOU GONNA CLOTHE HER?
HOW ARE YOU GONNA BUY DIAPERS?
THE CRYING AND THE UP ALL NIGHT,
GOING TO SCHOOL.
YOU GUYS CAN'T EVEN GET JOBS
YET.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
SO THEN THE BURDEN OF THIS
FALLS ON ME, WHICH I'M ALREADY
STRETCHED TO THE LIMIT.
YOU KNOW, WHAT DO I DO?
AND ADOPTIONS AREN'T LIKE
THEY USED TO BE, WHERE,
YOU KNOW, YOU JUST GAVE IT AWAY
AND NEVER SAW IT AGAIN.
YOU CAN HAVE OPEN ADOPTIONS.
>> IT'S MY KID;
IT'S NOT THEIRS.
LIKE, THEY'LL BE ABLE TO SEE HER
GO THROUGH, LIKE,
OH, FIRST STEPS.
OH, FIRST SMILE.
OH, SHE CUT HER HAIR.
OH, SHE FELL DOWN THE STAIRS.
NO, THAT'S NOT THEIR JOB.
IT'S MINE.
>> [sniffles]
I DON'T WANT YOU TO HAVE TO
STRUGGLE.
I DON'T.
AND I KNOW IT'S GONNA BE HARD
FOR YOU.
[chime dings]
>> I KNOW IT'S NOT GONNA
BE EASY, BUT I WANT TO RAISE
MY OWN BABY.
I JUST HOPE MY MOM WILL SUPPORT
MY DECISION.
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
>> I'M GLAD NATHAN AND I
ARE KEEPING THE BABY,
AND I THINK MY MOM IS STARTING
TO ACCEPT OUR DECISION,
BUT SHE AND MY SISTER WANT
TO HAVE A TALK WITH US.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL TODAY?
>> PREGNANT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GONNA BE THAT WAY FOR
A WHILE?
>> I THINK EVERY POUND I GAIN,
YOU GAIN THREE TIMES THAT.
>> I KNOW, I HAVE BEEN.
I'VE BEEN GAINING.
EVERY TIME SHE DOES, I GAIN.
>> SYMPATHY POUNDS.
>> I DON'T KNOW. I HAVE BEEN.
>> I REMEMBER WHEN I FOUND OUT
YOU WERE PREGNANT.
I MEAN, YOU OBVIOUSLY WANTED HER
TO GIVE IT UP FOR ADOPTION.
BUT I THINK HAVING A STRANGER
RAISE THE BABY WOULD BE HARD
FOR YOU, AND IT WAS MORE
MOM'S DECISION THAN YOURS.
>> I WASN'T--
>> I'M NOT ALLOWED TO MAKE
THAT DECISION FOR HER BY LAW,
THOUGH, EVEN THOUGH SHE IS
A MINOR.
>> WELL, COMPARED TO OTHER
PEOPLE IN THIS WORLD, I THINK
I'D DO A LOT BETTER THAN
MOST OF THE PEOPLE.
>> I'M SURE YOU WOULD.
I DON'T DOUBT THAT--
>> I DON'T THINK THAT YOU WILL
DO A BAD JOB.
I JUST THINK IT'S GONNA TAKE
A LOT OF YOUR OWN HAPPINESS
AWAY.
IT'S A CONSTANT, 24-7.
THERE'S REALLY NEVER A BREAK
IN THE BEGINNING OF THIS.
THERE'S BOTTLE WASHING,
THE LAUNDRY, THE DIAPERS.
YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA HAVE TO
GET AT LEAST A PART-TIME JOB.
>> AND SHE LOOKS AT ME.
>> I CAN'T EVEN GET A JOB YET.
I'M NOT OLD ENOUGH.
>> THIS ONE LIVING BEING
IS COMPLETELY DEPENDENT ON YOU.
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU TO HAVE
A RUDE AWAKENING WHEN IT FINALLY
GETS HERE.
BETTER START PREPARING NOW.
>> MY SISTER IS RIGHT.
I'M DUE IN TEN WEEKS,
SO WE REALLY NEED TO FIGURE OUT
HOW WE'RE GONNA GET READY
FOR THIS BABY.
WE'RE NAMING HER AUBRI,
BUT THAT'S ABOUT ALL WE KNOW.
NOW THAT WE'RE GONNA KEEP HER,
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
THE PLAN IS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING YOU.
>> TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> WELL, DUH.
HOW ARE WE GONNA PAY
FOR THE BABY?
MY MOM CAN BARELY EVEN
SUPPORT US.
>> I'M GETTING A JOB SOON.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU CAN'T ALWAYS
RELY ON PEOPLE.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
I'M GETTING A JOB SOON.
I CAN RELY ON MY MOM IF I WANT.
IT'S MY MAMA.
>> IT'S NOT YOUR MOM'S KID,
THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
I'M GETTING A JOB.
I'M 16 NOW.
ALL I GOT TO DO IS FINISH
ALL THE APPLICATIONS.
MY MOM JUST HAS TO GIVE ME
MY SOCIAL SECURITY, AND THEN
I GOT TO GO TURN THOSE IN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE TRYING.
I AIN'T COMPLAINING.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT NATHAN
STARTS HIS JOB HUNT SOON,
BECAUSE SUMMER IS ALMOST OVER,
AND IT'S ONLY GONNA GET HARDER
WHEN SCHOOL STARTS.
>> 23, 24!
OH!
>> WE'RE GONNA LOSE MOST OF
THESE GAMES, BY THE WAY.
I SPENT THE NEXT FEW WEEKS
BABYSITTING MY SISTER'S KIDS
HERE AND THERE TO MAKE SOME
MONEY.
>> YEAH!
>> I JUST GOT BEAT BY
A THREE-YEAR-OLD.
IT'S NOT SUPER CONSISTENT,
BUT IT'S MORE THAN I CAN SAY
FOR NATHAN, WHO HASN'T
SUBMITTED ONE JOB APPLICATION
YET, AND IT'S MAKING ME WONDER
IF HE'S SERIOUS ABOUT BECOMING
A DAD AFTER ALL.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU AND NATHAN
DOING?
>> HE'S ANNOYING ME.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE HE'S ANNOYING.
HE'LL BE LIKE, "EVERYBODY ALWAYS
ASKS THE MOM HOW THE BABY
IS DOING, NEVER THE DAD."
IT'S LIKE, "YEAH, YOU GONNA
PUSH IT OUT YOUR PENIS?"
I DON'T THINK SO, SO...
>> [laughs]
>> I'M LIKE, OBVIOUSLY, LIKE,
THEY'RE GONNA ASK ME.
>> DO YOU THINK NATHAN
IS READY AND MATURE ENOUGH
TO BE A DAD?
>> UH, SOMETIMES.
OTHER TIMES, I DON'T REALLY
THINK SO.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT NATHAN
TO HAVE AS A DAD, LIKE...
>> A JOB.
A JOB.
>> IS THAT, LIKE,
THE MAIN THING?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
MY MOM PAYING FOR IT
OR HIS MOM PAYING FOR IT
ALL THE TIME.
>> BE INDEPENDENT.
>> AND I FEEL BAD, 'CAUSE I KNOW
IT'S NOT THEIR RESPONSIBILITY.
I DON'T WANT TO, LIKE, SIT THERE
AND TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THEM.
>> HAVE YOU TALKED TO HIM ABOUT
GETTING A JOB?
>> YEAH.
>> NOTHING?
>> AND HE OBVIOUSLY DON'T CARE,
SO...OR HE WOULD HAVE HAD
A JOB BY NOW.
>> THERE'S MY MAMA.
WHAT'S UP, MAMA?
>> HEY.
>> HI.
SUMMER IS ALMOST OVER,
AND THE BABY IS LESS THAN
TWO MONTHS AWAY.
WE'RE USING MY BABYSITTING MONEY
AND SOME HELP FROM NATHAN'S MOM
TO GET READY FOR AUBRI.
I THINK I'M JUST GONNA GET
THE BASIC STUFF THAT A BABY
NEEDS AND THEN, LIKE, CLOTHES,
AND THEN I KIND OF WANT
A PLAY--LIKE, A PLAYPEN
AND MORE WINTER CLOTHES,
'CAUSE WE HAVE A LOT OF ONESIES.
WE DON'T HAVE, LIKE, A LOT
OF WINTER CLOTHES.
[upbeat guitar music]
* *
IT'S CUTE.
I LIKE THAT PLAYPEN.
>> HOW MUCH IS IT?
>> $100.
>> YIKE.
>> TOO MUCH MONEY.
I HAVE $25 ON ME, I THINK.
YOU SHOULD HAVE WORKED OVER
THE SUMMER, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
'CAUSE, LIKE, THEN YOU WOULD
HAVE HAD MONEY SAVED UP.
>> IT'S HARD TO GET HIRED.
>> IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
TRUST ME.
>> STOP SWEATING ME.
RELAX.
I'LL GET A JOB.
>> WELL, I THINK YOU JUST SHOULD
HAVE GOT A JOB OVER THE SUMMER.
THAT WAY, WE'D HAVE MONEY.
>> WELL...
I KNOW, TOOTS.
YOU SAY IT ALL THE TIME.
>> [growls]
YOU'RE MAKING ME MAD.
"I KNOW, I KNOW."
>> 'CAUSE EVERYBODY TELLS ME IT
ALL THE TIME.
>> WELL, WE UNDERSTAND THAT
YOU KNOW, BUT YOU STILL DO IT.
>> $7.50.
>> THAT ONE'S $4.50.
$50 RIGHT THERE.
>> THAT AIN'T BAD.
I MEAN...
>> THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
[chime dings]
NATHAN DOESN'T THINK THIS STUFF
IS EXPENSIVE, BUT HE'S NOT
THE ONE PAYING FOR IT.
IF HE DOESN'T GET A JOB SOON,
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE GONNA
AFFORD THIS BABY.
>> AFTER BICKERING FOR MOST
OF THE SUMMER, NATHAN FINALLY
REALIZED HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
TO GET A JOB, AND HE STARTED
APPLYING.
I'M DUE IN SIX WEEKS, SO I'M
GLAD HE'S GETTING SERIOUS
BEFORE THE BABY COMES.
SCHOOL STARTS TOMORROW,
AND I HAVE NOTHING THAT FITS,
SO EVEN THOUGH MONEY IS TIGHT,
I'M GOING SHOPPING.
>> PEOPLE STARE AT YOU.
>> YEAH, THEY STARE AT MY BELLY
OR...SOMETHING.
THIS--LOOK.
THIS COULD FIT, LIKE, ME AND YOU
AND NATHAN IN IT.
AND THESE PANTS, LOOK AT THEM.
THEY'RE, LIKE--I COULD PUT
ANOTHER PERSON IN THERE.
[lively rock music]
* *
I'LL TRY THIS ON WITH...
>> YEAH, IT LOOKS REALLY CUTE.
>> I THINK I'M GONNA BUY THIS.
>> SO ARE YOU NERVOUS FOR
THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL?
>> KIND OF, 'CAUSE, LIKE,
THE PEOPLE I TOLD I WASN'T
PREGNANT TO, I THINK THEY'RE
GONNA MAKE THEIR, LIKE, LITTLE,
"I TOLD YOU SO," LITTLE
DRAMA-MAKING REACTIONS.
WHATEVER.
IF SOMEONE CALLS ME FAT, THOUGH,
THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY.
>> YEAH.
THAT WOULDN'T BE COOL.
>> IT'S ON AFTER THAT.
BUT I'M JUST KIND OF EXCITED
JUST SO I CAN GET OUT OF THE
HOUSE AND JUST SEE PEOPLE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN SHE'S BORN?
ARE YOU GONNA STAY IN SCHOOL
OR...
>> UH, I WANT TO TRY AND KEEP
DOING SCHOOL, BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF I'LL BE ABLE TO,
JUST 'CAUSE ME AND NATHAN
CAN'T AFFORD, LIKE, A DAY CARE
OR BABYSITTER OR ANYTHING.
IF I CAN'T STAY IN SCHOOL,
I GUESS I'M GONNA HAVE TO DO
VIRTUAL SCHOOL, BUT I REALLY
DON'T WANT TO.
>> WHAT EXACTLY IS VIRTUAL
SCHOOL?
>> IT'S WHERE YOU DO SCHOOLWORK
AT HOME, BUT YOU STILL GET,
LIKE, YOUR CREDITS AND STUFF.
YOU JUST DO IT ON A COMPUTER.
KIND OF BE BORING, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU DON'T GET
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
>> YEAH, LIKE, YOU CAN'T REALLY
HAVE ANY--MUCH FUN.
SO I'M GONNA TRY REALLY, REALLY
HARD TO DO REGULAR SCHOOL.
SCHOOL STARTS TODAY, AND NATHAN
IS COMING OVER SO MY MOM
CAN DRIVE US IN TOGETHER.
>> YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
>> IT'S FREEZING.
I'M GETTING TOO FAT TO WALK
AND FIT IN MY CLOTHES.
FIRST PERSON TO TOUCH MY STOMACH
IS GETTING SMACKED.
>> YOU KNOW PEOPLE ARE GONNA
TOUCH YOUR STOMACH, SO DON'T BE
OFFENDED BY IT AND DON'T GET
GROUCHY ABOUT IT.
JUST SMILE AND LET THEM DO IT.
>> I'LL MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
I'LL LET THEM TOUCH MY BABY
IN THE BELLY.
>> OKAY, GUYS, SO I GUESS
THIS IS IT.
HAVE FUN.
[chime dings]
>> IT WAS GREAT TO SEE ALL MY
FRIENDS AND BE BACK IN CLASS.
I'M ALREADY EXCITED TO COME
BACK AFTER THE BABY IS BORN
SO I CAN ACTUALLY ENJOY
HIGH SCHOOL WITHOUT BEING
PREGNANT.
BUT WITHOUT A BABYSITTER,
IT MIGHT BE HARD TO CONVINCE
MY MOM THAT THIS IS THE BEST
PLAN.
>> HOW MANY PEOPLE RUBBED
YOUR BELLY?
>> NOBODY, NO.
>> OH.
THAT'S SURPRISING.
WE NEED TO SIT DOWN AND SEE HOW
WE'RE GONNA WORK THIS SCHEDULE
OUT, AS TO HOW YOU ALL ARE GONNA
WORK IT WHEN THE BABY COMES.
YOU KNOW A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
THAT VIRTUAL SCHOOL, DON'T YOU,
NATHAN?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DOES THAT WORK?
>> YOU DO WORK ON A COMPUTER.
>> I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO DO THAT.
>> BUT YOU GOT TO THINK,
WHO'S GONNA WATCH THAT KID
DURING THE DAY?
>> I KNOW, BUT IT'S GONNA BE
RETARDED SITTING IN A SMALL
LITTLE CLASSROOM ALL DAY
ON THE COMPUTER FOR THREE HOURS.
LATER THAT WEEK, WE MET UP
WITH NATHAN AND HIS MOM TO MAKE
A PLAN FOR WHEN THE BABY
IS BORN.
>> I THOUGHT MAYBE EVERY OTHER
NIGHT, HE COULD COME OVER
AND HELP HER.
>> I MEAN, THAT SEEMS
PRETTY REASONABLE.
>> BUT I'M JUST REALLY CONCERNED
AT THAT TIME FRAME THAT THEY'RE
IN SCHOOL, THAT WE DON'T HAVE
A GOOD BABYSITTER TO GIVE THEM.
I WORK 9:30 AT NIGHT UNTIL
5:30 IN THE MORNING.
>> I WORK 6:00 IN THE MORNING
TILL 2:00 IN THE AFTERNOON.
>> SEE, SO THERE'S WHERE
OUR PROBLEM LIES.
THAT'S THE PART I'M AFRAID OF.
IT'S GONNA MEAN THAT ONE OF THEM
HAS TO SACRIFICE.
>> OBVIOUSLY, NEITHER OF US
WANT TO DO VIRTUAL, BUT...
>> I'D RATHER YOU DO THE
VIRTUAL, AND I COULD STICK
TO SCHOOL.
>> THAT'S NOT FAIR THAT I HAVE
TO GIVE UP EVERYTHING IN
THE WORLD WHILE YOU STILL GET
THE, "YEAH, I'M A DAD, BUT
I CAN STILL GO TO HIGH SCHOOL
AND GO TO FOOTBALL GAMES
AND DO THIS AND THIS."
>> WHO SAYS I'M DOING THAT?
I DIDN'T SAY I WAS--
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE MAKING IT
SOUND LIKE.
>> THERE REALLY IS NO
ALTERNATIVE.
SOMETHING HAS TO BE DECIDED
UPON, BECAUSE THERE'S NO ONE
TO WATCH HER FOR SEVEN HOURS
WHILE YOU GO TO SCHOOL.
SO YOU HAVE TO FIGURE SOMETHING
OUT.
SUCK IT UP AND DO SOMETHING.
I TOLD YOU THERE WAS GONNA BE
A LOT OF SACRIFICING.
>> I KNEW THAT KEEPING THE BABY
WOULD MEAN GIVING UP
A LOT OF THINGS...
[chime dings]
BUT I DEFINITELY DIDN'T THINK
HIGH SCHOOL WOULD BE ONE
OF THEM.
>> I'M BUMMED THAT I HAVE TO DO
VIRTUAL SCHOOL FROM HOME WHEN
THE BABY IS BORN, BUT IT'S
IMPORTANT THAT I KEEP UP
WITH SCHOOL SO I CAN BE
A GOOD MOM FOR AUBRI.
I HAVE ONE WEEK UNTIL SHE'S DUE,
AND I'M GONNA MAKE THE MOST
OUT OF IT.
[upbeat quirky music]
>> PERFECT.
* *
>> IS IT DARK ENOUGH FOR MY EARS
YET?
>> MMM...
>> OH, YEAH.
TRICK OR TREAT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU ARE WELCOME.
>> I HEAR YOU'RE GONNA
BE PARENTS.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I HEAR YOU'RE GONNA
BE PARENTS.
[laughter]
>> I'M TOO OLD FOR DRESSING UP.
I JUST WANT THE CANDY.
TRICK OR TREAT.
[candy rustling]
>> SO WHAT'S NEXT YEAR GONNA
BE LIKE?
ARE YOU GONNA DRESS THE BABY UP?
>> YEAH, WE'RE GONNA TAKE HER
TRICK-OR-TREATING, AND THEN
I'M GONNA EAT HER CANDY,
'CAUSE SHE WON'T BE ABLE
TO EAT IT YET.
IT'S SAD.
>> WHAT'S YOUR PLAN FOR WHEN
THE BABY COMES?
>> FOR RIGHT NOW--SINCE HE'S
STILL IN SCHOOL, AND THEN I'M
GONNA DO HOMESCHOOLING--
THAT HE'S JUST GONNA COME OVER,
LIKE, THREE NIGHTS OUT OF
THE SCHOOL WEEK, I GUESS.
THEN THE WEEKENDS,
WE'LL JUST DO WHATEVER.
I MEAN, WEEKENDS DON'T REALLY
MATTER.
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS ABOUT
THE DELIVERY OR ANYTHING?
>> I'M NOT REALLY SCARED.
LIKE, OBVIOUSLY,
IT'S GONNA HURT.
I MEAN, THERE'S A KID
COMING OUT OF YOUR CROTCH.
BUT I THINK PROBABLY
ONCE IT COMES, I'LL BE LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD!"
MY DUE DATE CAME AND WENT,
BUT I STILL HAVEN'T FELT
ANY CONTRACTIONS.
I FEEL SO FAT NOW.
BUT MY DOCTOR SAYS I JUST
HAVE TO WAIT AND WAIT
AND WAIT AND WAIT.
AND FINALLY, FIVE DAYS AFTER
MY DUE DATE, MY DOCTOR DECIDED
TO INDUCE ME TONIGHT.
MOM?
>> YES?
>> SHOULD I TAKE, LIKE,
SHIRT SHIRTS AND THEN, LIKE,
TANK TOPS?
>> TAYLOR, YOU'RE GONNA BE
IN A BED FOR TWO DAYS.
>> OKAY, I UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T WANT TO WEAR THE
STUPID--I DON'T WANT TO WEAR
THE STUPID LITTLE GOWN WITH
YOUR FRICKING BUTT HANGING OUT.
>> THE THING IS, THEY DON'T HAVE
MUCH TIME WHEN THEY COME IN
AND WANT TO EXAMINE YOU
AND DO THIS AND DO THAT.
THEY WANT SOMETHING THEY CAN
PULL UP, CHECK YOU, AND GO.
>> WELL, I'M TAYLOR, SO THEY'RE
GONNA TAKE THEIR SWEET OLD TIME.
>> HOW MUCH STUFF ARE YOU
TAKING?
>> TOO MUCH.
>> YOU NERVOUS YET?
>> [whining] NO.
I'M NOT NERVOUS.
>> ARE YOU--ARE YOU CRANKY?
>> ARE YOU ANXIOUS?
>> YES, I'M CRANKY.
I'M SICK OF PEOPLE ASKING ME
IF I'M NERVOUS.
>> YOU THINK YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO KEEP PUSHING AND BE STRONG,
SUPERWOMAN, HUH?
>> AND BREATHE.
[huffing]
YOU'VE NEVER HAD ANYTHING
LIKE THIS PAIN.
>> NOTHING.
>> TRUST ME.
>> IT'LL HURT BAD ENOUGH THAT
YOU'LL WANT TO GET HER OUT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I BIT MY CHEEK.
OH...
>> NOW ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
[laughter]
>> YOU HIT A FREAKIN'--
>> MULTIPLY THAT BY 10,000.
[laughter]
ALL RIGHT, GET UP
AND GET READY.
OOH, WE'RE GONNA GO HAVE A BABY!
OOH!
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE A BABY
IN LESS THAN 24 HOURS.
[monitor pulsing]
>> MMM...
>> ONCE I GOT SETTLED
AT THE HOSPITAL, THEY STARTED ME
ON PITOCIN.
AFTER A FEW HOURS,
THE CONTRACTIONS BEGAN,
AND IT WAS THE WORST PAIN EVER.
>> DEEP BREATHS.
>> [whines]
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
>> USE THAT PILLOW.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
>> [whines]
>> BABY, IT'S OKAY.
>> IF I COULD TRADE SPOTS,
I WOULD.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> NO.
DOES IT LOOK LIKE I'M OKAY?
>> I KNOW, SWEETHEART.
>> [sobs]
[sobbing]
>> OH, GOD.
>> [sobbing]
>> SHE'S JUST TOO YOUNG.
>> I WANNA LEAVE.
I WANNA GO HOME.
>> OH!
>> YOU GOT TO GET IT STARTED.
YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> I WANNA GO HOME!
>> YOU CAN'T.
THAT'S NOT AN OPTION.
>> AFTER 13 HOURS OF
EXCRUCIATING PAIN, I WAS FINALLY
READY FOR MY EPIDURAL.
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT,
IT WAS TIME TO START PUSHING.
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS?
>> YOU CAN STAND OVER HERE.
>> NO, I'M FINE.
I'M NOT NAUSEOUS.
>> NO, NERVOUS.
>> OH...
>> OKAY, SO WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
WHEN YOU HAVE A CONTRACTION,
BIG DEEP BREATH IN.
>> BE STRONG, TAY.
>> AND PUSH.
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
SHE'S ALMOST HERE.
GOOD JOB.
>> ONE MORE, ONE MORE.
>> GOOD JOB, BABY.
>> FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN.
GOOD, TAKE A BREATH.
DO IT AGAIN.
YOU CAN DO IT, COME ON.
BIG DEEP BREATH.
>> WHOA.
>> COME ON, PUSH RIGHT
THROUGH IT.
HER HEAD'S ALMOST OUT.
THAT'S IT.
[inspirational music]
>> THAT A GIRL.
GOOD JOB.
YOU GOT IT.
LOOKS GREAT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
HEY, LITTLE TINY.
>> YOU'RE ALL RIGHT, MAN.
>> GO RIGHT IN BETWEEN
THESE TWO, OKAY?
>> OH, SHE'S GONNA HELP YOU.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> PERFECT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, BABY...
>> OH, LOOK AT HER, TAY!
[laughter]
HONEY, I AM SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU DID IT, BABY.
>> OH, SHE'S PERFECT.
>> SHE IS BEAUTIFUL.
>> * HONEY, YOU ARE *
* THE SWEETEST THING *
* THAT THESE EYES *
* HAVE EVER SEEN *
* I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW *
* IF YOU'RE EVER WONDERING *
* I DON'T WANT TO BE LOVED *
* BY ANYONE BUT YOU *
* WILL WE WAIT TOO LONG? *
* 'CAUSE I'M NOT SURE *
* IF THERE'S ANYTHING *
* LEFT HERE *
* WE SHOULD BE WAITING FOR *
>> AUBRI'S ONLY ONE DAY OLD,
BUT THINGS WENT SO WELL
THEY'RE DISCHARGING US TODAY.
I'M SCARED TO BRING HER HOME,
BUT I'M HOPING WITH NATHAN
STAYING OVER EVERY OTHER NIGHT,
WE'LL GET THROUGH IT.
>> ARE YOU, LIKE, NERVOUS
TO BE HOME?
>> IF I CAN TAKE THE NURSES
HOME WITH ME, I THINK I'D BE
GOOD.
>> JEANA, DO YOU WANT
TO BURP HER?
>> YOU'RE GOOD AT THAT.
>> YOU CAN EITHER SIT HER UP...
>> NO.
>> AND EITHER RUB HER
UP AND DOWN OR PAT HER.
>> HOLD HER A LITTLE BIT,
SO I CAN--THAT--SHE ALREADY DID
IT WITHOUT ANYBODY HITTING
HER BACK.
>> [belches]
>> LOOK.
>> OOH.
>> WITHOUT ANYBODY HITTING
HER BACK.
>> HOLD HER UP.
I THINK THAT RIDE HOME
UPSET HER BELLY.
>> I NEED A LITTLE THING.
>> WHAT DO YOU NEED?
>> SOMETHING TO WIPE HER OFF
WITH.
>> THAT'S WHAT THE BIB IS FOR.
>> OH...
[laughter]
[squelching noise]
EW!
[laughter]
>> WAS THAT THROW UP OR POO?
>> THAT WAS...
>> THAT WAS POOP, BUT I THOUGHT
IT WAS THROW UP.
>> SHE BLEW UP!
>> OKAY, WHO'S CHANGING
THAT DIAPER?
>> JEANA, JEANA.
>> NOPE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
EW, IT STINKS.
EW...
[Aubri belches]
>> EW!
>> [screams]
JEANA!
>> OH, THE DIAPER...
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THEY ARE CRAZY.
>> PUT THIS DOWN.
>> HOLD ON.
YOU GUYS GOT HER LAYING
IN A PILE OF PEE.
>> WELL, IT'S 'CAUSE
SHE PEED EVERYWHERE.
GOD, NOW SHE'S SPITTING UP.
THIS IS...
>> YOU'RE OKAY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO HER,
JEANA?
>> SHE WAS CHOKING.
>> OH...
>> BABY, IT'S OKAY.
>> OH, GOD.
>> IT'S NICE HAVING MY SISTER
HERE, BUT NATHAN AND I OBVIOUSLY
HAVE A LOT TO LEARN.
I START VIRTUAL SCHOOL
IN TWO WEEKS, BUT NATHAN WENT
BACK TO HIGH SCHOOL AFTER ONLY
A FEW DAYS.
AND EVEN THOUGH HE HELPED OUT
AT FIRST, HE'S STARTING
TO SLACK OFF.
WHAT?
TELL ME.
[Aubri coos]
OH, I KNOW.
IT'S COLD.
NEXT TIME YOU GO OUTSIDE,
CAN YOU TAKE THAT OUT WITH YOU?
>> YOU TAKE IT OUT.
>> I CAN'T TAKE IT OUT.
>> I'M NOT TAKING ALL THAT.
SHE'S RIPPING IT.
>> YOUR TURN.
>> NO.
>> NO?
ARE YOU GONNA CHANGE HER?
>> IT'S DISGUSTING.
>> HOLD STILL.
>> EW, IT STINKS.
>> REALLY...
>> NO.
>> RIDICULOUS.
I REALLY NEED MORE HELP
FROM NATHAN, AND IT LOOKS
LIKE I'M ON MY OWN TONIGHT
BECAUSE HE'S STAYING AT HIS
HOUSE AGAIN.
>> [crying]
>> [shushing]
[peaceful acoustic music]
>> * KEEP WANDERING *
* *
* CAN HEAR YOU TALK *
* IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE SENSE *
[Aubri crying]
* IT DON'T ADD UP *
* ALL I WANT *
* IS A PLACE TO REST MY HEAD *
* *
>> HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> I WANT SOME SLEEP.
>> THAT'S A BABY FOR YA.
I TOLD YOU; ONCE YOU HAVE
A BABY, YOU'RE NEVER GONNA
HAVE ANY SLEEP AGAIN.
YOUR SLEEPING DAYS ARE GONE
FOR ABOUT 11 YEARS.
>> LIKE, AN HOUR WOULD AT LEAST
BE NICE.
I AT LEAST NEED AN HOUR OF SLEEP
TO FUNCTION RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST FRUSTRATING THAT
I HAVE TO DO IT ALL BY MYSELF.
I REALLY WISH NATHAN WAS MORE
SUPPORTIVE, BUT NOT MUCH
HAS CHANGED.
HE STILL DOESN'T HAVE A JOB,
AND WE STILL HAVE TO RELY
ON OUR PARENTS.
>> LET'S LOOK AT THE PRICES
HERE.
THAT'S $10.99.
>> IT'S ALL $10.99.
>> SO THIS IS WHAT WE WANT,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> ADD THIS UP REAL QUICK.
>> $11, $15, AND THEN...
>> UH, 4 TIMES 6 IS ANOTHER $3.
>> PLUS TAX PROBABLY IS ABOUT
$34, $35.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
SOMEBODY NEEDS TO GET A JOB
BESIDES ME AROUND HERE.
>> I'M TRYING.
I'VE BEEN FILLING OUT
APPLICATIONS.
>> BUT LET'S TRY HARDER
SO THAT WE CAN--SO IT DOESN'T
ALWAYS FALL ON ME.
>> MY MOM IS GETTING ANNOYED
WITH NATHAN TOO, AND I FEEL BAD
ABOUT DEPENDING ON HER FOR
EVERYTHING.
I'M HAVING A HARD TIME FOCUSING
ON MY HOMESCHOOLING BECAUSE
I'M SO EXHAUSTED FROM TAKING
CARE OF AUBRI.
[Aubri cries]
AND I'M REALLY STARTING TO MISS
HIGH SCHOOL AND ALL MY FRIENDS.
>> HEY.
>> HI.
>> IT'S REALLY GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> I KNOW.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANYBODY
IN, LIKE, FOREVER.
>> OH, GEE, I HAVE TO SEE HER.
DO YOU CARE IF I HOLD HER?
>> MM-MM, HERE.
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
HOW DO YOU LIKE BEING A MOMMY?
>> IT'S A LOT OF WORK.
YOU CAN'T GO OUT AND DO THINGS
WITH PEOPLE OR STAY AT PEOPLE'S
HOUSES ANYMORE.
>> YEAH, THAT KIND OF STINKS.
>> I'M SO SICK OF BEING HERE.
SO I WANT TO GO BACK
TO REGULAR SCHOOLING.
>> WE'RE MAKING THE PIATAS IN
SPANISH RIGHT NOW.
I'M MAKING A FLOWER.
>> OH...
I WANT TO MAKE A PIATA.
>> AH!
>> OH...
YOU WANT HER BACK?
>> NO.
I HAVE HER 24-7.
YOU CAN HOLD HER.
SITTING IN A ROOM WITH
A COMPUTER AND A BABY ALL DAY
IS NOT WHAT I THOUGHT
HIGH SCHOOL WOULD BE LIKE.
IT'S EXHAUSTING, BUT NATHAN
IS STAYING OVER TONIGHT,
SO I'M HOPING I'LL GET
SOME SLEEP.
GO TURN THE LIGHTS OUT.
>> I'M NOT TURNING THEM OFF.
>> TURN THEM OUT!
>> NO.
>> COME ON...
>> I'LL TURN THAT ONE OUT.
>> JUST TURN THE LIGHTS OUT.
NATHAN, IT'S NOT SO HARD
OR NOTHING.
>> NO.
>> SHE'LL PROBABLY GET UP AT
ABOUT 3:00, SO REMEMBER,
IT'S YOUR TURN.
AND DON'T JUST SHOVE A BINKI
BACK IN HER MOUTH.
>> IS THERE ANY BOTTLES
IN THERE?
>> NO.
>> WELL, GO GET THE BOTTLE
AT LEAST.
>> UH-UH.
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE GETTING THE BOTTLE.
>> I'M SLEEPING.
>> GO GET THE FRICKIN' BOTTLE.
YOU DON'T DO ANYTHING, SEE?
>> IT'S NOT MY TURN.
>> THAT DOESN'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING WITH THE TURN.
JUST GO GET--
>> PREPARE YOUR SANCTUARY.
>> [sighs]
>> YOU ALWAYS TRY TO HAVE ME
DO EVERYTHING, AND I AIN'T
DOING NOTHING.
>> OH, MY GOD, NATHAN.
YOU DO THINGS--
>> IT'S NOT THAT HARD
TO GO GET A BOTTLE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO IT,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT MY TURN.
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE LAZY.
>> NATHAN, GO GET IT.
OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE SO
FRICKIN' IRRITATING.
YOU CAN'T EVEN FRICKIN' GET UP
AND GET A STUPID BOTTLE.
[clattering]
[bottles banging]
>> CHILL OUT.
YOU'RE GONNA WAKE THE BABY UP.
>> SHUT UP.
[door slams]
>> THINGS HAVE BEEN GETTING
PRETTY TENSE WITH ME AND NATHAN
LATELY, AND WITH HIM GOING
TO HIGH SCHOOL WHILE I'M STUCK
AT HOME, I'M GETTING EVEN MORE
FRUSTRATED.
>> LOOK, WE JUST GOT TO FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT IF YOU DO WANT
TO GET BACK.
>> I WOULD, IF I HAD THE MONEY
TO PAY FOR A BABYSITTER.
>> IF YOU HAD THE MONEY
GO GET YOU A JOB TOO.
>> WHY CAN'T YOU GET A JOB?
>> I'M TRYING.
NOBODY CALLS BACK.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD JUST
TRADE PLACES.
>> NO.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE,
AND THEN I WANT TO BE A NURSE.
YOU JUST WANT TO BE AROUND
PEOPLE ALL THE TIME.
>> NO, I JUST GOT TO GO
TO SCHOOL, 'CAUSE I GOT TO
GRADUATE.
>> SO?
>> AND I WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO DO HOMESCHOOLING.
>> YOU COULD IF YOU TRIED.
YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO TRY.
SAY, "BYE."
[Aubri fussing]
I WISH I WOULD HAVE PUT UP
MORE OF A FIGHT FOR NATHAN
TO DO HOMESCHOOL, BECAUSE THIS
REALLY SUCKS.
EW, YOU STINK LIKE PEE.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO GET
ANY WORK DONE WHEN YOU PEE
AND POOP ALL THE TIME?
THAT'S ALL YOU DO:
PEE, POOP, AND EAT.
IT'S OBVIOUS THAT I'VE BEEN
HAVING A HARD TIME DOING SO MUCH
ON MY OWN, AND MY FAMILY
IS STARTING TO GET WORRIED.
>> SO HOW ARE THINGS
WITH NATHAN?
>> HE GETS ON MY NERVES.
HE LIKES TO BE ANNOYING,
AND HE FRUSTRATES ME.
>> WHAT THINGS DOES HE NOT DO
THAT YOU WANT HIM TO DO?
>> LIKE, NOT COMPLAIN ABOUT
RANDOM STUFF, LIKE,
"OH, SHE WON'T BE QUIET."
OR, "OH, SHE'S ALWAYS HUNGRY."
LIKE, I'M SICK OF BEING THE ONE
THAT HAS TO DO EVERYTHING
AND THE ONE WHO ALWAYS SEEMS
LIKE THE BAD GUY.
>> THEN YOU NEED TO TELL HIM
THAT.
NATHAN NEEDS TO STEP UP.
HE NEEDS TO DO THE FEEDINGS.
HE NEEDS TO DO THE CHANGING.
HE NEEDS TO STEP UP
AND BE A BETTER DAD.
AND YOU NEED TO BE ASSERTIVE
AND SAY, "LISTEN, YOU NEED
TO STEP UP A LITTLE MORE WHEN"--
>> WHEN I SAY THAT, HE SAYS,
"WELL, WE TAKE TURNS."
IT'S LIKE--
>> THERE SHOULDN'T BE TURNS.
IT SHOULD BE--
>> IF THERE'S NOT TURNS,
I END UP DOING IT 10,000 TIMES,
SO I MADE UP TURNS.
>> OKAY, WELL, THEN THERE HAS
TO BE TURNS WITH HIM.
>> YOU ALL ARE BEING VERY
CHILDISH.
>> BUT THEN AGAIN, YOU ALSO HAVE
TO UNDERSTAND; THEY'RE 15
AND 16 YEARS OLD.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT,
BUT THEY PUT THEMSELVES
IN THIS POSITION.
>> WE TEND TO FORGET THAT,
THAT THEY'RE STILL TEENAGERS.
>> RIGHT.
>> I NEED NATHAN TO START
DOING MORE, BUT I'M GETTING
NERVOUS HE'S NOT WILLING
TO CHANGE.
>> YOU ACT LIKE I DON'T HELP.
>> SHH!
[whispering] QUIT YELLING.
>> SHUT UP.
>> QUIT YELLING.
IF YOU WAKE HER UP--
>> YOU ACT LIKE I DON'T HELP.
>> YOU HELP, BUT YOU DO IT ONLY
WHEN IT'S YOUR TURN.
AFTER YOU FEED HER, IT'S LIKE,
"I'M NOT DEALING WITH HER."
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
I DO EVERYTHING AROUND HERE.
EVERY TIME--LIKE, IF I--
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> YEAH, I DO.
YOU ASK ME TO DO SOMETHING--
>> YOU TAKE OUT TRASH.
>> SHUT UP.
>> YOU ACT LIKE IT'S SUCH
A HARD JOB.
LIKE, I WOULD RATHER
TAKE OUT TRASH.
>> ARE YOU STUPID?
>> THE THING IS, MOST OF
THE DAY, I TAKE CARE OF HER,
AND JUST BECAUSE I ASK YOU TO
GET ME ONE THING DOESN'T MEAN--
>> I DO STUFF FOR YOU
ALL DAY LONG.
>> OKAY, BUT IT'S FOR AUBRI
MOST OF THE TIME.
>> IT'S ALWAYS SOMETHING
WITH YOU.
>> BECAUSE YOU FRUSTRATE ME.
>> SEE, IT'S ME.
>> YOU FRUSTRATE ME.
>> YOU FRUSTRATE YOURSELF.
>> NO, YOU FRUSTRATE ME.
THIS RIGHT HERE IS
FRUSTRATING ME.
I'M GOING TO BED.
GIVE ME MY PILLOW.
thump!
whap!
>> GOD, YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
>> MY MOM OVERHEARD OUR FIGHT
LAST NIGHT AND IS FINALLY
FED UP.
>> YOU KNOW, ALL TAYLOR
IS ASKING FOR IS HELP.
YOU BITCH, YOU KNOW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO YOUR SHARE.
>> WHO SAYS I DIDN'T?
I ALWAYS DO.
>> SHE DOES!
YOU'RE HERE, BUT YOU'RE NOT.
>> I DO HELP.
WE SHARE LIKE WE'RE SUPPOSED TO.
>> BUT YOU COMPLAIN ABOUT IT.
I DON'T SIT THERE AND COMPLAIN
ABOUT IT AND WAKE YOU UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
"PUT A BIB ON HER!"
I DON'T SIT THERE AND DO THAT.
>> YOU GET UP.
YOU DO YOUR SHARE.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO DO IT
BY YOURSELF.
SHE DOESN'T NEED TO PUT
A BIB ON THE BABY.
YOU DON'T NEED TO GO
TO THE BATHROOM RIGHT AWAY.
FEED THE BABY.
THEN DO WHAT YOU NEED--
DO YOUR BUSINESS.
YOU DON'T NEED HER TO GET UP.
THAT'S WHY SHE ASKED YOU
TO HELP, SO THAT SHE CAN
STAY IN BED AND SLEEP.
THIS ISN'T EASY FOR ANYONE,
NATHAN.
>> EVERY TIME WE TALK,
YOU SIT HERE AND YELL AT ME,
AND IT'S LIKE--
>> NO.
>> YES, YOU DO.
>> 'CAUSE SHE GETS ATTITUDES.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE MEAN TO ME!
>> OKAY.
>> YOU ARE MEAN TO HER, NATHAN.
>> YOU SHOULD SEE HOW SHE TREATS
ME WHEN YOU'RE NOT AROUND.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE MEAN TO ME.
IF YOU WERE NICE, YOU WOULD GET
THE SAME RESPECT BACK.
WHY SHOULD I SIT HERE
AND BE NICE TO YOU
WHEN YOU DON'T EVEN--
>> EVEN WHEN I DO TRY TO BE
NICE, YOU STILL GET ATTITUDE.
>> I CAN'T HAVE THIS.
I CANNOT LIVE LIKE THIS.
>> HE COMPLAINS ABOUT
EVERYTHING, THOUGH.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
>> THIS SITUATION IS
OUT OF CONTROL, AND I WILL NOT
HAVE IT, PERIOD.
I'M NOT LIVING LIKE THIS.
YOU HAVE AN ATTITUDE PROBLEM.
THIS WHOLE SITUATION
IS WHY I SAID THAT CHILD NEEDED
TO BE PUT UP FOR ADOPTION.
IT WASN'T 'CAUSE I DIDN'T LOVE
HER, AND IT WASN'T BECAUSE
I DIDN'T LOVE YOU TWO.
IT'S THE FACT THAT KIDS
SHOULD NOT HAVE KIDS,
'CAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW HOW
TO HANDLE SITUATIONS YET.
>> EVEN THOUGH MY MOM HAS HAD
ENOUGH OF NATHAN, I'M NOT READY
TO GIVE UP ON HIM.
I WANT TO GIVE HIM ONE MORE
CHANCE TO DO THIS TOGETHER.
OKAY, WE'RE GONNA SIT HERE
AND TALK, AND WE'RE NOT GONNA
CALL EACH OTHER NAMES.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA YELL AT ME.
I'M NOT GONNA YELL AT YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M UP 24-7 WITH THIS CHILD
WHEN YOU ARE NOT HERE.
>> THAT DOESN'T MEAN NOTHING.
>> SO I'M HOME ALONE WITH HER
ALL THE TIME.
>> YOU ACT LIKE I'M NEVER THERE.
I'M THERE ALL THE TIME.
>> OKAY, BEING THERE
AND HELPING OUT ARE JUST
TWO DIFFERENT THINGS.
>> WHEN I'M THERE, I DO HELP,
AND YOU ACT LIKE I DON'T.
>> I HAVE TO FORCE YOU.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> YOU SHOULD JUST BE ABLE
TO DO IT.
I'M THE ONE WHO GIVES HER BATHS.
I'M THE ONE WHO FEEDS HER.
BASICALLY WHAT I'M SAYING IS,
YOU OWE IT TO HER TO BE
A GOOD FATHER, AND YOU OWE IT
TO ME TO BE A GOOD BOYFRIEND.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
NOT TO HAVE A DAD; WE BOTH DO.
BUT ALLS WE DO IS SIT HERE
AND FIGHT, OR YOU'RE MAD AT ME,
OR YOU WANT TO BE MEAN
AND HATEFUL TOWARDS ME.
>> WELL, EVERYBODY THINKS
IT'S ALWAYS ME.
IT'S ALWAYS THE GUY
IN TAYLOR AND DEBI'S WORLD.
>> OKAY, THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH MY MOM.
I TRY TO KEEP US TOGETHER.
YOU--WE STAY--I THINK THE ONLY
REASON WE STAY TOGETHER IS
A LITTLE BIT OF LOVE
AND BECAUSE OF HER.
>> IS THAT REALLY THE REASON?
>> I'M SURE IF WE DIDN'T
HAVE A KID, WE WOULD STILL BE
KIND OF HAPPY AND IN LA-LA LAND
AND TEENAGERS, BUT...
>> YOU GUYS EXPECT ME NOT TO BE
STRESSED OUT, PUTTING ALL THIS
FRICKIN' STRUGGLE ON ME.
>> AND I'M NOT STRESSED?
>> WHAT ARE YOU STRESSED ABOUT?
YOU AIN'T GOT TO GET A JOB.
YOU AIN'T GOT TO GET
ALL THIS CRAP TO SUPPORT
AND ALL THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU STRESSED ABOUT?
>> US.
US.
IF SHE'S GONNA HAVE A FATHER,
IF I'M GONNA HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH NATHAN
IS HARDER NOW, 'CAUSE NOW WE'RE
KIND OF STUCK WITH EACH OTHER.
IT'S LIKE AN OLD MARRIED COUPLE
OR SOMETHING.
IT SUCKS.
GO WASH IT OFF.
>> YOU WASH IT OFF.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I BET IF WE DIDN'T HAVE AUBRI,
OUR RELATIONSHIP MIGHT BE
A LITTLE BIT BETTER
AND NOT SO HARD,
BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH MOODY.
WE'RE BOTH TIRED.
WE'RE JUST--WE JUST WANT
OUR TEEN YEARS BACK,
SO IT GETS--IT JUST PUTS
A STRAIN ON IT.
LEAVE IT.
OH, MY GOD, STOP.
YOU'RE BEING ANNOYING.
I DON'T WANT AUBRI GROWING UP
WITHOUT A DAD, 'CAUSE ME AND HIM
BOTH KNOW HOW IT FEELS.
THAT ONE LOOKS KIND OF GOOD,
ACTUALLY.
HERE, LET'S DO ONE MORE,
JUST IN CASE.
AND I DON'T WANT HER JUST
TO HAVE THAT CONSTANT PAIN
THAT WE BOTH HAVE, AND IT'S JUST
NOT FUN GROWING UP WITHOUT
TWO PARENTS.
>> THERE, YOU AIN'T KICKING
THEM OFF.
>> BUT IF HE DOESN'T TAKE
THE RIGHT STEPS TO BECOME
A BETTER DAD, THEN HE CAN'T
BE AROUND AUBRI.
IT MAKES ME SAD THAT NATHAN
GETS TO GET UP AND GO TO SCHOOL
EVERY DAY, 'CAUSE EVERYBODY SAYS
HIGH SCHOOL IS THE BEST THING
EVER, BUT I'M MISSING OUT
ON THAT EXPERIENCE,
AND I FEEL OLD.
>> IT'S HARD TO TAKE CARE
OF A BABY AND BE A TEENAGER.
>> IT'S HARD WHEN I KNOW
MY FRIENDS ARE OUT HAVING FUN,
AND I'M STUCK AT HOME
WITH AUBRI.
BUT I DON'T EVER REGRET
HAVING AUBRI.
I JUST REGRET HAVING HER SO
YOUNG AND NOT HAVING THE STUFF
I NEED TO TAKE CARE OF HER
AND JUST MISSING OUT ON
MY TEEN YEARS.
THAT'S THE BIGGEST PART,
AND IT'S THE SADDEST PART.
EW, IT'S UP HER BACK, NATHAN.
HOLD HER LEGS.
>> OH!
>> OH, MY GOD.
I THINK THERE'S GONNA BE MORE
HARD TIMES BUT HOPEFULLY MORE
GOOD TIMES THAN BAD.
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW.
IT'S LIFE, SO YOU JUST
GOT TO DEAL WITH IT.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> I KNOW IT'S YOUR MOM,
BUT DO YOU KNOW HOW SHE GETS
ANGRY?
>> I WANT HER OUT.
YOU'RE NOT TO SET FOOT
IN MY [bleep] HOUSE!
YOU BITCH!
smack!
>> I'M NOT EVEN GONNA GRADUATE
IF WE STAY OVER THERE.
>> GET YOUR [bleep] OUT OF
MY [bleep] HOUSE!
>> I CAN'T JUST LEAVE.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> OH, I'LL GET HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I EVEN ASK.
YOU DON'T HELP.
>> YOU'RE FREAKING UNGRATEFUL!
>> I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
IT'S DONE.
>> WHEN DID WE BECOME SO BROKEN?
>> WHEN YOU STOPPED
TAKING CARE OF AIDEN.
>> 'CAUSE OF THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> [crying]