[laughter]
>> HI, I'M MADDY.
I'M 16 AND LIVE IN TINLEY PARK,
ILLINOIS, OUTSIDE OF CHICAGO.
WE HAVE A FULL HOUSE, WITH MY
MOM, MY BROTHER, KYLE, MY
SISTER, EMILY, AND MY BABY
HALF SISTER, ALYSSA.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED, AND MY
DAD LIVES AN HOUR AWAY IN
INDIANA, BUT WE'RE STILL SUPER
CLOSE.
[giggles]
I'M ABOUT TO START MY JUNIOR
YEAR, AND I PLAY ON ALL THE
SPORTS TEAMS AT SCHOOL.
BUT WHEN I'M NOT ON THE COURT,
I'M GETTING SILLY WITH MY BEST
FRIENDS.
A FEW MONTHS AGO, MY
EX-BOYFRIEND DUMPED ME, AND I
WAS REALLY UPSET, SO I WENT ON
FACEBOOK, LOOKING FOR A REBOUND,
WHEN I MESSAGED CODY.
AFTER KNOWING EACH OTHER FOR
ONLY AN HOUR, WE HOOKED UP.
IT WAS JUST A ONE-TIME THING,
SO WE HAVEN'T BEEN HANGING OUT
SINCE.
BUT NOW HE'S GOING TO BE IN MY
LIFE FOREVER, BECAUSE, AFTER A
ONE-NIGHT STAND, I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
IN TWO MONTHS, I'LL BE HAVING
A BABY GIRL, AND I DECIDED TO
NAME HER AUBREY.
MY PREGNANCY HAS BEEN PRETTY
UNCOMFORTABLE, SO I HAVEN'T HAD
MUCH FUN THIS SUMMER.
BUT TODAY, MY FRIENDS ARE COMING
OVER TO HANG OUT.
>> HEY, MADDY.
>> HI.
>> HEY, MADDY. WHAT'S UP?
>> YOU LOOK SO LITTLE.
>> 'CAUSE I'M WEARING BLACK,
IT LOOKS SO SMALL.
>> YOU LOOK SMALL.
>> I'LL BE EIGHT MONTHS
TOMORROW.
>> THAT'S EXCITING.
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT'S CRAZY.
>> IT WENT BY SO FAST.
>> SERIOUSLY, LIKE, I REMEMBER,
YOU USED TO BE, LIKE, THIS BIG
WITH YOUR SIX-PACK GOING ON,
AND YOU WERE ALL ABOUT SPORTS.
LIKE, IN GYM, YOU DID
EVERYTHING, AND NOW IT'S LIKE--
>> NOW I CAN'T EVEN PLAY ANY
SPORTS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I MEAN, SPORTS WERE MY LIFE.
LIKE, I COULD'VE HAD
A SCHOLARSHIP FOR MY SPORTS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WERE, LIKE, SO SHOCKED.
>> I WASN'T READY FOR A BABY
YET.
>> I KNOW.
>> LIKE, THE WHOLE REASON I'M IN
THIS SITUATION RIGHT NOW IS
BECAUSE I WAS TRYING TO GET OVER
MY EX, AND THEN I SLEEP WITH
CODY ONE TIME AND THIS HAPPENED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HOW DID CODY REACT?
HE HAD TO BE SHOCKED.
>> I MEAN, I WAS IN DENIAL.
JUST LIKE, I BARELY KNOW HIM AND
THEN I'M GOING TO RAISE A BABY
WITH HIM WHEN WE DON'T EVEN--
WE'VE HUNG OUT, LIKE, SIX TIMES?
>> YEAH, TRUE.
>> SO I LITERALLY CALLED HIM,
AND I WAS LIKE, "SO YOU'RE GONNA
BE A FATHER," AND HE'S JUST
LIKE, "WOW."
LIKE, DIDN'T EVEN--LIKE,
HE DIDN'T EVEN CARE.
HE DIDN'T THINK IT WAS HIS
KID.
>> WOW.
>> AND THERE'S NO WAY IT COULD
BE ANYONE ELSE'S.
>> YEAH, WHO ELSE--
>> BUT HE JUST DIDN'T WANT IT TO
BE HIS.
>> SERIOUSLY? WOW.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE COMING
TO MY DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT WITH
ME THIS WEEK, THE FIRST ONE HE'S
EVER BEEN TO, BUT I DON'T SEE IT
HAPPENING.
SO...
IT'S JUST REALLY STRESSFUL.
HAVE YOU GUYS GOTTEN USED TO THE
FACT THAT I'M PREGNANT YET?
>> I MEAN, IT'S STILL WEIRD,
BUT...
>> KIND OF HAVE TO ACCEPT IT.
I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO BE
A GOOD MOM, THOUGH.
>> I DO TOO 'CAUSE THE WAY I AM
WITH ALYSSA.
I'M SURE CODY'S, LIKE,
FREAKING OUT.
HE'S NEVER MET KYLE OR EMILY.
HE DOESN'T EVEN REALLY KNOW YOU,
MOM.
>> WHOSE FAULT IS THAT?
>> I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU SAY
TO ME?
LIKE, "HI, I GOT YOUR SISTER
PREGNANT"?
LIKE, "NICE TO MEET YOU"?
>> KYLE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY, WE GOT TO GET
TO KNOW HIM, RIGHT?
HE'S GONNA BE PART OF
EVERYBODY'S LIFE.
>> CODY'S HERE.
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> YOU GUYS READY?
>> YEP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU EXCITED?
>> YEAH.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER IN A LONG
TIME.
>> OKAY, LET ME TURN THE LIGHTS
OFF.
>> IT'S SO COLD.
>> THERE WE GO.
SO THERE'S THE BABY'S HEAD.
SO HER FACE IS RIGHT HERE.
OKAY?
>> IS SHE FACE--
HEAD DOWN ALREADY?
>> YEAH, SHE'S HEAD DOWN.
>> WOW.
>> GOOD GIRL.
HERE'S KIND OF THE HAND.
HERE'S THE NOSE.
>> YOU SEE YOURSELF IN THERE?
BECAUSE SHE LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE
YOU.
>> THERE'S THE CHIN.
ALL RIGHT, SO YOUR NEXT
APPOINTMENT IS GONNA BE IN TWO
WEEKS, SO GO AHEAD AND SCHEDULE
THAT UP FRONT.
IT'S GOOD.
CONGRATULATIONS AGAIN.
EXCITED?
>> YEAH. IT'S CRAZY.
>> IT MAKES IT A LITTLE BIT MORE
REAL, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M HAPPY CODY FINALLY SEEMS
EXCITED TO BE A DAD.
SHE'S KICKING.
>> OH, I FELT THAT ONE.
>> I DIDN'T FEEL ANYTHING
THAT TIME.
>> I DID.
I SEEN IT TOO.
[both chuckle]
IT'S CRAZY.
TIME'S FLYING.
>> FOR YOU, BECAUSE YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN THERE THE WHOLE TIME.
DIFFERENT FOR ME.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN PREGNANT
FOR, LIKE, 12 YEARS.
>> [chuckles]
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT WERE YOU GLAD
I WAS THERE FOR THE FIRST TIME
AT THE DOCTOR'S?
>> YEAH, IT MEANS A LOT TO ME
AND THE BABY THAT YOU'RE THERE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO MISS
ANYTHING ELSE.
>> I KNOW.
I DON'T WANT TO MISS ANYTHING
ELSE EITHER.
I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T BE IN THIS
SITUATION.
I SHOULD'VE LISTENED IN HEALTH
CLASS A LITTLE MORE.
I SHOULD'VE USED A CONDOM.
>> YEAH, PROBABLY.
DON'T THEY SHOW YOU HOW TO PUT
ON A CONDOM IN HEALTH CLASS?
>> THEY DON'T, LIKE, DO IT,
THOUGH.
>> THEY DON'T DO IT FOR YOU,
YEAH, I HOPE SO.
>> NO, I MEAN, LIKE, I DIDN'T,
LIKE--I PUT IT ON, AND YOU SAID
IT WAS ON WRONG, SO...
>> 'CAUSE YOU KEPT SAYING, "OW."
WHO SAYS "OW" PUTTING ON
A CONDOM?
I'VE NEVER HEARD THAT BEFORE.
I DON'T KNOW... [laughs]
BUT IT'S GOOD THAT YOU'RE
ACTUALLY GOING TO THINGS NOW
AND, LIKE, STEPPING UP.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> I WANT AUBREY TO HAVE BOTH
HER PARENTS IN HER LIFE,
BUT IT'S GOING TO TAKE SOME TIME
TO FIGURE OUT IF THERE'S
ANYTHING MORE BETWEEN US.
WITH MY DUE DATE LESS THAN TWO
MONTHS AWAY, MY MOM WANTS TO GO
OVER THE PLAN FOR AFTER THE
BIRTH.
>> IT'S HARD FOR ME TO SEE MY
BABY WITH A BABY INSIDE HER.
I JUST BECAME A MOM AGAIN THREE
MONTHS AGO.
I'M NOT READY TO BE CALLED
A GRANDMA YET.
I'LL NEVER FORGET THE WAY YOU
TOLD ME,
FOR YOU TO TEXT ME TO COME
UPSTAIRS 'CAUSE YOU HAD
TO TALK TO ME.
>> BUT I TOLD YOU IN PERSON.
>> AND WHEN I CAME UPSTAIRS,
WHAT WAS MY FIRST WORDS?
"YOU BETTER NOT TELL ME
YOU'RE PREGNANT."
AND WHAT'D YOU SAY TO ME?
>> "SORRY."
>> "I'M SO SORRY, MOM."
IT'S A LOT OF WORK, MADISON.
>> I KNOW.
>> I JUST THINK YOU'RE TOO YOUNG
FOR THIS.
I THINK YOUR WHOLE LIFE IS...
DONE.
ALL THE PLANS THAT YOU HAD FOR
YOUR FUTURE, BEING A LAWYER,
DOING INTERIOR DESIGN,
DO YOU STILL PLAN ON DOING ANY
OF THAT?
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE TRYING TO,
LIKE, SCARE ME MORE THAN
I SHOULD BE.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO SCARE YOU.
I'M TRYING TO PREPARE YOU.
THIS IS A LOT OF WORK.
>> I KNOW THAT, BUT YOU MAKE IT
SOUND SO NEGATIVE.
>> IT'S NEGATIVE WHEN YOU'RE 16.
YOU DON'T HAVE A JOB.
YOU'RE JUST SUPPOSED TO BE
STARTING YOUR JUNIOR YEAR IN
SCHOOL.
>> CODY HAS A JOB.
>> HIS FAST-FOOD RESTAURANT JOB?
>> [sniffles]
YOU MAKE IT SEEM LIKE MY LIFE
IS, LIKE, RUINED.
>> I FEEL THAT IT IS.
>> IT'S NOT.
JUST 'CAUSE I'M HAVING A BABY
DOESN'T MEAN EVERYTHING IS
RUINED AND THAT I CAN'T DO WHAT
I WANTED TO DO.
>> IT'S GONNA BE A LONG TIME
BEFORE YOU CAN DO WHAT YOU WANT
TO DO.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> EVERYTHING'S CHANGED NOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> MADISON, I'VE TOLD YOU FROM
DAY ONE THAT I WOULD ALWAYS KICK
YOU OUT IF YOU EVER GOT PREGNANT
AT 16.
>> YEAH, WELL, THINGS HAPPEN,
MOM.
THINGS CHANGE.
>> I'M GIVING YOU A MONTH TO
STAY HERE AFTER THE BABY'S BORN,
BECAUSE THAT'S THE HARDEST TIME.
BUT AFTER THAT, YOU HAVE TO GO.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THERE'S NO ROOM, AND
IT'S NOT FAIR TO EVERYBODY ELSE
IN THE HOUSE.
WE HAVE TO GO WITH OUR OTHER
OPTIONS, AND THAT'S EITHER YOU
GOING DOWN TO LIVE WITH CODY
OR GOING DOWN TO LIVE
WITH YOUR DAD.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO TO CODY'S
OR DAD'S.
CODY AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW EACH
OTHER, AND THEN I'M GONNA HAVE
TO LIVE WITH HIM WITH A BABY?
>> MADISON, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO
TELL YOU.
I DON'T HAVE THE ROOM FOR YOU.
>> YOU CAN MAKE ROOM.
>> I CAN'T.
THAT WOULD BE SEVEN PEOPLE IN
THIS HOUSE.
MADISON, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO
CHOSE TO GROW UP SO FAST.
>> I DIDN'T CHOOSE TO GET
PREGNANT AT THIS AGE, MOM.
I DIDN'T PLAN IT.
BUT I CAN'T TAKE IT BACK.
[sniffles]
>> [sighs]
>> IT REALLY SUCKS THAT MY MOM
IS KICKING ME OUT OF THE
HOUSE...
[knock at door]
SO CODY'S COMING OVER TODAY TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
>> HEY.
>> HI.
IT'S REALLY MESSY.
>> YOUR BELLY BUTTON, LIKE--
>> NO, DO YOU WANT TO SEE IT?
I KNOW YOU LOVE IT SO MUCH.
LOOK AT HOW GROSS IT LOOKS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THERE'S A BABY IN THERE.
MY MOM BASICALLY SAID I CAN ONLY
LIVE WITH HER UNTIL A MONTH
AFTER THE BABY'S BORN.
>> WHAT?
>> SO I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
I'M GONNA DO AFTER THAT.
>> HOW AM I GONNA LIVE WITH YOU
AND, LIKE, SLEEP IN A SAME BED
AS YOU AND STUFF WHEN WE'RE NOT
TOGETHER?
>> I'LL SLEEP ON THE FLOOR.
>> I'M JUST SO STRESSED.
>> I KNOW.
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN.
>> I CAN'T.
NOTHING IS READY OR, LIKE, 100%,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> I JUST--I DON'T KNOW.
I WISH I COULD TAKE EVERYTHING
BACK, BUT I REALLY CAN'T.
IT'S GONNA WORK OUT.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW THAT, THOUGH.
>> I DO KNOW THAT.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS BY MYSELF,
CODY.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO.
WHEN I GET HOME, I'M GONNA TALK
TO MY PARENTS ABOUT YOU MOVING
IN.
MY MOM COULD BABYSIT.
SHE WOULD LOVE IT.
>> EVEN THOUGH I BARELY KNOW
CODY, I'M LEANING TOWARDS MOVING
IN WITH HIM.
BUT WHEN I TOLD MY DAD, HE DROVE
AN HOUR FROM INDIANA SO WE COULD
TALK.
>> HELLO.
TWO, PLEASE.
>> SURE.
AND SHE'LL BE WITH YOU
IN JUST A MOMENT, OKAY?
>> OKAY, THANKS.
>> ENJOY.
>> THANK YOU.
SO YOU'RE MOVING INTO A KID'S
HOUSE THAT YOU'VE ONLY KNOWN FOR
HOW LONG?
>> NINE MONTHS.
I'M NINE MONTHS PREGNANT, AND
I'VE KNOWN HIM FOR NINE MONTHS.
>> IT'S NOT WHAT I HOPED WOULD
HAPPEN FOR YA.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU THINK YOU DO, BUT YOU
DON'T.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A DIFFICULT
THING, AND YOU'LL SEE.
IN A FEW WEEKS, YOU'LL REALLY
SEE.
I MEAN, MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS,
RUINED YOUR LIFE.
AND I DON'T KNOW THE KID.
>> YEAH, WELL, I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING IN HIM.
IT'S JUST, I DON'T WANT MY
DAUGHTER TO GROW UP WITHOUT HER
DAD.
>> NO, AND IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
THE DAD BE, YOU KNOW, AROUND.
>> THAT'S THE ONLY THING.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
I'M GOING THERE.
I'M STILL TALKING TO HIM.
BUT WE'RE NOT, LIKE, TOGETHER,
SO...
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE DOWN THERE,
BUT I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A CHOICE.
I MEAN, I NEED HIS MOM TO BE
ABLE TO BABYSIT SO I CAN GO TO
SCHOOL AND WORK AND STUFF
SO I CAN EVENTUALLY MOVE OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> SO...
>> YOU'RE WELCOME TO MOVE IN
WITH US.
>> OH, I KNOW, BUT MY FRIENDS
ARE GONNA BE FAR AWAY.
I'M NOT EVEN GONNA GET TO SEE
THEM.
SO I THINK I SHOULD TRY GOING TO
CODY'S HOUSE.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW IT'S
GONNA WORK.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
AT ALL.
I KNOW IT'S RISKY TO MOVE IN
WITH CODY, BUT I REALLY THINK
IT'S THE BEST OPTION FOR ME AND
AUBREY.
I HAVE NO IDEA IF LIVING WITH
CODY IS GOING TO WORK OUT OR
NOT, BUT HE AND HIS FAMILY ARE
COMING OVER TONIGHT TO DISCUSS
THE DETAILS.
[knock at door]
YOU CAN COME IN.
>> HELLO.
I'M JENNIFER, MADISON'S MOM.
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> SO ARE YOU GUYS OKAY WITH HER
MOVING IN A MONTH AFTER THE
BABY'S BORN?
>> I'M OKAY IF SHE WANTED TO
MOVE IN NOW.
>> [laughs]
>> HONESTLY, I MEAN, WHATEVER
SHE WANTS TO DO.
>> I MEAN, I KIND OF HAVE TO.
>> IT'S NOT AN OPTION WITH HER
STAYING HERE, AND SHE DOESN'T
WANT TO GO TO HER DAD'S.
IT'S FAR.
>> IF SHE IS GONNA COME, WE CAN
TURN THE DINING ROOM INTO THE
BABY'S ROOM.
SO IT'S NOT HUGE, BUT IT'LL BE
A BEDROOM FOR HER.
>> AND YOU GUYS ARE READY TO
JUST DO THAT, NO PROBLEMS?
>> NO PROBLEMS.
MORE THAN WELCOME TO COME STAY
WITH US.
>> THEY JUST NEED TO SAVE THEIR
MONEY, YOU KNOW, JUST PUT THEIR
MONEY AWAY SO THEY--
>> I MEAN, I THINK THERE'S
ALREADY, LIKE, OBSTACLES IN THE
WAY FOR THEM MOVING IN TOGETHER,
AS FAR AS--WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
THEY HARDLY KNOW EACH OTHER.
>> YES.
>> BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THEY'RE
NOT GOING NOT GOING TO WORK OR,
YOU KNOW...
>> IT DEPENDS ON THEM, IF THEY
WANTED TO MAKE IT WORK.
>> RIGHT.
>> I MEAN, ARE YOU WANTING TO BE
WITH MADDY?
>> YEAH.
>> OR ARE YOU WANTING TO BE--
>> YEAH, I WANT TO BE WITH
MADDY, BUT I DON'T KNOW IF SHE
WANTS THAT.
BUT THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE NEED TO GET TO
KNOW EACH OTHER MORE BEFORE THE
BABY'S HERE.
>> RIGHT, WHICH IS
UNDERSTANDABLE, AND I THINK HE
KNOWS THAT.
>> BUT EVEN IF I WASN'T WITH
CODY, I'D STILL LIVE THERE.
>> SEE, SHE THINKS THAT SHE'D BE
ABLE TO DO THAT.
WOULD YOU HONESTLY--WOULD YOU BE
ABLE TO DO THAT?
>> AND YOU'D SLEEP IN THE SAME
BED TOGETHER?
>> YEAH.
>> NO, I HAVE A BED.
I COULD BRING MY BED.
>> AND YOU'RE ALL GONNA FIT IN
HIS LITTLE ROOM?
>> THE BABY WILL HAVE HER OWN
ROOM.
>> WELL...
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE EXTREMELY
HARD.
>> IT WILL.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M MOVING IN
WITH CODY, I'M NOT SURE
HOW I FEEL ABOUT HIM.
[chime dings]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU NEED TO GET READY FOR
SCHOOL.
>> TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY OF MY
JUNIOR YEAR.
AND WITH EVERYTHING GOING ON,
I REALLY DON'T FEEL UP TO IT.
[laughs]
>> ARE YOU EXCITED TO BE GOING
BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
>> WHY?
>> WHY WOULD I BE?
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOUR FRIENDS?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE EVERYONE
ELSE.
>> WHY?
>> MOM, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> WHY WOULD YOU LET IT BOTHER
YOU?
YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL.
YOU'RE DOING A GOOD THING.
>> WHY AM I CRYING RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS RIGHT
NOW.
I DON'T WHY I'M--
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS.
>> ARE YOU JUST UPSET 'CAUSE
YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL?
>> NO, I DON'T WANT TO SIT IN
THAT CHAIR AND BE--MY LEGS ARE
GONNA HURT.
>> THE DOCTOR DIDN'T SAY YOU
COULD MISS SCHOOL, THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
I JUST DON'T EVEN WANT TO GO.
>> YOU KNOW THIS IS IMPORTANT
FOR YOU TO STAY CURRENT SO YOU
DON'T HAVE TO GET A G.E.D.
OR DROP OUT.
>> I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY I'M DOING IT.
I KNOW.
>> IT'S ONLY ONE SEMESTER.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, YOU GET YOUR
STUFF TOGETHER, 'CAUSE WE GOT TO
GET GOING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'LL WAIT FOR YOU OUT HERE.
AS IF GOING TO SCHOOL EIGHT
MONTHS PREGNANT ISN'T BAD
ENOUGH, AS I EXPECTED, SITTING
THROUGH CLASS ALL DAY WAS SUPER
PAINFUL.
I FELT LIKE I WAS GONNA POP,
AND EVERYONE KEPT STARING AT ME.
BUT THINGS GOT BETTER AFTER
SCHOOL WHEN I MET UP WITH MY
SOFTBALL FRIENDS.
>> DO YOU GUYS REMEMBER WHEN WE
ALL PLAYED TOGETHER?
I MISS THAT.
>> I WISH WE STILL COULD.
WE WERE THE WHOLE TEAM.
>> SO TRUE.
>> SO BAD.
>> MADDY, ARE YOU GETTING TIRED?
>> YEAH, MY LEGS ARE TIRED.
CAN'T STAND UP FOR THAT LONG.
>> WE SHOULD PROBABLY GO IN.
>> I'M DONE.
DON'T WANT TO SIT ON THAT THING.
LOOK AT MY STRETCH MARKS ON MY
STOMACH.
YOU CAN, LIKE, FEEL THE CREASES,
AND IT'S GROSS, AND THEY'RE NOT
GONNA GO AWAY.
>> THEY'RE, LIKE--OH, MY GOSH.
>> I KNOW.
I USED TO HAVE ABS THERE INSTEAD
OF STRETCH MARKS.
BUT ONE DAY, THEY'LL BE BACK,
AND THEN I'LL JUST HAVE, LIKE,
TIGER STRIPES.
>> YEAH, YOU'LL LOOK LIKE
A TIGER.
>> YEAH, WELL...
>> WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN WHEN YOU
HAVE AUBREY?
ARE YOU GONNA STAY IN SCHOOL,
OR...
>> THEY WANT ME TO GO BACK SIX
WEEKS AFTER SHE'S BORN.
LIKE, SHE'S NOT EVEN
TWO MONTHS OLD.
>> THAT'S SO SOON.
>> YEAH, SO I DON'T--
>> YEAH.
>> I'M LEANING TOWARDS ONLINE
CLASSES.
>> YEAH.
[cell phone tone plays]
>> HELLO?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> SITTING AT THE BASEBALL FIELD
WITH AUTUMN AND JEANELL.
>> NOW IS NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WE'RE, LIKE, A MARRIED
COUPLE, BASICALLY,
EXCEPT WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
WE'VE NEVER BEEN ON A DATE.
>> REALLY?
>> THE ONLY TIME WE EVER LEFT
HIS HOUSE WAS WHEN WE WENT TO GO
BUY A PREGNANCY TEST.
[laughter]
>> WELL, THAT'S A DATE.
>> YEAH, I PAID FOR IT.
>> WOW, THAT'S CRAZY.
>> IT'S BAD.
I'M NINE MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND WE'VE NEVER BEEN ON A DATE,
AND I'M MOVING IN WITH HIM.
I DON'T KNOW HOW IT'S GONNA GO,
THOUGH.
LIKE, HE'S REALLY, LIKE, STEPPED
UP, AND HE'S TRYING TO, LIKE,
BE THERE FOR ME.
>> I MEAN, I THINK YOU DESERVE
AT LEAST ONE DATE.
>> YEAH.
WE GOT TO GET IT OVER WITH NOW,
I FEEL LIKE, 'CAUSE WE'RE NOT
GONNA HAVE TIME TO GO OUT ONCE
SHE'S HERE.
BUT HE EXPECTS US TO BE
TOGETHER.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I FEEL BAD SAYING IT, BUT
IT'S JUST LIKE--I FEEL LIKE,
JUST 'CAUSE WE HAVE A KID, LIKE,
EVERYONE ASSUMES THAT WE HAVE TO
BE TOGETHER.
[chime dings]
I FEEL LIKE A HOBO.
[laughs]
NO, BUT I DON'T REALLY CARE
EITHER.
I MEAN, WHO DO I GOT TO IMPRESS?
I'M ALREADY PREGNANT.
OW.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I DIDN'T REALLY EXPECT, YOU
KNOW, TO BE PREGNANT BEFORE WE
WENT ON A SINGLE DATE.
>> YEAH.
>> IT PROBABLY DOESN'T LOOK GOOD
FOR EITHER OF US.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT OH, WELL.
>> SO SINCE WE'RE ON A DATE NOW,
DOES THAT MEAN, LIKE, WE'RE
GETTING CLOSER TO DATING, OR...
>> IT'S A STEP TOWARDS THAT,
BUT WE'RE NOT TOGETHER STILL.
>> YEAH, BUT HOW DO YOU THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK WITH US, LIKE,
LIVING TOGETHER AND NOT BEING
TOGETHER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I'M NOT CONCERNED WITH
US RIGHT NOW.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE EITHER.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, IT'S GONNA
CHANGE MY ATTITUDE TOWARDS A LOT
OF THINGS.
>> IT SHOULDN'T CHANGE YOUR
ATTITUDE ABOUT BEING THERE FOR
YOUR DAUGHTER.
ALL THAT MATTERS IS HER.
WE'RE JUST BOTH GONNA RAISE HER.
>> YEAH.
WELL, IT'S GONNA BE MY LAST
NAME, RIGHT?
>> WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T NEED A REASON.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
YOU DON'T NEED A REASON?
MY DAUGHTER SHOULD HAVE MY LAST
NAME.
THAT'S SERIOUSLY, LIKE, A BIG
THING FOR ME.
>> BUT WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
>> THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
YOU, LIKE--
>> YES, IT DOES.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LIKE, I DON'T--
>> IF WE GOT TOGETHER OR
SOMETHING DOWN THE ROAD,
WE COULD ALWAYS CHANGE HER LAST
NAME.
>> NO, THAT'S SERIOUSLY, LIKE--
WHAT KID DO YOU KNOW HAS THEIR
MOM'S LAST NAME?
THE DAD SHOULD HAVE THE LAST
NAME IF HE'S GONNA BE IN THE
KID'S LIFE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT'S THE
BIG DEAL.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT HOW
THAT WORKS.
SO IF SHE DOESN'T HAVE YOUR LAST
NAME, YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE IN HER
LIFE?
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M SAYING.
I'M SAYING, 'CAUSE I AM IN HER
LIFE, I SHOULD HAVE THE LAST
NAME.
>> NO.
>> IT'S REALLY MAKING ME MAD.
>> I'M NOT GONNA FIGHT WITH YOU
OVER IT.
>> THAT'S MESSED UP.
I THINK THAT'S, LIKE,
DISRESPECTFUL.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO EXPECT US
TO BE TOGETHER THEN
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE LIKE THAT
WHEN I MOVE IN.
DON'T EXPECT SOMETHING.
>> WELL, I'M JUST SAYING.
>> TODAY IS HOMECOMING, BUT
SINCE CODY AND I ARE FIGHTING
ABOUT THE BABY'S LAST NAME,
I'M NOT FEELING UP FOR IT.
BUT I STILL AGREED TO TRY ON
DRESSES WITH MY FRIEND.
>> HEY.
>> HI.
THIS IS A SIZE 11.
>> REALLY?
>> THAT'S TEN SIZES HIGHER THAN
I'M USUALLY IN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA GO TRY
ON THIS ONE.
>> OKAY.
>> I CAN'T EVEN GET IT ON.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> YOU WANT ME TO PULL IT DOWN?
>> OH, GOD, THINGS ARE RIPPING.
>> [laughs]
IF YOU WEREN'T PREGNANT,
THIS WOULD BE TEN TIMES EASIER.
>> FOR YOU?
>> FOR EVERYONE.
LIFT THE DRESS UP A LITTLE BIT.
>> DON'T RIP MY BELLY RING OUT.
>> I'M NOT RIPPING YOUR BELLY
RING.
JEEZ.
SUCK IN.
>> I CAN'T SUCK IN.
[laughter]
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT HOMECOMING?
ARE YOU GONNA GO?
>> NO.
I JUST KIND OF WANT TO SLEEP.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S NOT HAPPENING.
OKAY.
>> JUST NOT FEELING IT?
>> YEAH. I HATE THIS DRESS.
I WAS WAY TOO UNCOMFORTABLE TO
GO TO THE DANCE, SO SKIPPED IT.
[chime dings]
BUT THE NEXT DAY, CODY TEXTED ME
TO APOLOGIZE FOR FIGHTING ON OUR
DATE.
HE STILL HOPES I GIVE THE BABY
HIS LAST NAME, BUT HE DOESN'T
WANT TO STRESS ME OUT BY
ARGUING, SO I'M GOING OVER TO
HIS HOUSE TO SEE THE PLANS FOR
BUILDING AUBREY'S NURSERY.
>> SO YOU WANT TO SHOW HER WHAT
YOU GUYS FIGURED OUT WITH THE
ROOM?
>> ALL RIGHT, THE WALL'S
GONNA COME FROM RIGHT HERE
ALL THE WAY OUT TO THE EDGE OF
THIS WINDOW HERE.
IT'S GONNA SQUARE OFF RIGHT
HERE, OKAY?
AND THEN THE DOOR WILL COME
RIGHT HERE.
>> BUT THAT'S GONNA BE, LIKE,
AN AWKWARD LITTLE THING
RIGHT THERE.
>> THE FRIDGE ISN'T GONNA BE
HERE.
THE FRIDGE HAS TO GO OVER THERE,
WHICH IS GONNA LOOK STUPID,
BUT--
>> YEAH, THIS WILL BE OPEN
RIGHT HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> SO THE DRESSER WOULD HAVE TO
BE HERE, AND ON EACH SIDE,
THERE WOULD BE THREE RECESSED
SHELVING, THREE--
>> THAT GOES INTO THE WALL.
>> THEY GO INTO THE WALL ON EACH
SIDE SO YOU COULD PUT LOTIONS,
POWDERS, WHATEVER BABY STUFF YOU
NEED, SINCE IT'S GONNA BE
A CHANGING AREA.
AND THEN, ABOVE IT, YOU WOULD
HAVE, LIKE, A RECESSED, DIM
LIGHTING, SO WHEN YOU GET UP IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT TO
CHANGE HER, YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO
TURN ON THE BIG LIGHT.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS THE COOLEST
IDEA.
BUT IF YOU DON'T WANT IT,
YOU NEED TO FIGURE IT OUT, LIKE,
TODAY, BECAUSE LOTS OF MONEY
PUT OUT.
BUT WE WANT TO DO IT.
WE WANT TO DO IT 'CAUSE WE WANT
YOU GUYS HERE AND STUFF, BUT
JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
>> I THINK I NEED WALLS TO BE UP
FOR ME TO BE ABLE TO PICTURE
EVERYTHING.
>> THEY WILL BE TOMORROW.
>> THEY WILL BE TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> I CAN'T WAIT.
I HOPE THE NEXT COUPLE MONTHS
GO BY FAST.
>> I'M GLAD CODY'S PARENTS ARE
EXCITED, BUT SEEING AUBREY'S
ROOM IN THEIR HOUSE IS REALLY
WEIRDING ME OUT.
BUT BEFORE I COULD FIGURE IT
OUT, I STARTED HAVING
CONTRACTIONS.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
YOU THINK IT'S CONTRACTIONS?
>> I JUST THINK WE SHOULD GO.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA GET
ALYSSA'S COAT ON, THEN WE'RE
GONNA GO TO THE HOSPITAL, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> THEN BREATHE THROUGH THEM.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
CAREFUL.
CAREFUL GOING DOWN THE STAIRS.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> NO.
GET THIS BABY OUT OF ME.
I TEXTED CODY ON THE WAY TO THE
HOSPITAL, AND HE MET ME THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
EVEN THOUGH I'M REALLY CONFUSED
ABOUT HIM RIGHT NOW, I'M GLAD HE
SHOWED UP.
I JUST WANT IT TO STOP.
MOM...
[mumbling indistinctly]
[moaning]
>> NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'M GONNA DIE.
THE PAIN GOT SO BAD THAT I HAD
TO GET AN EPIDURAL.
AND AFTER THAT,
THINGS MOVED PRETTY FAST.
A FEW PUSHES LATER,
AND AUBREY WAS BORN.
>> * FATE HAS BROUGHT US HERE
* AND I'VE NEVER BEEN *
* SO IN LOVE
* NEVER BEEN SO IN LOVE
>> I THINK THAT'S MY MOUTH
THAT SHE HAS.
>> * OH, ALL THIS TIME
* YOU WERE MINE
* YOU ARE MINE
>> CODY STAYED OVERNIGHT WITH ME
IN THE HOSPITAL, BUT HE SLEPT
THROUGH AUBREY'S CRYING, AND I
HAD TO TAKE CARE OF HER ON MY
OWN.
AND THINGS ONLY GOT WORSE THE
NEXT MORNING WHEN WE HAD TO SIGN
THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
CODY PUSHED HARD AGAIN TO GIVE
AUBREY HIS LAST NAME,
BUT I DECIDED TO GIVE HER MINE.
>> IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
>> CODY, YOU'RE STARTING TO
FRUSTRATE ME NOW A LITTLE BIT.
I'VE EXPLAINED IT TO YOU
A THOUSAND TIMES.
>> AND YOUR REASONS DON'T MAKE
SENSE, THOUGH.
LIKE, IT USUALLY HAS THE GUY'S
LAST NAME.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE YOUR LAST
NAME FOREVER, REGARDLESS.
NO MATTER WHAT, YOU'RE
NOT GONNA HAVE YOUR LAST NAME.
>> THE PARENTS ARE USUALLY
MARRIED TOO, CODY, AND NOT 16
YEARS OLD.
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT...
>> NO MATTER WHAT, SHE'S ALWAYS
GONNA BE WITH ME.
>> SHE'S GONNA BE LIVING AT MY
HOUSE.
>> BUT IF ANYTHING WERE TO
HAPPEN, SHE WOULD BE IN MY
CUSTODY.
IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
>> THE DOCTOR DISCHARGED US
TODAY, SO MY MOM IS PICKING US
UP TO GO BACK TO HER HOUSE
SINCE I HAVE A MONTH TO STAY
THERE BEFORE I HAVE TO MOVE.
[Aubrey crying]
>> BABY GIRL, HEY.
HEY.
IT'S OKAY, BABY.
MAMA.
HEY, IT'S MAMA.
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE GONNA MOVE IN A SECOND.
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
>> LET ME TAKE A PICTURE OF YOU
GUYS REAL QUICK.
>> CODY'S PARENTS MET US AT MY
MOM'S SO THEY COULD SPEND SOME
TIME WITH AUBREY.
>> OKAY.
>> FEELING ANY BETTER?
>> WORSE.
>> WORSE?
IT'S GONNA BE HARD THIS FIRST
MONTH.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT FIRST NIGHT WAS JUST
RIDICULOUS, THOUGH.
>> THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T DO
NOTHING.
>> NO, IT'S 'CAUSE YOU SAID
I WASN'T DOING NOTHING.
IT REALLY MADE ME MAD.
>> 'CAUSE YOU FELL ASLEEP EVERY
FIVE SECONDS AND DIDN'T HELP.
>> I FELL ASLEEP ONE TIME,
AND I'M NEVER GONNA HEAR THE END
OF IT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU COULD'VE WOKEN ME UP.
>> I DID, AND YOU ROLLED OVER
AND DIDN'T GET UP.
>> OBVIOUSLY I WASN'T WOKEN UP
THEN.
I'M USUALLY GOOD WITH IT.
>> GOT TO PAIN AND GET CARPET.
>> YEAH?
THERE'S ENOUGH ROOM IN THAT ROOM
FOR TWO BEDS?
>> WE'LL MAKE IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THERE'S GONNA HAVE TO BE.
>> TWO QUEEN-SIZED BEDS AND
DRESSERS AND WHATEVER ELSE THERE
IS?
>> YEAH, IT MAKES SENSE, THOUGH,
TO HAVE TWO BEDS.
WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
IT'D PROBABLY MAKE THINGS WEIRD.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T WANT TO FEEL LIKE WE'RE
BEING FORCED TO BE TOGETHER.
WE WANTED TO KILL EACH OTHER
AFTER A NIGHT TOGETHER IN THE
HOSPITAL.
AFTER HOW THINGS WENT AT THE
HOSPITAL, I'M STARTING TO
RECONSIDER MY DECISION TO MOVE
IN WITH CODY.
[chime dings]
>> I HAVE TO MOVE OUT IN TWO
WEEKS, AND EVER SINCE COMING
HOME WITH ME FROM THE HOSPITAL,
CODY HASN'T CALLED OR BEEN BY
TO HELP.
IT'S REALLY HARD HAVING TO DO
EVERYTHING BY MYSELF.
[Aubrey crying]
>> POOR BABY.
DID YOU FEED HER?
>> I HAVE A MILLION TIMES.
I MEAN, I FED HER, LIKE,
20 MINUTES AGO.
>> MAYBE SHE'S GOT A BURP
IN HER.
>> NO, I'M GONNA SEE IF SHE'S
HUNGRY.
SHE'S JUST NOT HAPPY TODAY.
[Aubrey and Alyssa crying]
>> OH, NO, EITHER IS
SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> ALYSSA FELL AGAIN.
>> OH, I GOT TO GET ALYSSA.
[Aubrey and Alyssa crying]
>> HEY.
>> OKAY, OKAY.
>> AUBREY.
>> OH, MY GOD, ALYSSA,
YOU'RE KILLING ME.
MY GOODNESS, YOU'RE BOTH GOING
CRAZY.
MY GOSH.
DO YOU SEE WHY YOU CAN'T HAVE
MORE THAN ONE BABY IN THIS
HOUSE?
I'M GONNA GO NUTS.
IT'S OKAY. LISTEN--
OH, MY GOODNESS SAKES.
THERE'S TOO MANY BABIES, HUH?
>> I'M TEN DAYS AWAY FROM
MOVING, AND CODY'S STILL NOT
SHOWING INTEREST IN HELPING OUT
WITH AUBREY.
>> MADDY.
SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> IF SHE WAKES UP, SHE'S GONNA
SCREAM, SO I DON'T WANT TO...
>> OH!
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> LOOK AT THAT LIP.
SHE LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE CODY.
>> SO SPEAKING OF THAT,
UPDATE ME.
>> HE'S ONLY COME OVER ONCE,
SO...
IF HE DOESN'T COME SEE HER,
WE CAN'T NOT FIGHT.
HE KEEPS SAYING THAT IT'S 'CAUSE
HE'S AT WORK ALL THE TIME,
BUT EVEN WHEN HE'S OFF,
HE DOESN'T COME.
>> OH!
>> [chuckles]
>> YOU'RE SO CUTE.
OH, MY GOD.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA START SCHOOL?
>> I'M GONNA DO THE ONLINE STUFF
RIGHT NOW.
BUT I'M NOT GOING BACK IN
JANUARY.
>> WHY?
I WANT YOU TO BE AT SCHOOL
SENIOR YEAR.
>> I DON'T HAVE CHOICE.
I HAVE TO.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS THE POINT WHERE IT'S
"GROW UP, MADDY" TIME.
>> OH, I HAVE A LOT.
TRUST ME.
>> OH, MADDY.
OH, CODY.
YOU SEE WHAT HAPPENS
IN TWO MINUTES, MADDY?
IN TWO MINUTES?
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
TRUST ME.
[Aubrey fussing]
BEING UP EVERY NIGHT WITH AUBREY
IS EXHAUSTING.
I'M REALLY FRUSTRATED THAT CODY
HASN'T BEEN HELPING,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I'M SUPPOSED TO
MOVE IN WITH HIM IN ONE WEEK.
[Aubrey crying]
AND I'M AFRAID THINGS AREN'T
GONNA CHANGE.
[cell phone tone plays]
HELLO?
>> HOW'S AUBREY?
>> OH, YOU'RE GONNA CALL AND
CHECK ON HER NOW?
>> YEAH.
CODY, SHE'S ALMOST THREE WEEKS
OLD, AND YOU'VE COME
TO SEE HER ONE TIME.
>> WHO CARES?
YOU CAN STILL COME SEE HER.
YOU HAVE THE MORNINGS OFF
SOMETIMES.
>> SHE'S DOING FINE.
>> WHATEVER.
[sighs]
I HAVE TO MOVE OUT IN FIVE DAYS,
SO TODAY I DROVE TO INDIANA TO
VISIT MY DAD SO HE CAN SPEND
TIME WITH HIS GRANDDAUGHTER.
>> HEY, YOU MADE IT.
>> HI.
IT'S SO COLD.
>> COME ON IN.
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
>> OH, YOU KNOW, JUST A BABY.
[Aubrey fussing]
>> [chuckles]
SHE'S GOING NUTS OVER THERE.
HOW ARE THINGS GOING AT YOUR
MOM'S?
I MEAN, HOW'S IT HAVING THE TWO
LITTLE BABIES IN THE HOUSE?
>> THEY LOVE EACH OTHER.
LIKE, THEY'RE GONNA BE BEST
FRIENDS.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> YEAH, BUT I GOT TO GO TO
CODY'S NEXT WEEK.
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
>> NOT AT ALL.
I JUST THINK I'M GONNA BE
MISERABLE THE ENTIRE TIME.
I MEAN, I LITERALLY HAVE NO
FEELINGS FOR HIM AT ALL, AND
WE'RE GONNA BE LIVING--LIKE,
SLEEPING IN THE SAME ROOM.
SO, LIKE, I DON'T THINK I SHOULD
BE THERE AT ALL ANYMORE.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE TO ME.
IT SOUNDS LIKE A '70s SITCOM.
IT MAKES ABSOLUTELY NO SENSE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
THE ONLY REASON THAT I WAS GONNA
GO TO CODY'S INSTEAD OF HERE IN
THE FIRST PLACE WAS BECAUSE YOU
GUYS WOULD BE AT WORK AND I
NEEDED HELP WITH HER AND STUFF.
BUT, I MEAN, MOM HELPS ME, BUT
JUST AS MUCH AS YOU WOULD BE
ABLE TO.
>> LIKE I SAID, YOU'RE WELCOME
TO MOVE IN HERE.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE SOME,
YOU KNOW, ROOM DOWNSTAIRS.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD CONSIDER DOING
THAT INSTEAD.
AND WE'LL HELP OUT AS MUCH
AS WE CAN.
>> OKAY.
I'D RATHER DO THAT THAN GO
THERE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW TO TELL
THEM THAT.
I MEAN, PENNY IS GONNA BE REALLY
UPSET.
THEY BUILT A ROOM AND SPENT ALL
THAT MONEY AND STUFF.
>> WELL, I MEAN, THAT WAS NICE
OF THEM TO DO.
YOU KNOW, I'M SURE YOU CAN LET
THEM KNOW HOW MUCH YOU
APPRECIATE THAT.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I FEEL BAD, BUT I HOPE
HE, LIKE, UNDERSTANDS THE FACT
THAT, LIKE, THIS IS BETTER
FOR ME.
>> * THERE IS AN ANSWER
* YOU RUN INTO THE FIRE
* AND GRAB THE WOOD
* TO BUILD IT UP AGAIN
[cell phone chimes]
>> MADDY TEXTED ME.
>> WHAT'D SHE SAY?
>> SHE'S GOING TO HER DAD'S IN
INDIANA AND SAYS SHE DOESN'T
WANT TO LIVE HERE.
>> I MEAN, SERIOUSLY, AFTER ALL
THIS WORK, ALL THIS TIME,
ALL THIS MONEY?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
THAT'S JUST MESSED UP.
>> YEAH.
SHE SAID SHE JUST DOESN'T THINK
THINGS WOULD WORK OUT AND IT'D
BE BETTER FOR BOTH OF US
IF SHE DIDN'T LIVE HERE.
>> HOW YOU ARE GONNA SEE AUBREY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
>> THIS CRAP'S STRESSING ME OUT
BAD.
>> YEAH, IT STRESSES YOU OUT.
[scoffs]
>> I KNOW MY DECISION PROBABLY
HURT CODY AND HIS FAMILY,
BUT I HAVE TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT
FOR ME.
[chime dings]
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
TODAY'S MOVING DAY, AND IT'S
BEEN ALMOST A WEEK SINCE I TOLD
CODY MY DECISION, BUT HE'S
STILL REALLY UPSET AND ISN'T
SPEAKING TO ME.
I FEEL BAD, BUT I CAN'T FORCE
MYSELF TO LIVE THERE.
IT JUST SUCKS THAT I'M LEAVING
'CAUSE, LIKE, MY MOM'S THE ONE
WHO, LIKE, HELPS ME WITH AUBREY.
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
LIKE, HE HASN'T EVEN ASKED ABOUT
AUBREY.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I WISH I KNEW THAT I
WASN'T MOVING THERE BEFORE THEY
BUILT THE ROOM SO THEY DIDN'T
WASTE THE MONEY.
BUT MY DAD'S GONNA BE HERE TO
GET ME IN, LIKE, TEN MINUTES.
>> [groans]
>> I KNOW.
IT'S GONNA SUCK.
IT'S SO FAR AWAY.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO MAKE IT WORK.
>> YEAH, I GUESS SO.
>> * THIS BOTTLE'S *
* ALMOST EMPTY
* I THINK I'LL SLEEP ALL RIGHT *
>> OKAY, OKAY, BABY, OKAY.
SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
>> * I'M NOT ALL RIGHT *
>> YOU KNOW THIS ISN'T
A GOOD-BYE THING, AND, YOU KNOW,
AND I'M NOT DOING THIS TO
PUNISH YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> I REALLY THINK THIS IS GONNA
WORK OUT GREAT.
YOU KNOW, I JUST DON'T HAVE ROOM
FOR THE BABY.
YOU KNOW THAT.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU'D STILL BE HERE.
ALL RIGHT, CALL ME WHEN YOU GET
THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE GOT TO GO.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
>> BYE, LOVE YOU.
>> BYE, BABY GIRL.
>> * I'M NOT ALL RIGHT *
[thunder rumbles]
>> [grunts]
>> CAREFUL.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'LL STILL BE
WITH FAMILY, IT WAS REALLY HARD
MOVING OUT OF MY MOM'S HOUSE
SINCE I'LL BE SO FAR AWAY
FROM EVERYONE.
I'VE SETTLED INTO MY DAD'S
HOUSE, BUT SINCE HE WORKS
FULL-TIME, I'M USUALLY HOME BY
MYSELF TAKING CARE OF AUBREY...
AUBREY, YOU'RE NOT EVEN DOING
ANYTHING.
SO I WAS GLAD WHEN CODY TEXTED
ME THAT HE WANTS TO SEE HIS
DAUGHTER.
[knock at door]
WHO'S HERE?
HI.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
[Aubrey cries]
OH...
IS THIS, LIKE, YOUR ROOM?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S NICE.
>> I KNOW. IT'S SO BIG.
SHE GOT THE HICCUPS.
SHE MIGHT GET PISSED OFF.
SHE CAN HOLD HER HEAD UP KIND
OF, SO YOU DON'T GOT TO HOLD HER
LIKE A TINY LITTLE BABY.
>> HEY.
[chuckles]
IT FEELS GOOD TO FINALLY SEE
HER.
>> YEAH, BUT SHE'S ALMOST TWO
MONTHS OLD, AND YOU'VE ONLY SEEN
HER TWICE.
>> YEAH, IT'S HARD WITH WORK
AND EVERYTHING.
I GOT TWO JOBS.
>> YEAH, MINE'S A FULL-TIME JOB
EVERY SECOND OF THE DAY, SO...
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT, LIKE--
[Aubrey cries]
>> OH...
I NEED TO FEED HER.
SHE'S GOT THE HICCUPS.
WE GOT TO GET RID OF THE
HICCUPS.
OH, HEY.
I'M GETTING IT.
>> WHAT MADE YOU CHANGE YOUR
MIND ABOUT MOVING IN?
>> WELL, I MEAN, WE DIDN'T
REALLY KNOW EACH OTHER IN THE
FIRST PLACE, SO I WAS JUST KIND
OF WITH YOU BECAUSE I WAS
PREGNANT AND I WANTED OUR LITTLE
FAMILY JUST TO, LIKE,
BE TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU COULD'VE TOLD
MY MOM THAT, LIKE, A WHILE AGO,
'CAUSE, LIKE, YOU KNOW, YOU GOT
HER ALL HYPED UP.
>> YEAH, I FELT BAD, BUT I
DIDN'T SEE A POINT IN ME BEING
MISERABLE THE ENTIRE TIME I WAS
THERE.
SO YOU JUST HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
THAT IF AUBREY WASN'T IN THE
PICTURE, THEN WE WOULD NOT
EVEN HAVE A RELATIONSHIP
OR BE TALKING OR ANYTHING.
>> YEAH, BUT I WANT TO START,
LIKE, SEEING HER MORE, THOUGH.
SHE'S GONNA NEED HER DAD TOO.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN SEE HER
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
I'M NOT TELLING YOU YOU CAN'T
COME HERE.
>> YEAH, WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW IF I FEEL EVEN
COMFORTABLE COMING HERE.
LIKE, YOUR DAD I DON'T THINK
LIKES ME AND--
>> MY DAD HAS NO PROBLEM
WITH YOU.
HE UNDERSTANDS, LIKE,
IT'S YOUR DAUGHTER.
YOU'RE GONNA COME SEE HER.
>> WELL, WE'RE STUCK WITH EACH
OTHER FOR A GOOD 18 YEARS,
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO, LIKE,
WORK SOMETHING OUT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT AUBREY NOW.
>> I MEAN, I NEVER WANTED AUBREY
TO GROW UP WITHOUT BOTH OF HER
PARENTS.
>> * I WAS STUCK IN THE GROUND
* TRYING TO COVER MY EYES
* I SPENT ALL NIGHT
* TRYING TO REMEMBER YOUR FACE
>> I WANTED IT TO WORK FOR HER,
BUT THEN I REALIZED, LIKE,
I CAN'T BE WITH SOMEONE JUST
BECAUSE I HAVE A BABY WITH HIM.
I HAVE TO ACTUALLY HAVE FEELINGS
FOR HIM.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, I GOT TO GO.
>> * TRYING TO GET BLOOD
* FROM A STONE
>> ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU.
>> BYE.
>> * THERE'S NOTHING TO SAY *
>> IF I HADN'T GOTTEN PREGNANT,
I'D BE DOING SCHOOL.
I'D STILL BE LIVING AT HOME.
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH MY FRIENDS
IS, LIKE, NONEXISTENT NOW.
IT'S BASKETBALL SEASON RIGHT
NOW, SO I'D BE PLAYING
BASKETBALL AND HANGING OUT WITH
MY FRIENDS.
IT'S JUST, EVERYTHING CHANGED
SINCE I GOT PREGNANT.
IT'S A STRUGGLE, AND IT'S HARD.
I WANT AUBREY TO GROW UP
AND MAKE SMART DECISIONS
AND JUST LEARN FROM MY MISTAKES.
[chime dings]
>> all: OH!
>> HAVE YOU STOPPED SMOKING POT?
>> IF SOMEBODY COMES OVER AND
THEY HAVE WEED, SURE,
I'M GONNA TAKE A HIT.
>> NOT IN MY HOME.
IT'S ILLEGAL!
>> NOW I JUST FEEL LIKE THE
BIGGEST ASS[bleep].
>> WILL YOU GO TAKE
THE DRUG TEST?
>> MM-MM.
>> GO TAKE THE TEST.
>> I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> NO, LIKE, HONESTLY, YOU JUST
PISSED ME OFF WITH THAT ONE.