your whole life changes
in an instant.
But for many
the reality does not sink in
until they're alone, exhausted,
feeding their newborns
in the middle of the night.
We have our 12 teenage mothers
from this season here today.
Along with the people
who continue to support them
and some of those
who disappeared
when the going got tough.
This is the 16 and Pregnant
finale special,
Life After Labor.
[music playing]
[applauding]
I'm Dr. Drew.
Now each of the stories
we are gonna revisit today
comes with triumphs
and challenges.
So, let's begin by looking back.
Here is a quick recap
of this season
of 16 and Pregnant.
♪
>>: Teenagers are supposed
to, you know,
have fun, do their things,
but I can't do that
because I'm pregnant.
>>: You did something
and now you gotta pay
the consequences.
[man] What's wrong?
>>: My weight.
>>: I don't know why,
you still look cute to me.
>>: Let's worry about
when reality hits.
>>: Oh, it already has.
>>: Oh, it has...
[chuckles]
>>: I'm having
a contraction.
Ma!
[straining]
[woman] Oh, we did it!
[baby crying]
>>: Oh, she is turning purple.
[woman] We need NICU now.[woman 1] Now.
>>: God! Lord Jesus! [crying]
>>: My fiance passed away.
I just remember
being pulled to shore,
looking around
and him not being there.
[crying] He doesn't get
to hold him.
>>: I just don't want you
to go away.
>>: Sucks to... your family.
You do what you've gotta do
>>: You can go
but don't expect me to be here
when you get back.
>>: I'll talk to you
and everything.
>>: I guess so.
>>: I'm forced
to get a job.
[Briana] I'm forced
to be a mother.
If I could grow up
over night,
you could do the same.
>>: I know what's best.
Adoption.
I just want you to grow up
and you won't.
And you know it's gonna ruin us.
>>: How is he gonna
raise a black baby?
>>: I still wanna be key
and wanna have fun.
[woman] "Oh, you are my dad,
but you keep walking
in and out of my life."
Yeah. That's what
she's gonna know.
>>: It's no secret
that I have a drug addiction.
>>: She only thinks
about herself
and doesn't care about me
or her grandchild or anything.
>>: I'm trying to figure out
what the [bleep]
is going through your head.
Whether you wanna
see that little girl
who is sitting in that room
or you wanna walk away
and go hangout
with your crackhead friends?
>>: Sit around the pumpkin,
I wanna take a picture.
Say, "Cheese, Dad."
[laughing]
[man] Look at her
holding the bottle.
Hey, girl!>>: Hey!
>>: I can put a pillow
under your b#*#*t
if you want me to.
[man] What's the coils
on that boy?
>>:We're gonna give him a bath.
♪
>>: Wow. Pretty clear,
this was a season
filled with challenges
at every turn.
And today we're gonna address
some of those challenges
and hear the updates
and some of this stuff
may surprise you.
Now, later, we're gonna have
all 12 of the moms,
the teen moms,
right here together
for the very first time.
For now though, we're gonna
get it started with Briana.
Now, Briana,
you were a great student,
you graduated high school
a year early, right?
>>: Yeah.
>>: What's been
the biggest sacrifice for you?
>>: Giving up my teenage years.
Not being able
to live a carefree life.
[Drew] Yeah.>>: Yeah.
>>: Well, here is a look back
at Briana's journey
on 16 and Pregnant.
>>: We didn't use protection.
>>: You weren't scared of,
"Oh, my God,
I might get pregnant."
>>: I didn't think
anything would happen.
And then it happened.
>>: When I went in,
I got my abortion
then I knew Briana wasn't
gonna have hers,
now we're gonna have to see
a baby in the house.
>>: I know that
that hurts you.
And I'm sorry that
you have to stay here
and watch her have her baby
and you can't.
>>: It's up to you,
if you want the last name,
then you show me
that you want the last name.
[screaming]
[woman] Oh, my God!
>>: Oh, my god!
>>: The more time you spend here
with the baby,
learn the ropes about the baby.[mobile chimes]
You don't think that
that's disrespectful?
I'm talking to you.
>>: Alright, Briana,
I'll talk to you later.
>>: Bri, sometimes
some daddies are not...
willing to wanna
make it work.
[Briana] I don't want to have
anything to do with him.
As much as I wanted us
to work out,
It's not going to.
>>: Well let me pass out
the Kleenexes.
Pass that along to your mom.
She needs it more than you
it seems like to start out with.>>: Yeah.
>>: It's hard to see that, huh?
>>: Yeah.
[Drew] You know what?
I'm gonna start with Roxanne.
Mom, you get sad.
[Roxanne] Of course.>>: Why?
>>: This is not
what I wanted for them.
It almost feels like...
It's the hardest path
anyone can take
at the age of 17.
>>: So, is it the hardest path?
Hmm.>>: [softly] Hard.
[Drew] It's hard, yeah.
What's the hardest part
about being a teen mom?
>>: I feel alone.
[Drew] And yet you have
a supportive family.
So, it's--
>>: Me and Devon were supposed
to parent together
and it's just me by myself.
>>: How about you, Britney?
You had a pregnancy too though,
right? Is that right?
>>: Yeah, when she was pregnant.
[Drew] You had a pregnancy
when she was pregnant?
>>: Same time.
[Drew] And you took
a different path?
>>: Yeah.>>: And it seems like
it was a good choice for you?
>>: I know
I did the right thing.
But I did it for many reasons
and it wasn't for myself.
I didn't do it
so I could have a free life.
Because l Iove my niece,
so if I love my niece,
imagine how I would
have loved my own.
So... It's not because of that.
[crying]
But I did it
so my mom wouldn't struggle.
I did it
'cause my boyfriend
at the time wasn't supportive.
And I did it so my sister
and her baby wouldn't struggle.
And I love them too much
to put them through things.
>>: Did you tell them this?
Did you talk about this?
>>: No, because I don't want
to put...
to make them feel bad
or anything.
I don't want them
to think, like,
"Oh, she did it
because of us."
I didn't do it
because of you guys.
I did it for our family.
>>: I don't think they feel bad
when you say that.
I think they feel relief.
You feel relieved
to hear her say that?
Or do you feel guilty?
>>: Guilty.>>: It is my choice.
You know, no one forced me
to do it.
So no one can feel guilty
for my actions.
>>: Yeah. Are you at school now?>>: Yeah, I'm at school.
>>: So you're doing
what you need to do?
>>: Yeah.>>: Have you had
to sacrifice school?
Briana?
>>: No. Well,
in a sense, yeah.
Because since I don't have
any babysitter
to watch Nova,
I can't just
get up and go to school.
I've to think about her.[Drew] How about socially?
>>: Oh, I have no friends.
[Drew] Yeah.>>: Everybody just left.
>>: This is something we hear
from the teen moms a lot.
They feel very alone.
You imagine it to be
as most teen moms do,
flowers and snow flakes.>>: Yeah. It's like...
>>: And the perfect family where
the dad is gonna stick around
and form a perfect unit
with you.
Statistically, it almost
never happens like that.
>>: No.
>>: Okay.
Britney, Roxanne,
thank you for joining us today.
We're gonna take
a quick break
and then Devon is gonna
come on out here and join us.
So do not go away.
[applauding]
>>: Welcome back
to Life After Labor,
the 16 and Pregnant
finale special.
I'm Dr. Drew and I've been
chatting with Briana.
Now, it's time to bring
the father of her baby
into the conversation.
Devon, welcome to the show.
>>: How's it going?>>: Appreciate you coming out.
So, Devon,
it seems like you had trouble,
sort of, being present
as a dad, is that accurate?
>>: Hmm, yeah, I guess
you could say that
>>: Briana, what kind of dad
has Devon been?
>>: Not the dad
he is supposed to be.
>>: Devon, what do you
say to that?
>>: I agree with that.
[Drew] You wanna be a dad?
Did you expect
to be a dad at your age?
[Devon] No.>>: No.
>>: Hmm-mmm.>>: How's it been for you?
>>: You don't feel
like a kid anymore.
>>: But you still do
kid things.
[Devon] What do you
mean by that?
[Briana] You never put
Nova first, Devon.
You work, what,
two days out of the whole week?
So you work 24/7?
No, you don't work 24/7.
You could see Nova.
What do you do?
What honestly do you do all day?
That you can't come see Nova.
>>: If I'm not working...
I live away in Poinciana,
they live, like, 45 minutes
away from there.
>>: He is always
on my side of the area
but he can't come see Nova.>>: That's not true.
>>: So when you hear
he is visiting your friends,
and he doesn't come
see Nova you feel...
>>: It pisses me off.
[Drew] Because?>>: Because that's his daughter.
He is supposed
to be there for her.
>>: It feels like the feelings
are little more complicated
than that.
'Cause anger on the surface
but there is, sort of,
pain underneath.
Can you tell him
about that pain
because I think all
he hears is about the anger.
>>: I'm disappointed.[Drew] Can you tell him?
>>: Very disappointed
at you.
You fed me lies
during my whole pregnancy
that you were
gonna be there, Devon.
And I'm doing it on my own.
You don't help financially,
you don't help emotionally
and you don't help physically.
Nothing whatsoever,
you don't help.
I left him alone for now
with the baby,
he couldn't handle it.
He doesn't know
how to be a father.
[Drew] Well, it's hard.
It's hard.
>>: Real hard.>>: But if he wants be a father,
wouldn't you think
he would be there all the time
to get to know
his daughter?
To bond
with his daughter?
He doesn't. Why is that?
You keep making up excuses.
>>: I don't make excuses at all.
You know my situation.
You know where I live at.
>>: But you still always come
to do your thing...>>: No, I don't always come.
>>: ...on my side of the town.
>>: I don't... How do you know
I'd be on your side of the town?
>>: All your...>>: How do you even know?
>>: ...with this person
and that person
and they live on my side.
>>: How do you know
they're in contact with me?
>>: Not once have you
came to my house,
"Briana, here are some diapers
for the baby.
Here is some formula,
here is this."
You are worried about sneakers,
tattoos and phones.
[Drew] Alright, let's move on.
Devon, what kind of dad
you wanna be?
>>: Well... [scoffs]
I'd want a close relationship
to my daughter, and I...
I do want to know who I am.
>>: This is the challenge
of being a teen dad.
You need to grow up
but your baby always needs you.
So you, sort of, sacrifice
in the growing up piece
to be a dad.
Is there a way that we can
get to that place
where you're feeling better
about what you're doing
and they are feeling
like supported?
Is there, maybe, a structure?>>: I think... Right.
It was just a bunch of pride.
We have too much pride.>>: On your part?
I know I had a lot of pride.
And I willing to put that
to the side.
>>: For the baby?>>: She is doing the same thing.
She does the same thing, like...
I know at one point
she hated me, like,
to the T.
She really hated me.
But she would accept me
being there, like,
at her house.
And I respected that, like,
I appreciated that.
Little did she know.
I know she really, really
hated me
but she would invite me over
to come see Nova.
>>: He is right, isn't he?[Briana] Mmm-hmm.
>>: Okay. And he is willing
to say that
and willing
to continue to try
to craft a relationship with you
and your family for the baby.
>>: But the thing is,
with me it's like,
he has my hopes up and then
he always disappoints me
And that's not fair.
Don't say you are gonna do it,
you wanna do it.
Do it.
>>: It's hard to just come
into the baby's life.
And like she said she let me
watch the baby for an hour,
and I hadn't know how to like...
I barely knew anything
about the baby, like...
>>: Yeah, so I'm giving you guys
some assignments.
[Devon] Yeah, I didn't...>>: Here is the assignment.
[Brian chuckles]>>: Here's your assignment.
You need to spend all day
with the baby at some point.
You need to let him do that.
And you need to have
a shared experience,
the three of you together
doing something.
Zoo, what comes to mind,
something like that.[Briana] Okay.
>>: And you guys have got to be
willing to do that.
Let that happen.
Briana and Devon, thank you.
it's tough. It is tough.
Briana is gonna be back later
along with other 11 teenage moms
right here together on the stage
for the first time.
Now, in a moment
we're gonna return with Lindsey.
She and her
baby's father Forest,
I think you saw, did a lot
of fighting this season.
But when the dust cleared,
did he stay by her side?
I'm gonna speak with
both of them after the break.
[applauding]
>>: I'm Dr. Drew,
and this is Life After Labor,
the 16 and Pregnant
finale special.
Now, before we go any further,
I want to tell our viewers
to head on over
to itsyoursexlife.com,
where you can get answers
to s#*x questions
and tips on how do you take
and use birth control properly
and take control
of your s#*x life.
We're gonna talk
to our next young mom Lindsey
right after this look back
at her story
on 16 and Pregnant.
♪
>>: So, when I first told you
I was pregnant,
you wanted nothing
to do with me,
all you wanted was
me to get out of your sight
and for me to get an abortion.
>>: It seemed
as if you got pregnant
to kind of tie me down.
[Lindsey] I can't do anything
I normally would do.
So as much as I want
to still continue cage fighting,
I need to put it
on hold for a while.
The baby comes first.
And the bassinet would be
$25 to $80.
The crib, about $200.
I've been the only one working.
Are you gonna get a job?
>>: You think
he's gonna be responsible?
So far he's been
pretty irresponsible.
>>: Mom! I think
I'm having contraction.
[straining]
[baby crying]
[Lindsey] I'm, like, up
almost all night,
with the baby.
I take care of her all day.
>>: Are you gonna want
to get back into cage fighting?
>>: Yeah, definitely.
I wanna become professional.
So, do you think
if I work my b#*#t off,
I could still go pro
like we had planned?
[man] I mean,
it's gonna be hard,
that's the one thing
you have to understand.
>>: When do you
go into training?
>>: Every other day.
>>: Every other day?
>>: You're gonna be
watching her a lot.
>>: I'm joined now by Lindsey,
her mom, Anita,
and her baby's father Forest.
So, you were having
a reaction there?
>>: Yeah.[Drew] You're gonna use Kleenex.
What were you crying about?>>: I don't know. [giggles]
[Drew] Just watching...>>: It's just hard to, like...
That was such, like,
a rough period in my life
and then, yeah, to go back
and watch it, it's hard.
>>: What was rough about it?
>>: The hard part was, like,
the hormones
and then, like,
us not being together
and we weren't
even on good terms
when I became pregnant.>>: So, you were by yourself.
[Lindsey] Yeah.>>: You stepping up now for it?
>>: Yeah.
[Drew] Is he?>>: Yeah. I'm so thankful
I couldn't ask
for a better boyfriend.
He's like...
Yeah, he is great.
>>: I thought you used
some strange logic with condoms
that if you've used it once
and you didn't need
to use it again.
What was that?>>: I thought because...
We didn't use it one time
and I thought--
[Drew] You didn't get pregnant
therefore you never
use it again?
>>: Yeah, we thought that
we couldn't make babies.
Like, I thought I couldn't
or he couldn't
and then we were just, like...
It was dumb, we should have.
>>: What are you doing
for birth control now?
>>: Um, well, actually right now
we are using condoms.
And then I went to go get, like,
the IUD with my insurance,
since they cover it,
so it's like, 1,000 bucks,.
So I found a different place
that I could go to,
and it's a free clinic
and they are gonna
give me birth control
but it takes, like,
they said a month to get me in,
so I'm still waiting.
>>: Yeah, but it's
Catholic insurance,
so they won't
cover birth control.
>>: Yeah.>>: At all.
>>: But we are so careful now
with condoms.
We have them by the bed
ready to go, like...
[laughing]
>>: There is no doubt
about it.
[Drew] But insurance covered
your pregnancy,
your prenatal care,
postnatal care?
>>: Yeah, they paid $12,000
for me to have a baby
but not a hundred bucks
to cover the birth control.
>>: And if you were talking
to a Li,
let's say
she is 17-years-old now.
What are you gonna tell her?
How you're gonna advice her
to avoid the cycle going on?
>>: I'd get her on birth control
as soon as she start to period.
No ifs and buts about that.
And then just always be
open with her.
And you wanna just let her know,
you don't need
to waste your childhood.
[Drew] Did you try
to tell her that stuff?
>>: Yes.>>: Of course.
[laughing]
Forest, your mom wants you
to not work
and to go to school, right?
>>: Yeah.
[Drew] Is that... is that...>>: I don't really get it.
[Drew] Do you agree with that?>>: No.
>>: Do you think
your mom is enabling you
in some way by...
>>: She wants me... I think
she is trying to protect me
for a better future.
Like, she doesn't wanna see me
juggle school and then the job
and then babysitting.
>>: Alright, but then...
>>: I don't think this is gonna
carry on forever.
I know I'm gonna have to...>>: Better not.
>>: I'm going to get a job.[Drew laughing]
[Drew] Lindsey is like,
"You gotta get a job."
>>: Yeah, you are.
>>: So the first hospitalization
you kinda bailed
on Lindsey, right?
[Forest] Yeah.
>>: What was going on
with you then?
[Forest] Well, because she had
a bunch of complications.
She was always in the hospital,
and then when me and her
fought one time,
I was just like, I am done.
I don't wanna talk to you,
I don't wanna deal with it.
And then something hit me
and it was just kinda like,
my daughter was inside of her.
And it wasn't more
just about her,
it's, like,
actually my daughter.
And so, I wanted to go.
>>: You are still a little sad
thinking about that, huh?
[sniffles]
>>: It just cute to see him,
like, care about his daughter.
Like, to me,
that is so attractive.
[laughing]Yes.
>>: However, he, sort of,
let you down.
[Lindsey] Yeah, he did.
But I'm just...
I don't know,
I'm glad that he is here now.
I' rather have him here now...[Drew] No, it wasn't...
>>: ...than before and not now.
>>: That's good.
Way to go, Forest. Well done.
Anita, thank you.>>: Thank you.
And, Lindsey, of course,
I appreciate you
sharing the story.
Now, here is a fact
for all sexually active teens.
Having unprotected s#*x regularly
leads to 85% chance
of pregnancy within one year.
We're gonna take a break
and return with Mackenzie.
The question now is,
her baby's father, Josh,
has he given up bull riding?
Or has the adrenal rush got
too much of a grip on him?
We are gonna find that out soon.
So don't go away.
[applauding]
We are back with more of
16 and Pregnant finale special.
And here is a scary stat,
nearly three in ten girls
in the United States
will get pregnant at least once
before the age of 20.
One of those young ladies
is a competitive cheerleader
named Mackenzie.
Let's take a look back
at her time
being 16 and pregnant.
♪
>>: See, how good is she?
[woman] College days?>>: Yeah, you had a six-pack.
[man] Push, push, get there.
>>: That was me
before I got pregnant.
[chuckles]
>>: This isn't my baby sister.
For you to take
on a responsibility like this,
it worries me.
>>: We need to both settle down
and get jobs.
It takes time. I can't just
go out there and apply for a job
and expect for...
>>: But that's the only way
we're gonna come close
to doing it,
is doing it together.
>>: I have no money.
You can't work.
You can at least say,
"It will all work out."
>>: No, you just don't get it.
You don't.
You think everything is
gonna be alright. But it's not.
>>: I wanted things
to be better than this.
Like, when Ganon was born.
>>: But the bottom line is,
there is a baby coming
in a few weeks.
Actually, it could be any day.
[Lindsey straining]
[woman] Oh,
he is gorgeous, Mackie.
[crying]
>>: You're cute.
>>: And she just wants me
to give up
rodeo and broncing.
She said...
Yeah, it's too dangerous.
>>: Man, do not get
on with...
>>: Please don't
do this, Josh. Please.
>>: It's not life
or death, man.
>>: If your plan
is to stay with me...
you can't ride anymore.
>>: So, Mackenzie,
is he still riding?
>>: Yes. [chuckles]
>>: Josh?
You're freaking
the baby's mom out.
>>: Yeah, a little bit.
>>: But what do you feel
about him riding broncos
and doing rodeo?
>>: I'm just like,
hoping he won't get hurt again.
But he's had...
How many concussions
from bull riding?
>>: I don't know.>>: A lot. He is--
>>: He can't remember because
he has had so many concussions.
[laughs]
Don't you worry
about being available
as a dad for Gannon?
[Josh] Yeah, I'm gonna
be there for him.
I don't wanna rodeo and get in
the way of everything,
but I still wanna do it.
>>: How about the tumbling?
Are you back doing that?
[Lindsey] Mmm-hmm.
>>: And you're able to do
the heavy stuff again?
>>: Everything I was
doing before.
>>: Okay, did you have to change
your educational plans?
>>: Yeah! Oh, yeah.
Since I was,
uh, in first grade,
I had this dream
to go to this college
called Oasis.
They have one of the best
cheer squads.
Now I can't...
I don't even think
I can go to college and cheer.
So...
>>: So, that's a tough thing
to swallow.
>>: Yeah. And I would like
to go to college,
but I think about it every day
and I don't think
there is a way I can.
>>: Were you using
birth control?
[Mackenzie] [softly] No.>>: No!
And how come?
>>: Um...
I didn't wanna gain weight!
[laughs]
But then I got pregnant
and gained
a lot of weight!>>: Yeah!
You were diabetic
during your pregnancy, right?
>>: Oh, yeah. I'm type 1.
I've been diabetic--
>>: Oh... also diabetic.>>: Yes!
>>: Oh, okay. Okay.>>: Yeah.
So, it just makes your pregnancy
more complicated.
>>: Oh, my gosh. Yeah.
>>: Yeah.>>: I had a...
>>: He was 4.5 weeks early
and almost 10 pounds. [chuckles]
>>: A lot of people don't know
for juveniles that are diabetic,
the babies are actually bigger.
They have big babies.>>: Oh, yeah.
>>: Yeah.>>: Yeah.
>>: You had
a ten pound baby,
and you are
not a big girl.
>>: No!>>: Wow!
>>: Are you using
birth control now?
[Josh chuckles softly]So you wanna have another baby?
>>: No. No. [laughs]
>>; Help me understand
how that's not gonna happen.
>>: I don't know!
I don't like
birth control.
getting pregnant neither. But...
Um...
>>: Condoms are not scary!
What about that?
Condoms.[Josh groans]
>>: Josh?>>: He is allergic to latex.
>>: I think that's why
I got pregnant.
[Drew] Polyurethane condoms,
animal skin condoms.
There are plenty of options
other than latex.
For people out there
that may have latex allergies
which are rather common,
polyurethane, so called
animal skin condom.
Two different kinds of options
other than latex.
By the way, Josh,
I'm just saying.
>>: Yeah.
>>: What do you guys
are doing for work now?
>>: He is waiting
to get a job.
And I've applied
at 16 places.
And I've been looking
for a job for six months.
>>: So, how are you
supporting yourselves?
>>: Our parents. [laughs]
>>: Both of your
parents are...
>>: Yeah.>>: Yeah.
>>: Are you living
with them?
>>: We don't live together.
We both live
with our parents.
>>: Oh!>>: We have no money.
I had to ask my mom
to buy some...
Little stuff like
Titan tablets.
I can't even do that. But...>>: Hmm.
>>: How is your relationship
with your mom?
>>: She is my best friend.>>: Your best friend.
Does she know
you're having unprotected s#*x?
>>: Um...
We haven't had an whoopsie,
since the baby
is been born.
But I don't know
how much longer
that's gonna last.
I mean, me and my mom
have talked about it.
And she would like for me
to be on birth control in case,
but she thinks
it gives us a reason
to just have s#*x all the time.
Let's bring out mom and talk
about this. How about we?
Angie, come on out here.
How are you?[applauding]
[Angie] Hello. Hi.>>: Nice to meet you.
So, it seems like
they are, uh...
Kind of a Russian roulette
going on between these two.
Mom, what are we gonna do about
birth control for these guys?
[Angie] Um...
I... I do not agree
with anyone having s#*x
that's not married.
I'm sorry.
I know that I'm not normal.
[Drew] That's fine.
No, that's fine.
>>: But that's way I feel.
And I have that right
to feel that way.
There are just
too many risks.
It causes too many
emotional problems.
And it's not
the right thing to do.
And you have to be careful also
with birth control and diabetes.
So, it would have to be,
um, something highly suggested
by an endocrinologist.
>>: A condom would be
a simple solution.
If we're really gonna...
And that simple enough.
>>: Copper IUD is other one.>>: Right.
>>: You know,
we don't wanna think
about out kids having s#*x,
but they do.
And especially with,
somebody as diabetic,
you gotta be really
super thoughtful
and...[Angie] It's...
>>: Yeah. And I don't think
people fully understand.
If she doesn't take care
of herself
or if she got pregnant again,
she may not be the one who gets
to watch Gannon grow up.
[Drew] I know.>>: It's that serious.
>>: She doesn't see that.
We need some sort of commitment,
I guess, from both of you
that she is gonna go see
an endocrinologist
and get appropriate
birth control.
No? Mom.[chuckles]
One that meets
everybody's criteria.
>>: Yeah.>>: No?
>>: Yes, I want her
to be healthy
but I also wanna her to make
better choices.
>>: I'm just so fearful that
if there is an whoopsie,
as she calls it, that her life
hangs in the balance...>>: I completely agree.
>>: That's to support the body.>>: I do.
>>: So at least commit you'll
talk to endocrinologist...
>>: Yes.>>: ...about this.
>>: Okay.>>: I'm a realist too.
>>: This one takes away
my breath away a little bit.
This is a lot at risk here.
And, medically,
very very complicated.
Both of them. Very complicated.[Angie] Very complicated.
This is not something
most people have to deal with.
I mean, between
your head injury,
your neck injury,
your medication,
your diabetes,
your gestational issues,
your birth control issues,
your appropriate
kinds of values and concerns.
That makes this
very complicated.
Again,
I end up saying
almost every time
a new couple comes out here.
And it's...
Spirals out of control
because of a teen pregnancy.
That makes it just
so much more complicated.
>>: It does.
>>: Okay, and a reminder
to our viewers.
You need to understand
the importance
of pregnancy prevention.
This has been
a very cautionary tale
of how complicated it gets.
So, to educate yourself
log on to
16andpregnant.mtv.com
And when you're there,
just give this some thought,
think about what your life
would really be like
if you got pregnant
or if you got someone pregnant.
Also, discuss this
with your partner.
I'd say,
with your parents.
If your partner is cool enough
to have s#*x with you,
they are certainly cool enough
to talk about prevention.
Thanks to Mackenzie,
Josh and Angie.
We're gonna have more with
Mackenzie at the end of show
when she and the 11 other girls
come together for
the very first time right here.
But for now,
it's time to take a break.
We return with Sarah.
We saw Blake leave her
for life on a shrimp boat.
That's right.
Did he leave for good
or is he back
in his daughter Tinleigh's life?
That and more
when we return.
[applauding]
Welcome back to
Life After Labor. I'm Dr. Drew.
Now, incredibly, get this,
there are nearly
750,000 teen pregnancies
every year in this country.
Sarah is one of those teens.
And we are gonna talk to her
and her mom Tina.
And her baby's father Blake.
They have not all been together
in quite some time.
After this recap of her story.
Take a look.
♪
>>: I guess,
sometimes I wish that
we'd a little bit longer
before I got pregnant.
>>: Hopefully,
he will be supportive.
I just don't like the way
that he treats you sometimes.
Between Blake and mom,
they still aren't talking.
>>: Do you think
that Blake will leave
because of the stuff
with him and your mom?
>>: Well, I don't wanna be,
like, without him.
I don't know why
you'd call me a b#*##*h.
>>: I don't appreciate
you disrespecting my daughter
like that.
>>: I got nothing
to say to you.
I never do!
She ain't in this relationship.
Why does she have
to start in on me?
Well, that's why I don't like
staying here.
It's 'cause I'm not welcome.
>>: He better start
taking responsibility
because I'm not gonna tolerate
this behavior.
>>: Sometimes I...
just pay child support
and get out of here.
[baby crying]
[indistinct] ...disgusting.
I never ever wanna do this.
Something... [mumbling]
>>: It's terrible
that you don't wanna try.
To give [bleep]
about her family.
You [bleep] use us.
>>: That's it.
>>: How do you feel,
now that he has left?
>>: It'll be a lot easier
to talk about how I feel
if you didn't hate him.
>>: But he left.
>>: I understand that.
I realize he is not here.
[crying] I wish I would
have waited to have a baby.
>>: You are already tearful.
>>: Yeah.>>: What are you crying about?
>>: Just watching about,
like, talking after he left
is so hard.
Because it's all still...
Like, it still hurts.>>: Still fresh.
And where is he now?
>>: He lives
in South Georgia now.
So...
>>: Does he see Tinleigh at all?>>: No.
>>: So, it hurts
not just for you, but her too.
>>: I think it hurts
more for her than for me.
And, Tina, you have
to suffer through this
both for Tinleigh and Sarah.[Tina] Yeah.
You know,
we let him come
and stay at our home
and he just didn't
appreciate anything.
>>: So, you are feeling their
abandonment as much as they are.
>>: Yeah.
I mean, I'm not sad
that he is gone now.
'Cause I think she is better off
without him.
>>: Well, let me play
Devil advocate!
He said
he was sending you money.
He went to make
more money for you guys.
He went to be a shrimp--[Sarah] He didn't send anything.
He sent me, maybe, $200.
And $200
isn't gonna buy you...
[Tina] Is nothing.>>:...a month worth of diapers.
It makes me so angry.
>>: What is the worst part,
Sarah, of all this?
>>: Probably doing it alone.
>>: Mmm. You have your mom,
thank god.
>>: Yes. Yeah. I mean,
I'm so thankful for family.
If I didn't have
my family, I...
[Drew] Where would you be?
>>: Not in school.
>>: You missing up there,
in your education right now.
>>: I am in high school.
And I will graduate in June.
So, I'm excited.[Tina] Grades are good.
>>: Yeah, my grades are good.>>: Grades are good.
Towards the end of your episode,
you talked about
how you regretted
motherhood.
>>: Yeah, I remember it.>>: Tell me about that.
>>: Well, before
I got pregnant
I never wanted kids.
I didn't... Like, it wasn't
something that was, like,
"Oh, one day I'm gonna
get married and have kids."
That was never
in the plan for me.
I wanted to go
to college.
I wanted to move
to New York.
And I wanted
to be an editor
of a magazine.
And, now it's like...
I have to change everything
I wanna do.
Of course, like,
after you have a baby
postpartum depressions
is like a big thing.
>>: Did you have that?>>: Yes. Really bad. Really bad.
Especially after Blake left.
>>: Let's see what Blake
has to say about all this.
Let's bring him out.
You guys have not seen him
in several months.
Blake, come on out here.
Come on, Blake.
[applauding]
>>: Hey, Blake.>>: How are we doing?
>>: Have a seat.
So, you heard
what they are saying.
>>: Yeah.>>: You only sent 200 bucks
up from your
shrimp boating expedition
that was supposed to generate
so much resources
for your family.
>>: Right!>>: Let's start with that.
How come no money
for the kid?
>>: Oh, well,
first, I sent
a little more than that.
I sent, I think $300-$400.
And they are saying $200.
>>: Needless to say,
even if it was 400,
that doesn't support a baby.
Blake, is there anything
you wanna tell Sarah?
Well, you know...
Sorry, like...
I do have goals.
You know, I'm, uh,
Me and my cousin, we're gonna
buy a boat this year.
You know,
I've got my own house.
You know, I've got ambition.
>>: What kind of father
do you wanna be?
I will be there
for our daughter.
[Drew] Were your parents
there for you?
[Blake] Yeah,
a little bit, but...
You know, like...
Yeah, I don't know my dad.
I don't know him.
>>: You don't know your dad?
>>: No! I ain't got a clue
who he is.
>>: Do you want your daughter
to go through that?
>>: No, I don't.
[Drew] Haven't you, sort of,
set that all up.
She did... That's what
she wanted to avoid.
Well, both of you,
you guys are both recreating
your both childhoods.
>>: Both of you![Blake] Right.
>>: He says he wants
to be there
but he doesn't do
anything to be there.
Like...
"Because I gonna wanna move
back up there.
There is nothing
for me up there."
But if you love your child,
you would do that.
>>: Where would I work?
What would I do?[Tina] You had a job...
>>: Who cares if he makes
7.25 an hour.
If you with your child,
that's what matters.
>>: That's why you finish school
and go to college.
>>: If you love your...>>: No, that's not
what I might be doing>>: If you love your child.
>>: Okay, it isn't...
You screwed yourself
out of being happy
when you got me pregnant.
You don't get to choose
this is the job I wanna do
for the rest of my life.
Being eight hours
away from my child
and then say
you wanna be in her life.
It doesn't work that way, Blake.
If you love Tinleigh,
you give up
doing what you love.
Because I'm giving up
doing what I wanna do,
something that
I would have loved
because I love Tinleigh.
And I'm not gonna
put my self first.
>>: You got nothing to say?
[Blake] Mmm. I wish
I can take it all back.
I'd take back even leaving.
>>: You would've stayed
with Tinleigh?
>>: I would stay
with Tinleigh and Sarah.
I really would.
I'd do anything now,
getting 'em back in my life.
Really.
You know, I'd move back.
If I had a place to go.
>>: We'll see!
>>: No!>>: We won't see?
>>: No.>>: [chuckles] Okay!
>>: He said it
too many times.
[Drew] Alright,
fair enough!
Sarah, Tina, Blake,
thank you guys for joining us.
I appreciate it.
We are gonna step aside
for a break.
And then return with Kristina.
Her baby's father, Todd, died
when she was
three months pregnant.
Now the question is,
how is she doing today?
And what's become of the
relationship with Todd's family?
We will be right back
with the answers.
[applauding]
>>: We are back
with more Life After Labor.
This is the 16 and Pregnant
finale special.
Hosted by my self, Dr. Drew.
Now, our next mom, Kristina,
is here with me now.
And her story comes
with some really tough emotions.
Let's revisit her journey
on 16 and Pregnant.
♪
>>: My fiance passed away.
[woman] I remember
screaming her name
and just taking off
for the water.
Then I realized
Todd wasn't with 'em.
[Kristina] What's the point?
God let me... to be with
and get attached to.
And then just take him
but save you.
My stomach is cramping
and I have pressure.
>>: I think maybe we should
take you to the hospital.
[doctor] We have
a growth restricted baby
with low fluid.
>>: Do you think
he will be okay?
>>: Don't know.
But their environment
in there says,
I'm not conducive
for growth
and I'm not conducive
for the good things happening.
[Kristina] Look here.
Looks like Todd.
I can't handle
knowing it could
be different
if he was here,
He looks just like him.
He makes me remember.
>>: Remembering is not all bad.
>>: And welcome, Kristina,
into the program.
>>: Hello.>>: It's tough stuff.
>>: That's a lot.>>: That's a lot.
You almost drowned too.
Tell me what happened.
>>: Um, well,
we are just out
in the water playing. And, uh...
Todd got caught
in undertow first
and then we went to help.
'Cause we didn't really know
what was going on.
And then we all...
Caught in it.
>>: Did you know right away
something awful had happened?
>>: Yeah. Like, I remember
when they were, like,
pulling me to shore.
We were trying to tell 'em
that he was still out there
but they didn't see
anybody else.
So!
They were like,
"No, everybody is at shore."
And then you get to shore,
and then
he wasn't there.
>>: You kept complaining in
your episode of feeling numb.
>>: Like, it was like
the only emotion I had,
was to cry.
Like, that was it.
>>: To be crying
all the time?
>>: Mm-hmm. But t was like...
it was just like...
What happened made me cry but...
Then having
a complicated pregnancy,
that was tough,
and then leaving Lukas
and the NICU, it was...
That was even tougher.
It was just too much
at one time.>>: Too much.
And then you went to therapy?
>>: Mmm-hmm.>>: And that helped?
>>: It helped a lot
to talk to someone
who didn't know me.
Who didn't know anything
and just, like, vent it all out.
>>: How do you feel now?
Having to deal with
all this by yourself
or your mom still there?
>>: My mom is still there.
My grandma's there.
>>: Is there anybody else
in your life now?
>>: You know... My new, uh...
Fiance...
>>: Fiance?
>>: ...is there, a lot!>>: You have a fiance?
>>: Yes.
>>: That's a surprise.
>>: Yeah, it...
Fast.
>>: No, I don't think
it's too fast.
>>: Has he?>>: For me.
>>: Is he being a father?
>>: Yeah, he's there for Lukas.
But Lukas is gonna know
who his father is.
>>: What's your fiance's name?>>: TJ.
>>: TJ is stepping up
and doing the fathering?
>>: Yes. He's... Yes.>>: He's being supportive.
>>: He's being supportive
and taking care of him.
But Lukas is...
He has Todd's name.
He's gonna keep Todd's name.
He's gonna know about him.
>>: Kristina, it get's
a little complicated here
because your mom Kim's sister
is Dotty
who's married to Daniel
who is Todd's brother.>>: Yes.
>>: How are Daniel
and Dotty doing now?
>>: They're doing pretty bad.
>>: What's happening?
>>: Um, there're just
very critical
about what, um,
what my choices are.
>>: Seems like you had
a lot of guilt
about having survived
that drowning.
>>: Yeah.
It was hard to just like...
Sometimes to talk
to Dotty or Daniel.
Or Todd's mom.
'Cause I don't think
they understand how I feel.
It's just, when I talk about it,
it brings everything back, like,
he passed away
but it also brings back
the pain of me drowning
and me thinking
I was gonna die.
It scares me.
>>: And does TJ
now help you deal
with some of that?
Does he fill a void
that Todd left behind?
>>: Mmm.
>>: Is that a rush
to fill that void?
>>: I just wanted to be happy.
And feel happy.
And that's how he makes me feel.
>>: Now, during your episode,
we see you fighting
with your mom
an awful lot, right?
>>: Yes.>>: Kim?
Kim's your mom?>>: Mmm-hmm.
>>: How's your relationship
with her now?
>>: It's really good.
It's... We get along, we bicker.
Every now and then.
>>: But you were able to heal?>>: But--
>>: Mmm-hmm.>>: And she likes TJ?
>>: Yes.
>>: Alright, let's talk about
teen pregnancy for a second.
How did you get pregnant?
>>: Um, I was on birth control
but I didn't know that
when you take antibiotics
it cancels out
your birth control.
>>: Mmm.
>>: So that's what happened.
>>: What are you guys doing now
for birth control?
>>: Um, I tried the shot.
And I didn't like it.>>: Mmm-hmm.
>>: Side effects were so bad
for me, so...
But now I'm gonna
get the Mirena.
>>: The IUD. Excellent.>>: Mmm-hmm.
>>: Well, I must tell you,
it's quiet a story.
It is quiet something.
>>: But you're not dead.[chuckles]
You didn't die.
>>: I know.>>: And you deserve to live.
Lukas deserves to have a mom
and have a rich life.
And I want to give a reminder
to the people out there,
if you or a friend
are having a tough time
dealing with a loss
or any other tragic event,
head on over to halfofus.com
for resources and support.
Kristina, thank you
for sharing your story.
We're gonna step aside
for a second here
and take a break
then come back with Alex.
She strongly considered adoption
for baby Arabella
but ultimately,
she kept the baby.
Did she stick with that plan?
That answer
and more on the way.
[applauding]
♪
And we're back in the
16 and Pregnant finale Special.
I'm your host Dr. Drew.
And it is time now to speak
to our next mom, Alex.
But first, let's take
a look back
at how she got here.
♪
[woman] I mean, I did everything
I possibly could
to prevent this situation.
Do you have a plan of action?>>: I'm still figuring it out.
How do you feel
about adoption?
>>: It seems like
a pretty good idea.
>>: But I'm liking the feeling
of being called mommy.
>>: You have to put her
before yourself
and say what's gonna give her
the best opportunities
to have a successful life.
>>: We need to talk. Now!
I'm going into [bleep] labor.
[winces]
[baby crying]
I think it's pretty set
right now
that she's mine for now.
All I ask is that
you're committed to her.
Well, I want to be there.
I want to be a part of it.
[baby crying]
>>: Where are you, Matt?
and you flake out.
>>: We're two teenagers,
so that would be one reason
that a viable option
would be adoption.
But something came over me
at the hospital
and I couldn't
get rid of her.
>>: You didn't even sit down,
think of all the stuff.
Like, yeah.>>: Yes, I did every damn day
when you went disappearing.>>: [bleep] this. I'm done.
>>: Matt!
[crying] All you do everyday
is hurt me.
I don't want you anywhere
near my daughter anymore!
[sniffling]
[Drew] And Alex joins me now.
Alex, that was the last thing
you wanted
to have happen, right?>>: Yeah.
>>: But it's what happened.
>>: Yeah, pretty much.
>>: What are your feelings now?
>>: I just... [sniffles]
Looking back on it,
it kills me
because I know the only reason
in the world
why he didn't want her
was because he was more worried
about his friends.
I... I mean,
I'm very proud of him.
He, um... He...
He went into rehab
and he went to go get help.
But now that he's home,
it's just as bad.
>>: Well, he couldn't be here
with us here today.
We do have him
on the phone though.
Uh, Matt, are you there?
>>: [Matt over speaker]
Yeah, I'm here.
>>: How are you doing, buddy?
[Matt] I'm doing alright.
How about yourself?
>>: We are okay.
I'm here with Alex.
And give us an update.
You couldn't come down
and join us
because of
a legal issue, right?
[Matt] Yeah, I'm on probation,
so...
My probation officer
didn't me go down there.
>>: Are you sober now, Matt?
[Matt] Yes.
I'm doing Alright.
N.A. AA. meetings...
>>: Yeah, you have commitment
today in the meetings?
[Matt] Oh, yeah,
I've been trying to go.
I'm trying to go
at least two times a week.
>>: Two times a week?
Matt, dude!
I looked... I watched
your episode
and I can see
how bad your drug problem is.
You need to be going
two times a day.
Um...
Matt, you said
some rather profound things
during your episode
about being a teenager
and being a parent.
You wanna give us
some of your thoughts
about that right now?
[Matt] I remember going
[clears throat]
to the adoption agency.
And they had, like,
a little list of criterias.
What, um, parents should
be able to provide and...
I looked it out,
saw into myself and...
I couldn't really see
either one of us
being able to do those things,
meet those requirements.
And when I sit back and think
to even back then where I was,
I'm still in no way
to ready to raise a child--
>>: Matt, let me
just interrupt you and say,
the reality is,
I think most teen parents
would not meet those criteria
you mentioned
and yet everyone
is still a teen parent.
And that's the reality
of what's happening here.
But nothing right now,
for her,
is more important
than your recovery.
So, my friend,
I wish you the best.
And we'll say prayers for you.
Stay focused
and I'll try to talk to Alex
about your condition
a little bit, okay?
[Matt] Alright, thank you.>>: Alright. Good luck, Matt.
[Matt] Alright, thank you.>>: Alright, so...
Matt has an illness.
That's the reality.
And as a result,
just like any other disease,
it handicaps him
while he's in treatment,
while his disease is active.
And things like work
and parenting
are deeply affected by it.
>>: But he constantly
is asking me,
"I wanna see my child.
Can I see my child?
Can I watch my child?"
Sure, you can watch
your child.
And what I find out is,
he drops him... drops her off
with his mom and goes out.
And he's going behind my back
with other girls.
And then I'm getting
threatening voice calls
and text messages.
And I'm being attacked
and harassed
and I tell him about it.
And I tell... I show him
what they're saying to me
and he does nothing.
And then I find out
that he drinking alcohol
behind my back.
Because he'll do it
on one night...
Because he'll know that
it'll be out of his system
by his next meeting.
And then I find out
that he'll be smoking something
that wont show up in a test
or doing something
and it's like,
don't sit here and tell me
that you want to be
in your daughters life
if you, right now,
are supplementing your addiction
with something else.
>>: Two things
I would advice you.
One is I would
call his treatment program
and tell them.>>: I did.
>>: And, number two,
um, he's not allowed to see her
if he's using. Period.
>>: I just... I told him, I said
I want him out of my life.
I want him to sign
his rights over to me.
Just walk away
and let me find somebody else
that's gonna make it better
for her.
>>: What does he say to that?
>>: Nothing. He'll leave,
disappear
and then I'll get a phone call
later saying, "I love you
and I'm sorry and I miss you.
And I want to be with you guys."
>>: When was the last time
you guys hooked up?
>>: A week
and a half ago.
>>: Ten days ago.>>: Mmm-hmm.
>>: This is a pretty
tumultuous relationship.
>>: It's constantly
back and forth
and I can't take it.>>: Intense.
It's an intense relationship.
Now, it seemed like he was
pushing the adoption idea
and certainly your mom was.>>: Yeah.
>>: Tell me your thoughts
about that now.
>>: I still agree
with adoption.
Um...
Let me ask you
a tough question.
Would that have been better
for Arabella?
>>: I don't know.
>>: She wouldn't have
to deal with Matt.
She wouldn't have you
but you could've
an open adoption
where they could've...
>>: And I couldn't
have handled that.
I... I...
>>: Yeah, but you couldn't
have handled that.
Was that the right thing
for the child?
>>: No.>>: At one point
you had spoken
to a friend's parents
about adopting Arabella.>>: Mmm-hmm.
>>: Do you guys
still talk about that
or is that something
you contemplate?
>>: No.>>: Is that door shut?
>>: That door is shut.
I... After she was
a few weeks old
I did think about it
a little bit
but I can't let her go.
I have panic attacks
when I'm away from her
for just like five hours.
You know, I love having
that girl around me.
>>: Do you think
Matt will be in your life
ten years from now?>>: Nope.
I don't want him there.
>>: You hooked up with him
ten days ago.
>>: I know.
That's my biggest problem
I have right now is that
I always go back to him
because I care about him
that much.
>>: What are your biggest fears
for Arabella?
>>: Being in the situation
that I am.
>>: The cycle continuing.>>: Mmm-hmm.
>>: Well, a lot of...
a lot of your story
is the story of addiction
and substance abuse.
It certainly affected
your life deeply.
And now if anyone out there
knows someone struggling
with substance abuse issues,
head on over to
substanceabuce.mtv.com.
Or check out your
local 12 step resources,
AA, NA, CA.
Just go online, they'll actually
come and get you.
That's where you need to start.
Raise your hand, ask for help.
Alex, thank you
for being here.
>>: Thank you.>>: Alright.
When Life After Labor returns,
I'll chat with Myranda
and her baby's father Eric
as well.
So we'll be right back.
Stay with us.
[applauding]
♪
Welcome back to the
16 and Pregnant finale special.
I'm Dr. Drew and it's time
for our next story.
This now is Myranda's journey.
Have a look.
♪
>>: Are you ready
to have a baby?
>>: No. [chuckles]>>: Take care of it?
>>: I'm not ready at all.
You think you're ready
to be a daddy?
>>: Oh, hell no.[both laugh]
>>: Both of y'all are just
ruining each others lives.
Babies having babies!
>>: I'd rather just move
somewhere if we could.
It's a big step.
Living on our own.
[lock clicks]
Ew!
Gross!
It's messy.
[Eric] It used to be nice.
>>: I don't know.
>>: It's no secret
that I have a problem
with alcoholism
and drug addiction.
>>: Yeah, they found her.
They took her to a hospital.
And that hospital said
they're gonna send her
to some rehab.
I don't want my baby
to be around somebody like that.
[Myranda wincing][indistinct chatter]
[baby crying][woman] Yes!
Oh, mama! Oh, we're crowning.
>>: Can I hold
my grandbaby now?
>>: No, I'm holding him.
>>: Give me the baby.
>>: I guess, I'm scared
for her to watch her
'cause of how I've grown up
with her.
I pray that my trust for her
will build in time.
But it's not up to me.
It's up to her.
>>: So, Myranda,
there you go.
It's been up to her.
Has your trust grown?
>>: Um...
I want to trust her, you know,
as much as I can.
But you know, it...
It takes time in order
to trust somebody again.
>>: Yeah. Is she sober
right now?
>>: As far as I know.>>: How long has she been sober?
>>: Um...
>>: Couple of months.>>: Couple of months?
[both] Yeah.>>: Pretty good for her, yeah?
>>: Yeah.>>: That's something.
>>: Let's hope she is today.>>: Of what? [chuckles]
>>: We saw you hand the baby
over to her for a night.
What happened?
>>: Well, she said she didn't
have the phone on her.
>>: Did you believe her?
>>: I don't know
if I believed at first.
You know...
I mean, you could've got over
the baby to answer the phone.
>>: Yeah, you know,
I told her to make sure
you have your phone
on you.
And she
didn't answer it.
>>: When she didn't answer
the phone what was your fantasy?
What did you figure
was happening?
She was...[Eric] Passed out or something.
>>: Yeah.
>>: One of the cameras
came with you when you came back
and your mom
seemed pretty drowsy.
>>: Yeah, it's just
so hard to tell.
>>: Mmm.
>>: That's why it's so hard
to trust her.
>>: How's your
relationship now?
>>: It's perfect.
>>: It's great.>>: Perfect?
>>: Are you guys engaged now?
[Eric] Mmm-hmm.>>: Yeah.
Congratulations. That's nice.>>: Thank you.
>>: How did you...
How did you propose?
>>: I let the baby, like,
just, play with it.
And then I told her that
the baby had something
playing with it,
to get it from her or she might
stick it in her mouth.
And she was all mad at me
because I told her
to get the baby instead of me.[laughing]
And she walked over and got it
and started crying and stuff.
She'll always get mad at me
and then she'll turn like that.
[Drew] He's good at surprises.>>: Yeah.
>>: Yeah, he was.[laughing]
>>: Eric, when it comes
to birth control, uh...
Condoms, dude?
>>: Yeah. We...
We had condoms but...
Her.[chuckles]
>>: Oh, it's her fault
that you didn't use a condom?
[Eric] Ask her about it.
>>: I'm asking her.[Myranda] No. [chuckling]
>>: Yeah, tell him.
>>: No...>>: I had 'em.
>>: You had 'em?>>: Mmm-hmm.
And I wanted
to use 'em.
>>: She said she was
on birth control.
>>: I figured
since I was on birth control,
it wouldn't be
that big of a deal.
>>: And how is your relationship
with the Nana going?
>>: Um, it's going good.
You know, we have
rough times
but we also have
great times.
>>: Alright. Well, lets...
Eric's grandmother Nana is here.
She had a big part
in this story.
So let's bring Nana out
right now.
[applauding]
>>: How are you?>>: Fine.
>>: Nice to meet you.
Have a seat.
Oh, Nana, you said
something prophetic.
"Babies having babies."
>>: Isn't that what this is?[Nana] Yes.
>>: What did you think
when they first came home
with a baby?>>: Oh!
When they first
told me about it...
Ugh, I was... sick!
[chuckles]
'Cause Eric was still
in school,
she was
in school and...
That all changed.
>>: Eric, seriously,
what does your grandma's support
mean to you?>>: Everything.
>>: What would you do
without her?
>>: I wouldn't go
do anything without her.
>>: Do you ever tell her that?>>: I probably be...
>>: Do you ever tell her
how much you appreciate her?
>>: Yes.>>: I want to see you
do it tight now.
>>: Turn all the way over
to your grandma. Come on.
>>: I appreciate everything
you've done for me.
and I love you.>>: I love you too.
>>: I don't know what I'd do
without you. [chuckles]
>>: Now, Myranda,
you have to give her
similar kudos, right?
You appreciate her too,
don't you?
>>: Yeah, I appreciate her.
She knows it.
[laughing]
>>: Oh, goodness!
You guys are funny.
Alright, guys, well,
Myranda, Eric and Nana,
thank you so much
for sharing the story.
We're gonna take a break
and then return with Katie.
She and Joey
fought quiet a bit
but were trying
to make things work.
So where are they now?
That and much more on the way.
[applauding]
♪
Welcome back to the
16 and Pregnant finale Special.
I'm Dr. Drew and it's time
for our next story.
This is Katie's experience
being 16 and pregnant.
♪
>>: I never knew you as
the type of guy
that would, like,
want a girlfriend.
>>: Because I'm not
the type of guy
that normally
want a girlfriend.
>>: I wanted to go
to Denver with you.
I wanted to live
with my bestfriend.
And now, like,
I can't do that.
>>: We have been planning this
since day one.
>>: Not that I'm trying
to kick you out
when you get here, but...
I just want to know
what are you thinking?
>>: I don't want to, like,
to bring the baby home here
because I don't want to push
my child on you guys.
Like, I want to be able
to take care of my kid.
>>: Just 'cause
we're not out now,
don't mean
we're not gonna move out.
And it don't mean we're gonna
be there for five more years.
>>: It'd be perfect
if we could get our own house.
>>: I am sorry
but I obviously
can't do that for you.
I am sorry
that I make you feel
like such a piece
of [bleep], Katie.
I am sorry that
I [bleep] your life.
>>: At this point I don't want
the epidural. [chukcles]
>>: Okay.>>: I wanna do it naturally.
[straining]
[screaming]
[woman] There she is.
Here is your daughter.[baby crying]
Short hair!
>>: So, where am I taking you?
>>: To your mom's house.
[baby crying]
It doesn't feel like
I'm a person anymore at all.
It's really like,
I just sit home at night,
change, feed,
bathe.
>>: I feel like I work,
come home,
changes diapers,
get ready for work.
>>: I just feel like I...
gave up everything.
>>: Katie, Joey, welcome.
Katie gave up everything?
>>: For the most part.
>>: Joey, you're having
a reaction?
It's the first time
I've sat here
with the mom and the dad
and the dad's having as much
of a reaction as the mom.
[laughing]>>: Yeah.
>>: It's good.
What's going on?
>>: I don't know. I just don't
like watching us fight.
>>: The said fight
on bridge was tough.
>>: Yeah.>>: What was that all about?
>>: It was just kind of, like,
the stress of everything
that was happening.
And like, so much stuff came
crashing down on us at once.
And it was like
the hormones and...
We were scared.
[Drew] Sure.>>: Like, you hear so much
that it's not gonna work out.
And, like, we both come
from divorced families
and so we've never really seen
a relationship work.
And I am just kind of scared
that it's not going to work.
>>: How are things now?
[Katie] They are good.
We live together
on our own, finally.
And, um, he works
and I go to school.
>>: In the mine stone?
>>: Yeah.>>: You back in the mines?
So you are able
to live independently
because of what he is doing.
>>: Yes. He works
night shifts, so...
that's very rough on us.
>>: Is your work safe, Joey?
Would you worry
about his safety?
>>: Yeah, sometimes
I can't sleep at night.
'Cause I am afraid, like,
that something is gonna happen.
And then he comes homes
and he is like,
"Three ambulance came on
to my work today."
And I really don't wanna know
what happens
because it just makes things
harder for me.
You hear about cave-ins
all the time on the news.
[Drew] Yeah.>>: And...
I couldn't imagine what my life
would be like without him.
And I definitely won't be able
to do it without him.
>>: What are you doing
for birth control now?
>>: Now I am
100% birth control.
I am on the IUD,
condoms--
>>: IUD and condoms?>>: Yeah.
>>: So you...>>: I am breast feeding.
That's 100% but...
>>: And breast feeding?
You've got three protections.
[Katie] Yes.>>: Breast feeding, condom...
Breast feeding reduces
the risk of pregnancy.
Condom and IUD.[Katie] Yes.
>>: And did you think
about abortion or adoption
once you got pregnant?
>>: We considered
adoption, but--
>>: I did not
consider adoption.
You considered adoption.>>: I considered adoption.
We brought home, like,
these little books,
like, they make scrapbooks
with possible parents.
And we looked through it
and we sat down
with both of our parents.
And both of our parents
pretty much thought
that it was our choice
in the end,
and they'd support us
no matter what.
That's the way they are
and we realized
how supportive of a system
we had
and that we have
a lot of love to give.
>>: And how have
you changed your life?
>>: I didn't get
to go to school.
I didn't, like, get to go do
all my clubs stuff and--
>>: You were gonna go to Denver
to go to school, right?
>>: Yeah, my best friend
lives there now
and I don't. [chuckles]
So I gave up that,
like, all of my plans
for school
and my education
and my life alone.
>>: How about socially?
You've said
at point you felt lonely.
[Katie] Yeah.>>: You lost all your friends?
>>: Yeah, all of my friends
went away and...
Or they are doing other things.
We're completely different.
So, we don't really have
anything to talk about.
Like the times
that I do spent with them,
it's weird.
>>: So the pregnancy has changed
the direction
of your life entirely?
>>: Oh, yeah.>>: Yeah.
>>: Completely
flipped it around.
>>: So, no more...
Maybe not Dr. Katie
at least not for a while.
>>: Not for a long while.>>: Not for a long while.
We offer more information
about all the methods
of birth control.
How they work? What they cost?
Where to get them?
How to use them properly.
You can avoid getting pregnant
before you are ready.
Go to a great website,
it's called bedsider.org.
It's really good.
You can even sign up
for free text messages
to remind you to take your pill
or get your shot.
That's available at bedsider.org
Well, thank you guys
for sharing the story.
And when we come back,
Katie will be joined
on the stage
by the rest of the teen moms.
It's the first time
they'll be together in one place
and we will get to see
their babies as well.
So don't go away.
♪
[applauding]
Welcome back
to Life After Labor.
I am Dr. Drew.
Now, I am joined
by all 12 of our teen moms
in the same place, on the stage
for the firs time.
So I am gonna ask'em questions.
Okay.
Some of you have specific
questions for one another.
Hope, you have something
for Sarah and Kristina, right?
[Hope] Yeah, and Briana.>>: And Briana.
>>: I was just wondering
how's it like
to be a single mom.
Like, I can't imagine
doing it without Ben.
>>: I was born and raised to...
to realize that you really don't
need a man in your life.
You could do it by yourself.
But, I have my mom
and my sister.
[Drew] Kristina?
>>: It's hard
but if I need any help
then I could just call.
[Drew] Sarah?
>>: Um, in this, like,
by the definition single mom,
it's really hard.
Because I wanted my daughter
to have a dad and, like,
to be able to just...
How, like an example,
how a boy
should treat her one day.
But, like...
I have my mom,
and my grandma
and my family.
So it's not as hard as...
It probably would be
if I didn't have them.
>>: Anything you want
people out there to know
before we bring out the babies.
Lindsey?
>>: I just wanna tell everyone
that you should wait,
because you are only young ones.
And once you have a kid,
there is no going back.
>>: Mmm-hmm.>>: And it's hard. It really is.
>>: Alex, you have
something to say?
>>: Just respect yourself.
It's never ever worth it.
Because in the end,
you always lose.
You will always
feel like total crap
when they just walk away.
>>: Okay, well, listen.
I wanna thank all 12 of our moms
for sharing their
young lives with us.
It's been quite a journey
and thank you all
for watching this season.
But, it's now time
to bring out the babies.
Let's bring'em on out here.
♪
[applauding]
[Drew] For our viewers,
it's important to remember
that teen pregnancy
is 100% preventable.
Once there is a pregnancy,
every road ahead
is difficult, tough.
Go online to learn everything
you can about prevention.
All the facts are right there,
itsyoursexlife.com
We are gonna continue to follow
four of these girls,
their achievements
and their struggles
on an all new series,
Teen Mom 3.
Just keep an eye out for that.
It's coming soon.
I am Dr. Drew. Take care.
[appaluding]
♪