[funky music]
- Hi, my name is Catelynn.
[chime dings]
I'm 16, and I'm from
Algonac, Michigan,
a small town right across
the river from Canada.
During the winter,
there's absolutely nothing
to do around here,
unless you like ice fishing.
That's my boyfriend, Tyler.
We've been together since
seventh grade.
You're a little flirt,
especially in music class.
- We used to write notes
back to each other.
- My family situation
is totally chaotic.
- Let's get 'er done.
- I've lived in 13 different
houses since I was born.
Hate moving.
- My mom is pretty
unpredictable, and she can be
really moody.
- Bitch.
- She does her best,
but I never know if she'll
really be there for me.
My mom ended up driving drunk
last night and got pulled over
and went to jail.
Tyler's life has been hard too.
His dad, Butch, has been
in and out of prison for
most of his life.
[chime dings]
Even though Tyler and I are
used to surprises, nothing could
have shocked us more than
when our parents fell in love
and then got married.
So technically,
we're stepsiblings.
But we say that they're
the weird ones, because we
were dating first.
Even though it seems like
a recipe for drama,
for the most part,
everyone gets along.
But it's about to get a whole
lot crazier around here,
because I'm pregnant.
We're still juniors in high
school, and we're not sure
we're ready to be parents,
so we're talking about adoption.
- She cried.
- No, I cried for--
- I would cry too, Tyler.
- I did cry. I was so scared.
- It's, like, I got something
growing in me.
- You got something growing
in you.
- And that something turned out
to be a baby girl.
I don't really know
what I'm gonna do.
Me and Ty talked about, like,
keeping it, but there's not
really a lot of good things
about keeping it.
Like, there is, but there isn't.
You know.
There's scary things about
adoption, but I mean, like,
parenting, that, I mean,
that's even scarier.
- Dude, how'd you learn
don't get pregnant earlier?
You didn't use condoms?
- Yeah, I did.
I used them, and then they got
washed in the washing machine.
- And now you're pregnant.
- So are you gonna keep it?
- I don't know what I'm gonna
do yet.
If I give her up for adoption,
like, I always say, like,
imagine, like,
walking in there and, like,
feeling it move and, like,
it's in you, and then
walking out with nothing.
And you're just, like,
leaving with nothing.
- Like you did the total
nine months--
- Yeah.
- --for nothing.
- I don't think you're really
in, like, a position to raise
a kid.
- Like, how am I supposed
to raise a kid when I'm a kid
myself?
- Yeah.
I would cry, if I were you.
- I already did enough of that.
[percussive music]
♪
Although our friends think
adoption makes sense,
my mom is pretty disappointed
that we're considering it.
I thought it would be different
after I told you.
[chuckles]
Just 'cause that's--
- What? That I would hate you?
- No, just that you would,
like, that things would be
different, like...
- No, I still love you.
- I know you don't agree
with adoption, though, really.
- No, I don't agree with it.
You know, that's why I got to
state my opinion very much,
so...
You can change your mind
anyways.
Doesn't matter.
- And Tyler's dad was anything
but supportive.
- I couldn't imagine
giving you away.
I couldn't do it.
I wouldn't let your mother
do it.
I mean, I'll find some way.
- I want my daughter to have,
like, a chance at life.
And I know she'll have a chance
at life with me, okay?
But I just don't want her
to be raised the way
that she's gonna be raised--
- I'm gonna put it out here
like this.
Here's my son.
He's 16, 17 years old.
He has his baby.
He gives it away,
gives the kid away to some
great family, which are
great people.
And, uh, he didn't man up.
You didn't man up.
You wasn't the cowboy
I thought you were.
I don't know.
What am I gonna think?
I don't know what else to think.
- It really changes things not
to have our family's support.
But as hard as it might be
for my mom and Butch,
ultimately, we're the ones
who have to make this decision.
What do you think that
we should do?
- Keeping it.
Adopting it.
Those are our last two options.
- Well, keeping it would
probably be kind of stressful.
- I think keeping the baby
would totally ruin us.
- You think so?
- I know so.
I don't think our lives are
very stable to raise a child.
- No, like, my household.
- My household and your
household.
- Mm-hmm.
- You don't even got a job.
We're not graduated.
- Like, who would watch it if,
like, I went to school?
- Yeah.
- Whatever--whatever we decide
to do, I just hope everybody's
there to back us up.
- I don't care if anybody's
- Yeah.
- 'cause no one else's opinion
matters, especially my dad.
- We don't really know that
much about adoption, though,
really, just that...
I think it would be good,
though.
- I think adoption would be
the best option.
[mellow guitar solo]
[chime dings]
- Okay, so we've decided we're
not ready to raise a child,
but are we strong enough
to give one away?
- Our parents may not support
us, but we've decided to go
to the adoption agency anyway
to get things started.
- Can you tell me in your
own words why you think
an adoption plan might be
the right choice for you?
- I think it's the right choice
just because I don't really
have a stable household.
We're too young.
We want to go to coll--
we want to go to school,
you know, go to college,
finish college, get on our feet,
and then maybe have kids
later on.
- You're in the driver's seat
of your adoption plan.
This is gonna look and feel the
way that you guys want it to.
- I want to be able to, like,
maybe call her if I want to
or send her pictures
or send her Christmas presents
and birthday presents and get
pictures of her and stuff.
- So what--what we would do
when we're looking at adoptive
families is, we look at what's
called a profile book,
and it's a book that they
put together that has pictures
about them, that shows their
interests in life,
and you have the ability
to look through these.
So I can send some of these
home with you today.
- All right.
- Okay.
- You have to come to the place
where you make a decision
about what's right for you.
Sometimes the most loving thing
we can do is to be selfless
and let go.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- And so that doesn't mean
it's easy.
- No.
- It doesn't mean that it's not
without grief and without loss,
because I'll tell you,
it will be the hardest thing
that you've ever had to do
in your life.
[school bell rings]
- I was keeping up in school
and actually feeling pretty good
about our decision.
- Are you guys still thinking
about the adoption thing?
- Yeah.
Been a lot harder for me
than I thought it was gonna be.
- Yeah.
- You know, like,
actually deciding to do it
has been harder.
- You think you're gonna end up
going through with it?
- Oh, yeah.
Especially--for sure.
- Once you actually hold it--
- I'm not holding her.
I don't want to hold her.
- I'm holding that baby when
it comes out of your [bleep].
- I want to too.
[laughter]
- I know it's the best thing,
so I don't want to be selfish.
I don't want to hold her
and be, like, "Oh, I want you."
- This is the best thing,
though.
- But you should hold her--
- Could you imagine if we
kept her, how screwed up
that baby would be?
And, like, I talked--
I talked to everybody,
and they're, like, "Dude,
if I got pregnant right now,
I would just get an abortion."
- I would.
I'm telling you right now.
And I wouldn't have the strength
to give it away like you guys.
- Yeah.
- How many family profile books
did Dawn give you?
- There's ten of them.
Just gonna pick one.
- "Left is our
current family."
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, but see, we don't want
anybody with kids, though,
unless they're adopted.
- They're older, I think.
So this is the family that
I really like.
- [together] Brandon
and Teresa.
- She's skiing,
or whatever it's called.
- Water-skiiing?
- Water-skiing.
- I think it's good for our
daughter to have a stay-at-home
mom too, so that way, like,
she's not always in day care.
- I want--I want the dad to be
definitely college-educated.
Bachelor's, master's, whatever.
As long as he graduated
from college.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, husband.
He's a financial planner.
- So what's that?
I don't even know what that is.
- And this would be a good--
really good family, I think.
- I know, I really like them.
- I like these people.
- Look at that house.
- It's a nice house.
- So what do you think we're
gonna tell dawn next time
we go in there?
- We looked at some of them,
and we read them.
And--but nobody really
sticks out like they do.
- I think the same way, so...
With our family selected,
we made another appointment
to see Dawn, something Butch
wasn't too happy about.
- Where do you think
it's gonna be better off?
Not with your own natural
parents?
- Because we can't.
- I don't understand.
I mean, material-wise?
- Both: No.
- Emotionally-wise.
- Emotional, stable.
- Stable household.
A stable household.
- So it's not moving
all the time.
- Stable house--you make that.
That's your choice.
- Ha.
- Ha?
- How about so we keep
the baby?
Okay, so we keep the baby.
Six months from now,
we get it here.
Okay, the crib's in Catelynn's
small little room.
- Oh, it ain't good enough?
- No, you're absolutely right.
It's not good enough.
Not good enough for my kid.
My kid deserves way better
than this.
Way better.
- Okay.
- You're absolutely right.
Not good enough for my kid.
- Okay, I see what you're
saying.
All that baby needs is love.
- No, that's not all a baby
needs is love, Dad.
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
- I gave you the role model.
- You gave me a role model?
You weren't even in my life
for my whole life.
What are you talking about,
"Gave me a role model?"
you made a stupid choice,
and you were in prison.
- Give the kid some love, man.
- And it's gonna have plenty
of love in the house that
it's going to. Plenty of it.
- Screw that house,
that wherever it's going.
- Yeah. Screw this house.
[peaceful guitar music]
♪
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Despite our parents'
disapproval, Dawn came over
to Tyler's house because we're
ready to move forward with
the adoption plan.
- So you took home a whole
bunch of profile books, right?
- Yeah.
- And did you get a chance
to look them over?
- Yep, we did.
- Okay, did anything stand out
to you in them?
- [together] Brandon
and Teresa.
- Brandon and Teresa.
Okay, what about them stands out
as "the right family
for our baby?"
- Well, pretty much, I just
like everything about them.
Everything that I wanted,
they have, pretty much.
She's gonna be
a stay-at-home mom.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- And the dad's gonna be
the provider.
Like, in my heart it was, like,
a feeling that you just get.
Like, it's, like,
these are the people.
- So when's the soonest
that we can meet these people?
- Well, I--you know,
they have to book a flight,
so probably within a week or
two, we can do that.
If you guys are up for it.
- Okay.
- Oh, I'm up for it.
- When we get to the adoptive
family meeting, we talk about
exactly what you'd like to see
happen at the hospital.
- Okay.
- And, Catelynn, a lot of that
is up to you.
When the baby is born,
do I want immediate contact with
the baby in the delivery room?
And you're shaking your head,
"No, I don't."
so you've thought about it
a little bit. That's good.
- Yeah, I already know,
actually, what I want to do.
If I were to, like, even see
her, I'd get already attached,
be like, "No, I'm taking her
home with me."
I'd think I'd get really selfish
at that moment.
- I will tell you.
I have never had somebody regret
doing a hello and a good-bye.
- Yeah.
- And that is--that's a moment
that you can't recapture
later on.
And so it's something you want
to think about.
- Makes me want to cry.
- It does?
- Yeah.
- What part of it makes you
want to cry?
- I don't know.
- Aw.
- This is going to be harder
than I thought.
- Because it's harder to move
around these days, I'm trying
to keep up with school from
home, but I never thought
schoolwork would be the least
of my worries.
My mom knows I'm going forward
with the adoption,
but she's been dropping
not-so-subtle hints that she
wants me to change my mind:
bringing baby clothes home
and even buying a bassinet.
- 'Cause I think you'd be
a good mom.
- Mm-hmm.
- Me and Butch would help you.
- Yeah.
- It's my first grandbaby.
I already love her.
- Mm-hmm, well, yeah,
you love her.
- Well, I'm always gonna
be thinking about her.
And I think it will bug you.
- You think it will bug me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Scared 'cause if I keep her,
you know, and then I'm scared
if I give her away.
I'm scared of, like,
the pain I'll go through.
- Wait till she's born.
How do you think you're gonna
feel then?
- Yeah.
I don't know what to expect,
honestly.
- It's your decision.
You're the one that has to live
with it.
And you still got time
to change your mind.
- Yeah, I know.
Only nine weeks away from
my due date, my mom is taking me
to get a sonogram to check
the baby's growth and position.
I think she hopes it's going
to make me change my mind.
- Catelynn, do you know
what you're having already?
- Yep, it's a girl.
- Okay.
I'm gonna bring this up,
and we're gonna put warm gel
on your belly.
This is the placenta across
the top of the uterus here.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, now we're gonna try
and get a little bit
of the face.
It's tucked down here
pretty low.
- Oh, I see.
- You can see the eye
right here.
- She looks like you, Tyler.
- A little bit of the other
eye and the side of a hand
blocking her.
- Look at whose nose she's got.
- She's definitely got my chin.
- Mm-mm.
- For sure.
[soothing instrumental music]
♪
- I was worried that seeing
the baby would make my mom
too attached, but it may be me
who's getting attached.
Before I knew it,
we were only a day away
from meeting the adoptive
parents, Brandon and Teresa.
What happens if we meet them,
and, like--
- [together] We don't like 'em.
- Yeah.
What if they're really
snobby people?
But he just seems very, like--
- Dorky.
- Mm-hmm.
Dorky, but that's all right.
She can have a dorky dad.
- She's gonna be really loved
and cared for and watched out
for.
- When she's older, and, like,
she's, like, our age,
and if she wants to come visit
for, like, the summer
or something.
You know, she might be 18,
and she might just want to come
stay with us.
- Maybe.
- You never know.
The prospect of meeting Brandon
and Teresa for the first time
is making me seriously anxious.
I texted my mom to see
if she wanted to come,
and she was not happy.
Here's mom.
Hi, mom.
- Mom!
Through this whole time that
you've been pregnant, she's,
like, "I just have a funny
feeling she's just not gonna
end up giving her up
for adoption."
- Who, me?
- Yeah.
- That I'm not going to
or I am?
- Mm-hmm.
- That I'm not going to?
- She's, like, "I just have--
I just have this feeling.
She's just not gonna end up
giving her up for adoption."
- [sighs]
Now that the day to meet
the adoptive parents is here,
I'm even more nervous.
I just hope we like them.
- Hey, Brandon and Teresa.
This is Tyler.
- Hey, Tyler.
- How are you doing?
- Hi.
- I get the hug?
- Yeah, you get the hug.
- Good to see you.
- It's good to see you.
- So good to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi. [giggling]
My heart's racing.
- I know it.
- [giggles]
- You can sit there.
You guys have a seat here.
- Okay.
- It's good to meet y'all.
- I know; it's really nice
to meet you guys.
- The buildup to this, I mean,
we've been hearing about y'all
for the last few weeks.
Just time to meet.
Just time to get in front
of you, say hello.
So we're glad to be here.
- What--how many weeks are you
now, Catelynn?
- 31.
- Yep, 31 weeks.
- So we have nine weeks
till d-day.
So we're just gonna spend some
time getting to know each other.
And I'll just ask questions
and put you all on the hot seat.
Brandon, tell us how you guys
met each other.
- Teresa and I met, actually,
at church in our hometown.
Some mutual friends
introduced us.
- What do you guys do
for work, for employment?
- I work for a small
financial services company.
- And I work for a private
Christian school.
- So what brought you to
an adoption decision?
- When we got married,
we started trying to have
children, and, um,
just have not been able
to have children.
And so I have just felt for
several years that there's
a child that we're gonna have
through adoption,
and that's the right plan
for us.
- So I wanted you guys
to kind of tell them too
what you're thinking in terms
of, you know, pictures and
letters and kind of updates
and getting information.
- Personally, I want to be able
to, like, you know, like,
send her birthday presents,
'cause I will do that
every year.
I'd be, like,
"Got to go shopping.
Got to go get something
for her."
I want her to know that
I'm still there.
Like, I didn't just, like,
not care about her, like--
- It makes sense.
I think having correspondence,
interaction, certainly pictures,
and kind of whatever we can do,
it makes all the sense
in the world.
- I have a feeling we would
take tons and tons of pictures.
- What are your goals, then?
What kind of things are you
looking towards in the future?
- I really want my daughter to,
like, live in a household where
she's raised in a household
and she's not moving
like I've moved my whole life.
Like, I don't really have, like,
a really good, stable household.
Like, my mom, she used to have
problems, and I had, um--
I had to live, like,
go move in with my grandparents
and live with them for
seven months 'cause I couldn't
live where I was living.
And, um, sorry.
- It's okay.
- And, um...
[sighs]
I just want her to have better
than what I had,
and I know that I can't do that.
So I'm just doing the thing
that I think is the best.
And I know that you guys
can provide for her a lot more
than I can.
So I don't know.
- It's okay.
- [sniffles]
- After our meeting with
Brandon and Teresa,
Dawn wanted to see how we felt.
- So how did you feel?
- I feel like I know them.
- They're gonna be awesome
parents.
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah, they are.
- And I just loved that too,
like, right when I came in here,
she just, like, hugged me
so tight, like, she's, like--
Really loving people.
You can just tell.
- Okay, well, good.
We'll consider it an official
match, and we'll just keep
plugging along here,
moving forward.
- Mm-hmm. Definitely.
I really like it.
[cell phone chirps]
It's my mom.
- Whoa.
- She decided to call me back.
Hello, mother.
- Um, I went to go meet
the parents.
- Oh, well, I thought I already
told--
Bye.
- Bye.
- What did she say?
- Nothing.
She goes--she goes,
"You didn't even tell me
that you were going to meet
the parents today.
Thanks for bringing me."
- Yes, you did.
- And obviously, I didn't.
It sucks not having my mom
on my side.
I just hope she comes around
before the baby is born.
Over the next few weeks,
I tried to focus on
the good things.
Tyler and I spent more time
getting to know Brandon
and Teresa.
- Good to see you guys.
- It's been forever.
- I know. I know.
- They picked out a name
that we like: Carolyn,
Carly, for short.
We sewed a baby blanket.
- Too cute. Love it.
- That is really cute.
- And made a scrapbook
for the baby.
- Yeah, I think it's important
for her to be able to, like,
see what we look like, and--
- What everybody looks like.
Before I knew it, my due date
was around the corner,
and to my total surprise,
I went to the doctor,
and she told me she would
induce labor in three days.
[phone ringing]
Hi.
- Do you have something
to tell me?
- Yes. I went
to the doctor's today.
- And?
- I'm getting induced
on Monday.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Oh, my goodness.
How do you feel?
- [laughs]
- Are you nervous?
- Yeah, I'm nervous.
- Maybe--maybe we can get up
there in time and we won't
miss it.
- Yeah.
[door slams sharply]
Are you locking me out?
- [sobs]
- You okay?
- No.
- Don't sit in here.
You're making me feel bad.
- [sniffles]
- It'll be all right, Ma.
Since we're going to
the hospital Monday morning,
Tyler decided to write a letter
to our daughter so she will
always know where she comes from
and that she is loved.
I want to hear what it--
yours says.
- Okay.
"first off, I want to tell you
I love you so much.
Words can never explain the love
a father has for his daughter.
When your mom and I found out
she was pregnant with you,
we didn't know what we
were going to do.
We were so young and
inexperienced in life yet.
After thinking and thinking,
we came to the decision that
adoption was the best choice
for you.
The thought of what kind of dad
I wanted to be and what you
deserve in life just didn't mix.
I think about you every day.
You are everything to me.
I don't ever, ever want you
to think I didn't want you.
I will always love you.
You are in my thoughts
every day.
Love, your daddy."
- That's sad.
You're gonna make me cry.
Come here.
Give me a hug.
- I don't know.
But it's so hard
to give her away.
- I know. It's gonna be
really hard.
- And now it's getting
so close.
It's, like, the reality
is really starting to hit.
[inhales]
- Like, you always tell me
we can do this, right?
- Yeah.
- We have to do this.
- This is what we prepared for.
- But it doesn't matter
how ready we are,
because ready or not...
[chime dings]
this baby's coming.
- I can't believe I'm on my way
to the hospital to be induced
and that I'm going to give birth
sometime today.
I've been through so much
already, and I still feel
totally unprepared.
[woman speaking indistinctly]
- Do you have a problem
with IVs?
- No, I just don't like
needles.
- Okay, then don't watch.
- Once it's in, I'm done.
- Okay. I'm gonna
draw your blood.
So you're gonna feel it
move around.
It's gonna feel weird.
- Okay.
- Every half hour, we're gonna
put the pitocin dose up.
- Does that make my
contractions or something?
- It will make your
contractions.
- 'Cause I've already felt that
they were already getting
a little bit worse,
unless that's in my mind.
It feels like I had
a little one.
- A little contraction?
- Mm-hmm.
- [heartbeat thumping]
- How far apart are they?
They're not that far apart.
- Uh-uh.
- Yay.
Then they're gonna come in
here and...
- Boost it up more.
- Mm-hmm.
- Knock, knock.
- Hi.
- Hey, how you doing?
- All right, I guess.
- Yeah?
What I'd like to do is
go ahead and check your cervix,
and I want to break your water
for you.
- All right.
- Once we break your water,
there's no turning back.
Okay, now I'm going to break
your water, so you'll feel
pressure here, and just again,
feel your muscles.
Let them fall into the bed.
Perfect. Pressure now.
And that's your water.
Here you go.
And the fluid--
- God, it feels like
I'm peeing myself.
- I need a towel, please.
- Okay.
- There you go.
You're doing good.
Hang in there.
We waited nine months for this.
- Yeah.
[exhales]
- Okay, honey.
- [breathing deeply]
[sniffles]
[heartbeat pulses on monitor]
- Oh, honey.
- [sighs]
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- It's gonna get better.
- Once you get your epidural,
there's gonna be a pump
hooked up--
- [sighs] Sorry.
- That's okay. You can
breathe through it.
Just keep breathing.
You're doing great.
- [exhales]
- There you go.
It's at its worst right now.
It's gonna be coming down.
- Is she getting the epidural
now?
- Yeah.
- Yep. Yep.
They're right outside the door.
- Okay.
- I will--
Breathe, Cate.
- Mom, it frickin' hurts.
- You got to breathe, Cate.
- I got my epidural
while Tyler went to meet
Brandon and Teresa,
who were going to wait
in the reception area.
- Hi, guys.
- How you feeeling?
You doing all right?
- Yeah.
- Hanging in there?
- Hanging in there.
Yeah, trying to, at least.
Trying to hang in there.
- Ty, you're a little pale.
- Yeah.
- Got a little pale.
They checked her just now,
and she's between five and six.
- And she's right between
five and six?
- And she's 100% effaced.
- That's good.
She's definitely progressing,
then.
Like, who else is upstairs?
- My mom, her mom, and Sarah.
- Do they know we're coming?
- Yeah, yes.
[laughter]
- I hope I'm not getting
everyone freaked out,
but they told me.
It's--she's at 9 1/2.
It's, like, okay.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my.
- I'm shocked.
- You're at 9 1/2?
- Mm-hmm.
- Holy crap.
How are you feeling?
- All right.
I'm glad I had her check me
again.
- How are you?
- Are you feeling the urge?
- Yeah.
[exhales]
Yeah.
- Okay, I called Dr. Niver,
and she's coming up.
- I'm feeling the urge
right now.
Like, I am, bad.
- I know.
- [exhales]
Hi.
- Yeah.
- That's good.
- So, Tyler, you're gonna help
her hold one of her legs?
- Okay.
- Okay, I'm gonna have you
come over on the left here.
We'll have Tracy over here.
You're gonna bring them
up and out.
You're gonna take a deep
breath in, and you're gonna
push down right on your bottom
like a bowel movement
would feel.
Do you feel like you
need to do it?
- Yeah.
- Let me get some gloves on.
And we'll try.
Just breathe.
Doing--
your baby's head's nice
and low, so you're gonna do
great with this.
All right.
- Yeah.
- Put my game clothes on.
Now, remember what I said.
Knees this way.
More. More.
Perfect.
Now, right now,
take a deep breath in.
Hold your breath.
And push down right here.
Push.
Even more.
You're doing great, Catelynn.
Harder. Harder.
Perfect. You're doing awesome.
Baby has hair.
- [exhales]
- Okay, let it go.
Another breath in.
Push down hard.
Two, three.
Stronger. Four.
That's okay. Five, right here.
Hold on. Seven, eight.
Push, push, push, nine.
Ten, let it go.
Hard.
Push down.
Two.
Pull those legs back.
Push down. Right there.
Four, pour it out.
Five, we're moving her.
Six, keep going.
Seven, don't stop.
Eight, go, Catelynn.
[all speaking at once]
- [gasps]
- Okay, another try.
Another breath. Big breath.
- You ready?
- And go, there we go.
There we go, honey.
- Eight, lots of pressure.
- And there we go, honey.
- Let it go.
You're okay.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're doing good.
You're doing--
You're doing really good, honey.
You're doing so good, honey.
- Now, I want you to open
your eyes.
I want you to open your eyes,
and I want you to look
right down here.
- I don't want to see.
- Look, Cate.
- Open your eyes.
- I don't want to see.
- No, she doesn't want to see.
- Then just push. Go ahead.
Push her out. That's it.
- Okay.
[all gasping]
- There she is. You did great.
Hey, baby.
Aren't you cute?
- Just sucking her nose out.
Catelynn, you want
to take a look?
You want to take a look?
- No.
- She's beautiful.
- Aw.
- All right.
- Standing by.
- Fresh from god.
There you go, love.
- I know.
- It's okay. I'm fine.
- She's okay.
Support her, honey.
Don't think about yourself.
- I'm fine.
I'm all right, okay?
[slow instrumental music]
♪
[chime dings]
- You okay?
- Just sore.
- Yeah.
- Did you see it?
- I'm shaking so bad.
- I know.
- Did you take pictures?
- They're all down there
taking pictures now.
- Good-bye.
Don't worry.
- Don't even think about it.
- I kind of want to see her.
- I think so too. I feel it.
Even though I said Brandon
and Teresa could hold the baby
right away, I wanted
to be the first to hold her.
- Hey.
- All right.
- What's the story?
- Well, she--Catelynn just
had her, and she's healthy,
and everything's good.
She wanted to, um,
see her real quick
and just hold her
and say whatever.
- She does?
- And then after she's done
with her, she kind of wants,
you know, to let you guys
can hold her.
- Okay.
- Yeah, that'll be easy.
I bet none of us
will be crying through that.
Where is she now?
- She's in the nursery.
- Okay. Have you held her yet?
- No.
- Okay.
Are you going to? Okay.
- Yep.
- You doing all right?
- You hanging in there?
- Yeah.
- We'll do the very best
we can.
We look forward to holding her--
- We're gonna love her so much.
- I know.
- I promise.
- I know. I know.
- I promise we'll take
good care of her.
- I know.
[echoing music]
♪
- Don't matter.
- Like this?
- Yep.
Okay.
Hi, baby.
You're right.
She looks like you.
Are you kidding me?
- You think?
- Yeah.
- ♪ You could take this
for granted ♪
♪ Or you could take it
so hard ♪
- You want to hold her, Ty?
- Yeah, I'll hold her.
Hi, sweetheart.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
You want to hold her?
- Hi, little one.
Even though Butch isn't here
and my mom's making herself
scarce, my friends came
to the hospital to see the baby.
- Oh.
- Hi, Tyler.
How are you?
- Oh, my god.
It's good to see you
out of Catelynn's belly.
- Are you okay?
- Hi.
What I would--I was just
wondering if I could talk
to you and Tyler for just
a minute.
Since we're five hours out
from delivery, I was wondering
if you would feel comfortable
for--with us, like, taking
a time-out from friends
and family, and you going ahead
and doing with Brandon
and Teresa.
So what do you think?
- All right, well, I want
to get pictures with Ty first.
- Right.
- So I'll just tell them--
I'll just try to entertain them
and hold them off for--
- Oh, it'll only be, like,
ten more minutes, I think.
- Okay, all right.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Do you want to hand her off
or...
- I don't care.
- No, sit over here.
[inhales]
- There they are.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Hi.
- We saw her through
the window.
- I know. I'm sorry.
- No, no, no.
So cute.
- Catelynn.
She's beautiful.
[gasps]
Hi, baby girl.
[laughs]
Wait, don't start crying on me.
Hi, precious.
Hi.
You're so pretty.
- I don't know if you've
seen her eyes yet or not.
Has she opened her eyes at all?
- She opened her eyes.
- In here?
- Yeah, it's in the bag.
- Here, I'll pull the card out.
I'll give this to you,
and I'll let you read the card,
and then I can kind of
further explain it.
- Moving around a little bit.
- It's pretty.
- That's my little--
- I like that.
- What does it say?
[giggles]
- Oh.
"Always in my heart."
- I have one too.
And we have one for Carly too.
And, um...
So the plan is that I will
always be wearing mine,
and you can be wearing yours,
and then when she's old enough,
we'll give her hers as well
to wear.
We're just so gonna be linked
for life, and we just can't
thank you enough for, um...
For this gift.
We just want you to know
that you will always be
in our hearts.
- I'm never gonna take it off.
- I'm never gonna take mine off
either.
And it'll be really special
for her when she gets old enough
to know that--that--
how much we love her,
but also just how much
you guys love her as well.
- That means so much.
- We needed my mom to sign
the adoption papers
in order to give Brandon
and Teresa the baby that day,
but since she refused,
the handoff could not happen
on hospital grounds.
[sniffles]
[solemn piano music]
♪
- It'll be okay.
- I know.
- ♪ I want faith
♪ I want faith in everything
♪ I want faith
♪ I want time to slip away
- It's okay.
- ♪ Let tomorrow be the day
- She knows that we love her.
- ♪ I want time
[door clicks open]
- Hi.
You guys getting ready to roll?
- Yeah. We're getting ready.
- Okay.
All right.
You're gonna be okay, right?
- Yeah.
- Hey, honey, we'll take
a ride on the elevator.
- Okay.
All aboard.
[mellow rock music]
♪
- You have to keep this
over her face
because of the wind.
- ♪ Open up your eyes
- There's our cute outfit.
- Hi, baby girl.
- ♪ Waking up from sleep
♪ The storm is over
- Let's see if I can make it
through this hug.
See you later. See you later.
- Bye, Teresa.
- Bye.
- She's just really gone now.
- Yep.
Well, she's off to
a better life now.
I kept her blanket.
- Did you? Yeah?
That's good.
- [sighs] Yeah.
[soothing guitar music]
♪
- It's not easy, like,
having a baby inside of you
for nine months and getting that
connection and wondering what
she's gonna look like
or who she's gonna look like
and then just giving her
to somebody that you
barely even know.
It took a lot of strength
for me not to take her home
with me and Tyler.
- I love you.
- I love you too, Ty.
- I didn't have a stable
household.
I didn't have two parents.
I think she's gonna have
a really great life,
because Brandon and Teresa
are really awesome people.
I'm really interested to see
what she's gonna be like
when she's older too,
like, if she's in gymnastics
or if she's a runner
like Teresa.
Maybe one day when she's older,
we might be able to get
to know each other.
Santa Claus--me and Santa Claus.
[giggles]
It hurts my feelings that
my mom doesn't support me.
It's kind of hard to deal
with that, because your mom,
out of all people, should be,
like, your number one supporter.
Getting pregnant at 16,
I really wasn't ready for it.
It made me want to make
my life better, go to college,
get an education.
- So the answer is ten.
- Really?
And me and Ty, we've gotten
a lot closer through this
whole experience, and he's still
the love of my life,
and hopefully one day
me and him will get older
and have kids together.
Giving my child up for adoption
was the hardest thing that I'll
ever have to do in my life.
Nobody wants to give their child
away.
I just did what my heart
told me to do.
I think that Carly's gonna
one day come to me and Tyler
and tell us, "Thank you."
I'm at peace with my decision.
[chime dings]
- We're gonna get deep inside
each mother's story
as the entire cast comes
together for the first time.
- I felt so bad for you.
- Baby Weston has
some medical issues.
- He has something wrong--
- It's better without a condom.
- Don't listen to that.
- You should have wrapped
your willy.
- Where is
your supportive partner?
- God, you're gonna
make me cry.
- Do you currently have
a boyfriend?
- I wish I could
find a man.
- DR. DREW: We have got a
surprise you do not wanna miss.
[upbeat piano music]
♪
- ♪ Go these nine awful weeks
♪ Don't know how I'm gonna
get through it all ♪
♪ I'm weak,
but I'm strong enough to see ♪
♪ When it's ♪