- I'm Chelsea, and my life
is all about having fun.
I live in Vermillion,
South Dakota, and I'm really
close with both of my parents.
But since they got divorced
a few years ago, I mostly live
with my dad, because I'm a total
daddy's girl.
Can we make this?
- Squash?
- I've wanting it all day.
My dad really gets me...
except when it comes
to my boyfriend Adam.
[chime dings]
Adam, like, changed his Facebook
status, and it was, like,
"I wish Chelsea wasn't such a
whore and didn't want all my
friends and just wanted me."
- Well, then, I suppose, we
don't need to talk to him
anymore, do we? Ever?
- With me and Adam, there's
always drama.
He usually has a problem with
whatever I do and whoever I do
it with.
Are you going to Jack's?
- I have no idea.
- Well, I'll probably go,
if that's okay.
- No matter how much drama we
may have, he's in my life for
good now, because I'm pregnant.
- I was a junior when I got
pregnant, but now it's the end
of summer before my senior year,
and I'm coming back to school
with a much bigger belly.
I don't really know what to
expect.
All I know for sure is,
I'm having a girl, and we're
naming her Aubrey.
- When you go back, do you
think will be shocked, like,
at how big you are?
Or, like, does everybody know?
- I'm pretty sure everybody
knows.
Like, I think everybody knows.
- What are you going to do with
Aubrey?
- I'll probably just put her in
daycare.
Unless you want to, like, quit
school and come be my nanny?
- Totally.
- Hey.
I don't think I'm scared of
giving--having her.
Like, giving birth.
- I'm scared for you.
- You are?
- Yeah.
- I don't want to poop when I
push her out.
Seriously, I asked my doctor
about it.
- What did she say?
- She said, "Oh, it's normal.
We won't tell you if you do."
- I would want to know.
- No, I don't want to know.
I'll be all embarrassed.
You better not tell me.
- [laughing] I won't.
- If you start laughing,
I'm kicking you out.
You'd be scared.
- If I was pregnant and I was
pushing out a baby and I started
pooping, you would laugh your
ass off.
- Shut up.
- You would.
- Not if we're in the moment.
Talking to Megan about being
pregnant is easy,
but telling my dad about it
was one of the hardest things
ever.
Didn't mom tell you I was
pregnant?
- Yeah, she just called and
said, "We got a problem."
And I just kinda guessed.
- Yeah, but I can't even take
regular medicine.
- I know.
- I was just really scared to
tell you.
I felt like you were going
to be sad
that your, like, your youngest
baby was going to have a baby.
- "Disappointed" is the word
you're thinking of,
and I was.
There's no use flying off the
handle and wigging out about it,
because you can't undo it,
so you have to accept it.
- There's not a choice to undo
it for us.
- No, not for us.
- Did you ever think I should
give it up for adoption?
- I didn't think so. No.
Because we've got a strong
enough family that we could
always take care of it.
- Like, I was in the hospital
and the doctor, like, as he was
telling me I was for sure
pregnant, Adam was texting me,
like, breaking up with me
and saying I should get
an abortion and stuff.
Then the next day he, like,
completely switched.
He's just being really nice
and, like, happy.
So I was like, "Okay, maybe it's
going to be good.
Maybe this is going to fix
everything."
- The last thing he was looking
for was more responsibility.
- Like, it's going to turn out
fine.
My dad's not going
to take my word for it.
He wants to talk to Adam
himself.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
- Want to have a little talk?
- I s'pose, yeah.
- "S'pose, yeah," huh?"
We've had a little past,
you and I.
- Yeah, it's been bad.
- And, you know, I'm not above
forgiving...
- Yeah?
- And accepting things if you'd
treat my girl the way she needs
to be treated.
It's time to put up or shut up,
and is it going to change?
- Yeah, it's going to change.
It's time to get serious and
grow up.
- Why is it time now?
- I don't know.
It's just time.
- You know, some of the things
that you said in the past
would've led me to believe that
you really couldn't give a hoot
about the baby.
Is that the way it is, or is
that--I don't have a whole lot
of faith in things.
- Yeah, it'll change.
When the baby is born, I planned
on staying here for a couple
weeks.
Pretty much just, like, almost
live here and stay with her
while Chelsea's in school.
- I don't know about moving in.
As far as--but staying for
periods of time is two totally
different things.
- Yeah, definitely.
- Odds are you won't be moving
in.
You think it's going to be cool
to get--to have a baby?
I mean, you're excited?
- Oh, yeah. Really excited.
- You like staying up all
night?
- Yeah, actually I do.
- Poopy diapers.
Screaming kids.
- I don't know about that.
- Throwing up.
You don't have to like it,
but you just have to be ready
to deal with it.
So I want to toss the ball to
you. It's in your court.
- Okay.
- What did he say?
What did he say?
- He said it was time to get,
like, serious.
Obviously.
- And not get mad so easy?
- You too?
- I know, both of us.
So we're together.
- Yeah, we're together.
- And serious.
- Yeah.
- I love you.
[chime dings]
- My dad tossed the ball to
Adam, and he's running with it.
Things are better than ever.
We've never been so in sync.
Okay, bye.
Give me a smooch.
I just hope it lasts.
- I've been having early
contractions, so I've been going
in for ultrasounds every week.
Adam can't come to my
appointment today, so I invited
Megan and my mom instead.
- No. I don't even know
what they are.
- It's like a practice
contraction.
And when I went to that doctor,
I was a fingertip dilated.
- Fingertip?
- Yeah, that's the beginning.
- So it's, like, always open
that much?
- Yeah, I guess.
That's weird.
- It can go up to, like, what,
ten?
- That's too big.
- I don't know.
Shoulders.
You got to get those shoulders
in there.
- Tight squeeze.
- And the head. Oh, boy.
- Don't even start.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
- My mom should be coming.
- When is she coming?
- Soon.
We can start it.
- All right.
[bottle squelching]
- Ooh.
- Is this first pregnancy for
you?
- Yeah.
- Third.
- Shut up.
- She's driving me crazy.
- It's going to be kind of dark
in here.
- Hi. I didn't want to miss it.
- I'm going to have you put
this arm up, if you can.
The head's down right now.
- Oh, please move, baby.
- She's so cute.
- You've been having
contractions or anything?
- Yeah.
Because of my contractions,
the doctor wants to see me.
- So what I'm going to do is,
I just want to check your cervix
with those contractions, okay?
Let's see, you're just going to
feel my fingers.
- Okay.
- So, yeah, that head is
dropping.
And, yeah, I would say that you
are about a centimeter dilated.
And that cervix is starting to
thin down, so--
- Is this going to mean I'm not
going to go 40 weeks?
- It's hard to say,
but I wouldn't, you know--
potentially.
- Since the baby could come
early, my friend Laura is
helping me get organized.
- What do you think you're
going to bring her home in?
- I don't know. I want her
to be comfortable.
Those are all newborn onesies.
I like this one.
Do you like this?
- Yeah.
- Okay, we have our outfit.
[chime dings]
Now let's try it out.
I don't think this is going to
work.
- I think the diaper's too
little.
- [laughs]
it's on backwards.
She's so fat.
She doesn't even really care.
- This is the part that
the dog--[laughs]
- Look, everybody.
Chelsea and Aubrey.
- Good girl.
Okay, we'll take it off.
While I was spending my
free time getting ready
for the baby,
Adam's been spending his free
time working on his car.
But tonight he's supposed to
meet me for one of the last
parties of summer.
[phone rings]
The only problem is,
I can't reach him.
- He ignored it.
- This is bull.
- So either way, if he's
coming, are you going?
- He doesn't want me to go to
the party,
if he's not here.
But I'm going to to anyway,
I think.
- You think?
- No, you're going.
- I'm scared.
- Why are you scared?
- Because he'll be mad.
He thinks, like, that I'm going
to go out and, like, get guys
and stuff. Which I'm not.
- Have fun go getting guys--
- With my big belly.
- Call again and see if he'll
answer.
[phone rings]
- What time are you going to be
here?
Or what time can you leave,
do you think?
- So will you try to hurry
and get here not too late?
- Okay, bye.
- So are we just going to sit
here and wait for him?
- No.
[upbeat rock music]
♪
Okay, so we're going to go
even if Adam's going or not,
right?
- Yep.
- Like, before he gets there?
- We're just going to meet him
there.
- Okay.
Adam and I have been so good
lately, I don't want to rock
the boat, but my friends are
tired of waiting.
- Did you text him?
- I told him to meet us at
Ryan's, and he's pissed.
- Just don't worry about it.
- That's good stuff.
- [laughs]
- Hey.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- How's it going?
- [indistinct chatter]
- Savies.
Do you want to feel?
Feel, like, right there.
- Push?
- Yeah, push. Don't you feel,
like, a--
- Yeah, I feel it.
- Hi, Adam.
- What's up?
- Adam.
- What's going on, dude?
- You won't even kiss me.
I'm your girlfriend.
- Making me feel alone in a room
full of people is not what I
need from my boyfriend.
Whatever.
- What am I supposed to do?
- What, am I supposed to stay
here?
- Aren't you coming back?
- I don't [bleep] know.
God.
- Why does he have to ruin
everything I do?
- It's okay.
- It's not okay.
This isn't fair.
If this is Adam trying to make
our relationship work,
I'm in trouble.
- I thought Adam left me at
the party.
Oh, it's Adam.
But a few minutes later,
he came back.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- So you just want me to leave
you alone until you calm down?
- I'm calm.
- Then give me a kiss and hug
and be nice. Yeah?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Stand up.
[chime dings]
I'm glad Adam came back.
Thank you.
But when he treats me like this,
it just makes my friends even
more concerned.
- So you guys have been together
for, like, a year and a half?
- A year and a half, yeah.
Off and on.
- But he wasn't like this at
the beginning--
like, acting like this.
- So why do you keep on going
back to him, though?
- I want it to work.
Like, I really like him.
Obviously.
Like, I go back to him no matter
what he does.
And I'm pregnant.
- Well, yeah.
- And now, like, I really want
it to work.
- Yeah, just for--even just for
the baby's sake.
- Yeah, I think she deserves
to have a mom and dad.
- I don't know, he's just,
like, said so many, like, mean
things and, like, horrible
things.
- But then I feel bad.
Like, maybe I was the one who
made him, like, mad,
that he would say that.
- But you didn't do anything.
- Nobody understands, I know.
- I understand.
- I'm kind of, like, hoping
when he sees his baby--
- He might changed.
- --something might change.
- And then I think when you get
to a certain point, you need to
stop going back to him though.
But do you know
when that point is?
- I don't know.
[chime dings]
and I don't want to find out.
As of right now, we're still
together, and we're spending our
last Saturday of summer fishing
with our friends.
Ooh!
I'm going to catch a fish.
- You couldn't catch a cold.
- [giggles]
- What do you think of starting
your senior year pregnant?
- I don't know.
It just--I'm kind of sad.
- Why are you sad?
- Because I won't be able to do
everything.
- Do you wish you weren't
pregnant so you could?
- No.
- Then why are you sad?
- Because that's part of senior
year, going out and doing
whatever you want.
- I can still go out and party.
- Don't be dumb.
I kind of want her to be, like,
a daddy's girl.
You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
- Like, he wants a boy,
but I think when he has his
little girl, it'll be different.
- Ha ha.
- And how many weeks till
the baby's born?
- Like, nine.
She can come before that.
Why do you have a rock?
- They're throwing it.
- Why?
- Because that's what they do.
- Where you throwing it in at?
[splash]
[laughs]
There goes all our fish.
- I'm glad Adam and I are being
kids while we still can.
I wish summer would never end,
but there's a lot to figure out
before the baby comes.
- What you doing?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
We got to talk over school.
What's my number one goal?
- You want me to graduate.
- With your class.
- Yeah.
- How do you think you're going
to handle walking through
the halls pregnant?
- Fine. That's not a big deal
at all to me.
- That's not a big deal?
- Not at all.
- Okay. What about the stupid
talk behind your back
as you walk down the hall?
- I'll yell.
- Well, no, you don't yell.
You can't change it,
so you hold your head up high.
- Hey, I'm not worried at all
about how school's going to be.
- [bell rings]
- When I used to imagine my
senior year, I wondered what
yearbook title I'd get;
if I'd be homecoming queen,
and what I'd wear to prom.
I never imagined being pregnant
and not being able to fit into
my desk.
- Yeah.
Aubrey Skye.
Actually now I'm having one of
those Braxton Hicks contractions
or whatever.
My stomach is really hard.
- So now go back into your
"y" equals--
- I suddenly feel like I'm
having contractions.
I'm trying to focus on math
class since they're probably
just practice, but they seem to
be getting worse.
- Negative 2 is?
What do you think, Chelsea?
What are you doing?
Laura, will you help me?
- Yes.
- Something doesn't feel right,
and I need to get out of here.
Laura and I ran to the nurse.
She thought I was in labor.
The next thing I knew, I was
being rushed to the hospital.
By the time Adam and my family
got there,
the pain was unbearable.
[moans]
Finally, the doctor said it was
time to push.
But it's five weeks early,
and I'm terrified for my baby.
I can't believe this is
happening now.
- Here we go. Grab those legs.
There you go.
Push down nice and hard.
Push, push, push, push, push.
Good.
One more big push.
Big breath.
Good job. Very good.
That's a great last push.
Okay, ready?
Here we go.
Come on, big push.
A nice and strong one.
- Go, go, go, go.
Good job, Chelsea.
- Good.
- Good job.
- Go. Oh! Oh!
- She's so small.
- Ms. Harmony, 3792.
Dr. Harmony, 3792.
- Even though Aubrey was born
five weeks early, and the
doctors were really worried
at first,
it seems like she's going
to be okay.
- She is quite jaundiced,
which is something that is--
all pre-term babies are at risk
for.
- Yeah, so this light makes
the jaundice levels go down.
- It does.
- But having a preemie means
having to deal with all kinds of
problems.
- I know you wanted to nurse,
but she just doesn't have the
strength to do that right now.
- What about her temperature?
Is that a big concern?
- Yeah, when babies are
premature like this,
they have a harder time
regulating their own
temperature.
That might make her start having
respiratory problems.
- Does it hurt?
- No, it feels cool.
[laughter]
- Yeah, there you go.
- Okay, I don't want to get,
like, your hair in the milk.
- Look at that.
Hey, I think she smiled at me.
- What about her temperature?
Is she keeping--
- It's better.
Like, she only has one blanket.
She doesn't need a hat.
Aubrey's getting stronger and so
is our family.
Adam even asked that she take
his last name on her
birth certificate.
I couldn't be happier.
- ♪ Just a little bit
- Baby's not going home today,
maybe even not going home
tomorrow--
may not be going home for
a week--but you are getting
discharged today.
- Even though it's time for me
to go, the doctors want to keep
Aubrey in the hospital so she
can gain some weight.
I don't want to leave you.
Yeah.
I'll be back.
Since my mom lives near the
hospital, Adam and I are staying
there to be close to her.
When I woke up the next morning,
I couldn't wait to get back
to Aubrey.
Are you coming with me or not?
- I don't know. I'm tired.
I don't see whey we can't stay
here for a couple more hours
and just sleep.
- Because I want to go there.
- Okay, then go.
- Well, can you please just
come and sleep there?
- No, I can't sleep there.
- I feel like you don't care.
- Don't even start.
- Well, I do.
Okay, whatever.
I'm going to go see our--
my daughter.
- It's not like I'm not ever
going to see her again, Chelsea.
- My mom drove me to the
hospital, where Adam said he'd
meet us later.
- She just ate about 22 ccs,
okay?
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Oh, I missed her.
- Did you call him again and
see if he's coming, or
what's the deal?
- He won't answer.
He's sleeping.
[phone rings]
- Your call has been forwarded
to a--
- Irritating.
- Super irritating.
It may have taken awhile,
but Adam finally showed up
to see Aubrey.
[laughs]
- She's just going crazy. Oh.
- Look at that.
She's, like, doing it herself.
Don't even have to hold it.
- Adam brought his friend along
because he's got big plans
later.
You can go work on your stupid
car.
- Don't call it stupid.
I don't call her stupid.
- That is not the same thing.
Don't even compare that.
- I know.
Don't get all mad.
- That was a really dumb thing
to say.
When are you going to be back?
- Later.
- What time?
- I don't know.
- So Adam took off to attend to
his other baby.
[engine puttering]
- That sounds so good, dude.
Are you going to drag race it?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- I told Adam that I'm spending
the night at the hospital
because we might be able to
bring the baby home tomorrow.
I really want him to be here
with me.
Then I talked to him this
morning, and he didn't even
sleep last night.
He worked on his car all night.
So he hasn't even gone to sleep.
- Oh, my gosh.
So then he'll sleep all day.
- Yeah.
- Probably.
- If she gets to go home
and he misses that, like,
I don't know how I'd be able
to forgive him.
- Oh, my god.
- Chelsea.
- Hi.
- The doctor's been here,
and everything's good.
And she's ready to go home.
- She is?
- Yay.
- Hey.
- Nice diaper bag.
- It's so cute.
I'm scared to drive with her.
I can't believe Adam's missing
this.
I thought he'd show up to be
part of Aubrey's first moments
at home, but I guess not.
I've decided to stay at my mom's
for the first week so she can
show me what to do with this
baby.
What if she starts pooping?
- Well, I'm going to leave her
diaper on for now.
Okay, let's do her hair first.
You kind of start from the top
and go down.
Okay, and then put a little bit
of soap on her.
You getting your first bath.
- I like your hair better
fluffy.
- Then you kind of just work--
work down her body.
And that's really it.
- She's clean?
Did you like it?
I'm starting to realize just how
much there is to learn.
Even though I could've use some
help getting home, Adam finally
woke up and came over.
Here, help me.
Don't you hold 'em like this?
- I don't know.
I've never done this.
- Okay, you gotta hold still.
Okay, ready for boob time.
You gotta help me, babe.
- What?
- You gotta hold her,
or something.
Ugh.
- Oh, my god.
- It hurts.
- Is something coming out?
- I don't know.
It hurts.
How do I do this?
Can I switch boobs?
- I don't know. I don't care.
- You should care.
- We should go to Z'kota Grill
tonight.
- Why?
- Well, Adam, I have her.
- I know.
Can't your mom look after her?
- Well, maybe it'd be best for
you to stay here since it's
the first day she's home.
You said it was going to be
different once she came home.
Didn't you?
- What?
You didn't say it was going to
be different?
- So can you just stay here
today?
- [sighs] The whole day?
- Yes, the whole day.
- And the whole night?
- Yes, the whole night.
- No. It is
the first night home.
- Ooh. So?
[chime dings]
- Adam promised to step up
now that Aubrey's here,
but it seems like he's stepping
out instead.
- After a week at my mom's,
I'm ready to come home to my
dad's and try to get back to my
normal life.
I'm so happy to be home.
[coos]
Ugh.
She always--
Why did she do that?
- [crying]
- You should paint her teeny
little fingernails.
- I know, I want to.
When do they start smiling?
- Not for a long time.
- Hold still, bubba.
Don't cry. Owee.
Ugh.
- [crying]
- What are you doing?
But nothing about my life is
normal anymore.
- [crying]
- The baby stays up all night.
Can you go to sleep, please?
I'm tired.
- You're not tired.
You took a nap.
- I'm so tired.
Do you think I'm lying about
being tired?
- Well, it doesn't matter.
You get used to it.
- It seems like I'm never going
to get a break.
- [crying]
- Especially since Adam's never
around.
- Hey, time to get up.
It's 2 o'clock in the afternoon.
- What the hell?
[sighs]
- I'll get on that.
[door slams]
- I think your mommy's grumpy.
- I can't even think about
going back to school.
And to be honest, I'm not sure I
even care.
- [crying]
- What's the matter?
She's so sick.
Are you going to go to
the doctor today?
Yeah.
Aubrey's breathing funny.
The doctor thinks that she has
RSV, a respiratory virus
that preemies are at risk for.
So I'm taking her in to get
checked out, and I'm hoping
Adam will come.
But not surprisingly,
I can't reach him.
Hi.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Good.
Should we take a look at her?
Sometimes RSV just causes the
cold symptoms and the stuffy
nose, and again, sometimes
there's issues with the lungs.
So we'll listen and see what she
sounds like.
[phone vibrates]
- Hello?
- I was just going to see if
you were going to come to her
doctor's appointment with me.
- Well, yeah, "probably not"
because I'm already here.
- Okay, bye.
- Um, in the lungs I do hear
just a few little wheezes.
We have to watch that pretty
closely.
- Would she have to stay in the
hospital at all for this?
- If it got bad, yes.
- Okay.
- If she starts breathing
really fast, um, or hard,
then she needs to be seen again.
Yep, yep.
- [coughs]
- You okay?
Yeah.
- [coughs]
- Adam's showing no concern for
Aubrey's health.
I know I have to confront him.
Adam is coming, and I'm, like,
scared.
- Why are you scared?
- I don't know.
Because I want to bring up how
he, like, doesn't come around
when she--
like, she was sick, and he just
said he didn't want to come.
And it's not--it's
not an option.
And he just doesn't come around
for, like, the important things.
He wasn't there when she came
home.
He doesn't come to her doctor's
appointments.
- When is he there?
Just randomly?
- When I go to him.
- Do you ask him what he wants?
- Yeah.
"I want you to not be dumb."
but I don't know what that
means.
Like, I don't know how I'm being
dumb.
Like, I'm "being dumb" because I
want to hang out with him
and because I want him to come
help.
- But that's not being dumb.
- I know it's not.
- He shouldn't even say that.
- ♪ It's better on Sunday
- Okay, he's here.
Oh, my gosh.
- Don't let him talk down
to you.
- ♪ Just go away
♪
- Hi.
Hey.
- What have you been doing?
- I was up in Bridgewater
pheasant hunting.
- Why didn't you come the other
day when I needed you?
- I don't know.
Because I was talking to my
parents about some stuff.
- Okay, well, you could have
come after.
I really needed your help.
- Looks like you did fine.
She's not dead or nothing.
- You are her dad.
Don't you think you should help
me?
- I understand that I'm her
dad.
You should stop saying that.
You say it about every damn day.
- Do you have any idea how you
make me feel?
- Okay, do you have any idea
how you make me feel when you
ask the same [bleep] every day?
It gets pretty annoying,
and that you call me, like,
constantly.
Like, every missed call on my
phone is from you.
- What do you want, like,
with us?
- You to stop being annoying.
What do you want out of this?
- I thought you'd come around
more.
- It's not like I'm doing
anything bad.
I'm either working on my [bleep]
or hunting.
- Yeah, well, sometimes when
you're doing that stuff,
you should be there helping me
with the baby.
I want you to be able to, like,
give up hunting or something
one night to come help me.
- Yeah.
- I don't get to do those
things.
- What, you want to go hunting?
- No, I mean, like, I don't get
to, like, just go out one night
with my friends all the time
like you do.
- I don't know what--
you want me to [bleep] take her
so you can go out and party or
what?
- I never once said anything
about partying.
Can you please get off your
phone?
I'm just trying to talk to you.
- What does that have to do
with anything?
I'm listening to you.
- Because it's distracting.
- Now you're just preaching
at me.
- I'm not--
- Yeah, you are.
- I'm just trying
to have a conversation.
I want to be good.
- Okay, I'll just shut up
and quit talking about this.
My god.
- [sighs heavily]
I thought Adam would change
when the baby came,
but I guess I was wrong.
I just don't know if I can do
this without him.
- Since our talk, Adam shut me
out completely.
Your dad's a jerk.
A big jerk.
He won't even answer my texts
anymore.
The more I try to reach him,
the more depressed I feel.
How do I stop wanting him?
- Just keep concentrating
on her.
- Her who likes just like him
and is half him?
- Yeah.
- Chelsea, have you ever
noticed how, like, you don't
dress up anymore?
- Well, I spill, like, crap
all the time.
Like, now when I get dressed up,
I just don't even think I look
good.
I feel so humungous.
- Oh, shut up.
- No, I'm serious.
Like, you don't understand.
Mama feels ugly.
You made me fat.
I'm getting more and more
depressed, and my dad's tired of
seeing me sulk over Adam.
- You just have to move on;
you know it, everybody knows it,
everybody tells ya.
- I don't know what's wrong
with me.
Like, I don't want to be done
with Adam.
I just thought he was going to
change, but he didn't.
- He thought he was going to
change, and he didn't,
and he won't.
- Like, this is not what it
used to be at all.
And it's not just because I had
a baby.
- You gotta just get your
priorities straight:
baby, school.
And have fun at school.
It's still your senior year
regardless.
- Since I haven't been to
school in almost three months,
I'm worried that I won't be able
to catch up.
But my dad's right.
It's time to get back out there.
So I made an appointment to
speak to my guidance counselor
about reenrolling.
Pixie!
But getting out of the house
takes forever now,
so I'm already running late.
We're going to be late.
Now that I'm at school,
everyone wants to see her.
And now Aubrey
needs a diaper change.
Ooh, that's kind of cold.
It's so weird just being at
school, and I have my baby.
You're at school.
We don't like this place.
- You can't let her think like
that.
- Yeah, you're supposed
to like school,
but mommy doesn't like school.
Mama wants to stay with you.
Everything's taking way longer
than I expected, and I was late
to meet with my guidance
counselor.
I just want to know if I'm going
to be able to catch up and
stuff.
And all the fricking lights
are off.
Are you serious?
What do I do?
Just leave?
- I guess.
- [sighs]
I realize that I'm missing out
on a lot by having this baby.
But I've decided not to miss out
on tonight's homecoming game.
Do you think people are going to
think I'm being a bad mom
because I'm going out tonight?
- No, it's your homecoming.
- Honestly.
- It's your homecoming.
- I'm really scared.
Like, I feel bad.
- Your priorities have changed.
- Why doesn't Adam get that
feeling?
He hasn't seen her in, like,
three weeks.
Why does--I want to know why.
- I can't answer why he does
things.
I don't know what goes on in
his head.
- I always tell him that, like,
he needs to bond with her
and stuff, and all he says is,
"I have her whole life to bond
with her."
- He's just bonding with his
car.
[hip-hop music]
♪
- [together] S-E-N-I-O-R-S!
Seniors!
Whoo!
- Please, will you go to
the dance?
- I don't know.
I kinda want to go, and then I
kinda don't.
I'd just rather, like, chill
at home with my baby.
- You can bring her.
She'll have so much fun.
- Even though I'm having fun
hanging out with my friends,
I skipped the dance because I
really want to be somewhere
else.
I missed my pumpkin.
It didn't take long for Adam to
hear that I'd gone out.
[phone rings]
- Yeah?
- Do you say this stuff just to
make me feel like crap?
- Okay.
- Okay, sorry.
[phone vibrates]
- Hello?
- Dad?
- Yes?
- Can you come home, please?
- He said, "Tell me where and
when to sign the papers over
for that mistake."
- Dad, please come home.
Dad, please.
I don't want to be home alone.
- Chelsea.
- I just really need someone to
be home.
Please come home.
- Okay.
- I need my dad to come home
because I feel totally destroyed
after Adam's hateful text.
- Hey.
What's all going on?
- He, like, says mean things
to me which, like, hurts my
feelings.
But when he said that about her,
that was different.
I think it's sinking in that
he's mean.
Like, when he said that he wants
to sign over his rights to
"that mistake."
- How does that make you feel?
- Makes me feel way worse
than when he tells me anything.
- You know why?
- Because she's--
- Because now you're the adult
and you're seeing him say and
pick on somebody who has no
defense.
- Yeah, she didn't do anything
wrong.
- You have to start using his
meanness as your motivation
to get out of this.
- I think we need to change
her last name.
- He's done nothing to deserve
to have his name carry on.
- I don't feel nervous, and I
don't feel sad.
I feel like changing her name
is, like,
what I'm supposed to do.
- Yeah.
- I'm over, like, being sad.
- Are we here today to talk
about a name change maybe?
- Yes.
- How did the current name
become the baby's last name?
- He kind of, like, talked me
into it.
- This has been a yo-yo
relationship.
- Okay.
When was the last time that this
was on again?
- A week ago. Two weeks ago.
It's been, like, off and on
so many times.
- So is there a chance that you
may change your mind?
- No. Not about her name.
- When Aubrey starts school
someday, you want her to have
the same last name as you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Is that, like, your top
reason or--
- There's a lot of reasons.
That's, like, a big one.
- Okay.
Megan, I have a question
for you.
Are Chelsea's motives good,
in your opinion?
- Absolutely.
- I mean, is she doing this
for the best interests of
Aubrey?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- I know closing this chapter
with Adam will be hard,
but I'm doing it for Aubrey.
- What are you doing?
- Smile.
With Adam out of the picture,
it's time to focus on moving
forward.
- All right, guess who I talked
to.
- Who?
- School.
They're giving you a break.
So you're going to take care
of it.
You can finish and you can
graduate.
- They said that? How?
- By not missing anymore
and getting the work done.
- Were they mean about it?
- No, they want you to
graduate.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be
bending over backwards for you.
- So I just need to, like, make
up what I missed
and then it's cool?
- Yeah.
Just make up what you missed
and go to class.
- Honestly, like, I know it's a
big deal, but, like, that's just
not what I think about.
- Well, it should be.
- I know.
I know it's what I should be,
but it's not.
- Ideally, it would have been
great if you'd have graduated
at semester time.
- Okay, sorry.
I'm not an overachiever.
- It's just,
I want an achiever.
- Dad!
- I'm not being greedy.
- I achieved a baby.
A pretty cute one.
- I want you to achieve
a diploma.
- We need more formula.
Before I found out I was
pregnant, I didn't really have
a care in the world.
And then I found out I was
pregnant and everything changed.
- [together] Hi.
- Hey, little peanut.
- First, Adam was really
supportive and nice.
But the reality is, he's just
not ready for this,
and he's not ready to grow up
and take responsibility.
He's not ready to get a job
and be a little family,
which is sad because that's what
I wanted.
I'm working on trying to make
the best decisions that are for
me and for Aubrey.
No, I do want to graduate.
It's just harder than I thought.
But I want to graduate.
- You will.
- I want to.
- As of right now, I'm getting
incompletes in all of my
classes, and I'm not sure
if I'm going to be able to fix
this, but I, like, I want to.
I don't know all the answers.
What's the matter?
Are you having a bad dream?
I'm just trying to figure out
what the right thing to do is
for me and my daughter.
[chime dings]
- Female announcer: on the next
16 and pregnant...
- This is the only
blood-related family I have.
And now everyone's making me
give him to somebody else.
Let them raise him.
- It would be such a mistake
for you and for this baby
to bring him into this house.
- I have my final answer,
whether they like it or not.
I'm keeping him.
- Why are we playing these
games, Lori?
- I'm not really not decided
yet.
- I'm just at, like, wit's end.
- She's been causing problems
since day one.
- Dad, get him out of here.
Get him out; oh, my god.
- ♪
♪ All these nine weeks
♪ Don't know how
I'm gonna get through it all ♪
♪ I'm weak
♪ But I'm strong enough
to see ♪♪