>> I'M MEGAN.
[grunts]
IT'S GETTING A LITTLE BIT
BETTER.
I'M A HIGH SCHOOL JUNIOR
FROM AULT, COLORADO.
I'VE NEVER BEEN OUTSIDE
OUR TINY TOWN, SO I'M REALLY
EXCITED TO GO TO COLLEGE
AND SEE WHAT ELSE IS OUT THERE.
I'M 16 YEARS OLD AND THE BABY
OF THE FAMILY.
IT TASTES FUNNY.
>> WELL, YOU WANT CEREAL?
>> NO.
>> YOU WANT PANCAKES?
>> YOU WANT EGGS?
>> MM, NO.
MY DAD AND MY SISTER ARE BOTH
IN THE MILITARY, SO THEY'RE ONLY
HOME A FEW MONTHS OF THE YEAR.
>> HI.
>> I LOOK UP TO MY SISTER
MORE THAN ANYONE IN THE WORLD.
>> YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
>> SO IT REALLY SUCKS
WHEN SHE'S NOT HERE.
MOST OF THE TIME, IT'S JUST
ME AND MY MOM IN THE HOUSE.
OR AT LEAST IT WAS,
UNTIL I MET MY FIRST BOYFRIEND
AND THE LOVE OF MY LIFE,
NATHAN.
>> YOU'RE A BAD-ASS.
>> I KNOW.
NATHAN WAS A BIG PARTIER,
BUT ONCE HE MET ME,
HE SETTLED DOWN.
HE GRADUATED FROM HIGH SCHOOL
LAST YEAR AND HASN'T GOTTEN
A JOB, SO INSTEAD, HE PLAYS
VIDEO GAMES AND VIDEO GAMES
AND VIDEO GAMES.
HE FIGHTS WITH HIS PARENTS
A LOT ABOUT IT, SO MY MOM LET
HIM AND HIS VIDEO GAMES MOVE IN
WITH US.
MY DAD WAS AGAINST NATHAN
MOVING IN, BUT SINCE HE WAS
IN AFGHANISTAN AT THE TIME,
IT HAPPENED ANYWAY.
>> STOP THAT.
>> NOW THAT HE'S BACK,
HE THINKS NATHAN SHOULD GET UP
OFF OUR COUCH AND GO GET A JOB,
ESPECIALLY NOW, BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
WHEN I LOOK AT MY BELLY,
IT'S SOMETIMES STILL HARD
TO BELIEVE, BUT NATHAN AND I
HAVE HAD SOME TIME TO GET USED
TO THE IDEA.
>> SO WHAT NAMES DO YOU LIKE
NOW THAT WE KNOW IT'S A BOY?
>> UM, I LIKE BLAKE.
AND ETHAN'S KIND OF CUTE.
>> ETHAN?
>> YEAH.
>> I DO LIKE BLAKE.
I THINK BLAKE'S THE BEST ONE
SO FAR.
>> YEAH.
HOPEFULLY HE'S OUTGOING LIKE YOU
AND NOT SHY LIKE ME.
>> WELL, WE ARE, WHAT,
THREE YEARS APART?
>> THREE YEARS, THREE MONTHS.
>> AND YOU'RE PRETTY IMMATURE
STILL.
>> [laughs]
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> NO, I JUST HAVE A CHILDISH
SIDE.
>> YOU'RE STILL JUST
A LITTLE KID, YEAH.
>> WHICH MEANS I'LL HAVE MORE
FUN WITH THE BABE.
>> YOU'RE A 5-YEAR-OLD TRAPPED
IN A 16-YEAR-OLD'S BODY.
>> YOU ARE A JERK.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S WHAT'S WRONG WITH
19-YEAR-OLDS.
[laughter]
I'M GLAD NATHAN AND I CAN JOKE
AROUND ABOUT BEING SO YOUNG,
BUT MY DAD JUST GOT BACK FROM
OVERSEAS, AND HE DOES NOT
THINK THIS IS A LAUGHING MATTER.
>> SHE SENT ME A FRICKIN' EMAIL
AFTER I WAS ALREADY BACK
IN IRAQ.
>> IT WAS YOUR MOM'S IDEA.
>> YOU KNOW, I OPENED IT UP,
AND I WAS...
FRICKIN' TRUTHFULLY
BROKENHEARTED.
>> WELL, I WAS EVEN WORRIED TOO,
'CAUSE YOU LEFT, AND SHE DIDN'T
HAVE A BELLY.
YOU COME HOME, AND SHE
HAS A BELLY.
SO I WAS AFRAID THAT WOULD
TRIGGER--
>> IT'S CUTE.
>> IT'S NOT CUTE.
IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST SO
DISAPPOINTED BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS CAN'T BE KIDS ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW, YOU GOT TO MAN UP.
YOU GOT TO GROW UP.
>> I TOOK IT OKAY,
BECAUSE I HAD TO.
>> I KNOW, AND WE'RE GONNA
DEAL WITH IT.
DOESN'T MEAN WE HAVE TO LIKE IT.
>> I WISH MY DAD WERE MORE
APPROVING, BUT HE'S BARELY BEEN
HOME IN THE PAST YEAR, SO HE
HASN'T HAD TIME TO SEE WHAT
I SEE IN NATHAN.
>> IMAGINE WHERE WE'D BE IF WE
DIDN'T--IF WE WEREN'T GONNA HAVE
A BABY.
>> NOT STANDING IN
A BABY'S ROOM.
>> WELL, THIS WOULDN'T BE
THE BABY'S ROOM.
THIS WOULD STILL BE WHERE
OUR BED AND STUFF WAS.
>> YEAH, YOU PROBABLY
WOULDN'T LIVE HERE.
>> YEAH.
I'D BE LOST SOMEWHERE.
>> PARTYING.
>> YOU THINK I STOPPED, THOUGH?
>> YEAH, YOU WERE A BAD KID.
NATHAN USED TO SPEND ALL HIS
TIME PARTYING WITH HIS FRIENDS,
BUT NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT,
HE HAS TO GIVE THAT ALL UP.
I THINK HE WILL STEP UP,
BUT MY FRIENDS TEND TO AGREE
WITH MY DAD.
>> YOU KNOW HOW I FELT
ABOUT YOU AND NATHAN
ALL THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I NEVER REALLY LIKED IT
'CAUSE I THOUGHT--I JUST--
I THOUGHT IT WAS BAD NEWS.
>> YOU ALWAYS SAID I COULD
DO BETTER.
>> SO HOW DID YOU REACT?
LIKE, HOW DID YOU FEEL WHEN
YOU FOUND OUT?
>> I CRIED, AND I WAS SCARED.
>> OOH.
>> ISN'T THAT CUTE?
>> I'M SO HAPPY IT'S A BOY.
THEIR CLOTHES ARE CUTER.
>> [laughs]
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT
OF ANY NAMES?
>> YEAH, WE'VE THOUGHT OF
A COUPLE.
WE REALLY LIKE THE NAME BLAKE.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED WITH
THE BIRTH CONTROL?
>> IT GOT CANCELED OUT
BY SOME ANTIBIOTICS I WAS ON.
>> OH...
DID YOU EVER CONSIDER
ALTERNATIVES?
>> WE HAD TALKED ABOUT THEM,
BUT I KNEW FROM THE, LIKE,
BEGINNING THAT I WANTED
TO KEEP IT.
>> IT'S JUST, LIKE, YOUR
TEENAGE YEARS ARE OVER.
WHAT KIND OF DAD DO YOU THINK
NATHAN WILL BE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WANT TO BELIEVE HE'LL BE
A GOOD DAD, BUT IT'S HARD WHEN
EVERYONE ELSE HAS SO MUCH DOUBT,
ESPECIALLY MY SISTER.
>> IF MOM HADN'T LET NATHAN
LIVE IN OUR HOUSE, YOU'D STILL
BE A SWEET LITTLE INNOCENT GIRL,
AND YOUR LIFE WOULDN'T BE
RUINED.
>> I STILL AM SWEET AND
INNOCENT.
>> BEFORE, YOU COULD HAVE DONE,
LIKE, ANYTHING,
ANYTHING IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
NOW YOU ARE VERY, VERY LIMITED.
YOU THINK YOU CAN GO TO
A REGULAR COLLEGE?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GOT A KID.
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD IT IS?
>> YEAH.
BUT I'M STILL GOING TO DO IT.
>> I THINK SHE CAN DO IT.
I KNOW SHE CAN DO IT.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, I WANT
NOTHING MORE THAN TO HAVE HER
DO WELL.
STATISTICS ARE AGAINST HER.
>> YES, THEY ARE.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY.
>> I KNOW.
>> I THINK ONCE THE BABY COMES
AND THINGS START GETTING ROUGH,
NATHAN'S GONNA SPLIT.
NOW YOU'RE NOT GONNA TALK
TO ME, ARE YOU?
>> I JUST HAVE NOTHING TO SAY.
I REALLY LOOK UP TO MY SISTER,
SO IT KILLS ME THAT SHE FEELS
THIS WAY.
I REALLY HOPE NATHAN STEPS UP
AND PROVES HER AND EVERYBODY
ELSE WRONG.
[chime dings]
>> IT'S MY JUNIOR YEAR,
AND TONIGHT'S MY VERY FIRST
HOMECOMING DANCE.
SINCE I'M ONLY GOING TO BE
IN SCHOOL ANOTHER SIX WEEKS
BEFORE THE BABY COMES, IT MEANS
A LOT TO ME TO BE ABLE TO GO.
AND EVEN THOUGH HE ALREADY
GRADUATED, I'M GLAD NATHAN'S
COMING WITH ME.
>> HEY, BABY, YOU ALMOST DONE?
>> YEAH, ALMOST.
>> WHAT ELSE DO YOU HAVE TO DO?
>> GET DRESSED.
[laughter]
>> LOOK AT YOU.
WHOO!
>> DAMN.
LOOK AT THAT.
[laughter]
>> SHE PULLS IT OFF.
>> I LOOK HUGE.
>> I THINK YOU GET BIGGER
EVERY DAY.
>> I THINK I DO TOO.
>> LOOK AT ME, EVERYBODY.
>> I WAS PLAYING WITH MY HAIR.
>> YOU ARE SUCH A BRAT.
>> BYE!
>> I'LL SEE YOU ALL LATER.
>> SEE YA.
>> OKAY, AND NOW THE NEXT ONE
CAN BE SILLY.
>> BEING AT HOMECOMING MAKES ME
FEEL LIKE A NORMAL TEENAGER
AGAIN, AND NATHAN AND I HAD
A BLAST.
BUT THE NEXT DAY, REALITY
SANK IN WHEN MY DAD WANTED
TO TALK TO US ABOUT THE FUTURE
BEFORE HE RETURNED TO
AFGHANISTAN.
>> SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> WHAT PLAN?
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GONNA DO?
>> YOU GONNA GET MARRIED?
ARE YOU GONNA...
>> ONE DAY.
>> BETTER HAPPEN.
>> I'M TALKING WORK.
>> I KNOW, I...
I NEED TO LOOK EVEN HARDER
THAN I AM.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SETTLE FOR
A FAST-FOOD JOB.
>> BUT IT'S ALWAYS EASIER TO
FIND A JOB WHEN YOU HAVE A JOB.
>> IT'S EASIER TO GET A JOB
WHEN YOU HAVE A JOB.
>> I WANT YOU GUYS TO BE ABLE
TO STAND ON YOUR OWN TWO FEET
TOO, BECAUSE IT DOESN'T FEEL
GOOD TO HAVE TO RELY ON SOMEBODY
ELSE FOR EVERYTHING.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO RELY
ON YOU GUYS FOR A HOUSE AND FOOD
AND STUFF, BUT IT'S NICE
TO HAVE IT.
[laughs]
>> OH, THERE'S A SHOT CLOCK.
>> HE MEANS YOU CAN'T LIVE WITH
US FOREVER.
>> OH, I KNOW.
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT GOING
INTO THE AIR FORCE?
>> BUT...
>> BUT HE DOESN'T WANT
TO BE AWAY.
>> YEAH, WITH A NEW BABY.
>> WELL, I DIDN'T WANT
TO BE AWAY.
>> I KNOW, BUT...
>> YOU DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, I USED TO SAY
THE SAME THING.
I'M NOT GONNA DO THIS.
I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT.
YOU KNOW, BUT REALITY, YOU KNOW,
CHANGES YOUR MIND AFTER A WHILE.
>> SINCE I GREW UP NEVER KNOWING
HOW LONG MY DAD WOULD BE AWAY,
I'D RATHER NATHAN NOT GET
A JOB IN THE ARMY TOO,
BUT HE'S GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
>> YOU BE GOOD.
>> YOU TOO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
DO WELL IN SCHOOL.
>> YOU BE SAFE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'VE BEEN SAYING
GOOD-BYE MY WHOLE LIFE,
IT NEVER GETS ANY EASIER.
MY DAD'S WORDS OBVIOUSLY DIDN'T
MEAN MUCH TO NATHAN, BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T WASTE ANY TIME GETTING
BACK TO HIS FAVORITE CHAIR.
YOU AND THIS STUPID GAME,
IT'S ALL YOU EVER DO.
>> I HAVE NOTHING BETTER TO DO.
ONE DAY, I'LL FIND MY LIFE
AGAIN.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU SAID, LIKE,
TWO MONTHS AGO.
>> IT BETTER BE SOON.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE IT'S NOT GONNA BE
EASY TO TAKE CARE OF A BABY
WITH A CONTROLLER IN YOUR HAND.
[chime dings]
NATHAN FEELS LIKE EVERYONE
IS GANGING UP ON HIM.
I DON'T WANT TO GET ON HIS CASE
TOO, BUT WE DO NEED TO FIGURE IT
OUT.
SO DO YOU HAVE A PLAN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE ANYTHING
I DO IS NEVER GOOD ENOUGH.
>> LIKE, IF YOU JOINED THE
AIR FORCE AND WENT TO BUCKLEY,
THEN I WOULD GO WITH YOU, 'CAUSE
THAT'S JUST DOWN IN DENVER.
I MEAN, YOU MIGHT GET DEPLOYED,
BUT NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO IN
THE MILITARY, YOU HAVE A CHANCE
OF GETTING DEPLOYED.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO IT, NO.
>> LIKE, YOU DON'T WANT TO
BE DEPLOYED OR ANYTHING?
>> NO, LIKE, I'M NOT
A GUN PERSON.
I THINK THE HARDEST THING FOR ME
TO GO INTO THE ARMY IS,
I DON'T WANT TO MISS OUT
ON ANYTHING.
I KNOW IT'S AN OPTION, BUT IT'S
NOT ONE THAT I LIKE.
>> I WAS HOPING NATHAN WOULD
STEP IT UP, BUT OVER THE NEXT
FEW DAYS, INSTEAD OF LOOKING FOR
A JOB, NATHAN CHOSE TO HANG OUT
WITH HIS FRIENDS AND PLAY
VIDEO GAMES.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
HIS HEAD IS AT ANYMORE.
EVEN THOUGH NATHAN AND I ARE
SUPPOSED TO GO TO A HALLOWEEN
PARTY AT HIS PARENTS' HOUSE,
HE'S ACTING EVEN MORE DISTANT
AND SAYING THAT I'M CROWDING HIM
BUT THAT HE MIGHT COME OVER
WHEN HE'S FINISHED PLAYING
VIDEO GAMES WITH HIS FRIENDS.
>> YOU ARE A PIRATE MAIDEN.
>> I LOOK DUMB.
>> YOU LOOK SO CUTE.
>> YOU'RE NOT TAKING PICTURES.
>> I'M NOT?
REALLY?
>> REALLY.
>> ARE YOU SURE?
'CAUSE IT LOOKS LIKE I AM.
>> I'M GONNA HURT HER, SADIE.
>> [giggling]
>> STOP LAUGHING AT ME.
>> I THINK YOU'RE ADORABLE.
>> THAT LOOKS REALLY GOOD
ON YOU.
>> IT DOES.
>> IT WAS THE ONLY NON-SLUTTY
PIRATE COSTUME.
>> IT'S SO CUTE.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE NATHAN
IS STILL NOT HERE.
>> DUDE, YOU USED TO RUN WILD
EVERYWHERE WITH ME.
YOU WERE, LIKE, THE WILD STEED
THAT DON'T EVER GET CAUGHT,
BUT IT'S, YOU KNOW, YOU GOT
CAGED IN.
>> I DO FEEL LIKE I'M KIND OF
STUCK HERE.
MAN, THIS IS SO STRESSFUL.
>> DUDE, YEAH.
YOU JUST NEED TO BE ABLE
TO HAVE A LITTLE TIME AWAY.
I REALLY THINK THAT MAYBE
COMING TO STAY WITH ME,
THAT'LL HELP YOU TO COME BACK.
>> THAT WILL HELP A LOT.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW ANYMORE.
>> I'M NOT GONNA MAKE ANY
EXCUSES FOR HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I KNOW THAT THIS IS
A HUGE CHANGE FOR EVERYBODY.
I MEAN, THAT'S A LOT OF PRESSURE
ON YOU, ON HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, HE NEEDS TO REALIZE
WHAT HE'S DOING AND WHAT HE'S
DOING TO YOU, BECAUSE IT'S NOT
OKAY FOR HIM TO TREAT YOU THAT
WAY, IT'S NOT.
>> I THINK IT'S JUST...
IT'S ALL JUST STARTING
TO HIT HIM, ESPECIALLY 'CAUSE
IT'S ONLY A FEW MONTHS AWAY.
>> IT'S ONLY A FEW MONTHS AWAY.
HE DOESN'T HAVE A JOB.
HE DOESN'T REALLY WANT TO GET
A JOB.
>> YEAH.
I KNOW ALL THIS CHANGE
IS REALLY OVERWHELMING.
[chime dings]
MAYBE ALL NATHAN NEEDS
IS SOME SUPPORT.
I WENT HOME TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT
IT, BUT ALL I FOUND WAS A NOTE
SAYING HE DECIDED TO SPEND THE
WEEKEND AT HIS FRIEND TYLER'S.
TYLER IS NATHAN'S PARTY BUDDY,
WHO HE WOULD HAVE BEEN LIVING
WITH IF I HADN'T GOTTEN
PREGNANT, AND IT MAKES ME
KIND OF NERVOUS, SO I WENT
TO TALK TO HIM THERE.
>> YOU KNOW, IF I NEED MY SPACE,
I NEED MY SPACE.
>> I THINK IT'S 'CAUSE BOTH OF
US ARE STARTING TO GET STRESSED
ABOUT THE BABY.
A LOT OF TIMES, WHEN I GET UPSET
AND STUFF, IT'S 'CAUSE YOU'RE
PLAYING YOUR VIDEO GAMES 24/7.
>> SO YOU REALIZE IF WE WEREN'T
HAVING A BABY, I WOULDN'T BE
HERE, RIGHT?
>> NO.
I DID NOT REALIZE THAT.
>> AFTER HIGH SCHOOL, I WAS JUST
GONNA MOVE TO FORT COLLINS WITH
MY FRIENDS, UNTIL I FOUND OUT
YOU WERE PREGNANT.
BUT I WAS PLANNING ON MOVING
OUT OF YOUR HOUSE AND LEAVING,
UNTIL WE FOUND OUT.
LET'S JUST HOPE YOU DIDN'T
PUSH ME TO THE EDGE.
>> I HAD NO IDEA NATHAN FELT
THIS TRAPPED.
I'M STARTING TO WONDER IF
MY SISTER IS RIGHT ABOUT
HIM NOT STICKING AROUND.
>> I COULDN'T BRING MYSELF TO
TELL MY MOM NATHAN SAID HE'S
ONLY WITH ME BECAUSE I'M
PREGNANT, BUT SHE KNOWS HE'S
BEEN STAYING AT HIS FRIEND'S
HOUSE AND THAT I AM TOTALLY
DOWN.
>> YOU KNOW I'M HERE,
AND YOU KNOW I ALWAYS KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE UPSET,
AND I ALWAYS SAY,
"WHAT'S WRONG, MEGAN?"
>> YEAH, AND THAT GETS ANNOYING.
>> "NOTHING, MOM.
NOTHING, MOM."
"WHAT'S WRONG, MEGAN?"
AND IT'S USUALLY SOMETHING.
AND YOU SHOULD FEEL COMFORTABLE
TALKING TO ME ABOUT IT.
DO YOU KNOW YOU CAN COME TO ME?
>> I KNOW I CAN COME TO YOU,
BUT I DON'T LIKE TALKING TO YOU
ABOUT IT.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT HE'S GOT,
LIKE, RESENTMENT, MAYBE, BECAUSE
HE'S NOT SINGLE AND FREE
ANYMORE?
HE'S GOT RESPONSIBILITIES,
AND HIS FRIENDS ARE MAYBE,
"COME ON, NATE, WE NEED TO..."
>> YEAH, HIS FRIENDS ARE--
I KNOW, ARE A BIG PART OF IT.
THEY'VE TOLD HIM THAT THEY THINK
HE NEEDS HIS SPACE.
>> WELL, YEAH, 'CAUSE HE'S
A GUY, AND HE'S A TEENAGER.
>> I THINK IT'S PROBABLY JUST
A STAGE THAT ALL BOYS GO
THROUGH.
>> I KNOW, BUT I THINK YOU'VE
MATURED A LOT FASTER THAN
HE HAS.
>> THAT'S 'CAUSE I'VE GOT HIM
IN MY BELLY.
>> A CONSTANT REMINDER.
>> YEAH.
IT'S THE MORNING OF MY BABY
SHOWER, AND BECAUSE OF
EVERYTHING GOING ON WITH NATHAN,
I'M IN NO MOOD FOR A PARTY.
[chime dings]
THE SHOWER IS AT NATHAN'S
PARENTS' HOUSE.
I'M GLAD THEY'RE BEING
SUPPORTIVE, BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT FROM HIM.
>> HEY, MEG.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU FEELING
ABOUT THE SHOWER?
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK
TO EVERYONE.
>> SHE'S JUST SO TIRED
AND STRESSED.
>> ARE WE READY?
>> YEAH.
I JUST GOT TO GET MY SHOES ON.
I'M GLAD THAT SO MANY OF MY
FRIENDS ARE HERE, BECAUSE
I WORRY THAT EVERYONE HAS BEEN
AVOIDING ME SINCE I GOT
PREGNANT.
DESPITE HIM NEEDING HIS SPACE,
NATHAN SHOWED UP.
>> WOW.
THERE'S SO MANY PEOPLE HERE.
>> OH, I'M BOTH.
IT'S ALL A NEW EXPERIENCE FOR
ME, AND IT'S PRETTY
OVERWHELMING.
>> ARE YOU GUYS READY?
MEGAN'S GONNA OPEN PRESENTS.
>> I WAS HOPING HE WOULD
OPEN PRESENTS WITH ME, BUT HE
TOOK OFF WITH HIS FRIENDS.
MY SISTER IS NOT HAPPY ABOUT
THE WAY NATHAN'S TREATING ME,
SO SHE WANTS TO TALK TO HIM.
>> OBVIOUSLY, I LOVE MY SISTER
VERY MUCH, AND I DO HAVE A LOT
OF CONCERNS AS TO WHETHER OR NOT
YOU AND HER ARE GOING TO
ACTUALLY MAKE IT.
YOU CAN STOP GLARING AT ME
AT ANY POINT IN TIME.
>> I'M NOT GLARING.
I'M JUST SITTING HERE.
>> AND MY CONCERNS AS FAR AS
YOU GO IS, I'M PRETTY SURE THAT
ONCE THE BABY COMES AND YOU SEE
HOW DIFFICULT IT'S GONNA BE,
YOU'RE GONNA BE GONE.
>> OKAY, WELL, I GUESS I'M GONNA
PROVE YOU WRONG, 'CAUSE THERE'S
NO WAY I'M GONNA LEAVE.
>> RUMOR HAS IT YOU'VE ALREADY
TOLD MEGAN THAT IF THINGS DON'T
CHANGE, THAT YOU'RE LEAVING.
>> THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M GONNA
LEAVE MY BABY, THOUGH.
YEAH, IF ME AND MEGAN AREN'T
TOGETHER, IT DOESN'T MEAN
WE CAN'T RAISE HIM STILL.
>> I ALSO DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU INTEND ON TAKING CARE
OF THIS BABY IF YOU DON'T
HAVE A JOB.
>> I'M LOOKING.
IT'S A LITTLE HARD RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH, I GET THAT.
THERE'S ALWAYS ANOTHER OPTION.
LIKE, THE ARMY IS STILL THERE.
>> I'M NOT GOING INTO THE ARMY.
>> [groans]
YOU'RE SO DEFINITIVE ABOUT THAT
ANSWER, BUT THE FACT THAT YOU'RE
LIVING OFF OF MY DAD'S PAYCHECK
WHEN HE'S OVER IN AFGHANISTAN
RIGHT NOW, DOESN'T REALLY
THRILL ME.
EVEN IF YOU START CONSIDERING IT
AND YOU TAKE THAT ONE LITTLE
STEP, YOU WILL HAVE A LITTLE BIT
MORE RESPECT FROM ME AND MY DAD.
WE HAVE SEVERE DOUBTS ABOUT YOU.
>> MY FAMILY DOUBTING NATHAN
IS NOTHING NEW, BUT NOW I'M
STARTING TO DOUBT HIM TOO.
>> NATHAN SAYING HE MIGHT
LEAVE ME REALLY HAS ME DOWN,
SO I DECIDED TO HAVE SOME FUN
TO TAKE MY MIND OFF THINGS.
[laughter]
>> WOW, THAT'S SHOCKING, HUH?
>> I REALLY MISS HAVING NATHAN
AROUND, AND AFTER A FEW DAYS,
I GUESS HE STARTED TO MISS ME
TOO.
>> WE NEED TO TALK, BABE.
I FEEL BAD FOR LEAVING
AND KIND OF HAVING YOU GUESS
ABOUT EVERYTHING,
NOT KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
IT'S JUST--A LOT IS ON MY MIND
NOW.
YOU KNOW, ONE DAY I'M OUT,
YOU KNOW, DOING WHATEVER I WANT
TO DO, PARTYING AND JUST MESSING
AROUND, AND THE NEXT DAY,
I FIND OUT I'M HAVING A BABY,
AND THAT'S JUST A COMPLETE
CHANGE.
I GUESS I'M STILL JUST TRYING
TO COPE AND TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> IT KIND OF MADE ME THINK,
LIKE, HOW MANY TIMES ARE YOU
GOING TO NEED TO GET AWAY,
AND WHAT HAPPENS WHEN, ONE OF
THOSE TIMES, YOU JUST DECIDE
TO NOT COME BACK?
'CAUSE IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY
IF I HAVE TO RAISE THIS BABY
ON MY OWN.
>> I WANT IT TO BE US
AND NOT JUST YOU, YOU KNOW?
YOU AND THEN ME, SEPARATE.
I GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
COUNTING ON ME TO FAIL,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT,
AND I NEED TO STEP UP,
AND I REALIZE THAT I WAS STUPID.
OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> OKAY.
MY DUE DATE IS TWO WEEKS AWAY,
SO I'M GLAD NATHAN IS BACK
IN THE PICTURE, AND THIS TIME
IT'S NOT JUST TALK.
HE'S ACTUALLY TAKING SOME
ACTIONS.
HE'S BEEN APPLYING FOR JOBS
AND WENT ON AN INTERVIEW,
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN EASY.
HOW DO YOU THINK YOUR INTERVIEW
WENT?
>> IT WENT OKAY.
I JUST THINK HE WAS LOOKING
FOR MORE OF--SOMEBODY OLDER.
>> OH.
>> 'CAUSE I JUST CAME RIGHT OUT
OF HIGH SCHOOL.
IF I DON'T GET THIS JOB,
I THINK I SHOULD TRY TO FIND
A DIFFERENT ONE, EVEN IF IT'S
SOMETHING SMALL.
>> IT WOULD BE NICE IF YOU GOT
A GOOD-PAYING JOB, 'CAUSE THEN
MY MOM WOULDN'T HAVE TO BUY
EVERYTHING.
I ALWAYS FEEL BAD WHEN SHE PAYS
FOR STUFF.
>> YEAH, I'VE BEEN TRYING,
BUT...
IT'S, LIKE, ALL I DO.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'LL SEE.
[chime dings]
>> MY DUE DATE CAME AND WENT,
SO TODAY WE'RE GOING TO THE
DOCTOR TO CHECK THINGS OUT.
>> I WANT TO CHECK YOUR CERVIX
AND SEE HOW IT GOES, AND THEN
IF WE'RE LUCKY, YOU'LL JUST
GO INTO LABOR THIS WEEKEND.
SO YOU'RE, LIKE, STILL JUST 1.
BUT THINNED OUT, SO THAT'S GOOD.
THAT LAST MONTH OF PREGNANCY
STARTS GETTING PRETTY OLD,
DOESN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, IT'S HARD.
LET'S JUST CHECK THE BABY
ON MONDAY TO MAKE SURE THAT
THE BABY'S DOING OKAY, AND THEN
WE CAN KIND OF MAKE A PLAN FROM
THERE IF WE NEED TO.
>> OKAY.
>> WELL, IT'S STILL GONNA
BE SOON, THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> NO MATTER WHAT, IT'S GONNA
BE HERE WITHIN THE WEEK.
>> NATHAN DOESN'T SEEM TO CARE
THAT I'M OVERDUE, BUT MY
SISTER'S LEAVE IS UP, AND SHE
HAS TO GO BACK TO HER BASE
IN NORTH CAROLINA.
TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE,
SHE MIGHT GET DEPLOYED OVERSEAS
BEFORE THE BABY ARRIVES.
>> SO YOUR SISTER JUST
TEXTED ME.
BECAUSE OF THE EARTHQUAKE IN
HAITI, THE 82ND'S BEING
DEPLOYED, SO SHE WON'T BE HERE
TO SEE BLAKE LIKE SHE PLANNED.
I THINK SHE'S LEAVING TOMORROW.
SHE ONLY GETS, LIKE, ONE MORE
PHONE CALL, I THINK,
BEFORE SHE LEAVES.
SO SHE'S GONNA TRY AND CALL YOU.
[cell phone ringing]
IT'S YOUR SISTER CALLING
RIGHT NOW.
>> HELLO?
>> WELL, I GUESS YOU HEARD THAT
I'M GOING TO HAITI.
>> YEAH.
>> WE CAN LEAVE AS EARLY AS
TOMORROW NIGHT, SO...
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
I'M GONNA BE OVER THERE.
BUT WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'RE
PROBABLY GONNA TURN AROUND
AND GO RIGHT TO AFGHANISTAN,
SO IT MIGHT BE...[laughs]
MORE THAN A YEAR BEFORE
I COME HOME AND SEE YOU.
>> OH, WOW.
I'LL SEND YOU PICTURES
AND STUFF.
>> WELL, I KNOW YOU'RE TIRED,
SO I'LL LET YOU GO.
>> OKAY.
>> I LOVE YOU. GOOD LUCK.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
THANKS.
>> BYE.
>> I'VE ALWAYS LOOKED TO MY
SISTER TO HELP ME GET THROUGH
ANYTHING SCARY IN LIFE,
AND I'M ABOUT TO FACE MY
SCARIEST EXPERIENCE YET,
BUT THE ONE PERSON WHO I'VE
ALWAYS COUNTED ON WILL BE
HALFWAY ACROSS THE WORLD.
>> ANOTHER WEEK HAS PASSED,
AND I STILL DON'T HAVE MY BABY.
I'M BUMMED THAT MY SISTER IS
GONE, BUT MY DAD WAS ABLE TO GET
SOME TIME OFF TO COME HOME
FOR THE BIRTH.
>> HI, BABY.
>> HI.
>> I MISSED YOU.
>> MISSED YOU TOO.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
SO F--BIG.
>> YOU ALMOST SAID FAT.
[laughs]
>> I THOUGHT ABOUT SAYING FAT.
>> [laughs]
>> SO WHERE'S THE BABY?
>> RIGHT THERE.
>> HOW COME YOU DIDN'T
HAVE IT YET?
>> IT'S NOT UP TO ME.
HE DECIDED HE DIDN'T WANT
TO COME YET.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HOME.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD I'M HOME TOO.
I HOPE YOU HAVE THIS THING
BEFORE I HAVE TO GO BACK.
>> I WILL.
DON'T WORRY.
>> THE CLOCK IS TICKING.
>> MY DAD COULD GET CALLED BACK
TO DUTY AT ANY TIME, SO I REALLY
WANT TO GET THIS BABY OUT WHILE
HE'S HERE, AND AS OF TODAY,
I'M OUT OF SCHOOL UNTIL AFTER
THE BABY COMES.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOGLING HOW TO INDUCE LABOR.
SO NATHAN AND I ARE STUDYING UP
ON HOW TO GET THIS BABY OUT
OF ME.
OH, I FOUND A LIST.
[bell dings]
WHAT ONE SHOULD I DO, HONEY?
>> DO THE SKI ONE.
>> THE SKI ONE?
[bell dings]
>> OH, I THINK I'M GONNA HAVE
A BABY BEFORE YOU DO.
>> [laughs]
[bell dings]
I CAN'T DO IT.
>> JUST DRINK IT STRAIGHT.
I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE
THAT BAD.
>> I'M GONNA GO STAND OVER THE
SINK, JUST IN CASE I PUKE IT UP.
>> ONE, TWO...
>> THREE.
GO AHEAD, TAKE A DRINK.
TAKE A DRINK.
[laughter]
>> THE CASTOR OIL WAS NASTY,
BUT IT MAY HAVE WORKED, BECAUSE
THE NEXT MORNING, I WOKE UP
WITH HORRIBLE CONTRACTIONS,
AND THE PAIN WAS SO BAD.
I COULD BARELY WALK INTO
THE HOSPITAL.
[gasps]
HONEY?
[whimpers]
[whines]
>> KEEP SQUEEZING.
>> THESE CONTRACTIONS
ARE SO STRONG.
THEY SHOULD BE DOING SOMETHING.
SO I JUST WANT TO SEE IF THEY
WERE CHANGING YOUR CERVIX.
>> OH.
I'M LEAVING.
>> [laughs]
>> OH!
I'M GONNA SAY YOU'RE 9 1/2.
THERE'S, LIKE, A LITTLE RIM
THERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> JEEZ.
>> YOU'RE GOING FAST.
>> WE'RE GONNA BRING YOUR LEGS
BACK.
NATHAN CAN HOLD ONE SIDE.
CURL AROUND YOUR BABY AND GO.
MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE, MORE.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
BLOW IT OUT.
>> [exhales]
>> YOU LOOK A LITTLE
OVERWHELMED.
>> I'M ABOUT TO PASS OUT.
[laughs]
>> AND LET'S GO.
GOOD, GOOD.
MORE, MORE, MORE.
TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT,
NINE, TEN.
>> YOU OKAY, HONEY?
>> MEGAN, DO YOU WANT A MIRROR
SO YOU CAN SEE?
>> LET'S GO.
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO,
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
GOOD.
>> YOU'RE DOING AMAZING, BABY.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> MEGAN, YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
>> OH, I'M SO MAD.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU'RE DOING FABULOUS.
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE THAT.
>> JUST WAIT.
JUST WAIT.
IT'S JUST PERFECT.
WE'RE GONNA SNEAK THIS BABY OUT
WITHOUT A TEAR.
>> OH, IT HURTS SO BAD.
>> JUST KEEP BREATHING.
>> YOU'RE DOING AMAZING.
>> OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
NOW GIVE ME A LITTLE PUSH,
JUST LITTLE.
JUST A LITTLE.
>> OH, THE BABY!
>> OH, THERE'S HIS LITTLE EAR.
>> HERE HE COMES.
PERFECT, PERFECT.
[applause]
ALL RIGHT, NOW WE'RE GONNA
CLAMP THE CORD FAST.
[baby cries]
>> YOU DID IT, BABY.
>> GOOD JOB, MEGAN.
[peaceful music]
>> * OOH *
>> CONGRATULATIONS, BABY.
>> HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> * AND I WANT *
* YOU TO KNOW *
* HOW I NEED YOU NOW *
[chime dings]
>> BABY BLAKE IS FINALLY HERE,
AND WE'VE HAD TONS OF FAMILY
MEMBERS VISIT.
BUT I AM A LITTLE BUMMED
BECAUSE NONE OF MY FRIENDS
CAME TO SEE HIM.
[baby crying]
>> OH...
>> AND BEFORE WE KNEW IT,
IT WAS TIME TO TAKE BLAKE HOME.
[baby crying]
[baby fussing]
OH, OF COURSE.
OF COURSE.
YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM?
>> YEAH.
OHH...
>> HEY, LOOK AT HOW MUCH
HE LIKES MY DAD.
HE'S BEING, LIKE, PERFECT
FOR HIM.
>> HE HATES YOU, SORRY.
>> HE DOES.
>> YEAH.
>> HE LIKES NATHAN SO MUCH MORE
THAN HE LIKES ME.
[laughter]
[baby crying]
I WANT TO MAKE THE BABY
COMFORTABLE, BUT EVERY TIME
I HOLD HIM, HE CRIES.
[baby crying]
I KNOW. I KNOW.
OH, SHOOT.
IS HIS LITTLE BABY BAG
DOWN HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> BLAKE HASN'T BEEN HOME FOR
A FULL DAY, AND THINGS WITH
NATHAN ARE ALREADY GETTING
TENSE.
[baby crying]
>> YOU'RE STILL NAKED.
OOH, YOU STINK TOO.
I'M TRYING TO LEARN HOW TO TAKE
CARE OF THIS BABY, AND AS USUAL,
NATHAN IS MORE INTERESTED IN
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES THAN HE IS
IN HELPING OUT.
HONEY?
YOU WANT TO CHANGE HIM?
>> NOPE.
>> IT'S POOPY.
>> OH, 'CAUSE THAT'S GONNA MAKE
ME RUN OVER THERE.
>> WELL...
HE'S PRETTY MUCH BACK TO
HIS OLD ROUTINE, WHICH SUCKS
FOR ME.
>> NO.
YOU HIT HIM IN THE HEAD.
>> HE WAS TRYING TO CATCH IT.
>> I'M GRATEFUL MY DAD HASN'T
BEEN CALLED AWAY, SO HE CAN HELP
PICK UP THE SLACK.
[baby crying]
I'VE BEEN STUCK IN THE HOUSE
WITH THE BABY ALL THE TIME.
MY FRIENDS SEEM TO HAVE
FORGOTTEN I EXIST.
I'VE BEEN TEXTING MY FRIEND
KRISTIN, BUT I HAVEN'T
HEARD BACK.
>> SHE'S NOT TEXTING BACK?
>> I'VE BEEN TRYING TO TALK
TO HER, BUT SHE DOESN'T REPLY
OR ANYTHING.
>> YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHY?
SHE'S PROBABLY JUST NOT SURE
HOW TO HANDLE HER FRIEND
BECOMING A MOM.
AND NOW YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING
TO SCHOOL, AND EVERYBODY ELSE
IS AT SCHOOL, SO DO YOU THINK
THAT'S PART OF IT?
>> COULD BE.
KIND OF SUCKS.
MY MOM CAN TELL THAT I MISS
MY FRIENDS AND SUGGESTED SHE
WATCH THE BABY SO NATHAN AND I
CAN GET OUT OF THE HOUSE.
>> SWEET.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> OKAY, I CALL THESE SIX.
>> OKAY.
>> SO HAVE YOU HEARD FROM
ANYBODY SINCE THE HOSPITAL?
>> NO.
I KIND OF HAD THE FEELING
THAT A LOT OF MY FRIENDS
WOULDN'T BE MY FRIENDS
AFTER ALL OF THIS.
BUT I JUST--I DIDN'T WANT IT
TO HAPPEN, BUT...
>> A TRUE FRIEND WILL MAKE
THE EFFORT.
YOU DEFINE YOUR FRIENDS BY
IF THEY'RE THERE FOR YOU.
IF THEY'RE NOT GONNA MAKE
THE EFFORT, IT'S NOT WORTH IT
AT ALL.
I THINK HARD TIMES DEFINES
WHO SOMEBODY REALLY IS.
>> NATHAN CAN TALK A PRETTY GOOD
GAME SOMETIMES.
I JUST WISH HE WOULD LISTEN
TO HIS OWN WORDS.
TOMORROW IS MY FIRST DAY
BACK AT SCHOOL, AND I'M REALLY
NERVOUS.
I FINALLY HEARD BACK FROM
MY FRIEND KRISTIN, WHO WANTS
TO COME BY AND MAKE SURE
I'M READY FOR IT.
WELL, DON'T SPIT IT OUT.
>> HE IS FUSSY.
SO TOMORROW'S THE BIG DAY?
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU LOOKING FORWARD
TO BEING BACK?
>> NO.
IS IT GONNA BE HARD TO BE AWAY
FROM BLAKE?
>> YES.
>> I MEAN, TOMORROW, YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO GET BACK IN
THE SWING OF THINGS AND--
>> [sneezes]
>> BLESS YOU.
>> IT'S GONNA BE WEIRD,
'CAUSE, LIKE, THE FEW TIMES THAT
I'VE GONE IN TO TURN IN STUFF,
EVERYONE'S, LIKE,
JUST LOOKED AT ME.
>> YEAH.
AND PEOPLE ARE KIND OF, LIKE,
"SHOULD I GO SAY HI?
GO SEE THE BABY?
OR WHAT DO I DO?"
IT'LL BE INTERESTING.
>> I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO GO BACK.
>> I DON'T BLAME YOU.
OH, SO FUSSY.
ARE YOU LOOKING FORWARD
TO SEEING ANYBODY?
>> NOT REALLY.
BUT IT'LL BE NICE TO KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
IT MIGHT BE A LITTLE BIT
AWKWARD.
BUT I'VE GOT MORE IMPORTANT
STUFF RIGHT NOW TO THINK ABOUT.
HUH, BABY?
WE'RE SLEEPING IN THE LIVING
ROOM SO WE CAN BE CLOSER
TO THE KITCHEN TO HEAT UP
BOTTLES.
>> YOU CAN SIT NEXT TO ME, OKAY?
OKAY, NOW WE CAN PLAY.
NOW IT'S THE RIGHT COLORS, OKAY?
>> HONEY, I'M GONNA GO TO SLEEP.
>> OKAY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> MWAH.
[baby crying]
EVEN THOUGH I'M THE ONE WHO HAS
TO BE UP IN THE MORNING FOR
SCHOOL, NATHAN IS NOT MOVING.
[baby crying]
>> OH, YOU'RE UP.
CAN I HOLD YOU WHILE MAMA
GETS READY FOR SCHOOL?
>> [yawning] HE IS OUT.
>> OKAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GOING
TO STAY AWAKE IN CLASS WITH
HARDLY ANY SLEEP.
I'M TOTALLY DREADING SCHOOL,
AND WHEN I GOT THERE,
EVERYONE WAS STARING AT ME.
SEEING MY FRIENDS ONLY CONFIRMED
THAT I HAVE NOTHING IN COMMON
WITH THEM ANYMORE.
WHILE I'M TRYING TO BE A MOM
AND A STUDENT, NATHAN REFUSES TO
GET OFF THE COUCH AND PITCH IN.
SO MY MOM HAS NO CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE CARE OF BLAKE
WHEN I'M AT SCHOOL.
>> HE LIKES THAT HE'S BEEN
AROUND AND HASN'T HAD TO DO
ANYTHING.
YOU GUYS DON'T...[scoffs]
YOU WANT TO MOVE OUT AND HAVE
HIM HAVE A GOOD JOB AND ALL THIS
STUFF, BUT YOU STILL DON'T KNOW
ALL THE STUFF YOU HAVE TO DO
TO HAVE A HOUSE AND A BABY
AND GO TO SCHOOL AND WORK,
ALL THAT STUFF.
>> BECAUSE WE'RE COMPLETELY
IGNORANT.
>> NO, I DIDN'T SAY THAT.
BUT WHO WASHES THE BOTTLES,
AND WHO WASHES THE CLOTHES?
>> I CAN DO THAT.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO DO IT,
THEN TELL ME.
I'LL DO IT.
THE ONLY REASON I DON'T
IS BECAUSE YOU OFFERED TO.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF SOMEONE'S
GONNA OFFER TO DO THAT STUFF,
THEN WHY NOT TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF IT?
I'M GETTING ANNOYED WITH MY MOM
BECAUSE I KNOW SHE HAS A POINT.
NATHAN SAID HE WOULD GET A JOB
AFTER THE BABY CAME, BUT SO FAR,
HE HASN'T FOLLOWED THROUGH.
EVERY DAY I COME HOME TO
THE SAME THING: MY MOM WATCHING
THE BABY AND NATHAN PLAYING
VIDEO GAMES INSTEAD OF LOOKING
FOR A JOB.
>> HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> BORING.
YOU AND YOUR VIDEO GAMES.
>> THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH VIDEO GAMES.
>> UNLESS YOU'RE GETTING PAID
FOR VIDEO GAMES, THEN THERE'S
SOMETHING WRONG WITH VIDEO
GAMES.
>> WELL, LET'S FIND A WAY
TO GET ME PAID, THEN.
>> CAN YOU PAUSE THAT OR
SOMETHING FOR A LITTLE BIT?
>> NO.
>> PLEASE?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M PRETTY TIRED OF LIVING
UNDER MY MOM'S ROOF.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I KNOW YOU'VE APPLIED
FOR WORK AT A LOT OF PLACES, BUT
THERE'S ALSO A LOT MORE PLACES
THAT YOU HAVEN'T APPLIED TO.
NOW THAT WE'RE PARENTS,
WE KIND OF NEED TO LAY OFF
THE VIDEO GAMES AND HELP CHANGE
MORE DIAPERS AND EVERYTHING
AND GET A JOB.
>> WHAT THE HELL DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO?
DO YOU WANT ME TO FIND A JOB?
DO YOU WANT ME TO STAY HOME
AND TAKE CARE OF THE BABY?
WHICH ONE IS IT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I WOULD LIKE IF
YOU GOT A JOB.
MAYBE IF YOU TALKED TO SOME
OF YOUR FRIENDS WHO HAVE JOBS
AND ASK IF THEY COULD HELP YOU
GET A JOB OR SOMETHING,
THAT WOULD HELP A LOT.
LIKE, I DON'T WANT IT TO JUST
KEEP ON GOING, LIKE, EVERY DAY
WAITING FOR SOMETHING TO HAPPEN.
I HOPE HE TAKES THIS SERIOUSLY,
BECAUSE I'M NOT SURE HOW MUCH
LONGER I'M WILLING TO WAIT.
>> THE PRESSURE IS BUILDING
FOR NATHAN TO GET A JOB,
SO HE INVITED HIS FRIENDS OVER,
WHO JUST GOT JOBS LAYING FLOORS
IN TEXAS, TO FIND OUT
ABOUT WORK.
>> OH.
>> GONNA DO SOME HOOKAH?
>> YEAH, MIGHT AS WELL, RIGHT?
>> YUMMY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WHAT YOU GONNA PUT IN THERE?
>> WE GOT APRICOT, GRAPE,
AND CANTALOUPE.
>> SO HOW'S THE BABY GOING?
>> GOING GOOD.
A LITTLE TIRING.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON WITH
THE TEXAS?
>> I JUST GOT MY TICKET
THIS MORNING.
>> YEAH, WHEN DO YOU LEAVE?
>> I ACTUALLY LEAVE THIS
SATURDAY, YOU KNOW?
[hookah bubbling]
IF STUFF DOESN'T START PICKING
UP HERE, WE COULD EASILY HAVE
YOU OUT THERE WORKING,
IF YOU WANTED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> WELL, I DO.
I JUST--I DON'T KNOW.
IT DEPENDS.
>> THEY WANTED ME TO INVITE SOME
PEOPLE OUT LAST TIME I WAS OUT
THERE, 'CAUSE THERE'S JUST
SO MUCH WORK.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU COULD ALWAYS RELY
ON THERE BEING SOME MONEY.
>> WE NEED MONEY.
WE NEED TO--
YOU KNOW, WE NEED TO START
DOING SOMETHING.
>> WHEN I CAME HOME FROM SCHOOL,
NATHAN TOLD ME THAT THERE IS
A JOB OPPORTUNITY, BUT IT'S
ALL THE WAY IN TEXAS.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
I WOULD BE THERE.
I DON'T KNOW.
I KNOW IT'S DOING TILE,
DOING FLOORS.
I MEAN, IF TYLER CAN DO IT,
I CAN DO IT.
>> YEAH, BUT LAST YEAR,
WHEN HE WAS THERE, HE ALSO
PARTIED A LOT.
>> WHO SAID--WHO SAID I WAS
GONNA GO PARTY?
>> WELL, YOU'D GO WITH HIM,
'CAUSE YOU'D BE STAYING
WITH HIM.
>> IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT?
>> NO, I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE
GONE EITHER, 'CAUSE IT WOULD BE
HARD TAKING CARE OF HIM WITHOUT
YOU HERE.
>> I KNOW.
BUT IT'S KIND OF HARD TO BEGIN
OUR LIFE WITHOUT ANY MONEY,
WITHOUT A JOB, TRUE?
THIS IS, LIKE, ONE OF THE ONLY
OPTIONS.
WHAT ELSE DO I HAVE?
I CAN GO TO SCHOOL, BUT THAT'S
NOT GONNA HELP US ANY.
REALLY, THE ONLY OTHER OPTION
IS SOME TYPE OF MILITARY.
AND WITH THAT, I'M GONNA
BE GONE TOO.
I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT ME TO
LEAVE, BUT LIKE YOUR DAD SAID,
IF I DON'T...
YOU KNOW, IF I'M NOT SACRIFICING
NOW, I'M GONNA HAVE TO SACRIFICE
IN A LITTLE BIT.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT YOU TO GO
ANYWHERE.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> * THINK I'M SLIPPING UNDER *
* YES, I'M DROWNING *
* IN MY THOUGHTS *
>> I KNOW WE NEED TO SUPPORT
OUR BABY, AND I WANT NATHAN
TO GET A JOB.
I JUST DIDN'T MEAN HALFWAY
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
BEING A TEEN MOM, I HAVE HAD
TO MAKE A LOT OF SACRIFICES.
I THINK HAVING A BABY HAS PUT
A LOT OF PRESSURE ON MINE
AND NATHAN'S RELATIONSHIP.
>> I KNOW MEGAN'S GOT A PROBLEM
WITH YOU GOING TO TEXAS, BUT,
BABY, A GUY'S GOT TO TAKE CARE
OF HIS FAMILY, YOU KNOW?
AND I'M SORRY IF THAT
SOUNDS SEXIST.
MEGAN'S MY DAUGHTER, AND FOR
BETTER OR WORSE, I'M GONNA
EXPECT YOU TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> OUR WHOLE FUTURE IS DEPENDING
ON IF WE GET JOBS OR NOT.
NATHAN NEEDS TO FOCUS MORE ON
HIS FAMILY AND LOOK FOR A JOB,
SO WE CAN GET OUR LIFE MOVING.
>> LOOK AT THAT!
>> JUST HAVE OUR OWN PLACE
AND BE OUR OWN LITTLE FAMILY.
>> YOU'RE BETTER THAN DADDY.
>> BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
ALL I CARED ABOUT WAS JUST
HAVING FUN.
NOW ALL I CARE ABOUT
IS FINISHING SCHOOL AND TRYING
TO FIND A JOB, AND I WORRY ABOUT
MONEY AND ALL THE IMPORTANT
STUFF.
AS MUCH AS I LOVE BLAKE,
I DON'T LOVE THE FACT THAT
IT'S PUSHED AWAY MY FRIENDS,
BECAUSE YOU NEED FRIENDS
ALL THE TIME.
IT'S HARD NOT HAVING PEOPLE
TO TALK TO.
I DO WISH I WOULD HAVE BEEN
OLDER BY THE TIME I HAD
MY FIRST KID.
I LOVE HIM, BUT IT'S JUST
REALLY HARD AT THIS AGE.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> BOTH MY MOM AND I,
WE CONSIDERED EVERY OPTION.
>> YOUR AUNT LISA CALLED.
LISA AND KENNY CALLED,
AND THEY WANTED ME TO ASK YOU
IF IT WAS OKAY IF THEY COULD
ADOPT YOUR BABY.
>> WE JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU REALIZE, THERE'S REALLY NO
GOING BACK ON IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE GONNA
GO THROUGH WITH THIS.
>> [sniffles]
>> DO YOU HONESTLY THINK YOU
MADE THE WRONG CHOICE?
YOU DON'T--
>> YES.