[laughing]
I'm Kailyn.
I'm a high school senior
from Nazareth, Pennsylvania.
Wow.
You look like a princess.
I am a princess, Kendra.
When I was six months old,
my dad left,
and I haven't seen him since.
My mom's always struggled
to hold down a steady job,
boyfriend, and home.
She's currently
living in a hotel
with her new boyfriend, which
doesn't leave much room for me.
Hi, honey.
Did you find
any apartments yet?
Well, I'm not going to jump
into purchasing a house now.
I mean, that's--that's
a huge investment.
If I had to rely on my mom,
I'd be lost.
Thankfully, I met my boyfriend,
Jo.
-You know I love you, right?
-Yeah. I know.
We've been dating
for nine months.
And since I had
nowhere else to live,
his family invited me
to move in with them.
Are you gonna cut it?
Since my mom's rarely around,
Jo's mother Janet
is like a second mom to me.
Good job. Go ahead.
Keep cutting it.
Ever since Jo and I started
sharing a bedroom,
we've been really cramped
and it's caused
a lot of tension.
Can you get out of the
bathroom when I'm getting ready?
And things are about to get
even more crowded
because I'm pregnant.
[music playing]
Jo and I used to tell each other
everything.
But ever since his parents
invited me to move in,
it's like we barely talk at all.
Especially about the baby.
You never even told me
how you felt about it.
I don't know. Like--
-You don't know?
-What do you mean?
When you first, like, found out,
like, what were you thinking?
-You were in denial, right?
-Yeah.
-I showed him the pregnancy
-Nah, she's not pregnant.
I showed him the pregnancy test
and he just looked at me.
I didn't know what to say.
What other options
did you consider?
My mom wanted me to do, like,
an abortion.
And I knew my mom
would say that.
So what made you decide
to keep it
and have the baby for yourself
and take care of it?
She didn't like
the idea of adoption.
I mean, it's good.
I wouldn't be able to do it.
Did you want to look
into adoption more
and you didn't say anything?
Well, you have to understand
the reason for that
is because this is going to be
a very difficult thing
to do right now
is having a baby,
going to college,
going to school.
I think things will get worse
before they get better,
and eventually they
will get better.
Things are not
going to get worse.
-They can't get worse, sweetie.
-They can.
How are they gonna get worse?
They better not get worse.
Things can always get worse.
Jo's being really negative,
which makes it worse for me.
We're going shopping
for baggy clothes
because aside from family
and a few close friends,
I'm trying to hide
the pregnancy.
I'm not ready
to tell anybody yet.
I'd rather just tell everybody
and get it over with.
I know. But I wouldn't even know
how to tell anybody.
Hi. I'm pregnant.
I would never say that.
I guess bigger clothes
will help cover it up.
I'm glad Jo's coming shopping
with me.
We don't do much together
these days,
but getting out of the house
seems to help us get along.
Wanna try it for size?
I could try that one.
I don't know.
All right.
Do you think I look fat?
No, I don't think so.
Do you think it
will hide a pregnancy?
Why do you want to hide it?
I'm just, like, not ready
to tell people at school.
OK.
Thinking, like,
maybe black will hide it
because it's supposed
to make you look skinnier.
-Yeah.
-I don't know.
So how far along are you?
Almost--I'll be
six months on Tuesday.
Soon you're not going
to be able to hide it.
I know.
Well, I'm thinking maybe I won't
get that much bigger than this.
Hiding this pregnancy
is exhausting enough.
And to add to that,
I have to take my SATs tomorrow.
I don't even know
what any of these words mean.
I'm trying to graduate
a semester early
and then study dental hygiene,
so I have to do well.
But studying often
leads to daydreaming.
Since I got pregnant, I've been
thinking a lot about my dad.
His sister had found me
on Facebook,
and I've been debating on
whether to send her an email.
I guess I don't have
much to lose.
Now all I could do is wait.
Or study.
[music playing]
[phone ringing]
It's the morning of the SATs.
I know I should be nervous
about the test,
but I'm more nervous
about people noticing my belly.
Oh my god.
I'm, like, freaking out.
I really don't want to do this
right now.
-All the people?
-Yeah.
They're making me nervous.
-Bye.
Love you.
Good luck!
Standing outside, I started
to feel really uncomfortable.
And when I got inside,
things got even worse.
I can't focus on this test.
Everyone is staring at me
and whispering behind my back.
This five hour test feels
more like an eternity.
When it finally ended,
my friends and I went to unwind.
But when we started talking,
I found out all that staring
was not in my head.
Everyone stares at Kail.
But I feel like they stare
because they don't know
if I am pregnant or not.
We'll be in the bathroom
after lunch and she'll, like--
she'll walk in
and people will be like--
staring at her.
So I'm like,
I can see you staring at her.
-I know.
-I see it.
If you don't get any bigger,
do you just plan
-on not telling people?
-Yeah.
Doesn't it hurt to
hold in a secret like that?
it's soon for the pregnancy,
like...
But I feel like
I don't even look pregnant.
I feel like I just look fat.
It's not anybody's business
at this point.
I mean, maybe when it gets
closer and you can really tell.
People think what they think,
like, but-- It is hard.
You know, you could say you
don't care, and then, like--
I'm the type of person
I say I don't care,
and then I'll go home
and cry about it.
-Cry about it.
-Right.
I'll cry about it behind
closed doors, like--
Same way.
Are you hiding
in your baggie clothes?
-Kind of.
- Why?
She doesn't want--
Are you afraid
of what the girls are saying?
Why?
You're not ashamed, are you?
KAILYN: No, but they're mean.
Kail.
You don't have anything
to be ashamed of.
No, I'm not ashamed,
but they're, like, mean.
They were talking
about me today,
and they don't even
know me and stuff.
Exactly.
They don't know you,
but they feel
they have the need
to talk to you--
talk about you.
Do you understand that?
Yeah.
Listen, you're special,
you're smart, you're beautiful,
and you're pregnant.
And guess what?
You're going to do it.
You're going to be fine.
OK?
Mhm.
Do you trust me?
[kailyn crying]
I've been struggling a lot
with trying to hide
my pregnancy,
and I really need to talk
about it with my friends,
who I've already told.
I feel like it could happen
to any one of us.
-It could have been any of us.
-It, like--well--
-I mean, if you're--yeah.
-Right.
But--
Did you use a condom that night?
-Didn't--
-That was the one night--
-That--
-Prom night.
-Gotcha.
Prom night '09.
I remember
when you first started,
kind of looking pregnant,
everyone was like--
-I didn't believe it.
-Is she pregnant?
-Or is she just fat?
-Or is she just gaining weight?
And I was like, I don't know.
Well, I think, like,
it's going to start to,
really pop out soon,
so I'm not going to be able
to hide it anymore.
It's not really being hid.
Sure, it is.
-I just look fat right now.
-No.
-You're pregnant.
No, I know I'm pregnant.
But I'm saying I don't actually
look like I'm pregnant.
No.
As a friend to a friend,
you look pregnant.
-I'm still in denial.
-I know.
Since my mom's
still between homes,
I only get to see her
once in a while
when she picks me up
from school.
Did you see
who I brought along?
She'll come up
and greet you in a second.
There you are.
[cat meowing]
She's taking me shopping
for baby furniture,
which is nice,
but I'm more concerned
with her getting her life
on track.
Are you're not going
to look for an apartment
until you get a job?
I'm doing both at the same time.
Should be there in the pocket
but go ahead and answer it.
No.
Even though
they're together all the time,
it seems like my mom's boyfriend
always manages
to interrupt our alone time.
Love you too. Bye.
Do you have any change?
Like a quarter?
Quarters only.
Oh, I don't have quarters.
Oh, Mom!
Oh, how cute.
Oh, I love that.
Four piece floor model sale.
-Isn't that beautiful?
-How much is it?
That's a wonderful price, too.
Can we afford it
is the question.
Oh, that's not the question.
Price is the question
because I know Janet and Eddie
are going to end up paying,
and I'm always worried
about being a burden to them.
The baby furniture that they
have is, like, heirloom quality.
That's pretty.
And what are their prices like?
Are they expensive?
I don't know what your price
range was that you looked.
It was like $900.
These are probably
around $1,300.
Suzi, can I get you
something to drink?
No, actually,
I'm going to head out.
-He's called about four times.
-I don't care about him.
Oh, well, I do.
As usual, my mom's boyfriend
is more important than me.
What's the matter?
You seem upset.
Well, because she's always
in a rush to go hang out
-with her boyfriend.
-Oh, stop.
Don't even start.
She misses you.
Well, do you want me
to come over Sunday?
I don't know.
She misses
the hell out of you.
=Wants to spend time with you.
-I know. I know.
Absence makes the heart grow
fonder, so let me leave.
You want to walk me to the door?
-Be safe.
-OK. You too.
Always concerned
about her boyfriend.
It's the love of her life
right now.
Right now.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
Yeah?
Everything just
don't work your way.
I hate to tell you that.
Well,
what do I want to work my way?
I just want my mom
to spend more time with me.
That's all.
Like, this is the time
I need her the most.
Kail,
that's why we're here for you.
No, I know,
but she's still my mom.
I know she's your mom.
I just don't understand
her train of thought.
Like, I don't understand
why he's more important than me
right now.
Like, I don't get it.
Like, why is he more important?
He's been in her life
for less than a year.
She's going to do what she's
going to do no matter what,
and you know that.
She's proven that to you
many times.
All right.
I need to go to bed.
Sleep well, my darling.
[music playing]
Halloween
is one of my favorite holidays,
and every year my friend Steph
and I go pumpkin picking.
I want to get one with a stem.
If I find a nice one, you know?
This green one's cute.
If would be, like,
baby's first pumpkin.
So are you gonna, like, do
this next year with your baby?
-Hopefully.
-I wanna come.
I don't if he'll be, like,
old enough.
Well, you can just,
like, carry the baby.
Yeah.
How are you and, like, Jo
doing so far
since you guys are kind of stuck
sharing one room?
I don't know. We have really off
days where we fight nonstop.
Or, like,
we don't even talk at all.
Yeah.
And it's always stupid stuff.
You guys used to, like, see
each other, like, every day,
not be with each other
every single minute.
24 hours. Yeah.
You guys just got to separate
a little bit.
Like, let him do his thing,
you can just do your own thing,
you know?
I feel like people
don't ever invite me to,
like, parties or any--
anything like that anymore.
It's probably because, like,
they know you're pregnant.
So it's like,
why invited her since I
-know she's going to say no?
-Yeah.
But they don't know
if I'm going to say no.
-Like, I could still hang out.
-True.
It's not like I can't
leave the house or something.
So are you gonna,
like, actually go trick
-or treating on Halloween?
-No.
No?
-I don't think so.
-I think you should.
-You have to.
-It will be your last Halloween.
Come with us.
We're probably just, like,
chilling at Nicole's house.
I don't know.
It kind of sucks, though.
Why?
Because it sucks if I just,
show up somewhere.
And they're like,
oh, why is she here?
-She won't care.
-She's pregnant.
Or they're like--
it's just a bummer.
That night, I went on Facebook
and found an email response
from my aunt.
Oh my god.
My dad is inviting me to come
down to Texas to meet him.
This is a huge step
after 16 years.
[music playing]
I'm carving pumpkins
with the girls today,
and I can't wait to tell them
about my dad.
My dad's sister
found me on Facebook.
-Oh, really?
-Really?
-Were you surprised?
-That's, like, a positive.
Yeah. Because that's what I've
always talked to my mom
about was, like, I wonder if
they'd try to find me at all.
Yeah.
I mean, you've been
trying to find your dad too.
So that's really cool.
So I'm going to go stay with him
over Thanksgiving break.
I'm going to meet his--
-So it's not just him.
---a sister.
-You're meeting everybody.
-Yeah.
And then two nieces
and a nephew.
And like, that's
his entire family.
-Are you excited?
-Yeah.
Like, I'm excited, but
it's like,
what if we don't have
anything in common?
I'm sure you will,
he's your dad.
Yeah.
And it's going to feel
a little awkward at first
because this is your first time
meeting him.
-Are you going to cry?
-I'll probably cry, yeah.
[laughter]
[wistful music]
-Jo?
-What?
Can you help me?
I guess not.
I don't have pants on.
Sharing one small bedroom
is hard for a teenage couple.
I always feel like I'm
invading Jo's space,
but I have nowhere else to go.
We're, like, not even
talking right now.
I don't know what--
He doesn't want
to do anything, so--
What did you guys do
before you guys started--
when you were dating?
-Going to movies a lot.
-Yeah.
What?
-He said, yeah, we did.
-See?
This is what he does.
He shuts me out.
Like, I'm not going
to try anymore.
He doesn't want to go out and
do anything ever, and he--
Kailyn, don't get--
He's like, well, it's Sunday.
I don't want to do anything.
He doesn't want to
do anything ever.
Kailyn, don't get upset.
Well, I'm tired of it.
When the baby comes,
it can only get worse.
We can't sit here
and deal all that either.
Oh, I'm sure as hell not.
Well, I keep telling him,
if this is how it's going to
be, I don't have to be here.
I can figure out
somewhere else to go.
Got to go talk to him.
Kailyn is in a very
sensitive situation.
You have to be a little bit
more receptive and understand.
I do understand.
I don't--what--
OK, but why won't
you talk to her?
You go walking right past her,
you don't even say
anything to her.
OK, what is there to say now?
-What is there to say?
-How are you going to--
OK, I'm trying
to help her out.
I'm--
How are you helping her out?
So she's not a single mother?
That's not helping her out?
I'm sacrificing a lot,
and all she does
-is complain about me, so--
-And you know what?
It is your responsibility
and your duty to--
I guess I don't
need to be here if all
-I'm going to be doing is--
-Excuse me.
It is your responsibility
and your duty to sacrifice,
because you are the father
of that child.
-It was your decision to make.
-Yeah.
-Her decision.
-Ooh.
Her decision, Jonathan?
Hold it.
Jo, you're rolling
the wrong way.
You really are.
-The wrong thing to say.
-Her decision, Jonathan?
Don't say that.
It ain't right, bro.
No, it's not.
I decided to keep the baby
because that's what she wanted
and I'm going to
support her on that.
I'm not going to just leave
her with the baby by herself.
It takes a lot more than that.
You have to have some type
of emotional
and physical involvement
in what she does
and what you do,
the both of you together.
Because you have to get along.
Whether you stay with her for
the rest of your life or not,
she's the mother of your child.
You're going to have to live
with it for the rest of your--
-life.
-18 years plus college.
♪ Things
Just need some time ♪
Jo and I can't seem
to agree on anything.
We're not even on the same page
about finding
out the baby's sex.
So we're going to find
out the sex this time?
No.
Why not?
Because it's more fun
if we don't know.
Kailyn?
Today we have a sonogram.
And even though
I don't want to know the sex,
I can't wait to see our baby.
-There, can you see the face?
-Yeah.
Look, are those
the eyes right there?
Look at the mouth.
Look at the tongue?
-Did you see it?
-Oh, did you see it, Jon?
-Mm-hmm.
-Look.
Oh!
It's going to look like you, Jo.
-Do you like seeing it?
-Mm-hmm.
Turn your head to the side.
Oh, my gosh.
It looks just like you.
Look at that. My god.
Whoa.
Even the ears are
sticking out the same.
Oh, yeah.
Jo seems really overwhelmed.
His friends are
coming over tonight,
so maybe that will help
calm him down a little.
Do you want me
to leave those with you?
Yes.
-That's scary, bro.
-It is scary.
No, the middle one is scary.
No,
the whole situation is scary.
-What up, bro?
-You all right?
-Yeah.
-How's the baby?
-Big.
-Big?
-These are pictures.
-Those are the pictures?
Yeah.
I can't even tell
where the baby is at.
All right.
Everybody talking about
how this baby look like me.
-How do you know, man?
-That's what I'm saying.
How do you know that
that looks like me?
-I don't know--
-Who said that looked like you?
Everybody's saying
it looks like me.
-I don't know what--
-You can't even tell!
Exactly.
It don't got a face.
How do you feel about
having a baby, son?
You ain't really
talking about it too much.
-It hasn't hit you yet.
-It's hitting me.
It's hitting you?
It hit me, a long time ago,
right in the gut.
I'm still trying to plot
my next move.
Got to figure out
what the hell I'm doing.
Still trying to figure it out.
[cheerful music]
My trip to Texas to meet
my dad is coming up soon.
I have so many questions,
and there's only one person
who could possibly answer them.
Even though she wasn't thrilled
when I told her my plans,
my mom agreed to meet me
for dinner that night.
I didn't want to ask this.
-What?
-It's just about going to Texas.
Is there anything that you
want me to know before I leave?
Know about what?
Just anything, like my dad.
Well--
And let's not use
any negativity here.
I'm going to just say it
like it is.
Don't expect
a whole lot from him.
But I don't.
But I'm just telling
you ahead of time,
don't expect anything from him.
It's totally up to you.
If you want a father-daughter
relationship, that's fine.
Please don't come crying to me.
I don't want to say,
I told you so.
I don't want to go there.
I mean, he's going to promise
you the moon and the stars
-and nothing--
-But he hasn't done that.
He tells me
he can't do much for me,
but what he can do, he will do.
Right.
So that's all that I ask for.
And that's fine.
I mean, it's the same with you.
I'm sure there's tons of things
that you want to do for me,
-but you can't.
-Exactly.
I just don't want you
going there
with really high expectations.
I know I shouldn't
get my hopes up,
but I can't help but fantasize
about finally
having a dad in my life.
I want to get Jo's take on this.
What if it, like, goes awful?
It won't
It'll be all good. Trust me.
More options for the future,
maybe.
What do you mean,
more options for my future?
I don't know.
If we ever broke up,
then you could go live
with your dad or something.
You would be OK with me taking
the baby all the way to Texas?
I didn't say you
were taking the baby.
But I would be.
-You wouldn't be.
-Yeah, I would.
Take me to court, bitch.
I'll win.
Why would you even say that?
Jo's so negative, and he always
wants to check out.
I want to talk to him
about it,
but he decided to go pick up
his friend Carlos from work.
Are you leaving now?
-Oh, my god.
-What?
-What happened now?
-Nothing happened.
So why--
I just asked him to spend
time with me for a little bit
and he wants to leave.
We're going through
a lot right now.
Is it really that important for
you to go hang out with him?
Do you understand
why I want you here?
I just don't feel the same way.
[sad music]
What's wrong with Jo?
He's saying
that he don't want to be here,
-like we're--
-Wait, wait, wait.
Like we're somewhere
in his way, or--
Where are you going?
Jo?
-What?
-Come here.
You have some [bleep] going
on here you need to attend to.
It is your responsibility.
Finish your business here first.
Be a man about it.
And then you go do whatever
the hell you have to do.
She gets upset over nothing.
Like, I'm coming back.
Because I just want you to
be nice to me
and you're leaving!
And I haven't spent time--
I'm [bleep] coming right back.
-No, you're not!
-I don't understand.
You just told me you were
going to hang out with Carlos.
Why is he so important that you
can't fix things with me first?
You always put him first.
You never put me first
in front of him.
What the [bleep]
are you talking about?
-Exactly what she just said.
-You--
I put who first.
You are going to work
things out with Kail,
spend time with her.
That's all she's asking for.
She don't ask you
for nothing else.
I [bleep] live with her.
What do you mean--
-But we never hang out!
-But you're never together.
You used to hang out
with her all the time.
I'm telling you as your mother,
what you're doing
right this minute is not right.
What do you want me to do,
[bleep]
go to sleep with her right now?
No. That's not what
I want you to do.
I work and I stay--
And you never hang out
with me when you can!
And I go to sleep
during the day.
You're always out
doing other things!
You told him
you'd give him a ride home?
Yes.
Knowing that you had a
responsibility here tonight?
I think he can walk
home tonight, too.
That's ridiculous.
Come on.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
[door slamming]
[crying]
Are you hurt?
Yeah.
I want you to know,
regardless of what happens,
that dad and I
are still here for you, OK?
That doesn't make me feel
any better about him, though.
I still have to
sleep in his bed.
This is your bed now.
He gave up his rights
when he did what he did.
I don't know what I did--
Well, I'm going to have
to talk to him, OK?
[crying]
[music]
♪ From you
Just to stay with me here ♪
How are Jo and I
going to raise a baby
if we can't even talk?
All I want is to give my
baby what I never had.
After our huge fight,
Jo never came home.
Of all the days for
him to check out,
he had to pick the day I leave
for Texas to meet my dad.
So are you excited?
You nervous
about meeting daddy?
-Mm-hmm.
-Yeah?
Try not to get upset.
You know?
This is your second chance
at having
a relationship with your dad.
Make the best of it.
I'm really nervous to be doing
this all by myself.
Luckily, Janet and Eddie
are taking me to the airport.
Kailyn, you've got to try
to have a good time.
I want you to just let go
of all of the stuff
that went on last night.
Just, hopefully, something good
will come out of it.
I hope I don't like it too much.
What's wrong
with you liking it a lot?
Because I won't want
to come back.
I thought about this day
many times before,
but it's hard to believe
it's actually happening.
[contemplative music]
Hello.
How are you doing?
Good.
Oh, man.
What's wrong?
I don't know where
to get my bag.
You are short.
I told you.
-You're short.
-Told you I wasn't tall.
Are any of these ones--
this one's mine.
What'd you expect, 6 foot?
[laughing]
You have Dunkin' Donuts
around here?
Oh, yeah.
You like Dunkin' Donuts?
Everything cool
up there in Pennsylvania?
Yeah, I guess.
Meeting your dad
after 16 years is pretty weird.
I'm glad he's trying
to spark up some conversation.
That's where the Cowboys
used to play
until they got that new stadium.
You know why they left that hole
in that roof, don't you?
So God could watch
his team on Sunday.
Oh, yeah, right.
We're starting to warm up a bit,
but it's beginning to hit me
how much of a stranger
he really is.
There's the kitchen, and then
the backyard back there.
Can't see nothing
out there right now.
Why is this locked?
We had $200 worth of meat
in there,
and I don't like sticky fingers,
so I put that lock on it.
That's weird.
-Is that weird?
-Yeah.
Oh, well.
I broke that chair
the other day, by the way.
But it's OK, you sit--
it ain't going to break.
You ever go to one of them
road kill things
up there where you live?
You know what I'm talking about?
Road kill?
They'd have, like,
elk, porcupine, bear.
Don't know about them?
This is really awkward.
We have nothing in common.
But I came all this way to get
to know him, so I have to try.
Is this what it's like
in your house all the time?
Do what?
Is this what it's like
at your house all the time?
Yep.
Did you ever think we were going
to actually meet in real life?
Yeah, I knew one day we would.
Just didn't know when.
Do you plan on being
around when the baby is born?
The only drawback about that is,
you don't ever know
when it's coming.
You think you'll be
around more often now?
This is not exactly
the father-daughter reunion
I was hoping for.
-Hi.
-Hi, Janet?
What's the matter?
I want to come home.
What happened?
Nothing.
Why do you want to come home?
I don't like it here.
Why is it that you
don't like it there?
I don't know, it's just not
what I thought it would be.
You've got to hang
in there,
because you can't
leave right now.
It's just weird.
I mean, he's your dad.
You gotta try, OK?
OK.
-All right.
-Bye.
♪ Now all is said and done ♪
♪ I'm not the one
You thought you wanted ♪
I guess it's safe to say
to say I didn't find
what I was looking for here.
Oh, there she goes,
there goes Kail.
I didn't know where to go.
Meeting my dad
did not go how I expected,
but I've got to say,
I'm pretty happy to be back.
How was all week, overall?
Did you have a good time?
It was all right.
-It was all right?
-I probably won't go back.
My trip was a major letdown,
but the time away seems to have
been really good for Jo and I.
And we're featuring
warm brownie
with vanilla ice cream,
whipped cream,
and it's drizzled
in chocolate and caramel.
-Can I have that?
-That sounds good for me.
[laughter]
OK, I'll get this going.
Are we going to keep
fighting when the baby comes?
Oh, I think we'll
be fine, love.
The baby's going to come,
we're going to have
our own little family.
It'll be all right.
Times are changing.
I'm scheduled to be
done with high school
before I give birth,
so I'm going to tour
our community college today.
Jo was going to
come with me,
but he just got
called into work,
so I'm hoping my mom
can come instead.
-Hi, mom.
-Hi.
I know it's kind
of short notice,
but I have a tour set up
at NAC today to tour the campus.
I didn't know if you
would want to go with me
so I don't go by myself.
I can't right now.
I'm in the middle of
a major application
here on the computer.
It's, like, 75 questions.
The whole thing is, I just
don't want to go by myself.
I don't even know what
questions to ask and stuff.
All right, well, I mean, good
luck, I guess, I don't know.
OK, bye.
Are you crying?
I wanted my mom to go
with me, but she can't.
I'm sorry.
Should I ask about the
financial aid and stuff, or no?
Just anything
you want to know.
-Just ask.
-I don't want to ask.
-Like, I'm embarrassed.
-Don't be embarrassed.
You have to take anything
you can get right now.
Love you.
Trying to get into
college is scary enough.
Figuring it out on my
own is even scarier.
-Kailyn?
-Yeah.
-Hi, I'm Jim McCarthy.
-Hi. How are you?
-Nice to meet you.
-Hi, I'm Amber.
-Great.
-Thanks for coming.
-Yeah. I'm excited.
We're going to take
you around on a tour.
What major are
you interested in?
-Dental hygiene.
-Dental hygiene, great.
All right.
Well, we'll get started.
-OK.
-This is our fitness center.
It's all brand-new,
as you can see.
Is there an extra
charge for it when you go?
No, it's actually free.
Well, I'm looking
forward to this gym.
We'll go upstairs.
Yeah.
So this is our
dental hygiene clinic.
You'll spend a lot
of time in here.
The dental hygiene
graduates have
been our highest-paid
graduates, and last year
they started at about
$55,000 a year to start.
Right out of the program.
Hope you're in here someday.
Yeah, I hope so too.
Are there other students
that have babies?
Actually, I have
a two-year-old son,
and I found that the college
has worked with me so much.
Is your family supportive?
For the most part.
My boyfriend's family
is more supportive.
My parents haven't even
met their grandchild.
They've not been in my life.
They kicked me out when I--
But you're doing really
well though, right?
Yeah.
Personally I do not
regret it for one second.
My son is my world.
I'm going to cry.
He seriously
gave me my strength.
Because if I didn't have him,
I wouldn't have anything.
So you can do it.
And we have something in us,
as mothers, that keep us going.
That makes me
feel a lot better.
If I look at other
people that can do it,
then it'll make me
feel more motivated.
I'm really looking forward to
applying and everything now.
For the first time, I
actually feel
like I can see
my future falling into place.
And thank goodness,
because that night,
my water broke
and it was time to find out
if we were
having a boy or a girl.
Breathe, mama.
Relax the legs,
don't tense up.
Don't breathe so fast,
take it easy.
Mom, you have to be quiet,
I have contractions.
OK.
-Over here.
-OK?
You OK, Jojo?
I mean, you're shaking
just as bad as she is.
Just keep breathing.
Stay strong.
Baby's coming.
Pretty soon, you're going to
have a bundle of joy to hold.
-That's right.
-And love.
[laughter]
Mom!
God.
No, no.
Keep breathing.
If you want an epidural,
now's your chance.
I want it right now.
I'm having a contraction.
Hold on.
Mom, sign my name on that paper.
You want to push.
Sign my name on the
epidural paper right now.
Kail, you have to sign for it.
So just do it as
quick as you can.
[beeping]
Keep breathing.
No, don't push, no pushing.
I'm having
another contraction.
Ugh, oh my god.
-It's OK, honey.
-Keep breathing.
Can't they just suck
it out real quick?
[laughter]
Hi, Kailyn,
are you feeling better?
I just feel pressure,
like, I'm in denial.
I don't think I'm going
to have a baby after this.
She's in a lot of pain.
Oh, she's feeling
like she's got to push.
-I've got to go back.
-Bye.
Five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, good.
Keep breathing, good.
-You got to push.
-All right.
You're doing fabulous, honey.
Hold my foot, Jo!
OK, honey.
One more, right on top of it.
Go ahead, Kailyn.
-Go ahead, keep pushing.
- You can do it, baby!
Push, push, push.
There, you're doing it, honey.
It's OK.
[screaming]
Oh.
Ready?
-It's a boy!
-You did it, honey.
-Congratulations!
Good job.
[baby crying]
Oh, my God.
-He's so cute.
-I know!
Who wants to cut the cord?
Oh, baby.
All right.
We're bringing baby
Isaac home today.
I'm not quite sure
how to feel about it.
Are you excited?
I don't know.
Scared?
You're going to be fine.
My life has
taken a major turn,
and having my friends
come over to meet Isaac
only makes it more clear.
How much does this kid eat?
Well, he eats,
like, every two hours.
Sounds like me.
I have to breastfeed,
and you guys can't watch that.
Um, that's what
the pillows are for.
Your put them in
front of your face.
Well, I'm still
getting used to it.
And he's not--because I'm not
producing regular milk yet.
It's just like--
Skim milk?
You guys are so stupid.
I suddenly feel so grown up.
In my life, I don't
come first anymore.
And Jo's realizing that
he doesn't, either.
We've never been more stressed.
And it doesn't help that neither
of us have slept in days.
You going to wake up at
night and feed him for me?
If you don't get up first.
[beep]
[baby crying]
A crying newborn is basically
the new soundtrack to our lives
and both of our patience
is starting to wear thin.
[music playing]
[baby crying]
It's definitely
taking a toll on us.
You left the milk out again.
What?
Oh, well.
No, Jo.
I'm really [bleep] pissed
right now.
Thanks for that, Jo.
Morning.
How are you, Kail?
I don't even want
to talk about it.
What's the matter?
Because Jo left
the milk out again.
It's one [bleep] once of milk.
-Just shut the [bleep] up.
-No, it wasn't.
-Stop bitching about it.
-Well, why do you do that?
-Kail, I was a-[bleep] -sleep.
-I don't care!
Shut up.
Don't bitch about it.
You do it all the time.
It was [bleep] mistake,
shut the [bleep] up!
-Cut it out.
-Damn.
Well, you don't
pay for anything anyway,
shut the [bleep] up.
Jonathan, was
that even necessary?
-[bleep]
-[bleep] you, Jo!
That wasn't necessary, though.
It was.
I guess I was hoping
things with Jo would get better
once the baby came,
but now there's someone
more important to focus on.
-Do you want him?
-Yeah.
With all the stress
I've been under,
my mom has barely
been around to help.
He's so cute, look at him.
But she did finally get a job
and a place to live,
so I'm hoping things
will change now.
Well, this is a nice place.
I made your favorite,
homemade chili.
Go watch your mommy eat.
Is he sleeping better
through the night for you?
-Oh.
-No.
Did you tell your
father about boog?
Well, I didn't tell
him, but he knows.
He does?
Who told him?
He just saw it
on the computer.
Oh, what was his response?
He said something
about coming to see him.
When?
And I didn't really say much,
and then I checked my email
yesterday or the day before
and he was like, I plan
on coming to see him soon.
When hell freezes over, right?
Whatever.
So do you talk to him
on a regular basis?
No, I haven't talked to him
on the phone since I got back.
Has he made any
attempt to call you?
-No.
-No?
That's nice.
Pretty much done with the
whole dad thing, or what?
It is what it is.
And believe me,
life's much better without him.
It's easy for my mom
to criticize my dad,
but the truth is, she hasn't
exactly been around for Isaac
-or me herself.
-He loves his nona.
Look it.
He's even trying to say it.
He's not going to say
Nona first
because you don't
spend enough time with him.
OK.
So you should probably
stop by more often.
I'm serious.
And I understand that.
Even if you only
come by for 20 minutes.
That's all fine
and dandy, but--
But what?
When there's so
many people around,
it's hard to spend quality
time over there with him.
I can bring him here,
but you don't ever invite us.
You need a written invitation?
I don't think so.
So what you want me to do?
Every time I call you're
like, oh, well, I'm busy.
What do you do on the weekends?
I usually work on a
Saturday or Sunday.
You even pass my house
on the way home from work.
-I don't go that way, though.
-But you can.
-I can, is right.
-And so you'll come by.
-Yes, I will.
-And you'll help me.
I will but not on Mondays
or Thursdays or even Saturdays.
Maybe.
I don't know.
OK.
It's becoming more and more
clear that things with my mom
are never really
going to change.
It's up to me now
to get my own life together.
To find out what you can do
to prevent pregnancy,
go to itsyoursexlife.org
My life is moving on.
I did well enough on my SATs
to get into
the community college,
which has a daycare
program for Isaac.
And even though it's not easy,
Jo and I are trying
to get the hang
of this parenting thing.
What is wrong with you?
It can get really frustrating,
but we're learning to put
our issues aside for Isaac,
and we're actually
even communicating.
So I'm kind of glad that
we don't have time to fight
anymore because of Isaac.
I think it's more,
we were fighting
because we're still
getting like,
accustomed to living
with each other.
I think that was
more the reason.
Well, it is kind of
hard to move in with somebody
when you were only
together for nine months.
So you don't think
I nag you anymore?
Sometimes, but it's not--
-You don't fight with me?
-It's not unreasonable.
Oh...
thank you.
So I put up with it.
It really is all
about Isaac now.
But I don't mind,
I really don't.
Hi, baby.
Since I got pregnant, it taught
me really how to love deeper.
-What are you doing?
-Jumping in the tub with him.
Hey.
I think there is a
good chance that Jo and I
can stay together as long as
we're not selfish,
we don't fight
about stupid things,
we realize we have a baby now.
So we have to work
that much harder
to make things better for him.
-Did you wash his hair?
-No, not yet.
And behind his ears.
Janet has helped me
through everything.
I couldn't really ask
for a better mother.
Even though she's not
really blood related to me,
she is like my mom.
And get some rest,
all right?
Jo's parents
are so good to me.
And they just-- they treat
me like I'm their own child.
And I don't know where
I would be without them.
I think if I could go back,
I wouldn't have
had sex this early.
I think I would have
waited altogether.
This is like room
service right here.
I think the hardest part
about being a teen mom
is the fact that you
have to give up your youth,
your social life
is non-existent.
I've had to fight my whole life,
so I'm just waiting
for things to get easier.
I got it.
He sneezed.
I think there's a little
light at the end of the tunnel,
as long as I keep working hard--
probably harder than
most teenagers my age.
Hard work will
keep the light coming--
keep it shining through.
[relaxing music]
Coming up next, Dr. drew
hosts a tear-filled finale
special you won't want to miss.
You don't deserve to
be treated like that.
It's just a bunch of hate.
And they can get along,
they just don't want to try.
She really doesn't
tell me she loves me.
I tell you all the
time I love you, Janelle.
And I tell you I want you
to do the right thing.
He was the first guy
I fell in love with,
and I got pregnant by him.
Does she need to
just get over you?
I would say yes.
I got this for you, baby.
[Audience] Whoa!
[MUSIC -KEITH JARRETT, "MY
SONG"]