>> THREE, TWO, ONE, GO!
>> AH!
>> I'M COURTNEY.
I LIVE IN WOODLAND PARK,
COLORADO, AND I'M A SENIOR IN
HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, I GOT IT!
>> DID YOU?
>> OH.
I'M PRETTY SURE I WON IT.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
BUT THEY STAYED GOOD FRIENDS.
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M REALLY CLOSE
WITH MY MOM, I LIVE WITH MY DAD.
>> OH, I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
I WAS BORN WITH A CLEFT LIP
AND A CLEFT PALATE, MEANING
I HAD A GAP ON BOTH SIDES OF MY
LIP AND A GAP BETWEEN MY NOSE
AND THE ROOF OF MY MOUTH.
>> OH, YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
>> SO I'VE HAD A TOTAL OF SEVEN
RECONSTRUCTIVE SURGERIES
SINCE I WAS A BABY.
AND I WAS ALWAYS WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT PEOPLE THOUGHT OF MY CLEFT,
BUT WHEN I MET MY BOYFRIEND,
SCOTT, HE COULDN'T EVEN TELL,
AND WE FELL IN LOVE.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> AND EVEN THOUGH I'M REALLY
RELIGIOUS AND ALWAYS KIND OF
BEEN SAVING MYSELF FOR MARRIAGE,
THAT DIDN'T GO SO WELL,
AND NOW I'M PREGNANT.
WHEN I GOT PREGNANT, MY PARENTS
WERE REALLY DISAPPOINTED,
SO I STARTED GOING BACK TO
CHURCH AND DECIDED THAT I WANTED
TO BE ABSTINENT.
SCOTT WASN'T THRILLED,
BUT HE STUCK BY MY SIDE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE SEX UNTIL
I WAS MARRIED, AND--
>> YOU MAKE IT SEEM LIKE IT WAS
ALL MY FAULT.
>> NO, I GAVE IN.
IT WAS MY FAULT TOO.
>> YOU GAVE IN A LOT WITHOUT ME
EVEN TRYING.
>> I JUST GAVE IN TO YOUR LONG
HAIR.
YOUR LONG, LUSCIOUS HAIR.
>> OH, GOD.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK OF ME
RIGHT WHEN YOU MET ME?
>> I DON'T REMEMBER.
>> YES, YOU DO.
[laughs]
"SHE'S GOT SOME BIG OLE
BOOBIES."
>> AND YOU LOOKED BEAUTIFUL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> THAT WASN'T THE ONLY THING.
>> YEAH, YOU NOTICED THAT LAST.
>> NO, I NOTICED THAT FIRST.
LOOKED AT THE FACE THEN DOWN.
>> SCOTT WORKS FULL-TIME AS AN
ELECTRICIAN'S APPRENTICE
AND MAKES ENOUGH MONEY TO RENT
HIS OWN TWO-BEDROOM APARTMENT,
AND HE WANTS ME TO MOVE IN WITH
HIM BEFORE THE BABY IS BORN.
>> CAN WE GET TWO WHEAT GRASS
SHOTS AND THE 12-OUNCE
MELLOW MANGO?
>> OKAY.
>> UGH.
READY?
>> ALL RIGHT, READY?
THREE, TWO, ONE.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE
A SUPER BABY.
[giggles]
I'M WORRIED THAT IF I MOVE IN
WITH YOU, WE'LL BE TEMPTED
TO HAVE SEX.
IS IT HARD FOR YOU?
>> YEAH.
OF COURSE IT'S GONNA BE
A CHALLENGE.
>> YOU'RE A 19-YEAR-OLD,
FULL OF HORMONE,
WANT TO GET THE HANKY-PANKY.
>> 90% OF GUYS, I WOULD SAY, DO.
>> I WANT TO BE WITH THAT 10%
OF GUYS.
>> MORE LIKE 99.9% OF GUYS.
>> WELL, THEN, I HOPE
YOU'RE THE 1% OF GUYS.
>> 99.999% OF GUYS.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE THEY DON'T
LOOK AT IT LIKE I LOOK AT IT,
AND I WANT YOU TO GET ON THE
SAME LEVEL AS ME.
>> I JUST SEE IT AS,
WE'RE PREGNANT, YOU KNOW?
WHAT HARM'S GONNA COME OUT
OF IT?
>> THE RELIGIOUS PART OF IT IS,
WE SHOULD WAIT FOR SOMEBODY TO
KNOW THAT WE LOVE EACH OTHER
AND TO KNOW THAT IT'S NOT LUST.
ALSO, IF I DO MOVE IN,
I WANT TO GET--START READING
THE BIBLE MORE AND GETTING MORE
DEDICATED TO THAT.
>> I JUST WANT US TO GET ON THE
SAME MORALS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK WE'RE PRETTY GOOD
COMPARED TO MOST.
>> THE WAY I LOOK AT IT IS,
IF YOU WAIT FOR ME, THEN I'LL
KNOW FOR SURE THAT YOU WANT TO
BE WITH ME, 'CAUSE YOU'LL DO
ANYTHING TO BE WITH ME.
>> YEAH.
[laughs]
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> JUST SAY...
>> YES, COURTNEY, YOU ARE RIGHT.
>> I KNOW I EXPECT A LOT FROM
SCOTT, BUT MY RELIGION IS A HUGE
PART OF MY LIFE.
MY FRIENDS WERE SHOCKED WHEN
I STRAYED FROM IT AND GOT
PREGNANT.
AND NOW THAT I'M FINISHING
SCHOOL ONLINE, IT'S HARDER AND
HARDER TO SEE THEM.
>> I'M KIND OF SAD THAT YOU
CANNOT GO ROLLER SKATING WITH ME
RIGHT NOW, BECAUSE I'VE BEEN
WANTING TO ASK YOU TO GO ROLLER
SKATING, AND EVERY SINGLE TIME
I'M LIKE, "WAIT, NO, I CAN'T.
SHE'S PREGNANT."
THAT'S NOT COOL.
>> I'M SAD I WON'T BE ABLE TO
WALK WITH MY CLASS.
IT'S LIKE, WHEN YOU THINK OF
HIGH SCHOOL, YOU THINK OF
SENIOR--YOUR SENIOR YEAR,
WALKING WITH YOUR CLASS,
THROWING YOUR HAT UP IN THE AIR.
>> DOES YOUR ONLINE SCHOOL NOT
DO A WALKING, LIKE, GRADUATION?
>> NO.
I'M NOT EVEN GONNA HAVE
A GRADUATION PARTY.
I MET SCOTT AT HIS GRADUATION
PARTY.
RIGHT WHEN I SAW HIM, HE WAS,
LIKE, TOWERING OVER ME,
AND I WAS LIKE, "HE'S SO TALL.
HE HAS NICE HAIR."
>> AND HE HAS NICE HAIR.
>> SO I WAS LIKE, "OKAY,
I COULD WORK WITH THIS."
>> HERE'S YOUR GIFTS FOR ALL
YOUR STUFF.
>> YUM!
>> Y'ALL LET ME KNOW
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING.
>> OKAY, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
I REMEMBER YOU ALWAYS BEING THE
ONE WHO WAS ABSTINENT.
DID YOU GUYS--WAS THAT THE FIRST
TIME YOU GUYS HAD HAD SEX?
>> NO, WE DIDN'T HAVE SEX FOR
THE FIRST FEW MONTHS, AND THEN
AFTER A WHILE, I KIND OF
GAVE IN, AND THEN WE WERE DOING
IT FOR A WHILE AFTERWARDS,
AND THEN I GOT PREGNANT.
AND THEN I JUST KIND OF GATHERED
MYSELF BACK UP, GOT MY MORALS
BACK, AND WAS LIKE, "OKAY,"
SO WE STOPPED.
>> I THINK THAT WOULD BE HARD
FOR MOST PEOPLE TO GO FROM
HAVING SEX TO JUST, LIKE,
OH, CUT OFF.
>> OH, YEAH.
SCOTT WANTS ME TO MOVE IN WITH
HIM, BUT I DON'T WANT TO TEMPT
HIM AND MYSELF TO HAVE SEX.
I THINK THAT WOULD JUST MAKE IT
A LOT HARDER.
I THINK IT WOULD BE GOOD IF YOU
GUYS WERE BOTH THERE FOR THE
BEGINNING PARTS.
YOUR DAD AND YOUR SISTER
PROBABLY AREN'T GONNA HELP YOU
TAKE SHIFTS WITH THE BABY.
>> NO.
>> SO I THINK PROBABLY FOR YOUR
MENTAL HEALTH YOU SHOULD
PROBABLY JUST MOVE IN WITH
SCOTT.
>> MOVING IN WITH SCOTT WOULD
PROBABLY MAKE THINGS EASIER
BECAUSE HE LIVES 45 MINUTES
AWAY, AND SOME WEEKS I ONLY SEE
HIM WHEN HE COMES OVER FOR
SUNDAY DINNER.
>> CAN WE GET SCOTT TO PRAY,
YOU THINK?
>> NO. [laughs]
>> NO?
>> DAD, HE'S SHY.
>> THANK YOU, FATHER, FOR THIS
FOOD, AND THANK YOU FOR THIS
BEAUTIFUL DAY, AND GIVE US
WISDOM AS WE SPEAK.
>> AMEN.
>> YOU REMEMBER WHEN WE BOUGHT
YOUR PURITY RING?
>> YEAH.
>> AND WE TALKED PRETTY
EXTENSIVELY ABOUT THAT, AND YOU
HAD MADE A COMMITMENT.
>> MADE A PROMISE TO GOD.
>> THAT WAS A LITTLE BIT OF
A SHOCKER, YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE
WE'D TALKED ABOUT THAT,
YOU KNOW?
ARE YOU ACTIVE?
>> WELL, AT THE SAME TIME,
THIS MADE ME CLOSER TO GOD.
>> YEAH? HOW SO?
>> I STARTED READING THE BIBLE,
AND I STARTED PRAYING MORE,
AND I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST CHANGED ME.
>> SO YOU WERE NOT PRACTICING
ABSTINENCE, GOT PREGNANT.
WHERE ARE YOU AT NOW WITH
BEING PURE?
>> WE'RE REMAINING ABSTINENT.
>> UNTIL...
>> WE GET MARRIED.
WHICH, HE WANTS TO GET MARRIED
TOMORROW.
>> [laughs]
>> WELL, HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT, THOUGH?
HERE'S THE THING:
THAT'S NORMAL.
>> IT'S HARD TO GO FROM BEING
INTIMATE TO ALL OF A SUDDEN
JUST NOT.
I DON'T KNOW IF I COULD DO IT.
>> I THINK IT TAKES A LOT OF
DEDICATION TO GOD.
AND YEAH, IT'S HARD,
BUT I JUST PRAY,
AND IT HELPS ME THROUGH IT.
>> SCOTT, WHAT DO YOU FEEL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I STILL FEEL THE SAME ABOUT HER.
IT'S HELPING HER.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HOW IT'S
HELPED YOU.
>> ME?
>> OUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> TO HELP IT GROW STRONGER?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> YEAH, TO BE ON THE SAME
MORAL LEVEL.
>> YEAH.
>> SO THAT'S TOUGH, ISN'T IT?
IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S REALLY TOUGH
ON SCOTT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, I DON'T BLAME HIM.
>> I DON'T BLAME HIM.
IS IT TOUGH?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SURE.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO, SCOTT?
HOW DO YOU... [laughs]
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
THIS.
CAN WE NOT?
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST AWKWARD FOR ME BECAUSE
I DON'T LIKE TALKING ABOUT
THAT STUFF.
>> IT'S DIFFERENT FOR YOU.
YOU GOT TO UNDERSTAND.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IT, 'KAY?
>> I'M JUST SAYING.
>> I'M JUST SERIOUS.
>> * IT'S FINE *
>> WHAT AM I GONNA DO IF I GO
INTO LABOR BY MYSELF?
WHAT IF I'M IN SO MUCH PAIN
THAT I CAN'T DRIVE?
WE'RE TOO BROKE TO CALL AN
AMBULANCE.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU NEED TO MOVE
IN.
>> YEAH, BUT WHAT IF YOU'RE GONE
WHEN I MOVE IN?
>> I'M ONLY 10, 15 MINUTES AWAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M TRYING TO THINK THINGS
THROUGH.
I KNOW SCOTT IS EAGER FOR ME TO
MAKE A DECISION, BUT I WANT TO
DO WHAT'S BEST FOR MYSELF
AND THE BABY.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
>> ABSOLUTELY NOTHING?
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS HUNGRY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU KINDLY.
>> SO IS COURT STILL LIVING
AT HOME?
HOW'S YOUR GUYS' RELATIONSHIP
DOING?
>> I WANTED HER TO MOVE IN,
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF SHE DOES.
I'M HOPING SHE DOES, JUST
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO BE
A WEEKEND DAD.
>> AND HAS SHE GIVEN YOU ANY OF
HER, LIKE, POINT OF VIEW ON THIS
WHOLE MOVING IN THING?
>> YEAH, BASICALLY,
WE'RE NOT MARRIED.
DON'T WANT TO BE TEMPTED TO HAVE
SEX AGAIN.
>> YOU'VE DECIDED YOU'RE NOT,
LIKE, HAVING SEX ANYMORE?
>> YEAH, HER WHOLE PHILO--IS,
"IF YOU CAN'T WAIT, THEN YOU
OBVIOUSLY DON'T LOVE ME."
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT EVERYBODY
HAS NEEDS...
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN YOU'RE IN
A RELATIONSHIP.
>> BELIEVE ME, I'M NOT TOO
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT EASY AT ALL.
IT'S NOT FUN AT ALL.
BUT THERE AIN'T NO CHANGING HER
MIND.
>> SO DO YOU THINK IT'S GONNA BE
HARDER IF SHE MOVES IN TO DO
YOUR ABSTINENCE?
>> DEFINITELY.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GONNA BE EASIER TO RAISE
A BABY.
THE WAY I SEE IT,
I'M JUST PAYING MY DUES.
I'M JUST GONNA WAIT IT OUT
AND HOPE THAT EVERYTHING WORKS
OUT THE WAY I'M PLANNING.
>> DO YOU PLAN ON DOING THIS
BECAUSE YOU HAVE THAT STRONG OF
FEELINGS FOR COURTNEY,
OR IS IT BECAUSE YOU HAVE THAT
STRONG OF FEELINGS TO RAISE
A FAMILY, AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO JUST BE A WEEKEND DAD?
>> WELL, IT'S 'CAUSE I LOVE
COURTNEY FOR COURTNEY.
YOU DON'T JUST GIVE UP ON
SOMETHING YOU LOVE.
AND THEN I ALSO DON'T WANT TO BE
A FAILURE OF A FATHER.
>> TODAY, SCOTT AND I HAD
A SONOGRAM, AND WE FOUND OUT
THAT OUR SON, DAYTON,
HAS A CLEFT LIP AND POSSIBLY
A CLEFT PALATE TOO.
THEY DON'T KNOW HOW BAD IT'S
GOING TO BE, BUT HE'LL
DEFINITELY HAVE TO HAVE SURGERY.
IT WAS HARD TO HOLD BACK TEARS.
WHY ARE YOU SO QUIET?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST THINK IT'S NOT GONNA BE
BAD JUST 'CAUSE IT TOOK FOUR
DOCTORS JUST TO SAY,
"ALL RIGHT, YES, HE DOES HAVE
A CLEFT PALATE."
>> BUT THEY CAN'T TELL HOW
SEVERE IT IS UNTIL HE'S BORN.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T THINK IT'LL BE BAD.
I'M LOOKING AT THE POSITIVE.
>> I'M JUST ASKING YOU TO KEEP
AN OPEN MIND.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO LOOK AT
THE NEGATIVE.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
THAT'S WHY I KEEP SAYING WE'RE
BLESSED.
BUT I'M NOT--I'M KEEPING AN OPEN
MIND, BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO
HAVE AN IMAGE ALREADY IN MY
HEAD BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO EXPECT ANYTHING.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN WORRIED ABOUT
PASSING ON MY CLEFT LIP BECAUSE
I INHERITED MINE FROM MY MOM,
AND SINCE SHE WENT THROUGH THIS
WITH ME, SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN UNDERSTAND HOW I'M
FEELING.
I FEEL LIKE A PART OF IT IS MY
FAULT FOR PASSING ON
THE CLEFT LIP.
>> I WENT THROUGH THAT.
I STILL GO THROUGH THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> SO THAT GUILT--
>> DOESN'T GO AWAY.
>> WELL, IT DOESN'T, BUT IT CAN
TEAR YOU UP, THOUGH,
IF YOU DON'T DEAL WITH IT.
I MEAN, I KIND OF WORRY ABOUT
THIS WITH YOU TOO, THAT WHEN
THE BABY'S BORN, IT'S QUITE
DIFFERENT WHEN YOU SEE THAT IN
PERSON.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE GOING THROUGH
ALL KIND OF FEELINGS WHEN THAT
BABY'S BORN, AND I THINK THE
MOST THING THAT I WANT TO GET
THROUGH TO YOU IS,
DON'T REJECT HIM.
>> OH, I WOULD NEVER.
>> YOU NEED TO BOND WITH HIM,
NOT MATTER WHAT, AND I WOULD
SUGGEST THAT YOU GUYS BE
PREPARED.
IT'S HARD BECAUSE YOU KNOW THAT
THEY'RE GONNA FIX IT...
>> MM-HMM.
>> BUT IT'S REALLY HARD TO
VISUALIZE THAT WHEN THEY'RE
BORN AND IT'S COMPLETELY OPEN.
>> RIGHT, AND THAT'S WHAT I KEEP
TELLING SCOTT, AND HE DOESN'T
BELIEVE THAT--HE'S LIKE,
"IT'S JUST A SCAR."
HE'S NOT UNDERSTANDING.
LIKE, HE THINKS THAT HE KNOWS
EXACTLY HOW HE'S GONNA COME OUT.
>> WELL, AND HE PROBABLY HAS
SOMETHING IN HIS MIND, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN, THAT, AFTER SEEING
THE ULTRASOUND.
I WOULD JUST SAY BE OPEN,
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA TREAT HIM
ANY DIFFERENT, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TREAT YOUR BABY
ANY DIFFERENT.
DON'T CRY.
DON'T GO THERE.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE SOMEBODY TIME,
AND YOU HAVE TO GIVE THEM A
CHANCE, AND SCOTT'S A GOOD KID.
BUT IT'S GONNA BE DIFFICULT.
YOU KNOW, IT MIGHT BE MORE OF
A LITTLE BIT OF A SHOCK FOR HIM,
THOUGH.
>> I STILL HAVEN'T DECIDED
WHETHER I WANT TO MOVE IN WITH
SCOTT.
AND NOW THAT WE KNOW DAYTON HAS
TO HAVE SURGERY, WE'RE PRETTY
STRESSED OUT ABOUT THE COST.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS APPLY FOR
WIC, AND THEN HOPEFULLY APPLY
FOR FOOD STAMPS.
IT'S GONNA BE ROUGH, BUT...
>> WE'RE GONNA STRUGGLE.
>> OH, YEAH, WE'RE DEFINITELY
GONNA STRUGGLE.
>> WE CAN SAVE UP FOR THAT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK WE'LL BE FINE,
HONESTLY.
ASK, AND YOU SHALL RECEIVE.
GO IN GOD'S WAY.
GOD WILL PROVIDE.
>> AMEN.
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID
IN CHURCH.
>> GOD JOB PAYING ATTENTION.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M PROUD OF YOU.
>> I'VE ALWAYS LIKED FRIED
PICKLES, BUT EVER SINCE I GOT
PREGNANT, I'VE WANTED THEM,
LIKE, EVERY SECOND.
>> THIS IS, LIKE, THE FOURTH
TIME YOU'VE MADE THEM.
>> YEAH, BUT EVERY TIME,
THEY GET BETTER AND BETTER.
LET'S EAT THESE.
THAT'S A GOOD PICKLE.
[giggles]
>> SO WHAT ELSE DO YOU GUYS HAVE
TO GET FIGURED OUT BEFORE THE
BABY COMES?
>> I HAVE TO FIND DOCTORS FOR
HIS SURGERY.
I HAVE TO FIND OUT INSURANCE
STUFF.
I HAVE TO...UGH.
FREAKING ME OUT, MAN.
>> IT'S A LOT.
ARE YOU DOING THE SURGERY RIGHT
AFTER HE'S BORN, OR ARE YOU
GONNA WAIT?
>> WE DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH THE
SURGERY'S GONNA BE.
>> IT'S WORTH IT, YOU KNOW?
>> I'M JUST NERVOUS FOR HIM TO
GET, YOU KNOW, BULLIED A LITTLE
BIT.
>> HE'S JUST GONNA HAVE
A LITTLE SCAR.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S JUST GONNA
BE A SCAR.
IT'S GONNA BE--A CLEFT LIP
IS JUST, LIKE--IT GOES UP.
I'M SCARED THAT YOU'RE--
HE'S GONNA COME OUT, AND YOU'RE
GONNA BE LIKE, "OH, THAT'S A
LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN I THOUGHT
IT WAS GONNA BE."
>> IT JUST ADDS CHARACTER.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER WHEN
COURTNEY WAS BORN.
YOU WENT THROUGH A LOT.
>> I FEEL AWKWARD WHEN EVERYBODY
TAKES OUT THEIR BABY PICTURES,
AND I'M LIKE, "CRAP, I HOPE THEY
DON'T ASK ME TO TAKE OUT MY BABY
PICTURE, BECAUSE ALL THESE
PEOPLE LOOK SO CUTE WITH THEIR
FULL LIP.
>> YOU WERE CUTE TOO.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
>> AND THEN I TAKE MINE OUT,
AND I'M LIKE--HAVE CLEFT LIP,
AND IT'S, LIKE, SAD.
>> DO YOU STILL STRUGGLE
WITH SELF-IMAGE?
>> SOMETIMES.
LIKE, SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE--
IF THEY'RE JUST STARING AT ME,
I'M LIKE, "ARE THEY STARING AT
MY CLEFT LIP?"
THEN I'LL BE LIKE--LIKE, I DON'T
WANT TO BLURT OUT, LIKE,
"I HAVE A CLEFT LIP."
'CAUSE THEY'LL BE LIKE,
"I WAS JUST LOOKING AT YOUR
HAIR.
LIKE, I WAS..."
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE DON'T MAKE
EYE CONTACT WITH ME.
I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE ARE LOOKING
AT MY CLEFT LIP ALL THE TIME.
>> IT'S JUST NOT THAT BAD.
IT'S A THING IN THE PAST.
>> 'CAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE IT.
YOU REMEMBER WHEN I WOULD CRY
AND--
>> YOU WOULDN'T EVEN LOOK IN THE
MIRROR, AND...
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S HARD.
I DON'T LIKE FEELING DIFFERENT
FROM PEOPLE.
>> I THINK YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
>> I'M HERE.
>> 'SUP, BRO?
>> HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
>> IT WAS ALL RIGHT.
IT WAS A LITTLE COLD OUT.
>> SO I WAS THINKING
I COULD MOVE OVER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BUT I THINK THAT WE SHOULD
HAVE SEPARATE ROOMS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> JUST SO WE'RE NOT TEMPTED.
>> 'KAY.
>> YEAH.
>> COOL.
>> YEAH, KIND OF.
>> OKAY.
DO YOU GET WHY I'M DOING THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S NOT 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
TO SLEEP IN THE SAME ROOM
AS YOU.
IT'S BECAUSE I WANT TO SLEEP IN
THE SAME ROOM WITH YOU TOO MUCH.
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU MAD AT ME FOR IT?
>> [sighs]
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> YOU'RE JUST SEXUALLY
FRUSTRATED.
>> IT'S LIKE HAVING SOMETHING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU BUT IN
THE NEXT ROOM,
AND YOU CAN'T GET TO IT.
>> WELL, YEAH, AND I THINK,
LIKE, YOU WOULD JUST GET
FRUSTRATED IF I'M SLEEPING WITH
YOU AND NOT DOING ANYTHING
WITH YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, WE CAN STILL CUDDLE.
BUT NOT DO THE DO.
WHENEVER YOU GET TEMPTED,
GO OUTSIDE AND GO FOR A RIDE IN
YOUR CAR, OR I'LL JUST GO
OUTSIDE FOR A SECOND.
>> I'M GLAD THAT YOU MADE THIS
DECISION NOW RATHER THAN AFTER
WE HAD THE BABY, 'CAUSE THEN WE
WOULD'VE HAD TO TAKE CARE OF THE
BABY AND MOVE AND GO TO WORK.
>> WELL, DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA BE HAPPIER?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M HAPPY.
MY DAD SUPPORTS MY DECISION,
AND TODAY HE'S HELPING US MOVE.
WATCH OUT.
>> WHERE DO YOU WANT THIS,
COURT?
>> PUT IT IN THERE.
>> COOL SWING.
[laughs]
>> THANK YOU.
>> OH, I LOVE YOU.
[toothbrush buzzing]
>> ALL RIGHT, ARE YOU GONNA COME
CUDDLE WITH ME?
>> I'M PRETTY TIRED.
>> LOVE YOU.
NIGHT.
>> GOOD NIGHT.
[chime dings]
[banging]
>> I'M HERE.
>> HEY, COURT.
>> DOING DISHES FOR THE FIRST
TIME EVER?
>> OH, GOSH, THERE'S, LIKE,
FIVE OF THEM IN THERE.
>> DO YOU NEED HELP?
>> NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> LIVING WITH SCOTT IS REALLY
GREAT SO FAR.
I'M DUE IN A WEEK,
SO I'M TRYING NOT TO WORRY ABOUT
DAYTON'S CLEFT LIP,
AND I HAVE TO FINISH MY FIRST
SEMESTER OF SENIOR YEAR BEFORE
HE'S BORN.
>> CINNAMON ROLL?
>> YES, PLEASE.
>> THERE YOU ARE.
>> THAT LOOKS DELICIOUS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
>> STANDING UP FOR, LIKE,
TEN MINUTES HURTS MY BACK.
>> IT'S GETTING SO CLOSE.
IT COULD PRETTY MUCH HAPPEN ANY
TIME NOW, COULDN'T IT?
>> MM-HMM.
SO I DECIDED TO MOVE IN WITH
SCOTT.
>> YAY.
>> BUT WE'RE NOT SLEEPING IN THE
SAME ROOM, 'CAUSE SLEEPING IN
THE SAME BED, IT'S JUST, LIKE--
LIKE A CALL FOR, LIKE, SEX.
>> I FEEL LIKE SEX CAN HAPPEN
ANYWHERE, NOT JUST IN A BED.
>> I KNOW, BUT I MEAN, YOU'RE
LAYING THERE, ALL SEX DEPRIVED.
>> YOU LAY ON THE COUCH AND
CUDDLE ALL SEX DEPRIVED
AS WELL.
>> [laughs]
I KNOW, BUT I THINK IT WILL
ELIMINATE SOME.
>> HAVE YOU GUYS TALKED ABOUT
HOW LONG YOU'RE GONNA WAIT TILL
YOU GET MARRIED?
>> NO.
>> HONESTLY, DO YOU THINK
IT'LL BE SOON?
>> UM...
>> DO YOU THINK IT'LL BE IN,
LIKE, A YEAR OR TWO?
>> YEAH, I THINK IN A YEAR.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO GET
MARRIED YOUNG.
>> NOW, DO YOU THINK THAT HE
MIGHT JUST WANT TO GET MARRIED
TO HAVE SEX?
>> HE WOULDN'T WANT TO GET
MARRIED FOR THE WRONG
INTENTIONS.
I DON'T THINK.
AND IF HE WANTED TO HAVE SEX
REALLY BAD, HE WOULD BREAK UP
WITH ME AND GO--
>> NO, HE WOULDN'T.
HE'S HAVING A BABY WITH YOU.
>> HE WOULDN'T BE WITH ME
JUST FOR A BABY.
>> YOU KNOW HOW YOU GUYS HAVE
SEPARATE ROOMS?
HOW IS SCOTT GONNA WAKE UP IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND TAKE TURNS WITH YOU?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
BEFORE SCOTT AND I COULD TALK
ABOUT OUR PLAN, I STARTED HAVING
REALLY PAINFUL CONTRACTIONS.
I WASN'T SURE IF I SHOULD GO TO
THE HOSPITAL, SO I CALLED MY
DAD, AND HE CAME RIGHT OVER.
>> YOU'RE GETTING CLOSE, GIRL.
ALMOST TIME.
MR. DAYTON WANTS OUT.
HE DON'T WANT TO PLAY AROUND
IN THERE ANYMORE.
>> I'M SCARED FOR THE EPIDURAL.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE IT.
>> BUT I WANT IT.
>> OWIE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> HEY, WE'RE HEADED TO THE
HOSPITAL.
HER CONTRACTIONS ARE A MINUTE
AND A HALF APART.
>> OWIE.
OW.
THE NURSES MEASURED ME AT
4 CENTIMETERS AND ADMITTED ME
RIGHT AWAY.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'LL HELP A TON.
IN AND OUT.
>> I GOT AN EPIDURAL, BUT I WAS
STILL IN A LOT OF PAIN.
[moaning]
I FEEL LIKE PUSHING.
>> I KNOW.
JUST BREATHE.
>> [moans]
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> A LITTLE NERVOUS.
>> I'VE BEEN A BASKET CASE
THE LAST WEEK.
>> I'M GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
KEEP BREATHING.
>> [moans]
>> KEEP BREATHING.
KEEP BREATHING.
[Dayton crying]
>> HEY, IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
>> HEY, MAMA.
>> [laughs]
>> WE'RE PARENTS.
>> NO.
[chime dings]
>> I'M SO EXCITED THAT DAYTON IS
HERE AND THAT SCOTT IS SO
ACCEPTING OF HIS CLEFT LIP.
>> I THINK HE'S PERFECT.
>> IT'S REALLY MINOR, AND WE'RE
HOPING HE'LL ONLY NEED ONE
SURGERY.
HIS LIP IS BARELY...
>> NOTICEABLE.
>> I KNOW.
>> LITTLE ADORABLE DAYTON.
>> OKAY, WE'RE ALL READY FOR THE
BATH WHENEVER YOU ARE.
>> OH, OKAY.
SO JUST PUT HIM ON?
>> YEAH.
>> UH-OH, IT'S COLD.
[Dayton crying]
OH, IT'S COLD.
>> YEAH, JUST...
>> OH...
>> PICK HIM UP.
RUB IT ALL OVER.
OH...
HE'LL BEGIN TO LOVE HIS LITTLE
BATH.
ALL NICE AND RINSED, AND THEN
YOU JUST CUDDLE HIM IN HIS
LITTLE TOWEL.
JUST LIKE THAT.
THERE YOU GO.
SWADDLE HIM JUST LIKE THAT.
TAKE THAT OUT OF THE WATER.
>> I GOT HIM.
>> THERE YOU GO.
AND THEN YOU'LL WANT TO DRY HIM
OFF REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> THE FIRST ONE'S ALWAYS
THE WORST.
>> CAN YOU GET ME A ONSIE?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, IT'S OKAY.
HE JUST POOPED.
OH.
CAN SOMEBODY HELP ME?
>> YEAH.
>> COVER HIM.
[Dayton crying]
>> SCOTT WENT BACK TO WORK,
SO HE ONLY SEES ME AND DAYTON
AT NIGHT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OH...
I HAVE TO FEED HIM.
CAN YOU GET ME A BLANKET?
>> OH, NO "PLEASE"?
>> PLEASE?
CAN YOU GET ME SOME WATER?
I GET SO THIRSTY WHEN I FEED
HIM.
>> ANYTHING ELSE YOU WOULD LIKE?
>> FOR YOU TO CHANGE HIM.
>> I SUPPLY FOR THE HOUSE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> MM-HMM.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
>> HELP WITH DAYTON WOULD BE
LOVELY.
>> MY FOUR DIAPERS A WEEK SHOULD
BE VALUED.
>> THAT'S A GOOD WEEK IF YOU
CHANGE FOUR DIAPERS.
>> HEY, I'LL CHANGE NONE THEN.
>> TODAY MY PARENTS ARE TAKING
ME AND SCOTT TO MEET WITH
DR. FOLK, WHO'S GOING TO DO
DAYTON'S SURGERY.
SHE'S DONE A FEW OF MY
SURGERIES, SO I FEEL REALLY
COMFORTABLE WITH HER.
>> OH, WOW!
[laughs]
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HEY, BABY.
DID ANYONE LOOK INSIDE TO SEE IF
HE HAD A SUBMUCOUS CLEFT PALATE?
>> THEY DID, BUT NOT, LIKE,
IN DEPTH.
>> LET'S JUST GO AHEAD
AND TAKE THIS OUT.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I'LL TRY NOT TO MAKE YOU
TOO MAD.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
THIS STINKS.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, SO FAR,
THAT LOOKS ACTUALLY REALLY GOOD,
WHAT I CAN SEE.
WHEN HE'S ASLEEP IN SURGERY,
I'LL TAKE A LITTLE BETTER LOOK.
IF THE LIP IS THIS MILD,
I WOULD EXPECT ONE SURGERY.
>> HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK WE'LL
PAY ACTUALLY OUT-OF-POCKET?
>> UNFORTUNATELY, WE DON'T KNOW.
YOU'LL GET A HOSPITAL BILL
AND AN ANESTHESIOLOGIST BILL,
AND THEN OUR BILL.
>> ANY OTHER QUESTIONS?
>> WILL HIS MUSTACHE
STILL GROW NORMAL?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> 'CAUSE, LIKE, HE'LL HAVE,
LIKE, A LITTLE SCAR.
>> YEAH.
[laughs]
>> ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GO FEED
THIS MAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S SO GOOD SEEING YOU GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, DR. FOLK.
>> WE SCHEDULED THE SURGERY FOR
AUGUST, WHEN DAYTON IS EIGHT
MONTHS OLD, AND IT SUCKS THAT WE
CAN'T FIND OUT THE TOTAL PRICE
UNTIL AFTERWARDS.
ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT MONEY?
>> RIGHT NOW, I HAVE, LIKE,
$140-SOMETHING SAVED UP.
>> WE BETTER START SAVING.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> IT'S JUST, HE'S SO CUTE.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO CHANGE.
HE'S JUST SO PERFECT.
>> HE'LL STILL BE PERFECT.
IT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE WHO HE IS.
HOW'S THE LIVING RELATIONSHIP
GOING?
>> SHE ALWAYS PLAYS THE "HOW
MANY DIAPERS HAVE YOU CHANGED
TODAY?"
[laughter]
IT'S LIKE...
>> THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T
CHANGE A DIAPER IN TWO DAYS.
>> [laughs]
>> DO YOU REALLY WANT TO?
>> YOU COME OVER AND HELP ME.
>> SHE GETS MAD AT ME, AND IT'S
LIKE--IT'S 3:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> YEAH, BUT SHE'S GOT TO DO IT
AT 3:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> IF YOU CAN JUST REMEMBER THAT
THIS IS NOT FOREVER.
IT'S TEMPORARY, IT'S HARD,
BUT YOU GUYS WILL GET THROUGH
IT, INSTEAD OF IT BUILDING UP
AND BUILDING UP, AND THEN YOU'RE
JUST LIKE...
>> IT'S EASY TO THINK SOMETIMES,
"OH, I'LL GO TO WORK, AND SHE'S
JUST LAYING AROUND ALL DAY AND
NOT DOING ANYTHING."
AND THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S--
>> OR VICE VERSA.
>> THAT'S NOT--
>> HE JUST GOES TO WORK,
BUT HE DOESN'T HELP AT HOME.
>> BE GOOD FOR MAMA TODAY WHILE
DADDY'S AT WORK, 'KAY?
[Dayton farts]
EW!
DAYTON, THAT IS NASTY.
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES I BRING
IT UP WITH SCOTT, HE STILL
REFUSES TO HELP ME.
"CHANGE ME."
>> I DO AN 8:00 TO 5:00, COURT.
>> I DO A 24/7.
>> I DO LABOR WORK ALL DAY.
I GOT TO GO TO BED, 'CAUSE I GOT
TO GET UP EARLY.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> GOOD NIGHT.
>> SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[Dayton crying]
>> IT'S OKAY.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
MY SECOND SEMESTER OF SENIOR
YEAR STARTS TODAY, BUT IT'S
REALLY HARD TO DO SCHOOLWORK
WHEN I'M TAKING CARE OF DAYTON.
I HAVE TO DO MY HOMEWORK,
PUMPKIN.
IT'S OKAY.
OH...
AND I FEEL LIKE I HAVEN'T SPENT
ANY TIME WITH SCOTT.
YOU SLEEPING?
>> NO.
TRYING.
>> JUST CAME IN TO SAY GOOD
NIGHT.
>> YOU SHOULD JUST STAY IN HERE
WITH ME TONIGHT.
>> YEAH?
YEAH?
>> YEAH.
>> [chuckles]
DON'T.
I'M GONNA GO TO SLEEP IN MY
ROOM.
>> WHY'D YOU LEAVE?
>> 'CAUSE YOU WERE GETTING
A LITTLE TOO TOUCHY-FEELY.
IS IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR YOU TO LAY
IN BED WITH ME WITHOUT DOING
ANYTHING?
>> DO YOU GET HOW HARD THIS IS
FOR ME?
>> I GET THAT IT'S TEMPTING.
IT'S JUST--I WISH THAT YOU COULD
JUST RESPECT ME A LITTLE MORE
UNTIL WE'RE MARRIED.
>> IT'S A LOT HARDER FOR A GUY
'CAUSE YOU SEE HOW MUCH I GET
TEMPTED, BUT IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU'RE NEVER TEMPTED.
>> JUST PRAY WHEN YOU GET
TEMPTED.
IT MIGHT HELP YOU.
>> AND IT'S HARD.
>> I KNOW IT'S HARD.
THAT'S WHY MAKES IT SO SPECIAL,
THOUGH.
AND THIS IS REALLY HARD,
SO I KNOW WE'LL BE ABLE TO GET
THROUGH HARD TIMES.
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE I MOVED IN HERE, DID
YOU THINK THAT I WOULD GIVE IN?
>> NO.
I KNEW THERE MIGHT BE TIMES,
BUT I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D JUST BE
LIKE, "OH, I'M MOVING IN.
LET'S GO CRAZY."
>> HAVE I DISAPPOINTED YOU WITH
THERE NOT BEING TIMES?
>> A LITTLE BIT.
>> I CAN TELL THAT EVER SINCE WE
STOPPED THAT YOU GET REALLY
FRUSTRATED VERY, VERY, VERY
EASILY.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S THE NEGATIVE SIDE.
I'M JUST...EDGY ALL THE TIME....
WITH NO WAY TO RELIEVE IT.
>> THAT'S NOT THE ONLY WAY TO
RELIEVE BEING STRESSED OUT.
>> JUST ADDS TENSION.
>> I THINK YOU CAN LAST UNTIL
WE'RE MARRIED.
>> EVERY MAN HAS A BREAKING
POINT.
>> CAN YOU CHANGE HIM?
>> DO YOU NEED ME TO?
IF YOU'RE INCAPABLE, I CAN.
IF YOU'RE CAPABLE--
>> HEY, I DID THE LAUNDRY.
I DID LAUNDRY TODAY.
I'M STILL NOT GETTING THE HELP
I NEED FROM SCOTT, AND IT SEEMS
LIKE ALL WE DO IS ARGUE.
AND AFTER HE GETS HOME FROM
WORK, HE KEEPS HIS DISTANCE.
[Dayton crying]
IT'S PRETTY DEPRESSING SITTING
AROUND THE HOUSE.
SO TODAY, I'M GETTING OUT FOR
A BIT.
>> COURTNEY, I MISSED YOU
SO MUCH.
>> I KNOW.
>> HE'S GETTING SO BIG.
>> IT SUCKS NOT HAVING YOU IN
SCHOOL WITH ME EVERY DAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> I'M ALONE IN JOURNALISM NOW.
>> THE HARDEST THING ABOUT BEING
A MOM IS NOT REALLY DOING
ANYTHING.
LIKE, I'M NOT IN SCHOOL.
I DON'T REALLY HANG OUT WITH
FRIENDS A LOT.
AND, LIKE, I DON'T REALLY HAVE
A SOCIAL LIFE AT ALL.
>> OH, HE'S SO CUTE.
[laughs]
>> NO MORE BEING A TEENAGER.
WE USED TO JUST CHILL AT YOUR
HOUSE ALL THE TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> LISTEN TO MUSIC.
>> HAD SLEEPOVERS ALL THE TIME.
>> I KNOW.
>> HERE IS YOUR ENCHILADA
WITH NO PICO AND NO SOUR CREAM.
>> THANK YOU.
I LOVE BEING A MOM, BUT IT'S
SUPER HARD.
HARDER THAN IT LOOKS.
LIKE, SCOTT, HE'LL CHANGE HIM,
LIKE, ONCE OR TWICE A WEEK,
AND HE CAN'T GET UP WITH HIM IN
THE NIGHT BECAUSE I HAVE TO FEED
HIM, WHICH MAKES IT SUPER
STRESSFUL, BECAUSE I WAKE UP
WITH HIM, FEED HIM, CHANGE HIM,
TRY AND PUT HIM BACK TO BED.
IT'S STRESSFUL.
>> SO YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN
FIGHTING A LOT?
>> KIND OF.
LIKE, EVERY OTHER DAY.
JUST ABOUT STUPID THINGS TOO.
IT'S, LIKE, NOTHING ABOUT--
NOTHING BIG.
LIKE, I THINK SCOTT SHOULD HELP
MORE WITH DAYTON, AND IT'S JUST
CAUSING, LIKE, US TO FIGHT MORE.
>> DO YOU GUYS, LIKE, STILL
SPEND TIME TOGETHER,
JUST YOU GUYS?
>> MM-MM.
WE MAINLY HAVE DAYTON
ALL THE TIME.
WHEN SCOTT GETS HOME, HE TAKES
A SHOWER, EATS, AND THEN CHILLS
FOR A LITTLE BIT,
THEN GOES TO BED.
>> THAT SUCKS.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE DON'T REALLY GO OUT ON DATES.
WE LOST A LITTLE AFFECTION.
I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT, LIKE,
SEXUAL AFFECTION.
I'M TALKING, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
JUST HUGGING AND KISSING AND
HOLDING HANDS, AND IT KIND OF
FEELS LIKE WE'RE ROOMMATES NOW,
NOT BOYFRIEND AND GIRLFRIEND.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, I THINK THAT'S THE
HARDEST THING ABOUT HAVING
A BABY, IS KEEPING YOUR
RELATIONSHIP GOOD.
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW, HE DOESN'T
SEEM VERY HAPPY.
SCOTT IS OFF TODAY, SO I ASKED
HIM TO WATCH DAYTON FOR A LITTLE
BIT WHILE I TAKE A NAP.
[Dayton crying]
I NEED MORE HELP WITH DAYTON.
I WANT YOU TO HOLD HIM.
>> YOU'RE MAKING IT SEEM LIKE
I NEVER HOLD HIM.
WHY WOULDN'T I HOLD HIM?
>> SCOTT, HOW LONG DID YOU GO
WITHOUT HOLDING HIM?
>> FOUR DAYS.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
>> IT'S A HUGE DEAL.
FOUR DAYS WITHOUT HOLDING YOUR
SON.
AND NOT JUST NOT CHANGING HIS
DIAPER OR ANYTHING.
HOLDING HIM.
I GET IF--
>> A MAN'S GOT TO WORK.
A MAN'S GOT TO REST.
>> IT DOESN'T GIVE YOU AN EXCUSE
NOT TO HOLD HIM.
>> I DO.
I JUST DON'T DO IT LIKE YOU.
I DON'T SMOTHER HIM.
>> THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
YOU'RE HIS DAD.
>> I'M ON MY FEET ALL DAY WITH
30-POUND TOOL BAGS, CLIMBING UP
AND DOWN LADDERS AND PULLING
WIRE AND BENDING PIPE.
WHEN I COME HOME, I JUST WANT TO
GET OFF MY FEET.
I WANT TO SIT DOWN AND JUST
RELAX FOR ONCE.
>> OKAY.
>> DO YOU NOT SEE WHERE I'M
COMING FROM?
>> SCOTT, I'M JUST SAYING,
DAYTON NEEDS TO BOND WITH HIS
DAD.
>> AND HE'S GETTING IT.
HE DOESN'T NEED TO BE A LITTLE
GIRL AND BE HELD EVERY SECOND
OF EVERY DAY.
HE NEEDS TO LEARN THAT HE'S
GONNA HAVE TO BE ON HIS OWN.
I'M GONNA MAKE HIM INDEPENDENT.
>> HE'S A BABY.
>> IT STARTS FROM BIRTH.
DON'T GET MAD.
I KNOW YOU'RE GETTING MAD.
>> IT'S JUST 'CAUSE YOU DON'T
RECOGNIZE ANYTHING THAT I DO
FOR YOU.
>> I DO RECOGNIZE.
I DO RECOGNIZE THAT YOU HOLD
DAYTON ALL THE TIME.
I DO RECOGNIZE THAT YOU TAKE
CARE OF DAYTON ALL THE TIME,
BUT THAT'S YOUR JOB.
THAT IS A MOTHER'S JOB.
NOT JUST A MOTHER.
A STAY-AT-HOME MOTHER'S JOB.
IT'S YOUR JOB.
>> WELL, USUALLY DADS HELP.
USUALLY DADS HELP.
>> DO I NOT SUPPLY?
>> YOU DO.
>> DO I NOT SUPPLY ENOUGH?
DO I NOT HELP ENOUGH
WITH EVERYTHING?
WE LIVE; WE EAT; WE DRIVE;
WE DO.
I PAY FOR IT.
>> YOU CAN STILL HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR SON.
>> EVERYTHING IS 'CAUSE OF ME.
ME.
IT'S PISSING ME OFF.
I'M GETTING IN A BAD MOOD NOW.
HONESTLY.
DO YOU NOT SEE THAT I DO STUFF?
>> HOW MANY TIMES DO I TELL YOU
THAT I DO?
>> THEN WHY ARE YOU ASKING FOR
MORE?
I GIVE YOU $100,
AND YOU WANT $200.
I GIVE YOU A FOOT, YOU TAKE TWO.
YOU ALWAYS WANT MORE.
BEEN PISSING ME OFF, HONESTLY.
[Dayton crying]
>> I'M GONNA PUT HIM IN HIS
CRIB.
[Dayton crying]
>> ARE YOU TRYING TO PISS ME
OFF?
>> NO, I'M JUST SAYING.
YOU DON'T REALIZE WHAT I DO
FOR YOU.
YOU DON'T.
>> IT'S BEEN HOW LONG NOW
WITHOUT SEX?
>> SEX ISN'T THE ONLY THING
GOING WRONG IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> NO, BUT IT'S A MAJOR THING.
>> NOT REALLY.
>> NOT TO YOU.
>> YOU'RE PISSING ME OFF, SCOTT.
STOP.
JUST STOP.
>> IS THIS NOT WHAT YOU'VE SAID?
>> YOU'RE RIDICULOUS.
I'M DONE.
I AM DONE.
>> PEACE OUT.
[door slams]
I'M [bleep] DONE.
[bleep] HAD IT, DUDE.
[Dayton crying]
>> * BUT IN YOUR MIND
* THE WAR CAN STILL BE WON
[tires screech]
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
AFTER OUR BIG FIGHT, I WENT TO
STAY WITH MY DAD FOR A FEW DAYS,
AND SCOTT'S COMING OVER TO TALK
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
HE MIGHT BE HUNGRY.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
>> HAS IT?
>> YEAH.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN AWAY FROM ME
LONG ENOUGH?
>> YEAH.
DID YOU GET ENOUGH SPACE
FROM ME?
>> UH...
>> I THINK I HAVE TO FEED HIM.
>> THERE'S SO MANY THINGS THAT
MAKE US BICKER OR THAT HE MAKES
US BICKER FOR.
>> HE DOESN'T MAKE US DO
ANYTHING.
HE'S A GOOD BABY.
>> I'M NOT SAYING HIM.
LIKE, HE'S NOT SITTING THERE
MAKING US, BUT WHEN HE WON'T
STOP CRYING
AND I GET FRUSTRATED SO THEN
YOU GET FRUSTRATED WITH ME
'CAUSE I'M FRUSTRATED AT HIM,
AND THEN WE GET IN AN ARGUMENT
BECAUSE OF IT,
OR BECAUSE I DON'T CHANGE HIS
DIAPERS...
I'M SAYING IT ADDS STRESS ON THE
RELATIONSHIP.
MONEY, SURGERY, TIME,
CRYING, SLEEP.
THE WHOLE ABSTINENT THING.
>> WELL, I JUST DON'T WANT TO
GET MARRIED--RUSH INTO GETTING
MARRIED JUST SO WE CAN HAVE SEX.
>> IT'S HARD BECAUSE I FEEL SO
CLOSE TO YOU, BUT WE CAN'T GET
THAT CLOSE.
I FEEL STUCK IN THE WHOLE THING
'CAUSE I CAN'T CHANGE YOU.
>> I MEAN, SEX ISN'T THE ONLY
KIND OF INTIMACY THAT WE CAN
HAVE, YOU KNOW?
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
BUT IT'S A BIG ONE.
>> IF WE DIDN'T HAVE DAYTON AND
I WANTED TO BE ABSTINENT,
WOULD YOU STICK WITH ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW, HONESTLY.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IF WE DIDN'T HAVE DAYTON--
>> I CAN'T PREDICT ANYTHING.
MAYBE WE WOULDN'T BE.
I'M JUST SAYING.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S DEPRESSING.
IT MAKES ME THINK THAT YOU'RE
JUST WITH ME 'CAUSE OF DAYTON.
>> * THERE'S A MYSTERY *
* I'M CHASING DOWN *
* I'M NOT SURE WHAT I BELIEVE *
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> * I MAY NEVER KNOW
* NEVER KNOW
>> ONCE I GOT PREGNANT,
I DIDN'T HAVE ANYBODY ELSE THAT
I FELT I COULD TURN TO,
SO I JUST TURNED TO GOD,
AND HE REALLY HELPED ME
THROUGH IT.
"WHEN YOU BELIEVE IN GOD,
YOU THROW OFF YOUR OLD SINFUL
NATURE AND YOUR FORMER WAY
OF LIFE."
IT'S SCARY TO THINK THAT I COULD
POSSIBLY BE A SINGLE MOM, BUT
WITH SEX, I'M NOT GONNA GIVE IN
TO IT BECAUSE I'M VERY FIRM IN
WHAT I BELIEVE NOW.
I MEAN, IT STRENGTHENS MY
RELATIONSHIP WITH GOD, WHICH IS
MY NUMBER ONE PRIORITY.
>> HOW ARE THE SEPARATE ROOMS
GOING?
>> SCOTT GETS A LITTLE
FRUSTRATED SOMETIMES.
OH.
IT'S OKAY.
HE'S PROBABLY HOT.
IN THREE MONTHS, DAYTON'S GONNA
HAVE TO GET HIS SURGERY.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
HIM GOING UNDER ANESTHESIA,
AND I'M GONNA HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT HOW HIS LIP IS GONNA COME
TOGETHER, AND IT'S JUST GONNA BE
HARD.
>> YOU GIVE HIM ALL THAT
AT ONCE?
>> YEAH.
>> AH, HE LOVES IT.
>> I STILL HAVE TO FINISH HIGH
SCHOOL, BUT IT CAN BE REALLY
DIFFICULT WHEN YOU HAVE A CRYING
BABY.
[Dayton crying]
I HAVE TO FINISH THIS
ASSIGNMENT, AND THEN I'LL FEED
YOU.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FUTURE
HOLDS FOR SCOTT AND I
AND DAYTON.
I'VE REALIZED THAT I NEED TO
FOCUS ON MYSELF.
I CAN'T MAKE YOU CHANGE.
YOU HAVE TO DO THAT ON YOUR OWN.
WHEN I GOT PREGNANT, I THOUGHT
THAT MAYBE IT WOULD BRING US
CLOSER IN A WAY, BUT IT'S JUST
OUR TWO DIFFERENT VIEWS PULLED
US APART.
YOU CAN STICK TO FOUR DIAPERS
A WEEK IF YOU TAKE OUT ALL OF
HIS DIAPERS.
BUT I CAN'T PICTURE MY FUTURE
WITHOUT SCOTT.
I DON'T WANT TO PICTURE MY
FUTURE WITHOUT SCOTT.
[chime dings]
>> * HALLELUJAH
* I'M COMING HOME TO YOU *
>> WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
YOU DID TELL ME WE WERE GONNA DO
THIS TOGETHER, AND I FEEL LIKE
I'M DOING IT WITHOUT YOU BECAUSE
OF YOUR DRINKING.
I'M TIRED OF SEEING MY MOM
STRUGGLE.
[siren wails]
>> MOVE IT!
LET'S GO!
>> MOM, THEY'RE LOOKING FOR YOU.
>> HE NEEDS TO LEAVE.