When you're 16
and pregnant life
becomes all about sacrifice.
Sacrificing education,
friendships and
even your childhood.
This season we follow
the ups and downs
of nine pregnant teens.
We attended weddings,
witnessed breakups
and watched nine
lives transformed
each in nine short months.
Were those sacrifices worth it?
Where do these teen
moms stand today?
And who is still
standing beside them?
Well you're about to find out.
This is the 16 and
Pregnant finale special
"Life After Labor."
♪♪
[audience cheer and applaud]
Thank you guys, hi.
I'm Dr. Drew and I'd
like to say hello
to our nine moms
here, welcome ladies.
They come from
across the country
but today they're here together
in one place for
the very first time.
We've got Megan, Christinna,
Aubrey, Ashley,
Markai, Kayla, Emily,
Felicia and finally Brooke.
Welcome to the show and
welcome you all as well.
Now certain themes kept creeping
into the surface of this season.
For instance, finishing high
school, fights with parents,
surprise surprise,
money issues, shocking,
and of course drama with
the babies' fathers.
Today we'll go deep
inside every story
to find out which couples
are trying to make it work
and which ones are thinking
of going their separate ways.
You might be surprised
by what you see.
We'll talk to the main
supporters who are here today
and of course we'll get
to see the babies as well.
But in case you forgot how
they came into this world
here's a quick recap of this
seasons 16 and Pregnant.
♪♪
[Mom] What are you going
to do for homecoming?
I bought a maternity
dress already.
[Family] Ah cute, woooo.
I was hoping I was
just gonna gain belly
not gain all that.
I had so much
planned for myself,
I mean I'm still going
to do what I planned.
We've had dads pass out.
[Emily] Please don't.
We got him.
Oh my goodness.
I want nothing more
than to have her do well.
Statistics are against her.
[Ashley] My aunt and uncle
want to adopt the baby.
[Mom] The more time that
you spend with the baby
the more you're going to bond.
Let's just get
it over with then.
[Mom] I feel we should
still have a DNA test,
'cause if it aint
yours there's going
to be some rumble in the jungle.
Why are you acting
like this Cody?
I'm saying that I
need to graduate.
You know I've been
emotional all day today
and now you're just
making it worse.
Are you--
[Boyfriend] No,
let me the fuck go.
I hate you, oooo I hate you.
[Boyfriend]
You've got to stop.
I hate you.
I think that you
can have it all.
My life's not going to stop
just because I'm having a baby
and everyone seems
to think that.
Well there you go.
How's it feel to see
all that on television?
[girls laugh]
Okay how does it feel to
see that blowup on TV?
I don't know, it's
surprising actually to me.
Is it painful or
you're embarrassed?
Both.
[Dr. Drew] Both.
Yeah.
We'll talk more about that.
All right we'll have a
very touching reunion later
between Ashley and
her baby Callie
and Callie's adoptive parents
who are family
members of Ashley's.
Also I'll be spending quality
time with the other moms
as well as the babies' fathers.
Coming up is our first
mom of the day, Kayla.
Stay tuned now
we'll be right back.
[audience applause]
♪♪
[Dr. Drew] Did you ever cheat?
Mmmm, once.
[Dr. Drew] How is it
trying to raise a baby
without a dad around?
It just sucks.
[Dr. Drew] It
sucks doing it alone?
Yeah.
You know I've been staying
by myself since I was 15,
I decided to do my own life
so that's what I'm
doing, you know.
It's just not easy.
[Dr. Drew] What's the
matter with you being close?
I'm scared I might
get hurt again.
Right.
I've been hurt too many
times from Guy, I don't want
to take that anymore.
[Dr. Drew] I know.
Can't look at
any woman anymore.
[guys laugh]
Oh no, you can look
just don't touch.
[guys laugh]
When was the last
time you saw Callie?
Two months.
Lets bring them out right now.
[audience applause]
Welcome back to
Life After Labor,
the 16 and Pregnant
finale special.
I'm Dr. Drew.
Now, the fact is that one out
of every six girls in America
will become a teen mom, amazing.
One of these teen
moms is with us today.
Kayla, how are you?
Good.
Are you surprised that
so many young people
end up in your position?
Yeah, sort of.
It's surprising?
You didn't expect to be here?
No, I was one of those that
thought it would never be me.
Never be me.
Well before we dive
into more questions,
here is Kayla's story.
I reckon you're excited
about having a little boy.
I'm really thrilled
that I have my boy.
What are your plans?
Because I feel real strong
about not moving in together
until you're married.
Kayla, will you marry me?
Yeah.
Okay, we're going
to the hospital now.
♪♪
[baby crying]
I just don't feel
like anybody's good
enough to watch him.
I wanna move in this
house really soon.
This is a big decision.
I mean we've got a
lot to think about.
It's like a big step that
we're not ready for yet.
I wanna be your husband
and I want to provide
for you and Ryland.
I don't wanna be
getting married.
I've had to grow up so fast.
And you've got to do all
these things you wanted to do,
I didn't and I'm
still a teenager.
Okay Kayla, let's
get right to it.
What's the relationship
status with JR?
We're still engaged.
What's holding you back?
We both have jealousy issues
and like he looked at a
couple other girls' pictures
on the internet, and then he
went and lied to me about it.
And I was like, "If
you're gonna lie to me
"about the small stuff,
"then you're not gonna
tell me the truth
"about the big stuff."
Were you searching around
on his phone or something
or his computer history?
I was on his phone and I
don't know how to work it.
So I was typing in something
and then the girl's
name popped up.
Then I started snooping.
And this is the reason
or is it the fact that
you're having difficulty
leaving home?
I make sure both.
Like I realized that,
I mean I took mine and my
mom's relationship for granted
and now, being pregnant,
me and her got a lot closer
and I just want
more of that time.
She's a special person,
I don't know how I would've
got through this without her.
Oh.
It's not easy.
All right, let's
bring JR out shall we?
[audience applause]
How are you sir, welcome.
Fine, thank you.
Did you know that
it's because of mom
that caused her to push back
the wedding a little bit?
Yeah, I think in a way,
it's probably a good thing
that we're pushing back.
You know, not just
because of her mom
but I want us to
have enough money
to be a stable family too
when we do move out.
Her mom warned you about
sneaking into her room at night.
[giggles]
Is he still doing it?
Yeah.
[laughter]
What do you use for
birth control now?
I have the IUD.
IUD.
Before I got pregnant,
I was on the pills.
But I couldn't remember
to take them daily.
I'd go days without taking them.
So I figured, you know,
this is the best way
and it'd give us a
little time period
before we have another baby.
[Dr. Drew] Yes.
Yeah.
[Dr. Drew] Is there a
plan to have another baby?
JR?
I want it in the
future some time.
It's hard to afford
the one we got.
So we definitely
can't afford another.
Yeah, it gets a
lot worse with two.
Do you resent JR at all,
having now lost really
your teenage years?
Sometimes, because you know,
he got to have his senior year
and I've missed out on
a lot of my senior year.
And it makes me
mad at him because
I guess he doesn't
really understand
where I'm coming from.
And if I want like just to take
a minute away or something--
[Dr. Drew] And JR
doesn't approve of that?
Not all the time.
Is that back to the
trust issues again?
Yeah, I guess, you
can call it that.
So you guys both
have jealousy issues.
I mean that's what causes
most the arguments and stuff.
JR, do you feel like your
relationship would be different
if there wasn't Ryland around?
No.
[Dr. Drew] It'd be the same?
You'd still be asking
her to marry you?
Yeah.
Do you tell her that?
Does he tell you that enough?
Not enough.
[Dr. Drew] Tell her right now.
I love you.
And I always wanna be with you.
I never wanna lose
you or Ryland ever.
I want to grow old with you.
And us watch Ryland
grow up together,
send him off to college
and watch him get married
and us become
grandparents together.
Way on down the road.
Yeah.
Not as young as we was.
When you tell me how much
you love me, it means a lot
and it's something
I need to hear often
even when we fight.
I just need to know
that you still care.
[laughter]
Let's make
something clear here.
You two are extraordinarily
unusual as teen parents
because you both have
two supportive parents,
you have one another,
you have determination
to finish your education,
you have a job
and in spite of it being
an optimal circumstance,
it's still hard.
It is.
[Dr. Drew] Right?
It's very hard.
Well thank you
guys for being here.
It's an inspiring story
and in a moment, we will
return with Christina and Izea.
Now it sometimes seem like
Izea cared more for his car
than he did for his baby's mom.
We will get his priorities
straight right after the break
so do not go away.
[audience applause]
[audience clapping]
And we are back.
I'm Dr. Drew and this is the
"16 and Pregnant"
Finale Special.
Today, I'm talking with nine
extraordinary young women,
each of whom had their
lives turned upside down
after taking a pregnancy test.
I'm here now with Christinna.
Let's take a look back at her
story on "16 and Pregnant".
♪♪
Still don't like
Isiah's grandma.
Then she's like, "It's not his
baby, we will get it tested."
Nowadays, people don't,
because you're pregnant,
they don't run around
getting married.
You got a scholarship
to college.
You didn't have to be here.
And not only are you here, you
brought something with you.
[loud clap]
Your baby should be
your number one priority
and she's not.
Isiah has three hundred
dollars left from his check
and he wants to spend that.
I told you I was gonna
get me two fifteens, man.
Like, if I wasn't pregnant
I would've just been like
"Adios, bye I'll see you later."
[Woman] Go, go,
go, go, go, go.
She's here.
Say "Hi", mom.
[baby crying]
[Man] You like
being a mom now?
I don't like it or dislike it
Everybody has a purpose in life.
I didn't think my purpose
was to take care of a baby
before I had her.
If I walk away,
then what was the hell
my purpose was giving
up my scholarship
if I'm just gon'
walk away that easy?
I feel we should still
should have a DNA test.
I don't see the point in it.
Why not?
I know whose baby it is
and that's all that's
important to me.
Bought it.
Granny knows things.
Granny knows
♪♪
[door slamming]
Whoa, that is intense.
So, did you use that
DNA paternity test?
I got fed up with it,
so I went and I got it
from Isiah's mom's house
and I swabbed all our mouths,
and nobody wanted to send it
off and pay the money for it.
How does it feel that she's
so rough on you about that?
It's very frustrating.
I try to be respectful
because that's my husband
and my daughter's grandmother
and great grandmother but-
Was there a specific issue?
They blame me for
the fact that he didn't
go off to play college and
they resent me for that
and won't let it go.
Isiah's grandma and mom
had beaten you up pretty good
about the football scholarship.
Mhm.
Why didn't you try to get
the scholarship to stick?
Try to work it out?
Well, the problem was,
that college is a
private Baptist school
and they don't have any
married student housing at all
and it's very expensive.
And so, like, I just
couldn't afford to go there.
So if he would of went I
would've either stayed in
Alabama
or went back to New York.
So did you ever go
to the school and say
"Hey, we've got the situation,
can you help us with this?
What are our options?"
Yeah, they told him to
get a copy of his transcript
whenever he got his final
grades for the semester.
So he got those
transcripts together.
No.
He just never did it?
Yeah.
Don't know.
I gotta hear from him
when he gets out here.
I guess so.
How's relationship
with Isiah now?
It's okay.
Are there issues?
Yeah, there's a lot of 'em
Alright, lets get him out here
and talk about
these things, okay?
Isiah, come on out.
[audience clapping]
How are you, sir?
I'm good.
How ya doing.
So she was saying
there's some issues.
What's she talking about?
I'd say there
were past issues.
Like, present day, I don't
say there's any issues.
That's from my
stand point though.
And from your stand point?
I say the two main
problems would be,
not necessarily
cheating, but mingling-
[Dr. Drew] Mingling?
Texting
Did you ever cheat?
Mmm.
Once.
Not since we've
been married though.
Okay.
So once you've made a commitment
in front of God and
everybody you live up to it?
No, I found out he cheated
on me after we got married.
And, I think that's something
you should tell somebody
before you marry them.
How'd you find out?
He was texting the girl again
and I saw text messages
in Isiah's phone.
And you couldn't
figure it out?
Oh, I texted her.
I hope she told you.
I think Christinna's
living in the house
where she doesn't feel
very supported by your kin.
Yeah.
My kin, them some tough
people to get along with.
How do you feel about this
issue with the paternity test?
My grandma, I don't know,
I let her think
whatever she wants to.
[audience laughing]
Did you ever question?
The paternity.
I would say I did, when
she was first born though.
Just what I would always think,
like, "Wow she doesn't
really look like me."
but now, like, months went by,
like, wow she really looks
close to just like me now.
Let me ask something,
just why not go back after
the scholarships?
I'm at a two-year
college right now
so that gives us time for
our baby to get older,
us to get our associate's and-
[Dr. Drew] You got some
work in the meantime.
figure out a better plan.
How did you get pregnant?
Didn't you say you didn't
use any birth control or-
Nothing.
Isiah, you just-
Nah.
I don't know, me, high school,
I was the invincible kid.
I was the football star,
the track star, the base-
everybody liked me.
Had just signed my scholarship,
I didn't think I could
go wrong with anything.
What about now,
what are you doing?
Nothing.
No contraceptives?
Huh?
[audience laughing]
Well, you're keeping up
with the stats that way.
About one in fourteen
moms get pregnant again
within two years.
So, do you want a second baby?
Not now.
Isiah, put a
condom on, you know.
I know.
[audience laughing]
I'll go buy you some
when they do the break,
I swear to God.
[audience laughing]
The problem though is, If
you have a second child
you're just gonna be scrambling
financially from then on.
Yeah
But imagine if another
child comes along,
what that's gonna do to Destiny.
It's not fair.
No
Okay, so contraception, yeah?
Yeah. [laughs]
Isiah, Christinna, thank
you for sharing with us today.
Now, bottom line, If
you're not using protection
you can get pregnant.
To learn more head over
to 16andpregnant.mtv.com.
We're gonna take a quick break
and then I'll bring
out Brooke and Cody.
Question here is, has car
racing taken a back seat
to motherhood or vice versa?
Find out when we return.
[audience clapping]
♪♪
Welcome back to the show.
I am Dr. Drew and this the 16
and Pregnant Finale Special.
Today's show is all
about the teen mothers
but we'll make some room
for the guys as well
because we're gonna be chatting
with all the dads together
on this stage, so
stay tuned for that.
I'm looking forward to that one.
Right now I'm joined by Brooke
and her baby's father, Cody.
Guys, how are ya?
Good.
Now, you come
from a family where
teen pregnancy has
not been that unusual.
Not really.
And you were gonna
break that cycle.
Yeah, I thought I was.
Supposed to.
Okay, we'll talk
more about that
but first, let's
take a look back
at how Brooke handled
being 16 and pregnant.
[Woman] Did you take one?
Three.
[Woman] Third time's a charm.
No, all three of 'em
said the same thing.
Why do y'all wanna
get married right now?
'Cause I don't wanna
be fat at my wedding.
[Officiant] Do you,
Brooke, solemnly agree
to receive this man as
your lawful wedded husband?
I do.
[Officiant] You
may kiss the bride.
[Brooke] I love you.
I love you too.
Go daddy, go
daddy, go daddy, go!
And y'all have
to pay for daycare,
me and dad can't help you.
We know, we have
to pay for daycare.
One, two, three...
Come on sweetie, push!
Four, five.
Come on, he's a long guy!
Look at him!
The house needs to be cleaned
and it's not happening.
You guys gotta pick
up your slack, period.
We aren't putting
anything aside for
paying back mom and dad
or the house or anything.
So are we gonna change that now?
Oh goodness is right.
Oh goodness.
You're a junior in high
school, is that right?
[Brooke] Mmhm.
[Dr. Drew] Well that
must have been tough.
I had a lot of support
from my friends and family
so it wasn't as tough as
it is for most people.
[Dr. Drew] Also you
had a supportive partner.
[Brooke] Yes.
Cody, you tried on a
pregnancy suit at one point,
how'd that feel?
Like, my back's killing
me, my legs are killing me.
So then I had the bright idea of
going out in public with it on
and the looks I
got there was like
what is he doing?
But, I mean it's, it's
more understanding now
to know what she went through
and I think that should be
something every guy tries on.
Brooke, is it emotional to see
all of the other
moms' stories too?
Yeah, 'cause it's sad
when they don't have
the support that they
need to get through it.
There's no way I could
do it without him
or my parents or his
grandparents or his parents.
My understanding
is that you're pretty
connected to Brody,
you're with him all the time.
You went to prom?
That was the first
time I left him.
It was sad but it was good
for me to start to know that
I have to leave him
every once in a while.
And you're starting
to get used to
handing him over to people?
I didn't think it
would be this hard
to leave him every
once in a while.
I mean, did you decide,
oh, I'll just keep
going to school?
I think that's what you
said even in your segment
was just, I'll go to
school, I'll get a job,
I'll do all these things.
And I'm going to school and
I start my job in the summer.
But it's gonna be hard,
it's gonna be really hard.
You come from a
long heritage of
women that got married
young and teen moms.
For Brody, do you expect
he'll be a teen dad?
I hope not, I'm gonna
teach him what I can, but.
Did your mom talk to
you about those things?
Yeah.
I didn't listen. [laughs]
How tough for mom,
she's trying to tell
you all this stuff
and what, you run
out of the room?
It's awkward to me, I
don't know why, it just is.
It's a difficult topic.
Yeah.
Well guys, thanks for joining
and thanks for
sharing the story.
Thank you.
Our next mom is Megan,
here is what she went through
this season on 16 and Pregnant.
Yeah, I'm not ready.
You will be.
It's heartbreaking.
You know, you guys
can't be kids anymore.
You and this stupid game.
[Nathan] I have
nothing better to do.
It's not gonna be easy
to take care of a baby
with a controller in your hand.
I think once the baby comes
and things start getting rough,
Nathan's gonna split.
So you realize if we
weren't having a baby,
I wouldn't be here, right?
You're doing amazing,
baby, look at that.
Meghan, you were
right, he's perfect.
[Woman] Good job, Megan!
I realize that I
was stupid, I'm sorry.
[Meghan] It's okay.
[Meghan] 'Kay.
Now that we're parents,
we kinda need to
change our priorities
a little bit more.
What the hell do
you want me to do?
[Megan] You need to
lay off the video games
and change more diapers.
Your living off
my dad's paycheck
doesn't really thrill me.
You can stop glaring at
me at any point in time.
I would like if you got a job.
I can go to Texas and work.
I don't want you
to go to Texas.
It's kinda hard to begin
our life without any money.
Very stressful, right?
80% of teen moms'
baby daddies take off.
Where's Nathan?
He's at home.
Why isn't he here?
'Cause we've been having
problems and stuff, so.
He should be here
supporting you, right?
Yeah.
You live with your mom now?
Mmhm.
And he was living with
your mom too, right?
Where's he living now?
His grandma's.
[Dr. Drew] So he's taken off?
Yeah.
Tell us what's going on.
Well, we were
engaged but he said,
last week he said he
didn't know what he wanted
so we kind of broke up, I think,
we haven't made it
like official though,
and he moved out,
but he still comes by like
every day to see the baby.
Did you expect the baby to
kinda keep him in the game?
Kind of.
Yeah, eight out of 10
times it makes 'em split.
[laughs]
I bet a lot of people
complain about Nathan.
Yeah.
And I bet you have to
come to his defense a lot.
Why do you think that is?
Because I don't
want it to be true.
I think that's very honest.
What is it you
don't want to be true?
Like, him not
wanting to be around.
How is it trying
to raise a baby
without a dad around?
I've basically been doing all
of it since he was born, so.
[Dr. Drew] It's the same?
It just sucks.
It sucks being,
doing it alone?
But you have your mom.
I am so sorry he's letting
you down like this,
you don't deserve that.
Is there something
particularly difficult now
about the caretaking alone?
Yeah, just like,
not having him there
to just even like talk to me
while I'm having
problems with Blake, and.
So just the
supportive presence?
I'm still a little unclear, so
things are going along okay,
a little too much video games,
and then he just leaves?
Yeah.
No warning?
Mm-mm.
Like we didn't even have
a fight or anything.
He just said he didn't think
he wanted to get married
and he didn't know whether
he wanted to be with me.
You got a little
explaining to do,
I mean, right?
Yeah.
All right Megan, well
thank you for coming today,
I appreciate you sharing.
Yeah.
The emotional
reunion, don't forget,
between Ashley and baby Callie
and Callie's adoptive
parents is still on the way,
and up next is Felicia.
Her mom and her baby's father
didn't always see eye to eye
and they're both here.
So we'll see where things stand
with them after the break,
do not move.
[audience applauds]
[audience applause]
Welcome back to
life after labor.
I'm Doctor Drew and
here's a disturbing fact.
Less than 2%, that's
2%, of teen mothers
graduate from college
by the age of 30.
One teen mom who hopes to
beat those odds is Felicia.
Hi Felicia.
Your mom was always on
you about graduating.
Did you do it?
I went to night school,
so I got a lot of
classes done faster.
So I'm graduating a year earlier
than I was supposed to be.
All righty, well here
is Felicia's journey
on 16 and Pregnant.
I just handed the
pregnancy test to her.
She's like, "So
you're not pregnant?"
I was like, "No mom,
it says I'm pregnant."
[Alex] Do you remember
when we first met?
Yeah, do you?
You used to be such a
little goody goody girl.
You have to graduate.
You were the only
one who promised me
that you was going to graduate.
That's always been my goal.
Alex, he tells me,
I'm coming home early.
He doesn't get home til
like 2:30 in the morning.
Yeah that's messed up.
So after she's born are
you still gonna be going out?
I can't really answer that.
It's just not the same anymore.
[Female] Good job.
Oh Felicia.
[Operator] Your call
has been forwarded
to an automatic voice.
He needs to hurry
up and come home.
I just wish I should have
waited just a little more.
You're not happy are you?
No.
Now that I have Genesis,
I could care less
if you're with me, but
this is your daughter.
I could care less if I'm
with you too, honestly.
Uh-oh.
I haven't even spoken to you
yet and you're already crying.
What are you crying about?
I don't know, it's
just hard watching that.
[Dr. Drew] Yeah.
Just the things he said,
how he could care less
if he was with me.
Did you at one
time imagine the baby
was gonna solve these
relationship problems?
I thought maybe we
would come closer.
That isn't usually
what happens.
You still have friends?
I wouldn't say I
have true friends.
[Dr. Drew] Why's that?
I lost a lot when
I got pregnant.
[Dr. Drew] They just
fell by the wayside?
I just didn't really have
any support from my friends.
Were they just not
supportive the way
you needed them
to be supportive?
I know your mom's
got a lot to say,
and it seems like
she's been a very
supportive parent
throughout your pregnancy,
even though it's
freaked her out a bit.
And then seems like Alex
is stepping it up a bit,
he is not?
Mm.
Although he said
some horrible things.
[Felicia] Yeah.
Let's get them both out here
and discuss this a
little further, okay?
Alex and Reina, come on out.
[audience applause]
Mom, how are you?
Good.
What are you thinking?
I think she really
disappointed me.
How old were you
when you got pregnant?
I was 16.
Was your mom mad?
No, she threw me out.
She said, "Get outta here."
[Dr. Drew] She was really mad?
Yeah she was mad.
[Dr. Drew] Same
anger you have.
Same, yeah.
How does it feel
to hear that you
disappointed your mom so much?
I didn't wanna disappoint you.
Alex, what are you feeling?
I don't know.
Mom and Felicia, would
you switch positions
for a second, please?
I'm doing that because I
want Alex next to Felicia.
What's the status of your
relationship right now?
Just together.
[Dr. Drew] Just together.
Is there any talk
about marriage?
Uh yeah, but I don't
wanna get married.
I don't really wanna
get married right now.
[Dr. Drew] How come?
[Felicia] I wanna
see how it goes.
I mean we have some
issues right now, so.
What does he need to
do to get to the point
where you would trust
him as a husband?
Show me that he
cares more about me.
I do show you that I care.
Every morning I go
to work, come back,
you know, I'm taking
care of you and Genesis.
You can't say that I didn't.
I started taking
care of you even
way before you had Genesis.
You came from a
broken family too.
Yes, my momma
raised me by herself.
I mean I've been through
so much since I was little.
I didn't have a dad.
He don't have a father.
He don't have no dad.
My dad didn't
show me any love.
It's hard.
How does it feel
when it's not enough?
It's just not easy.
Yeah.
Do you understand
what he's saying?
You got a mom
that you can go to,
I don't got nobody.
And you got your step-dad.
You know I've been standing
by myself since I was 15.
I decided to do my own life
so that's what I'm doing.
You know?
I'm just looking at you
guys on the couch here,
you need to join forces.
You know what I'm saying?
I mean you need to be a unit,
you need to support each other.
Who's gonna make the first move?
That's right.
[laughing]
What's the living situation now?
We still live with my mom,
but we're planning to
move out in a little bit,
'cause my mom's moving.
Where you going?
Oh I'm renting my
house so they can move
and they have their own life.
Okay but you'll
still be in the...
Yeah we're going to
be closer, you know,
the baby, I'm not
leaving the baby,
no way, it's a beautiful
baby and I like the baby.
The baby is mine.
All right.
Felicia, Alex,
Reina, thank you for
sharing with us and joining us.
I appreciate it.
Markai is up next.
Now in her episode, Markai
couldn't get past the fact
that James once cheated on her.
So is she ready to
forgive and forget?
I will ask her that
in just a moment.
Don't go away.
[audience applause]
♪♪
We're back with
more Life After Labor,
this is the 16 and
Pregnant finale special
hosted by myself, Dr Drew.
I'm here with Markai
and her boyfriend James.
Here's what Markai went
through on 16 and Pregnant.
♪♪
I just want her
to have a good life.
She can know that her parents
are always gonna be there.
Both parents.
You're right.
Think when I looked at you,
or felt you move in my stomach,
it was, I want her
to be pregnant at 16.
That was not my
dream for my child.
[Nurse] Push,
push, push, push.
[Second Nurse] Push!
Push, don't give up.
[baby crying]
[Markai] I don't trust him.
I don't even have
that [beep] number!
I didn't even, my
own MySpace, okay.
So what?
So that means you still
wanted to chill with her.
What happened?
Girl, she ended up
coming to [beep] school.
[Friend] Who
came up to school?
The girl.
[Friend] He
cheated on her with.
You can't park right there!
Oh my God, we'll die!
So you're gonna be like this?
Are you freaking serious?
You don't know who did this!
It's you!
Two weeks into
our relationship!
It doesn't [beep] matter!
You the one who did this [beep]!
You wanted to fight
me for custody,
don't ever come see my child.
I love you so much and I'm
scared that she's just gonna
come back and she's
gonna take you.
♪♪
Wow.
What do you think watching that?
It hurts seeing it
because I know how I felt.
I was obsessed with
her being with him.
Just picturing them in my head,
does he kiss her the
way that he kisses me?
Does he touch her the
way he touches me?
Does he say he loves her as much
as he says that he loves me?
No girl's gonna give it
up unless they have play.
They're not just gonna just
sit up there and just be like,
I'm gonna be the
other woman to him,
unless the guy has a part in it.
Do you think James did that?
[laughs] Yeah.
You think he did that?
All right, James, hear from you.
Man, it ain't
even like that, man.
I told her a thousand times,
it ain't even like that.
I'm sorry and I love you.
You're the only one for me.
And you know that.
[Dr. Drew] Markai,
what does hanging on
to those resentments do for you?
Nothing.
What's the matter
with you being close?
Scared I might get hurt again.
Right, right.
I've been hurt too
many times from guys,
I don't wanna take that anymore.
[Dr. Drew] I know,
James knows too, yeah?
I'm with you today.
And like I told her, I'm
not gonna stay with you
because of a child, I
didn't fall in love with you
because you was pregnant,
I fell in love with you for you.
Do you want Zakariya
to not have a dad?
All right.
Can you let it go for her?
Mm, now try.
I love you.
[Dr. Drew] There we go.
Point blank, period.
[Markai sniffing]
Can I get an I love you
back or something, I mean?
[all laughing]
I do love you.
[Dr. Drew] Did that help?
Yeah.
Little bit.
How are we preventing
another pregnancy?
Depo shot. [laughs]
[Dr. Drew] Oh, depo?
Yeah.
That work okay for you?
I'm good with it.
You good with it?
It ain't bothering me.
[all laughing]
Are your friends still
hanging out in your life
or they gone?
They text every
now and then but--
[Dr. Drew] What
happens to them?
I mean, when you have a child,
you can't do what you used to.
They couldn't
relate to your life?
Or is it--
Not at all.
They can't relate.
But then by the same token,
you needed something different
from friends, too,
than they had to offer.
Yeah.
Okay, I wanna talk
about the aggression
that bubbles up between you two.
Is that still going on?
Yep. [laughs]
It is?
We still get aggressive.
I mean, that's just how we
communicate with each other.
No.
I mean, I'm not saying
it's the right thing to do,
I'm just saying it's
how we communicate,
that's our way, that's
our relationship.
You can't just go,
"Oh, that's just us,"
that's not good,
that's not okay.
Does it get bad?
I'm not gonna lie, I get
aggressive, I want to fight.
We need to get you
some help for that.
That's called domestic violence.
And that's a common thing
and it has a treatment
and you can be helped.
You must've seen that
sometime growing up, too.
That's where kids get that.
Yeah.
That must've been awful.
I don't wanna fight,
I don't wanna punch
and I hate every time I
do put my hands on him,
I do feel bad.
You become the
abuser at that point.
It's not okay to
be abusive, okay?
But it happens understandably
and with certain histories
and circumstances and then
there are things we can do
to make sure it doesn't happen.
Thank God you wanna
do something about it
and that you've got this
guy hanging in with you.
We actually have some
information out there
for people that might
wanna learn more
about domestic violence.
Go to the website
loveisrespect.org,
that's loveisrespect.org.
It's a website you guys
might wanna check out.
[both laughing]
It's such a common thing,
it is a common thing
and the sad thing in my life is
that people don't do
something about it.
When they do, I
consider it a triumph.
James, Markai, thank
you for sharing, okay.
Up next, we've got
Aubrey and Brandon.
Brandon wanted Aubrey to
stay at home with the baby
but Aubrey had other plans.
So what's Aubrey doing today?
You stay tuned,
we're gonna find out.
[audience applauding]
♪♪
We are back in the 16 and
Pregnant finale special,
I am your host Dr. Drew.
And it is a fact that less
than half of teen mothers
graduate from high school.
One teen mom who is determined
to get her GED is Aubrey.
I'm here with Aubrey and
her baby's father Brandon.
How are you guys?
Good.
What's the status of your
relationship right now?
We're married.
And stable?
Yes.
And is the stress of the baby
affected your relationship?
It's tough.
We had to kind of redo our
whole relationship you know
based around something
completely different.
We will talk more about that,
but first, let's take a look
back at Aubrey's journey
being 16 and pregnant.
[Woman] Do you have a plan?
Yeah, it's gonna be hard
but I have to go to school.
What are those
shoes for, Brey?
[Aubrey] The wedding.
I now pronounce
you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
You don't have
a place to live.
You don't have a job.
You guys gonna have to
get something going,
those diapers aren't cheap.
Don't be so mean.
I would make enough to
take care of both of us.
I'm not going to be just
like a typical housewife.
Well you're better at cooking,
you're more efficient
at cleaning.
I'm really excited
to get my GED
so that I can go to college.
Unfortunately you
fail the math test.
I'm so depressed
sometimes like...
Quit whining.
This is the first time
I brought it up to you,
this is the first
time I've like...
Well don't bring it up again.
Here he comes.
There you go.
How much money
have you kids saved?
I have 99 cents in
my savings account.
This is a complete kit
of everything you need to
get started in prospecting.
This will make you money.
You know I thought
we would definitely
be out of mema's house by now.
Yeah, me too.
So I got the job.
Are you excited?
I'd be so nice to
have the extra money.
So you're out of
mema's house yet?
No.
And Brandon, you pretty
clearly wanted Aubrey
to be a stay-at-home mom,
but that doesn't sound
like what her plan is.
Initially, my thought
it always goes to daycare,
because I know childcare
is very expensive.
And would it really
be cost-effective to,
for her to work and then
you know her what she make
might not even be
what it's gonna cost
to have him in daycare.
What about her being
able to feel productive
and good about her life?
Well, that's kind of what we
came to a compromise on that.
Good.
Who was there for Aubrey
in the delivery room?
Actually I just
had Brandon in there.
[Dr. Drew] That was it?
Your mom didn't
want to be there?
When I was giving birth I
didn't want anybody in the room.
[Dr. Drew] How about your
family, did they show up?
Well, no, not right away,
just because really the one
I'm the closest to is my dad,
and he just didn't
have the finances
at that point to come down.
Where's your mom?
She's away.
Yeah.
I've stayed pretty
disconnected since she left.
How old were you
when she took off?
I think like six or seven.
So you've not really
had females in your life?
Not really any positive ones.
I've always gotten along
better with women than men.
Have you had
girlfriends before Aubrey?
One.
[Dr. Drew] Did that end okay?
No.
Excuse my language,
she's a dumb [beep].
Sorry.
Aubrey, how do you
really feel about her?
[laughs]
How's the panning
for gold going?
Awesome, we are rich.
I've got a mansion in
the Hamptons, it's great.
And, what are we doing
to prevent another baby?
Now my understanding
is you used to use
the pull-out method?
Yes, we did.
It works terribly.
[Dr. Drew] Yeah,
don't do that.
What are you doing now?
I got the non-hormonal IUD.
Good.
Did you have any kind
of health sex classes
in your high school,
health education?
We did.
They went over the
thought of you know
you can get pregnant if you
don't use birth control,
but they didn't go
over all my options.
They didn't talk about
all the different
kinds of contraception.
If somebody had discussed
this with you ahead of time,
do you think you would
have gotten pregnant?
I probably would have
already been on the IUD.
I probably honestly
would have been.
Thank you, it's an
important point to make.
Thank you for
making that, Aubrey.
For more information
on prevention,
go to 16andPregnant.mtv.com.
Educate yourself.
Thank you guys for
being here again.
Let's move right on
now to our next mom.
It's time to revisit Emily's
story on 16 and Pregnant.
I'm living my whole high
school life in one year
and I'm pregnant
and having a baby.
I don't want no baby.
I mean I do now I guess but.
Do you feel like
you're mature enough
to have made the
decision to have a baby?
I guess.
Board of Education states
failure due to attendance.
Little lucky 'cause
she's pregnant.
It really doesn't matter
what you think though.
I can keep her from
even marrying you, pal.
Push, push,
push, there you go.
Oh my god.
So what's been going
on with you and Daniel?
He feels bad about saying
he's gonna like come over
and then like not coming over.
You think being this far
away is gonna be a big deal?
Daniel's gonna be
missing major things.
I've drive like almost
an hour to come see you.
If you think that you're not
going to get along with him now,
what's gonna change when you
move off and live together?
I don't think we took enough
time to look at everything.
I guess I realized that
I have that options.
I guess that don't include me.
[Dr. Drew] A lot
of your dad in that.
Yes.
It's a good thing you've
got your dad up there, right?
Mm-hmm.
What's the status of
relationship with Daniel now?
I mean everything's
gotten a lot better.
Since what we just saw?
Yes, yes, definitely.
You're better.
Are you engaged?
Yes.
Did I see you sort of putting
off the marriage is that--
Yeah, but we haven't broken
up or anything like that.
It seems like
your dad and Daniel
have come a long way
in their relationship.
How they get along now?
They get along good.
So that's improved?
Yes.
Why don't we bring them out
and see how they're
doing right now.
Alrighty.
[audience applauding]
Hi there.
Gentlemen, welcome.
How are you guys?
Fine.
Stacey, from your
standpoint, things better?
Yes sir, getting a lot better.
You were very skeptical
for a while there.
Still am.
Emily was a great
student right, a majorette.
What happened?
I would like to
though that myself.
Daniel, you smiled when
I asked that question.
Oh I mean I know
she was really smart,
she still is really smart.
I mean she did really
good in school.
I hate that she had
to go to home school
and not be able to finish
out at regular high school.
Where are you living now?
At my house.
How far is that
from where Emily is?
Like 45 miles.
45 miles.
And so when do you see them?
Every day that I don't work.
Like two or
three times a week.
[Dr. Drew] Two or
But not on the weekend.
Is that plan working?
Yeah, it sucks, but that's
what we have to deal with.
It's just amazes me how
everything can be
tooken so lightly.
So you think she
should marry Daniel?
I think that it would
have been a great you know--
Good move?
Yeah.
Step up, do it.
And then you think he'd
step up a little further
if he were the husband.
He'd have to.
I don't think it's real
until we live together,
and I think that's what's
gonna be the problem,
is when we finally
move in together
and have to pay our own
bills and our insurance--
Yeah, that's gonna be
a whole different thing.
Well it breaks my heart for her,
and every time I talk to her
I keep thinking about this is
you were a talented
student, it's obvious.
That's gonna get sacrificed?
That's just gonna be
out to the vapors.
I mean there's a lot of things
that have been sacrificed.
Like what else?
Well, like my
school and my friends
and then I have to move away
and then college
and stuff like that
and just being able
like everybody else
has said to be normal.
And pregnancy has
taken that away.
Yes, definitely.
Did you imagine yourself
in this position at this age?
No.
No, never.
Emily, you were
living with your mom
when you got pregnant.
[Emily] Yes.
How was your relationship
with your mom at that point
before you got pregnant?
Before I got pregnant
it was always a
negative relationship.
What was the matter?
I mean she just never gave
me the freedom that I wanted.
And then when I started
like dating or liking him,
she just hated him like
from the start immediately
and I liked him so much
so I rebelled against her
and did things and got
in trouble for them.
And what kind of consequences
would you get for that?
I wasn't allowed to
like go out places-
Did you get grounded?
My life was
basically grounded.
And so you got pregnant,
how did she take that?
She was angry obviously,
and then it was like, well
what are you gonna do?
She didn't have like
an initial reaction,
she just questioned me.
And you were prepared
to be a parent?
No.
You prepared to step
up to try to be a parent?
I'll try.
To try.
Yeah.
Is it different
than you expected?
Yeah.
How?
I thought I was gonna
be a little bit easier,
but it's not easy.
And again, sex education
classes in high school?
They promote abstinence and--
[Stacey] And him
get a condom, I mean.
They don't even say that.
They don't?
[Daniel] No.
Stacey, what do you
think it should include?
What do you think
it should include?
Oh my god, something to
give these young ladies
an opportunity to
make a decision
when they've god forbid
want to have sex,
but I mean it's
happened and obviously.
I think negotiation skills
are what are essential
and that's usually left out
of these education classes,
is to be able to listen to
what you want and negotiate it.
Yeah.
It's not easy.
No, it's definitely
put a lot of stress
on our relationship for sure.
Yeah.
You can't take back.
[Emily] No.
Well, you guys, thank
you for joining us.
Appreciate it, Stacey.
Thank you sir.
Good luck.
Daniel, keep going
man, keep pushing.
I'll try.
Next, we're gonna have
all the dads out here
right here on this stage
to see what they thought when
watching their own episodes.
So stay put, do not go away.
[audience applauding]
♪♪
[applauding]
We're back.
I'm Dr. Drew, and this
is Life after Labor.
As you know, 16 and Pregnant
is all about the moms,
but their day-in day-out
lives are greatly impacted
by these guys right here,
the babies' fathers.
Now I want to hear
their side of the story.
We've got a little bit of
a boys club going here.
Never done this before
partly because we've never
had enough men to do this.
So, first of all,
congratulations, gentlemen,
for not just being
another statistic.
[applauding]
Show of hands.
How many watch your
episodes and regret
something that you did?
[sighs] Keep thinkin'.
[chuckles] One by
one, the hands go up.
How many of you think you
will be regularly involved
in your child's life
10 years from now?
You guys are not the norm.
You should be the norm,
but you're not the norm.
Anybody have any
questions to start out?
What's been the
hardest thing to give up?
Yeah, I gave up
basically my childhood.
I mean, that's what you do.
You give everything up.
You can't look at
other women anymore.
[laughing]
I don't know, you can
look, just don't touch.
[laughing]
[Teen Dad] That would not
fly with [muffled speaking].
You guys the kind of
dads you thought you'd be?
I hope so, I hope so.
You had something in your mind
that you wanted to live up to?
That was always
the rock in my life.
It was always my dad.
Always, he was always
the one I could turn to.
He was the only one
that was supporting me,
so if I could just be like him
or even half as good as him,
I know I'm doin' a good job.
Anybody feel
like they're doing
a better job as a dad than...
Yeah, I feel I'm
doin' a lot better job
than my dad, though.
I mean, my dad was there for me,
but he wasn't there
to raise me, though.
I'm goin' to at least try
to be there for my daughter,
a lot more.
It's important for the
girls, the little girls.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
[Dr. Drew] Dads being there
is a huge deal for young women.
James, was it
me, you, and Alex,
I think we got the
only girls on there.
They grow up, man, we're
goin' to have to hate
the same dudes we
once was, though.
Hey man, I'm gonna
look back like,
"Man, I was that dude,
man, 18 years ago.
"That was me, man."
You could talk
to those guys now.
They're out there
watchin' this show.
What do you tell 'em?
Just kind of like understand
that your partner needs you.
There's no way that they
can do it on their own
and be completely successful.
It'd be so much
harder on someone
if they're by themselves.
I mean, if you don't
stick with them,
that says something
about your character.
Mm-hmm
Well said.
There's a lot of support
out there for teen moms,
not so much for
teen dads, is there?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
I just want to take this
second to applaud you guys
for hanging in and
showin' your character
and being a part
of the girls' lives
and your children's lives.
It says a lot, so
well done on that.
[applauding]
How does it feel being able
to share with other teen dads?
'Cause really, there isn't
anything like this out there
where you get
together with the guys
who are in your position.
How does that feel?
It makes you feel
good 'cause you're
around positive men.
It's really like, man,
you feel like you hang out
with these guys,
you can't go wrong.
Just hanging out with these
guys for the past couple days,
it feels like--
We understand each other.
We are on a same level,
whereas I've grown up
with people that I've been
best friends with
forever, and it's like
we run out of stuff
to talk about.
We never do.
Good for you guys.
All right, gentlemen, thank you.
We're going to take a
break, and when we return,
Ashley, she's here
with her mom Debbie
and baby Callie's adoptive
parents, Kenny and Lisa.
It's the emotional reunion
everyone's been waiting for.
We'll be right back.
[applauding]
♪♪
Welcome back to the 16
and Pregnant finale special.
I'm Dr. Drew, and
listen to this fact.
Of the 57% of teen pregnancies
that end in a live birth,
only about 1% results
in an adoption.
Ashley chose adoption
for baby Cali,
and she's here with
her mom Debbie today.
Hey guys.
So does that piece
of data surprise you?
Only 1% ends up in adoption.
Yeah, that 1% nothing.
It's a tiny number.
Well Ashley's uncle and aunt,
who we will come to know
is Cali's adoptive parents
are here with us as well.
We'll bring them out
along with baby Cali
after this recap of Ashley's
up and down experience
being 16 and pregnant.
Who was the first
person to have adoption
out on the table?
Both my mom and I, we
considered every option.
Your aunt Lisa called.
Lisa and Kenny called
and they wanted me to ask you
if it was okay if they
could adopt your baby.
Well thank you for doing this
and stuff, it's relieving.
Here we go.
There she is.
It's gonna be hard
to sign the papers.
You honestly think you
made the wrong choice,
you know?
yes.
I wish I could go
down and get her,
like, I would seriously
drive down there right now.
I want to do this and I
feel like I can do this.
We just want to see
that you're confident.
I can do this, I'm gonna be
the best mom that I can be.
I've had her for
about a month now.
[baby crying]
Sometimes I think like I never
should've went and got her.
Lisa.
[Lisa] Hey Ash.
I've been thinking about it,
and I just think the best
thing is not with me.
♪ I feel so sick that
I can't unmiss being ♪
Emotional for
both of you guys.
How do you feel about
the decision now?
It's still ambivalent?
What's the hardest part?
Not seeing her everyday.
Like, when I had her, I was
waking up to her every morning.
It was still hard,
but I still did it.
Teen pregnancy
changed a lot for you.
Yeah, I didn't even know
what I was getting myself into.
Did you use contraception?
No.
[Dr. Drew] At all?
We talked about it though.
All the time.
Yeah, we talked about it.
Oh yeah, there's that.
Yeah, we were
very open about it.
I think I messed up though
because she did come to
me at some point and say,
"I think I wanna
get on the pill."
And we had a heart to
heart and I thought,
we should wait, it
should be special.
And I thought it was resolved.
[Dr. Drew] And what happened?
[Ashley] I didn't wait.
Did he contemplate
staying around as a dad?
We didn't talk,
so I don't know
if he contemplated or not.
He dated with my best friend.
Ex best friend.
I'm so sorry.
Debbie, when you took Cali back,
I noticed you were pretty
patient about all that.
What were you actually feeling?
I just wanted to support
whatever choice she made.
And how do you feel
about the adoption?
Well I'm happy.
Like I'm really thankful that
they are the ones who did it
because I don't know if I
could've given her to strangers.
But there's always that what it.
Just like if I kept her,
there's always what if.
Do you wish you'd stuck
with the original agreement
when you left the hospital?
You wish you hadn't
gone through that month
you had with Cali?
I don't know because maybe
if I didn't bring her back,
I would've felt
like I never tried.
You guys thought
it would be easier
having a familial adoption.
Has it been?
I think it's been amazing.
I mean I think it's a wonderful,
I think it's something
wonderful that happened,
because she gets
to be in our lives.
But because it was family,
everybody had Ashley's
best interest at heart
and at times we'd forgotten
what was best for Cali.
Trying to make Ashley better,
letting her come back and
trying it out for a while
and of course my brother
and my sister were in pain
and their family was devastated.
The fact that there
was a lot of pain,
Cali didn't experience it.
That's the great news.
She was taken care
of, no matter what.
You guys sucked up all
that pain in the front end
so she didn't have to
experience it later.
Yeah.
When was the last
time you saw Cali?
Two months?
Well, Lisa and Kenny
are here with baby Cali,
and let's bring
them out right now.
[applause]
[Ashley] She's asleep?
She was, until
everybody clapped.
[Ashley] Can I hold her?
How's it going for you guys?
[Kenny] Good.
How was that month
when she took her back,
it must have been tough?
It was tough to
watch Ashley hurting.
You know, how she struggled.
That was tough.
This is intense for you.
It is, it's been a tough
few months for all of us.
I mean, we just didn't realize
the emotions that we
would all experience
and everything we
would go through.
And the time when she decided
to give Cali back to you
after that month,
tell me about those few days.
When Cali went
back with Ashley,
we really felt like
Ashley was gonna do this.
We sent her back with
the intentions of
she was not gonna
get back to us.
And for us and our
family, to kind of go on.
You have to think that way?
We had to think that way,
and we couldn't
think it was possible
that she would come back.
We wanted the best
and I guess we all just
came to the conclusion
that this was the best.
I don't know if Debbie,
if they heard what you said
about how you felt about that.
That you're all
awesome and incredible
and wonderful people.
Don't cry.
I'm trying not to.
They're just amazing.
[Ashley] They are.
Everything
they've done for us.
Well hats off to you guys
for absorbing all this,
both these young
people's behalf.
She is very lucky to have
all these people in her life,
is she not?
Yes, okay.
We're gonna take one last break,
then return with all the moms
who will have the chance to
ask questions of each other,
we'll be right back.
[audience applause]
To find out what you can
do to prevent pregnancy
go to itsyoursexlife.org
♪♪
[audience applauding]
Welcome back to life
after labor, I'm Dr. Drew.
Now, we've spent a lot of time
talking about prevention today,
but there is much more
for you to learn online.
So head on over to
16andpregnant.mtv.com
and get yourself educated.
I'm joined now by all
nine of our teen moms.
We got to know each of them
over the course of the season.
I've had a chance to talk
with them here today.
Now it's time to let them
ask each other questions.
Kristina, you had a question?
I have a question
for Marquise.
I wanna know how you got over
it when James cheated on you.
I just realized that
I was blaming James now
for James who was.
If I'm just gonna
keep getting on him
about something
he did back then,
it's only hurting me,
you know what I mean?
Not hurting nobody but me.
Aubrey, did you have
a question for Ashley?
I just kinda wanted
to let you know
that we're all here for you.
And you said in your
show that you felt like
people looked down on you
for giving up your baby,
and I could never look
down on you for that, ever.
You made the strongest
decision and I respect it 100%.
Thank you.
I have a question
for everyone.
I want to know how
long everyone had been
with their significant other
before they got pregnant.
Mm-mm, you don't wanna ask.
You don't wanna ask that.
[girls laughing]
[Presenter] Anybody
who wants to answer that?
A month.
A month?
Same, I was with him
for a year and a half.
Year and a half.
I think it was eight months,
I'm not sure.
Eight months?
Year and a half.
I was nine months.
Nine months.
Six months.
[girls laughing]
Am I the only one?
Ashley, Ashley I just.
Ashley?
Two and a half.
Two and a half months?
Months? Enough months?
Let me ask something.
Ashley, since you
feel I wanna ask,
did you feel like if you
didn't you would lose him?
Uh-uh.
No? Okay.
I don't know, I
don't even know why.
Oh my god, I don't
even know why.
Like, I think about it and just
don't even know
what I was thinking.
I do too.
I've felt like that before.
[Presenter] If you
didn't have sex with him
you'd lose him?
Yeah.
Yeah, a lot of
girls feel that way.
I had something to
say to all of the girls.
When I thought about coming here
I thought I was just
maybe an awkward person
and I just didn't fit in,
'cause after I had my baby
me and my close
friends all grew apart.
I don't have any
of my close friends
to call on anymore when. [sobs]
[Girl] Don't do it,
please do not do it.
When I need to
talk to somebody.
And when I got here
and met all of y'all,
it's like I was closer to y'all
than people I've grown
up with my whole life.
[girls laughing and sobbing]
Me too.
Ladies, thank you.
Thank you very much for sharing,
thank you for being so
supportive of one another.
Thank you to the dads,
thank you to the families,
thank you all for
being here as well.
To those of you at home, thanks
for tuning in this season.
Now, let's bring out the babies
and we'll see you next time.
♪♪
[audience applauding]