>> HI, MY NAME IS SAMANTHA,
AND I'M FROM ROSENBERG, TEXAS,
A SMALL TOWN OUTSIDE OF HOUSTON.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM;
HER BOYFRIEND, GREG;
AND MY LITTLE BROTHER, JACOB.
>> THERE'S TOO MANY GIRLS
IN THIS HOUSE.
>> MY PARENTS AREN'T TOGETHER,
BUT MY DAD AND I ARE REALLY
CLOSE.
CAN I GET GUMMY BEARS WITH IT?
YES.
SADLY, OUR HOUSE ISN'T VERY BIG,
SO I HAVE TO SHARE A ROOM WITH
MY BROTHER, WHICH REALLY SUCKS.
TURN OFF THE LIGHT.
>> NIGHT.
AND IT'S GONNA GET A LOT MORE
CROWDED SOON, BECAUSE MY MOM
IS HAVING A BABY.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
I'M TIRED OF BEING SICK.
>> MY BOYFRIEND, ERIC, IS 18.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR
TWO YEARS, AND WE SPEND
ALL OF OUR TIME TOGETHER.
I DID MISS YOU TODAY.
>> MISSED YOU TOO.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A GOOD GIRL,
SO I STAY OUT OF TROUBLE
AND STAY ON TOP OF MY
SCHOOLWORK.
THIS YEAR, I'M GONNA BE
A SENIOR, AND I'VE DEFINITELY
BEEN LOOKING FORWARD TO ALL
THE PERKS OF BEING AN
UPPERCLASSMAN.
HEY, HEY.
>> GET HIM!
>> BUT MY SENIOR YEAR MAY NOT BE
AS CAREFREE AS I'D HOPED,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
[mellow rock music]
* *
LAST YEAR AT SCHOOL,
NO ONE KNEW I WAS PREGNANT
BECAUSE I WASN'T SHOWING.
BUT NOW THAT I AM SHOWING,
WHEN SCHOOL STARTS AGAIN,
EVERYONE WILL KNOW,
AND I'M KIND OF NERVOUS ABOUT
BEING THE PREGNANT GIRL.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT PEOPLE,
LIKE, TALKING ABOUT YOU?
>> PEOPLE ARE GONNA TALK,
BECAUSE I MEAN, LIKE, I KNOW HOW
WE WERE AT LUNCH, REMEMBER?
AND THEN THERE'D BE GIRLS
WALKING BY PREGNANT, AND WE'RE
JUST LIKE, "OH, THERE'S
ANOTHER ONE."
NOW...
[laughter]
>> YOU'RE THE NOTHER ONE.
>> IT'S GONNA SUCK, BECAUSE ERIC
DOESN'T EVEN GO TO THE SAME
SCHOOL AS ME.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO IT'S GONNA BE LIKE
I'M JUST WALKING IN THE HALLS,
LIKE, WITH MY BIG BELLY
BY MYSELF.
>> [together] OH!
I'LL WALK WITH YOU.
[laughter]
>> ARE Y'ALL GONNA LIVE
TOGETHER?
>> HE WANTS ME TO MOVE IN
WITH HIM.
>> 'CAUSE YOU WANT A BIGGER
HOUSE?
>> BUT YOUR MOM...
>> YEAH, I HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER
ABOUT THAT YET.
>> HOW DID YOU AND YOUR MOM AND
ERIC, EVERYTHING BEEN SO FAR?
>> IT'S BEEN, LIKE,
A LOT BETTER.
>> I REMEMBER WHEN YOU
FIRST TOLD ME YOU WERE PREGNANT.
I CRIED, AND I CRIED.
LIKE, SERIOUSLY.
>> WHY?
>> SENIOR YEAR, WE WERE GONNA
DO ALL THIS STUFF.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN.
YOU CAN.
>> IF YOU'RE HAVING SEX,
LIKE, YOU CAN'T--YOU CAN'T,
LIKE, REALLY...
>> THERE'S BIRTH CONTROL.
THERE'S CONDOMS.
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS.
>> THERE'S CONDOMS.
THERE'S FEMALE CONDOMS.
>> OR JUST DON'T HAVE SEX.
>> EXACTLY, ABSTINENCE.
[laughter]
[chime dings]
>> I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE TAKEN
MY OWN ADVICE.
HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SUMMER IS OVER,
AND WE'RE ALREADY BUYING
SCHOOL SUPPLIES.
EVEN THOUGH OUR HIGH SCHOOLS
ARE CLOSE BY, IT SUCKS THAT
ERIC WON'T BE THERE AT MY
FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL.
>> SO WHAT CLASSES ARE YOU
TAKING?
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE ALGEBRA.
I'M TAKING THAT FAMILY CLASS.
IT'S CRAZY THAT ONCE THIS
SEMESTER IS OVER, WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A BABY, WHICH IS WHY
ERIC AND I HAVE BEEN TALKING
ABOUT MOVING IN TOGETHER.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
>> THE PLAN IS FOR YOU TO COME
AND MOVE IN, RIGHT?
>> WELL, YEAH.
BUT IS YOUR MOM OKAY WITH IT?
>> SHE'S OKAY WITH IT.
>> WELL, WHEN ARE WE GONNA
TELL MY MOM?
>> THINK SHE'LL BE MAD WHEN YOU
TELL HER YOU'RE GONNA MOVE OUT?
>> WHEN WE'RE GONNA TELL HER,
NOT JUST ME.
I'M PRETTY SURE SHE'S GONNA
BE REALLY MAD.
>> I THINK, AT FIRST, SHE WON'T
LIKE IT, BUT I THINK AFTER
A WHILE, SHE'LL BE OKAY.
I MEAN, SHE'LL HAVE HER BABY
TO WORRY ABOUT.
[chime dings]
>> MY MOM WAS A TEEN MOM,
AND IT WAS REALLY HARD FOR HER.
SO WHEN SHE FOUND OUT ERIC AND I
WERE HAVING SEX, SHE FREAKED.
SHE MADE ME SWITCH SCHOOLS
AND GO LIVE WITH MY DAD,
AND THEY FORBID ME TO SEE ERIC.
BUT WE WERE IN LOVE, SO ERIC
GOT HIS MOM TO HELP US HANG OUT
BEHIND MY PARENTS' BACKS.
THEN I FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT,
AND I HAD TO TELL MY PARENTS
EVERYTHING.
THEY WERE NOT HAPPY.
MY MOM CALMED DOWN AND LET ME
MOVE BACK HOME, AND NOW SHE'S
EVEN FRIENDLY WITH ERIC.
BUT SHE HASN'T FORGIVEN HIS MOM
FOR HELPING US SNEAK AROUND.
>> THE ONLY REASON THAT I WAS
REALLY, REALLY UPSET IS BECAUSE
AFTER I TOLD HER TO DO HER PART
AS A PARENT, SHE JUST SAID
THAT, I GUESS, Y'ALL WERE IN
LOVE AND Y'ALL WERE GONNA KEEP
SEEING EACH OTHER, AND THAT'S
NOT HOW 14-YEAR-OLDS SHOULD ACT.
YOU SHOULD BE WORRIED ABOUT
YOUR SCHOOL AND NOT HAVING SEX.
YOU KNOW?
AND I WAS JUST UPSET BECAUSE
SHE WASN'T ON OUR SIDE.
>> I REALLY WANT OUR MOMS
TO GET ALONG, SO I'M TRYING
TO GET THEM TO MAKE UP.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHERE YOUR MOM
IS COMING FROM BY BEING UPSET,
YOU KNOW, WITH ME.
BUT THE THING THAT GOT ME WAS
HOW THEY WERE ONLY BLAMING ERIC.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S THE THING THAT HIT ME
TO WHERE--YOU KNOW WHAT,
THE LEAST AMOUNT OF TIME
I HAVE TO SEE THESE PEOPLE
IS BETTER FOR ME.
YOU ALSO GOT TO UNDERSTAND
THAT THERE'S A LOT OF EMOTION.
A LOT OF THINGS HAVE BEEN SAID,
AND YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IT'S GONNA
TAKE TIME.
[chime dings]
>> MY EFFORTS TO GET THEM
TO TALK HAVE PRETTY MUCH
GONE NOWHERE.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> YOU'RE RIDING WITH US, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> TODAY WE FIND OUT THE SEX OF
OUR BABY.
I'M REALLY EXCITED, AND EVEN
THOUGH ERIC WANTS A BOY, I'M
SECRETLY HOPING FOR A GIRL.
BECAUSE OUR MOMS STILL AREN'T
TALKING, ERIC'S MOM STAYED HOME,
AND HIS DAD AND SISTER CAME
INSTEAD.
BUT IT SUCKS WE CAN'T ALL
DO THIS TOGETHER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HOW ABOUT MAKE HIM DANCE
AGAIN.
>> WHAT IF IT'S A GIRL?
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE A GIRL.
>> READY TO FIND OUT WHAT
YOU'RE HAVING TODAY, HUH?
>> YEAH.
>> SO ARE WE PUSHING FOR
A BOY OR A GIRL OR...
>> GIRL.
>> A GIRL, HUH?
NO, WE'RE MIXED, 50/50 HERE.
>> HE'S MOVING.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE
A LOOK HERE.
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH.
>> OH, LOOK.
>> LOOK AT THE HEAD.
>> LOOK.
>> YOU SEE BABY'S HANDS TRYING
TO TOUCH ITS FEET UP HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU READY TO FIND OUT
WHAT YOU'RE HAVING?
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU ARE HAVING A BABY GIRL.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> [screams]
[applause]
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> ERIC, LOOK AT HER
BEAUTIFUL PROFILE.
>> AND YOU BOUGHT ALL THIS STUFF
FOR BOYS, MAN.
>> DID YOU START SHOPPING
ALREADY, ERIC?
>> OH, SHE'S MOVING ABOUT NOW.
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY GIRL.
>> OH, MY GOSH, LOOK AT HER.
>> YEAH, I'M EXCITED.
>> ARE YOU EXCITED?
LOOK AT JORDYNN.
>> YES, TAKE--
OH, IS THAT THE NAME?
>> JORDYNN.
>> JORDYNN?
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> OH.
>> I'M EXCITED WE'RE HAVING
A GIRL, BUT I HOPE OUR FAMILIES
CAN RESOLVE THEIR ISSUES
SO JORDYNN CAN BE BORN INTO
ONE BIG, HAPPY FAMILY.
>> I'VE BEEN REALLY NERVOUS
ABOUT GOING BACK TO SCHOOL,
SO MY MOM THOUGHT A TRIP
TO THE NAIL SALON WOULD BE NICE.
>> WHEN I FIRST FOUND OUT
THAT SHE WAS PREGNANT...
>> I KNOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SAMANTHA, WERE YOU NERVOUS
TO TELL YOUR MOM?
>> I THINK I WAS MORE SCARED
ABOUT HER THAN MY DAD.
>> IT'S JUST--YOU KNOW,
THERE'S GONNA BE A LOT OF
CHANGES, AND THERE'S GONNA BE
A LOT OF THINGS THAT ARE GONNA
BE REALLY, REALLY HARD.
>> CAN'T GO BACK NOW.
>> I JUST DIDN'T WANT YOU TO
HAVE TO GO THROUGH THAT.
>> I'M SCARED.
>> ARE YOU?
>> [giggling, crying]
YEAH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SCARED OF?
>> EVERYTHING.
>> IT'S GONNA BE OKAY.
>> I REALLY, REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO EXPECT.
>> I MEAN, IT'S A LOT
OF RESPONSIBILITY, 'CAUSE
YOU'RE GONNA BE A MOM NOW.
YOU'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR SOMEBODY.
>> NOT MY HAMSTER.
>> NOT YOUR HAMSTER.
>> WITH SCHOOL STARTING
TOMORROW, I'M BEGINNING TO
REALIZE THAT MY CAREFREE HIGH
SCHOOL DAYS ARE OVER.
>> * IN THIS TOWN *
[acoustic guitar music]
* WE ALL KNOW *
* WHAT'S GOING DOWN *
* WHAT GOES UP *
* AND WHAT COMES ROUND *
* NOTHING HERE'S EVER THE SAME *
>> MOM.
>> * EVERYONE'S HEADED *
* FOR CHANGE *
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO WEAR
TOMORROW.
>> THAT'S CUTE.
I LIKE THAT.
>> I'M GONNA HAVE TO WEAR
THE STOMACH BAND OVER IT.
THAT WAY I CAN WEAR
MY REGULAR JEANS.
>> * IN THIS TOWN *
* *
* WE ALL KNOW *
* WHAT'S GOING DOWN *
>> HEY, JACOB.
>> BE NICE.
WE NEED TO GO TO BED.
>> * MM *
* *
[alarm clock beeping]
* WHAT GOES UP *
* AND WHAT COMES ROUND *
* NOTHING HERE'S EVER THE SAME *
* *
* EVERYONE'S HEADED FOR CHANGE *
>> WHEN I WALKED INTO SCHOOL
BY MYSELF, I WAS REALLY NERVOUS.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW PEOPLE
WOULD REACT TO MY BIG BELLY.
THE HARDEST PART WAS FACING
MY TEACHERS, AND THEN WHEN
I WALKED INTO THE CAFETERIA,
EVERYONE WAS STARING.
I'M GLAD THE DAY'S FINALLY OVER
BECAUSE ERIC'S PICKING ME UP
TO GO BOWLING.
>> THERE WE GO, BABY.
YEAH.
WOW.
>> SEE, I'M A PRO.
>> REALLY?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
>> SO HOW WAS YOUR DAY
AT SCHOOL?
>> [giggles]
YOU SOUND LIKE MY MOM
OR SOMETHING.
IT WAS KIND OF AWKWARD.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE ASKING ME
IF I WAS PREGNANT.
>> SHOULD HAVE SAID NO.
>> YEAH.
>> I SHOULD HAVE.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN LIKE, "NO."
>> SAID, "NO, IT'S A BEER GUT."
[laughter]
>> ARE YOU GONNA GO TO
HOMECOMING THIS YEAR?
>> I WANT TO GO TO HOMECOMING.
WELL, ERIC WANTS TO GO TO PROM,
BUT IT'S EXPENSIVE.
UNLESS YOU'RE PLANNING ON
SAVING UP A LOT OF MONEY
SO WHERE WE'LL HAVE ENOUGH FOR
THE BABY FIRST.
>> ARE YOU GONNA BE BACK
FOR GRADUATION?
LIKE, BE ABLE TO GO WITH THE
BABY AND ALL?
>> I HOPE I'LL BE CAUGHT UP AND
STUFF SO WHERE I'LL BE ABLE--
>> TO GRADUATE AND HAVE
ALL YOUR CREDITS.
>> YEAH.
[chime dings]
>> MY MOM HAD ME WHEN
SHE WAS 16, AND THEY BROKE UP
WHEN I WAS 2.
BUT NOW WE ALL GET ALONG,
AND I SEE MY DAD A LOT.
AND HE CAN DEFINITELY RELATE
TO WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD FOR YOU
TO GET SLEEP, YOU KNOW,
ENOUGH REST.
YOU KNOW, BUT I WANT YOU
TO FINISH SCHOOL.
>> THAT'S DEFINITELY
GONNA HAPPEN.
>> I DIDN'T HAVE ANYONE TELLING
ME, "DON'T DROP OUT OF SCHOOL."
>> THERE'S THIS PROGRAM
CALLED HOMEBOUND, AND THE
TEACHERS WILL COME, LIKE,
WHENEVER THE BABY KIND OF--
LIKE, THEY'LL BRING ME MY WORK,
TO THE HOUSE.
THAT WAY WHEN I GO BACK,
IT'S--LIKE, I'M CAUGHT UP.
AND I WAS THINKING I'D LIKE
TO BECOME A TEACHER.
>> WHAT'S THE PLAN BETWEEN
YOU AND ERIC?
>> YEAH, ABOUT THAT.
I MEAN, I KNOW THIS SOUNDS
LIKE A BAD IDEA RIGHT NOW,
BUT WE WERE TALKING ABOUT
ME GOING OVER THERE.
THEY HAVE, LIKE, AN EXTRA ROOM
AT THEIR HOUSE FOR THE BABY.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T REALLY WANT YOU
TO GO AND MOVE IN WITH HIM
BECAUSE WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN IS,
THERE'S JUST GONNA BE
REPETITION.
YOU'RE GONNA GET PREGNANT AGAIN.
YOU KNOW, IT WAS HARD FOR US.
IT WAS HARD FOR ME TO GIVE UP
MY FRIENDS AND GOING OUT AND
HAVING A GOOD TIME AND THEN JUST
START WORKING.
FROM THAT DAY FORTH, I MEAN,
IT WAS JUST WORK, WORK, WORK,
AND IT DIDN'T--IT HASN'T
STOPPED YET.
YOU KNOW, I WANTED YOU TO
TAKE YOUR TIME, ENJOY LIFE.
YOU'RE MY ONLY DAUGHTER.
YOU KNOW?
BUT YOU NEED TO MAKE THIS
DECISION ON YOUR OWN.
YOU KNOW, I CAN TELL YOU
I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT IT'S UP TO YOU.
>> TALKING TO MY DAD GAVE ME
A LOT OF THINGS TO THINK ABOUT.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
I WAS FEELING PRETTY GOOD
UNTIL MY MOM CAME HOME FROM
WORK AND WANTED TO TALK.
HEY, MOM.
>> HEY, SAM.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I TALKED TO YOUR DAD,
AND HE MENTIONED SOMETHING ABOUT
YOU MOVING IN WITH ERIC.
>> WELL, ERIC AND I HAVE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT IT AND STUFF,
'CAUSE WE THOUGHT IT WOULD
KIND OF BE EASIER IN A WAY,
INSTEAD OF HAVING TO MOVE HER
BACK AND FORTH.
>> [sighs]
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE READY
TO LIVE WITH SOMEBODY RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN IN THAT
SITUATION BEFORE.
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE
AND I GOT PREGNANT AND IT
WAS HARD, AND I JUST DON'T WANT
YOU TO HAVE TO GO THROUGH THAT.
>> THE MAIN REASON WHY
WAS JUST BECAUSE, LIKE,
I KNOW THERE WAS GONNA BE
MORE SPACE AND STUFF.
AND HIS MOM SAID SHE'D WATCH THE
BABY DURING THE DAY AND STUFF.
>> I MEAN, MINE AND HER
RELATIONSHIP ISN'T CLOSE
TO BEING OKAY.
SO IT'S LIKE--I WOULDN'T
BE GOING OVER THERE.
>> I WANTED TO HAVE A SOLID PLAN
BEFORE THE BABY COMES, AND NOW
EVERYTHING IS UP IN THE AIR.
AND I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO.
>> A MONTH HAS GONE BY,
AND NEXT WEEK, I'M GOING WITH
ERIC TO THE SENIOR HOMECOMING
DANCE.
IT'S GONNA BE OUR LAST
HIGH SCHOOL CELEBRATION
AS NORMAL TEENAGERS.
THIS ONE'S PRETTY.
>> I LIKE IT.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GET THIS ONE.
>> THIS DRESS LOOKS BIG,
LIKE, WIDE.
[laughter]
AND WE GOT REALLY NICE CORSAGES.
>> OH, YOUR DRESS.
>> DO YOU LIKE IT?
>> MM-HMM.
WHAT SIZE IS THAT?
>> SIZE 13.
>> WOW.
>> [laughs]
>> I GOT YOU THIS PINK FLOWER.
>> ERIC'S GONNA SAY
I LOOK PRETTY.
THANK YOU.
>> THIS IS PRETTY.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> I FEEL SO BIG.
>> Y'ALL SMILE.
[camera clicking]
TURN TO THE SIDE LIKE THIS.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'LL BE THE
ONLY ONE THERE WITH A BABY
ON THE WAY?
>> I THINK SO.
SO ARE YOU GONNA DANCE WITH ME?
>> YEAH.
>> [giggles]
LIKE ALL SCHOOL DANCES,
ERIC'S CASINO-THEMED HOMECOMING
WAS A LITTLE LAME.
[chime dings]
BUT IT WAS FUN TO BE CAREFREE
FOR A FEW HOURS AND HAVE FUN
WITH ERIC.
WITH MY DUE DATE IN SIX WEEKS,
I'M TRYING TO FOCUS ON
PARENTHOOD.
IS IT STILL A GIRL?
>> IT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE,
SAMANTHA.
>> [giggles]
THANK YOU.
AND GETTING READY
FOR TWO BABIES.
[metal clicks]
>> OOH, SORRY.
[laughter]
>> EVERYONE SEEMS TO THINK
MOVING IN IS A BAD IDEA.
SO WE'RE HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS,
BUT WE HAVE TO MAKE A DECISION.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
AM I JUST GONNA STAY HERE?
>> [sighs]
WELL...
I'D LOVE FOR YOU TO COME
MOVE IN.
I'D LOVE TO WAKE UP EVERY
MORNING AND SEE MY BABY AND YOU.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
US RUSHING INTO EVERYTHING
LIKE THAT, I REALLY, REALLY
DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOU.
I REALLY LOVE YOU.
>> SO WHY ARE YOU SCARED THAT
IF I MOVE IN, THINGS ARE GONNA
GO BAD?
>> LIKE, BEING YOUNG,
WE GOT A LOT OF TIME,
EXTRA TIME TOGETHER.
AND I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE,
LIKE, 30s OR 40s AND GETTING
TIRED OF EACH OTHER,
AND WE START HATING EACH OTHER.
SO I'M KIND OF STUCK IN
THE MIDDLE.
THAT'S WHY WHATEVER YOU PICK,
THEN I WON'T REALLY HAVE
A CHOICE, SO...
>> WITH MY MOM'S BABY HERE,
IT'S JUST GONNA BE REALLY,
REALLY CROWDED, AND I MEAN,
MY MOM'S BABY IS GONNA BE
SHARING A ROOM WITH JACOB,
SO IF ONE BABY'S CRYING,
I'M HOPING THE OTHER BABY
WON'T WAKE UP.
BUT I GUESS I'LL JUST STAY HERE
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
>> SO TALK TO YOUR MOM,
JUST LET HER KNOW THAT
YOU'RE STAYING.
>> OKAY.
[chime dings]
I HAVE TO ADMIT.
I'M A LITTLE DISAPPOINTED THAT
ERIC AND I AREN'T MOVING IN
TOGETHER, AND I HOPE THINGS
WILL BE OKAY.
MY DUE DATE IS TWO WEEKS AWAY,
RIGHT BEFORE CHRISTMAS,
AND I'M WORRIED BECAUSE DESPITE
MY EFFORTS, OUR MOMS ARE STILL
NOT TALKING.
SHE HAS A LOT OF BLANKETS.
I HAD TO HAVE TWO DIFFERENT
BABY SHOWERS.
I DON'T WANT JORDYNN GROWING UP
WITH GRANDPARENTS WHO CAN'T
GET ALONG.
I JUST WANT US TO TRY AND
GET ALONG, LIKE, AT LEAST FOR
THE BABY.
SO I GOT ERIC'S MOM TO AGREE
TO COME TO DINNER WITH MY MOM.
>> FOR THE BABY'S SAKE,
I WILL DO IT.
I WILL BE THERE.
>> AND I CONVINCED MY MOM
TO SHOW UP.
>> WHAT?
>> NOTHING.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> HEY.
>> HOW'S IT GOING, MAN?
>> HI.
>> DON'T LEAVE YOUR COAT
ON THE FLOOR.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GETTING
TO DRINK?
>> I'M GONNA GET A SUPREME.
[tense music]
* *
>> SO HOW'S THE WEATHER?
>> SAMANTHA.
[laughter]
>> GETTING BETTER.
>> SAMANTHA.
>> THANK YOU.
WELL, I'M GLAD Y'ALL COULD COME.
WE JUST WANT TO, LIKE,
PUT EVERYTHING IN THE PAST.
I WAS SCARED NO ONE WOULD BREAK
THE AWKWARD SILENCE, BUT
FINALLY, MY MOM SPOKE UP.
>> I JUST FELT LIKE YOU GOING
BEHIND OUR BACK PICKING HER UP,
TAKING THE CELL PHONE JUST SO
THAT THEY CAN HAVE
CONTACT TO SEE EACH OTHER,
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT THAT WAS
A RESPONSIBLE MOVE AS A PARENT.
>> I FELT Y'ALL WERE JUDGING
ERIC BEFORE GETTING
TO KNOW ERIC.
>> BUT YOU KNOW WHAT,
IT'S NOT THAT WE DIDN'T GIVE
ERIC A CHANCE, BECAUSE IT WASN'T
UNTIL THE FACT THAT WE FOUND OUT
THAT THEY WERE HAVING SEX.
THAT'S WHEN I STARTED BEING MAD,
NOT ONLY AT HIM;
I WAS MAD AT HER.
IT'S BOTH OF THEM.
>> SO?
>> I'M...
>> START FRESH?
>> I HAVE TO TELL YOU THAT
I DO APOLOGIZE FOR TAKING HIM
TO SEE HER.
YOU KNOW, I KNEW IT WAS WRONG--
NOW I DO.
AT THE TIME, I DIDN'T.
AT THE MOMENT, I'M THINKING,
"I'M SEEING MY SON CRY.
I'M SEEING MY SON HURT."
YOU KNOW, SO AT THAT MOMENT,
I'M THINKING, YOU KNOW,
"I GOT TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT
FOR MY SON."
NOW I UNDERSTAND, AS A MOTHER,
HOW OFFENDED YOU MUST HAVE FELT,
AT THE TIME, FOR WHAT I DID.
YOU KNOW, AND THEN I DO
APOLOGIZE FOR THAT.
YOU KNOW, I DO.
>> YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENED
BEFORE, IT'S IN THE PAST.
AND IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NOT ABOUT ME.
IT'S ABOUT THE BABY.
SHE MADE HER BED.
SHE'S GONNA HAVE TO LIE IN IT.
THAT'S HOW THEY'RE GONNA LEARN.
I TELL YOU THAT ALL THE TIME.
RIGHT?
>> AND I ALWAYS TELL YOU,
"MOM, I DON'T MAKE MY BED."
[laughter]
>> SAMANTHA.
>> I DO.
I HOPE THINGS STAY GOOD,
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW,
IT SEEMS GOOD.
>> ME TOO.
[laughter]
>> TONIGHT WAS REALLY GREAT.
OUR MOMS MAY NOT BE BEST FRIENDS
ANY TIME SOON, BUT IT'S A GOOD
STEP IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
>> NOW THAT THE BABY'S ALMOST
HERE, I'M REALLY HAPPY TO HAVE
OUR PARENTS' FEUD BEHIND US.
I GUESS LAST NIGHT WENT OKAY.
>> YEAH, IT WENT GREAT.
>> HOPEFULLY, THEY TALK
NEXT TIME THEY SEE EACH OTHER.
>> WHICH WILL BE...
>> PROBABLY NOT TILL
THE HOSPITAL.
[chime dings]
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE ABOUT TO
HAVE A BABY IN LESS THAN A WEEK.
AFTER I HAVE THE BABY,
I'LL BE DOING HOMESCHOOL
FOR SIX WEEKS BEFORE I GO
BACK TO HIGH SCHOOL,
SO I'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET AHEAD
IN MY SCHOOLWORK SO I DON'T
FALL BEHIND.
AND MY MOM AND I HAVE BEEN
MAKING ROOM FOR OUR BABIES.
>> OUR BABIES CAN PLAY TOGETHER.
>> THROW 'EM IN THE PLAYPEN.
>> YEAH.
THEY COULD BE TOGETHER AND STUFF
ALL THE TIME.
>> IT'S GONNA BE WEIRD, THOUGH.
LIKE, ONE OF THE BABIES IS GONNA
BE CALLING YOU GRANDMA,
AND THE OTHER ONE'S GONNA BE
CALLING YOU MOM.
[laughter]
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME THAT IF
I DIDN'T GO INTO LABOR BY MY DUE
DATE THAT HE WOULD INDUCE ME.
MY DUE DATE CAME AND WENT,
SO TONIGHT, I'M HEADED TO THE
HOSPITAL TO START THE INDUCTION.
YOU GOT IT?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> NOTHING.
>> * GO *
[lively rock music]
>> [sighs]
NO GOING BACK NOW.
>> YOU READY?
>> AS READY AS I'LL EVER BE.
>> * GO *
>> ARE YOU READY TO PULL
AN ALL-NIGHTER?
>> YEAH.
IT'S GONNA BE LONG.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY.
>> READY?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M EXCITED.
>> YES, BUT THE PAIN,
SWEETHEART, IS GONNA BE SO HARD.
>> NO.
ERIC'S GONNA BE THE ONE
THAT'S GONNA BE FREAKING OUT.
>> REMEMBER HER WORDS, OKAY,
EVERYBODY.
>> BYE.
[laughter]
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M DOING GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO AHEAD
AND START THE PITOCIN NOW,
WHICH WILL GET THE CONTRACTION
GOING.
TAKE CARE.
>> BE AS COMFORTABLE AS YOU CAN,
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> EVEN THOUGH I WAS HAVING
CONTRACTIONS LAST NIGHT,
I DIDN'T FEEL MUCH AND GOT
A GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
BUT WHEN MY DOCTOR ARRIVED
THAT MORNING, EVERYTHING STARTED
MOVING REALLY QUICKLY.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO
AHEAD AND CHECK YOU AND SEE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> I WILL ATTEMPT TO BREAK
YOUR WATER, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S ABOUT 1 1/2.
ALL RIGHT.
>> [gasps]
>> OKAY, RELAX, RELAX.
WE'LL GET BACK ALREADY.
>> SAM, LOOK AT ME.
LOOK AT ME.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD, SLOW.
>> YOU'RE GONNA FEEL WET
THE REST OF THE WAY, OKAY?
YOU DID GOOD THERE.
HOPEFULLY SHE'LL MOVE
QUICKLY.
>> USUALLY MOST PEOPLE GET
AN EPIDURAL ABOUT AT ABOUT
3 TO 4 CENTIMETERS.
YOU'RE 1 NOW.
YOU GOT TO GET TO 10.
AND WHEN ARE YOU DUE, MOM?
>> I'M DUE IN FEBRUARY.
>> WERE YOURS NATURAL?
>> NO, I HAD C-SECTIONS.
[monitor beeping]
>> [sighs]
>> THE BABY'S A LITTLE BIT
SLEEPY.
I MAY GO AHEAD AND PUT
SOME OXYGEN ON YOU AND SEE
IF I CAN LIVEN UP THAT BABY
JUST LITTLE BIT, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
[air hissing]
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> YOU OKAY?
[sighs]
YOU FELT A CONTRACTION?
>> [sobs]
>> JUST FOCUS.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN, I STARTED
FEELING MY CONTRACTIONS,
AND THEY WERE REALLY INTENSE.
[groans]
>> SAM, I'M GONNA CHECK YOU,
OKAY?
TO SEE IF YOU'RE DILATED.
IT WOULD BE GREAT TO HAVE A 3.
THEN WE CAN GET YOU YOUR
EPIDURAL, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> I KNOW, LOTS OF PRESSURE,
LOTS OF PRESSURE.
>> [gasps]
[cries]
[screams]
>> I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
OKAY, YOU'RE 2, OKAY, SAM?
>> BECAUSE MY BODY ISN'T
DILATING, THEY CAN'T GIVE ME
THE EPIDURAL.
[crying]
[whimpering]
IT HURTS.
>> TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
>> DON'T TAKE--DON'T TAKE
THE MASK OFF.
>> YOU CAN'T TAKE THAT OFF,
MAMA.
>> [yelps]
>> WAIT, SWEETIE.
>> SAM, HOLD ON, BABY.
>> SHE'S GONNA CHECK YOU
TO SEE IF SHE CAN GET YOU
YOUR MEDICINE, OKAY?
>> [screaming]
>> MAMA, JUST RELAX.
>> [shrieks]
NO!
>> STILL 2.
>> [sobs]
>> OKAY.
OKAY, SAM, OKAY, I KNOW.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> AFTER 14 HOURS IN LABOR,
I WAS BARELY DILATED,
AND THE PAIN WAS ONLY
GETTING WORSE.
[whimpers]
>> DEEP BREATH, BABY.
>> MY BACK IS KILLING ME.
I HATE YOU.
[cries]
>> THE HARD PART OF YOUR BABY'S
HEAD IS ON YOUR BACK.
WE'RE GONNA TRY TO HELP YOU UP.
>> [moans]
>> I KNOW, RIGHT THERE.
>> I WAS HAVING HORRIBLE
BACK LABOR, AND I JUST WANTED IT
ALL TO STOP.
STOP TOUCHING ME.
>> WE'RE GONNA TRY SOMETHING
TO TAKE SOME OF THE PAIN OFF
OF YOU, OKAY?
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU ON YOUR
HANDS AND KNEES.
>> [whines] I CAN'T.
[groans]
>> COME ON, MAMA.
>> [cries]
STOP IT.
STOP.
>> YOU WANT TO TURN BACK OVER
ON YOUR SIDE?
OKAY.
>> [sobbing]
IT HURTS.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT HURTS.
>> SAMANTHA.
I JUST CALLED DR. FAGBOHUN,
OKAY?
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU YOUR
EPIDURAL.
HE'S GONNA LET YOU HAVE IT,
ALL RIGHT, 'CAUSE YOU'RE, LIKE,
2, ALMOST 2 1/2-ISH, OKAY?
[monitor beeping]
>> SUP.
>> TIRED?
SO HOW WAS SHE ACTING WHEN
THE CONTRACTIONS STARTED COMING,
LIKE, REALLY, REALLY HARD?
>> SHE STARTED TRYING TO TAKE
OFF ALL THE MONITORS AND TELLING
PEOPLE NOT TO TOUCH HER AND...
>> HOW MUCH LONGER DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
[monitor beeping]
>> UM, MOM?
I JUST CHECKED HER.
SHE IS 3 CENTIMETERS.
THAT SOMETIMES IS AN INDICATION
THAT BABY'S JUST NOT GONNA FIT.
COULD BE A C-SECTION.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT SHE STILL
CAN'T GO VAGINALLY, BUT BABY
DOESN'T LOVE THE PITOCIN.
>> OKAY.
[acoustic guitar music]
* *
>> SWEETHEART, YOUR TEMPERATURE,
WHEN I LAST CHECKED IT,
WAS 100.3, OKAY?
I JUST SPOKE WITH DR. FAGBOHUN.
WE'RE GONNA STOP THE PITOCIN
FOR RIGHT NOW, AND UNLESS YOUR
BODY STARTS DOING SOMETHING
DIFFERENTLY, THEN THOSE ARE SOME
OF THE SIGNS THAT SAY,
WE ARE GONNA GO AHEAD AND DO
A C-SECTION, OKAY?
>> YOU OKAY WITH GETTING
A C-SECTION?
>> AFTER ALL THAT TIME IN LABOR,
I HAD TO GET A C-SECTION.
I WAS SCARED, BUT I WANTED
THE WHOLE THING TO BE OVER WITH.
>> NURSE JANICE HAS IT.
>> OKAY, HONEY, JUST CLEANING
YOUR TUMMY, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> ERIC?
>> SAMANTHA,
HE'S RIGHT HERE, OKAY?
JUST TAKE SOME DEEP BREATHS,
SAMANTHA.
>> [screams]
>> SLOW.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, HEAD'S OUT.
>> TAKE SOME DEEP BREATHS.
>> CORD AROUND THE NECK.
THAT'S A BIG BABY.
>> IT'S ALMOST THERE.
>> OKAY, THERE WE GO.
>> TIME OF BIRTH, 23.
>> 27.
>> 27, 27.
>> HEY, BABY.
>> OH.
>> AW.
[baby cries]
>> CONGRATULATIONS, SAMANTHA.
>> SHE'S--
>> READY FOR COUNT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[baby cries]
>> 7 POUNDS, 8 OUNCES.
>> SHE'S SO BIG.
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU.
>> SHE'S COMING RIGHT NOW.
>> HI, JORDYNN.
>> [indistinct]
>> HEY, JORDYNN.
>> LOOK AT ME, DAD.
FIRST FAMILY PHOTO.
>> JORDYNN.
WERE YOU IN MY BELLY
THIS WHOLE TIME?
[chime dings]
WHILE I WAS STILL IN SURGERY,
ERIC GOT SHOW OFF OUR NEW
BABY GIRL TO OUR FAMILY.
>> HERE WE ARE.
>> 7 POUNDS, 8 OUNCES.
>> OH, THERE SHE IS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
SHE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
>> THAT'S ALL GOOD.
[all cooing]
>> DID YOU WASH UP?
[chime dings]
>> WHEN I FINALLY GOT BACK
TO MY ROOM, MY DAD CAME
TO SEE ME.
HI.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> I FEEL OKAY, BUT OH, MY GOD,
I WAS ACTING SO CRAZY.
>> I HEARD.
YOU'RE GONNA BE HERE
FOR A WHILE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, I LOVE YOU, OKAY?
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
EVEN THOUGH I WAS EXHAUSTED,
IT WAS NICE TO HAVE BOTH OUR
FAMILIES SUPPORTING ME.
THE ONLY THING THAT WAS MISSING
WAS JORDYNN.
>> YOU FEEL OKAY?
>> YOUR BABY LOOKS GREAT, OKAY?
HOWEVER, YOU'RE RUNNING
A LITTLE BIT OF A FEVER,
SO WITH THAT GOING ON,
WE NEED TO KIND OF PROTECT
THE BABY JUST IN CASE YOU MIGHT
HAVE SOMETHING THAT SHE MIGHT
GET.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY AND TAKE
A NAP.
>> OKAY.
>> AFTER ALL I'VE BEEN THROUGH,
I REALLY HADN'T EVEN HELD
JORDYNN, SO THAT AFTERNOON,
I FINALLY GOT ENOUGH STRENGTH
TO GO SEE HER.
IT HURTS SO BAD.
OH, IT HURTS.
>> CAN YOU SIT DOWN?
>> OKAY.
YOU READY?
OKAY.
>> ERIC, COME GET HER
REAL QUICK.
I NEED TO SIT BACK.
>> OKAY, RELAX A SECOND.
>> OW.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> * WALK A THOUSAND MILES *
* FOR YOU *
>> I HAD TO WALK ALL THE WAY
OVER HERE JUST TO SEE YOU
SLEEPING.
>> * I WILL COME FOR YOU *
* *
* THERE AIN'T MUCH *
* THAT I WOULDN'T DO FOR YOU *
>> SHE'S PERFECT.
>> HEY, BABY.
YOU READY TO GO?
>> AFTER ALMOST A WEEK
IN THE HOSPITAL,
I'M SO EXCITED TO FINALLY BE
TAKING JORDYNN HOME.
HEY.
>> HEY.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> SORE.
[Jordynn fussing]
>> YOU DON'T LIKE ME?
>> NO.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> MOVE IN A LITTLE BIT CLOSER.
DON'T BE SCARED.
>> HEY, JORDYNN.
LOOKIT.
JORDYNN LOOKS SCARED.
[chime dings]
I'M TIRED.
>> Y'ALL ARE GONNA HAVE
A LONG NIGHT AHEAD OF Y'ALL.
>> JORDYNN, THIS IS YOUR ROOM.
CHECK YOUR DIAPER.
OOH, SHE'S WET.
THERE.
LOOK AT HER LITTLE FEET
AND HER TOES.
SO WEIRD.
YOU GET TO SPEND THE NIGHT.
LIKE, IN THE BEGINNING, YOU
COULDN'T EVEN COME OVER HERE.
>> YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M GOING TO GET ANY SLEEP
TONIGHT.
>> I'M GOING TO GO GET READY
FOR BED.
NASTY.
[mobile jingling]
EVEN THOUGH IT SEEMS LIKE
I'VE GOT EVERYTHING UNDER
CONTROL, IT'S DEFINITELY
A NEW LEVEL OF RESPONSIBILITY
THAT I WASN'T QUITE READY FOR.
AND I'M NOT SURE MY FRIENDS
WILL UNDERSTAND.
>> [sniffs]
YOU'RE A MOM.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> DO YOU FEEL ANY DIFFERENT?
>> KIND OF, BUT I REALLY DON'T
KNOW HOW TO EXPLAIN IT.
>> SO WHAT'S YOUR NEXT STEP
FROM HERE?
LIKE, JOB OR SCHOOL?
ARE YOU GONNA WAIT TILL
SCHOOL'S OVER?
>> I'M FINISHING SCHOOL,
AND THEN AFTER SCHOOL,
I'M GONNA GO TO THE COMMUNITY
COLLEGE...
>> MM.
>> AND JUST GET MY BASICS AND
THEN TRANSFER SOMEWHERE CLOSE.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
[chime dings]
>> ERIC'S BEEN HELPING WITH
JORDYNN...
>> SHE'S SMILING.
>> BUT NOW HE HAS TO GO BACK
TO SCHOOL AND WORK.
>> I GOT TO CHANGE.
>> OKAY.
[Jordynn crying]
IT'S OKAY, BABY.
>> I GOT TO GO.
>> YOU WERE ASLEEP, AND YOU
DIDN'T FEED HER.
>> YOU'RE MAKING HER MAD.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
[shushes]
[Jordynn wails]
OKAY.
JORDYNN, YOU'RE BEING SILLY.
FOR THE NEXT SIX WEEKS,
I'M STAYING HOME WITH THE BABY.
WOW.
YOU ARE HUNGRY.
I STARTED HOMESCHOOLING,
BUT IT REALLY SUCKS BECAUSE
I MISS MY FRIENDS.
NOW THAT ERIC ISN'T HERE
TO HELP, DOING EVERYTHING FOR
JORDYNN BY MYSELF IS TOUGH.
SEE, YOU'RE ALREADY
GETTING FUSSY.
>> [sighs]
WHAT DID YOU DO TODAY?
>> JUST TOOK CARE OF HER
ALL DAY.
>> YES, DADDY HAD TO GO
TO SCHOOL.
AND THEN HE CAME TO SEE YOU.
THEN HE WENT TO WORK,
AND NOW HE'S TIRED.
YES, MA'AM.
[sighs]
[Jordynn fussing]
>> ERIC?
GET HER.
>> [groans]
[shushes]
TAKING CARE OF JORDYNN
HAS GOTTEN A LOT HARDER.
YOU'RE SUCH A SILLY LITTLE GIRL.
I KNOW ERIC HAS WORK AND SCHOOL,
BUT I STILL NEED HIM TO HELP
GET UP WITH JORDYNN DURING
THE NIGHT.
YEAH?
>> I GOT TO GO.
>> TIRED.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO TODAY?
JUST YOU AND ME AGAIN, JORDYNN.
DADDY'S AT SCHOOL.
THEN HE HAS TO GO TO WORK,
SO JUST YOU AND ME TILL 10:00.
BY THE TIME THE WEEKEND CAME,
I WAS SO EXHAUSTED.
I WAS ABOUT TO LOSE IT.
>> NOW THAT SHE'S BORN,
HOW'S Y'ALL'S RELATIONSHIP
CHANGED?
>> I JUST WANT HIM TO HELP MORE,
AND THEN, LIKE, HIM NOT HELPING,
IT'S JUST FRUSTRATING,
AND IT MAKES ME MAD.
>> I DO FEED HER SOON AS I GET
HOME FROM SCHOOL.
>> NO.
I TELL YOU, "ERIC, FEED HER."
AND THEN YOU'LL TRY TO,
AND THEN YOU'LL SAY, "OH,
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO EAT."
AND THEN YOU'LL START
PLAYING WITH HER.
>> SHE WANTS TO PLAY.
>> YOU NEED TO DISCUSS THIS.
I'M GOING TO TAKE HER UPSTAIRS.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO START
YELLING AT YOU BECAUSE WHENEVER
I TELL YOU SOMETHING, YOU MAKE
IT SEEM LIKE IT'S NOTHING.
>> AND THEN YOU GO CRAZY.
>> I WANT YOU TO HELP ME.
>> JUST 'CAUSE YOU GOT TO GO
BACK TO SCHOOL, IT'S STILL
GONNA BE EASIER ON YOU,
'CAUSE YOU DON'T GOT HER
DURING THE DAY.
I STILL GOT TO GO TO WORK.
>> AND I'M GOING TO HAVE HER
IN THE EVENING, AND I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO BE DOING MY HOMEWORK,
AND THEN I'M GONNA HAVE TO BE
TAKING CARE OF HER.
>> WANNA TRADE?
>> [scoffs]
GLADLY.
>> OKAY.
YOU GO TO WORK THEN.
I'LL STAY HOME WITH HER.
>> I WOULD GLADLY MAKE
SANDWICHES ALL NIGHT LONG.
>> YEAH, THAT'S ALL WE DO.
>> YOU MAKE IT SEEM LIKE
SHE'S SO EASY, LIKE, THE EASIEST
THING IN THE WORLD.
>> SHE'S A MONTH.
COME ON.
IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
>> REALLY?
I HAVE IT SO EASY,
AND IT'S JUST SO TOUGH ON YOU.
I'M SORRY.
EXCUSE ME FOR GETTING PREGNANT.
>> SINCE OUR FIGHT, ERIC'S TRIED
TO HELP MORE WHEN HE HAS TIME,
BUT HE'S STILL NOT TAKING
PARENTING AS SERIOUSLY AS I AM.
>> NO.
ERIC, YOU'RE NOT EVEN HELPING.
>> I'M TRYING TO KEEP HER HAPPY.
>> SHE NEEDS TO EAT.
>> BETTER NOT.
[head clunks]
>> OOH.
>> YOU HIT HER HEAD.
>> [laughs]
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
YOU'RE OKAY, RIGHT?
>> AND I'VE BARELY BEEN OUT
OF THE HOUSE OR SEEN ANY
OF MY FRIENDS.
>> YOU OKAY?
YOU SEEM MAD.
>> TIRED.
AND MY MOM FINALLY HAD
HER BABY BOY, GREG JR.
>> HEY, Y'ALL.
>> HOW'S THE BABY?
>> GOOD.
>> CUTE.
>> GOD, SHE'S SO MUCH BIGGER
THAN HIM.
>> EVERYTHING'S BEEN A LITTLE
CRAZIER WITH TWO BABIES IN
THE HOUSE.
[baby crying]
>> HE PEED ON ME.
>> HE PEED IN YOUR FACE.
>> ALMOST.
>> EW.
AND I'VE BEEN STRUGGLING TO KEEP
UP WITH MY WORK.
I HAVE TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
OKAY, HERE.
>> HAVE A GOOD DAY AT SCHOOL,
MOMMY.
>> SO LUCKILY, ERIC'S MOM
HAS AGREED TO WATCH THE BABY
DURING THE DAY.
[chime dings]
[school bell rings]
HEY.
>> HEY.
>> I'M SO SLEEPY.
LIKE, IN ECONOMICS, WE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING TODAY, AND I FELL
ASLEEP IN CLASS.
THINGS ARE GETTING REALLY
CHAOTIC, SHUFFLING BETWEEN
SCHOOL, ERIC'S HOUSE,
AND MY HOUSE.
I FEEL LIKE I'M GETTING SHOT
IN ALL DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
THE ONLY TIME I CAN CATCH MY
BREATH IS ON THE WEEKEND.
I KNOW ERIC REALLY CARES ABOUT
JORDYNN, BUT IT FEELS LIKE I'M
THE ONLY ONE WORRYING ABOUT HER,
AND I NEED MORE SUPPORT.
[sighs]
>> WHAT?
>> YOU MAKE ME ANGRY.
>> HOW?
>> IT'S LIKE YOU WANT TO PLAY
ALL THE TIME, AND IT
CAN'T ALWAYS BE ABOUT FUN.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THERE'S A LOT
TO WORRY ABOUT, AND YOU DON'T
LIKE TO THINK ABOUT THAT STUFF.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> THE FUTURE AND MONEY.
>> REALLY?
>> AND YOU'RE JUST NOT AS
SERIOUS ABOUT IT.
SOMETIMES I JUST DON'T KNOW
ABOUT US.
>> I MEAN, I KNOW I GOT
TO GO TO WORK.
I KNOW I GOT TO MAKE MONEY,
BECAUSE WE DO, IN TIME, NEED
OUR OWN HOUSE AND EVERYTHING,
BUT THAT'S LATER.
YOU'RE EXPECTING SO MUCH OUT
OF ME THAT ISN'T NEEDED YET.
>> WELL, MAYBE I DO NEED TO
LOOSEN UP A LITTLE BIT,
BUT YOU ALSO NEED TO BE A LITTLE
MORE SERIOUS.
>> WELL, WE'LL WORK ON IT.
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MAKE
YOU FEEL LIKE THAT.
>> I HAD NO IDEA BEING A PARENT
WOULD BE SO HARD, BUT AT LEAST
ERIC IS TRYING TO UNDERSTAND
WHY I'M SO FRUSTRATED.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> JORDYNN'S SCRAPBOOK.
>> SO HOW'S EVERYTHING WITH
ERIC NOW?
>> IT'S, IN A WAY, BETTER,
BUT I MEAN, I GUESS WE HAVE
OUR DAYS.
>> YEAH, EVERYBODY DOES.
AS LONG AS HE'S THERE
AND HE'S WANTING TO HELP YOU
AND TRY TO BECOME A FAMILY,
THAT'S A START.
DON'T GET MAD AT HIM,
BUT JUST REMIND HIM.
>> IT'S NOT, LIKE, EASY.
>> RIGHT.
>> LOOKING BACK, YOU AND DAD
TELLING ME NOT TO HAVE SEX
AND STUFF.
I MEAN, Y'ALL WERE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT.
I WASN'T READY.
AND IT'S, LIKE--
I DON'T REGRET ANYTHING
BECAUSE I LOVE JORDYNN SO MUCH,
BUT IT WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE
TO WAIT A WHILE.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN A LOT BETTER
FOR HER TOO.
YEAH.
MY MOM WAS A TEEN MOM,
AND SHE TOLD ME HOW HARD
IT WAS GONNA BE, AND I WISH
I WOULD HAVE LISTENED,
BECAUSE IT'S, LIKE, NOW
I HAVE TO GO THROUGH IT MYSELF,
AND THIS IS NOT HOW MY LIFE
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE.
COLLEGE AND EVERYTHING IS GONNA
BE SO MUCH HARDER, BUT I HAVE
TO DO IT.
I HAVE TO FOR JORDYNN.
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH ERIC NOW
IS CRAZY, 'CAUSE IT'S LIKE
I REALLY DON'T KNOW IF
WE'RE GONNA LAST.
I MEAN, I WANT US TO,
AND I'M HOPING WE WILL,
BUT SOMETIMES I'M JUST NOT
REALLY SURE, AND IT'S SCARY
BECAUSE I WANT HER TO HAVE
BOTH OF US IN HER LIFE, LIKE,
ALL THE TIME, 'CAUSE THAT'S
HOW IT SHOULD BE.
>> * ALL YOUR PETALS *
* FLOAT AWAY *
>> SHE'S LIKE, "YOU BETTER NOT
PISS OFF MY MOMMY.
I'LL BEAT YOU UP."
>> NO.
>> EVERYBODY THOUGHT I WAS,
LIKE, LITTLE MISS PERFECT,
AND THEN WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
EVERYBODY'S LIKE,
"YOU'RE PREGNANT?
YOU DON'T EVEN DO STUFF
LIKE THAT.
YOU'RE A GOOD GIRL."
AND IT'S JUST, LIKE--
I AM A GOOD GIRL.
I JUST MADE A DECISION
TO HAVE SEX, AND IT HAD
CONSEQUENCES.
AND NOW I'M LIVING WITH THEM.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com