Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
*
>> I'M DR. DREW.
WELCOME TO 16 AND PREGNANT'S
SPECIAL EPISODE,
UNSEEN MOMENTS,
AN INTIMATE PEEK INTO THE
INCREDIBLE STORIES YOU SAW
IN SEASON ONE.
AND BELIEVE IT OR NOT, THERE'S
EVEN MORE YOU DIDN'T SEE.
ON THE SHOW, YOU SAW MACI
AND RYAN'S WEDDING PLANS
DISSOLVE, BUT TODAY YOU'LL SEE
SOME OTHER MOMENTS THAT
CONTRIBUTED TO THEIR
WEDDING WOES.
YOU SAW CATELYNN AND TYLER
CHOOSE ADOPTION, BUT TODAY
YOU'LL SEE THEIR PRIVATE MOMENTS
OF DOUBT: THAT AND MUCH,
MUCH MORE.
IT'S THE CHRONICLES OF
WHAT TO EXPECT WHEN IT'S ALL
UNEXPECTED.
FIRST UP, A REALITY CHECK.
LET'S START WITH MACI AND
TAKE A LOOK AT HOW PREGNANCY
REWROTE HER WEDDING PLANS.
>> OKAY, I WANT A MERMAID DRESS.
>> WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
>> PLAIN WHITE.
I WANT ALL PLAIN WHITE.
I DON'T WANT ANY DIAMONDS.
>> WHAT'S "MERMAID" MEAN?
>> LIKE THAT, JUST PLAIN WHITE,
THAT KIND ALL THE WAY--
>> SO YOU ARE, LIKE, FOR SURE
GETTING MARRIED STILL?
>> IF WE GOT MARRIED, WE WOULD
ACTUALLY FEEL THE COMMITMENT
TOWARDS EACH OTHER,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> BUT JUST GETTING THERE IS,
LIKE, HARD.
>> RIGHT.
>> LET'S GO TRY DRESSES ON
NOW, BECAUSE--
>> YOU MEAN ME GO TRY
DRESSES ON?
>> YEAH.
>> ISN'T IT PRETTY?
>> OHH.
>> HOW WEIRD.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
>> I'VE GOT TO GO TO WORK, MACI.
>> OKAY.
WELL, I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO TAKE IT OFF.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT AFTER BENTLEY WAS BORN,
MACI AND RYAN'S RELATIONSHIP
GOT ONLY ROCKIER, AND MONEY
STARTED GETTING EVEN TIGHTER.
>> HELLO, FAT BOY.
SO I CALLED THAT COUNTRY CLUB
PLACE IN CLEVELAND THAT ME
AND RYAN WANTED TO GET MARRIED
AT, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> SHE ASKED ME WHAT DATE
WE WERE LOOKING AT, AND I TOLD
HER VALENTINE'S DAY,
AND SHE SAID THAT THEY DON'T
HAVE THAT DAY OPEN, AND
THE NEXT DAY IN FEBRUARY
IS THE 28TH.
>> WELL, WE'VE GOT TO COVER
ALL THE BILLS FROM HIS DELIVERY.
WE'VE GOT CHRISTMAS COMING UP,
YOUR GRADUATION.
>> SO WHEN CAN WE?
>> MAYBE WE COULD JUST MAKE IT
A BEACH WEDDING.
>> THAT WOULD ALMOST BE CHEAPER
THAN A REGULAR WEDDING, THOUGH,
BECAUSE, I MEAN, RYAN COULD WEAR
KHAKIS AND A BUTTON-DOWN,
AND I COULD WEAR, LIKE, A WHITE
SUNDRESS OR SOMETHING AND BE
BAREFOOTED OR WEAR FLIP-FLOPS.
>> I STILL DON'T KNOW IF WE'RE
GONNA HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO
PULL EVERYTHING OFF.
I DON'T KNOW; MAYBE WE NEED TO
PUSH IT ON INTO THE SPRING
SOMEWHERE.
>> THE 14TH IS VALENTINE'S DAY,
AND IT WAS OUR ANNIVERSARY
OR WHATEVER, BUT, UM...
'CAUSE IF WE CAN'T GET THAT
DATE AND WE CAN'T GET IT
ANY EARLIER, THEN THERE'S NO
POINT IN TRYING TO RUSH IT.
>> FARRAH, AS YOU SAW ON THE
SHOW, LOVES THE LIMELIGHT.
IN FACT, SHE'S ALWAYS IMAGINED
SHE'D END UP A MODEL OR EVEN
A BEAUTY QUEEN.
BUT SINGLE MOTHERHOOD IS GOING
TO MAKE IT VERY HARD FOR FARRAH
TO FIND HER WAY BACK
TO THE SPOTLIGHT.
>> I WAS, LIKE, WONDERING IN
DENIAL FOR, LIKE, MAYBE A MONTH.
I WAS JUST QUESTIONING BECAUSE
I NOTICED, LIKE, MY BODY
WAS CHANGING.
>> YEAH.
>> MY FRIEND HILDA AND I WENT
TO PLANNED PARENTHOOD AND GOT
A PREGNANCY TEST.
AND SO, UM, I HAD THAT HAPPEN,
AND THE LADY TOLD ME I WAS
PREGNANT, AND I COMPLETELY WAS
PISSED, AND--
>> DID YOU CRY?
>> NO, I DIDN'T REALLY CRY.
I JUST SCREAMED AT HER,
AND THEN--
>> WHY DID YOU SCREAM AT HER?
IT'S YOUR PROBLEM, NOT HERS.
>> I JUST SCREAMED AT HER,
AND ANYWAYS--
>> DID YOU HAVE A SEX TALK
WITH HER?
DID YOU?
>> NO, SHE WAS TOO SCARED.
>> DID YOU ASK ABOUT IT
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNGER?
>> FARRAH NEVER LISTENS.
SHE NEVER LISTENS.
>> WHAT HURT MORE, KNOWING THAT
YOUR DAUGHTER WAS PREGNANT
OR THAT YOU WERE GONNA BE
A GILF?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT A GILF IS?
>> THE PROBLEM--THE PROBLEM--
>> WHAT'S A GILF?
I WANT TO KNOW.
>> INSTEAD OF A MILF, THINK
ABOUT IT WITH A "G," GRANDMA.
>> GRANDMA I'D LIKE TO...OKAY.
>> THE PROBLEM IS, YOU HAVE
GREAT ASPIRATIONS FOR YOUR
CHILDREN, AND YOU POUR
EVERYTHING INTO THEM, RIGHT?
SO KIND OF THE IRONY: THE DAY
SHE HAD THE BABY...
>> OH, MY GOD, MOM.
>> SHE GOT A LETTER IN THE MAIL
TO BE PART OF THE MISS AMERICA
PAGEANT.
>> OH, WOW.
>> AND I COME HOME, AND THERE'S
THE LETTER, AND, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN'T HELP AS A MOTHER CRY FOR
YOUR CHILD WHEN YOU KNOW THERE'S
SO MUCH--SO MANY THINGS THAT SHE
WILL NOT BE ABLE TO DO.
SO WHAT YOU GOT TO TRY NOW IS TO
REGEAR AND FOCUS ON WHAT CAN SHE
DO, HOW CAN SHE BE
HER ULTIMATE BEST?
>> COMING UP:
>> HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF
A THING CALLED A MUCOUS PLUG?
>> EW.
>> OH, MY GOD, MOM, I HAVE
BLOOD ON MY UNDERWEAR.
>> YOUR CERVIX IS DILATED
TO ONE.
>> WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND
PREGNANT: UNSEEN MOMENTS.
NOW, AS THE GIRLS' BODIES START
TO CHANGE WITH PREGNANCY, WELL,
YOU CAN IMAGINE THE NORMAL
HIGH SCHOOL BANTER BECOMES
A LITTLE LESS THAN NORMAL.
CHECK THIS OUT.
>> IN THE WINTER.
>> WHY?
>> THE DOCTOR SAID THAT
A PREGNANT WOMAN'S TEMPERATURE
IS TEN DEGREES HIGHER.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN SWIM.
REMEMBER, THAT'S, LIKE, ONE OF
THE BEST EXERCISES?
>> PEOPLE DO THAT SOMETIMES.
>> THAT'S PRETTY MESSED UP.
>> AND, LIKE, THE BABY SWIMS,
I HEARD.
>> OOH!
THAT'S NASTY.
>> IT IS WEIRD.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S ONE THING
WHERE GIRLS HAVE A HIDDEN ORGASM
AS THEY'RE GIVING BIRTH.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'D BE KIND OF COOL.
>> YEAH, IT WOULD.
>> FOR YOU GUYS.
OH, THAT PICTURE IN THAT BOOK?
OH, MY GOD.
>> LIKE, TEN CENTIMETERS IS,
LIKE, THIS BIG.
>> OH, GOD!
I NEVER WANT TO SEE ANYTHING
THAT SMALL EVER GET THAT BIG.
>> AND MORNING SICKNESS,
AS AMBER DISCOVERED, WELL,
IT CAN REALLY INTERRUPT
YOUR WEEKEND PLANS.
>> WE'LL PRESS THEM ON A HYDE
PRESS, AND...
>> GO AHEAD; YOU'RE FINE.
>> [retching]
OH, MY GOD, IT'S MAKING ME PUKE.
>> I DON'T KNOW; I THINK--
>> [coughing]
>> HERE WE GO.
>> WHAT'S WORSE THAN MORNING
SICKNESS?
WHITNEY THINKS THERE'S PLENTY.
>> LIKE, IN, LIKE, YOU KNOW HOW
IN MOVIES, LIKE, HOW YOUR WATER
WILL BREAK?
IT JUST ALL SPLASHES OUT.
WELL, IT DOESN'T REALLY HAPPEN
LIKE THAT, USUALLY.
LIKE, IN CERTAIN CASES, IT DOES
BUT USUALLY NOT.
AND THEN A LOT OF TIMES,
YOUR WATER NEVER EVEN BREAKS.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-MM, SO MOST PEOPLE, THEY
HAVE TO--THEY HAVE THIS LONG
LITTLE PLASTIC THING, AND IT
HAS, LIKE, A LITTLE KIND OF HOOK
AT THE END OF IT, AND THEN THEY
STICK IT INSIDE YOU AND BREAK
IT, BUT IT DOESN'T HURT YOU OR
NOTHIN' OR THE BABY.
AND THEY'LL GIVE YOU THE
EPIDURAL, AND, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN'T FEEL NOTHIN' FROM YOUR
WAIST DOWN.
LIKE, IF YOU HAVE GAS, WOULDN'T
THAT BE EMBARRASSIN', LIKE, TO
HAVE GAS IN FRONT OF THE
DOCTORS OR SOMETHIN'?
>> THEY'RE PROBABLY USED TO IT.
>> I KNOW, BUT THAT'D BE
EMBARRASSIN'.
AND THEN YOU'LL HAVE A THING
CALLED A MUCOUS PLUG.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT'S, LIKE, SOMETHING THAT
COMES OUT YOU, AND IT KIND OF
LOOKS LIKE SNOT, AND SOMETIMES
IT HAS BLOOD IN IT.
IT'S REAL NASTY.
>> EW.
I DON'T WANT TO BE
PREGNANT, EVER.
>> OH, MY GOD, MOM, I HAVE BLOOD
ON MY UNDERWEAR.
>> YOU DO?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU HAVE VERY MUCH
OR JUST A LITTLE BIT?
>> IT'S ABOUT LIKE A QUARTER'S
WORTH.
>> IS THERE ANY MUCOUS IN IT?
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT
THE DEFINITION OF IT IS.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, LIKE, YOU
KNOW, LIKE WHEN YOU BLOW YOUR
NOSE, HOW IT LOOKS KIND OF
SNOTTY OR SLIMY?
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
>> OKAY.
WELL, WE'LL CALL THE DOCTOR
AS SOON AS WE GET OUT OF HERE.
>> OKAY.
[toilet flushes]
THIS IS SO UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> THIS IS YOUR FIRST PELVIC.
>> AHH.
>> YOUR CERVIX IS DILATED
TO ONE.
>> OH, THAT'S SUPER.
>> AND YOU CAN FEEL THE HEAD
DOWN.
>> [giggles]
OH, WHAT DOES THAT FEEL LIKE?
>> HARD.
>> HARD?
NASTY.
>> AND YOU CAN ACTUALLY FEEL--
YOU KNOW HOW THE BABY HAS
A SOFT SPOT?
YOU CAN ACTUALLY FEEL THE
SUTURES IN THE LITTLE SOFT SPOT.
>> EW.
THAT'S ENOUGH OF THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ANY MORE.
>> ONCE YOU'RE FOUR,
THEN YOU'LL BE IN LABOR.
>> YEAH.
WOW, SO...
>> MEANWHILE, CATELYNN'S
APPETITE WAS RUNNING
DOUBLE TIME.
>> STILL GET BREAKFAST?
>> YEAH.
I WANT A NUMBER NINE.
>> YOU CAN CALL OUT THE ORDER
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
>> COMES WITH HASH BROWNS.
>> OH, A NUMBER NINE.
>> WITH ORANGE JUICE.
>> $13.36 AT THE WINDOW.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA HAVE YOU
TAKE YOUR SHOES OFF AND STEP
RIGHT UP HERE ON THE SCALE
FOR ME, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
THIS ISN'T THE FUN PART.
>> NO, IT ISN'T.
>> YOUR BLOOD PRESSURE'S GREAT:
126 OVER 60; THAT'S EXCELLENT.
NOW, YOU HAVE GAINED SEVEN
POUNDS SINCE YOUR LAST VISIT,
IN TWO WEEKS.
>> THAT'S SO BAD.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF WEIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU EATING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I USUALLY EAT ANYTHING.
>> ARE YOU DOING A LOT
OF FAST FOOD OR JUNK FOOD?
>> UM, I HAVEN'T ATE A LOT
OF FAST FOOD IN A WHILE.
>> WE JUST HAD MCDONALD'S.
>> YEAH, THIS MORNING I DID.
>> SO BE REAL MINDFUL OF THAT.
>> UH-HUH.
>> 'CAUSE WHATEVER YOU ARE
EATING IS BECOMING THIS BABY.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY?
>> HOW'D IT GO, KID?
>> GOOD.
>> SHE'S JUST GOT TO EAT MORE
TRADITIONAL FOOD,
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT SUPPOSED TO
GAIN AS MUCH WEIGHT AS SHE HAS.
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> I KNOW; IT JUST SUCKS, 'CAUSE
ONCE I GET COMFORTABLE IN MY OWN
SKIN, AND NOW I'M NOT ANYMORE.
>> BABE, YOU'RE GONNA LOSE
ALL THAT.
ALL THE WEIGHT,
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE BACK TO NORMAL.
>> MAYBE; WHO KNOWS?
>> YOU WILL.
>> JUST SUCKS.
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
>> [laughs]
>> DAD, SHE'S UPSET.
>> WELL, WHAT DID YOU EXPECT,
TO BE SKINNY AND PREGNANT
AT THE SAME TIME?
>> STOP! STOP!
THEY'RE WAITING FOR ME-UH!
LEARN HOW TO DRIVE.
>> I HAVE A BASSINET; I HAVE
CLOTHES AT MY HOUSE, 'CAUSE SHE
TOLD ME SHE WAS KEEPIN' HER.
>> MY MOM JUST SAID SHE'S NOT
SIGNING ANYTHING.
>> I'M NOT SIGNING NOTHIN'.
>> AND WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND
PREGNANT: THE UNSEEN MOMENTS
FROM SEASON ONE.
I'M DR. DREW.
NOW, YOU ALL SAW IN FARRAH'S
EPISODE A DRAMATIC CAR RIDE
WITH HER MOM.
NOW TAKE A LOOK AT THE CAR RIDE
WITH HER DAD.
>> GONNA DROP YOU OFF NOW,
PICK YOU UP AT WHAT TIME,
3:30, AT WILSON?
>> AT WILSON; THEN YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE ME TO...
>> TJ'S?
>> TJ'S AND MEET UP WITH MOM.
STOP! STOP!
>> I HAVE TO--
>> STOP!
>> I'M GOING TO, BUT I'M GONNA
DO IT LEGALLY, FARRAH.
>> THEY'RE RIGHT THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T STOP IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE ROAD, FARRAH.
>> YOU CAN-UH.
>> FARRAH.
>> OKAY, GO BEFORE THEY GO,
BECAUSE I HAVE TO MEET UP
WITH THEM.
THEY'RE WAITING FOR ME-UH!
LEARN HOW TO DRIVE.
>> I KNOW HOW TO DRIVE, FARRAH.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> I DO KNOW ONE THING:
YOU BE CAREFUL.
>> I PLAN TO BE, NOT LIKE YOU,
WHO DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO DRIVE.
>> HURRY UP, AND BE CAREFUL.
[sighs]
>> BUT HERE'S THE FLIP SIDE:
PARENTS BEHAVING BADLY.
HERE'S THE BABY SHOWER YOU
DIDN'T SEE, AS EBONY, IN THE
FINAL WEEKS OF HER PREGNANCY,
WAITS FOR HER MOTHER,
WHO PROMISED SHE'D BE THERE.
>> YOUR MOM'S COMING?
>> MM-HMM.
SHE'S JUST GONNA BE LATE.
I'M GONNA CALL MY MOM REAL QUICK
AND CHECK UP ON HER.
>> WHAT?
>> ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT? YES, NO?
>> HUH?
YOU'RE ALMOST DONE, BUT YOU
DON'T THINK SO, MOM?
THE BABY SHOWER STARTED LATE
ANYWAY, SO WE'RE JUST PLAYING
THE GAMES NOW, AND--
ALL RIGHTY, THEN.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> BYE.
>> AWW.
>> OHH.
[laughter]
>> THANK YOU FOR
ALL THE DIAPERS.
[laughter]
>> IT WENT GOOD.
I'M GONNA BE BRINGING THE BABY
GIFTS BACK OVER THERE LATER ON
TONIGHT, SO...YOU KNOW.
>> IT'S OKAY.
BYE.
[whispers] IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> SO IS YOUR MOM HOME NOW, HON?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT TIME DOES SHE GET OFF?
>> 8-SOMETHING.
THEN SHE HAD TO GO HOME
AND TAKE A SHOWER AND...
SO SHE COULDN'T MAKE IT.
SO IT'S COOL.
>> IT'LL BE OKAY.
>> AS YOU ALL KNOW, CATELYNN'S
MOM, APRIL, REFUSED TO SIGN
THE ADOPTION PAPERWORK
AT THE HOSPITAL.
NOW, OBVIOUSLY TOUGH CALLS LIKE
AN ADOPTION CAN HIT THE ENTIRE
FAMILY, AND IT'S ESPECIALLY
ROUGH GOING WHEN MOM AND
MOM-TO-BE DON'T SEE EYE TO EYE.
HERE'S HOW THAT ONE PLAYED OUT.
>> HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
HE'S LIKE...
>> OOP, BE CAREFUL.
GOT TO BE REALLY NICE
AND GENTLE.
>> WHY PUT HER NAME ON THERE
ALREADY?
SHE AIN'T ADOPTED YET.
>> NO, 'CAUSE WE HAD TO HAVE
A NAME FOR HER BIRTH
CERTIFICATE.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT NAME.
>> NO, STOP.
>> HI.
HEY, UM, NURSE, HI.
I'M DAWN; I'M THE SOCIAL WORKER.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> I NEED TO KEEP APRIL HERE FOR
A FEW MINUTES TO DO THE LEGAL
PAPERWORK.
WOULD YOU BE OPPOSED TO NICHOLAS
STAYING FOR THE NEXT, LIKE, 15,
20 MINUTES WHILE I COMPLETE
SOME PAPERWORK?
>> OH, OKAY.
>> 'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
WE NEED TO DO.
>> MY MOM'S JUST LIKE--
SHE'S NOT SIGNING ANYTHING.
>> YOU NEED TO SIGN--
>> LATER, BABE.
>> I'LL SEE YA.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WAS AFRAID OF.
>> SHE WASN'T GONNA SIGN
ANYTHING FROM THE START.
>> OKAY.
>> DIDN'T NEED ME TO GET
THE ADOPTION GOING, DIDN'T NEED
ME TO HELP PICK OUT THE PARENTS.
YOU DON'T NEED ME
TO SIGN THE PAPERS.
>> BUT YOU'RE FEELING LIKE SHE'S
JUST NOT GONNA SIGN.
SHE'S NOT GONNA WITNESS
ANYTHING.
>> NO.
NOPE, SHE WANTS NOTHIN'
TO DO WITH IT, SO...
>> OKAY.
I'LL JUST RIDE DOWN
WITH YOU GUYS.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> JESUS.
>> YOU'RE NOT COMFORTABLE
SIGNING ANYTHING.
>> YOU GUYS HAD NO PROBLEM
DOING EVERYTHING WITHOUT ME.
WHY DO YOU WANT TO INVOLVE ME
NOW?
SHE WAS 16 WHEN YOU STARTED
TALKING TO HER.
>> IF YOU'RE NOT COMFORTABLE
SIGNING SOMETHING TODAY,
WE DON'T NEED TO.
>> NO, I'M NOT SIGNING ANYTHING.
>> OKAY.
[indistinct speech]
COULD WE SIT DOWN OVER HERE
JUST FOR ONE MINUTE
SO I CAN EXPLAIN TO YOU?
OKAY.
UM, WELL, ESSENTIALLY,
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT THE KIDS
ARE GOING TO BE DOING TODAY.
IT WOULD BE--YOU KNOW, RIGHT
NOW, THEY HAVE PHYSICAL CUSTODY
OF THE BABY.
AND WHAT THEY WOULD BE DOING IS
TRANSFERRING PHYSICAL CUSTODY
FROM THEM TO AN ADOPTIVE FAMILY.
>> AS A GRANDPARENT,
I HAVE NO RIGHTS.
>> YEAH, UNFORTUNATELY,
IN MICHIGAN, THAT IS THE CASE.
UM, AND I KNOW THAT THAT SEEMS
VERY HURTFUL, BUT WHAT YOU DO--
WHAT YOU DO HAVE A RIGHT TO IS
THAT CATELYNN HAS ALLOWED YOU
TO HAVE INFORMATION ABOUT THE
ADOPTIVE FAMILY AND TO GET TO
KNOW THEM AND MEET THEM AND TO
HAVE ONGOING COMMUNICATION
WITH THEM.
I THINK THAT CATELYNN WOULD
REALLY, REALLY APPRECIATE
YOUR SUPPORT.
CATELYNN.
>> WOULDN'T KNOW IT BY THE WAY
CATELYNN ACTS, SO...
>> HI.
IT'S OKAY.
>> I WAS JUST TELLING YOUR MOM
THAT I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
APPRECIATE HER SUPPORT IN HER
JUST BEING THERE TO HEAR WHAT IT
IS THAT YOU GUYS WERE SIGNING
TODAY.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> LAST WEEK SHE WAS KEEPING
THE BABY.
THIS WEEK SHE'S NOT.
SO YOU KNOW, HOW AM
I SUPPOSED TO FEEL?
>> SO IT'S--YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'VE
HAD SOME CONFLICTING MESSAGES.
>> YES, I HAVE.
I HAVE A BASSINET; I HAVE
CLOTHES AT MY HOUSE BECAUSE SHE
TOLD ME SHE WAS KEEPING HER.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I FEEL SHE'S GIVING HER
UP BECAUSE OF TYLER, AND THAT'S
MY HONEST, TRUE FEELING.
>> BUT IT'S NOT.
>> WELL, THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
I GOTTA GO.
I'M NOT SIGNING ANYTHING.
>> OKAY.
>> UP NEXT, EVEN MORE REVEALING
UNSEEN MOMENTS FROM SEASON ONE
OF 16 AND PREGNANT.
>> WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND
PREGNANT: UNSEEN MOMENTS.
HERE NOW IS A TENSE MOMENT
FROM AMBER'S STORY.
YOU ALL REMEMBER GARY.
WELL, BEFORE HE RETURNED
THE PRICEY VIDEOGAME CONSOLE
TO THE STORE, BEFORE THE PINK
SAPPHIRE ENGAGEMENT RING,
GARY WAS IN FACT THE BOYFRIEND
IN THE DOGHOUSE.
THROUGHOUT SEASON ONE, THE GIRLS
KEPT THEIR OWN VIDEO DIARIES
WHEN THE CAMERA CREWS COULDN'T
BE WITH THEM, SO HERE NOW IS
A LOOK AT AMBER AS SHE LET US IN
ON HER PRIVATE THOUGHTS
ON A RELATIONSHIP IN CRISIS.
>> I MIGHT CALL MY MOM LATER ON,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO LIVE
HERE NO MORE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK
HE UNDERSTANDS EXACTLY
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE OUT THERE
WHO HAVE GOOD PREGNANCIES, YOU
KNOW, AND THEY GET SICK A LITTLE
BIT, AND THEN THEY STOP GETTING
SICK, AND THEN THEY GET SICK
A LITTLE BIT, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S HOW MOST PREGNANCIES ARE.
AND THEN YOU GOT SOME WHO ARE
REALLY BAD.
THEY GET SICK EVERY DAY.
YOU KNOW, IT MAKES ME FEEL BAD,
YOU KNOW, LIKE I'M A BURDEN
TO HIM.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR THREE
YEARS, AND HE'S LOSING, LIKE,
DESIRE OR SOMETHING.
I NEED SOMEBODY THERE FOR ME,
AND MY OLD MAN ISN'T EVEN THERE
FOR ME, SO...
YOU KNOW, HE WAS JUST LIKE--
HE WAS, LIKE, A CHRISTIAN BOY.
THAT'S HOW HE WAS RAISED,
WHICH REALLY--THAT'S ONE THING
THAT TURNED ME ON ABOUT HIM,
'CAUSE JUST, LIKE, HE HAD
MANNERS.
THAT WAS WHEN HE WAS SWEET.
>> ROMANTIC.
>> I THINK MAYBE HE'S ACTING OUT
RIGHT NOW BECAUSE HE MIGHT BE
SCARED HAVING THIS BABY, LIKE
HIS LIFE IS RUINED OR SOMETHING
OR--I THINK IT MIGHT BE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> SO AREN'T YOU GOING
TO GET MARRIED?
>> I DON'T--WHY WOULD I GET
MARRIED WITH HIM ANY TIME SOON?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW IF I WANT
TO BE WITH HIM FOR HOW HE'S
ACTING.
IF HE GOES BACK TO THE OLD GARY,
WHICH I WANT, THEN I WILL
MARRY HIM.
>> OF COURSE, FOR CATELYNN,
THE STABLE RELATIONSHIP WAS
THE EASY PART.
SHE AND HER BOYFRIEND, TYLER,
WERE UP AGAINST EVERYTHING
TOGETHER.
ULTIMATELY THEY DID CHOOSE
ADOPTION, BUT MAKING THAT TOUGH
CALL MEANT WRESTLING WITH
CONSTANT DOUBTS.
HERE CATELYNN TURNS FOR ADVICE
TO TYLER'S SISTER, AMBER,
HERSELF A TEENAGE MOM
WHO ONCE CONSIDERED ADOPTION.
>> WHEN I WAS GONNA GIVE
RIGHTEOUS UP, THE ADOPTIVE
PARENTS WERE THERE WITH THEIR
OWN ROOM AND THE CAR SEAT
AND TALKING ABOUT THE NURSERY
THEY GOT FOR HER; THEY JUST
GOT DONE WITH IT.
I WAS LIKE, "OH, SWEETIE,
SWEETIE," I MEAN, I DIDN'T HAVE
NO PLAN "B" OR ANYTHING, AND
THEN MATT WAS JUST LIKE,
"NO, JUST KEEP HER."
AND I WAS LIKE, "DUDE,
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?"
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, I WAS--I WAS ACTUALLY
SCARED, EVEN THOUGH I KNEW HE
HAD A JOB AND HE'D BE ABLE TO
TAKE CARE OF HER, BUT...
>> SO HAVE YOU AND TYLER--
YOU GUYS ARE 100% SURE
ON THE ADOPTION?
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T KNOW IF
TYLER TOLD YOU; DID HE?
TYLER, LIKE, FELL BACK ON IT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
>> YEAH, HE TOLD ME
A LITTLE BIT.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS BAD.
>> WHAT DID YOU--WHAT--
>> WHY WERE YOU MAD?
>> I WASN'T MAD;
I JUST WANTED TO KEEP HER.
>> WELL, YEAH.
THAT'S ONLY NATURAL.
>> FOR, LIKE, A COUPLE DAYS,
I WAS LIKE, "NOPE, I'M KEEPING
HER; THAT'S IT."
I WAS LIKE, "NOPE.
THERE'S NO WAY.
I'M NOT GOING BACK."
>> DOES IT MAKE YOU WANT TO GIVE
HER UP SO YOU CAN BE WITH MY
BROTHER OR...
>> I MEAN, NO, I MEAN, I
WOULDN'T WANT YOUR BROTHER TO
LEAVE ME, BUT I MEAN, IF HE DID,
THEN THERE'S NOTHING I COULD DO
ABOUT IT ANYWAYS.
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
HE DOESN'T REALLY SAY TOO MUCH
ABOUT THAT.
>> YEAH.
TO ME, HE'S JUST LIKE, "I THINK
WE'D BREAK UP JUST BECAUSE
OF ALL THE STRESS AND JUST
LIKE"...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DID HE EVER HAVE
SECOND THOUGHTS?
>> YEAH, TYLER, HE DOES.
HE DOES A LOT, ACTUALLY, BUT
HE JUST BRINGS HIMSELF BACK.
>> YES.
IT'S A LOT MORE THAN JUST
KEEPING HER, YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S JUST GONNA BE HARD.
>> I KNOW; IT'S GONNA BE
REALLY HARD.
>> BUT YOU DO WHAT YOUR HEART
TELLS YOU.
>> I KNOW.
>> COMING UP...
>> I JUST FEEL REALLY DIZZY
RIGHT NOW.
OH, GOD, I CAN'T STAND IT.
>> CAN YOU TAKE US
TO THE DOCTOR?
WINSTON'S SICK.
>> AND WELCOME BACK TO
16 AND PREGNANT:
THE UNSEEN MOMENTS.
I'M DR. DREW.
NOW, THERE WAS A BIG HEALTH
SCARE FOR AMBER, AND IT'S
SOMETHING THAT ALSO AFFECTS
135,000 AMERICAN MOMS
EVERY YEAR.
IT'S CALLED GESTATIONAL
DIABETES.
BY MONTH SEVEN, AMBER WAS
THROWING UP ALMOST EVERY DAY
BUT STILL EATING BADLY.
>> ON THE NUMBER FOUR, DO I GET
TWO SIDES WITH THAT?
LIKE, I WANTED COLE SLAW
AND MASHED POTATOES AND GRAVY
WITH IT.
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> YEAH, COULD WE GET A NACHO
CHEESE WITH MEAT AND TWO
CHILI DOGS?
THAT'S IT.
OH, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DRINK?
>> AND A GATORADE.
WHAT KIND OF GATORADE
DO YOU HAVE?
I'M JUST REALLY DIZZY
RIGHT NOW.
>> TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> I DON'T KNOW; I'M JUST
PUKING AND...I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE ANYTHING
IN MY STOMACH, YET I FEEL LIKE
I WAS STILL, LIKE, PUKING.
>> I THINK PROBABLY WHAT'S GONNA
BE BEST IS TO JUST STAY AWAY
FROM ANYTHING WITH SUGAR,
'CAUSE I SEE FROM YOUR CHART
THAT IT SAYS THEY THINK YOU
MIGHT HAVE GESTATIONAL DIABETES?
>> MM-HMM.
[coughing]
[spitting]
OH, GOD, I CAN'T STAND IT.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO AHEAD
AND GET IN LINE SO WE CAN GET
YOUR BLOOD TEST, BABY?
WANT TO WAIT A SECOND?
YOU'RE OKAY, SWEETIE.
>> JUST LAYING DOWN.
WHERE'S AMBER AT?
>> WE'RE OVER AT COMMUNITY.
WE'RE--WE'RE DOING A BLOOD TEST,
SO SHE'S LAYING DOWN RIGHT NOW,
WAITING FOR AN HOUR
TO DO THE BLOOD TEST.
>> I HOPE I DON'T HAVE DIABETES
LIKE MY MOM DID.
>> YOU'RE FINE, BABE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
>> FEELING OKAY?
>> YEAH.
I'VE BEEN ... ALL DAY.
>> GOOD.
>> AND YOU'RE FINISHED.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> AMBER.
>> SHE'S CHECKING TO SEE IF
YOUR BLOOD TESTS ARE IN.
>> OH, MAN, I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR IT.
I'M NOT TAKING INSULIN.
>> WELL, IF THEY MAKE YOU TAKE
INSULIN OR IF YOU HAVE TO,
YOU HAVE TO TAKE IT.
>> YOU KNOW I DON'T EAT BAD,
THOUGH.
>> IT DON'T MATTER.
YOU COULD EAT THE SMALLEST THING
THAT HAS SUGAR,
AND IT COULD REACT.
IT DON'T MATTER.
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
YOUR GLUCOSE TEST WAS 148, OKAY?
NOW, OUR CUTOFF IS 140.
>> ONCE AMBER FOUND OUT THAT
SHE DID HAVE DIABETES,
TREATMENT NEEDED TO START
IMMEDIATELY.
THIS MEANT DITCHING HER BAD DIET
AND TESTING HER BLOOD SUGAR
FOUR TIMES A DAY.
>> ARE YOU SHOOTING UP AGAIN?
>> 89; THAT'S GOOD.
>> THIS AIN'T THAT GOOD,
SO DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
>> SHUT UP; IT LOOKS GOOD.
I KNOW IT'S GOOD.
CAN'T LIE TO ME.
>> IT'S ACTUALLY DELICIOUS,
BUT...
>> I'M SURE THIS WILL BE GOOD
TOO.
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT KIND OF LEAF WAS THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHY? WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
>> GUT HURT.
NOW I ATE ONE OF THESE THINGIES.
>> TAKE THOSE OUT.
>> IT MADE ME, LIKE--
WHAT IS THAT?
>> GRASS CLIPPINGS.
>> THAT WAS GROSS.
CAN YOU GO GET ONE MORE THING
OF RANCH?
PLEASE?
>> YEAH, TOTALLY.
>> AS A PARENT, ALL YOU CAN
HOPE FOR IS A HEALTHY BABY.
UNFORTUNATELY ONLY A FEW DAYS
AFTER RETURNING HOME FROM
THE HOSPITAL, WHITNEY FOUND
HERSELF IN A VERY SCARY
SITUATION WHEN BABY WESTON
SUDDENLY COULDN'T KEEP
ANY FOOD DOWN.
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
>> CAN YOU TAKE US
TO THE DOCTOR?
>> TO THE DOCTOR?
>> YEAH.
>> WE THINK WESTON'S SICK.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> HE'S LOSING WEIGHT,
AND HIS EYES ARE REAL DARK,
AND HE'S STILL SPITTING UP,
NOT TAKING--
>> OH, HE IS?
>> YEAH.
>> DID YOU CALL
THE DOCTOR'S OFFICE?
>> I THINK WHITNEY'S ABOUT TO.
SHE'S GETTING THE NUMBER
RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY, CALL THEM, AND THEN
CALL ME BACK, OKAY?
>> OKAY, JUST GET READY.
>> OKAY, I WILL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU. BYE.
SHE SAID CALL THE DOCTOR'S
OFFICE, THEN CALL HER BACK.
>> IF YOU'RE CALLING TO SPEAK
WITH A NURSE, PLEASE...
[Whitney sniffles]
UM, YES, MY LITTLE
THREE-WEEK-OLD SON, HE'S SICK,
AND HE'S THROWING UP, AND I WAS
WONDERING IF I COULD BRING HIM
IN TODAY.
>> YOUR CALL WILL BE ANSWERED
IN THE ORDER IN WHICH IT WAS
RECEIVED.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST [bleep] STUPID.
>> LET'S GET READY, AND IF
ANYTHING ELSE, WE'LL JUST GO
UP THERE.
AT LEAST IF WE GO UP THERE,
WE CAN TALK TO SOMEBODY
AND NOT A RECORDING.
>> BABY WESTON HAS SINCE BEEN
DIAGNOSED WITH ALPHA 1
ANTITRYPSIN DEFICIENCY.
NOW, THIS IS A LIFELONG
GENETIC DISORDER.
IT AFFECTS THE LIVER AND
THE LUNGS, BUT WHAT DOES IT
REALLY MEAN?
WELL, IT MEANS BABY WESTON
SHOULD NEVER BE AROUND CIGARETTE
SMOKE, HE CAN NEVER DRINK EVEN A
DROP OF ALCOHOL, AND HE CAN'T
PLAY CONTACT SPORTS OR
ROUGHHOUSE LIKE A TYPICAL KID.
AND FOR PARENTS WESTON AND
WHITNEY, IT'LL TAKE A WHOLE LOT
OF INNER STRENGTH.
COMING UP...
>> WHERE ARE THE MATERNITY
COSTUMES?
OH, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> WHY ARE YOU BEING NICE?
>> HI, I'M DR. DREW.
WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND PREGNANT:
UNSEEN MOMENTS.
THROUGHOUT SEASON ONE, WE
WATCHED AS OUR TEEN MOMS
STRUGGLED IN THEIR
RELATIONSHIPS.
AND WHILE THE DADS SOMETIMES
MADE THEM AND THEIR FAMILIES
CRAZY, THEY ALSO MADE THEM
LAUGH.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS SCENE WITH
MACI, RYAN, AND THEIR FRIENDS.
>> WHAT ARE Y'ALL GONNA BE
FOR HALLOWEEN?
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA BE?
>> A GANGSTER.
>> OH, MY GOD, LOOK.
>> THERE'S A BABY?
>> THAT IS BENTLEY'S FRIEND.
>> EWW.
THAT'S NOT RYAN.
>> HOW STUPID DO THESE LOOK?
I WAS THE SLUTTY COP
LAST YEAR.
WHERE ARE THE MATERNITY
COSTUMES?
>> THEY GOT BIG TITTIES
OVER THERE.
WELL, THEY DO.
>> SHUT UP.
>> COME HERE.
HOLY [bleep].
IS SHE GONNA PUT HER DAMN HEAD
BACK ON?
>> RYAN, WHY'D YOU PICK
THAT UP?
>> DO YOU WANT IT NOW?
>> YES, WE'RE TRYING IT ON.
[laughs]
>> WHY DO THE PLUGS
LOOK LIKE THAT?
>> I HAD A BIRTH DEFECT.
>> A BIRTH DEFECT.
>> EW, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> NO.
>> GROSS.
>> GO GET ME SOME NYLON SOCKS.
>> AS JOSH LEARNS, FATHERHOOD
DEMANDS PATIENCE, SELFLESSNESS,
AND A TALENT FOR...
PRODUCT ASSEMBLY?
>> [grunts]
>> AND IT'S RIGHT--JOSH.
>> WHAT?
>> SEE THE SIGN?
IT'S RIGHT ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE SIGN.
I HOPE YOU KNOW HOW TO DO THIS,
'CAUSE IT'S--
>> I KNOW; I HOPE THERE'S
INSTRUCTIONS, THOUGH.
>> CAN YOU FOLLOW THEM?
>> "LAP BELT." HOLD ON.
THIS GOES THIS WAY.
WELL, THEN, NOW I CAN'T SEE
THE INSTRUCTIONS.
[sighs]
WELL, THAT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE AT ALL.
>> OKAY, THEN MOVE.
>> NOPE, DON'T MAKE NO SENSE
TO ME AT ALL.
>> SERIOUSLY, JOSHUA?
>> SERIOUSLY, MOTHER.
>> WHY INSERT--
>> WELL, YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN
THAT ONE TO ME?
>> [laughing]
NO, 'CAUSE THE BOTTOM PART'S
NOT OUT.
>> YEAH, SERIOUSLY,
DO YOU GET IT?
>> SERIOUSLY, HOLD THIS.
THE BOTTOM BELT'S NOT OUT.
>> "DO NOT USE AFTER
DECEMBER 2011."
>> OKAY, WELL, IT'S NOT 2011,
DADDY.
>> WE GOT TO GET A NEW CAR SEAT
AFTER 2011?
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BUY
A LOT OF THINGS AFTER--
>> THAT'S RETARDED, THOUGH.
I MEAN--
>> WHEN DOES SHE TURN 18?
>> IN 18 YEARS.
>> SO...
UM...
GO THERE.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO DO.
[laughing]
>> THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
>> LET ME LOOK AT IT AGAIN.
>> I THINK IT'S GOOD.
JUST DON'T GET IN A CAR WRECK,
'CAUSE IF WE ROLL...
>> JOSHUA, GET OUT OF THE WAY.
DON'T YOU EVER PUT HER IN A CAR
WITHOUT A CAR SEAT.
>> WELL, DUH.
>> I'LL BEAT YOU.
YOU'LL BE GROUNDED FOR LIFE.
>> WHY WOULD I NOT PUT HER
IN THE CAR WITH A CAR SEAT?
>> JOSHUA, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE 18, AND SOMETIMES THIS
NOGGIN DOESN'T ALWAYS WORK.
>> NEITHER DOES YOURS, AND IT'S,
WHAT, 50,000 YEARS OLD?
JUST KIDDING.
LET'S GO.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT?
>> WE NEED TO GET SOMEBODY TO
COME DOWN AND CHECK THE CAR
SEAT, THOUGH, TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE DID IT RIGHT.
>> WHAT ALL DO YOU NEED DONE
THAT I CAN DO FOR YOU?
HERE YOU GO.
THAT'S YOUR CHAIR TO PUT
YOUR FEET UP ON.
>> WHY ARE YOU BEING NICE?
>> DON'T QUESTION IT.
I'LL BE AN [bleep]
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
>> A FEW WEEKS INTO LIFE
WITH THE BABY, EBONY WAS HAPPY
TO SEE THE FIRST SIGNS
OF A NEW JOSH.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> I GOT YOU SOME WATER,
IF YOU'RE THIRSTY.
>> WHY, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
CAN WE HAVE HER SWING
OUT HERE?
>> IT WON'T SWING ANYMORE.
>> THE SWING WAS HER FAVORITE.
OKAY, CLOSE YOUR EYES.
PUT THE BLANKET OVER YOUR FACE.
NO, ALL THE WAY OVER.
NO PEEKING.
>> I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU CAN PEEK.
YOU'RE GONNA PEEK.
YOU'RE GONNA TRY TO PEEK.
YOU ARE GONNA PEEK.
OKAY.
>> REALLY?
GOOD IDEA.
THIS IS AWESOME.
THANKS FOR FIXING HER SWING.
>> SEE?
HERE, I CAN BE OVER HERE
AND, LIKE, DRINKING AND JUST...
>> AND WORKING OUT, HUH?
>> RIGHT.
>> COMING UP...
>> NO, I'M NOT HAVING DOUBTS.
I'M WONDERING IF YOU'RE
HAVING DOUBTS.
>> I JUST WANTED TO SAY
GOOD-BYE.
>> I'M DR. DREW.
WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND PREGNANT:
UNSEEN MOMENTS.
KIND OF HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
AFTER NINE MONTHS OF WAITING,
WORRYING, BREAK-UPS, AND
BREAKDOWNS, OUR GIRLS, WELL,
THEY STILL HAD LABOR ITSELF
TO GET THROUGH.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AS THE GIRLS
PREPARE FOR INCREDIBLE PAIN
AND THE GNARLY LABOR DAY
SURPRISES.
>> MAMA, YOU KNOW THE UMBILICAL
CORD ON THE BABY'S BELLY
AFTER YOU HAVE THE BABY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW LONG DOES THAT
STAY ON THERE?
>> A COUPLE WEEKS.
IT'LL FALL OFF ON ITS OWN.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP VASELINE
ON IT.
I WOKE UP, AND YOURS WAS
RIGHT THERE.
MM, IT WAS RIGHT THERE
IN MY FACE.
>> [snickers]
>> WESTON GETS TO CLIP IT,
CUT IT, PUT A LITTLE THING
ON IT.
MM-HMM.
>> WELL, GUESS WHAT, YOU GUYS?
YOU'RE GONNA SEE A LIVE BIRTH
TODAY.
>> OHH.
>> OH, GREAT.
>> ARE YOU READY FOR THAT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE IT.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE IT?
>> HE'LL BE FINE.
HE'LL BE FINE.
>> IT'LL BE OKAY.
IT REALLY WILL HELP YOU GET
PREPARED FOR WHEN YOUR BABY
COMES.
>> THE BOTTOM OF YOUR UTERUS
IS YOUR CERVIX.
PRIOR TO LABOR, A MUCOUS PLUG
BLOCKS THE CERVICAL OPENING.
>> THAT'S NASTY.
>> BUT WHEN THE BABY'S
GONNA COME...
>> THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> [giggles]
>> OHH.
>> CAN I PUSH?
>> PUSH.
[baby cries]
>> LOOK. IT'S A BOY.
>> OOH.
OH, GOOD.
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO SEE THAT NOW.
THAT IS SO NASTY.
UGH.
>> YOU'LL THEN PUSH OUT
THE PLACENTA.
>> both: EWW.
>> PRETTY COOL HOW IT ALL
WORKS, HUH?
>> THAT WAS...
>> EWW.
>> DIFFERENT,
DISGUSTING, DISTURBING.
>> HEY, HOW'D IT GO?
>> EVERYTHING I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
>> DID YOU DO OKAY?
>> YEAH.
HE'S FINE.
>> YOU SAID IT WAS WORSE
THAN YOU THOUGHT IT'S BE?
>> NO, IT WAS EXACTLY WHAT
I THOUGHT IT'D BE: GROSS.
>> EXACTLY.
OKAY, BUT YOU'RE GONNA BE ABLE
TO DO IT, HUH, SO YOU CAN BE
GOOD SUPPORT FOR EBONY?
>> YEAH, I'M JUST GONNA STAY
LOOKING AT HER FACE.
>> GOOD, STAY FOCUSED.
THE MORE YOU SEE IT AND GET
EXPOSED, THE BETTER SUPPORT
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO BE TO EBONY.
>> WHILE MOST OF THE GIRLS ARE
FOCUSED ON GETTING READY FOR THE
HOSPITAL STAY, FARRAH DISTRACTS
HERSELF WITH SOME INTERNET
SHOPPING.
>> WHAT'S THE WEBSITE
THAT WE NEED HERE?
>> I THINK IT'S JUST BABIESRUS.
HOLD ON.
I THOUGHT IT WAS IN HERE.
>> OH, SEE?
NOW, THAT'S WHAT YOU WERE
TALKING ABOUT, THE CAR SEAT
AND ALL THAT--STROLLER--
ALL FIT TOGETHER.
>> BUT I WANT THAT
IN A DIFFERENT COLOR.
I DON'T WANT IT THAT COLOR.
>> THERE'S THE KIND--
THIS IS THE KIND YOU HAD.
YOU HAD THIS GRACO.
>> MOM, I'M NOT PUTTING
WHAT YOU WANT ON IT.
IT'S NOT YOURS.
NOT THAT COLOR, MOM.
EWW.
>> BUTT PASTE?
OH, MY GOD.
>> ADD THAT TO IT.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> SO YOUR BABY'S BUTT'S GOOD.
>> BOUDREAUX'S BABY BUTT PASTE.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THAT BEFORE.
OH, MY GOD.
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE WEIRD.
>> WHERE'S THE EXPLANATION
OF THESE PRODUCTS?
>> I DON'T KNOW, MOM,
BUT THEY HAVE TO HAVE IT.
>> SO DO THE GIRLS KNOW THAT
YOU'RE THINKING ABUT HAVING
THE BABY WITHOUT ANY PAIN
MEDICATION?
>> OH, WITH NO EPIDURAL.
YEAH, WE TALKED ABOUT IT
LAST NIGHT.
THEY'RE ALL LIKE, "WHAT?"
>> DID YOU DO THAT?
>> ARE YOU CRAZY?
>> NO.
[laughter]
>> SHE WAS LIKE, "IT MAKES
YOUR LEGS GO NUMB."
I WAS LIKE, "I'LL BE LAYING HERE
FOR A LONG TIME.
IT WOULD NOT EVEN MATTER TO ME."
>> NOW IT'S THE FACT THAT IT
REALLY DOES FREAK ME OUT
TO HAVE MY LEGS NUMBED.
>> ISN'T IT, LIKE,
A HUGE NEEDLE?
>> IN YOUR BACK.
>> YES.
>> OH, I WOULD TAKE IT
IN A HEARTBEAT.
>> IF I'M, LIKE, IN LABOR, AND
IT'S, LIKE, SUCKING, AND I'M,
LIKE, DYING OF PAIN, I MEAN,
I MIGHT JUST BE HURTING SO BAD
THAT I'M JUST LIKE,
"GIVE IT TO ME," AND I'M NOT
EVEN GONNA THINK ABOUT THE FACT
THAT IT FREAKS ME OUT.
I'M GONNA BE LIKE,
"GOD, THIS HURTS."
>> SHE'S GOT AN ATTITUDE.
>> SHE'S MENTALLY PREPARED.
>> I AM.
IN MY HEAD, I'M LIKE, NO,
NO EPIDURAL.
>> THEY KNEW IT WOULD BE TOUGH,
BUT EVEN AFTER REHEARSING
FOR THE BIG DAY FOR MONTHS,
WHEN CATELYNN GAVE BIRTH, SHE
AND TYLER FOUND THEMSELVES
TOTALLY OVERWHELMED BY
THE REALITY OF PARTING
WITH BABY CARLY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING, TY?
>> DO YOU STILL WANT FOR SURE
TO DO THIS?
>> YEAH.
WHY, ARE YOU IN DOUBTS OF ME?
>> NO, I'M NOT HAVING DOUBTS.
I'M WONDERING IF YOU'RE
HAVING DOUBTS.
>> NO, I SAID ARE YOU HAVING
DOUBTS ON ME?
>> DOUBTS ON YOU?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
DOUBTS ON YOU?
OH, AM I DOUBTING YOU; I DON'T
THINK YOU'LL BE ABLE TO DO IT?
>> YEAH.
>> NO, I KNOW YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO DO IT.
>> I'M DOING IT.
IT'S JUST, I WANT TO SEE HER.
THAT'S NOT LIKE...
>> OKAY, I'M JUST ASKING.
>> I WANT TO BE ABLE TO SPEND
AS MUCH TIME WITH HER AS I CAN.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW IF SEEING
HER SO MUCH IS GONNA BE
A DESTRUCTIVE THING TOWARDS YOU,
OR IS IT GONNA BE A [...] THING
TOWARDS YOU?
>> I'M LEAVING WITHOUT HER.
IT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO DO.
>> YUP.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
>> WHAT?
>> [sniffs]
>> YOU WANT TO SAY GOOD-BYE?
>> UH-HUH.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT GONNA BE
GOOD-BYE FOREVER.
>> IT'S STILL HARD, THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
>> OKAY.
HI, BENTLEY.
UM, IT'S MACI.
I'M YOUR MOM...OR ABOUT TO BE
OR I ALREADY AM.
UM, YOU HAVE SIX WEEKS ALMOST
UNTIL YOU'RE HERE,
AND I'M VERY EXCITED.
I'M FINALLY GETTING OVER
MY NERVOUSNESS.
I'M READY FOR YOU TO BE HERE.
I WANT TO PLAY WITH YOU.
UM, I JUST TURNED 17
ABOUT A MONTH AGO,
SO IT'S BEEN PRETTY ROUGH,
BUT IT'S TURNING OUT BETTER
THAN I EXPECTED.
BUT I HAVE TO GO TO BED NOW.
HURRY UP AND GET HERE BECAUSE,
WELL, FOR ONE, I'M EXCITED,
AND FOR TWO,
YOU'RE MAKING MY BACK HURT.
I LOVE YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> YOU'VE SEEN A LOT TODAY,
BUT AS THESE GIRLS WILL TELL
YOU, YOU STILL HAVEN'T SEEN
IT ALL.
FOR MORE INFORMATION ON
PREVENTING TEEN PREGNANCY,
GO TO 16ANDPREGNANT.MTV.COM.
AND LOOK FOR 16 AND PREGNANT,
SEASON TWO, RIGHT AROUND
THE CORNER.
I'M DR. DREW.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
[upbeat piano music]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
* I'M WEAK, BUT I'M
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE
* WHEN IT'S ALL DONE... 3 2 F1