>> [laughs]
[chime dings]
I'M SAVANNAH.
I'M 17, AND I LIVE IN JEFFERSON
CITY, MISSOURI, WITH MY MOM
AND MY LITTLE BROTHER, BEN.
NO, YOU GOT TO LEAVE THAT ON.
MY DAD HASN'T REALLY BEEN AROUND
MUCH SINCE I WAS LITTLE,
AND MY MOM'S GONE THROUGH SOME
REALLY HARD TIMES WITH HER
ALCOHOLISM.
BUT WE'RE REALLY CLOSE NOW.
I WAS ALWAYS THE SHY GIRL AT
SCHOOL, AND I LOVE TO PAINT AND
DRAW, BUT HIGH SCHOOL HELPED ME
COME OUT OF MY SHELL,
AND I MADE A LOT OF CLOSE
FRIENDS...
>> LOOK AT YOUR HAIR IN THE
SECOND ONE.
[laughter]
>> INCLUDING STONE.
I GOT SMOKE IN MY EYES.
WE WERE BEST FRIENDS FOR THREE
YEARS BEFORE HE WON ME OVER,
AND WE STARTED DATED.
>> YEAH, GOOD JOB PUTTING ON
THE--YEAH.
>> OUR RELATIONSHIP IS GREAT
BECAUSE HE MAKES ME LAUGH,
AND WE GOOF OFF TOGETHER ALL THE
TIME.
NO, YOU'RE CHEATING!
>> NO, YOU CAN'T MOVE THE HAND
OFF--
>> BECAUSE YOU JUST DID!
BUT IT'S NOT ALL FUN AND GAMES
FOR US ANYMORE, BECAUSE
I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
SO IF STONE CAME OVER,
WOULD YOU FEEL GOOD ABOUT GOING
TO THE PLAYGROUND?
MY MOM STRUGGLES WITH STAYING
SOBER, AND IT'S ALWAYS AFFECTED
ME AND MY LITTLE BROTHER, BEN.
ANYTHING TO GET YOU OUT OF THE
HOUSE, HUH?
>> CAN I GO PLAY A GAME NOW?
>> YEAH.
SHE'S BEEN ON A GOOD PATH
LATELY, AND I'M TRYING TO
SUPPORT HER, BUT STONE HAS ONLY
BEEN PUTTING HER DOWN,
AND THAT WAS A BIG REASON WE
BROKE UP A COUPLE MONTHS AGO.
NOW WE'RE TRYING TO STAY FRIENDS
SO THAT WE CAN CO-PARENT.
[giggles]
[children screaming]
>> I-I WOULD NEVER BE AROUND
YOU.
[laughs]
WELL, I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT,
AFTER FOUR YEARS OF KNOWING YOU,
I ACTUALLY WANTED TO GO THROUGH
IN DATING YOU.
WAIT, THAT CAME OUT WRONG.
>> YOU CHASED ME FOR THREE OF
THOSE FOUR YEARS.
NO, YOU CHASED ME FOR THREE OF
>> THREE OF THE FOUR, YEAH?
>> I DIDN'T LIKE YOU.
>> YEAH, YOU DID.
>> NO.
>> I DIDN'T START LIKING YOU
UNTIL WE STARTED HANGING OUT
AND WE'D RIDE AROUND TOWN.
>> NOW WE'RE JUST BACK TO BEING
FRIENDS WITH A CHILD.
>> IT'S NOT REALLY WHERE I WANT
TO BE, BUT BEING THE FACT THE
BABY WILL BE HERE SOON AND WE
HAVE HAD SOME ISSUES WITH MY
MOTHER'S ALCOHOLISM,
ARE YOU CONCERNED, WORRIED?
>> I DON'T WANT TO ANSWER THIS.
>> JUST ANSWER IT.
>> I HAVE NO SAY IN IT, RIGHT?
AND OBVIOUSLY, YOU DON'T EITHER,
BECAUSE YOU'VE TRIED SO MANY
TIMES TO HELP HER TO STOP,
AND I KNOW YOUR LITTLE BROTHER,
IT AFFECTS HIM DEEPLY,
AND IF IT HASN'T STOPPED,
THEN IT'S NOT GONNA STOP.
>> ADDICTION IS A WEIRD THING.
>> AND I UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT...
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT TO STAY
THERE AFTER HE'S BORN,
AND I-I DON'T WANT HIM TO HAVE
TO DEAL WITH THAT.
>> OKAY, WELL, YOU HAVE TO KNOW
THAT IF IT WAS A CONCERN OF
MINE, I OBVIOUSLY WOULDN'T LIVE
THERE.
BUT ALL I CAN DO IS STAND BY
HER.
>> AND I FEEL LIKE SOME THINGS
LIKE THAT DO AFFECT US,
AND MAYBE THAT'S WHY WE CAN'T
GET BACK TOGETHER.
>> THIS IS JUST WEIRD.
[laughter]
>> OH, LOOK AT THE LITTLE BABY
BOY.
HE'S SO CUTE.
>> ARE YOU READY TO CHASE ONE
AROUND?
>> NO.
[laughter]
NO, NO, NO.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> THANK YOU.
I'VE NEVER BEEN SO EXCITED ABOUT
FOOD IN MY LIFE.
[laughter]
>> WHAT?
DO YOU MISS BEING IN SCHOOL?
>> YEAH, I REALLY DO.
LIKE, I'LL GO THROUGH MY
NEWSFEED AND THINK, "DAMN."
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I'M DOING G.E.D. CLASSES.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> BUT YOU HAVE TO HAVE TEN
HOURS A MONTH, AND IF I HAVE THE
BABY THIS MONTH, I WON'T HAVE MY
TEN HOURS IN AND I'LL HAVE TO
RESTART THE WHOLE CLASS.
SO WE DID DECIDE TO PUT IT OFF
UNTIL AFTER I HAVE THE BABY,
JUST BECAUSE--
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
ABLE TO, LIKE, PICK IT UP AGAIN
AFTER THE BABY?
THAT'S GOOD.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST THOUGHT
WHENEVER YOU FOUND OUT THAT YOU
GOT PREGNANT?
LIKE, WHAT WAS THE FIRST THING
THAT POPPED INTO YOUR HEAD?
>> I LITERALLY JUST SAW, LIKE,
LIFE FLASH BEFORE ME,
LIKE HOW THEY SAY WHEN YOU DIE.
IT'S LIKE, EVERYTHING YOU'D
EVER PLANNED OR TALKED ABOUT
GOES DOWN THE DRAIN.
>> YEAH.
>> SO...
>> HOW DID STONE REACT,
ACTUALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> HE DIDN'T BELIEVE ME.
I HAD, LIKE, FIVE PREGNANCY
TESTS SITTING THERE.
>> AND HE STILL DIDN'T, LIKE,
BELIEVE YOU?
>> YEAH.
HE JUST LOOKED AT ME.
I THINK HE WANTED TO CRY, BUT
PEOPLE WERE AROUND, AND HE
WAS, LIKE--WASN'T FOR REAL.
AND THEN NOW IT STILL
ISN'T REAL.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DON'T EVER THINK THOSE
THINGS ARE GONNA HAPPEN TO YOU.
>> UNTIL IT DOES HAPPEN.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, WE NEVER USED
PROTECTION, AND I NEVER--
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T THINK THAT IT
WAS POSSIBLE FOR ME TO CONCEIVE.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO...
>> SO HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
NAMES?
>> YEAH.
BUT STONE IS NOT AGREEING.
IT'S JUST MISERABLENESS
'CAUSE THAT REALLY--
HE WANTS TO NAME THE BABY
THE NAME OF A CAR THAT HE LIKES:
TALON.
>> [laughs]
>> YEAH, OKAY.
>> YEAH, MIGHT NOT THINK OF IT
THE SAME.
[laughs]
>> YEAH.
STONE WANTING TO NAME THE BABY
AFTER A CAR REALLY BOTHERS ME.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S WORKING TO
SUPPORT US FINANCIALLY,
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S READY TO BE
A DAD, SO IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
TO ME THAT MY MOM IS ABLE TO
HELP ME WITH THE BABY.
STONE!
>> [laughs]
>> WHY?
>> SEE?
WHY YOU GOT TO GET ALL
PISSED OFF?
>> BECAUSE THAT'S IMMATURE.
>> SO?
YOU DO IMMATURE [bleep].
>> SO YOU'RE BACK--I'M--
>> I CAN--I CAN'T--
>> JUST SHUT UP.
SO HOW DO YOU WANT TO DO
CO-PARENTING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS?
>> WELL, IT'S SOMETHING THAT YOU
GUYS GOT TO FIGURE OUT TOO.
I MEAN, YOU CAN ALTERNATE,
OR YOU KNOW...
>> YEAH, WE CAN ALTERNATE, AND,
YOU KNOW, NEVER WOULD I WANT
STONE TO FEEL LEFT OUT
AND UNAPPRECIATED
AND NOT A PART OF
HIS SON'S LIFE.
>> I WOULD NEVER WANT TO FEEL
THAT WAY EITHER.
THAT'S A TERRIBLE FEELING.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW I'M WILLING TO
TAKE HIM WHENEVER YOU NEED ME
TO IF, YOU KNOW--
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I'M ALSO THERE.
DO YOU GUYS FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH THE BABY BEING WITH ME?
>> I DO.
>> OH.
>> IF YOU DO, YOU KNOW, YOU NEED
TO FIX YOUR PROBLEM, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE YOU GOT A MAJOR PROBLEM.
I FEEL LIKE A [bleep] SAYING
THAT, BUT IF SHE WANTS
TO FIX IT.
>> YEAH.
UM, I'M TIRED OF SEEING MY MOM
STRUGGLE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND I KNOW THAT YOU'RE ON THE
ROAD TO RECOVERY, BUT THERE'S
BOUND TO BE SLIPUPS,
AND I WANT TO HAVE A COMPLETELY
SOBER ENVIRONMENT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I JUST KNOW THAT OLD HABITS
ARE HARD TO BREAK.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> I JUST--I WANT TO SEE--
I WANT TO SEE THINGS...
>> EVERYTHING WORK OUT?
>> WORK OUT FOR YOU.
>> * ALL THE BLUE EYES
* YOU GOT TO GO
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
WE ARE.
YOU KNOW?
>> I HAVE MULTIPLICATION
TABLES--OR THE FRACTION RULES.
EVEN THOUGH I'VE DECIDED TO PUT
OFF GETTING MY G.E.D. UNTIL
AFTER THE BABY IS BORN, MY MOM
HAS BEEN HELPING ME WITH MY
STUDIES.
PEMDAS: PARENTHESES,
EXPONENTS...
>> THAT'S LIKE FOREIGN LANGUAGE.
>> YEAH.
>> [laughs]
[indistinct chatter]
TODAY IS MY BABY SHOWER,
AND I'M NERVOUS ABOUT STONE
BEING THERE BECAUSE HE DOESN'T
ALWAYS GET ALONG WITH MY FAMILY.
>> NOW YOU WALK AROUND HER
AND MEET ME ON THIS SIDE.
>> MAKE SURE IT'S UP.
>> OH!
PRETTY CLOSE.
UH-OH.
>> WHOSE IS THAT?
>> IS THAT YOURS?
>> IT WAS GRANNY'S?
>> OH, SHE WAS PRETTY CLOSE,
HUH?
>> GO GIVE IT BACK TO HER.
TELL HER, "HANG ON TO IT."
>> OKAY, THAT'S IT.
WE CAN EAT CAKE.
OR PRESENTS.
WHATEVER YOU WANT TO DO FIRST.
PRESENTS?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> DO PRESENTS FIRST.
STONE, DO YOU WANT TO COME BACK
HERE?
[gasps]
THIS IS SO CUTE.
>> AH...
>> SO ADORABLE.
>> I HOPE HE STAYS THAT LITTLE
FOR A WHILE.
>> BUT GUESS WHAT.
HE'S NOT GONNA.
>> OH.
IT'S A MONKEY.
>> OOH!
>> AND A PACKAGE OF BABY WIPES
FOR THOSE TIMES YOU GOT TO
CHANGE STINKY DIAPERS.
>> YEAH, IF I GOT TO GO TO THE
BATHROOM OR SOMETHING.
[laughter]
>> LITTLE BOOTIES.
>> SO EVERYBODY WANTS TO KNOW,
YOU GUYS.
HAVE YOU GUYS PICKED OUT A NAME?
>> NO.
GRANNY.
>> GRANNY.
>> CAN YOU JUST--STONE.
>> DO NOT DO THAT.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
>> WELL, THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
YAY!
[laughs]
[applause]
STONE, YOU'RE A PIG.
>> [laughs]
>> WHO DOES THAT?
>> HO-HO.
>> TODAY'S BEEN STRESSFUL.
>> IT'S NOT THE END OF THE
WORLD.
>> OKAY, I UNDERSTAND THAT,
BUT GETTING MAD OVER A NAME AND
THEN GETTING UP AND WALKING AWAY
IS RIDICULOUS.
I'M NOT NAMING MY FIRST CHILD
AFTER...
>> A CAR.
AND MY GRANDMOTHER WAS RIGHT TO
SAY THAT, AND THEN HE JUST GETS
UP AND WALKS AWAY.
>> IT'S JUST DISRESPECTFUL.
>> YEAH, I'M KIND OF UPSET.
>> AND ESPECIALLY AT YOUR BABY
SHOWER.
>> HE EMBARRASSED ME, AND IT,
LIKE--I WAS READY TO CRY.
>> HONESTLY, I THINK WHAT HE DID
TONIGHT PROVES THAT HE'S NOT
REALLY READY TO BE MATURE ENOUGH
TO BE A FATHER.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHY WE'RE NOT
TOGETHER.
FAR FROM TOGETHER,
ESPECIALLY AFTER TODAY.
>> YEAH.
>> HMM?
>> LEAVE IT ALONE.
>> YEAH, DON'T TOUCH IT.
>> OH, MY GOSH, NOT AGAIN.
>> AFTER THE BABY SHOWER,
INSTEAD OF COMING BACK TO MY
HOUSE TO HELP SORT OUT THE
GIFTS, STONE WENT TO HANG OUT
WITH HIS FRIEND.
>> THAT GIRL RIGHT THERE,
SHE TOTALLY GAVE ME THE "DO ME"
EYES.
>> [laughs]
AND JUST WALKED AWAY.
>> I'LL GET HER BACK OVER HERE.
>> [laughs]
YOU WON'T DO IT.
>> SHE'S TALKING TO SOMEBODY.
>> I'M RUDE.
>> THEY'RE GETTING READY TO
LEAVE, SO...
>> YOU WON'T DO IT.
COME ON.
LOOK AT THAT.
I'LL GET HER ATTENTION FOR YOU.
>> NO, DUDE.
YOU HAVE A KID ON THE WAY,
BUT THAT DOES NOT MEAN YOU HAVE
BETTER GAME THAN ME.
>> I--HOW DOES IT NOT?
I MEAN, I'VE GOT SOME PRETTY
GOOD--I GOT MAD SKILLS.
>> I GOT SOME MAD SKILLS TOO.
>> YOU WON'T DO IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
CAN I HAVE YOUR PHONE NUMBER?
YOU'RE REALLY PRETTY.
>> I'M NOT A STRANGER.
MY NAME'S ROBBIE.
>> HIS NAME'S ROBBIE.
>> THAT'S HOW STRANGERS GET TO
KNOW EACH OTHER.
IF YOU GIVE ME YOUR PHONE
NUMBER, I'LL CALL YOU, AND WE'LL
GO GET ICE CREAM SOMETIME.
>> TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> TOMORROW NIGHT?
OKAY.
CAN WE WINDOW PAINT YOUR CAR?
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
NOT THE WINDSHIELD.
>> NOT THE WINDSHIELD.
>> THAT'S ILLEGAL.
>> OKAY.
[both laugh]
>> OKAY, YOU GOT A LITTLE BIT
MORE GAME THAN I THOUGHT
YOU DID.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> YOU'RE ONE LUCKY [bleep]
BASTARD RIGHT NOW.
>> THANK YOU!
>> IT'S BEEN REAL MEETING YOU
GUYS.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
>> OKAY.
SEE YOU GUYS.
>> BYE.
>> YOUR LACK OF CONFIDENCE IN ME
APPALLS ME, MY FRIEND.
>> HEY, FROM NOW ON,
IT WON'T BE LIKE THAT.
>> COOL.
>> DO YOU SEE THAT?
UGH.
THERE'S THIS PICTURE ON
INSTAGRAM, AND I DON'T KNOW IF
I SHOULD BE FREAKED OUT ABOUT
IT, BUT IT'S A GIRL SITTING ON
THE BACK OF STONE'S CAR.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH.
KIND OF LIKE RISQUE-LY.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT THAT.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT'S HIS
CAR?
>> THE BACK OF IT,
AND HE'S JUST DUMB ENOUGH
TO DO IT, SO...
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, LIKE, WHAT?
>> I WOULD PUT THAT--
NO, I WOULD, LIKE, THROW MY
PHONE AT HIM AND BE LIKE,
"WHAT IS THIS?"
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, I JUST FEEL LIKE THAT'S
DISRESPECTFUL.
YOU NEED TO CONFRONT HIM.
>> IT'S HARD TO SAY ANYTHING
WHEN WE AREN'T, LIKE,
OFFICIALLY AN ITEM.
I KNOW STONE AND I AREN'T
TOGETHER, BUT IT STILL BUGS ME
THAT HE'S MEETING GIRLS,
SO I ASKED HIM TO COME BY
AND TALK.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> HI.
>> YOU WANT TO HOP IN?
>> NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> TAKE YOU TO LUNCH.
>> IT'S NOT SAFE.
>> FOR WHO, ME?
>> FOR ME.
>> GET YOU A HELMET.
>> SHUT UP, STONE.
SO EVEN THOUGH WE AREN'T
TOGETHER, WHY DO YOU NEED TO
FIND FEMALES?
>> I WORKED ALL [bleep] DAY
LONG, AND YOU CALL ME FOR THIS
[bleep]?
>> [sighs]
I WOULDN'T DO THAT IF YOU'D
ACTUALLY TREAT ME LIKE THE
MOTHER OF YOUR CHILD.
LIKE THE BABY SHOWER
AND THE OTHER NIGHT.
LIKE, EVEN THOUGH WE'RE NOT
TOGETHER, I THINK YOU'RE BEING
INSENSITIVE ABOUT THE SITUATION.
>> THAT'S 100% CORRECT.
>> OKAY, SO THEN WHAT ARE WE
DOING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO BE WITH YOU
TO PARENT.
I REALLY DON'T.
>> I-I NEVER SAID YOU DID.
>> THIS IS GOING NOWHERE,
LIKE ALWAYS.
>> AIN'T THAT RIGHT?
>> YEP.
>> HEY, GOOD SPEAKIN' WITH YA.
>> [sighs]
>> SINCE THINGS AREN'T GOING
WELL WITH STONE, I'M TRYING TO
FOCUS ON THE BABY AND SPENDING
TIME WITH MY FRIENDS.
WHAT IF WE'RE PLAYING LASER TAG
AND I JUST POP?
>> WELL, THEN WE'RE RUSHING YOU
TO A HOSPITAL,
AND YOU'RE POPPING THAT BABY
OUT.
>> [laughs]
YEAH, OKAY.
>> ARE YOU READY TO GO?
>> YEAH.
>> SWEET.
>> LASER TAG.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> I SMELL FOOD.
[laughs]
IS IT BAD THAT I'M REALLY
THAT HUNGRY?
>> NO, 'CAUSE I'M STARVING.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> [laughs] HI.
>> HEY.
>> ARE YOU PREGNANT?
>> OBVIOUSLY.
WOW.
>> CLEARLY.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
THAT'S KIND OF SCARY.
[laughter]
WE'RE ABOUT TO ROCK OUT.
[lasers blasting]
>> AH!
YOU'RE GONNA TAG ME.
[lasers blasting]
NO, THAT'S CHEATING!
GO, GET THEIR BASE!
>> AH!
WHERE'S SAVANNAH?
WHERE'D SHE GO?
>> THERE.
>> NO.
[lasers blasting]
AH!
NO.
>> WHOO!
>> WHO WON?
>> YOU GUYS ARE CHEATERS.
YOU GUYS CHEATED.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> NO, I JUST LAID ON THE FLOOR
AND ROLLED AROUND
AND JUMPED STUFF.
>> YEAH, WELL, I CAN'T DO THAT.
[laughs]
>> HEY, IT'S THE THOUGHT THAT
COUNTS.
>> IS IT?
>> YOU GUYS READY TO HEAD OUT
OF HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M STARVING.
>> OKAY.
>> HOW MANY NAPKINS?
YOU GUYS ALL WANT NAPKINS?
>> I NEED A NAPKIN.
>> HERE, LET'S JUST PASS THE
PLATES DOWN.
>> I'LL DO NAPKINS;
YOU DO PLATES.
>> DID YOU SERIOUSLY TAKE MY
WATER AGAIN?
>> OOH.
SORRY.
NOT REALLY, BUT...
>> [laughs]
>> ARE YOU SINGLE?
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU INTERESTED IN ANYONE,
OR...
>> DAMN IT, SKYLAR.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I AM, ACTUALLY.
>> DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
>> I'M JUST LOOKING AT YOU.
[chime dings]
I HAD A LOT OF FUN WITH TAYLOR,
AND AFTER I GOT HOME,
WE STAYED UP LATE TEXTING.
[line rings]
>> HELLO?
>> HEY, TAYLOR.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> NOTHING.
KIND OF JUST WAKING UP.
>> OH?
>> LAST NIGHT WAS FUN.
>> YOU'RE TELLING ME.
I'M CARRYING, LIKE,
50 EXTRA POUNDS.
>> [laughs]
>> IT'S WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
I FEEL LIKE I DEFINITELY COULD
SEE US, LIKE, HANGING OUT MORE,
AND I KNOW THAT I WANT TO GET TO
KNOW YOU MORE.
SO, LIKE, WHAT NOW?
[laughs]
>> [laughs]
>> YEAH.
>> I WANTED TO TALK TO MY MOM
ABOUT EVERYTHING THAT'S GOING
ON...
MOM?
BUT SHE HASN'T COME HOME
FROM BEING OUT WITH HER FRIENDS.
IT WORRIES ME THAT SHE MIGHT BE
DRINKING AGAIN SO CLOSE TO MY
DUE DATE.
MY MOM MADE IT HOME BEFORE DAWN,
AND I'M GLAD SHE'S SAFE,
BUT I'M REALLY DISAPPOINTED.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT YOUR
SOBRIETY.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE THE OPTION TO
NOT GO GET A DRINK.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> BUT I WANT TO HELP YOU,
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO THAT
'CAUSE YOU DON'T REALLY TALK
ABOUT IT.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S NOT
SOMETHING THAT I NEED TO TALK TO
YOU ABOUT, BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
SOMETIMES WHEN I TELL YOU STUFF,
IT CAN BE TURNED AROUND
AND USED AGAINST ME.
I FEEL JUDGED.
>> I DON'T JUDGE YOU.
I MEAN, IF DRINKING'S WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO, YOU'RE A GROWN WOMAN
AND YOU CAN DO IT, BUT JUST KNOW
THAT IT DOES AFFECT ME,
BECAUSE WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
YOU DID TELL ME WE WERE GONNA DO
THIS TOGETHER, AND I FEEL LIKE
I'M DOING IT WITHOUT YOU
BECAUSE OF YOUR DRINKING.
>> YOU'RE WRONG.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU COULDN'T BE MORE WRONG.
YOU PROBABLY DON'T SEE THAT,
BUT YOU ARE.
I AM NOT GONNA JUSTIFY OR
EXPLAIN MY BEHAVIOR TO ANYONE.
>> YEAH.
>> MY DUE DATE IS TOMORROW,
SO MY DOCTOR SCHEDULED AN
APPOINTMENT TO INDUCE ME THAT
EVENING, AND NOW THAT MY MOM HAS
SHOWN ME THAT SHE'S NOT GOING TO
CHANGE HER WAYS, I WANT TO TRY
AND FIX THINGS WITH STONE.
>> SO WHAT DO THEY HAVE TO DO
TO YOU?
DO THEY HAVE TO, LIKE, STICK YOU
WITH...
>> NO.
>> NEEDLES?
>> SHE SAID THAT THEY'LL PUT--
EVERY THREE TO FOUR HOURS,
THEY'LL PUT MEDICINE UP BY MY
CERVIX TO SOFTEN IT AND HELP IT
DILATE.
>> SO THEY SHOVE A--
>> A SYRINGE.
CAN YOU HAVE A SERIOUS
CONVERSATION WITH ME?
>> YEAH.
THOUGH I AM QUITE HILARIOUS.
>> BE SERIOUS.
>> I AM.
WHAT IS IT?
>> I FEEL LIKE WE HAVEN'T BEEN
THE NICEST TO EACH OTHER...
>> WE HAVEN'T.
>> DURING THIS PREGNANCY.
AND IT'S NOT JUST YOUR FAULT.
IT IS MY FAULT.
BUT--
>> WOW, THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE EVER HEARD YOU SAY THAT.
>> YEAH.
BUT I'M SCARED THAT I DON'T HAVE
CONTROL OVER WHAT'S ABOUT TO
HAPPEN.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M
SAYING?
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> SO I NEED SUPPORT FROM YOU.
EVEN THOUGH WE AREN'T TOGETHER,
I NEED YOUR SUPPORT,
BECAUSE THIS IS YOUR SON.
AND I WANT YOU TO BE ABLE TO
ENJOY IT WITH ME.
>> OKAY, BUT WE STILL DON'T HAVE
A NAME, AND IT'S PROBABLY GONNA
BE DECIDED IN THE HOSPITAL.
I DON'T WANT SOMEONE ELSE'S
TWO CENTS IN OUR SON'S NAME.
I THINK THAT'S SOMETHING
THE PARENTS--
>> YOU AND I CAN DECIDE.
SOUND GOOD?
>> YEAH.
>> * CRY, ALL
* IS NOT
* LOST
* YEAH
[heartbeat]
>> READY?
>> YEAH, HOLD ON.
>> DEEP BREATH.
>> THE DOCTORS INDUCED ME BY
GIVING ME PITOCIN TO HELP ME
DILATE.
>> THE BAD PART'S DONE.
>> EVEN THOUGH MY MOM AND I
AREN'T GETTING ALONG, I'M GLAD
SHE FOUND A RIDE TO BE HERE
WITH ME.
>> 'KAY?
ABOUT AN HOUR, SO BUZZ ME, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
OH, IT HURTS.
AH.
OH...
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> ARE YOU CRYING?
>> DO YOU WANT A HUG?
YOU WANT A BIG OLE HUG?
MWAH.
>> CAN YOU BEND THOSE KNEES
UP FOR ME?
>> MM-MM.
I CAN'T FEEL THEM.
>> YOU'RE STARTING.
>> ARE YOU READY?
>> GRAB THOSE BARS.
PUSH DOWN, ALL THROUGH YOUR
BOTTOM.
TWO, THREE, FOUR.
BLOW IT OUT.
OKAY, BIG, BIG BREATH.
HOLD IT IN AND PUSH.
ONE, TWO, THREE,
FOUR, FIVE.
ONE MORE BIG BREATH.
HARDEST PUSH YET.
MAKE THIS LAST ONE THE BEST ONE.
COME ON, SWEETIE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
>> COME ON.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> OH, I HEARD HIM!
[baby crying]
THAT'S MY BABY.
OH, MY GOD!
LOOK AT MY BABY.
>> * YOU ARE NEW
* NEVER SEEN THAT FACE BEFORE
*
* I'M SUCH A FOOL *
* YOU THOUGHT THOSE WORDS
* WE ARE QUITE ASKEW
* AND SO THE RAYS
* WERE WELL ASSURED
[laughs]
[chime dings]
>> I ALREADY LOVE HIM.
>> [giggles]
>> WE AIN'T CUDDLING
IN THIS BED.
YOU'RE CUDDLING WITH THAT
OVER THERE.
STONE AND I FINALLY AGREED ON
A NAME: ROWAN JAMES.
>> ROWAN JAMES.
ROWAN.
ROWBO.
>> ROWAN.
NOT--LIKE, ROW-AN.
ROWAN.
>> ROWAN JAMES.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
ROWAN JAMES.
[chime dings]
HEY, DUNGLE-BUSS.
HI.
>> HEY.
BRING HIM HERE.
WHAT'S HE GONNA WEAR HOME?
BUT YOU'RE STILL CHANGING ALL
THE POOPY DIAPERS.
[laughs]
WE GOT A PERFECT LITTLE GUY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I MEAN, HE'S CUTE.
>> NO, I'M JUST GONNA LEAVE HIM
HERE WITH YOU.
SEE HOW YOU CAN DEAL WITH IT.
>> [laughs]
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> GET OFF TO WORK.
[Rowan crying]
IT'S OKAY.
OH, MY GOD, HE'S PEEING!
MOM.
>> SO?
[laughs]
YOU DO.
PEE ALL OVER YOU.
>> MY MOM'S SOBRIETY IS PRETTY
TOUCH-AND-GO.
AND STONE IS WORKING ALL THE
TIME, SO I'M TAKING CARE OF
ROWAN ON MY OWN, AND IT'S A LOT
OF WORK.
[Rowan crying]
OKAY, I'M GONNA GO GET YOUR
PACIFIER.
YOU CAN COME--OH.
DANG IT.
HOLD ON.
[Rowan crying]
OH, LOOKIE THERE.
MAMA DOES.
NOW, DO YOU THINK I CAN GET YOUR
DIAPER CHANGED?
COME AND GIVE ME KISSES.
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE LEAVING
ROWAN ALONE WITH MY MOM...
YOU SMELL SO GOOD.
>> TILL THAT DIAPER TIME,
THEN I DON'T SMELL SO GOOD, HUH?
>> SO I'M DROPPING HIM OFF WITH
STONE'S MOM AND MEETING UP WITH
SOME FRIENDS.
MY LITTLE BABY.
>> BYE.
>> IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
YOU'RE EVEN A MOM.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD BE,
LIKE, 25 YEARS OLD RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> [laughs]
>> DOES HE, LIKE, KEEP YOU UP
ALL NIGHT LONG, OR DOES HE SLEEP
MOST OF THE NIGHT?
>> HIS DAY LITERALLY CONSISTS OF
POOPING, SLEEPING,
AND PEEING.
AND EATING.
>> SOUNDS LIKE MOST OF THE GUYS
THAT I KNOW.
>> [laughs]
>> HOW ARE YOU AND STONE?
>> GOOD, ACTUALLY.
REALLY GOOD.
>> HAVE YOU GUYS GOTTEN BETTER
SINCE THE BABY?
>> NOT FIGHTING OR BEING MEAN
TO EACH OTHER?
>> NO.
SINCE I'VE BEEN HOME FROM THE
HOSPITAL, IT'S, LIKE--IT'S REAL.
IT'S REAL LIFE NOW.
I MEAN, BETWEEN MY MOM AND
STONE'S MOM AND DOING MY G.E.D.,
IT'S HARD.
IT'S DOABLE, BUT IT'S HARD.
>> YEAH.
LIKE, AND IT'S GONNA BE HARDER,
BUT I FEEL LIKE ROW CAN BE YOUR
MOTIVATION.
>> OH, YEAH.
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW HARD UNTIL
YOU HAVE FIVE STITCHED IN YOUR
VAGINA.
[laughter]
COME ON, ROW-TOUS.
MY FRIEND BREA WANTED TO SEE
ROWAN, SO SHE CAME WITH ME TO
PICK HIM UP FROM STONE'S MOM AND
THEN BACK TO MY HOUSE
TO HANG OUT.
MOM!
COME HERE, BEN.
BUT WHEN WE GOT THERE,
MY MOM WAS CLEARLY DRUNK,
AND I'M WORRIED ABOUT MY LITTLE
BROTHER.
GET OUT OF THE HOUSE
WITH THE CIGARETTE.
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
>> SHE'S JUST UPSET.
>> THIS IS MY HOUSE.
I'M NOT TRYING TO WRAP MYSELF UP
IN HER ISSUES.
THAT'S SOMETHING FOR ME TO DEAL
WITH AND TO STRUGGLE WITH.
IT'S CAUSING A WHOLE LOT OF
TENSION AROUND HERE BECAUSE
SAVANNAH'S RUNNING UP ON ME,
CHALLENGING ME.
THIS IS MY HOUSE.
>> YEAH.
I AM GONNA GO INSIDE AND CHECK
ON SAVANNAH.
>> PLEASE DO.
>> OKAY.
>> AND I'M GONNA GET UP.
>> [whispers] THAT WAS CRAZY.
>> SHE'S CRAZY.
>> SHE WAS, LIKE, GOING ON AND
ON, AND WAS LIKE--
SHE WASN'T MAKING SENSE.
LIKE, IT'S LIKE SHE'S A TOTAL
DIFFERENT PERSON.
I'VE NEVER--LIKE, THE WHOLE TIME
I'VE BEEN FRIENDS WITH YOU,
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOUR MOM DRUNK.
>> YEAH.
IT JUST SETS ME OFF.
SHE'S A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
PERSON.
SHE TRULY IS.
>> I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THAT.
>> YEAH.
[slams door]
STOP SLAMMING DOORS!
>> NO.
>> ROWAN IS ASLEEP.
[Rowan crying]
[slams door]
OKAY.
WHY ARE YOU ACTING LIKE THIS?
>> UGH.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT
YOU'RE DEAL IS.
>> SAME GOES FOR YOU, SAVANNAH,
IF YOU COME UP MISSING.
>> TAKE--
>> HELLO!
>> TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR YOUR
OWN [bleep] ACTIONS.
>> OH, GOD.
>> I'LL GET THE COPS OVER HERE
TO DO IT.
>> DO IT.
>> OKAY.
>> HE'S NOT YOURS, SAVANNAH.
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE HE'S SAFE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEP.
[line rings]
>> I'M NOT SURE WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE, BUT IT HAS COME TO THE
POINT WHERE I NEED TO LEAVE.
>> I HAVE A BELLIGERENTLY DRUNK
MOTHER WHO I DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE LEAVING MY BROTHER
HERE ALONE WITH, AND SHE WON'T
LET ME TAKE HIM.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
COME HERE, BEN.
THE COPS ARE ON THEIR WAY.
>> WHILE WAITING FOR THE COPS TO
COME, I TOLD STONE WHAT WAS
GOING ON, AND HE INSISTED ON
COMING OVER TO PICK US UP.
>> I WOULDN'T EVEN, LIKE, WANT
TO BE AROUND HER WHENEVER SHE'S
LIKE THAT.
>> IT'S STONE.
COME HERE, BEN.
GO.
[Rowan crying]
HERE.
THE COPS ARE ON THEIR WAY.
>> [crying]
>> NO, DON'T OPEN THE DOOR.
>> MOM, NO!
>> SAVANNAH...
AFTER TONIGHT, BABY, YOU GOT TO
GO STAY SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE TOO BIG FOR ME.
>> OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU HAVE TO BE
LIKE THIS.
I REALLY DON'T.
I JUST DON'T GET IT.
[siren wails]
>> OH, NO.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU COULDN'T STAY
SOBER FOR ME WHEN I WAS A KID,
BUT THE LEAST YOU COULD DO IS
HELP BEN GROW UP RIGHT.
>> OKAY, SAVANNAH, WE'RE NOT
BRINGING UP THE PAST.
YOU'RE JUST TOO MUCH.
>> OKAY.
YOU'RE TOO MUCH FOR ME.
>> I CAN'T DEAL WITH YOU.
>> OKAY.
GET OUT OF MY FACE.
I'M DONE SPEAKING WITH YOU.
YES, SIR, I HAVE A BELLIGERENTLY
DRUNK MOTHER,
AND AS FAR AS MY LITTLE BROTHER,
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE LEAVING
HIM HERE TONIGHT.
>> BUT I CAN'T FORCE HER TO GIVE
YOU HER KID.
>> BUT SHE'S NOT FIT TO TAKE
CARE OF HIM.
>> MOVE IT.
LET'S GO!
>> MOM.
>> MELANIE.
COME HERE, MELANIE.
>> NO.
>> BEN, COME THIS WAY.
>> MELANIE.
MELANIE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> NO.
>> THEY'RE LOOKING FOR YOU.
GO UP THERE AND STOP.
I'M GOING TO.
>> * THERE IS A FINE LINE
* ACROSS YOUR HEART
* WEAKER WITH EVERY BEAT
>> LET'S MOVE IT!
LET'S GO!
>> OKAY.
BEN, LET'S GO.
*
IT WAS BAD.
IT WAS REAL BAD.
BUT, I MEAN, I'VE DEALT WITH IT
FOR MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> BUT ONE THING I'M NOT GONNA
HAVE IS ROWBO GROWING UP IN THE
SAME LIFE BENJAMIN DID.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
YOU WERE SITTING THERE
SUPPORTING IT THE WHOLE TIME.
SO, I MEAN, DO YOU EVER THINK IT
WILL GET BETTER?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT I HAVE TO
HAVE SOMETHING TO HOLD ONTO.
I NEED MY MOM.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
BUT, I MEAN, YOU CAN SUPPORT
HER, BUT YOU CAN'T SUPPORT
HER...
>> YEAH.
>> ADDICTIONS, AS YOU PUT IT.
>> I KNOW.
>> 'CAUSE THAT MAKES IT WORSE AS
WELL, 'CAUSE THAT MAKES IT FEEL
LIKE IT'S ALL ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN...
'CAUSE YOU DO GOT A LOT GOING ON
OTHER THAN THIS, AND YOU DON'T
NEED OTHER STRESS.
>> WELL, IT'S HARD BECAUSE
I WANT TO BE AROUND MY MOM.
>> BUT, I MEAN, SOMETIMES YOU
GOT TO DO THINGS YOU DON'T LIKE
TO BETTER YOURSELF.
>> I REALLY JUST FEEL LIKE IF
I OPEN MY MOUTH AND SAY
SOMETHING TO HER, SHE'S GONNA
GET BETTER, AND I JUST NEED YOUR
EMOTIONAL SUPPORT WITH THAT.
>> WHATEVER YOU NEED TO DO.
I'LL TRY MY BEST TO HELP YOU IF
YOU NEED HELP.
KIND OF LIKE HELPING YOUR TEAM
WIN.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
THE NEXT MORNING, I FELT KIND OF
BAD FOR CALLING THE COPS, SO
I LEFT ROWAN WITH STONE AND WENT
TO CHECK ON MY MOM.
I WAS WONDERING HOW YOU WERE
FEELING.
I MEAN, IS IT SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO TALK ABOUT, OR SOMETHING THAT
I SHOULD JUST LEAVE ALONE?
>> IT'S NO GOOD.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I DON'T HAVE ANY EXCUSES
FOR YOU, YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE THERE
IS NO EXCUSE.
IT'S JUST NOT BEING STRONG
ENOUGH, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT, LIKE,
INPATIENT TREATMENT?
>> YOU KNOW HOW MANY TIMES I'VE
BEEN INPATIENT?
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT DO YOU FEEL
LIKE ONE MORE TIME COULD HELP?
'CAUSE, I MEAN, YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
THAT WAY IN A LONG TIME.
AND I WORRY THAT THAT COULD
HAPPEN MORE OFTEN NOW.
OBVIOUSLY, THIS IS, YOU KNOW,
MY BABY, SO MY RESPONSIBILITY,
BUT I FEEL LIKE I NEEDED HELP,
AND YOU'RE TOO INTOXICATED
TO HELP ME.
LIKE, WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
>> YEAH.
AND SOMETIMES I THINK
THAT CAN GET A HANDLE ON IT
IF I JUST, YOU KNOW,
START GOING TO MEETINGS.
I THINK THAT WOULD BE MY ONLY
WAY OUT OF IT.
YOU KNOW, I WANT TO BE A BETTER
EXAMPLE FOR YOU GUYS.
>> YEAH.
TO SEE MY MOM STRUGGLE
BREAKS MY HEART.
IT COMPLETELY TEARS ME UP
INSIDE,
BUT IT'S BEEN A PART OF MY LIFE
SINCE THE DAY I WAS BORN.
SOMETIMES I WISH I COULD JUST
REWIND TIME AND FIGURE OUT
WHERE EVERYTHING WENT WRONG
AND FIX IT.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE FUTURE
HOLDS.
NO IDEA.
WITH STONE, I HOPE THAT OUR
RELATIONSHIP CAN GET TO THE
POINT WHERE WE CAN BE A HAPPY
FAMILY.
THERE IS ALWAYS THE CHANCE THAT
WE ARE GONNA ARGUE, BUT I FEEL
LIKE WE'RE IN A GOOD SPOT NOW,
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> WHILE MY FRIENDS FINISH
SCHOOL AND GO ON TO COLLEGE,
WHICH IS SOMETHING I WANTED
SO BAD...
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP ME.
I'M STILL DEALING WITH BEING
A MOM, FINISHING SCHOOL, G.E.D.
BUT I KNOW THAT ONE DAY
EVERYTHING WILL WORK OUT THE WAY
IT'S SUPPOSED TO.
I JUST HOPE IT COMES SOONER
THAN LATER.
[chime dings]
[upbeat piano music]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA *
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
* I'M WEAK, BUT I'M *
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE
* WHEN IT'S ALL DONE... *