[laughter]
>> MY NAME IS EMILY.
WE SHOULD GO TO THE PUMPKIN
PATCH IN A LITTLE WHILE.
>> YAY!
>> YAY, S'MORES.
I LIVE IN HAYDEN, ALABAMA, WITH
MY DAD AND MY STEPMOM.
>> I'M GONNA DO EVERYTHING IN
THE WORLD TO MAKE SURE YOU'LL BE
ALL RIGHT.
[school bell rings]
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A GOOD
STUDENT.
BALANCING HIGH SCHOOL DRAMA
AND ACCELERATED COURSES IS
A PIECE OF CAKE.
>> THEY KNOW THAT SHE'S GOT
STRAIGHT "A"s.
I'M ALSO A MAJORETTE IN THE HIGH
SCHOOL MARCHING BAND.
THAT'S HOW I MET DANIEL.
HE PLAYS TENOR SAXOPHONE.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR OVER A
YEAR NOW, AND WE'RE ENGAGED TO
BE MARRIED IN JUNE.
ALABAMA'S GREAT, BUT I'M READY
TO GO TO COLLEGE.
THAT'S WHERE I'LL STUDY TO
BECOME A PHARMACIST.
BEING A TEENAGER HAS BEEN PRETTY
EASY SO FAR.
I'VE HAD A LOT OF SUPPORT FROM
MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
>> LOOK AT ALL THESE AWARDS.
LOOK AT ALL THAT.
YOU ARE, LIKE, THE TOP OF THE
CLASS.
>> BUT THAT'S ALL ABOUT TO
CHANGE, BECAUSE...
I'M PREGNANT.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
I USED TO LIVE WITH MY MOM,
BUT WHEN I GOT PREGNANT, I MOVED
OUT OF HER HOUSE.
IT REALLY HURTS KNOWING I DON'T
HAVE HER SUPPORT.
[door slams]
I HAD TO CHANGE HIGH SCHOOLS AND
MOVE INTO MY DAD'S HOUSE AN HOUR
AWAY TO THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
WHOA!
I REALLY WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO
LEAVE MY BAND FRIENDS.
I PROBABLY WON'T BE ABLE TO HANG
OUT WITH THEM AS MUCH
AS I USED TO.
[laughter]
>> DO YOU MISS, LIKE, BEING OUT
WITH THE BAND AND EVERYTHING?
>> I MEAN, YEAH, I MISS, LIKE,
PERFORMING, JUST BECAUSE I THREW
BATON FOR, LIKE, NINE YEARS.
SO IT'S KIND OF LIKE, "MAN, I
WISH I COULD STILL BE OUT THERE,
JUST ATTENTION ON ME.
[laughter]
AND IT'S LIKE, WELL, YOU KNOW,
TO SEE ANYBODY, IT HAS TO BE,
LIKE, 45 MINUTES, SO--
>> SO WHEN YOUR MOM FOUND OUT
YOU WERE PREGNANT, LIKE, HOW DID
SHE REACT?
>> DEFINITELY SHOCKED AND ANGRY.
AND SHE SAID I WAS NOT ALLOWED
TO LIVE UNDER HER ROOF PREGNANT.
>> WHY?
>> SHE DIDN'T EVEN CARE WHERE
YOU WENT?
>> MM-MMM.
AS LONG AS I WASN'T LIVING AT
HER HOUSE.
>> DID YOUR DAD TAKE IT EASIER
THAN YOUR MOM?
>> UM, I THINK MY DAD, HE HAD
TALKED TO ME.
"BE SAFE.
THAT'S ALL I CARE ABOUT.
DON'T GET PREGNANT.
MAKE GOOD GRADES."
SO OUT OF THREE RULES, I BROKE,
LIKE, THE MAIN ONE, YOU KNOW?
[laughter]
SO I KIND OF FELT LIKE I WAS
DISAPPOINTING HIM.
DISAPPOINTED IS AN
UNDERSTATEMENT.
MY DAD WAS READY TO KILL ME, BUT
HE KNOWS I DON'T HAVE ANYWHERE
ELSE TO GO RIGHT NOW.
>> I DIDN'T BELIEVE YOU.
I HAD TO HAVE A TEST.
>> MMM-HMM.
>> AND THEN ONCE I GOT THAT, YOU
KNOW, I WAS OKAY FOR A LITTLE
WHILE, BUT THEN THE ANGER SET IN
AND ALL THE EMOTIONS WADDED UP
AND I THOUGHT I WANTED TO
STRANGLE YOU.
YOU KNOW?
AND THEN THE FIRST THING THAT
WENT THROUGH MY MIND WAS
ABORTION.
I MEAN, THIS COULD HELP YOU.
>> I THINK THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
THE EASIEST THING TO DO, YOU
KNOW, NOT HAVING TO SPEND ANY
MONEY, BUT I, LIKE, LOOKED IT UP
ON THE COMPUTER, AND I DECIDED
THAT THAT WAS WRONG AND STUFF.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
MATURE ENOUGH TO HAVE MADE THE
DECISION TO HAVE A BABY?
>> YEAH.
I GUESS.
[laughs]
>> DO YOU SERIOUSLY FEEL LIKE--
THAT YOU'RE, IN YOUR BRAIN--
>> WELL, I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE
NOW.
>> WELL, THERE'S STILL A LOT OF
THINGS THAT BOTHER ME, MAYBE
WHERE I MESSED UP AT.
YOU KNOW, WHAT, DID I TELL YOU
IT WAS OKAY TO HAVE SEX?
>> MM-MMM.
>> WELL, YOU PROBABLY KNEW THAT
HAVING PREMARITAL SEX WASN'T
RIGHT.
I MEAN, IT JUST HAPPENED IN THE
MOMENT, RIGHT?
>> NO, I MEAN, I KNEW IT WASN'T
RIGHT, BUT IT'S NOT--
I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT'S GONNA TAKE ME A WHILE TO
ACCEPT DANIEL, BECAUSE I REALLY
DON'T KNOW HIM AS WELL AS YOU.
I MEAN, YOU'VE GOT TO KNOW EACH
OTHER.
BUT AFTER TIME, I'LL GET USED TO
JOHNNY BRAVO, I GUESS.
>> HOPEFULLY.
EVEN THOUGH I MOVED AN HOUR AWAY
FROM HOOVER, MY BOYFRIEND,
DANIEL, STILL COMES TO VISIT
EVERY WEEKEND.
IT REALLY MEANS A LOT TO ME,
SINCE I ONLY SEE HIM FOR A FEW
DAYS EACH WEEK.
WHAT DID YOU THINK
WHEN I TOLD YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T BELIEVE YOU.
>> YEAH, WHAT MADE YOU END UP
BELIEVING ME?
>> 'CAUSE YOU TOLD ME A BUNCH OF
TIMES.
>> DID YOU NOT WANT TO BELIEVE
ME, OR DID YOU JUST--
>> NO, I DIDN'T WANT
TO BELIEVE YOU.
>> WELL...
>> I DIDN'T WANT NO BABY.
I MEAN, I DO NOW, I GUESS,
BUT...
>> YEAH.
I THINK WE'LL LIKE THIS CHOICE.
>> I HOPE SO.
I MEAN, I LIKE YOU.
>> I'VE BEEN GOING TO THE LOCAL
HIGH SCHOOL FOR A COUPLE OF
MONTHS NOW.
IT WAS TOUGH LEAVING MY OLD
SCHOOL BEHIND AND ESPECIALLY MY
FRIENDS.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO MAKE MANY
NEW ONES YET, AND I DON'T LIKE
BEING ISOLATED, SO I STILL TRY
TO VISIT MY OLD FRIENDS
WHEN I CAN.
EVERYBODY GETS A POKER.
>> ALL RIGHT, GRAB YOUR WIENERS.
[laughter]
>> GRAB YOUR WIENERS.
>> SO WHAT'S, LIKE, Y'ALL'S
GAME PLAN?
>> POOP THE BABY OUT...
>> [laughs]
>> WELL, I GUESS, BEFORE THAT,
SAVE UP MONEY, AND THEN I'M
GOING TO U AT HUNTSVILLE.
AND MAJOR IN AERONAUTICAL AND
MECHANICAL ENGINEERING.
>> NICE.
>> GOOD MAJOR.
>> IT'S JUST A FANCY NAME.
>> SO ARE YOU GONNA LIVE OUT
THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> HECK, YEAH, SHE IS.
DUH.
>> YEAH, ABOUT LIVING BY
OURSELVES.
>> I'M NOT AS NERVOUS.
>> AND JUST DOING EVERYTHING ON
OUR OWN.
IT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH, BUT OUR
PLAN IS TO MOVE INTO COLLEGE
HOUSING TOGETHER AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF HUNTSVILLE ONCE
DANIEL AND I FINISH HIGH SCHOOL.
DANIEL IS A GRADE AHEAD OF ME,
BUT I'M GOING TO TAKE SUMMER
CLASSES SO I CAN FINISH ALL MY
WORK IN TIME TO GRADUATE EARLY.
MY DOCTOR SAYS I'LL NEED ABOUT A
MONTH TO RECOVER AFTER GIVING
BIRTH, BUT MY HIGH SCHOOL POLICY
ONLY ALLOWS TEN DAYS OF ABSENCES
PER SEMESTER.
HOPEFULLY I CAN TAKE MORE TIME
THAN THAT, EVEN THOUGH I'VE
ALREADY MISSED A BUNCH OF DAYS
DUE TO MORNING SICKNESS.
BUT THE NEXT DAY, MY STEPMOM,
KELLY, GOT A SURPRISE IN THE
MAIL.
>> LOOK AT THIS.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
>> "THE BOARD OF EDUCATION
STATES THAT IF YOUR CHILD HAS
MISSED MORE THAN THE MAXIMUM
NUMBER OF DAYS ALLOWED, HE OR
SHE MAY RECEIVE A GRADE OF 59,
FAILURE DUE TO ATTENDANCE."
>> SO THEY'RE GONNA MAE A BIG
DEAL OUT OF IT ALREADY, HUH?
>> MMM-HMM.
>> THEY DON'T LIKE IT 'CAUSE
SHE'S PREGNANT.
>> THEY KNOW THAT SHE'S GOT
STRAIGHT "A"s.
>> VALEDICTORIAN.
>> WE CAN'T GET RID OF THE FACT
THAT SHE HAS MISSED A FEW DAYS
THAT--OF BEING WHAT DO YOU CALL
IT--MORNING SICKNESS.
I'D RATHER YOU STAY HOME THAN GO
BARF ALL OVER HER DESK.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, I WOULD SIT THERE
MISERABLE ALL DAY ANYWAYS AND
NOT LEARN ANYTHING, SAME THING
AS NOT BEING THERE.
>> THIS COMMUNITY'S GONNA BE
KIND OF TOUGH.
>> THEY'RE NOT KIDDING AROUND
ANYMORE.
>> HOW ARE DANIEL AND I GOING TO
GO OFF TO COLLEGE TOGETHER IF I
CAN'T EVEN GRADUATE HIGH SCHOOL?
[wind whistling]
>> THE LETTER FROM MY HIGH
SCHOOL MAKES ME WORRY ABOUT
GRADUATING ON TIME.
I GUESS DANIEL AND I NEED TO
START THINKING ABOUT OUR FUTURE.
>> SO WHAT WERE YOUR, LIKE,
SCHOOL PLANS AND STUFF?
>> WELL, PROBABLY GO TO
U OF HUNTSVILLE.
YOU BETTER BE LIVING WITH ME--
AND THEN IN MARRIED STUDENT
HOUSING.
>> MY DAD REALLY DOESN'T THINK
THAT THAT'S AN OPTION, I GUESS.
>> HE'S GONNA HAVE TO GET
OVER IT, 'CAUSE YOU'RE A BIG
GIRL NOW.
>> I THINK WE STILL NEED TO SHOW
HIM, THOUGH.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO SHOW HIM THAT.
>> YEAH.
WE DEFINITELY NEED TO GET
MARRIED IN JUNE IF WE'RE GOING
TO LIVE TOGETHER IN STUDENT
HOUSING.
>> YEAH, I THINK IT COULD
HAPPEN.
>> YOU REALLY DO HAVE IT PLANNED
OUT, THOUGH?
>> YEAH, I PROMISE.
I REALLY DO.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE KIND OF
WEIRD TO LIVE BY OURSELVES,
'CAUSE NEITHER OF US KNOW HOW TO
TAKE CARE OF A BABY.
>> YOUR MATERNAL INSTINCTS WILL
KICK IN, AND I'LL BE A GOOD
DADDY.
>> I HOPE SO.
DANIEL AND I RECENTLY FOUND OUT
WE'RE HAVING A BOY, SO MY BEST
FRIENDS FROM BACK HOME ARE
BRINGING ME PRESENTS FOR THE
BABY TODAY.
>> TIE-DYE ONESIES.
>> HE IS A BOY, SO I MEAN...
[laughter]
>> CUTE.
>> YES.
>> BUT, YEAH, SINCE YOU'VE,
LIKE, MOVED HERE, YOU'VE BEEN A
LOT HAPPIER.
>> SHE REALLY HAS.
>> I CAN JUST TELL, BECAUSE IN,
LIKE, HOOVER, IT WAS, LIKE, ONE
BAD THING AFTER ANOTHER WITH
YOUR MOM AND...
>> SHE WAS REALLY SET ON ME
GETTING, LIKE, THE ABORTION AND
STUFF, AND WHEN I DIDN'T, UM,
YOU KNOW, SHE WAS JUST LIKE,
"IT'S GONNA BE HARD, AND YOU'RE
NOT GONNA LIVE HERE IN MY HOUSE
PREGNANT, SO YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO KEEP THE BABY AND GO LIVE
WHEREVER YOU CAN."
>> "WHEREVER YOU CAN."
>> AND IF MY DAD WOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN SUPPORTIVE, THEN ME AND
DANIEL, WE WERE PROBABLY GONNA
HAVE TO MOVE OUT.
>> WHAT DO Y'ALL PLAN ON DOING,
LIKE, ONCE THE BABY COMES?
>> HE'S GOT IT ALL PLANNED OUT.
>> OH, I GOTCHA.
>> HE'LL STILL HAVE TO FINISH
SCHOOL AND STUFF LIKE THAT, BUT
HE'LL DRIVE UP HERE, JUST LIKE
NORMAL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> UM, ACTUALLY, I'M NOT SURE ON
IF YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT OUR SCHOOL
DRAMA, BUT...
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> UM, THEY'RE TRYING TO, LIKE,
NOT LET ME BE ABLE TO GO TO
SCHOOL NEXT SEMESTER.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I ONLY GET TWO WEEKS OFF.
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> ONLY TWO WEEKS OFF?
THEY'RE GONNA FAIL YOU JUST
BECAUSE OF THAT?
THAT'S--OHH...
>> I HOPE NOT.
ALL OF DANIEL'S PLANS ARE RIDING
ON ME GRADUATING HIGH SCHOOL
EARLY, BUT IF MY SCHOOL IS GOING
TO FAIL ME, WE MIGHT NEED TO
RECONSIDER.
MY DAD WANTS TO MEET WITH
DANIEL'S PARENTS TO TALK ABOUT
MY SCHOOL SITUATION.
>> HE'S BEEN ACCEPTED TO
UNIVERSITY OF ALABAMA
HUNTSVILLE, AND THEY WANT TO
GIVE HIM A SCHOLARSHIP.
AND I'M VERY PROUD OF HIM.
RIGHT?
>> HIM GOING TO COLLEGE RIGHT
NOW IS SOMETHING THAT, YOU KNOW,
PERSONALLY, I COULD CARE LESS
ABOUT.
WE'RE HAVING PROBLEMS JUST
GETTING EMILY THROUGH THE
11TH GRADE.
WE REALIZED WHEN SHE MOVED OUT
HERE THAT THERE WAS GONNA BE
SOME...BUMPY ROADS, BUT I NEVER
THOUGHT THEY'D DO HER THAT WAY,
AND SHE'S GOT STRAIGHT "A"s.
>> AWW...
>> WELL, WHATEVER YOU WANT ME TO
DO--I'M NOT HER PARENTAL
GUARDIAN, BUT...
>> WE'RE NOT ASKING YOU TO BE,
BUT YOUR HELP AS FAR AS
SOMETHING TO GIVE US AN IDEA OF
WHAT WE COULD DO WOULD BE
AWESOME.
>> I SURE WILL.
I SURE WILL.
>> LUNCH WAS PRETTY AWKWARD, SO
WE'RE INVITING DANIEL'S PARENTS
BACK TO MY DAD'S HOUSE TO SHOW
THEM THE LETTER WE GOT FROM MY
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> "FAILURE DUE TO ATTENDANCE
FOR THE SEMESTER."
I MEAN, I'M SURE THEY COULD WORK
WITH YOU.
>> BUT WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO
MORE THAN JUST SIGN A LETTER.
>> WELL, ONCE YOU GRADUATE FROM
HIGH SCHOOL, WHAT ARE YOUR
PLANS?
>> BE GOING TO SCHOOL TO
U AT HUNTSVILLE.
AND THEN I'LL BE WORKING TOO.
'CAUSE THE RENT'S NOT GONNA BE
MUCH AT ALL.
>> ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT MARRIED
STUDENT HOUSING?
>> YEAH.
>> [clears throat]
>> HEY, THE KID IS SMART.
THAT'S GREAT AND WONDERFUL, BUT
I CAN HAVE MY OPINION ON PUTTING
A GOLDEN PATH DOWN FOR THIS
BOY'S EDUCATION, AND MY GIRL'S
GONNA BE WORKING AT THE LOCAL
PIGGLY WIGGLY AS A CASH
REGISTER--
>> OH, I HOPE NOT.
>> I HOPE NOT TOO.
>> IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER WHAT
YOU THINK, THOUGH, BECAUSE
EVERYTHING--
>> I THINK IT DOES MATTER,
BECAUSE I COULD STOP IT, PERIOD.
I CAN KEEP HER FROM EVEN
MARRYING YOU, PAL.
YOU HAVEN'T SHOWED ME ANYTHING
YET.
>> WHAT DO I NEED TO DO TO SHOW
YOU THAT I AM A RESPONSIBLE
PERSON?
I AM DOING EVERYTHING THAT I
HUMAN POSSIBLY CAN, AND YET
YOU'RE STILL NOT SATISFIED.
>> MAYBE THAT'S JUST THE FATHER
IN ME, I GUESS.
[crickets chirping]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOUR
PARENTS THOUGHT?
>> THEY PROBABLY THINK YOUR
DAD'S A JACKASS.
BUT I MEAN, THAT'S COOL.
>> BUT I SEE WHERE EVERYBODY'S
COMING FROM.
>> IT'S HARD FOR HIM TO GIVE YOU
UP TO ME.
BUT, YEAH, HE'S GONNA HAVE TO
GET OVER IT ONE DAY.
>> YEAH.
I HOPE MY DAD BECOMES MORE
ACCEPTING OF DANIEL.
HE JUST WANTS ME TO FINISH HIGH
SCHOOL AND NOT FALL BEHIND ON MY
EDUCATION.
WHEN MY STEPMOM CALLED THE
SCHOOL TO SEE IF THEY WOULD GIVE
ME MORE THAN TWO WEEKS OFF AFTER
I DELIVER, SHE LEARNED THAT I
WAS GOING MISS TOO MANY DAYS TO
PASS MY CLASSES.
DANIEL'S MOM WASN'T ABLE TO PULL
ANY STRINGS EITHER, SO MY DAD
AND STEPMOM WITHDREW ME FROM
SCHOOL THAT DAY.
I WAS KIND OF SHOCKED.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THIS WAS ALL
GONNA HAPPEN TODAY.
>> YEAH, WELL, I DIDN'T SEE ANY
REASON TO KEEP YOU THERE ONE
MORE DAY, BECAUSE THEY WERE NOT
GONNA BUDGE.
>> YEAH.
>> I CALLED YOUR COUNSELOR AT
SCHOOL, AND SHE GAVE ME A LITTLE
BIT MORE INFORMATION ON THE HOME
SCHOOLING, AND YOU NEED TO GO
AHEAD AND GET STARTED SO THAT
YOU COULD POSSIBLY GRADUATE
EARLY AND THINGS CAN MOVE ON
WITH YOU AND DANIEL.
>> YEAH.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT BEING
PREGNANT CAUSED ME TO BE
WITHDRAWN FROM HIGH SCHOOL.
I'VE ALREADY HAD TO SACRIFICE SO
MUCH: A RELATIONSHIP WITH MY
MOM, BEING WITH MY OLD FRIENDS,
AND NOW HIGH SCHOOL?
I HOPE HOME SCHOOLING DOESN'T
SLOW DOWN MY PLANS OF MOVING IN
WITH DANIEL AFTER GRADUATION.
I'M REALLY ANXIOUS FOR HIM TO
GET HERE THIS WEEKEND SO I CAN
BRING HIM UP TO SPEED ON MY
SCHOOL SITUATION.
>> HI, BABY.
>> HI.
I GOT WITHDRAWN TODAY, AND NOW
I'M GONNA BE HOME SCHOOLED.
>> YEAH.
WE'RE GONNA GO TOMORROW THERE
FOR A MEETING.
>> SO DO YOU THINK YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO COME OVER THIS WEEKEND?
>> WELL, I REALLY HOPE YOU CAN
COME BY SOON.
I MEAN...
>> I LOVE YOU.
BYE.
I KNOW DANIEL HAS A BUSY
SCHEDULE, BETWEEN WORKING AND
FINISHING SCHOOL, BUT I STILL
WISH HE COULD COME OVER MORE
OFTEN.
SINCE MY DAD AND STEPMOM
WITHDREW ME FROM HIGH SCHOOL, MY
ONLY OPTION SEEMS TO BE HOME
SCHOOLING, SO I'M GOING TO MEET
WITH THE COUNSELOR TO SEE IF
I'LL STILL BE ABLE TO GRADUATE
ON TIME.
>> HI.
HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
TELL ME, WHY ARE YOU HERE TODAY?
>> SHE IS PREGNANT, AND SHE'S
MISSING A LOT OF SCHOOL.
>> OKAY.
>> AND WE WERE GONNA SEE IF IT
WAS OKAY IF I COULD GRADUATE
IN MAY.
>> OKAY, IT IS POSSIBLE, BUT YOU
WILL HAVE TO PUT IN A LOT OF
SCHOOL DAYS BY WORKING YOUR
HOLIDAYS OR BY WORKING WEEKENDS.
>> WHO, LIKE, MAKES SURE THAT I
DO WORK AND THAT I DO COME?
>> YOU WILL REPORT TO ME EVERY
NINE WEEKS.
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS LONG ENOUGH
THAT I WILL BE ABLE TO TELL
IF YOU HAVE...
>> DONE THE WORK.
>> IF YOU HAVE NOT, I ALWAYS
HAVE THE OPTION OF DISMISSING
A STUDENT.
>> AND THEN EVEN WITH THE BABY
BEING AT THE HOUSE, YOU STILL
THINK I COULD WORK?
>> YOU CAN DO IT IF YOU WANT IT.
>> THAT'S THE PLAN, THEN.
>> WELL, SIGN HER UP.
>> OKAY.
THIS WILL BE FOR YOUR ANATOMY.
>> LITERATURE.
OKAY.
MATH WILL BE USING BOOKLET FORM,
AND HISTORY WILL BE THE VERY
SAME CURRICULUM.
>> OKAY.
YOU'D THINK HOME SCHOOLING WOULD
HAVE LESS HOMEWORK THAN REGULAR
SCHOOL, BUT IT LOOKS LIKE IT
MIGHT BE EVEN HARDER.
BEFORE OUR JUNE WEDDING, I NEED
TO FINISH BOTH THE 11TH AND
12TH GRADE CURRICULUMS IF WE'RE
GOING TO MOVE INTO MARRIED
HOUSING AT THE UNIVERSITY OF
HUNTSVILLE NEXT SUMMER.
IT'S A LOT OF WORK, SO I'D
BETTER GET STARTED.
>> SO HOW'S LIFE BEEN SINCE THE
LAST TIME I SAW YOU?
>> GOOD, I GUESS.
HOW ARE YOUR EXAMS?
>> UGH...
THE CLASSES ARE TOUGH.
HOW ABOUT YOUR EXAMS?
>> I DON'T HAVE TO TAKE EXAMS
WITH THE HOME SCHOOL, SO...
>> OH, YEAH.
I KEEP FORGETTING YOU'RE DOING
HOME SCHOOL.
>> MMM-HMM.
>> SO DO YOU LIKE IT MORE, OR...
>> UM, IT'S KIND OF, LIKE,
BORING NOT DOING ANYTHING ALL
DAY, BUT ALL I REALLY HAVE TO DO
IS MY MATH.
>> YOU'RE GOOD AT MATH, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, IT'S JUST HARD TO LEARN
MYSELF.
>> YEAH.
SO WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON WITH YOU
AND DANIEL?
>> HE'S REAL BAD ABOUT, LIKE,
UM, SAYING HE'S GONNA, LIKE,
COME OVER AND THEN, LIKE, NOT
COMING OVER OR HAVING SOMETHING
ALL OF A SUDDEN COMES UP TO
WHERE HE DOESN'T EVER COME OVER.
HE JUST HAS TO WORK A LOT.
>> THAT'S NOT COOL.
>> HE SAID HE'S GONNA TRY
HARDER, SO...
>> I KNOW LONG-DISTANCE
RELATIONSHIPS TAKE A LOT OF
WORK, BUT IT'S ESPECIALLY HARD
BEING PREGNANT AND NOT HAVING
DANIEL AROUND.
IT'S HARDER TO BE AWAY FROM HIM
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
SO I WAS GLAD HE DIDN'T CANCEL
ON ME THE FOLLOWING WEEKEND.
I'M GLAD YOU COULD GET OFF.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
I WANTED TO SEE YOU.
>> HOW COME YOU DIDN'T COME LAST
WEEKEND?
>> WELL, I HAD TO WORK.
>> I HOPE YOU'RE GONNA BE AROUND
THE SAME OR A LITTLE BIT MORE
WHEN HE IS HERE,
JUST 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO TAKE
CARE OF HIM BY MYSELF.
>> I MEAN, I WOULDN'T EITHER.
>> I KNOW YOU WOULDN'T.
I GUESS WE'LL HAVE
TO WAIT AND SEE.
>> YEAH.
[swallows audibly]
>> IT SEEMS THE CLOSER WE GET TO
MY DUE DATE, THE MORE I WORRY
ABOUT HIS COMMITMENT.
IT'S STRANGE NOT SPENDING
CHRISTMAS AT MY MOM'S HOUSE
THIS YEAR, BUT SOON ENOUGH, I'LL
BE ABLE TO CELEBRATE
WITH MY BABY.
DANIEL WAS SUPPOSED TO COME OVER
TO HELP DECORATE THE TREE, BUT
HE CALLED AND TOLD ME HE
COULDN'T GET OFF WORK.
>> JUST SAY ONE DAY THAT THAT
BOY DOES HAVE THE NERVE TO MARRY
YOU OR SOMETHING, THAT WHAT
YOU WANT?
>> YEAH, I GUESS.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, YOU GUESS?
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU AND
DANIEL ARE STILL GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER?
IS THERE THINGS THAT DO BOTHER
YOU ABOUT DANIEL THAT DIDN'T
BEFORE?
>> WE KNOW EACH OTHER.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T KNOW SOMEBODY
WELL ENOUGH IN A YEAR, ANYWAYS,
BUT I MEAN, YEAH, THERE'S STUFF
THAT BOTHERS ME.
[laughs]
HE GETS ON MY NERVES ALL THE
TIME JUST BECAUSE HE'S DOING
SOMETHING, BUT I MEAN, IF IT
DOESN'T WORK OUT AND WE CAN'T
GET ALONG, THEN WE WON'T HAVE TO
GET MARRIED AND MOVE IN
TOGETHER.
>> HMM.
SO THAT WAY THAT SOUNDED IS, SHE
WAS STILL ON THE SKEPTICAL SIDE
THAT...
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE PLAYING
HOUSE FOR A COUPLE OF YEARS
AND JUST DO, LIKE, A TEST TRIAL.
THIS IS A COMMITMENT.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
>> DO YOU?
>> IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T LOVE
DANIEL ENOUGH TO GET MARRIED;
I JUST HOPE HE'LL BE HERE TO
SUPPORT ME AFTER THE BABY COMES.
>> I'M PRETTY PREOCCUPIED
THINKING ABOUT THE BABY THESE
DAYS, SO I HAVE TO KEEP UP ON MY
SCHOOLWORK SO I DON'T FALL
BEHIND...
[bells chiming]
ESPECIALLY SINCE DANIEL AND I
PLAN TO GET MARRIED IN JUNE
AFTER I FINISH THE 12TH GRADE.
A FEW DAYS BEFORE MY DUE DATE,
I WOKE UP WITH REALLY BAD PAIN.
IT'S HAPPENING NOW.
GUESS I'M GONNA CALL DANIEL
REAL QUICK.
>> HI.
>> GOT TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> THEY'RE, LIKE, TWO MINUTES
APART.
I LOVE YOU.
I'LL CALL YOU.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> OKAY, AND IT JUST HAPPENED
THEN.
>> MY DAD IS AWAY ON BUSINESS
AND ISN'T ABLE TO COME BACK IN
TIME FOR THE BIRTH, SO MY
STEPMOM IS TAKING ME TO THE
HOSPITAL.
EVEN THOUGH DANIEL HAD A LONG
DRIVE TO THE HOSPITAL, HE MADE
IT AS SOON AS HE COULD.
AND IT MEANS A LOT TO ME THAT
HE'S HERE.
I WISH MY MOTHER WAS HERE
WITH ME.
I GUESS SHE'S STILL NOT READY TO
ACCEPT THIS YET.
[bleep], SORRY.
MY CONTRACTIONS ARE GETTING
STRONGER.
>> I'M JUST GONNA SWAB YOU
A LITTLE BIT WITH THIS.
>> OKAY.
>> TRY NOT TO TENSE UP YOUR
LEGS, SWEETIE.
>> [groans]
>> YOU'RE ABOUT ONE, ONE
CENTIMETER DILATED.
[electronic beeping]
>> YOU KNOW, WE JUST CAN'T TELL.
THOSE BABIES, THEY HAVE A MIND
OF THEIR OWN, SO WE JUST DON'T
KNOW.
>> OKAY.
THE PAIN IS GETTING WORSE.
THE NURSE SAID I'M THREE
CENTIMETERS DILATED--
STILL NOT ENOUGH TO HAVE THE
BABY.
WE'LL GIVE YOU AN EPIDURAL
WHENEVER YOU WANT TO.
>> CAN YOU CALL DR. SHUSTER FOR
SOME LIDOCAINE?
>> OKAY.
>> THANKS.
>> I KNOW IT WILL HELP WITH THE
PAIN, BUT GETTING AN EPIDURAL
KIND OF SUCKS.
>> SORRY, SORRY, SORRY, SORRY.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> REALLY?
>> IT'S A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN
"KIND OF" NERVOUS.
>> I MEAN, I KNOW YOU THINK I'M
CRAZY, BUT WE'VE HAD DADS
PASS OUT.
>> PLEASE DON'T.
>> OR EVERYTHING?
>> YEAH, I FEEL THAT.
[electronic beeping]
I HOPE THAT'S NOTHING BAD.
[beeping intensifies]
>> YOU'RE ALL THE WAY DILATED.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU READY
FOR DELIVERY.
>> WHOO.
>> PUSH, ONE, TWO.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
TEN...
>> [bleep].
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> [moaning] OKAY...
>> PUSH.
[voices overlapping]
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
THERE YOU GO.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> YEAH, HE'S COMING.
>> PERFECT.
HOLD IT. HOLD IT. HOLD IT.
HOLD IT. HOLD IT.
>> I CAN SEE HIS HEAD NOW.
GOOD JOB.
>> OH, JESUS.
>> WITH YOUR NEXT PUSHES, YOU
SHOULD HAVE A BABY, OKAY?
COME ON, AS HARD AS YOU CAN.
BEST PUSH ALL DAY.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> AAAGH!
OH, MY GOD.
>> 15:51.
>> OH...
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT HIM AND
SEE WHAT YOU'RE GONNA CALL HIM.
HEY, BUDDY.
>> YOU GET TO TELL SOME
STORIES.
[baby crying]
>> HE'S BIG.
>> * LATELY I'VE FOUND MYSELF *
* WONDERING OUT LOUD *
* WONDERING WHAT I WAS *
* TO BE *
>> * PATIENCE *
* MAKES HER HEART *
* GROW STRONGER *
[baby wailing]
>> * ONE DAY YOU'LL UNDERSTAND *
* HOW MUCH YOU HAVE ME *
* ONE DAY YOU'LL REALIZE *
* WE HAD IT EASY... *
>> DANIEL AND I STILL HAVE A LOT
TO LEARN ABOUT BEING PARENTS.
>> IT'S OKAY, BUD.
>> MY DAD'S STILL AWAY ON
BUSINESS.
YEAH, YEAH.
BUT AT LEAST MY STEPMOM IS HERE
FOR ENCOURAGEMENT.
>> I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
A GOOD MOMMY.
>> THANKS.
>> I AM REALLY PROUD OF YOU AND
DANIEL BOTH.
>> SO READY TO GO HOME?
>> YEAH.
ARE YOU?
>> I'M READY TO LEAVE THE
HOSPITAL, BUT I'M NOT READY TO
LEAVE ALL THESE PEOPLE THAT KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
>> YEAH.
>> MY DAD'S BACK FROM HIS WORK
TRIP, AND HE'S EAGER TO SEE
LIAM.
>> HOW ARE Y'ALL?
>> GROUP HUG.
OH...
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS.
>> WELL, Y'ALL MADE A BEAUTIFUL
CREATURE, DIDN'T YOU?
>> WE DID WHAT WE COULD.
>> WHAT'D YOU SAY, DANIEL?
>> MMM, WIPE MY EYES OUT,
PLEASE.
MMM.
>> THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I CRIED LIKE A LITTLE GIRL.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN ME.
>> THAT SMELLS LIKE A REAL ONE
THERE.
>> WE HAVEN'T ACTUALLY CHANGED A
MESSY DIAPER, JUST THE WET ONES.
>> THAT ONE'S A MESSY ONE,
THERE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S OKAY, BUDDY.
[baby crying]
I'M SORRY, BUDDY.
>> THAT LOOKS FUNNY.
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> GOLLY.
I PUT IT ON BACKWARDS.
[baby cooing]
>> DANIEL ONLY GOT TWO DAYS OFF
FROM WORK, SO I'D BETTER MAKE
THE MOST OF OUR TIME TOGETHER
WHILE I HAVE HIM HERE TO HELP.
>> HE JUST FARTED ON ME.
>> YOU WANT TO TRY TO FEED HIM?
SHHH...
I'M NOT LOOKING FORWARD TO DOING
THIS ALL BY MYSELF.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> I'M FINE.
>> IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU THINK DANIEL'S GONNA
BE ABLE TO DO WHAT HE SAYS?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SAID THAT A LITTLE
SARCASTICALLY.
YOU THINK BEING THIS FAR AWAY IS
GONNA BE A BIG DEAL?
I MEAN, YEAH, I KNOW IT'S KIND
OF LAME.
LIKE HIM WALKING AND STUFF
LIKE THAT.
AND HE STILL HAS TO GO TO WORK,
SO...
>> GIVE YOU A LITTLE MOM AND
BABY BOND TIME?
>> YEAH.
I WANT A LOT OF BONDING TIME
WITH LIAM.
I JUST HOPE I'LL BE ABLE TO DO
THIS ON MY OWN.
TAKING CARE OF A BABY IS
EXHAUSTING BY MYSELF.
I WISH DANIEL WAS HERE
TO HELP ME.
[baby crying]
[snorts]
IT FEELS LIKE I HAVEN'T SLEPT IN
THREE DAYS.
I'M EXHAUSTED, AND I HAVE TO
START DOING MY HOME SCHOOL WORK
AGAIN.
>> * INTO THE ICE AGE *
* INTO THE STONE *
>> BUT IT'S HARD TO CONCENTRATE
WHEN I'M WATCHING LIAM EVERY
SECOND.
>> * INTO THE DARK AGE *
* COMING DOWN *
* INTO THE ICE *
[baby whining]
* YOU KEEP FALLING ASLEEP *
* WE GO INTO THE ICE AGE *
>> CAREFUL.
>> * INTO THE STONE *
* AGAIN *
>> HOW AM I GOING TO GET ALL OF
THIS DONE?
OVER THE PAST TWO WEEKS, I'VE
BEEN DOING THE BEST I CAN WITH
LIAM WHILE DANIEL IS WORKING AND
FINISHING SCHOOL,
BUT IT'S EXHAUSTING TO RAISE
A BABY ON MY OWN,
AND DANIEL NEEDS TO KNOW THAT
I'M FRUSTRATED.
I'M GLAD YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO WORK
TODAY.
>> YEAH.
>> WISH YOU COULD BE AROUND ALL
THE TIME, 'CAUSE I DON'T LIKE
TAKING CARE OF HIM BY MYSELF.
>> I WISH I COULD BE AROUND
MORE, BUT I'VE GOT SCHOOL,
THEN WORK.
>> BUT I MEAN, STILL, THAT'S
KIND OF LAME.
I JUST DON'T LIKE WAKING UP WITH
HIM ALL THE TIME BY MYSELF.
'CAUSE YOU'VE NEVER REALLY DONE
IT ONE WHOLE TIME.
>> I MEAN, I DO EVERYTHING ELSE,
THOUGH.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> LIKE PROVIDE.
>> SO?
WE COULD TRADE.
>> OH, YEAH?
>> IT'S NOT AS EASY AS YOU
THINK.
>> I THINK YOU'RE MAKING IT
SOUND A WHOLE LOT HARDER THAN IT
IS, THOUGH.
>> NO, I PROMISE I'M NOT.
>> IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW, I GUESS.
>> OKAY, THEN.
THEN DON'T SAY THAT.
>> WHAT YOU DO IS NOT, LIKE,
24-7.
LIKE, YOU HAVE A BREAK WHEN YOU
GO TO SLEEP AT NIGHT.
I MEAN, I STILL HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT LIAM, AND I CAN'T, LIKE,
GO DO THINGS ANYTIME I WANT,
AND YOU CAN JUST BE, LIKE, "I'M
COMING HOME AT 12:00.
>> BUT I MEAN, I MIGHT AS WELL
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE
OPPORTUNITIES WHILE I HAVE IT.
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T HAVE ANY
OPPORTUNITIES--OR HAVE FEW AND
FAR BETWEEN.
YOU STILL HAVE THE SAME LIFE
NOW, EVEN THOUGH HE IS HERE AND
A RESPONSIBILITY.
I JUST HAVE MORE RESPONSIBILITY
OF TAKING CARE OF HIM ALL THE
TIME THAN YOU DO.
>> I DO THE BEST I CAN.
>> I JUST WONDER IF DANIEL'S
BEST IS GOING TO CUT IT.
OUR PLAN OF GETTING MARRIED IN
JUNE AND MOVING TO HUNTSVILLE
SOUNDED A LOT BETTER TO ME
THREE MONTHS AGO.
>> OH, EMILY, I JUST GOT A
LETTER FROM YOUR HOME SCHOOL,
AND SHE SAYS THAT YOU'RE NOT ON
TRACK TO GRADUATE.
>> WHAT THE HELL?
>> YOU'RE GONNA NOT BE ABLE TO
BE FINISHED BY THE END OF MAY.
>> YOU REALIZE THAT'S MY BIGGEST
FEAR.
>> I KNOW, BUT I MEAN, HAVING
LIAM, IT MAKES IT HARD, AND I
CAN'T READ, LIKE, A PAGE WITHOUT
HAVING TO LOOK UP, AND THEN HE
GETS MY TRAIN OF THOUGHT ALL OFF
AND EVERYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> I MEAN, TO ME, THERE'S NO
EXCUSE FOR IT.
>> YEAH, THERE IS.
>> NO.
IF YOU DON'T GET YOUR EDUCATION,
YOU'LL BE LETTING LIAM DOWN.
YOU QUIT TWIRLING YOUR HAIR AND
LOOKING OFF IN THE DIRECTION.
IT'S CRUNCH TIME.
>> LOOK, I'M GONNA DO IT, OKAY?
I'VE GOT A LOT ON MY MIND.
SCHOOL IS STRESSING ME OUT,
AND I'M GETTING MORE FRUSTRATED
WITH DANIEL EACH WEEK.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GET MARRIED IN
JUNE, AND I STILL HAVE A TON OF
HOMEWORK TO CATCH UP ON, AND I'M
STARTING TO FEEL RESENTFUL
TOWARDS DANIEL, BECAUSE IF HE
WAS AROUND MORE, I WOULDN'T BE
SO FAR BEHIND.
>> CAREFUL, BABY.
>> OH, NO!
>> DANIEL...
DANIEL, STOP.
SIT HIM UP RIGHT.
LOOK AT HIM.
>> OKAY, I'M DONE.
>> OH, MAN.
COME ON.
>> OH, HE'S PEEING.
>> WELL, COVER IT UP.
CAN YOU HAND ME HIS TOWEL?
>> IT'S GOT PEE ON IT.
>> HAND IT TO ME.
I'M NOT A BABY.
YOU GONNA DRY HIS HAIR?
>> WITH WHAT?
>> THE TOWEL.
>> THIS TOWEL?
>> IT DOESN'T HAVE PISS ALL OVER
IT, DANIEL.
>> YOU WANT ME TO GO MAKE HIM
A BOTTLE?
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE'D THE FORMULA GO?
[baby crying]
>> HURRY UP.
[formula sloshing]
WHY WOULD YOU JUST PUT YOUR
DIRTY FINGER ON IT?
>> IT'S NOT DIRTY.
I WASHED LIAM WITH THEM.
SO I KIND OF WASHED THEM AT THE
SAME TIME.
>> IT'S DIFFERENT WHEN YOU HELP,
AND IT'S YOUR JOB TO HELP.
>> UP UNTIL NOW, I'VE BEEN DOING
THIS BY MYSELF, AND IT'S
GETTING FRUSTRATING.
I BARELY FINISHED MY JUNIOR YEAR
OF HOME SCHOOL, AND I'M ALREADY
STRUGGLING TO FIND TIME
FOR THE REST.
I'VE NOT SEEN MY FRIENDS FROM
BACK HOME SINCE LIAM WAS BORN.
IT'LL BE NICE TO FINALLY CATCH
UP WITH THEM.
>> [laughing]
GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> SO WHERE'S LIAM?
WHO'S TAKING CARE OF HIM?
>> UM, MY STEPMOM AND MY DAD,
AND OTHER THAN THAT, I REALLY
DON'T WANT ANYBODY ELSE
WATCHING HIM.
>> DANIEL?
>> YEAH, HE'S THIRD.
[laughter]
>> OKAY...
>> WOW.
>> WELL, HE'S NEVER TAKEN CARE
OF--I MEAN, HE'S WATCHED HIM
MAYBE, LIKE, TWO HOURS AT THE
MOST BY HIMSELF, BUT IT'S JUST
LIKE--I DON'T KNOW.
HE GETS TIRED OF IT REALLY
EASILY, AND HE DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
DOING IT, AND IT MAKES ME SO,
LIKE, IRRITATED SOMETIMES.
LIKE, DANIEL DOESN'T FEED HIM
EVER, SO I MEAN, IT'S MORE
STRESSFUL, I GUESS.
>> WELL, DANIEL SHOULD HELP YOU.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT EVERYBODY
SAYS, BUT...
>> LIKE, WHEN HE DOES COME OVER.
>> HE'S LIAM'S DAD.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT ARE YOU STILL GETTING
HOME SCHOOLED?
>> YEAH, BUT I JUST FINISHED
MY 11TH GRADE YEAR.
>> ARE YOU ALMOST READY TO
FINISH?
>> OH, NO, I JUST STARTED, LIKE,
ONE BOOK, LIKE LAST WEEK.
>> EMILY!
>> GOSH, YOU HAVE TO WORK, LIKE,
SUPER HARD.
>> IT IS A LOT HARDER THAN I
THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE.
IT'S A CONSTANT, LIKE, 24-HOUR,
SEVEN-DAYS-A-WEEK JOB.
I NEED TO GET SOME ANXIETY PILLS
OR SOMETHING.
[laughs]
I'VE BEEN SO OVERWHELMED WITH
TAKING CARE OF LIAM THAT I HAD
TO ASK MY STEPMOM TO WATCH HIM
WHILE I TRY AND CATCH UP ON
SCHOOLWORK.
[baby crying]
BUT IT'S REALLY NOT HER JOB;
IT'S DANIEL'S.
HE AND I HAVE BEEN SO BUSY
ARGUING OVER WHO HELPS OUT MORE
WITH THE BABY THAT WE HAVEN'T
REALLY BEEN TALKING ABOUT OUR
WEDDING PLANS AT ALL.
I'M STARTING TO WORRY THAT
GETTING MARRIED IN JUNE MIGHT
BE TOO SOON.
>> YOU DON'T THINK WE'RE TOO
YOUNG TO GET MARRIED?
>> I MEAN, PEOPLE USED TO GET
MARRIED WHEN THEY WERE, LIKE,
13 OR 14 YEARS OLD.
>> YEAH, WELL, I GUESS I'M
EXCITED.
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> YOU'RE MAD HALF THE TIME.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> YEAH, YOU ARE.
>> SOMETIMES.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO FEEL LIKE
I'M STUCK WITH YOU.
>> WELL, YOU ARE.
>> WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
>> KINDA BOUND TOGETHER.
>> HOW COME?
>> BECAUSE OF LIAM?
>> AND I LOVE YOU.
>> I KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT A BAD THING.
IT JUST SOUNDS KIND OF LIKE--
"YOU'RE STUCK WITH ME,"
LIKE YOU DON'T HAVE ANY OTHER
CHOICES.
>> YOU DON'T.
>> [stammers]
OKAY, WHATEVER.
>> I'M READY FOR HIM TO BE ABLE
TO TALK SO HE CAN BE A LITTLE
SMARTER, JUST LIKE HIS MOM.
>> SHH.
DANIEL SAYS I DON'T HAVE ANY
CHOICES, BUT DECIDING WHEN TO
GET MARRIED IS REALLY UP TO ME.
>> DANIEL WILL BE STARTING
COLLEGE IN HUNTSVILLE SOON AND
WILL WANT ME AND THE BABY TO
FOLLOW HIM THERE, BUT I'M NOT
SURE THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
I THOUGHT HAVING A BABY WOULD
BRING US CLOSER TOGETHER, YET
SOMEHOW IT'S ONLY MADE ME MORE
FRUSTRATED WITH DANIEL.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GET MARRIED IN
JUNE, BUT I THINK I NEED MORE
TIME TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
RIGHT NOW, SINCE HE DON'T HELP
TAKE CARE OF LIAM ALL THE TIME
LIKE I DO, HE GETS ON MY NERVES,
AND I THINK THAT I'M GONNA GET
IRRITATED WITH HIM AND JUST FEEL
LIKE I DON'T WANT TO BE WITH HIM
ANYMORE, 'CAUSE THAT'S HOW I
FEEL NOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT AROUND HIM
ENOUGH.
ALL I KNOW IS, HE ACTS LIKE HE'S
TRYING TO DO THE RIGHT THING,
AND THERE'S SOME REASON NOW
YOU DON'T CLICK WITH HIM.
>> 'CAUSE DANIEL IRRITATES ME
SOMETIMES.
A LOT OF THE TIME.
>> IF YOU THINK THAT YOU'RE NOT
GONNA GET ALONG WITH HIM NOW,
WHAT'S GONNA CHANGE WHEN YOU
MOVE OFF AND LIVE TOGETHER?
>> BECAUSE WE'LL ALL BE
TOGETHER.
ALL I'LL I'M SAYING IS, MOVE UP
THERE AND LIVE TOGETHER FOR HALF
A YEAR, SIX MONTHS, AND IF
EVERYTHING'S PEACHY STILL, GET
MARRIED.
AND IF IT'S NOT PEACHY, THEN WE
EITHER WILL DECIDE IF WE DON'T
NEED TO BE TOGETHER OR IF WE
NEED TO SEE IF WE CAN WORK IT
OUT A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
>> SOUNDS LIKE TO ME YOU'RE
PRETTY POSITIVE THAT Y'ALL ARE
NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO LIVE
TOGETHER FOR VERY LONG.
>> I'M JUST SAYING THAT THAT WAS
A THOUGHT.
IT WAS A FEELING.
DANIEL DOESN'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT IT...
'CAUSE HE PROBABLY WOULDN'T
LIKE IT.
>> [sighs]
YOU MADE A CHOICE.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> WELL, WHEN ARE YOU GONNA
WAKE THE HELL UP AND KNOW THAT
IS NOW?
YOU GOT A BABY, SWEETIE.
>> I KNOW DANIEL WANTS TO GET
MARRIED BEFORE STARTING COLLEGE,
BUT I NEED TO MAKE SURE WE CAN
LIVE TOGETHER FIRST.
AFTER TALKING TO MY DAD, I
DECIDED TO TELL DANIEL THAT WE
SHOULD HOLD OFF ON GETTING
MARRIED THIS SUMMER.
HE DIDN'T EXACTLY TAKE
THE NEWS WELL.
>> YOU FEEL BAD?
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO GET
MARRIED ON JUNE 26TH?
>> WELL, IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER.
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
>> WELL, I DON'T THINK WE
TOOK ENOUGH TIME TO LOOK AT
EVERYTHING, AND WE JUST JUMPED
INTO IT, AND I MEAN, I'M SORRY
FOR CHANGING MY MIND, BUT I WAS
JUST REALIZING HOW DIFFERENT
THINGS WERE AND HOW EVERYBODY
WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOSH, DANIEL'S
GONNA GO TO SCHOOL.
YAY."
AND I WAS JUST LIKE, "WELL, YOU
KNOW, I MIGHT AS WELL JUST DO
THE HOME SCHOOL SO I CAN
GRADUATE SO WE CAN ALL STAY
TOGETHER."
AND THEN NOW I HAVE TO GO TO
SCHOOL THERE.
>> SO YOU DON'T WANT TO LIVE
WITH ME?
>> WELL, I REALLY DON'T WANT TO
GO TO SCHOOL UP THERE.
>> [bleep] GREAT.
YOU DON'T EVEN WANT TO MOVE UP
THERE AT ALL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> CAN YOU TRY IT FOR A YEAR?
>> AND PAY FOR SOMEWHERE WHERE
WE'RE GONNA LIVE THAT I DON'T
WANT TO MOVE ANYWAYS?
>> WHERE ELSE AM I GONNA GO
TO SCHOOL?
WHERE ELSE AM I GONNA BE ABLE TO
GET A SCHOLARSHIPS LIKE THAT?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO YELL.
>> [sighs]
>> IT'S NOT ALL ABOUT YOU.
>> I KNOW IT'S NOT.
I JUST WISH YOU HADN'T ALL OF A
SUDDEN CHANGED YOUR MIND.
>> I GUESS I REALIZED I HAVE
OTHER OPTIONS.
>> THAT'S WHAT MAKES ME UPSET.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE SOME OF 'EM DON'T
INCLUDE ME.
>> KINDA TIRED OF TALKING.
>> WELL, I DON'T REALLY CARE.
>> [sighs]
I'M GONNA GO OUTSIDE.
>> NO.
I THINK I'VE REALIZED IN THE
PAST COUPLE WEEKS THAT DANIEL
AND I NEED SOME TIME TO REALLY
THINK ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP.
BEING 16 AND HAVING A BABY, I'M
NOT STABLE IN THE RELATIONSHIP
WITH DANIEL.
I CAN'T FINISH MY EDUCATION
RIGHT AWAY, SO IT'S HARD.
I DEFINITELY WISHED I WOULD HAVE
WAITED.
IT'S A CONSTANT, 24-HOUR,
EVERY-SINGLE-DAY JOB, AND I JUST
REALLY HATE THE FACT THAT I'VE
GIVEN UP WAY MORE THAN HE HAS.
I REALLY HOPE THAT LIAM IS PROUD
OF ME IN THE FUTURE, AND WHEN
HE'S 16 AND 17 AND HE LOOKS AT
HIS LIFE, I WANT HIM TO REALLY
REALIZE AND UNDERSTAND WHAT I
GAVE UP FOR HIM.
I JUST HOPE HE LEARNS FROM OUR
MISTAKES TO NOT GET SOMEBODY
PREGNANT AT A YOUNG AGE.
* *
>> female announcer: ON THE
NEXT 16 AND PREGNANT...
>> I JUST WANTED HER TO KNOW
THAT HER PARENTS ARE ALWAYS
GONNA BE THERE, BOTH PARENTS.
>> YOU THINK WHEN I FELT YOU
MOVE IN MY STOMACH, IT WAS,
"I WANT HER TO BE PREGNANT
AT 16?"
THAT WAS NOT MY DREAM
FOR MY CHILD.
>> THEY CAN'T SAY WE'RE NOT
TRYING.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
[baby crying]
>> IDIOT!
I HATE YOU!
OOH, I HATE YOU!
[upbeat piano music]
* *
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS *
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA *
* GET THROUGH IT ALL *
* I'M WEAK, BUT I'M *
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE *
* WHEN IT'S ALL DONE... *