>> [laughs]
HI, I'M BRIANA.
I WAS BORN IN BROOKLYN,
NEW YORK, AND THEN MOVED TO
ORLANDO, FLORIDA WHEN I WAS TEN
WITH MY MOM, OLDER SISTER, AND
OUR DOG, PRINCE.
>> HI, PRINCE.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN A GOOD
STUDENT.
I EVEN GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL
A YEAR AHEAD OF MY CLASS.
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD TO
STARTING COLLEGE IN THE FALL.
I REALLY LIKE HANGING OUT WITH
MY FRIENDS AND TAKING PICTURES.
[shutter clicks]
MY DAD WASN'T AROUND MUCH
GROWING UP, BUT MY MOM HAS
WORKED HARD TO TAKE CARE OF ME
AND MY SISTER.
>> I THINK YOU CAN DO COLLEGE,
AND THEN FROM THERE YOU DECIDE
WHAT YOU WANT TO BECOME.
>> THE THREE OF US ARE REALLY
CLOSE.
WE TALK ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> SHUT UP!
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
>> MY BOYFRIEND DEVOIN AND I
BROKE UP A MONTH AGO, BUT I
STILL LOVE HIM AND HOPE WE CAN
WORK THINGS OUT, BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
TELLING MY MOM I WAS PREGNANT
WAS PRETTY SCARY, ESPECIALLY
SINCE MY OLDER SISTER, BRITTANY,
FOUND OUT SHE WAS PREGNANT
AROUND THE SAME TIME, BUT WE
BOTH MADE VERY DIFFERENT
CHOICES.
BRITTANY'S BOYFRIEND AT THE TIME
WAS NOT SUPPORTIVE, SO SHE
DECIDED TO HAVE AN ABORTION.
AT THE TIME WHEN I MADE MY
DECISION, MY BOYFRIEND DEVOIN
AND I WERE STILL TOGETHER, SO I
DECIDED TO KEEP MY BABY, BUT I'M
STILL QUESTIONING IF I MADE THE
RIGHT DECISION.
I DIDN'T WANT TO TELL HER IN
PERSON.
LIKE, "OH, MY GOD, MOM, I'M
PREGNANT."
>> LIKE, IT'S ONE OF THOSE
THINGS WHEN YOU LIKE A BOY, AND
YOU'RE LIKE, IN A TEXT MESSAGE,
"I LIKE YOU," OR IN A NOTE,
"I LIKE YOU. CHECK YES OR NO."
SO IT'S LIKE--
>> YEAH, I WASN'T GONNA TELL
HER TO HER FACE.
I COULDN'T DO THAT.
SO I WROTE HER LETTER.
>> I WAS SITTING ON THE SOFA,
AND SHE PASSED ME THE LETTER.
I GRABBED THE LETTER, AND I
KNEW.
MY HEART JUST SANK.
AND I OPEN IT, AND SHE SAID--
>> WHOO.
>> SHE'S PREGNANT,
THAT SHE'S SORRY.
YADA, YADA, YADA.
I GOT NAUSEOUS; I GOT DIZZY.
>> I PRAYED, HONEY.
I PRAYED AND I PRAYED.
>> I JUST KEPT SAYING, "SORRY."
>> I WAS TALKING ON THE PHONE,
AND THEN I HEAR "BOOM, BOOM,
BOOM."
I GOT SCARED.
I WAS LIKE, "WHAT THE HELL IS
GOIN' ON?"
>> I DIDN'T WANT HER TO HAVE IT.
I WAS DETERMINED.
I DID NOT WANT BRIANA TO HAVE
THE BABY.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO.
>> IT JUST FEELS LIKE I FAILED.
I COME FROM BROOKLYN, A VERY
TOUGH PART OF IT.
I BRING YOU GUYS HERE, AND
SOMETIMES I QUESTION, WAS IT THE
RIGHT THING OR NOT, BUT I HAVE
DOUBTS NOW.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD, BRI,
SERIOUSLY.
>> I KNOW.
BEING A TEEN MOM WILL BE A HUGE
CHALLENGE, SO I REALLY NEED TO
FIGURE STUFF OUT WITH DEVOIN
SOON.
THE TIMING SUCKS, 'CAUSE I GOT
TO GIVE BIRTH IN FIVE WEEKS.
>> IT'S WEIRD.
LIKE, I CAN'T PICTURE YOU HAVING
THE BABY, YOU KNOW?
>> IT DIDN'T HIT ME YET.
>> HOW DID THIS ALL HAPPEN?
>> WE DIDN'T USE PROTECTION.
>> BUT YOU GUYS NEVER USED
PROTECTION?
>> ONCE OR TWICE.
I DIDN'T SAY, "PUT ON A
SOMETHIN'."
THAT'S JUST AWKWARD AND WEIRD TO
ME, I THINK.
>> IF YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH
THAT PERSON, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
JUST ASK.
>> HE SHOULD'VE ASKED.
HE SHOULD'VE DID IT ANYWAYS.
>> YOU WEREN'T SCARED--"OH, MY
GOD, I MIGHT GET PREGNANT"?
>> I DIDN'T THINK ANYTHING WOULD
HAPPEN.
AND THEN IT HAPPENED.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE A
SCHOOL RELATIONSHIP.
ONCE HE GRADUATED, IT WAS GONNA
BE OVER, BUT IT WENT FARTHER
THAN THAT.
SINCE DEVOIN AND I ARE NOT
TOGETHER, RAISING A BABY ON MY
OWN IS GONNA BE REALLY TOUGH,
AND SOMETIMES I WONDER IF I
SHOULD HAVE DONE WHAT MY SISTER
DID.
SHE PUTS UP A GOOD FRONT, BUT
UNDERNEATH, I STILL THINK SHE'S
STRUGGLING WITH HER DECISION
TOO.
WERE YOU SCARED TO TELL HER,
'CAUSE MOM KNEW I WAS PREGNANT
FIRST?
>> YEAH.
WHEN I FINALLY DID TELL HER, YOU
COULD THE DISAPPOINT ON HER
FACE.
>> SHE DIDN'T GO DOWN YOUR
THROAT THE WAY SHE WENT DOWN MY
THROAT.
>> BECAUSE, IF YOU REALLY THINK
ABOUT IT, THE SHOCK ALREADY
SLAPPED HER IN THE FACE WITH
YOU, AND THEN I WAS, LIKE,
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
>> AND THEN I FOUND OUT YOU WAS
PREGNANT.
I WAS KIND OF SHOCKED.
THEN YOU SAY YOU WANTED TO GET
AN ABORTION, AND I WAS LIKE,
"YOU DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
SO DON'T DO IT."
>> I FEEL LIKE THE ABORTION WAS,
LIKE, WHAT I HAD TO DO.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT, "WHEN MY
SISTER--WHEN SHE HAS TO THINK
ABOUT HOW TO PAY FOR DIAPERS AND
STUFF, I DON'T HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT PAYING FOR DIAPERS.
WHEN BRIANA'S THINKING ABOUT,
'OH, DEVOIN'S OVER HERE MESSING
AROUND WITH HER AND STUFF', AND
SHE HAS TO TAKE CARE OF THE BABY
BY HERSELF, I'M NOT DOING THAT."
YOU'RE GONNA SEE ME DOING--GOING
OUT, DRIVING, HAVING FUN, AND
YOU'RE GONNA BE STUCK AT HOME
WITH A BABY.
>> MM-HMM.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
WHAT I HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> MY DUE DATE IS A MONTH AWAY,
AND DEVOIN STILL HASN'T BEEN IN
TOUCH.
BRITTANY HAS BEEN HANGING AROUND
THE HOUSE LESS AND LESS, SO IT
WAS UP TO MY MOM AND ME TO TAKE
CARE OF ALL THE STUFF LEFT TO DO
FOR THE BABY.
LOOK, MOM, THAT'S TWO.
YOU SEE TWO?
THIS IS TWO.
THAT IS DUSTY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WE GOT IT.
[gasps]
OH, MY GOD, WE DID IT.
JEEZ, LOUISE, WE DID IT!
WHAT IS THIS?
>> WE DID IT THE WRONG WAY.
>> WHO'S BLEEDING?
>> [gasps] I'M BLEEDING.
>> YOU ARE.
>> OH, MY GOD, BRI.
>> FROM WHERE?
>> YOU'RE FEET.
DON'T TOUCH ANYTHING.
PUT YOUR FOOT IN THE PLASTIC.
STAY THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
>> HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
>> JEEZ, LOUISE.
>> [laughs]
>> RIGHT IN YOUR FOOT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> BRIT!
LOOK AT THE MASSACRE THAT WE
HAVE--THAT HAPPENED.
>> CAN YOU IMAGINE IN LABOR, AND
ALL THAT BLOOD COMING OUT?
>> THAT IS DISGUSTING.
>> THAT'S GONNA DRIP.
WAIT!
IF YOU DRIP BLOOD ALL OVER
THE PLACE, I'M GONNA GET YOU.
OKAY.
>> NO, WHAT YOU SHOULD DO IS
LEARN HOW TO DO THIS, BECAUSE
WHEN YOUR BABY SPITS, YOU'RE
GONNA BE DOING THE SAME THING.
>> WHEN SHE DOO-DOOS, AND IT
LEAKS OUT OF HER DIAPER, I'M
SURE NOT GONNA BE THE ONE TO BE
CLEANING THAT MESS UP.
I DON'T CARE IF I'M BABYSITTING
HER.
>> EW, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE
CLEANING [bleep] DIAPERS.
>> IF I BABYSIT HER ONE DAY,
IT'S GONNA STAY THERE ON THE
FLOOR UNTIL YOU GUYS COME HOME,
'CAUSE I AIN'T TOUCHIN' THAT.
I'LL BE LIVING THE HIGH LIFE IN
MY CONVERTIBLE MUSTANG.
>> WHATEVER.
>> I WANT YOU TO LIVE YOUR LIFE.
I WANT YOU TO DO YOUR THING.
I WANT YOU TO BE SUCCESSFUL AND
ACCOMPLISH EVERYTHING THAT YOU
KNOW YOU CAN, AND I WANT HER TO
DO THE SAME.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT BOTH OF
YOUS WOULD BOTH JUST BE OUT, AND
DO YOUR THINGS, AND NOW IT FEELS
LIKE YOU GET TO DO IT ALL, AND
SHE CAN'T.
>> WELL, THAT'S THE CHOICES THAT
WE MADE.
I NEVER SAID THAT I'M GONNA NOT
DO ANYTHING.
I CAN STILL LIVE MY LIFE.
I JUST HAVE TO LIVE IT A
DIFFERENT WAY.
>> WHEN I WENT AND I GOT MY
ABORTION, THEN I KNEW WHAT I WAS
GOING FOR.
AND I KNEW THAT BRIANA WAS GONNA
HAVE HERS, AND I WAS GONNA HAVE
TO SEE A BABY IN THE HOUSE.
>> YOU DECIDED TO DO WHAT YOU
THOUGHT WAS RIGHT AND WHAT WAS
RIGHT FOR BRIANA, AND--
>> SOME DAYS I WISH I COULD TAKE
IT BACK, BUT I CAN'T GO BACK
NOW.
>> I KNOW THAT THAT HURTS YOU.
AND I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAD TO GO
THROUGH THAT.
AND I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAVE TO
STAY HERE AND WATCH HER HAVE HER
BABY, AND YOU CAN'T.
AH, I'M SORRY.
>> I'M NOT IN THIS HOUSE BECAUSE
I DON'T WANT TO--LIKE, NOT TO BE
RUDE, BUT I DON'T WANT TO SEE
YOU PREGNANT OR SEE MOM BUYING
STUFF FOR ANOTHER BABY.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO GET
DEPRESSED, OR I DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET MAD AND TAKE IT OUT ON ME
OR SOMETHING.
>> IT'S AWKWARD HAVING SO MUCH
TENSION AROUND THE HOUSE WITH
BRITTANY SINCE SHE'S STILL
STRUGGLING WITH THE FACT THAT
I'M HAVING A BABY, AND SHE'S
NOT.
AND ON TOP OF THAT, IT'S BEEN A
MONTH SINCE DEVOIN AND I SPOKE.
HE HASN'T SHOWN ANY INTEREST IN
MY PREGNANCY SO FAR, BUT I'M
HOPING HE STILL WANTS TO BE A
PART OF THE BABY'S LIFE.
I EXPECT HIM TO BE THERE.
HE HASN'T BEEN THERE.
I WANT HIM TO BE LIKE, "YOU
KNOW WHAT, BRIANA, I'M GONNA GO
TO THE DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT WITH
YOU."
NO, HE DOESN'T DO THAT.
>> AND WHEN THE BABY'S BORN,
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM HIM?
>> TO BE THERE FOR HER.
I WANT HIM TO WAKE UP IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT AND DO
EVERYTHING I HAVE TO DO.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO GO TO
BED--TO GO HOME TO HIS HOUSE AND
SLEEP THE WHOLE NIGHT.
>> HE CAN SPEND A FEW NIGHTS A
WEEK.
I'M NOT SAYING NO.
BUT I'M ALSO NOT GONNA MAKE MY
HOME A HOTEL FOR HIM.
>> I KNOW.
>> NO WAY.
>> I WANT HIM TO BE THERE FOR
HIS DAUGHTER, TO BE THERE FOR
HIS FAMILY, TO NOT BE SO...
>> LAZY?
>> CHILL AND LAID-BACK, LIKE
EVERYTHING--I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S SO DIFFICULT.
>> HE'LL GET IT EVENTUALLY.
>> I'VE BEEN TEXTING DEVOIN
ABOUT MEETING UP TO TALK, BUT HE
HASN'T RESPONDED YET.
I GRADUATED EARLY, AND I WAS
PLANNING ON STARTING COLLEGE IN
THE FALL, BUT IF DEVOIN ISN'T
GOING TO BE AROUND TO HELP ME
WITH THE BABY, I'M NOT SURE I'LL
BE ABLE TO ENROLL AT THE SAME
TIME AS MY FRIENDS.
>> DOES HE WORK AND GO TO
SCHOOL?
LIKE, IS HE ABLE TO...
>> SUPPORT YOU FINANCIALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> HE GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL, SO
THAT WILL HELP, BUT HE DOESN'T
WORK RIGHT NOW.
>> BUT DOES HE HAVE A CAR?
HE DOESN'T, DOES HE?
>> NO, HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE A
LICENSE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT'S WHY OUR RELATIONSHIP
HASN'T REALLY WORKED OUT, 'CAUSE
HE'S TOO BUSY, YOU KNOW, HANGING
OUT WITH HIS FRIENDS AND NOT
SPENDING TIME WITH ME.
>> YEAH, BUT, LIKE, HE NEEDS TO
LEARN A LITTLE RESPONSIBILITY.
HE PROMISED YOU WHEN YOU FOUND
OUT YOU GUYS WERE PREGNANT THAT
HE WAS GONNA TAKE CARE OF YOU
AND SUPPORT YOU.
AND THEN, NOW, HE'S NOT DOING
ANYTHING.
IF YOU HAD KNOWN THEN THAT HE
WASN'T GONNA BE PROVIDING AND
TAKING CARE OF YOU NOW, WOULD
YOU STILL HAVE KEPT THE BABY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE, LIKE, GLAMORIZED THE WHOLE
SITUATION.
HE WAS LIKE, "YEAH, WE'RE GONNA
DO THIS TOGETHER.
I HAVE A JOB.
I'M GONNA TAKE CARE OF HER.
WE'RE GONNA DO THIS AS A
FAMILY."
I DID NOT NEED TO GO THROUGH ANY
OF THIS, NOT AT ALL.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO CHOOSE A BABY
NAME WITH DEVOIN, BUT SINCE HE
HASN'T SHOWN ANY INTEREST
LATELY, AND MY DUE DATE IS ONLY
A FEW WEEKS AWAY, I'M GONNA PICK
ONE MYSELF.
>> WHAT NAME DID YOU HAVE?
>> I LIKE LUNA.
>> LUNA'S NICE.
IT'S ACTUALLY BEAUTIFUL.
>> I LIKE NOVA, BLISS.
>> BLISS? NO.
>> WHY?
>> SOUNDS LIKE A STRIPPER NAME.
>> WHY DOES EVERYBODY SAY THAT?
>> BECAUSE IT IS, BRIANA.
YOU HAVE--WHEN YOU THINK OF A
NAME, YOU HAVE TO THINK OF A
NAME FOR THE--ALL THE STAGES OF
LIFE.
THE NAME NOVA FITS THE SITUATION
PERFECT: THE BIRTH OF A STAR.
THAT IS YOUR BABY, AND THIS IS,
LIKE, SOMETHING THAT IS COSMIC,
UNIVERSAL.
>> OKAY, THAT'S WHY WE'RE NAMING
HER THAT.
>> I WANT YOU TO LIKE IT.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT, YOU DON'T
NAME HER, BRI.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> DON'T PICK IT BECAUSE IT
MEANS SOMETHING TO ME--FOR YOU.
YOU NAME THE BABY WHAT YOU WANT.
>> NOVA.
>> OKAY.
>> AFTER DECIDING ON A NAME,
IT'S REALLY STARTING TO HIT ME
HOW MUCH MY LIFE IS GOING TO
CHANGE, SO I WANT TO SPEND AS
MUCH TIME WITH MY FRIENDS AS I
CAN.
>> ARTS AND CRAFTS TIME, BABY.
THESE SHIRTS, RIGHT?
ARE YOU GONNA PUT SOMETHING
THAT, LIKE, PEOPLE--YOU FEEL
PEOPLE WILL JUDGE YOU BY?
>> WHY DON'T YOU TRY PUTTING,
"NOVA" ON IT?
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY A GOOD IDEA,
BECAUSE, LIKE--
>> BABY NOVA.
>> LOOKING AT YOU WITH YOUR
DAUGHTER WILL MAKE THEM JUDGE
YOU AUTOMATICALLY.
>> OKAY, SO WHAT DO WE DO NEXT
WITH THIS SHIRT?
I DON'T THINK I CAN DO THIS.
THIS IS SCARY.
OH!
[laughter]
OH, THAT'S COLD!
OH!
>> OH, THAT LOOKS SO AWESOME.
>> AH!
[laughter]
[screams]
[chime dings]
>> WHEN I TEXTED DEVOIN ABOUT
NAMING OUR BABY, HE ACTUALLY
RESPONDED AND SAID HE WANTED TO
MEET UP.
>> I'VE BEEN GETTING THINGS
READY FOR OUR DAUGHTER'S
ARRIVAL.
>> YEAH.
NOVA.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE A SAY
IN THE NAME?
>> I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD.
>> IT'S JUST I FEEL THAT YOU
DIDN'T REALLY DO MUCH AND FOR
YOU TO HAVE A SAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT'S UP TO YOU.
IF YOU WANT THE LAST NAME, THEN
YOU SHOW ME THAT YOU WANT THE
LAST NAME.
I THINK A LAST NAME IS MORE
IMPORTANT THAN A FIRST NAME,
'CAUSE WITH THE LAST NAME, YOU
HAVE RIGHTS.
WITHOUT THE LAST NAME, YOU DON'T
HAVE [bleep].
>> OVER THIS PAST MONTH, WE
HAVEN'T EVEN SPOKEN TO EACH
OTHER.
WE HAVE PERSONAL PROBLEMS.
>> I'M JUST ASKING A FEW SIMPLE
THINGS FROM YOU.
>> WHAT ARE YOU ASKING FOR?
>> I WANT YOU TO BE THERE AND TO
GET A JOB.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED I HAVE A JOB
FOR ME, OR ARE YOU WORRIED I
HAVE A JOB FOR YOUR SAKE?
>> FOR YOU AND HER.
I DON'T NEED ANYTHING FROM YOU.
WE WERE VERY CLEAR ABOUT THAT.
>> MM.
>> BUT SHE DOES.
>> WHAT DO YOU NEED PERSONALLY
FROM ME?
>> I NEED YOU TO BE THERE.
>> DON'T YOU WANT TO BE ABLE TO
SUPPLY HER WITH THINGS, NOT JUST
MY MOM?
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
BUT I CAN'T RIGHT NOW.
YOU COULD. YOU COULD.
YOU COULD.
>> I COULD WHAT?
>> GET A JOB AND DO THOSE
THINGS.
>> I FEEL YOU.
I'M FORCED TO GET A JOB.
>> I'M FORCED TO BE A MOTHER.
IF I COULD GROW UP OVER NIGHT,
AND BE LIKE, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE TO DO WHAT I HAVE TO DO,"
YOU COULD DO THE SAME.
>> I'VE BEEN DOING A LOT OF
THINGS YOU HAVEN'T NOTICED,
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT THERE.
CAN YOU SAY YOU'VE BEEN THERE
FOR ME?
OKAY.
DEVOIN ISN'T ACTING LIKE THE
FUTURE FATHER I NEED HIM TO BE,
AND I'M NOT SURE I CAN DO THIS
WITHOUT HIM.
>> IT SUCKS THAT DEVOIN ISN'T
SHOWING MORE INTEREST IN HELPING
TO RAISE OUR DAUGHTER.
>> WITH OR WITHOUT DEVOIN, YOU
NEED TO THINK ABOUT YOUR FUTURE.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO FOR
SCHOOL?
>> I WANT TO WATCH THE BABY TILL
THE BABY'S ABOUT, LIKE, MAYBE,
FOUR OR FIVE MONTHS.
I CAN START NIGHT SCHOOL.
>> YOU SHOULD START ENROLLING IN
DECEMBER, SO YOU CAN START
JANUARY.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE LESS THAN THREE
MONTHS TO DO ALL OF THIS.
>> OKAY.
>> I PROMISED YOU THAT I WOULD
ASSIST YOU WITH EVERYTHING THAT
YOU NEED FOR THE FIRST TWO YEARS
OF YOUR BABY'S LIFE WHEN IT
COMES TO SCHOOL.
AND BY THE TIME YOUR BABY'S
FIVE, YOU SHOULD ALREADY HAVE
FINISHED SCHOOL AND STARTED A
CAREER, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> IF YOU DON'T DO THE SCHOOL
THING, BRIANA, YOU'RE IN
TROUBLE.
ONCE THE BABY'S A MONTH OLD,
YOU'RE GONNA START RESEARCHING
WHERE IT IS THAT YOU WANT TO GO,
AFTER TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO BE A MOMMY, OKAY?
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW YOUR PRIORITY
IS BEING A MOMMY.
IT'S GONNA BE EXPENSIVE, AND
IT'S SCARY.
THE FINANCES IS A SCARY
SITUATION.
WE ALSO HAVE TO REMEMBER THAT IF
DEVOIN REALLY WANTS TO HELP, HE
CAN HELP, YOU KNOW.
AND IT WOULD MAKE THINGS A LOT
EASIER ON ME.
>> I KNOW IF HE HAD MONEY, IF HE
HAD A JOB, HE WOULD'VE BEEN
GETTING THINGS BY NOW.
I DON'T NEED HIM.
JUST BE THERE FOR BABY NOVA, AND
THAT'S IT.
MY DUE DATE IS LESS THAN A MONTH
AWAY, AND IT'S TIME FOR ANOTHER
SONOGRAM.
I TEXTED DEVOIN ABOUT THE
APPOINTMENT, BUT IT WAS NO
SURPRISE WHEN I DIDN'T HEAR FROM
HIM.
>> SO DO YOU KNOW IF IT'S A BOY
OR GIRL?
>> THEY SAID IT WAS A GIRL.
>> OKAY, WE'LL CONFIRM THAT.
>> PLEASE TELL US.
>> WE'RE GONNA MAKE SURE SHE'S
STILL A GIRL.
>> OKAY, PLEASE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I'M SCARED IF IT ISN'T.
>> I'M GONNA PUT A LITTLE BIT OF
GEL.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S WARM.
>> OH, THAT'S NICE.
>> SO THE FIRST THING WE'RE
GONNA DO TODAY, WE'RE GONNA SEE
THE POSITION.
HER FACE IS ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF
THE SCREEN.
SO LET'S GO AHEAD AND SEE THE
GENDER.
LET'S GO ALL THE WAY UP HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
CROSS YOUR FINGERS.
>> LET'S VERIFY IF SHE'S STILL A
GIRL.
>> I'M GONNA CRY IF IT'S A BOY.
>> [laughs]
THERE WE GO.
>> IT'S A GIRL?
>> IT'S STILL A GIRL.
>> YES!
>> OKAY, WHOO, THANK GOD.
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> SHE LOOKS GREAT.
>> THE TECHNICIAN PRINTED OFF
SOME PHOTOS AND GAVE ME A DVD OF
MY SONOGRAM.
IS THE DVD PLUGGED IN?
>> IT SHOULD BE.
>> NO, DO IT YOURSELF.
>> WAIT, I WANT TO SEE IT TOO.
>> COME WATCH IT WITH ME.
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA COOK?
>> COME ON, LET'S COOK
SOMETHING.
>> CAN YOU MAKE BEANS?
>> OH, MY GOD, LET ME SEE IF I
HAVE THE DAMN BEANS.
>> WE'VE EATEN BEANS, LIKE,
THREE TIMES THIS WEEK ALREADY.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO EAT IT.
>> MOM, YOU DON'T GOT TO MAKE
STUFF COMPLICATED 'CAUSE SHE
WANTS IT.
WHO MAKES HER QUEEN?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
GET THE HELL OUT OF THE
DAMN KITCHEN.
I'M ABOUT TO COOK, 'CAUSE I'M
GETTING ME REALLY FREAKING
ANNOYED, AND, HONESTLY, I NEED
TO GO, 'CAUSE I HAVE PLANS.
>> WAIT, WAIT. SHH.
>> GIVE ME THE DAMN MEAT.
IT'S JUST, WHY DID YOU HAVE TO
GO OUT OF YOUR WAY TO MAKE BEANS
FOR HER?
IF SHE WANTED BEANS, SHE COULD
COOK THEM HERSELF, OR SHE COULD
WAIT TILL TOMORROW TO EAT THEM.
EVERY DAY YOU MAKE SOMETHING TO
MEET HER WANTS.
IT'S ANNOYING.
IT REALLY IS.
I DON'T CARE IF SHE'S PREGNANT.
SHE'S PREGNANT; SHE'S NOT
DISABLED.
>> ARE YOU GONNA COME SEE?
>> BRIANA, ONCE I GET EVERYTHING
IN THE OVEN AND ON TOP OF THE
STOVE, I WILL RUN AND SEE
EVERYTHING WITH YOU.
GIVE ME A SECOND.
>> [sighs]
>> BRIANA, YOU'RE ACTING LIKE A
LITTLE BRAT.
STOP IT, OKAY?
YOU'RE NOT A BABY.
>> 'CAUSE YOU GUYS ARE
AGGRAVATING.
>> SHUT UP, BRITTANY.
>> WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> [crying]
>> YOU'RE CRYING?
WHAT'S WRONG?
BABY.
YOU'RE SAD, CONFUSED,
OVERWHELMED.
THAT'S NORMAL.
I'M GOING SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> BRIT, WHY DON'T YOU WANT TO
STAY?
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO STAY.
THAT'S IT.
YOU DON'T NEED AN EXPLANATION.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[chime dings]
>> THE TENSION BETWEEN ME AND MY
SISTER IS REALLY BUMMING ME OUT,
ESPECIALLY SINCE MY DUE DATE IS
ONLY TWO WEEKS AWAY.
I HAVE TO TIPTOE AROUND
BRITTANY.
LIKE, I CAN'T EXPRESS MY TRUE
FEELINGS IN FRONT OF BRITTANY,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT HER TO
FEEL DEPRESSED OR SAD.
TEENAGERS ARE SUPPOSED TO, YOU
KNOW, HAVE FUN, DO THEIR THING,
YOU KNOW?
LIVE LIFE.
YOU'RE ONLY YOUNG ONCE, BUT I
CAN'T DO THAT, BECAUSE I'M
PREGNANT.
YOU CAN'T ENJOY IT LIKE A
35-YEAR-OLD WOMAN CAN ENJOY HER
PREGNANCY.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE A 35-YEAR-OLD WOMAN
PROBABLY HAS A JOB, HER OWN
PLACE, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT YOU'RE
SAD, YOU KNOW, BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T ENJOY YOUR TEENAGE YEARS,
OR IS IT BECAUSE OF BRITTANY?
>> IT'S BOTH.
LIKE, THE OTHER DAY WITH THE
SONOGRAM SITUATION, WE HAD A
DVD, AND I WAS PLAYING IT IN THE
HOUSE, AND SHE DIDN'T WANT TO
SEE IT.
LIKE, SHE DIDN'T WANT TO BE A
PART OF IT, SO THAT SHOWED ME
THAT HER TIME IS GONNA COME
WHERE SHE IS GONNA GET REAL
DEPRESSED.
>> SHE'S GONNA BREAK DOWN.
>> SHE SAYS THAT IT'S NOT
GETTING TO HER, BUT...
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> WE ALL KNOW IT IS.
>> YEAH.
HOW DO YOU THINK BRITTANY'S
GONNA FEEL, LIKE, ON THE DAY OF
YOUR BIRTH?
>> THAT'S THE SCARY PART, 'CAUSE
I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE'S GONNA
REACT TO THE SITUATION.
>> DO YOU THINK SHE'LL BE IN THE
ROOM, THOUGH?
>> SHE WANTS TO.
>> IN THE HOSPITAL ROOM?
WELL, ONLY TWO MORE WEEKS, AND
YOU'LL BE GOOD.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT THE BABY TO
COME, AND THEN SHE GETS EXTRA
DEPRESSED, AND THEN SHE STRESSES
ME OUT AND MY MOM OUT, THEN THE
WHOLE HOUSE COMES CRUMBLING
DOWN.
I REALLY HOPE THINGS GET BETTER
WITH BRITTANY SOON, 'CAUSE I'M
FEELING REALLY ALONE, ESPECIALLY
SINCE DEVOIN KEEPS IGNORING ME.
>> YOUR CALL HAS BEEN FORWARDED
TO AN AUTOMATED VOICE MESSAGING
SYSTEM.
>> WHILE MY FRIENDS HAVE BEEN
ENJOYING THEIR SENIOR YEAR, I'VE
BEEN STRESSED OUT AT HOME
GETTING READY FOR THE BABY.
I REALLY MISS HANGING OUT WITH
THEM, BUT TONIGHT WE DECIDED TO
GO TO A HAUNTED HOUSE.
AND I'M GLAD BRITTANY AGREED TO
COME TOO.
AH, I CAN'T WAIT TO BE SKINNY
AGAIN SO I CAN GO OUT AND DO
THINGS.
>> HOMECOMING IS IN OCTOBER.
>> I'M THINKING YOU SHOULD TAKE
ME.
>> SHE'S GONNA BE THERE WITH THE
BABY.
>> YEAH, LIKE, "COME ON, LET'S
DANCE."
WHO ARE YOU GONNA TAKE TO PROM,
PATRICIA?
>> YOU KNOW MANNY?
HE'S TALL, SKINNY.
>> WHY DON'T YOU TAKE ME?
I COULD BE YOUR DATE.
I'VE NEVER BEEN TO PROM.
DEVOIN TOOK THAT PRIVILEGE AWAY
FROM ME BY NOT
GETTING PROM TICKETS.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> OH, MY GOD, NO, NO, NO.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I'M STAYING IN THE CAR.
>> WHAT IF, LIKE, I GET TOO
SCARED AND MY WATER BREAKS?
>> IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
COME ON.
>> IS IT GONNA BE THAT DARK?
>> YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S GONNA BE FINE.
>> YOU'RE ALL RIGHT; COME ON IN.
>> WELCOME TO OUR WORLD.
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW ANY OF THESE
PEOPLE DIED?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW THEY DIED,
BUT WE KNOW THAT THEY'RE HERE.
>> OKAY, ALBERT R. MYRTLE L.,
AKA IVES, COME OUT.
>> [laughs]
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT CHANDELIER
IS MOVING BY ITSELF.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU OKAY?
MY STOMACH STARTED HURTING A
LOT, AND I WAS FEELING NAUSEOUS,
SO BRITTANY DROVE US HOME.
>> OH, MY GOD, I THINK WE NEED
TO GO SEE A DOCTOR.
SHE'S HAVING CRAMPS.
>> OH, HELL, NO.
PLEASE, LORD, NOT TODAY.
NOT TONIGHT.
>> AND AS SOON AS WE GOT BACK TO
THE HOUSE, THE PAIN GOT WORSE.
I CALLED DEVOIN AND TOLD HIM IT
WAS TIME, AND HE, SURPRISINGLY,
SHOWED UP RIGHT AWAY.
SO MY MOM DROVE US ALL TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING, BRIANA?
>> YOU OKAY, BRI?
>> COME ON.
>> YOU WANT ICE, 'CAUSE YOU'RE
GONNA GET THIRSTY.
>> YOU CAN'T. YOU CAN'T.
BREATHE, BABY.
I WAS IN A LOT OF PAIN, SO I
ASKED FOR AN EPIDURAL.
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT, THE DOCTOR
SAID IT WAS TIME TO PUSH.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
VERY GOOD.
JUST LIKE THAT.
KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH IN, AND PUSH
HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> OW!
>> ONE MORE TIME.
THAT'S HIS HEAD.
PUSH HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD,
HARD.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> SHE GOT HAIR.
OH, MY GOD.
>> AGAIN, DO IT AGAIN.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> AND PUSH HARD.
>> [screams]
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> * I WAS LOST *
* GIVEN UP *
* THERE YOU WERE *
>> SHE'S SO CUTE!
>> * I HAD STOPPED *
* LOOKING FOR LOVE *
* AND THERE YOU WERE *
* THERE YOU WERE *
>> WHAT WAS THAT?
IT WAS NICE HAVING DEVOIN HERE
FOR NOVA'S BIRTH, BUT THE NEXT
MORNING, HE RAN OFF TO PLAY
BASKETBALL WITH HIS FRIENDS.
IT'S CLEAR HE'S NOT INTERESTED
IN BEING A DAD FIRST, SO I
DECIDED NOT TO PUT HIS NAME ON
THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
>> NOVA.
AND MY LAST NAME.
WHEN DEVOIN CAME BACK AND FOUND
OUT I LEFT HIM OFF THE BIRTH
CERTIFICATE, HE WAS REALLY
PISSED.
AFTER YELLING AT MY MOM AND
SISTER, HE DROVE AWAY AND DIDN'T
RETURN TO HELP ME BRING NOVA
HOME.
>> DEVOIN NEEDS TO STOP
WORRYING ABOUT THE DAMN LAST
NAME, 'CAUSE IT'S NOT GONNA BE
HIS LAST NAME.
THE WAY HE ACTED, STORMING OUT,
CURSING, RIPPING OFF HIS FATHER
BAND OR WHATEVER, LEAVING THE
HOSPITAL, WAS NOT CALLED FOR.
>> YOU WERE NOT HERE.
WHERE WERE YOU?
YOU SHOULD'VE STAYED IF YOU
WANTED IF YOU WANTED YOUR NAME
ON THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
OH, HE'S GONNA GO PLAY
BASKETBALL.
YOU'RE GONNA GO PLAY BASKETBALL
WHILE I'M IN THE HOSPITAL?
OKAY.
>> GOT EVERYTHING?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, GO IN FIRST SO PRINCE
CAN SEE YOU.
>> OH, I SEE HIM IN THE WINDOW.
HI.
>> HE DOESN'T NOTICE THE BABY
YET.
>> OH, LOOK.
GO LOOK AT THE BABY.
SHE'S WAKING UP.
>> HI, PRINCE.
>> OKAY.
>> [laughs]
>> YOU'RE HOME.
>> SHE JUST GOT CROSS-EYED.
THAT WAS FUNNY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I PROMISE YOU'LL BE OKAY.
I'M GONNA FEED YOU, OKAY?
I HAVE TO FEED HER, AND I DON'T
KNOW HOW I'M GONNA DO THAT.
>> I'M GONNA GO TAKE A SHOWER.
IF YOU NEED ANYTHING, JUST CALL
ME.
>> I'M GONNA DO IT NOW, BECAUSE
YOU'RE GONNA FALL ASLEEP, AND
THEN YOU'RE NOT GONNA SUCK.
COME ON.
ONE, TWO.
GO.
NO?
YOU GOT IT?
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
GO GET IT, GET IT, GET IT.
EAT IT, EAT IT.
[baby crying]
WHAT'S WRONG?
SHH.
[baby crying]
[exhales forcefully]
MA!
>> WHAT?
WHAT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> CAN YOU BURP HER?
>> OKAY.
>> GET AWAY.
GET OUT, GET OUT, GET OUT.
EVERYONE'S PANICKING.
GET OUT.
EVERYONE'S PANICKING FOR NO
REASON.
COME ON, BABY GIRL.
[baby crying]
WHY ARE YOU CRYING, BABY?
>> JUST BREATHE.
>> NO, SHE'S JUST OVERWHELMED.
IT'S HITTING HER.
COME ON.
[chime dings]
[baby crying]
>> YOU SPIT ON YOUR SHIRT.
EVER SINCE STORMING OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL, DEVOIN HAS BEEN
IGNORING ME AND HIS DAUGHTER.
SINCE YOU'RE UP...
HERE.
WHY AREN'T YOU EATING THAT?
LET'S GO SLEEPIES.
[baby crying]
BEING STUCK AT HOME ALL WEEK WAS
EXHAUSTING, SO I TREATED MYSELF
TO A NEW LOOK.
>> HI.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> THANK YOU.
EXCUSE THE MESS.
>> IT IS NOT EVEN THAT MESSY.
DOES SHE WAKE UP A LOT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT?
>> WHEN SHE'S GASSY, YEAH.
>> WHAT WAS IT LIKE GIVING
BIRTH?
>> IT HURT.
>> DEVOIN WAS IN THE ROOM?
>> YEAH.
AFTER SHE WAS BORN, HE LEFT.
HE WENT TO GO PLAY BASKETBALL.
>> HE SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT THE
HOSPITAL.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO BE THERE THE
WHOLE TIME.
>> I MADE AN EXCELLENT CHOICE BY
NOT PUTTING HIM ON THE BIRTH
CERTIFICATE.
>> I MEAN, HOPEFULLY HE GETS HIS
ACT TOGETHER, 'CAUSE SHE NEEDS
BOTH OF YOU GUYS.
>> AFTER IGNORING ME ALL WEEK,
DEVOIN FINALLY TEXTED ME HE
WANTS TO SEE HIS DAUGHTER.
>> HEY, GUYS.
COME IN.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> HEY, PEDRO, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M DOING FINE.
>> HI.
>> COME IN, GUYS.
>> LITTLE MUNCHKIN.
>> DO YOU GUYS WANT TO SEE?
>> SHE'S SO CHUBBY, RIGHT?
>> COME IN, GUYS.
HAVE A SEAT.
>> HOLD THIS.
[baby crying]
OKAY, SHH, SHH.
MOMMY'S HERE, MOMMY'S HERE,
MOMMY'S HERE.
AND YOU CAN'T LET THE MILK GO
ANYWHERE, 'CAUSE THEN SHE STARTS
TO SMELL LIKE CHEESE.
[phone tone chimes]
>> THIS GIRL EATS, LIKE, EVERY
HOUR.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA LET YOU TAKE
OVER.
>> DEVOIN, HOW ARE YOU GONNA
LEARN TO FEED YOUR BABY IF
YOU'RE ON YOUR CELL PHONE?
PUT THAT [bleep] AWAY.
>> TOO BAD.
TOO BAD.
>> TOO BAD?
YOU DON'T GOT TO GET RUDE WITH
ME.
I'M JUST SAYING HE'S NEVER HERE.
HE SHOULD AT LEAST WAIT--LET
HIS FRIENDS--CAN [bleep] WAIT.
[phone tone chimes]
>> I'M GOING SOMEWHERE BUT HERE.
>> YOU CAN BURP HER LIKE THIS,
OR YOU CAN BURP HER LIKE THIS.
THIS IS A LITTLE SCARY.
>> I AIN'T--I AIN'T MESSING
WITH THAT.
>> NO?
>> DEVOIN, FOR HER SAKE, WE HAVE
TO MAKE IT WORK.
SO, BRI, WHAT I THINK YOU HAVE
TO, YOU KNOW, MAKE CLEAR, IS
THAT THIS IS WHAT YOU WANT.
THIS IS NOT MY INFLUENCE, MY
PRESSURE.
>> DEVOIN KNOWS THAT.
DEVOIN KNOWS THAT IT WAS ALL MY
CHOICE WHAT I DECIDED.
>> YOU WANT HIM THERE; YOU WANT
HIM TO BE THERE FOR HER.
>> I AM.
I'M TALKING TO BOTH OF YOUS.
YOU'RE HERE.
THE MORE TIME YOU SPEND HERE
WITH THE BABY--LEARN THE ROPES
ABOUT THE BABY--THE EASIER IT'S
GONNA GET FOR YOU IN THE LONG
RUN.
I PROMISE YOU IT'LL GET EASIER.
[phone tone chimes]
>> BRI.
>> HMM?
>> I'M TALKING TO YOU.
>> I HEARD YOU.
>> YOU DON'T THINK THAT THAT'S
DISRESPECTFUL?
I'M TRYING TO, LIKE, HAVE A
SERIOUS TALK WITH YOU GUYS.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> I'M NOT HERE TO HURT YOU OR
THE BABY OR BRIANA.
I'M HERE TO MAKE IT WORK FOR THE
THREE OF YOUS.
>> [sighs]
YOU'RE RUDE FOR NO REASON,
DEVOIN, I'M SORRY.
>> NO, IT'S THE WAY YOU'RE
ACTING.
>> YEAH, YOU ARE.
>> YES, I'M SERIOUS.
>> NOBODY'S ARGUING.
WHO'S ARGUING RIGHT NOW?
WE'RE TALKING.
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S GETTING
OFFENSIVE.
>> WE'RE HERE TO MAKE IT WORK,
DUDE.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, BRIANA, I'LL TALK
TO YOU LATER.
[door clicks]
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO STAY
STRONG.
IT'S OKAY.
DON'T CRY.
SHE DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU CRY.
>> I'M NOT TOLERATING THAT.
I'M NOT DEALING WITH THAT.
NONE OF THAT WAS NECESSARY.
HE'S RUDE.
HE'S DISRESPECTFUL.
>> WE'VE NEVER ASKED HIM FOR A
DIAPER.
WE'VE NEVER ASKED HIM FOR A
WIPEY.
HE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT KIND OF
FORMULA SHE DRINKS.
SO YOU WANT TO BE A DAD?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> BEING A FATHER IS COMING HERE
EVERY SINGLE DAY TO SEE HIS
DAUGHTER, TO LEARN ABOUT HIS
DAUGHTER, TO CARE FOR HIS
DAUGHTER.
HE DON'T GIVE A [bleep].
>> I KNOW YOU WANT HER TO HAVE
HER DADDY.
I KNOW THAT.
BRI, SOMETIMES SOME DADDY'S ARE
NOT WILLING TO WANT TO MAKE IT
WORK.
>> SINCE DEVOIN'S NOT HELPING
OUT AT ALL, IT'S UP TO ME TO
WATCH NOVA DURING THE WEEK WHILE
I TRY TO GET BACK ON TRACK WITH
SCHOOL.
TODAY MY MOM GOT OUT OF WORK SO
WE CAN VISIT A LOCAL COMMUNITY
COLLEGE.
>> HOW WONDERFUL TO MEET YOU.
I'D LIKE TO GET STARTED BY
ASKING YOU WHAT YOUR GOALS ARE.
>> I JUST WANT TO START COLLEGE,
GET MY LIFE GOING.
>> ARE YOU LOOKING TO TAKE
FULL-TIME CLASSES?
>> OKAY, WELL, I'M A TEEN
MOTHER.
>> YES.
>> I DON'T WANT TO PUT TOO MUCH
ON MY PLATE, AND THEN I CAN'T
HANDLE IT.
>> MAYBE START OFF WITH ONE OR
TWO CLASSES IN THE SPRING, SEE
HOW THAT WORKS OUT.
>> NOW, HOW LONG WOULD IT TAKE
FOR ME TO GRADUATE AND FINISH?
>> WELL, OUR PROGRAMS ARE ALL
CALLED TWO-YEAR PROGRAMS, BUT IT
IS ALL DEPENDANT ON WHETHER
YOU'RE FULL-TIME OR PART-TIME.
IF YOU DO GO PART-TIME,
WHICH WOULD BE THAT ONE TO TWO
COURSES, IT COULD LONGER.
>> PART-TIME IS THE BEST OPTION
FOR ME, SINCE SO MUCH OF MY TIME
IS SPENT TAKING CARE OF NOVA.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I THINK SHE'S--
>> ARE THEY POO-POOS?
>> SHE'S A POOPY GIRL.
>> WE HAVE TO FEED HER.
>> I THINK WE HAVE TO CHANGE HER
FIRST.
OH, MY GOD, GIRL, WAIT.
WHERE THE HELL ARE WE GONNA
CHANGE HER?
[gasps]
OH, MY GOD, THEY DON'T HAVE A
CHANGING DIAPER RACKY.
>> WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, PUT HER
UP HERE?
[laughs]
>> THAT'S TOO TALL.
NOVA, YOU POOPY GIRL, THANKS A
LOT.
>> COME ON, BABY.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HOLD HER JUST
LIKE THIS.
BITE THAT.
JUST HOLD THAT.
ARE YOUR LEGS CRAMPING?
>> [muffled] THAT'S
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> DON'T DROOL.
OOH, SHE POOPY!
NOVA, COME ON, GIRL.
SHE'S STILL PUSHING.
GREAT.
>> [giggles]
THIS STINKS.
NOVA, STAY STILL, CHICA.
COME ON, WORK WITH ME.
>> IT SUCKS, BECAUSE DEVOIN
COULD'VE BEEN HERE.
I COULD'VE LET DEVOIN BABYSIT
THE BABY WHILE I WAS IN SCHOOL,
BUT...
>> WHATEVER IT TAKES, YOU HAVE
TO COME TO SCHOOL, BRIANA.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO MAKE
SACRIFICES.
>> WE'RE IN SCHOOL, BABY.
YOU'RE GONNA BE HERE IN
ANOTHER--HOW MANY YEARS?
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS ABOUT IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GONNA BE
ABLE TO JUGGLE SCHOOL, BEING A
MOTHER, TAKING CARE OF HER, AND
HOW I FEEL ABOUT DEVOIN AND MY
EMOTIONAL STATE.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE EMOTIONALLY
EXHAUSTED.
YOU JUST HAD A BABY.
YOU'RE 17 YEARS OLD, TRYING TO
GO TO COLLEGE, TRYING TO STILL
BE A TEENAGER, BECAUSE YOU'RE
STILL NOT AN ADULT.
I KNOW IT'S HARD.
>> I'M USUALLY REALLY EXCITED
FOR HALLOWEEN, BUT THIS YEAR IS
DIFFERENT, BECAUSE I HAVE TO
STAY HOME WITH THE BABY ALL
NIGHT, WHILE BRITTANY GETS TO
HAVE FUN WITH HER FRIENDS.
>> BYE, MOM.
>> BYE.
>> THIS IS HAUNTED, FOR REAL.
I'M SCARED.
[screaming]
[baby crying]
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH YOU.
>> GET CLOSE, GET CLOSE.
WAIT, I CAN'T SEE EVERYBODY.
[phone tone chimes]
>> OH, THEY'RE IN THE HAUNTED
HOUSE.
THEY'RE HAVING FUN.
IT'S PRETTY CLEAR I'M GOING TO
BE SACRIFICING A LOT TO RAISE
NOVA ON MY OWN.
I REALLY WAS EXPECTING MORE OUT
OF DEVOIN.
>> I THINK THAT WHEN YOU DECIDED
TO HAVE NOVA, YOU THOUGHT
EVERYTHING WAS GONNA BE SO
DIFFERENT, AND NOW THAT IT IS,
YOU JUST CAN'T EVEN
COMPREHEND IT.
AND I THINK IT'S HURTING YOU
REALLY BAD.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE SAD
ANYMORE.
'CAUSE, LIKE, I REALLY CAN'T
ENJOY BEING A MOTHER, BECAUSE
THIS IS NOT WHAT I WANTED.
I'M PRETTY SURE HE DOESN'T WORRY
ABOUT NOVA THE WAY I DO.
HE DOESN'T LOVE NOVA ENOUGH TO
STOP WHAT HE'S DOING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
[chime dings]
>> female announcer: DON'T GO
AWAY, THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND
PREGNANT CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> THE NEXT DAY, DEVOIN TEXTED
THAT HE WANTS TO DISCUSS THINGS,
BUT NOT AT MY HOUSE OR AROUND MY
MOM.
SO I AGREED TO MEET HIM FOR
DINNER.
[solemn piano music]
* *
I GUESS DADDY'S NOT COMING.
[frustrated sigh]
[door slams]
>> SO WHAT DID YOU WRITE HIM?
>> I SAID, "WHERE ARE YOU?
I'M HERE."
>> YOU TOLD HIM YOU HAD NOVA?
>> HE KNEW I WAS COMING WITH
NOVA.
HE COULD'VE CAME TO SEE HER.
HE COULD'VE CAME TO TALK.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU LOOK KIND OF SAD.
>> I HAD TUNNEL VISION.
I WAS LIKE, "HE'S GONNA BE
THERE.
WE'RE GONNA DO THIS."
>> PEOPLE LET OTHER PEOPLE DOWN,
BRIANA.
I MADE MY DECISION, SO I DON'T
HAVE TO EAT NOBODY'S [bleep].
I DON'T KNOW HOW THE HELL
YOU DO IT.
IT'S TOO HARD.
>> IT'S HARD TO HAVE A SOCIAL
LIFE, KNOWING THAT YOU HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF A KID.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
THAT, SO CAN SLEEP OVER AT
PEOPLE'S HOUSES, GO PARTYING.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> STAYING HOME ALL DAY LIKE YOU
DO IS NOT RIGHT.
YOU'RE ALWAYS IN THE LIVING
ROOM.
THIS IS, LIKE, ALL YOU SEE ALL
DAY.
>> IT'S NOT EASY TO JUST GO OUT
AND DO SOMETHING, EVEN IF IT'S
FOR AN HOUR.
YOU STILL HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
NOVA.
YOU STILL HAVE TO MAKE SURE
SHE'S FED, CHANGED.
AND IF I COULD GO BACK AND MAKE
THE DECISION YOU MADE...
I WOULD DO IT.
I'M NOT SAYING THAT I REGRET HER
OR ANYTHING, BUT YOU MADE A
VERY, VERY SMART DECISION.
BRITTANY HAS, LIKE, SURPRISED ME
COMPLETELY.
I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, SHE WOULD
BE, LIKE, REBELLIOUS AGAINST
EVERYTHING, BUT SHE HAS SHOWN SO
MUCH SUPPORT.
I WOULD TRADE PLACES WITH MY
SISTER ANY DAY.
I DON'T SEE MYSELF AS A TEENAGER
ANYMORE, BECAUSE I'M NOT DOING
TEENAGED THINGS.
I'M TOO BUSY TAKING CARE OF MY
DAUGHTER.
COME ON, LET'S EAT.
[baby crying]
SHE'S A 24-HOURS,
SEVEN-DAYS-A-WEEK KIND OF JOB.
YOU HUNGRY?
I'M TOO YOUNG TO BE GOING
THROUGH ANY OF THIS.
NEVER MAKE A PERMANENT DECISION
ON TEMPORARY FEELINGS.
DEVOIN, HE DOESN'T DESERVE NOVA.
I KEEP GIVING HIM CHANCES AFTER
CHANCES AFTER CHANCES, AND HE
KEEPS LETTING MY DOWN EVERY
TIME.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE ANYTHING TO
DO WITH HIM.
AS MUCH AS I WANTED US TO WORK
OUT, IT'S NOT--
IT'S NOT GOING TO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN
IN THE NEAR FUTURE, BUT I KNOW
I'M GONNA KEEP MY GRADES UP,
BECAUSE IF I DON'T HAVE AN
EDUCATION, I'M NOT GOING FAR.
I CAN'T LIVE OFF OF A HIGH
SCHOOL DIPLOMA.
MY MOM IS MY ROLE MODEL, AND I'M
SO GRATEFUL FOR HAVING HER
AROUND, 'CAUSE IF SHE WASN'T
HERE, I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO DO
HALF THE THINGS I'VE DONE.
I WANT THE BEST FOR MY DAUGHTER.
I DON'T WANT HER TO GO THROUGH
WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH.
[chime dings]
>> announcer: ON THE NEXT...
>> I WANT TO GO PRO AS SOON AS
I'M 18, BUT THE BABY COMES
FIRST.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
>> YOU'RE JUST DOUBTING ME ALL
THE TIME.
[baby crying]
I MISS THE GYM.
AND I MISS YOU.
THIS IS THE REASON I HAVEN'T
BEEN HERE.