>> HEY, MY NAME IS LEAH.
I'M 17 YEARS OLD,
AND I LIVE IN THE MOUNTAINS
OF WEST VIRGINIA
IN A SMALL TOWN CALLED ELKVIEW.
MY HOUSE IS PRETTY CROWDED.
THERE'S MY BROTHER, SISTER,
AND MY MOM.
MY DAD LEFT WHEN I WAS LITTLE,
SO I REALLY DON'T KNOW HIM.
ME AND MY MOM ARE REALLY CLOSE.
SHE SPOILS ME ROTTEN,
'CAUSE I'M HER FIRSTBORN.
THAT'S REGAN.
THAT'S RACHAEL.
THAT'S ME.
AND THAT'S ALYSSA.
WE'RE PRETTY MUCH INSEPARABLE.
WE'RE ALL ON THE CHEERLEADING
TEAM, AND THIS YEAR IS OUR
SENIOR YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL.
[laughter]
[chime dings]
THIS IS COREY.
HE DROVE ME HOME FROM A PARTY
ONE NIGHT, AND ONE THING LED
TO ANOTHER.
COREY'S TWO YEARS OLDER THAN ME,
BUT I'M DEFINITELY MORE MATURE.
ARE YOU GONNA?
WHY DON'T YOU LISTEN TO ME?
WE JUST STARTED DATING,
AND WE'RE STILL GETTING TO KNOW
EACH OTHER.
I DON'T KNOW IF WE'RE GONNA MAKE
IT, BUT WE'RE TRYING TO STAY
TOGETHER AND WORK IT OUT
BECAUSE...
LIGHT IT.
>> I LIT IT.
IT'S LIGHTED.
[laughter]
>> IT'S LIGHTED.
>> I'M PREGNANT...
[chime dings]
WITH TWINS.
ME AND COREY'S RELATIONSHIP
GOT SET ON THE FAST TRACK.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
COREY WAS JUST SUPPOSED TO BE
A REBOUND FOR ME, 'CAUSE WHEN
WE MET, I'D JUST GOT OUT OF
A THREE-YEAR-LONG RELATIONSHIP.
AT FIRST, THINGS WERE GREAT,
AND WE HAD FUN.
OH, MY GOD, COREY.
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> BUT WE WERE ONLY DATING
ONE MONTH BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT.
IT'S A LOT OF PRESSURE,
'CAUSE WE HARDLY EVEN KNOW
EACH OTHER, AND NOW WE'RE
HAVING TWINS.
>> MOST OF THE TIME,
YOU THINK, "OH, IF I GET
PREGNANT, I'LL HAVE A KID,
AND THAT'LL BE ALL RIGHT."
YOU NEVER THINK,
IF I HAVE TWO KIDS...
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> AND TWO KIDS IS GONNA BE
TWICE THE EXPENSE.
SO I FLIP OUT ABOUT THAT.
>> TWICE THE AMOUNT OF DIAPERS.
TWICE THE AMOUNT...
>> TWICE THE EVERYTHING.
>> EVERYTHING.
>> GONNA BE ROUGH.
ALL BECAUSE ONE FUN NIGHT
IN MY TRUCK.
>> IT WAS SAD, THOUGH.
>> IT'S YOUR FAULT.
>> COREY, SHUT UP, REALLY.
YOU SHUT UP.
[laughter]
YOU SAID, "OH, IT NEVER
HAPPENED BEFORE."
>> OKAY, NO, BECAUSE
IT DOESN'T--IT'S NEVER
AFFECTED IT BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU MISS IT,
AFTER A MONTH OR SO,
IT'S FINE TO, LIKE--
>> BUT YOU AIN'T NEVER BEEN
WITH A MAN BEFORE.
[chuckles]
>> OH, YEAH.
OKAY.
YOU'RE SOME KIND OF MAN HERE.
>> I THINK WE'RE GETTING
USED TO IT, TO EVERYTHING.
>> NO, I THINK WE'RE JUST
GETTING USED TO EACH OTHER.
FOR GOD SAKES, IT WAS WHAT?
A MONTH, AND WE WERE
BEING PREGNANT.
IT'S KIND OF FUNNY, THOUGH,
THAT, LIKE, I'M THE FIRST,
LIKE, REAL RELATIONSHIP
THAT YOU HAD.
>> YEAH.
>> AND WE'RE PREGNANT.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> MUST BE KIND OF HARD.
>> IT IS.
WASN'T READY FOR THAT YET,
DEFINITELY.
>> IT'S HARD FOR ME TOO,
BECAUSE I WAS USED TO, LIKE...
YOU KNOW, DON'T GET MAD
IF I SAY THIS, BUT, LIKE,
KNOWING SOMEBODY REALLY WELL.
BEING WITH SOMEBODY FOR TWO
YEARS AND NOT GETTING PREGNANT
AND THEN BEING WITH SOMEBODY
FOR A MONTH AND BEING PREGNANT.
WHILE I WAS WITH MY EX-BOYFRIEND
ROBBIE, I WAS ON BIRTH CONTROL
THE WHOLE TIME.
BUT WHEN WE BROKE UP,
I MISSED ONE OF MY SHOTS.
TURNS OUT, YOU REALLY
CAN'T DO THAT.
SO NOW I'M PREGNANT.
WE FOUND OUT WE'RE HAVING
TWO GIRLS.
THEY'RE FRATERNAL TWINS,
AND WE'RE NAMING THEM
ALIANNAH AND ALEEAH.
THERE'S NOT ROOM FOR ALL OF US
AT MY MOM'S HOUSE, SO BEFORE THE
GIRLS ARE BORN, ME AND COREY
HAVE TO MOVE IN TOGETHER.
IT'S A LOT TO GET USED TO,
NOT JUST FOR US BUT FOR
OUR FAMILIES TOO.
MAMA WAS STARTING TO GET
MORE EXCITED ABOUT THE WHOLE
BABY THING.
>> I COULD TELL DAD, HE WAS
READY TO BEAT MY HEAD OFF WHEN
I TOLD HIM YOU WAS PREGNANT.
HE SAT THERE.
HE WAS LIKE...
[huffing]
FOR, LIKE, A MINUTE.
>> WHEN OUR PARENTS FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT, THEY WERE
REALLY DISAPPOINTED,
BUT REALITY HAS SETTLED IN,
AND THEY'RE TRYING TO BE
SUPPORTIVE.
>> IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU COME OUT.
>> WHERE DO Y'ALL WANT TO SIT?
>> YEAH, GO AHEAD, JOETTA.
>> THEY'RE LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD."
AND I'M LAYING HERE LIKE,
"WHAT'S GOING ON?"
YOU KNOW, TELL--
YOU KNOW, THEY KIND OF SCARED ME
'CAUSE I THOUGHT SOMETHING
WAS GOING ON.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
THE WOMAN LOOKS AT ME,
AND SHE'S LIKE, "HONEY,
YOU'RE HAVING TWINS."
I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOD."
>> SHE SAID, "I HATE TO BE
THE BARRIER OF THIS NEWS,
AND YOU ONLY 17."
>> I WAS FLIPPING OUT.
I SAID, "OH, MY GOD."
AND I WAS STANDING THERE.
MY BOSS WAS LIKE,
"WHAT'S WRONG?"
AND I SAID, "I'M HAVING TWINS."
MY BOSS PULLS OUT A CHAIR.
AND I'M SITTING THERE SHAKING
LIKE THIS.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK,
REALLY.
I WAS JUST--I WAS...
BECAUSE SHE HAS PUT A HOLD
ON EVERYTHING SHE COULD HAVE
DONE IN LIFE, SO...
>> BOTH OF US DID.
>> THIS IS SOME OF THE BEST
YEARS OF YOUR LIFE NORMALLY.
Y'ALL GOT TO GROW UP QUICK.
THAT'S WHAT THE SHAME OF IT IS.
IT'S JUST, YOU GOT TO FORFEIT
THOSE YEARS OF DOING WHAT
YOU WANT.
I CAN IMAGINE WHAT A CHALLENGE
ONE BABY WOULD BE, BUT TWO,
I CAN'T IMAGINE.
>> WE'RE SCARED.
I'M SCARED TO DEATH.
>> YEAH.
I REALLY WOULD LIKE TO SEE
THEM TWO STAY TOGETHER.
>> AND MAKE IT.
>> YEAH.
>> I HOPE THEY WORK IT--
THINGS OUT FOR THE BEST
OF ALL OF THEM.
>> MM-HMM.
THAT'S WHAT WE REALLY WANT.
BEING PREGNANT WITH TWINS
IS WAY HARDER THAN I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE.
I WAS EXCITED FOR MY SENIOR
YEAR, BUT I JUST CAN'T JUGGLE
SCHOOLWORK ON TOP OF GETTING
READY FOR THE TWINS, SO I'M
TAKING OFF THE FIRST SEMESTER.
NOW I CAN'T BE ON
THE CHEERLEADING TEAM,
AND I HARDLY SEE MY FRIENDS.
>> SO WHAT DO YOU MISS MOST
ABOUT, LIKE, HIGH SCHOOL
AND THEN, LIKE, BEING ABLE
TO HANG OUT WITH YOUR FRIENDS
AND DO WHATEVER YOU WANT?
>> I CHEERED.
I CHEERED ALL THE TIME,
PEP RALLIES AND GAMES,
AND I DON'T HAVE THAT ANYMORE,
AND IT'S MY SENIOR YEAR,
AND I WANTED IT THE MOST.
SO I KIND OF MISS ALL THAT.
NOW I'M UP IN THE STANDS
LIKE THIS.
WHOO.
IT'S NOT THE SAME AT ALL.
I MISS IT.
>> ARE YOU COMING BACK
TO HIGH SCHOOL?
>> AH, MAYBE THE SECOND
SEMESTER.
>> YEAH, AND I HAD TO USE
A BREAST PUMP IN THE BATHROOMS
AT SCHOOL.
>> [squeals]
>> WHEN WE FIRST FOUND OUT,
IT WAS, LIKE, CRAZY,
'CAUSE LEAH, SHE TOOK, LIKE,
16 PREGNANCY TESTS.
[laughter]
ALL OF THEM CAME OUT POSITIVE.
SHE'S LIKE, "MAN, I DON'T THINK
THIS IS RIGHT.
YEAH, IT'S NOT RIGHT."
>> LEAH, ANSWER ME THIS.
WHAT'S THE SCARIEST THING
ABOUT BEING PREGNANT RIGHT NOW?
>> YOU KNOW, I REALLY WANT
TO TRY TO MAKE IT WORK WITH
ME AND COREY.
THAT'S, LIKE, THE BIGGEST THING.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT.
>> AND I DIDN'T HAVE MY DAD.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I DIDN'T HAVE MY DAD AT ALL,
AND I DON'T WANT MY KIDS
TO GO WITHOUT THAT AND NOT SEE
US TOGETHER.
>> I DON'T SEE THAT.
>> THEY NEED BOTH PARENTS.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T WANT MY KIDS TO GROW UP
WITHOUT THEIR DAD, SO EVEN
THOUGH WE'RE STILL GETTING
TO KNOW EACH OTHER, ME AND COREY
NEED TO STAY TOGETHER.
I JUST REALLY HOPE ME AND COREY
CAN MAKE IT WORK.
>> YOU CAN IF Y'ALL WANT TO
AND YOU WORK ON IT HARD ENOUGH.
BUT YOU ALL ARE YOUNG AND DON'T
KNOW WHAT YOU WANT OUT OF LIFE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S REALLY
MY SOUL MATE.
I MEAN, WE DON'T GET ALONG
ALL THE TIME.
WE--OH, GOSH.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHETHER YOU WANT TO FACE IT
OR NOT, YOU TWO HAVE TWO KIDS
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
>> BUT WE'VE ONLY BEEN TOGETHER
A MONTH, AND THEN WE GOT
PREGNANT.
AND NOW WE BOTH FEEL LIKE
WE HAVE TO BE TOGETHER.
YOU CAN'T JUST SAY,
"I DON'T WANT TO BE WITH YOU,"
WITH TWO KIDS ON THE WAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU CAN'T JUST BE LIKE, NO.
>> NOT YOUR AVERAGE BOYFRIEND
AND GIRLFRIEND RELATIONSHIP.
>> IT'S NOT THAT EASY TO BE,
LIKE, A SINGLE MOM WITH TWO
KIDS.
MOST PEOPLE FALL IN LOVE
AND THEN START A FAMILY.
I JUST HOPE IT WORKS OUT
THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
>> WHILE MOST OF MY FRIENDS ARE
GETTING READY FOR HOMECOMING,
ME AND COREY ARE GETTING READY
TO START A FAMILY.
COREY IS WORKING TWO JOBS
TO SAVE UP MONEY FOR WHEN
THE TWINS GET HERE.
AND I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR
A PLACE FOR US TO LIVE.
COREY'S SUPPOSED TO BE SELLING
HIS TRUCK, SINCE THERE'S NO ROOM
IN THERE FOR TWO BABY SEATS,
BUT SO FAR, HE'S BEEN DRAGGING
HIS FEET.
>> TAKES A LOT OF GROWING UP
TO GET RID OF THAT TRUCK.
>> YEAH.
BAD THING ABOUT IT IS, THIS
TRUCK'S BEEN BETTER TO ME THAN
LEAH HAS, AND IT'S GOT TO GO.
>> OHH.
>> BLACK THUNDER MY BABY DOLL.
>> BLACK THUNDER.
>> I LOVE MY TRUCK.
>> SO TODAY, I'M DRAGGING COREY
TO CHECK OUT A CAR FOR SALE.
I THINK SHE'S KICKING
MY BLADDER,
LIKE, STRAIGHT-UP KICKING IT.
>> WE'RE HERE TO LOOK AT
THE TAHOE FOR SALE.
[laughter]
>> [laughing hysterically]
CAN YOU HOLD ON?
OH, MY GOD.
I JUST PEED MY PANTS.
>> YOU CAN LOOK INSIDE OF IT.
>> I CAN'T HAUL TWO CAR SEATS
AND LEAH IN THAT TRUCK.
>> CAN'T DO THAT.
>> [laughing]
>> GONNA BE ROUGH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[laughing]
I CAN'T--I CAN'T--
PLEASE, GO.
GO, GO.
>> YOU GOT TO GET IN.
>> [whispering] COREY!
[laughter]
>> SHE PISSED HER PANTS.
SHE--SHE--[laughing]
SHE PEED HER PANTS.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[laughter]
>> ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE ALL RIGHT, MAN.
>> IT'S NOT FUNNY.
PLEASE, STOP.
[laughter]
ALL OVER MY PANTS.
PLEASE STOP LAUGHING AT ME.
>> [high-pitched babbling]
>> I THOUGHT MY WATER BROKE.
[laughter]
>> STINKS.
>> BABY.
I COULDN'T STOP IT.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY, COREY,
IT'S ALL THE WAY DOWN
TO MY SOCKS, MY SOCKS!
THAT WAS, LIKE, A BIG OLD PEE.
>> I DIDN'T MEAN TO LAUGH
AT YOU.
>> [moans]
THIS SUCKS SO BAD.
>> COME HERE.
LAY ON ME.
I WAS LAUGHING WITH YOU,
NOT AT YOU.
>> NO, YOU WAS LAUGHING AT ME.
YOU WAS LIKE, "YOU PEED
YOUR PANTS."
I'M TRYING TO LAUGH IT OFF,
BUT THIS WHOLE PREGNANCY
IS GETTING REALLY HARD.
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME, HAVING TWINS
MAKES MY PREGNANCY HIGH RISK,
AND I'M STARTING TO HAVE
A TON OF HEALTH ISSUES.
I'M SICK SMELLING THIS ALREADY.
I'M HUNGRY, THOUGH,
BUT I JUST CAN'T EAT.
LIKE, I WANT TO EAT THOSE WINGS.
>> EAT THEM.
>> STOP BEING A JERK.
I WISH YOU COULD GET PREGNANT.
>> I WISH I COULD TOO.
>> NO, YOU REALLY DON'T.
YOU HAVE NO CLUE HOW BAD
IT SUCKS.
OH, GOSH.
I JUST FEEL BAD.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH BEING SICK
ALL OF THE TIME, BUT ON TOP
OF THAT, I'M STARTING TO FEEL
LONELY.
I HARDLY SEE ANYONE SINCE
I'M NOT IN SCHOOL, BUT TODAY
IS MY BABY SHOWER, AND I GET
TO SEE ALL THE GIRLS AGAIN.
OH.
[women cooing]
GOT THESE TOO.
[laughter]
FEEL THIS RIGHT HERE.
>> IS THAT WHERE HER HEAD'S AT?
>> THAT'S HER HEAD.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> I WANT TO FEEL IT.
>> FEEL IT.
>> I WANT TO FEEL IT,
BUT I CAN'T, LIKE, REACH OVER
THE TABLE.
[laughter]
>> [gasps]
>> FEEL IT.
>> DOES IT HURT,
LIKE, WHEN THEY KICK YOU?
>> THE BABIES ARE LAYING
ON THE SCIATIC NERVE ON MY BACK.
SO MY LEG GOES COMPLETELY NUMB
SOMETIMES.
>> WHEN YOU SLEEP?
>> YEAH, AT NIGHT.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO SLEEP
FOR THREE NIGHTS IN A ROW
BECAUSE OF IT.
AND MY VEINS ARE BUSTED
ALL THE WAY DOWN MY LEG.
>> LIKE, FROM THE BABIES?
>> I'M NOT GONNA COME BACK
UNTIL JANUARY.
>> YEAH.
>> BECAUSE I'M MISSING OUT
ON EVERYTHING, EVERYTHING.
>> YOU MISSED HOMECOMING WEEK.
>> OH, THAT'S WHAT SUCKS
ABOUT BEING PREGNANT TOO.
I MISS OUT.
CHEERLEADING, GAMES.
[peaceful acoustic guitar music]
*
SEEING ALL MY FRIENDS
REMINDS ME OF EVERYTHING
I'M MISSING OUT ON.
I SHOULD BE HANGING OUT
AND SHOPPING FOR SENIOR WEEK,
BUT INSTEAD, I'M HOME,
SORTING BABY CLOTHES
AND DIAPERS.
I HAVE A LOT ON MY PLATE
RIGHT NOW.
[scoffs and sniffles]
I'M HAVING PROBLEMS WITH MY LEG.
I'M HAVING PROBLEMS WITH
MY BACK.
I HAVE TO GO SEE ANOTHER DOCTOR.
IT'S JUST LIKE, IF IT'S NOT ONE
THING THEN IT'S ANOTHER.
>> MM-HMM.
I AIN'T GOT ENOUGH MONEY
TO DO ANYTHING.
I WORK TWO JOBS.
I STILL DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MONEY.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO
ABOUT THE HOUSE SITUATION?
>> I'VE BEEN LOOKING.
>> WE WON'T EVER FIND ANYTHING,
JUST LIKE WE CAN'T FRICKIN'
SELL THAT TRUCK.
>> I HAVE TO WORK ALL DAY
AND THEN ALL NIGHT.
I DON'T HAVE TIME.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO GO RIDING
AROUND LOOKING FOR APARTMENTS
AND GOING PLACES.
>> [sighs]
THIS IS WAY TOO HARD.
ALL NIGHT, I COULD HARDLY SLEEP.
MY LEGS WERE HURTING.
MY BACK WAS HURTING,
AND I STARTED HAVING SHARP PAINS
IN MY STOMACH.
THIS MORNING, IT GOT EVEN WORSE,
SO WE CALLED MY DOCTOR.
>> BUT HER BELLY'S TIGHTENING
UP, AND SHE'S SAYING SHE'S
HURTING, AND HER BACK'S STARTING
TO HURT NOW.
WHAT DO YOU--
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
>> THERE'S TOO MUCH GOING ON.
THIS HAS BEEN THE WORST THING
I'VE EVER HAD TO GO THROUGH
IN MY WHOLE ENTIRE LIFE.
>> BUT COREY WAS WRONG.
IT'S NOT OKAY.
MY DOCTOR TOOK ONE LOOK AT ME
AND ADMITTED ME TO THE HOSPITAL.
THOSE SHARP PAINS I'M FEELING
ARE CONTRACTIONS.
I'M ONLY SIX MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND IT'S WAY TOO EARLY FOR ME
TO GIVE BIRTH.
>> I'M ONLY SIX MONTHS PREGNANT,
BUT LAST NIGHT, I STARTED
GOING INTO LABOR.
[rushing sound]
MY WATER DIDN'T BREAK,
BUT I'M HAVING REALLY BAD
CONTRACTIONS.
THIS IS HAPPENING WAY TOO SOON.
AND THE DOCTORS ARE TRYING
EVERYTHING TO STOP ME FROM
GIVING BIRTH.
THAT DOCTOR SCARED ME TOO
'CAUSE HE WAS ALL LIKE,
GET ME UP HERE NOW.
MY DOCTORS TOLD ME DELIVERING
THE TWINS THIS EARLY WOULD BE
REALLY DANGEROUS.
EACH BABY WEIGHS LESS THAN
TWO POUNDS, AND THEIR LUNGS
AREN'T DEVELOPED ENOUGH
TO BREATHE ON THEIR OWN.
I'M TERRIFIED THAT THE GIRLS
WON'T SURVIVE IF I HAVE TO
GIVE BIRTH.
BUT MY CONTRACTIONS KEEP GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE, AND IT SEEMS
LIKE NOTHING THE DOCTORS DO
IS HELPING.
>> THEY'VE UPPED IT,
AND IT'S NOT--IT'S NOT DOING
ANY GOOD.
SHE STARTING TO GET HARDER
AND HARDER CONTRACTIONS.
>> YEAH.
IT TOOK THREE DAYS IN
THE HOSPITAL, BUT THE DOCTORS
FINALLY FOUND A COMBINATION
OF MEDICINES THAT WORK FOR ME.
SO I MEAN, WITH THE MEDICINE,
THEY'VE STOPPED.
TODAY, THEY'RE LETTING ME GO
HOME, BUT I'M ON STRICT ORDERS
TO STAY ON BED REST FOR THE REST
OF MY PREGNANCY.
ANY LITTLE ACTIVITY COULD
TRIGGER MY LABOR.
DID YOU MISS ME, HUH?
HUH?
DID YOU MISS ME?
I JUST HOPE THINGS GO SMOOTHLY
FROM HERE ON OUT.
>> [barks]
>> BED REST SUCKS.
ALL I CAN DO IS LIE AROUND.
OOH, AND IT'S REALLY COLD
IN THIS HOUSE.
I'M GONNA GO LAY DOWN.
I'M BORED AND LONELY,
AND I CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT
ALL THE STUFF I SHOULD BE DOING
TO GET READY FOR THE GIRLS.
>> WHAT'S THE WORST THING
YOU HATE ON BED REST?
>> LAYING THERE.
THERE'S NOTHING FUN
TO LAYING THERE.
I WANT IT OVER WITH.
AFTER FOUR WEEKS, I'VE HAD
ALL I CAN TAKE.
SINCE I'VE BEEN LAID UP,
MY MOM STEPPED IN AND FOUND ME
AND COREY A PLACE TO LIVE.
MOVING IN TOGETHER IS A HUGE
STEP FORWARD IN OUR
RELATIONSHIP, AND I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M REALLY READY.
BUT READY OR NOT,
TODAY IS MOVING DAY.
I'M BREAKING MY BED REST
SO ME AND COREY CAN MOVE OVER
SOME OF OUR STUFF.
OUR NEW PLACE NEEDS
A LOT OF WORK.
BUT IT'S ALL COREY CAN AFFORD,
SO WE'LL JUST FIX IT UP
OURSELVES.
>> THAT'S DARK DARK.
>> YOU DON'T LIKE THAT BROWN?
>> NO, I THINK IT'S GONNA LOOK
WEIRD ON THE WALLS.
IT'LL LOOK YELLOW.
>> YOU NEED ONE OF THIS ONE?
TWO AND THREE?
>> AND THEN ONE HERE
IN THE WHITE.
>> ONE GALLON?
ALL RIGHT.
A SECOND THERE, AND I'LL...
>> OKAY.
>> IT'S GONNA BE $120 FOR...
>> NO, IT AIN'T.
>> 6 TIMES 20.
6 GALLONS TIMES $20, $120.
$120 PLUS TAX.
>> OH, GOD.
WHAT IF WE DON'T HAVE THE MONEY?
UM, COREY, WELL, YOU GO ASK HIM.
TELL HIM, DON'T GET THE
EXPENSIVE GALLON.
>> HOW MUCH IS A GALLON OF PAINT
THAT YOU'RE USING?
>> NEUTRAL BASE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND YOU'RE LOOKING AROUND
$24.99 A GALLON.
>> OKAY.
WELL, HOLD ON, HOLD ON,
HOLD ON FOR THAT A SECOND,
'CAUSE I GOT TO TALK TO HER
REAL FAST.
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> WE AIN'T GETTING PAINT TODAY.
$24.99 A GALLON.
I'M SORRY.
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT TILL
THE NEXT PAYDAY.
I'M SORRY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT SUCKS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> NOTHING.
TRYING--TRYING TO GET--
>> TRYING TO GET WHAT?
>> PAINT.
>> CHANGE?
>> PAINT?
>> JUST SAY YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU AGGRAVATED?
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I HATE BEING BROKE.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE NOTHING
ME AND COREY DO GOES RIGHT,
AND I'M GETTING REALLY
FRUSTRATED.
I THINK I'VE REACHED
MY BREAKING POINT...
[sniffles]
TO FLIPPING OUT AND JUST
GOING CRAZY, OKAY?
>> WHY?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED, BUT--
>> WELL, LET'S SEE.
>> WHAT HIT THE BREAKING POINT?
>> FIRST OF ALL, WE HAVE, LIKE,
$90 IN THE BANK.
>> THAT'LL BE ABOUT $60 NOW.
>> OH, YEAH, $60 NOW.
I FEEL LIKE CRAP.
I REALLY DO.
I FEEL LIKE I'M SWOLLEN, LIKE,
ALL OVER, REALLY BAD.
>> YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY,
AIN'T YOU?
>> I'M IN A WONDERFUL MOOD.
ACTUALLY, I'M REALLY NOT...
>> I KNOW.
>> IN A GOOD MOOD TODAY.
>> I KNOW, SARCASTIC.
>> I'M NOT.
>> OKAY, WELL, I GOT TO GO.
SORRY.
>> OKAY.
OOH.
DON'T THROW IT AT ME AGAIN,
YOU STUPID PIECE OF [bleep].
COREY THINKS HE'S FUNNY,
BUT RIGHT NOW, I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING FUNNY ABOUT OUR
SITUATION.
SEE HER HAND RIGHT HERE?
>> YES.
>> AND HER NOSE AND HER EYES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
>> TWO KIDS.
>> YEAH.
NOT JUST KIDS, THEY'RE GONNA
BE FRICKIN' BABIES.
>> INFANTS, YEAH.
>> YEAH, THEY'RE GONNA BE,
LIKE, SCREAMING, WAKING ME UP
AT NIGHT.
I WOULDN'T ADVISE ANYBODY
TO DO THIS, EVER.
>> HOW YOU AND COREY ARE NOW?
>> OH, WE'RE BETTER, I GUESS.
I GUESS, PREGNANCY--
LIKE, AFTER THE BABIES ARE HERE,
IT WILL REALLY...
>> ARE YOU HAPPY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> NEED A BETTER ANSWER
THAN THAT.
>> I AM.
[giggles]
I AM.
OR AT LEAST, I'M REALLY
TRYING TO BE.
>> LAST WEEK, ME AND COREY
MOVED IN TOGETHER, AND WE
FINALLY SOLD HIS TRUCK.
WE SPENT TWO WEEKS GETTING
SETTLED IN OUR NEW PLACE,
AND TODAY, I'M UNPACKING
THE LAST BOXES.
IT'S HARD, THOUGH, 'CAUSE
STARTING MY NEW LIFE JUST MAKES
ME MISS MY OLD LIFE.
>> OH, MAN, THIS IS ALL
YOUR OLD STUFF.
"HI, MY NAME IS LEAH.
I AM NINE YEARS OLD.
FIVE YEARS FROM NOW,
I WILL BE TRYING TO GET
A SCHOLARSHIP TO GO TO COLLEGE."
>> MM.
>> THAT CHANGED.
>> SHUT UP.
>> "THEN I'M GONNA GET READY
TO GO TO COLLEGE BECAUSE
I WANT TO BE A DOCTOR WHEN
I GROW UP."
>> "WHAT'S UP WITH YOU
AND LITTLE FISHER?"
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S ROBBIE.
"YOU AND LITTLE FISHER."
I DATED ROBBIE FOR TWO
FREAKING YEARS.
OH, NO--
>> 2 1/2 ALMOST.
>> YEAH, IT WAS ALMOST
THREE YEARS.
>> YEAH.
>> [sighs]
THIS IS SAD.
I WANT TO GO BACK TO THESE DAYS.
I HAVE "I LOVE ROBBIE" WRITTEN
ALL OVER THIS FRICKIN' BOOK.
>> KINDERGARTEN.
>> I REALLY DID LOVE HIM,
YOU KNOW?
AND THINGS JUST WENT SO WRONG.
[chime dings]
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO ROBBIE
SINCE I GOT PREGNANT, BUT WHEN
I THINK ABOUT HOW HAPPY I WAS
WITH HIM, IT MAKES ME QUESTION
WHAT I HAVE WITH COREY.
NOW EVERY LITTLE THING COREY
DOES DRIVES ME CRAZY.
COREY, DON'T DRIVE SO FAST,
PLEASE.
>> I AIN'T DRIVING FAST.
I'M GOING 40.
>> YOU'RE HITTING 40.
STOP GETTING ALL DRIVING FAST
AND [bleep].
>> GOD, I'M ALWAYS THE BAD GUY.
I'M ALWAYS THE BAD GUY.
>> DON'T ACT LIKE THE BAD GUY,
AND YOU WON'T BE THE BAD GUY.
>> WHY ARE YOU GETTING MAD
AT ME FOR?
>> IT'S NOT JUST THAT COREY'S
DRIVING TOO FAST;
THIS WHOLE RELATIONSHIP
IS GOING TOO FAST.
THE TWINS ARE DUE IN SIX WEEKS,
BUT I'M STARTING TO RETHINK
EVERYTHING.
THIS IS ALL JUST LIKE
AN EMOTIONAL ROLLER COASTER.
IT'S, LIKE, A BIG CHANGE,
FROM BEING ABLE TO GO AND DO
WHAT I WANT TO DO WITH FRIENDS
AND SCHOOL AND CHEERLEADING
AND TO TRYING TO BE A MOM,
STAY HOME AND DO THINGS
THAT A GROWN WOMAN WOULD DO.
>> YOU MADE DECISIONS THAT'S
PUT YOU IN THAT SITUATION.
I'M HAVING TO LET GO
OF MY DAUGHTER WAY BEFORE
I SHOULD HAVE HAD TO HAVE.
>> I DON'T REGRET MY KIDS,
BUT I LOSE SLEEP, AND THEY'RE
NOT EVEN HERE.
[sighs]
THAT NIGHT, I DECIDED TO STAY
AT MY MOM'S HOUSE BECAUSE
I NEEDED SOME SPACE FROM COREY.
WITH SO MUCH ON MY MIND,
I COULDN'T SLEEP AT ALL.
FINALLY, I WOKE UP MY MOM
BECAUSE SOMETHING DIDN'T FEEL
RIGHT.
I THINK I'M LEAKING.
>> YOU THINK WHAT?
>> I THINK I'M LEAKING.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO CALL
YOUR DOCTOR?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T WANT TO.
'CAUSE IF I GET THERE
AND IT'S PEE, THAT'S GONNA
BE EMBARRASSING.
I'M SCARED 'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
MY MOM TOOK ME TO THE HOSPITAL.
TURNS OUT MY WATER FINALLY
BROKE.
EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT DUE FOR
SIX MORE WEEKS, THE DOCTOR SAID
IT WAS NORMAL FOR TWINS
TO BE BORN EARLY.
COREY CAME OUT AS SOON
AS I CALLED HIM.
EVEN THOUGH WE'VE BEEN FIGHTING
A LOT, I'M REALLY GLAD
TO SEE HIM.
I HAVE TO HAVE AN EMERGENCY
C-SECTION BECAUSE THE BOTTOM
BABY IS BREECHED.
[sighs]
>> AW.
[kissing sounds]
>> I LOVE YOU, BABY.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
GONNA BE OKAY, PROMISE.
PINKIE PROMISE.
>> PROMISE ME.
BETTER BE.
>> THEY PREPPED ME FOR SURGERY,
AND COREY PUT ON SCRUBS AND
STAYED WITH ME THE WHOLE TIME.
[clock ticking]
[baby crying]
ALIANNAH WAS BORN FIRST,
AND ONE MINUTE LATER,
ALEEAH ARRIVED.
>> HERE COMES COREY.
>> SINCE THE TWINS ARE SIX WEEKS
EARLY, THE DOCTORS TOOK THEM
STRAIGHT TO INTENSIVE CARE.
I WAS STILL IN SURGERY AND
WASN'T EVEN ABLE TO HOLD THEM.
THEY'RE PERFECTLY HEALTHY,
BUT THEY WERE SO SMALL;
THEY HAD TO HAVE TUBES
TO GIVE THEM FOOD AND OXYGEN.
AFTER I RECOVERED FROM SURGERY,
I WENT TO INTENSIVE CARE
TO VISIT THEM.
[baby cries]
>> AW.
>> YOU'RE DOING FINE, HONEY.
THE TWINS HAVE TO BE CLOSELY
MONITORED, SO THEY'RE STAYING
AT THE HOSPITAL.
I DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE,
BUT THREE DAYS AFTER GIVING
BIRTH, I WAS DISCHARGED.
I WASN'T EXPECTING TO LEAVE
THE HOSPITAL WITHOUT MY BABIES.
I'M REALLY TIRED.
>> BABY.
>> [sobs]
>> COME HERE.
IT'S OKAY.
>> [crying]
>> I, LIKE, CARRIED THEM
FOR EIGHT MONTHS, AND NOW
I HAVE TO LEAVE THEM.
[sniffs]
THEN I'M WALKING OUT WITH JUST
BALLOONS.
[whimpers]
OH.
[sniffs]
IT'S HARD.
>> THE TWINS HAVE TO STAY IN
THE HOSPITAL FOR A WHILE
'CAUSE THEY'RE SO SMALL.
SO ME AND COREY VISIT THEM
EVERY DAY.
[monitor beeps]
[giggles]
IT'S A LITTLE SCARY CHANGING
THEIR DIAPERS 'CAUSE THEY'RE
SO TINY.
WHAT ARE YOU--
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> CHANGING THE DIAPER.
>> OKAY, THEN YOU PUT
A NEW DIAPER UNDER.
YOU GONNA PUT THE SAME DIRTY
DIAPER ON HER, DORK?
ALEEAH, I SEE YOU'RE ORNERY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
JUST TAKE THE DIAPER OFF.
JUST TAKE THE DIAPER OFF, HONEY.
>> OH, COME ON, GIRL.
>> OKAY.
COREY'S A TOTAL CHICKEN
WITH THE GIRLS, BUT HE BETTER
GET COMFORTABLE FAST, 'CAUSE
SOON IT'S JUST GONNA BE HIM
AND ME TAKING CARE OF THESE TWO.
AFTER THREE WEEKS IN
THE HOSPITAL, TODAY WE'RE
FINALLY TAKING THE TWINS HOME.
>> IT'S OKAY.
COREY, YOU CAN'T BE SCARED
DRIVING HOME, OH, PLEASE.
>> SO FAR, ME AND COREY
HAVE BEEN OKAY.
I JUST HOPE WE CAN HANDLE
EVERYTHING ON OUR OWN.
[baby cries]
TAKING CARE OF TWO NEWBORN
BABIES IS A LOT OF WORK.
WHEN ALI STARTS CRYING,
SHE WAKES UP ALEEAH.
COREY?
>> WHAT?
>> I LET YOU SLEEP.
YOU CAN GET UP AND HELP ME.
AS SOON AS I CHANGE ONE DIAPER,
THE OTHER ONE NEEDS TO BE
CHANGED.
OKAY, OKAY.
I'M BARELY GETTING ANY SLEEP
AT NIGHT, AND I'M REALLY
ON EDGE.
HERE.
[baby fusses]
SHE WOULD NOT GO TO SLEEP,
AND YOU'RE OVER THERE SNORING.
JUST TO HEAR YOU SNORE,
LIKE, INFURIATED ME.
I WAS LIKE, OOH.
>> SHOULD HAVE WOKE ME UP.
>> YOU DID WAKE UP SOMETIMES.
STOP YOUR GRUNTING.
[baby grunts]
OH, SO NOW YOU'RE GONNA
GRUNT TOO?
IS THAT GOING TOO FAST
OVER THERE?
>> [chuckles]
>> WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
>> NOTHING.
I WASN'T SAYING NOTHING.
I WAS JUST...
>> [mimics chuckling]
YOU DID THAT.
>> GOD.
>> YOU COULD HAVE BEEN LIKE,
"YEAH, THAT IS A LITTLE FAST,"
NOT...[chuckles].
>> I WANT A KISS.
YOU HAVEN'T KISSED ME
IN, LIKE, THREE DAYS.
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
WE BOTH HAVE MORNING BREATH,
AND THAT'S NOT COOL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I THOUGHT ONCE THE GIRLS
WERE BORN, MOTHERHOOD WOULD
COME NATURAL TO ME.
BUT DEALING WITH TWO BABIES
AND COREY IS MORE THAN
I BARGAINED FOR.
TODAY, REGAN AND RACHAEL CAME BY
TO CHEER ME UP.
>> IS IT HARD KEEPING UP
WITH BOTH OF THEM WHEN THEY'RE
BOTH CRYING AND FEEDING THEM?
>> YEAH, Y'ALL OUGHT TO
BEEN HERE EARLIER.
THEY STARTED CRYING,
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, GOSH."
AND I WAS TRYING TO FEED THEM
AND HOLD THEM.
I, LIKE, HELD THEM BOTH.
I HAD ONE RIGHT HERE
AND ONE RIGHT HERE IN MY ARM,
AND I'M TRYING TO MAKE A BOTTLE
LIKE THIS.
IT WAS CRAZY.
THEN THEY WANT TO CRY,
AND THEN I HAD TO FEED THEM.
I PUT ONE RIGHT HERE
AND ONE RIGHT HERE, AND I WAS
FEEDING THEM LIKE THIS.
>> DO YOU ENJOY BEING A MOM?
>> YES, SOMETIMES.
IT'S HARD.
THAT'S THE ONLY PART THAT
I DON'T ENJOY, BUT...
>> THE HARD PART?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, THAT'S PART OF
BEING A MOM.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD
NO MATTER WHAT.
>> I STILL LOOK AT THEM, THOUGH,
AND I'M LIKE, "OKAY, THAT WAS
IN MY BELLY?
THAT'S REALLY MINE?
NO WAY."
>> DID THEY REALLY JUST
KIND OF COME OUT THE OTHER DAY?
>> BUT THEY'RE MINE FOREVER.
MM.
[sighs]
I'M TRYING TO GET USED TO
BEING A MOM.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I CAN'T STILL BE A TEENAGER TOO.
NEXT WEEK, I FINALLY GO BACK
TO HIGH SCHOOL.
MY MOM'S GONNA WATCH THE GIRLS
DURING THE DAY, SO I DON'T EVEN
NEED DAY CARE.
WHEN WE GO BACK TO SCHOOL,
WE HAVE TO MAKE IT FUN.
I'LL BE DRIVING.
WE'LL LEAVE AT LUNCH.
>> YOU'LL GET IN TROUBLE.
>> I USED TO SNEAK OUT
ALL THE TIME.
>> YEAH, I KNOW YOU DID.
>> SO I'M GONNA LIVE IT UP.
LIKE, I WASN'T THERE FOR...
HOW MANY MONTHS IT'S BEEN
ALREADY?
I HAVEN'T BEEN A BIG PART OF IT.
I HATED MISSING HOMECOMING WEEK.
OH.
LIKE, ALL THE DRESSING UP
AND STUFF.
OH, MADE ME SO MAD.
I'M EXCITED TO FINALLY GET
BACK TO SCHOOL AND MAKE THE MOST
OF MY SENIOR YEAR.
BUT COREY'S GOT AN ATTITUDE,
'CAUSE HE KNOWS I'LL BE BACK
AROUND MY EX-BOYFRIEND ROBBIE,
AND WE USED TO GET INTO
A LOT OF TROUBLE TOGETHER.
>> WHEN ARE YOU GETTING
YOUR LICENSE?
>> WHENEVER I CAN.
IT'S MY SENIOR YEAR, AND I HAVE
NOT BEEN A PART OF IT AT ALL.
>> YOU KEEP A GOOD HEAD ON YOU,
AND IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
BUT IF YOU GO TO SCHOOL AND YOU
JUST GO HOG WILD, NO.
>> WELL, I'M GONNA LIVE IT UP
JUST LIKE I LIVE--I WOULD HAVE
IF I WASN'T THERE.
>> I'M SAYING, YOU CAN LIVE IT
UP WITHOUT GOING CRAZY.
>> HOW WOULD I GO CRAZY?
>> LIKE, PARTY EVERY WEEKEND,
PARTY EVERY DAY.
JUST LET THAT CRAP
GET IN THE WAY OF YOUR FAMILY
THAT YOU HAVE NOW.
>> UM, MY GIRLS MEAN MORE TO ME
THAN THAT.
I KNOW THAT I'M A MOM NOW,
BUT IT'S STILL MY SENIOR YEAR,
AND I SHOULD BE ABLE TO ENJOY
IT, NO MATTER WHAT COREY SAYS.
>> IT'S MY FIRST DAY BACK
AT HIGH SCHOOL.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
ALL OF MY FRIENDS.
[giggles]
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> NOTHING, BABY.
I LOVE YOU.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
MOMMY'S GOT TO GO TO SCHOOL.
SO I'M SO EXCITED.
AND RACHAEL'S LIKE, "ME TOO."
WALKING IN THE HALLWAYS
WITH ALL MY FRIENDS, I FELT LIKE
I WAS FINALLY GETTING TO BE
A TEENAGER AGAIN.
I HAVE LUNCH WITH RACHAEL AND
ALYSSA, AND REGAN AND ROBBIE
ARE IN MY FOURTH PERIOD CLASS.
[school bell rings]
TONIGHT, WE'RE ALL GOING OUT
TO CELEBRATE MY FIRST DAY BACK.
I GET TO GO OUT TONIGHT.
NOW, WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
>> I DIDN'T SAY IT WAS A DEAL.
>> WELL, I'M GOING.
>> I DIDN'T SAY NOT TO.
>> WELL, I WAS JUST SAYING.
I'M NOT SURE WHO ALL
IS REALLY GOING.
I KNOW THAT IT'S GONNA BE
ME, REGAN, VICTORIA.
SHE'S RIDING WITH FIELDS
AND ROBBIE.
UM...
[hair spray spritzing]
WHO ELSE?
RACHAEL.
SOME OTHER GUYS, I GUESS.
I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE TOLD
COREY MY EX-BOYFRIEND ROBBIE
WAS COMING, 'CAUSE NOW HE'S
RUINING MY NIGHT.
>> YOU TALKING ABOUT...
[mumbles]
ALL OF A SUDDEN, HERE'S ROBBIE
HERE, HERE'S ROBBIE--
IT KIND OF GETS KIND OF
A WORRY IN MY HEAD.
>> I DON'T EVER SAY THAT.
>> [bleep] PSYCHO.
>> WHAT IS IT WITH YOU
AND "PSYCHO"?
>> 'CAUSE YOU ARE, LEAH.
YOU GET MAD 'CAUSE I GET ALL
HUFFY-PUFFY ABOUT YOUR
EX-BOYFRIEND.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT IT, COREY!
YESTERDAY, YOU WAS ALL LIKE--
>> DON'T YELL, PLEASE.
>> WHATEVER.
I DON'T CARE.
YOU MAKE ME NOT CARE,
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
>> I KNOW.
I DON'T REALLY CARE EITHER.
>> I CAN'T STAND YOU.
I REALLY CAN'T.
>> I CAN'T STAND YOU
HALF THE TIME.
>> I CAN'T STAND YOU ALL
THE TIME, SO WHAT'S IT MATTER?
>> OKAY, THEN--
[groans]
WHY YOU WITH ME, THEN?
>> MAYBE BECAUSE I HAVE
TWO KIDS WITH YOU.
>> IS THAT THE ONLY REASON?
>> THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU
TO ACT LIKE THIS.
I'M GOING TO BE GOING TO SCHOOL
EVERY DAY.
ARE YOU GONNA ACT LIKE THAT
EVERY TIME I WALK IN THE DOOR?
>> NO, WHEN WE--CONVERSATION--
>> DO US A FAVOR?
WELL, THEN WHAT'S THE
DIFFERENCE?
I CAN'T HELP THAT HE HANGS OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO BUILD
A BRIDGE AND GET OVER IT.
AND I WANT TO GO OUT ONE TIME,
AND JUST BECAUSE ROBBIE'S GOING,
I CAN'T GO?
>> I DIDN'T SAY YOU COULDN'T GO.
I NEVER SAID YOU COULDN'T GO.
>> NO, BUT YOU ACT LIKE THAT.
>> I SAID, BUT--OKAY.
WHEN I GO OUT, I'M GOING--
>> THIS IS THE ONLY TIME WE
FIGHT, WHEN I WANT TO GO OUT.
>> NO, BECAUSE YOU GET THIS
LITTLE ATTITUDE WHEN YOU'RE
GETTING READY TO GO OUT,
AND YOU'RE LIKE, "EH, EH, EH,
I'M GOING OUT AND HAVING--
I'M GONNA GO OUT HERE
AND DAH, DAH, DAH."
YOU STRUT AROUND LIKE A LITTLE
CHICKEN TURKEY WITH HIS TAIL
PLUCKED OUT.
THAT'S THE WAY YOU ALWAYS ACT
EVERY TIME YOU GET READY
TO DO SOMETHING.
AND THEN I'M KIND OF LIKE, OKAY,
SHE'S GONNA GO [bleep] CRAZY
TONIGHT.
>> HOW AM I FLOCKING AROUND BY
TELLING YOU I'M GOING OUT AND
I TOLD YOU WHO ALL WAS GOING?
I COULD HAVE BEEN LIKE,
"NOPE, HE'S NOT GOING,"
AND THEN LIED.
>> BUT YOU ALWAYS--
SOME DAY, I WANT--ONE DAY,
I WANT YOU TO PUT YOURSELF
IN MY SHOES AND SEE HOW--
>> I HAVE!
I DON'T CARE.
HOW LONG WAS WE TOGETHER
BEFORE WE GOT PREGNANT?
>> NOT VERY LONG AT ALL,
BUT IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> IT WAS A MONTH.
>> DOESN'T MATTER.
>> WAS I IN LOVE?
NO, I WASN'T.
>> NOR WAS I.
NO, I WASN'T EITHER.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT DID I HAVE--
>> NOW WE HAVE TO STICK
WITH EACH OTHER.
>> STICK?
>> STICK.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING IF IT WASN'T
FOR THEM, YOU WOULD BE GONE?
>> WE BOTH WOULD.
[baby coos]
I FEEL LIKE I'M SUFFOCATING.
ALL I WANT IS TO GET AWAY
FROM THIS WHOLE SITUATION.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> LEAH?
>> HUH?
>> FIRST, I HAVE SHOP.
>> I HAVE A CRIB UP, THANK YOU.
I DON'T NEED TO MAKE IT.
>> YOU MIGHT FEEL MORE
ACCOMPLISHED IF YOU MAKE
YOUR OWN.
[laughter]
>> SHUT UP.
YOU CAN MAKE 'EM FOR ME.
>> NO, I DON'T HAVE SHOP CLASS.
>> YES, YOU CAN.
WELL, YOU CAN MAKE THEM ANYWAY.
>> WHAT CAR DO YOU WANT, LEAH?
>> I DON'T CARE, REALLY.
>> YOU DON'T CARE?
>> NO.
>> WHEN DO YOU GET YOUR LICENSE?
>> SHUT UP, ROBBIE, SHUT UP.
>> I'VE GOT NOTHING TO SAY
TO HIM.
THIS WEEK OR NEXT WEEK.
>> I'M GONNA STAY OFF THE ROAD
NEXT WEEK.
[laughter]
>> WHAT ARE YOU DRIVING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
COREY'S GONNA BUY ME A CAR.
>> COREY'S BUYING YOU A CAR?
THEN YOU'RE GONNA LEAVE HIM?
>> RACHAEL.
[laughter]
ANYWAYS, YEAH, HE'S GONNA
GET ME A CAR.
>> WHAT'S HE GETTING YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW,
WHATEVER I WANT.
HANGING OUT WITH ROBBIE
AND ALL MY FRIENDS JUST MAKES ME
REALIZE HOW UNHAPPY I'VE BEEN
WITH COREY.
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T BE WITH COREY
IF ALL HE DOES IS BRING ME DOWN.
COREY SAID, "YOU LOOK TOO GOOD
NOW TO JUST HAVE TWO KIDS
TO GO OUT," OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
>> YOU GOT TO SHARE IT
WITH THE WORLD.
>> I KNOW.
>> HE SHOULD BE PROUD OF THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE A MILF NOW.
>> YOU'RE A MILF.
>> I HONESTLY DON'T THINK
IT'S GONNA WORK, THOUGH.
>> YOU DON'T THINK SO?
>> WHY?
>> I'M NOT HAPPY.
AGAIN, I HATE TO SAY THAT
BECAUSE I'VE, LIKE, MADE MYSELF
STAY IN THIS POSITION FOR
SO LONG, BUT JUST BECAUSE
WE HAVE KIDS, I DON'T THINK
IT'S FAIR THAT I HAVE TO STAY
WITH HIM.
>> YOU GUYS WERE TOGETHER
FOR TWO MONTHS, SO...
>> WE WAS TOGETHER A MONTH.
>> SEE, THAT--
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO STAY
TOGETHER.
>> I'VE ALWAYS SAW CHEMISTRY
BETWEEN YOU GUYS.
>> SO MAYBE IF YOU GO SO LONG
AND YOU CAN'T FORGET ABOUT
SOMEBODY, THEN MAYBE THERE'S
JUST SOMETHING THERE.
THE TRUTH IS, THE MORE I SEE
ROBBIE, THE MORE I MISS HIM.
WHAT IF I ENDED UP WITH
THE WRONG GUY?
>> [imitates crying]
>> EVER SINCE I STARTED GOING
BACK TO SCHOOL AGAIN, I'VE BEEN
HANGING OUT WITH ROBBIE A LOT.
THINGS WITH ROBBIE ARE SO EASY.
IT MAKES ME WONDER IF I MADE
A BIG MISTAKE BREAKING UP WITH
HIM.
COREY CAN TELL SOMETHING'S UP
AND DOESN'T WANT ME GOING OUT
ANYMORE.
IT'S BECOMING A BIG PROBLEM.
THERE'S A BASKETBALL GAME
TONIGHT.
AND IT'S, LIKE, SENIOR NIGHT
FOR BASKETBALL.
>> MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU CARE IF I GO?
>> YEAH, WHO'S GONNA BE THERE?
>> I DON'T HANG AROUND ROBBIE
AT BASKETBALL GAMES.
>> YOU DID BEFORE.
YOU UNDERSTAND, IT'S YOUR SENIOR
YEAR, BUT YOU PUT YOURSELF IN
THIS POSITION.
SO YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO MAKE
MORE SACRIFICES--
>> YEAH, BUT SACRIFICES DON'T
MEAN THAT I CAN'T GO TO
A BASKETBALL GAME.
>> HOLD ON.
I GOT A GOOD EXAMPLE.
>> [sighs]
>> WHAT DID I SACRIFICE
FOR YOU AND THE GIRLS?
WHAT WAS MY NUMBER ONE PRIDE
AND JOY THING THAT I OWNED?
>> OH, A TRUCK.
>> I LOVED THAT TRUCK.
OKAY, THAT'S KIND OF LIKE
MY SENIOR YEAR TO ME.
>> I LOST EVERYTHING TOO.
I LOST HALF OF MY SENIOR YEAR.
I LOST HOMECOMING WEEK.
I LOST CHEERING.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING
THAT I LOST TOO?
IT'S NOT ALL ABOUT YOU EITHER.
>> NO, I'M NOT SAYING THAT
IT'S ALL ABOUT ME.
>> YOU SHOULD BE CARING ENOUGH
TO BE LIKE, "LEAH, I STILL FEEL
LIKE YOU SHOULD GO TO YOUR PROM.
I STILL FEEL LIKE YOU SHOULD BE
ABLE TO ENJOY YOUR SENIOR NIGHT
BASKETBALL GAME."
>> I NEVER SAID YOU COULDN'T GO
TO YOUR PROM.
I PRETTY MUCH BEND OVER
BACKWARDS FOR YOU AND DO
ANYTHING FOR YOU.
>> DID I SAY THAT YOU DIDN'T?
>> NO.
>> I'VE NEVER TALKED--
>> BUT I WISH YOU WOULD HAVE
REALIZED THAT BEFORE YOU LET IT
GO THIS FAR WITH ROBBIE,
'CAUSE THIS, THAT, HIM,
IS THE REASONS FOR US BEING
ON THIS GROUND RIGHT HERE.
>> I WISH I COULD SAY COREY
IS WRONG, BUT WHEN I'M WITH
ROBBIE, THINGS ARE SIMPLE,
AND I HAVE FUN.
I'M A NORMAL TEENAGER AGAIN.
[cheers and applause]
>> WAY TO GO, CARTER!
>> BUT WHEN I'M WITH COREY,
THERE'S ALL THIS PRESSURE
TO GIVE UP THE THINGS THAT
MATTER THE MOST TO ME,
AND EVERY DAY IT GETS WORSE.
>> WE HAVE A FAMILY NOW.
YOU'RE IN HIGH SCHOOL.
YEAH, THAT'S COOL.
BUT YOU HAVE TO THINK.
YOU HAVE A FAMILY, OKAY?
YOU CAN'T GO OUT HERE AND GO
HOG WILD AND DO [bleep] LIKE
THAT AND SAY THAT YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT I THINK.
>> NOT EVERYBODY'S AS INSECURE
AS YOU.
>> IT AIN'T THAT I'M INSECURE,
LEAH.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> DO YOU SERIOUSLY THINK THAT
ROBBIE CAN SUPPORT YOU AND
A FAMILY?
>> DID I SAY HE COULD?
>> NO, BUT THAT'S WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN IF WE SPLIT UP.
YOU'RE GONNA GO CRAWLING RIGHT
BACK TO HIM.
DO I THINK YOU'D PICK HIM
OVER ME?
YEAH, I DO.
'CAUSE YOU DATED FOR TWO YEARS,
AND YOU LOVED HIM,
AND YOU TOLD ME THAT.
>> JEALOUSY IS WHAT SPLIT US UP.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT'S GONNA
DO, AND YOU'RE LETTING IT.
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHAT TO DO
AND HOW WE'RE GONNA FIX IT
AND IF WE'RE EVEN GONNA FIX IT.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW
IF IT'S FIXABLE.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU.
>> OKAY, WHY?
>> THE WAY YOU ACT.
>> WE WAS PERFECTLY FINE
UNTIL HE WALKED IN THE DOOR.
>> NO, WE WAS NOT.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
>> WE WOULD TALK.
WE HAD FUN.
BUT WE'RE NOT FUN--
FUN LIKE GO OUT AND GO TO
HIBACHI'S AND TO TARGET
AND WALMART FUN.
'CAUSE WE HAVE A--
>> BECAUSE COREY DON'T WANT TO.
>> DO WE HAVE THE MONEY
TO DO THAT?
I WANT TO, LEAH.
I DON'T HAVE THE MONEY.
WE DON'T HAVE MONEY TO GO OUT
AND BLOW LIKE [bleep] THAT.
I DON'T THINK IT IS FIXABLE.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
'CAUSE WITH YOUR ATTITUDE,
NOTHING'S GONNA BE FIXABLE.
>> AND WITH YOUR ATTITUDE,
SEEMS LIKE ALL ME AND COREY DO
IS YELL AT EACH OTHER AND CHANGE
DIRTY DIAPERS.
GOING TO SCHOOL IS THE ONLY TIME
I CAN JUST RELAX AND HAVE FUN.
I SEE ALL MY FRIENDS.
I GO TO BASKETBALL GAMES.
I'M BACK WHERE I BELONG.
TODAY, ROBBIE AND HIS FRIEND
DROVE ME TO MY MOM'S HOUSE
AFTER SCHOOL.
I INVITED THEM IN TO SEE
THE GIRLS, BUT NOW ROBBIE'S
BEING SORT OF WEIRD.
WHAT?
YOU HEAR MOMMY?
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
>> WE JUST FED HER.
>> YEAH, WHAT?
[giggles]
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU GUYS?
>> NOTHING AT ALL.
>> MAN, YOU STINK.
SHE STINKS REALLY BAD.
>> DOES SHE, REALLY?
>> YEAH, REALLY BAD.
>> YOU GUYS WANT TO CHANGE
HER DIAPER?
[laughter]
>> THAT'S FUNNY.
THAT'S YOU RIGHT THERE.
>> YOU BETTER LEARN HOW NOW.
>> THAT'S ALL YOU.
IS--
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK
WHEN I GOT PREGNANT?
>> I THOUGHT YOU MADE
A DUMB DECISION.
>> YOU SAID I WAS STUPID.
>> IT WAS.
>> WELL, IT WASN'T ON PURPOSE.
>> IT'S USUALLY NOT
WHEN YOU'RE 16.
>> ROBBIE SEEMS REALLY
UNCOMFORTABLE AROUND THE TWINS.
MAYBE IT WASN'T SUCH A GOOD IDEA
INVITING HIM OVER.
THAT NIGHT WHEN COREY FOUND OUT
ROBBIE CAME TO MY MOM'S HOUSE
AFTER SCHOOL, HE WAS REALLY
UPSET.
>> I DON'T LIKE IT.
YOU CAN SIT HERE AND SAY
WHATEVER YOU WANT, BUT YOU
WOULDN'T LIKE THAT EITHER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I UNDERSTAND THAT THAT'S
YOUR FRIENDS, AND HE HANGS OUT
WITH 'EM, WHATEVER.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S COOL.
AND YOU JUST CALL IT STUPID
AND INSECURE.
THAT'S YOUR OPINION.
IF YOU'RE NOT HAPPY, LEAH,
THAT'S FINE.
I DON'T WANT YOU MISERABLE.
>> I THINK WHERE WE'RE--
>> I'M HAPPY IF YOU'RE HAPPY.
>> I KNOW, BUT I THINK WE'RE
BOTH MAKING OURSELF UNHAPPY,
COREY.
AND I MEAN, IT HURTS,
BUT WE CAN'T JUST STAY TOGETHER
JUST BECAUSE OF THE KIDS.
>> NO, WE CAN'T.
AND I DON'T WANT TO.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS BEFORE
THE KIDS CAME OUT.
AND IS IT GONNA HURT ME?
YEAH, IT'S GONNA SUCK.
'CAUSE I ALREADY KNOW THAT.
I KNOW WE'RE DONE.
I KNOW THIS, AND YOU KNOW IT.
WE'RE NOT HAPPY, AND WE FIGHT
TOO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU AND MY GIRLS
SO [bleep] MUCH, LEAH.
YOU KNOW?
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOU,
'CAUSE I KNOW IF I LOSE YOU,
I AIN'T GONNA SEE MY GIRLS
EVERY DAY WHEN I COME HOME
FROM WORK.
>> YOU WILL, COREY.
>> NOT WHEN I--
>> I'M NOT GONNA KEEP THE KIDS
FROM YOU.
>> NO, IF WE SPLIT UP,
I MEAN, LET'S SAY WE SPLIT UP
RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU CAME TO ME TOMORROW
AND ASKED IF I'D TAKE YOU BACK,
LEAH, I WOULD.
[sniffs]
I LOVE YOU SO [bleep] MUCH.
>> LIKE, I LAY IN BED AT NIGHT,
AND MOST OF THE TIME,
I JUST WANT TO CRY BECAUSE
I'M SO UNHAPPY WITH THE WAY
WE FIGHT, THE WAY WE ARGUE.
IT'S--
>> I DON'T WANT NOBODY
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
AND NOT BEING ABLE TO COME HOME
AND GIVE YOU A KISS AND A HUG
OR SLEEP WITH YOU OR CUDDLE
WITH YOU, YOU KNOW?
BUT IT'S WHATEVER YOU WANT,
LEAH.
>> ME AND COREY JUST GOT IN
A HUGE FIGHT.
>> WE JUST KIND OF ARGUED
ABOUT--HE DOESN'T WANT ME TO
HANG OUT WITH ROBBIE AT ALL,
REALLY.
AND, LIKE, COREY TOLD ME, LIKE,
TONIGHT THAT I COULD JUST, LIKE,
TELL HIM THE TRUTH ABOUT HOW
I FEEL, BUT IT'S SO HARD,
BECAUSE I DON'T--
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO HURT
HIM, AND I DON'T WANT THE GUILT
TO COME BACK ON ME.
AFTER OUR ARGUMENT, ME AND COREY
NEED A BREAK FROM EACH OTHER.
SO I'M STAYING AT MY MOM'S HOUSE
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
[chime dings]
AT SCHOOL TODAY, I TRIED TO TALK
TO ROBBIE ABOUT EVERYTHING,
BUT HE AVOIDED ME ALL AFTERNOON.
I THOUGHT HE WOULD BE HAPPY
TO HEAR I'M ENDING THINGS WITH
COREY, BUT NOW I'M NOT SURE
I KNOW WHAT ROBBIE WANTS EITHER.
AFTER SCHOOL, I SAT DOWN WITH
MY MOM TO TRY TO FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT.
SO ABOUT THE ROBBIE AND COREY
THING, I MEAN, I WAS WITH ROBBIE
FOR THREE YEARS, AND I LOVED HIM
AND THEN JUMPED INTO THINGS WITH
COREY AND GOT PREGNANT.
LIKE, ME AND ROBBIE HADN'T EVEN
BEEN APART THAT LONG.
>> COREY WAS A REBOUND FROM
BREAKING UP WITH ROBBIE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND THEN YOU ENDED UP
PREGNANT.
YOU WEREN'T OVER THE BOY.
>> IT WAS LIKE I WAS
IN THE MIDDLE OF TWO GUYS,
LIKE, ONE GUY I LOVED,
AND ONE GUY I HAD KIDS WITH.
SO I MEAN, I LOVED COREY,
BUT IT WASN'T THE SAME KIND
OF LOVE, I GUESS.
COREY AND I, WE ALWAYS FOUGHT.
LIKE, WE FOUGHT ALL THE TIME.
>> IF THERE WASN'T KIDS,
YOU AND COREY BOTH HAVE SAID
Y'ALL WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> IF YOU DON'T LOVE COREY,
YOU BETTER MAKE UP YOUR MIND,
BECAUSE IF YOU STAY WITH THAT
PERSON AND YOU DON'T LOVE THEM,
SIX MONTHS DOWN THE ROAD,
YOU'RE GONNA BE IN THE SAME
SITUATION THAT YOU'RE IN NOW.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS,
AND ME AND COREY HAVEN'T SEEN
EACH OTHER AT ALL.
BUT EVEN IF WE DO BREAK UP,
WE'VE STILL GOT A LOT OF STUFF
TO WORK OUT.
TWO BABIES IS TWICE THE DIAPERS,
TWICE THE FORMULA,
TWICE THE EVERYTHING.
I'M STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I DON'T HAVE A JOB,
SO COREY NEEDS TO HELP ME
WITH MONEY.
I'VE BEEN KEEPING THE GIRLS
WITH ME, BUT COREY WANTS
TO SEE THEM, SO TONIGHT,
WE'RE MEETING UP.
>> UM, NO.
YOU HAVE TO WORK AT 7:00
IN THE MORNING.
>> I CAN STILL BRING THEM
DOWN THERE.
>> NO.
>> YOUR MOM IS OFF TOMORROW.
>> MM-MM.
EXACTLY, NO.
>> WHAT?
EXACTLY WHAT?
HUH?
WHY?
WE'RE TRYING TO WORK STUFF OUT
FOR OURSELVES SO WE'RE AROUND
THEM ALL THE TIME, BUT IF WE
KEEP THIS UP, WE AIN'T GONNA
NEVER WORK IT OUT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I WISH WE COULD SWAP PLACES.
>> SWAP PLACES?
>> IT'S LIKE I'VE GOT SOME KIND
OF MENTAL PROBLEM.
I CAN'T SEE MY KIDS BY MYSELF.
>> OH, NO.
>> IT'S LIKE I GOT TO HAVE
VISITED--VISITATION.
>> YOU ARE CRAZY.
YOU REALLY ARE CRAZY.
>> I KNOW, I AM.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> YOU DROVE ME TO THAT POINT.
>> I'M SICK OF THIS [bleep].
ALL I WANT IS MY KIDS.
ALL.
>> COREY IS UPSET THAT I WON'T
LET HIM TAKE THE GIRLS.
WHEN I ASKED HIM FOR A LITTLE
EXTRA MONEY, HE BLEW UP.
>> BUT I STILL GOT TO PAY OFF
OUR ELECTRIC BILL, OUR RENT,
OUR--
>> IT'S FOR THE GIRLS.
>> OUR DISH AND TRASH BILL.
>> I CARRIED TWO KIDS FOR
NINE MONTHS STRAIGHT,
LIVED IN HELL, OKAY?
>> I WAS RIGHT THERE WITH YOU.
I WASN'T IN PAIN, BUT BY GOD--
>> YEAH, YOU DIDN'T GO THROUGH
IT EITHER.
>> NO, I CAN'T,
'CAUSE I CAN'T GET PREGNANT.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT NOW
OVER THERE, MISS PUCKER LIPS,
WHAT?
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO WORK
FOR NINE MONTHS STRAIGHT BECAUSE
I WAS PREGNANT.
>> THEN WE SHOULD HAVE
WORKED IT OUT.
>> I WAS ON BED REST.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"WE SHOULD HAVE WORKED IT OUT"?
>> WE SHOULD HAVE WORKED IT OUT
AND STILL BEEN TOGETHER.
>> IT WASN'T A ONE-NIGHT
DECISION.
>> I EXPECT EVERYTHING FROM--
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHAT?
>> [screams]
>> WHAT DID I [bleep] DO?
>> INSANE.
[cries]
>> WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
>> [sobs]
>> AFTER THAT HUGE ARGUMENT
WE HAD, COREY PACKED UP
ALL HIS STUFF AND MOVED OUT
OF THE APARTMENT.
[baby cries]
NOW HE LIVES AT HOME WITH
HIS PARENTS, AND IT'S JUST ME
TAKING CARE OF ALI AND ALEEAH
ALL BY MYSELF.
IT'S HARD THIS MORNING.
>> WHY?
>> JUST HAVING TO DO IT
ON MY OWN NOW, I GUESS.
IT'S JUST--IT'S DIFFERENT FROM
BEING WITH COREY.
I KIND OF LIKED THE COMPANY.
I HAVEN'T BEEN TO SCHOOL
IN A WEEK 'CAUSE I JUST CAN'T
JUGGLE ALL MY WORK ON TOP OF
THE TWINS.
I TALKED TO ROBBIE A COUPLE
TIMES ON THE PHONE, BUT THEN
HE STOPPED RETURNING MY CALLS.
I THINK THE TWINS WERE
TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
I CAN'T BLAME HIM 'CAUSE
SOMETIMES I FEEL LIKE THEY'RE
TOO MUCH FOR ME TOO.
OKAY.
HEY.
>> HEY.
>> MM-HMM.
AFTER EVERYTHING HAPPENED,
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO, LIKE,
STAY HOME.
IT'S BEEN KIND OF LONELY.
>> SO WHAT'S IT LIKE,
TAKING CARE OF TWO OF THEM
BY YOURSELF?
>> HMM, FIRST COUPLE DAYS
THAT WE WAS HERE, I WAS SO SAD,
THOUGH, BECAUSE I THINK
THE GIRLS JUST KNEW THAT I'VE
BEEN UPSET AND EVERYTHING,
AND THEY WOULD NOT STOP
SCREAMING.
I JUST THINK THERE'S BEEN
TOO MUCH HURT WITH EVERYTHING
THAT'S GONE ON.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> LIKE, WITH ME HURTING COREY,
AND WE BOTH HURT EACH OTHER
IN A LOT OF WAYS.
AND THEN I WENT BACK TO ROBBIE.
WELL, ACTUALLY, ROBBIE STARTED
COMING AROUND.
>> WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HE'S BAD NEWS.
>> HE WAS THERE.
I FELT LIKE HE LISTENED TO ME.
I DON'T KNOW.
AND I WANTED TO ESCAPE FROM--
LIKE, I MEAN, I KNOW I CAN'T
ESCAPE FROM THE SITUATION THAT
I'VE GOT MYSELF IN.
>> NO.
>> I THOUGHT ROBBIE WAS A WAY
TO, LIKE, BE ABLE TO GET OUT.
BUT HE'S NOT.
>> I JUST DON'T SEE WHAT'S
SO GREAT ABOUT HIM.
ROBBIE'S JUST NOT DADDY
MATERIAL.
[baby coos]
>> ROBBIE'S TOO IMMATURE TO BE
A GOOD DADDY, BUT THERE AREN'T
TOO MANY GUYS MY AGE WHO COULD
DO ANY BETTER.
COREY'S THE ONLY ONE I CAN
THINK OF, BUT THINGS WITH US
ARE WORSE THAN EVER.
THE ONLY TIME I SEE HIM
IS WHEN I BRING THE GIRLS BY
HIS PARENTS' HOUSE FOR A VISIT.
HEY.
BABY'S ASLEEP.
>> [chuckles lightly]
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW AWKWARD
THINGS ARE NOW.
ME AND COREY CAN BARELY
LOOK EACH OTHER IN THE EYE.
>> SHE IS GETTING BIG.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> SEE YOU.
BYE-BYE, GIRLS.
DADDY LOVES YOU A LOT.
BYE-BYE, BABY GIRL.
I LOVE YOU.
>> COREY'S A REALLY GOOD DAD,
AND SEEING HIM WITH THE GIRLS
MAKES ME WONDER IF I MADE
A BIG MISTAKE.
TO MAKE THINGS WORSE,
TODAY IS VALENTINE'S DAY.
DUDE, IT'S VALENTINE'S.
>> I DON'T LIKE VALENTINE'S DAY.
DO YOU LIKE VALENTINE'S DAY?
>> I DO, BUT I LIKE IT BETTER
WHEN I'M WITH SOMEONE AND
FEELING ALL SPECIAL, LIKE I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE IN THIS WORLD
OR SOMETHING.
YOU CAN'T BE WITH SOMEBODY
A YEAR AND NOT LOVE THEM.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
AND THEN I HAD KIDS WITH COREY,
SO IT'S LIKE REALLY
A DIFFERENT LOVE.
LIKE, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO EXPLAIN IT.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO
LOVE HIM RIGHT NOW?
>> SOMETIMES, YEAH.
LIKE, I CAN'T STAND HIM,
BUT I HATE TO SEE HIM LEAVE,
IF THAT EVEN MAKES SENSE.
>> ME AND LEAH, WE'RE DONE, MAN.
>> I'D SAY.
>> I'M SORRY I CAN'T BE
AS PERFECT AS ROBBIE.
I'M SORRY I ACTUALLY TRIED
TO MAKE IT WORK IN MY LIFE.
I TRIED TO ACHIEVE GOALS AND
MAKE IT BEST FOR MY FAMILY,
BUT YOU DIDN'T WANT NO PART
OF IT, AND NOW YOU'RE REGRETTING
EVERY BIT OF IT.
THAT AIN'T MY PROBLEM.
I DID NOT--I DID NOT
HAVE TO SELL THAT TRUCK.
I DID NOT HAVE TO WORK
TWO JOBS.
I DID NOT HAVE TO MOVE OUT.
I DID NOT HAVE TO BUY HER
EVERYTHING.
I HAD TO DO NONE OF IT,
BUT I DID IT BECAUSE I WANTED IT
TO WORK.
AND WHAT REALLY SUCKS IS,
IS FROM DAY ONE,
I WAS JUST LIKE A REBOUND
TO GET OVER ROBBIE, AND THEN
YOU GOT STUCK WITH ME NOW.
[singing indistinctly]
HEY, YOU WANT TO PULL OVER
AND TALK TO THEM?
>> WHERE THEY AT?
>> OVER THERE.
>> YEAH, GO.
>> [laughs]
HEY, ARE WE STILL HANGING OUT
TONIGHT, THOUGH?
HUH?
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> NOTHING.
ARE WE HANGING OUT LATER?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> I HEARD RUMORS THAT COREY
WAS DATING SOMEONE NEW,
BUT THEY CAN'T BE TRUE.
WE ONLY JUST BROKE UP.
IT SCARED ME, THOUGH,
AND I DON'T WANT TO BE ALONE
TONIGHT, SO MY FRIEND KAYLA
IS KEEPING ME COMPANY.
ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS COREY OUT WITH ANOTHER GIRL
ON VALENTINE'S DAY.
I DIDN'T THINK MY NIGHT
COULD GET ANY WORSE,
BUT ON THE WAY HOME, WE RAN
INTO SOME OF COREY'S FRIENDS.
>> YOU HAVE THE BABIES.
I WANT TO SEE THEM.
>> LOOK.
I'M GOING HOME TO TAKE CARE
OF BABIES.
I WAS SCARED COREY WAS GONNA
BE UP HERE.
ARE YOU [bleep] ME?
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH, YOU MISSED HIM BY,
LIKE...
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> THAT PISSES ME OFF.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL,
I'M GOING HOME.
IT'S ALL RIGHT,
BUT I'M GOING HOME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JUST [bleep] LEAVE ME.
YOU BITCHED AT ME FOR IT.
>> SORRY, I'M GOING HOME.
>> ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME A HOLLER.
>> DO YOU SEE HIM?
>> ARE THEY SITTING IN THERE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I SEE PAIGE AND ASHLEY,
BUT I DON'T SEE COREY.
>> THAT'S HIS CAR.
>> YEAH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[sniffles]
THIS AIN'T COOL.
THIS IS NOT COOL AT ALL.
I'M SORRY, BUT I'M GOING HOME.
I'M GOING HOME TO SIT--
AND YOU KNOW, TO TAKE CARE
OF KIDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT, I BLAME THAT
[bleep] ON MYSELF.
YOU KNOW?
I HATE MY LIFE.
I REALLY DO.
[sniffles]
JUST KIND OF HURTS,
REALLY BAD.
THIS IS THE WORST VALENTINE'S
DAY EVER.
>> VALENTINE'S DAY WAS THE WORST
DAY OF MY LIFE.
SEEING COREY WITH ANOTHER GIRL
REALLY HURT ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S MOVED ON.
>> YOU'RE REALLY HURT HIM, BAD.
HE DIDN'T DESERVE IT.
>> NO, I KNOW.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> I REALLY DO FEEL LIKE,
YOU KNOW, ME LOSING COREY AND
HIM BEING SO SERIOUS ABOUT IT,
ALL OF A SUDDEN HAS MADE ME
REALIZE, YOU KNOW, YOU NEVER
KNOW WHAT YOU HAVE UNTIL
IT'S GONE.
>> DEFINITELY.
>> AND YOU NEVER REALIZE HOW
MUCH YOU CARE ABOUT SOMEBODY
OR WANT THEM AROUND YOU ALL
THE TIME UNTIL IT'S NOT THERE.
I THINK THINGS ARE REALLY OVER
WITH COREY, AND I BLAME MYSELF
FOR RUINING OUR FAMILY.
I USED TO BE THIS HAPPY,
OUTGOING PERSON.
I MEAN, I WAS A CHEERLEADER,
OF COURSE.
ALWAYS, I WAS, LIKE, ALL PEPPY.
AND I MEAN, SOME PEOPLE STILL
ARE LIKE THAT AFTER HAVING KIDS,
AND I'M NOT LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
I JUST FEEL LIKE MY LIFE'S BEEN,
LIKE, SUCKED RIGHT OUT OF ME.
AT MY AGE, GIRLS ARE, LIKE,
DATING, AND THEY CAN DATE
SOMEBODY AND BE LIKE,
"ER, IT'S JUST NOT THERE."
AND I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> YOU CAN'T THINK AS
A 17-YEAR-OLD NO MORE.
YOU'RE NOT YOUR AVERAGE
17-YEAR-OLD GIRL NOW.
>> YES, I KNOW.
MM.
[sighs]
I JUST WANT TO COME BACK HOME
AND LAY IN THE BED AND BE ALL
OKAY AGAIN.
>> SHE WANTS TO STAY HERE,
SNUGGLE IT UP WITH MOMMY.
[laughs]
IT WOULD BE NICE TO STAY CUDDLED
UP HERE AND EVERYTHING--
SEEM LIKE EVERYTHING WOULD BE
OKAY, BUT IT'S NOT.
>> * NOW THE END
* IS DRAWING NEAR
[piano music]
*
* I CAN'T BELIEVE
* IT'S FINALLY HERE
* TAKE SOME TIME
* TO PRAY FOR ME
* FOR WHAT WILL BE
* I DON'T KNOW HOW
* I MADE IT TILL NOW
* LET THERE BE LIGHT
>> GETTING PREGNANT AT
A YOUNG AGE WAS HARD.
[baby cries]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HUH?
I MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES.
I WISH I COULD TAKE EVERY
BIT OF IT BACK, BUT I CAN'T.
ME AND COREY, OUR RELATIONSHIP
IS NOT THE SAME ANYMORE.
WE'RE NOT ON GOOD TERMS.
I'VE DONE HIM WRONG.
AND NOW HE JUST DOESN'T WANT
TO BE WITH ME.
IT'S REALLY HARD HAVING
TWO BABIES AT THE SAME TIME
AND ESPECIALLY NOT HAVING COREY
AROUND.
WE CAN'T DO IT TOGETHER.
I'M DOING IT ON MY OWN.
[baby crying]
[shushes]
THE WHOLE ROBBIE THING WAS
A WAY FOR ME TO ESCAPE FROM
EVERYTHING THAT WAS GOING ON,
THE PRESSURE OF HAVING
TWO BABIES.
I WAS TRYING TO BE A NORMAL
17-YEAR-OLD AGAIN,
AND THAT'S KIND OF IMPOSSIBLE.
NOW ME AND COREY IS NOT
TOGETHER, AND MY KIDS DON'T HAVE
A FAMILY LIKE THEY SHOULD HAVE.
I CAN'T TAKE BACK THE HURT
THAT I'VE DONE.
BUT I WOULD DO ANYTHING TO JUST
TAKE IT BACK AND CHANGE THINGS.
AND I'LL LIVE WITH THIS REGRET
PROBABLY FOR THE REST OF MY
LIFE, AND IT JUST SCARES ME.
>> * LET THERE BE MORNING
* I DON'T KNOW HOW
* I MADE IT TILL NOW
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> I'M NOT GONNA LET JUST
HAVING A BABY STOP ME FROM
DOING WHAT I LOVE.
>> PERSONALLY, I WOULDN'T
WANT TO BE PREGNANT.
>> WILL YOU MARRY ME?
>> I HAVE, LIKE, THE PERFECT
BOYFRIEND AND THE PERFECT RING,
AND I'M EXCITED ABOUT HAVING
A PERFECT BABY.
>> I'M IN NO HURRY FOR YOU GUYS
TO GET MARRIED.
>> DO WE HAVE ANY MORE NEWBORN
DIAPERS IN THE CLOSET?
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THOSE PACKS
I JUST BOUGHT?
>> THEY'RE GONE.
>> DO YOU THINK SKYLAR WOULD
CHEAT ON YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I MADE A MISTAKE A WHILE AGO.
>> THAT JUST MAKES ME LOOK
STUPID.
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR RING BACK.
[upbeat piano music]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
* GET THROUGH IT ALL
* I'M WEAK, BUT I'M
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE
* WHEN IT'S ALL DONE...