It was a season
full of complications
in life and in labor.
Complicated love,
complicated fights,
and complicated breakups.
We saw premature deliveries,
immature relationships,
and enough tension
to last a lifetime.
But at its core, this is
a season about ten girls
who each became teen mothers
over the course of nine months.
And today, they come together
for the very first time
to face one another
and to face tough questions.
This is the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special,
"Life After Labor."
♪♪
[applause]
Well, I'd like to welcome
our home viewers,
our studio audience here today,
and of course our
ten young moms,
Valerie, Lori, Nikkole,
Leah, Chelsea, Lizzie,
Nicole, Samantha, Kailyn,
and Jenelle.
Now, amongst them there was
talk of abortion and adoption.
There were emergency C-sections
and frightening
false alarm surgeries,
close calls, bed rest,
you name it--
we saw it all this season.
And, as viewers,
we went through it also.
So here's a quick look back
at Season 2
of "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
You're pregnant.No, I know I'm pregnant.
But I'm saying I don't
actually look like I'm pregnant.
A friend to a friend,
you look like it.
You're gonna be a mom now.
You're responsible for somebody.
It's not my hamster.
Not your hamster.
When did you find out
you were pregnant?
Just took tests?Took seven.
You weren't sure
the first three worked?
I don't appreciate
you having sex...
Mom!...whether she's
knocked up or not.
Nothing else worse
can happen, Mom.
You're 17 years old,
and you're pregnant.
And I just don't see
anything to celebrate.
It's just like,
"Honey, you're having twins."
I was like...
I might even have
to get a DNA test.
We had sex a lot,
and it was unprotected.
You know it's your baby.
I made a mistake.
You can have
your ring back.
I'm putting him
up for adoption.
I don't wanna lose you,
'cause I know if lose you
I ain't gonna see my girls
everyday when I come home
from work.
She's in labor,
so you shut your mouth
and you act like
a grown person.All right then!
[indistinct]
Give me my son, so I
can say good-bye, please.
You don't wanna raise a baby,
then you're gonna put it
up for adoption.
Get the [bleep]
out of my face!
Boy, that stuff
is so emotional.
And, Leah, you have twins.
Mm-hmm.Two babies.
Yeah.How they doing,
Aaliyah and Aliana?
Yeah, they're
doing really good.
They're doing great.
They're getting so big.
Valerie, Nevaeh's health
was touch and go
for a while there--
how's she doing?
Um, she had
meconium aspirations.
She inhaled her... poop.Poop.
Sometimes during delivery,
the child is stressed,
and there's a lot of fluid
flying around.
And some of the fluid gets
into the child's lungs,
and that's mixed with poop,
sometimes, and it's actually
really serious pneumonia
that they develop.Mm-hmm.
Nikkole, Brooklyn was
nine pounds, six ounces.
Ouch.[laughter]
How would you
describe your labor?
The contractions
were horrible.
Horrible. How long
were you in labor for?
Like 14 hours.Ooh!
Did anybody else do
more than 14 hours?
You did more than
14 hours?
Oh, my goodness.
All right, well, one issue
that's sure to come up today
is the prevention of pregnancy,
so to learn
more about prevention,
I want you all to head over--
in fact, I'm assigning you
to head over to
16andPregnant.mtv.com.
We're gonna chat with all ten
of these teen mothers,
and some of their main
supporters as well.
Together, we're gonna get
to the bottom of this season's
most burning issues.
We'll talk to Cory about being
caught between Leah
and her ex-boyfriend Robbie.
We're gonna ask Lori's mom
about some of the pressure
she put on her daughter when
the adoption was on the table.
We're gonna have Nikkole's
ex-boyfriend Josh
and her mother Rikki
on the same stage
to settle the fight which
began back when Nikkole
was in labor.
Plus, which of the ten couples
is now engaged?
After this break, we'll kick
things off with Jenelle.
[applause]
She really doesn't
tell me she loves me.
[crying]
I tell you all the time
I love you, Jenelle.
And I tell you I want you
to do the right thing.
You've had a tough life.
Is he a supportive father.
Mm-hmm.
He's a great father.
Once I got your daughter
pregnant, you totally--
Once you wanted her
to have an abortion?
Once you said you were gonna
punch her in the stomach?
I never said I was gonna
punch her in the stomach.
The list goes
on and on, Josh.
It's just a bunch of hate.
And they can get along,
they just don't wanna try.
He was the first guy
I fell in love with,
and I got pregnant by him.
[Drew]
Does she need to
just get over you?
I would say yes.
[Drew]
How's your guys'
relationship now?
It's great, I'm ready
to take it to the next level.
I want her to be my girl.
I got this for you, baby.
[audience gasping]
[applause]
Welcome back
to "Life After Labor,"
the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special.
I am Dr. Drew.
Now, sadly, it's a fact
that sons born to teen mothers
are more likely
to be incarcerated.
And for teen mom Jenelle,
her baby's father Andrew
had been in and out of jail.
Jenelle, how do you
feel hearing that fact?
You know, we have
a horrible past,
and I don't even want
Jace involved in that
at all.
Like, I don't want him
involved in Andrew's life.
I totally agree.
Well, let's take a look
back at Jenelle's life,
being "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
And you know what's
so great about me?
I feel like I'm gonna
be a good mom.
All the expense has been
on my shoulders.
What, do you have to be
a [bleep] millionaire
just to [bleep] calm down
and make her [bleep]
be happy?
I mean, there's no jobs.
That's the only thing.
The economy sucks right now
from depression.
How's he supposed
to support that baby
with no job?
♪♪
Hey, bud!
You add the wage--
I know, but,
Mom, right now,
all I need is support
from both of you guys.
He'll be long gone
very shortly.
It's basically over. Bye.  Really?
You've gone out
every night this week.
Can you shut up and listen?
Do you really think
I would take off
in the middle of the night
and leave him in the bed?
Yeah.Everybody's saying,
"Oh, well, she's
a [bleep] mom."
They wanna be held all the time,
they're clingy.
Imagine being in prison.
That's what it's like.
Being in prison.
Do the right thing
for this baby.
You know, when push
comes to shove,
you know, Jenelle,
it's all about family.
[sniffles]
That's what it is.
When you started motherhood,
you sort of described it
like something--
I almost imagined you
were playing house.
How different is it?
It's very different.
Like... you know,
I just thought of, you know,
when he was older
and like running around
and playing on the playground
and stuff, but...
I didn't look at the part
where you have to wake up
every two hours
when they're born.
And you have to feed 'em
and change their diaper
when you're sitting
there exhausted,
and no teenager wants
to get up in the middle
of the night.
There's been a lot of tension
between you and mom.
Oh, yes.Oh, yeah.
Me and my mom always argue.
Like, she... cusses at me
I cuss at her.
It's-- it's like
a daily thing, every day.
And we've been going
to counseling a lot, though.
Is that helping?Yeah, that's helping a lot.
Well, let's bring
your mom out here.
Barbara, come on in.
[applause]Welcome, Barbara.
Hello.
So... are you still
the primary caretaker,
or has some of that
shifted back to Jenelle?
Well, Jenelle's doing
a little better,
but I work 40 hours,
I bring the baby to daycare,
and when I walk in the door,
she leaves.
No-- Mom--And then she comes back
about 9 at night,
8 or 9, and he's
already in bed.
No, I take care of him
while you're at work.
True?
[Jenelle]
It is true.
It's not true.Yes, it is!
It's not true!
It's not true.Okay.
Uh, a lot of times
I ask Jenelle to watch him
while I'm getting
ready for work,
and she gets very mad
and says, "I'm tired.
I have to sleep."
Barbara,
she said it herself.
17-year-old imprisoned
by parenthood.
Well, I understand
that Jenelle is 17.
But I just wish she'd
kind of step up more.
Jenelle, you told your mom
when you turned 18
you were gonna go away
and never see her again.
You still feel that way?
No, we've been
getting along
a lot better.
But we still argue,
but we don't argue
as bad.
Is there something
you want to tell
your mom
about the fact
that she's the one
that hung out
and stuck with you?
Yeah. Um, I know
you've been the one
that's been helping me.
And I really appreciate
that you've been helping me.
Well, thank you.You're welcome.
[chuckling]
[Drew]
It feel good
to hear that?
It does.
Do you ever give her
positive strokes?
I do give her
positive strokes
when there's positive
things to say.
But when she's on--
Well, she says no.
You don't get to hear
any positive from her?
Even when someone
asked her one day, they said,
"Name three things good
about Jenelle.
"Name three things
that she's accomplished
and that you're
proud of her for."
Then she just sat there
and she just leaned back
and she was like,
"Well... I don't know."
She was like,
"I have no idea."
Can we try now?
I always tell her
she's very smart.
She's smart.Highly intelligent.
Pretty.Beautiful.
And?
And she can be
very ambitious.
And I love her deeply.
Do you tell her that?Mm-hmm.
Do you hear her when
she tells you that?
Mm-mmm.How come?
She... heh heh.
She really never
tells me that.
[crying]
I do, I tell you
all the time
I love you, Jenelle.
And I tell you I want you
to do the right thing.
And you don't want
to listen to me.
You do close her out.
You do.
Well, she really doesn't
tell me she loves me.
I heard her say it.
Well, I mean, not--
I mean, right now
she said it,
but not like
when we're at home.
She never does.
There's some heavy stuff
going on in your house.
I worry about her.
[sniffles]
You know, she's always
doing the wrong thing.
And I'm trying my hardest
to get her straightened out,
and she just totally, uh,
disrespects me and doesn't
listen to anything I say.
Keep at it.
I know want you want.
You want what's best for her.
For her and the baby.And the baby.
Of course.
You are so lucky
to have your mom.
Mm-hmm.
And I know I am.
I believe you're
gonna get through this.
I know we will.
All right, you guys,
thank you for being
here today.
Let's take a quick break,
and we will return with Kailyn.
She and her boyfriend Joe,
well, they fought a lot, too,
so where does their relationship
stand today?
That answer may surprise you.
So don't go away.
[applause]
♪♪
We're back,
I'm Dr. Drew, and this is
the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special.
And today we're chatting
with all the teen moms
from this season
of "16 and Pregnant."
Our next mom is Kailyn.
Here's a quick recap
of her story.
♪♪
I'm not ready to tell
anybody yet.
I wouldn't even know
how to tell anybody.
"Hi, I'm pregnant."
I think things will
get worse before
they get better.
Things are not gonna get worse.
They can't get worse.
[Kailyn]
We're like not even
talking right now.
See? This is what he does.
He shuts me out.
She's the mother
of your child.
You're gonna have to
live with it
for the rest of your life.
[father]
18 years, plus college.
My dad found me
on Facebook.
You want a father-daughter
relationship, that's fine.
Don't expect
anything from him.
Hello.
You think you'll be around
more often now?
I don't want you here.
[screaming and sobbing]
You're doing it.
Oh...
[overlapping chatter]
[baby crying]
You left the milk out again.
It's [bleep] milk.
Just shut the [bleep] up.
No, it wasn't.Stop thinking about it.
[overlapping arguing]
That wasn't necessary,
though!
♪♪
[applause]
I'm joined right now by Kailyn
and her boyfriend Joe.
How are things
going right now?
We recently got engaged.
You got engaged?
Congratulations.[applause]
How did you from all that
conflict to engaged?
What-- what happened?
Once Isaac was born,
things changed.
So it made him commit
more completely to
this relationship?
Mm-hmm.
Your mom, Joe,
is very instrumental
in Kayla's life
and in your
relationship.
Did she help cultivate
the relationship,
bring it back around?
I think she made
too much sometimes.
I think she needs
to just stay out of it.
I just think Janet
helped us through
everything in our relationship,
and if it wasn't for her,
we wouldn't have made it
this far.
So I think she had a right
to get in our business.
You've had a tough life.
[tearful chuckle]
What have you had
to sacrifice, being a mom?
Um, my relationship
with my mom.
With your mom?
Is that over with now?
You don't communicate?
That was already
pretty rocky, thought,
wasn't it?
She doesn't want to
participate with Isaac?
Mm-mm.Oh, boy.
I don't think it's Isaac.
I think it's more
of her and I.
We never really got along,
and now,
since I moved out of her place
and I'm with Joe...
she doesn't have an interest
in continuing our relationship
or taking part in our lives.
It's very painful,
right?
Mm-hmm.
That's why I always nag him
and I don't want him to leave,
because everyone just leaves.
That's why we talked
about Joe's mom.
It's so emotional
'cause she does not leave.
Mm-mm.She hangs in.
The way you're gonna
do with Isaac.
Mm-hmm.
You change that cycle,
can't you?
I think I already started.
I think you
got a pretty good
partner there.
I hope he sticks around.
[chuckling]
I won't be going anywhere
anytime soon.
I feel like
I don't express how much
I appreciate him sometimes.
You wanna tell him
how you appreciate him?
[chuckling]
I do appreciate
everything you do you.
I know.
Do you get a sense
of how much she sacrifices
to be a teen mom?
Yeah.You get it?
We both do.You both do.
We're in it together.
It's not just our...
Not just me.
It's my family.
Starting my own family.
Feels good to hear
that, doesn't it?
Mm-hmm.
Does he help enough
with the baby?
He's really good
with Isaac.
And even though he goes to work
from 5 a.m. to 7 p.m.
he still comes home at night
to help me.
I saw the part in the episode
where you went down
to visit your dad.
Mm-hmm.
What did you expect
to get from that?
What was your fantasy?
I thought that I would
gain a good relationship,
where we can call every day,
and I can go to him
to talk about things.
Turned out to be a fantasy.Mm-hmm.
He didn't want to meet me.
His sister was the reason.
Like, she was pushing him
to do it.
You do not deserve that.
Isaac's mom
doesn't deserve that.
And you're so lucky
to have Joe and Joe's
mom in your life.
I know.That's what
you deserve.
Mm-hmm.
How is Isaac doing?
He's doing really well.
We get to see him today?Yeah.
Oh, boy,
do you light up when
you talk about him.
Yeah, I love him.That's good.
Thank you guys
for joining us.
We're gonna move on
to our next mom, Samantha.
Here's what she went through
on "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
That's not how 14-year-olds
should act.
You should be worried
about your school,
not having sex.
I don't really want you
to go and move in with him
because what's gonna happen
is you're gonna get
pregnant again.
His mom said she'd
watch the baby during
the day and stuff.
I wouldn't be going
over there.
Mine and her relationship
isn't close to being okay.
I have to tell you that
I do apologize for
taking him to see her.
You know, what happened
before, it's in the past.
[screaming]
We are gonna go ahead
and do a C-section, okay?
[screaming]
[baby crying]
Congratulations, Samantha.
There's a lot to worry about,
and you don't like
to think about that.
I'll work on it.
Daddy had to go to school.
Then he went to work,
and now he's tired.
Let's nap.
[Samantha]
You and dad telling me
not to have sex and stuff,
I mean, y'all
were right about that.
I wasn't ready.
♪♪
[applause]
I am joined by
Samantha and Eric.
Hey, guys, how are you?
[both]
Hi.
I'll tell you what,
Samantha,
one of the things
about your story
is the cycle
of teen
pregnancy we see here
in your family system.
Your mom got pregnant when
she was a teenager, right?
Yes.
And in spite of them
really trying to do
some parenting with you,
and they were trying
to break the cycle,
here we are.Yeah.
Do you have
a different plan?
I'm gonna be
a little strict on her
and have rules for her.
So she's gonna
go out and have sex.
No! Heh.How do you figure?
I'm gonna talk
to her a lot.
Your mom talked
to you a lot, too.
Yeah, and birth control,
too, because...
teenagers have sex.
Are you gonna try to get
your daughter to delay?
I'm gonna try to,
and just talk to her,
[crying]
because it's not easy.
It's not easy being
a teen mom, right?
No. Maybe that's what
you gotta tell her.
Yeah.
Is there something
you wanna tell people
out there
about being a teen mom?
It's not at all
what I expected.
I mean, I knew it
was gonna be hard,
but it's so much harder
than what I pictured it to be.
And get through it,
all you need to do is school,
get a job, get a house,
and then think about kids.
You all right?I'm fine.
[giggles]
And it's just hard.
It is hard,
I know.
'Cause I really don't want her
to go through the same thing.
Eric, you guys,
did you contraception?
At all?
A little bit.
From time to time.A little bit?!
There are lots of options
for birth control out there.
Condom, of course, but not
only just for birth control,
but also to protect
against STDs and STIs, right?
How are your moms
getting along?
[giggles]
They actually--
They're not fighting.
Yeah, they're not fighting.They're not fighting.
But they haven't actually
seen each other face-to-face
since I was in the hospital.Since that restaurant?
Oh, since you were
in the hospital?
Yeah.
Where you guys live now?
Right now I'm staying
with Eric at his house.
How's your mom
feel about it?
My mom,
she's okay with it,
but I think it makes her feel
a little sad sometimes,
just 'cause I'm not
there with her.
Does she come visit you
at Eric's house?
No, but I go visit her.Mm.
Yeah, I see her like
almost every day.
So Jordan has a relationship
with both grandmas?
Mm-hmm.Okay.
Well, guys, Samantha, Eric,
thank you for joining us.
We're gonna take a break,
and when we return we'll explore
the busy, busy life of Leah.
She has two babies, twins,
making her life chaotic,
and two men making it
complicated.
So don't go away.
[applause]
♪♪
Welcome back to
"Life After Labor."
I'm Dr. Drew.
Now, clearly,
being 16 and pregnant,
it's far from easy, right?
But if you wanna
make things harder,
just add twins.
Leah, Leah, Leah.
Wow.
I'm a father of triplets.
Um, I'm telling you,
my heart goes out.
It's double everything.
Oh, my goodness.
How old are they now?
They're 12 weeks.
Oh, yeah, that first
six months is just so--
My hair turned gray
first six months of
my triplets.
I'm not kidding.I hope mine doesn't.
You took a leave
of absence from school.
Is it realistic to take
a brief leave as a teen mom?
No, it's not.
I had schoolwork I had to do.
I had to take care of not just
one baby but two babies.
I didn't sleep
through the night at all.
It was a baby crying at all
times pretty much.
And then trying to wake up
at 6:00 in the morning
and get ready.
It was... no, it's
not realistic at all.
Really tough.Mm-hmm.
All right.
This journey has been
filled with tough moments
and even tougher decisions
for Leah.
Here's what she went through
being "16 and Pregnant."
Woman looks at me
and she's like, "Honey,
you're having twins."
I was like, "Oh, my God."
I can imagine what a challenge
one baby would be.
But two, I can't imagine.
I think I'm leakin'.
You want me
to call your doctor?
I'm scared, 'cause I don't
know what it is.
♪♪
[baby crying]
I was up until 3:00.
Finally, I was like,
hopefully she just
grunts around
a little bit
and then goes to sleep.
How long was we together
before we got pregnant?
Not very long at all,
but does that matter?It was a month.
Does it matter?
Was I in love?
No, I wasn't.
Nor was I.
No, I wasn't either.Okay.
I have "I love Robbie"
written all over this
freakin' book.
I wanna go back
to these days.
[laughter]
Shut up, Robbie.
Shut up.
What did you think
when I got pregnant.
I thought you made
a dumb decision.
Jealousy is gonna
split us up, that's
exactly what it's gonna do.
If you don't love Corey,
or you don't love Robby,
you better make up your mind.
I know we're done.
I don't wanna lose you,
'cause if I lose you,
I ain't gonna see my girls
every day when
I come home from work.
♪♪
[applause]
It's tough seeing that,
isn't it?
It's hard being
a teen mom.
What part
affects you the most?
I don't know, like the whole--
everything does.
Is there any other experience
in life that is as stressful
as that?
I don't think that there is.
Especially being so young,
and having to deal with...
you know, school,
and trying to graduate.
And trying to keep
your family together.
It's hard.
As it pertains to keep your
family together...Mm-hmm.
Do you mean Corey?Mm-hmm.
You guys only dated a month
before you got pregnant.
Right.Where do you guys stand now?
[clears throat]
I really don't know.
Is he a supportive father?Mm-hmm.
[sniffles]
He's a great father.
Why don't we bring
him out? Okay?
Corey, come on out.
[applause]
Leah, she has
mentioned keeping
her family together,
and she said
that meant you.
Yeah. I mean,
the whole Robbie thing.
I mean, that really--
That's her ex-boyfriend.Yeah.
It happened more than once,
and every time I took her back.
And I was giving it my all.
I was trying to raise
my family the best I could.
So, you're kind of
like Jenelle,
running away
to the parties.
[giggling]
No, I never partied.
But you ran away
to Robbie.
Yeah. Yeah.
Do you regret it?
With everything?
Have you apologized
to Corey?
Mm-hmm.
You don't accept
the apology?
Yeah, I accept it, but...
it's just hard to give my--
everything out there again,
just for her to shut it down.
So you don't trust her.
No, no trust at all.
I'm just wondering
if there's something
you could say to Corey...
that would help him
understand or trust again?
When I was with you...
it was different.
Everything was different.
And I got really scared
of everything.
I-- I never felt someone
that loved me as much
as you loved me.
And it scared me,
and the only thing I knew
to even do was run.
And things that I've done,
it was not acceptable at all.
And, I mean, I want
your forgiveness,
but I mean, I completely
understand if you never
forgave me again.
[Drew]Corey.
It's hard, I mean...
To just go off
and just drop everything,
like it's never happened.
Do you know the outcome
on multiple parents
is not good under the best
of circumstances.
The marriages split up
'cause of the stress
that you're talking about.
All right, we have
a question from the audience.
Britney has question.
Um, I was wondering if you guys
were going to try to work it out
and get back together.
Um... I would love to,
but it's really up to Cory.
I mean, we've
been doing better
ever since I've got over
the fact that it's happened.
I mean, I have let the--
that go.
I mean, I'm starting to
get that feeling back
like we had when
we first was together.
But, I mean, I don't want my
kids to have like a split up
Christmas and Thanksgiving,
all that stuff.
I don't want that.
I want them with me and Leah,
I want the Mommy and Daddy,
come down the little stairs,
let's get their presents.
That's what I want.[laughter]
I gotta get the trust back
before I can take
another step...
towards that.
Any chance you will
trust her, Corey?
Yeah.The trust takes
a long time.
Yeah.She has to earn that.
Leah, how do you see
the next year going?
I want to be with Corey
and I want my family together.
In our own place,
like we was.
Got a couple million people
hoping this works out.
[laughter]
All right, guys.
Leah, Corey,
thank you
for joining us.
Before we move on I want to
reiterate the fact
that teen pregnancy
is 100% preventable.
So to learn more log onto
itsyoursexlife.org.
Time for a break,
and we'll return with Chelsea.
[applause]
♪♪
And we're back here
at the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special.
I'm Dr. Drew, joined by
another one of our teen moms.
This now is Chelsea
and her dad Randy.
Chelsea had some very, very
difficult moments this season.
Let's take a look back
at what she went through
on "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
[chanting indistinctly]
The doctor, like,
as he was telling me
that I was for sure pregnant,
Adam was texting me,
like, breaking up with me.
And saying I should
get an abortion and stuff.
That last thing he was looking
for is more responsibility.
He's just like said
so many like mean things.
I want it to work.
Like, I really like him.
[shrieking]
It is the first night home!
Ooh...
So?
What do you want?
You to stop being annoying.
♪♪
He said, "Tell me where and
when to sign the papers over
for that mistake."How does that make you feel?
It makes me feel way worse
than when he tells me anything.
I think we need
to change her last name.
He's done nothing to deserve
to have his name carry on.
Are we here today to
talk about a name change?
Yes. I'm just trying
to figure out
what the right thing
to do is for me and my daughter.
[applause]
I gotta tell ya, Chelsea,
your story was really
one of the more heartbreaking,
to see you go through
so much abuse.
It was hard to watch.
It was weird, like, watching
myself in those situations.
Like going back
to those times.Yeah.
And like when I would
watch it back I was like,
I was being so stupid.
Adam was horrible to you.
He was emotionally abusive.
So you broke it off.
No. We got
back together,
and broke up quite
a few times after that.
Okay.But now I have
a kid with him,
and I'm stuck with him
for the rest of my life.
What do you see him
doing, Randy?
Nothing.
Does he have any relationship
the child that you can tell?
Uh... minimal.
Um, at his parents' request,
I mean, they
want to see her,
his parents do.
Mm-hmm.They're good.
And they-- they adore her.
Um, but when Aubrey's
with them...
he's not a part.
He'll be gone, and they'll
be taking care of her.
Mm-hmm.
What's the status
of the relationship now?
With you and him.
We barely talk.
You pissed now?
Yeah. Now I'm pissed.
After all those times crying
because of what he did,
and bawling
and calling me and...
You know, it's--
I been watching this
two-year-long train wreck.
You can't fix her any more
than she can fix him.
No. You steer, but doesn't
change the direction.
We all watched you receive
that text from him
about changing the name
on what he called
his "mistake."
That's just devastating.
Well, that wasn't
like the worst--
That phone call to me,
wanting me to come home
because of whatever
happened, uh,
that was just one of many.
[crying]
Thank you.
That was all the time.
You're telling me that
you're done with him?
Mm-hmm.For sure?
Mm-hmm.
What do you
think, Randy?
I've heard it a lot of times.Yeah.
And this time,
I believe it.
She saw something
on the show
where she was
watching what we saw
from a third-person view,
and she was always
on the inside
and couldn't see it,
and she saw it now.
It got through.
Are you fearful she's
gonna drift back?
No, not this time.No.
No way.
She'll have a few million
people mad at her.
Amongst her family.
Your dad is very present
and supportive
and obviously a great guy.
Aubrey may not have
that hello it's me.
I know.
And that hurts me a lot.
I think about that
all the time.
'Cause I want her to.
I know I'm gonna
to cry again.
Do you think Grandpa
could serve a function
for Aubrey?
Till the right guy steps up.Yeah.
Have you left school?
I'm still going to school.
I go to an alternative
school.
Are you able to keep up
the way you want to?
I'm behind.
I want her
to get a diploma.
But she'll have to hustle.
And it takes work
to go to finish high school.
[Drew]And?
Don't go looking for a man.
It's the worst thing
you can do.
Are you looking for a man?
I wouldn't mind one.
[laughter]
But I'm not like searching.
Well, Chelsea, Randy,
thank you for being
here today.
Right now,
it's time for break,
and we will
bring out next Nikkole.
Her mom and boyfriend fought
over who was really
number one in her life.
Well, they're both here today.
Who is number one?
We're gonna ask Nikkole
right after the break.
[applause]
♪♪
We are back with more
"Life After Labor."
This is the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special
hosted by myself, Dr. Drew.
Let's move on
to our next mom,
who had to put up with a ton
of let's call unnecessary drama.
Here is the Nikkole's journey
on "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
I'm gonna hold your hand
and I'm gonna to walk you
through this.
I just want you to know
that I still love you.
I love you, too.
I'll be in the parking lot.
No, you won't.Yes, I will.
You told me you were
gonna be there at 9:00.
To hang out with me.
Josh, whatever.
I'm just gonna go home.
Do you wanna
be with him?Yeah.
He breaks up with you
to cheat on you.
I'm trying to share
space here, Josh.
I'm trying
to share the space.
[mother]
I'm telling you what she needs.
It may be your baby,
but this is my daughter.
I trump you.You don't trump
anything.
I trump you.You guys, stop.
You wanna tell her--
say she Trumps me, Nikkole.
I wanna hear it.She doesn't.
Come on, you can do it.
Oh, my God.
[man]
Here's your baby.
Last week, Becca called me
and told me that Josh
is hanging out with Kyla.
What-- I'm like, what
would you do if you
found out
that your boyfriend
was cheating on you?
I'm just not ready to,
like, totally commit
myself to you.
It's just not fair to me.
I'm not gonna
be here forever.
All right, then.
And I'm over it.
♪♪
[applause]
Nikkole, did you think
that the pregnancy was gonna
somehow improve your
relationship with Josh?
Mm, yeah.
I was hoping it would.
I mean, I think lots
of girls think that way.
That if we have a baby
together, somehow
he'll stay with me?
Yeah, like we'll be
bonded together.
Does it work out
like that?
[giggling]
No.
Nikkole, when I see Josh
on TV behaving
the way he does,
I swear I hear 2 million viewers
screaming at their televisions.
Yeah.
How do you feel when you
see the way he behaves?
It's sad, 'cause
it's not fair to me.
That he
treated me that way.
Does he continue
to treat you that way?
Mm-hmm.
I can see the sadness
in your face.
[crying]
Do you deserve to be
treated like that?
No.
How's he treating you
these days?
He just doesn't care,
and every time we do
try and work things out,
he always messes it up again
by talking to other girls.
And then how do you guys
get along when he's there?
I mean, we get along okay
most of the time.
How about the relationship
with your mom,
or between mom and Josh?
Um, they still
hate each other.
Do you feel torn,
stuck in the middle?
Yeah, all the time.
Let's hear what they think.
Let's bring out Josh
and your mom Rikki.
Come on, guys.
[applause]
Josh, Rikki,
thanks for joining us.
So, Josh when you watch
the footage of how you behaved
in the labor delivery room,
do you have any thoughts
about that?
There was a lot going on
at that point in my life.
Um, and like the pregnancy
just like pushed me
over the edge.
And instead of facing it
like a man,
I kind of took
the coward way out.
Which was?Like treating Nikkole
like [bleep].
Do you treat her
better now?
I try.
It's still really hard.
[Drew]Rikki?
I believe that Josh
uses Nikkole.
And I don't think
she sees that.
[Drew]
For what?
Um, for a ride,
for money,
for... different things.
Just various things
that he needs,
probably one being sex,
when he's not with
the other girl.
And it hurts me
that I feel that way.
We don't even have sex.
Do you believe that?No.
Do you understand how much
she has sacrificed
to raise Lyle?
She sacrificed a lot.
Have you sacrificed
much for Lyle?
No, not really.
[Drew]No.
What's best for the baby?
For us to sort things out
and to be together,
but there's more and more
obstacles every day.
Rikki, what are we
gonna do with him?
Uh, I think she should
dump him and be done with it.
I have no contact
with him.
And your point?
You shouldn't.
You should be done with it.He's the father of my child.
I get that.
How is this environment
gonna affect Lyle,
do you figure, Nikkole?
It's not good for him.
It's just a bunch of hate.
And they can get along,
they just don't wanna try.
I plan on getting along
for the baby's sake with him
and his family,
but I definitely don't want him
in my daughter's life no more.
[Josh]
No.
Audience, do you guys
have any questions?
I heard a lot of,
"Uh-huh, uh-huh."
There's some hands up
in the audience.
Um, this is for Mom and Josh.
I was wondering,
do you guys ever think
you'll reconcile
your differences?
I think the damage is done.
Have you tried, Rikki?I have tried.
And I tried to,
you know, say,
"Okay, people change.
People can change."
Once I got your daughter
pregnant, you totally--
Once you wanted her
to have an abortion?
Once you said you were
gonna punch her in the stomach?
I never said I was gonna
punch her in the stomach.
The list goes
on and on, Josh.
[overlapping arguing]
I was done.I never, ever, ever said
I was gonna punch
Nicole in the stomach.
It was in your driveway.
Whatever.
But, Rikki, what are you
fearful is going to happen
if you let her figure
it out on her own?
I believe he's having sex
with other people,
so when he goes back
to have sex with my daughter,
and there's diseases
if you don't protect yourself.
There's, uh,
other pregnancies.
What's the worst thing
can happen here?
She'll end up
like you.
Ohh...
[audience murmuring]
[Drew]
What are you afraid of?
Physical violence.Afraid he's gonna
hurt her physically?
Harm her? Moms think
about the worst things
that can happen
when they feel things
going a certain direction.
Right.Things can go bad.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not saying you intend to
do anything like that, Josh.
All right. Heh.
Nikkole, do you
think that Josh
is appropriate
role model for Lyle?
No.So what does
he need to do?
Um... go to college,
get a job.
And you're gonna
go to college?Yeah.
And you're gonna support
Nikkole and the child?
At least Lyle.
I mean...
[audience gasping]
[Drew]
I do hope you find
some kind of
an equilibrium where
you can at least...
co-parent.
Mm-hmm.
Well, Rikki, Josh, Nikkole,
thank you for joining us.
And in just a moment,
we're gonna return with Valerie.
She said three's a 99% chance
she'll wind up
with the father of her baby.
Have those odds changed?
Stay tuned.
You're gonna find out.
[applause]
♪♪
[music and applause]
Welcome back
to "Life After Labor."
I'm Dr. Drew.
Now this season,
despite some serious issues,
Valerie is on the record
saying she is 99% sure
she's going to end up
with Nevaeh's daddy, Matt.
We'll ask her whether that
number is the same today
as it was when she first issued
that declaration.
But first, here's a look
back at her story.
♪♪
We don't have any reason
to be talking
unless it's about the baby.
That's not fair to me.
I don't want
a relationship, period.
School starts Monday.
Are you gonna come back?
I'm trying.
Call the doctor!
Are you retarded?!
As far as you can, babe.
Come on, push.
Hey, buddy.Baby...
I wanna at least
talk to somebody
about going back
to school.
The reason I'm really
against it is because
all the suspensions
we went through.
That was different, Mom.
Matt is not gonna be
in the picture
like that anymore.
[Valerie]
Matt promised to visit us
every month.
You take a picture?I don't care.
Really?
Oh...I gotta leave
at midnight tonight.
No later.
He's not really around as much
as I'd like him to be,
but I'm gonna just
make the best out of it.
♪♪
[applause]
Well, Valerie,
you were adopted.
And you've said
that motherhood
with the relationship
with the birth mother
was something
you didn't have
and you'd like to give
your daughter, Nevaeh.
Do you still feel that way?Yes.
Yeah?Mm-hmm.
This is important to you?Very.
Talk about Matt.
How often do you see him now?
Um, close to every day.
Matt comes every day now?
Work wasn't good for him,
and then he decided
to move back home,
which is like five minutes
from my house.
For a while there,
you were kind of on your own
with Nevaeh, though, right?
Yeah, I mean, it was
really hard to deal with
at first because,
just becoming a mom was enough
and then not having
that support I needed
from like my boyfriend
'cause he was
so far away at that time.
And we saw that
in the episode, right?
Mm-hmm.Does that bring back
painful memories?
Just like a lot
was going on...
[voice breaking]
...and I really
needed him there.
[crying]
And then like scared
that he might not...
[sniffling]
...be there.
That it would go back
the way it was.
Mm-hmm, and I do not
want that at all.
Okay, let's bring Matt
out here
and let's tell him
about that, can we?
Mm-hmm.Okay, Matt, come on out.
[applause]
Okay, my friend,
did you hear
what she just said?
Yeah.Well, that she feels alone
and it feels like a wound
when she was alone by herself
with the baby and you were
somewhere else.
I know.And she doesn't want it
to go back to that again.
No.Can you reassure her?
Not gonna be
like that again.
[Dr. Drew]
I don't believe you.
It's not that simple.Oh, no, but I learned a lot.
Like I felt so bad.
Like I had like the worst
guilt trip in my whole life
like for like being
not around
and stuff like that.
So you don't wanna
feel like that either.
No, like it made me
feel bad as a person
because that's not the type
of person I truly am,
you know what I mean?Do you feel reassured?
Not yet.
[sniffles]
What's it gonna take?
You know, she was adopted
as a young-- young baby.
So abandonment's
a big deal to her.
Yeah.
Sometimes I'm rude.
I admit it.
I'm a rude guy
every now and then.
But that was like
a really hard time in my life.
What are you thinking?
Like I know he tried,
but I tried, too.
And it just feels like
I needed so much more.
Even now?
I don't mean now,
but just when
it really mattered,
he wasn't there.
And then when it does matter,
it's like
you can't go back
and fix it.
But you can forgive.Mm-hmm.
I can honestly say
and I think she'd agree
that we have so many more
nice times than we ever had.
And I wouldn't want to be
with any other girl,
you know what I mean,
like no matter what.
You're not gonna be alone.
Not no more.It's like I promise.
You'll see.
Do you guys use
contraception now?
Yes. No more Nevaehs
any time soon.
[audience laughing]Excellent.
Well, guys, Valerie, Matt,
thank you for chatting.
Very, very powerful story.
It's time to delve
into the story
of another one
of our team moms.
This is what Lizzie went through
on "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
Will you marry me?Yes.
[Lizzie]
I have like the perfect ring,
the perfect boyfriend,
the perfect family.
And now I'm excited about having
a perfect baby.
I've been hearing stuff
about Crista and Skylar.
Sounds like they hooked up.
I just feel stupid.
You can have
your ring back.
[girl]
How long do you think
you will take to get over it?
He just has to prove to me
that it's gonna be
all right
and last forever,
and he's never gonna do
anything like that.
I miss you and I think
we need to work stuff out.
[Lizzie moaning]
[baby crying]
Aww... don't cry.
You take her
when I need a break.
She loves you
and you love her.
[baby crying]
She won't stop crying.
Skylar, make her stop.
The best 19-year-old
daddy I know.
Mwah.
♪♪
[applause]
We are here now with both
Lizzie and Skylar.
Guys, how are you?Doing good.
Good, how's Summer doing?She's fabulous.
Now, Skylar, eight out
of ten dads do not marry
the teen moms
that had their babies.
Are you the exception?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
What makes you guys different
than other young couples
that makes you think
you're gonna make it?
Just-- I think our relationship
is strong enough
to work everything out.
And so far, everything's
been going fine
and we're just happy together.
Perfect relationship,
perfect ring,
perfect baby, perfect family,
perfect perfect.
Nothing's perfect.
I know, there's flaws
in everything.
Talk to us about
what's not perfect.
The bump in our relationship
we hit wasn't perfect and...
That was really
not so perfect.
No, that was the farthest
thing from perfect.
How far into the relationship
was the cheating?
Two and a half,
three months.
Something like that.Yeah, something like that.
Have you gotten over that?
Have you forgiven him?
Yes.I still see you as angry.
Me?You're still angry.
I saw it flash
over your face.
[giggles]
I'm like not really
angry at him.
I'm just angry
at the whole situation.
So... partly him, yeah.Well, he was part of it.
Yeah.And I'm just angry
that I didn't know about it
for so long.
Well, you said
you felt stupid.
I did feel stupid
because
other people knew about it,
but I didn't.
And... I just wish
someone had told me earlier.
I get it.
How is he as a dad?He's amazing.
He helps out
when I need it.
If I'm too tired
to get up
in the middle of the night,
he'll get up.
He changes diapers without me
even having to ask.
So talk to me about
contraceptives.
Are you using
contraceptives now?
Are we gonna have
another pregnancy?
No, absolutely not.
What are we doing?
Right now
I'm on the Depo shot.
Depo shot.
And then I'm gonna get
the Implanon on
in a couple weeks. Yeah.Excellent.
You've said in the past
that you wanna have four kids.
Do you still feel that way?
I wanna have two now.
But the other one's
not for a while.
A long while.
Skylar, two?
Is that about right?Yeah.
Whatever she wants?[giggles]
All right, you guys,
thank you for joining us.
Now, quick reminder
that 16andPregnant.mtv.com
has a ton more information
about prevention.
So do not forget to log on
to learn all the facts.
Lizzie isn't going anywhere
and neither should you.
Because just in a little while,
she and the other moms
are gonna come together
on this stage
and ask each other questions.
When we return,
we'll chat with Lori.
She chose adoption
for baby Aidan,
a decision that didn't
make Daddy very happy.
We'll hear from Lori, Corey,
and Lori's mom
in just a minute,
so don't go away.
[music and applause]
And welcome back
to the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special.
I'm Dr. Drew and today
we've chatting
with young mothers who had
no idea what they were in for.
Now, Lori knew motherhood
would be an uphill battle
so she made the decision
to choose adoption
for baby Aidan.
And it was by no means
an easy decision,
as we learned from
Lori's fights with her mom.
We'll bring out Lori's mom
in just a minute.
But first, this is
what Lori experienced
on "16 and Pregnant."
♪♪
We first found out
I was up for the adoption,
but now I can't do it.
Are you pretty much
set on your decision?
I'm 90%.I feel the exact same way.
It will be such a mistake
for you and for this baby
to bring him
into this house.
I got a hold of Corey.
He's convinced
that there's no way
that you guys can parent.
What caused you
to change your mind?
Just not financially stable.
I have no choices.
I'm giving him up
for adoption.
Lori...Go, go, go, go...
Come on, Lori.
Oh, look.[baby crying]
My family doesn't want me
to give him up.
Dad, get him out.
Dad, get him out...
Give me my son so I can
say good-bye, please.
I'm going.
Gee, what an ass[bleep].[crying]
[woman]
We're here
to celebrate adoption.
Celebrate this wonderful life.
You are so lucky.Thank you.
We are all so lucky.
[baby crying]
♪♪
[applause]
It really was
a beautiful ceremony.
Thank you.
You're tearing up
a little bit
just looking at that.
Do you regret
choosing adoption?
No, I don't.
And how often do you
see baby Aidan now?
I see him pretty frequent.
So it's a wide-open adoption.It is.
We get pictures
all the time.
Being able to see him makes
everything so much easier.
You know, adoptive moms
really have to make
a sacrifice of themself
on behalf of the baby.
Mm-hmm.
I wanted to parent.
I did at first.
And I know that I really
couldn't have given Aidan
everything that
I wanted him to have.
And because of that,
I found a family
who I knew could
and would let me still see him.
Now, during your episode,
you said you felt like
you don't have any choices,
was that true?
I questioned whether or not
I made the decision
or my parents did.
And I realized in the end
that I did.
Or I wouldn't be content
and happy and everything.
What do you think
motivated your parents
to put the pressure on
like that?
Well, we are surrounded
by adoption.
I'm adopted.
My older brother's adopted.
And they understand what it is
like to be adoptive parents
and how great
of a feeling that is.
And they also--
They know me.
Well, they just didn't think
it would be such a good idea.
Well, let's bring
your mom out here.
Mary Jo, why don't you
come on out?
[applause]
Is that about right?
You were doing your job
as a parent?
I felt like we were.
You know, we gave Lori
and Corey both
the option to parent.
That was, you know,
that was always on the table.
But we made it clear
that we were not going
to be parents.
We would be grandparents.
What would you say
to folks that are critical
of the pressure you put on
your daughter?
I want everyone to realize
that the decision
was ultimately Lori's.
Because they weren't
together.
You know,
they had broken up.
And I said, "He is going
to have rights to this baby.
"How are you going to feel
"when he pulls in our driveway
three or four times a week,
"maybe with a different
girlfriend every time,
"and you have to hand
that baby over to him?
How are you going to feel?"
Because that's something
to consider.
Yeah, it's tough.Yeah.
So, Lori, how did you feel
watching your episode?
It was a lot harder
to watch it
than to go through it.
Harder to watch it
than to go through it.Yes.
Was there a particular part
that was difficult?
Just everything.
Um, Corey and I,
we watched it by ourselves
for the first time.
I think we both cried
through the entire thing.
Yeah.It's just like, um,
we had come so far,
and then watching it again
kinda took us back.
I just-- I don't think
I'll be able to watch it again.
I'm happy and I know Aidan
is so happy.
And I think I wanna
leave it with that.
The fact is,
another piece of data,
only 2% of teen moms
actually choose adoption.
It's a very courageous
decision.
Congratulations.Thank you.
Well, Lori's episode left off
with the baby's father
angry about her decision.
Corey is backstage
and we will talk to him
about baby Aidan right after
this break.
So do not go away.
[music and applause]
And we are back at
the "16 and Pregnant"
finale special.
I'm the host, Dr. Drew,
and I'm still here with Lori.
Now, Lori chose adoption
for baby Aidan
which wasn't what
the child's father wanted.
Corey joins us now.
Corey, how are you?I'm good. How are you?
Thanks for joining us.
So we had discussed you
a little bit
before with Mary Jo.
How do you feel
about the adoption?
It was really hard
to come to terms with.
Um... my father walked out
and my mother passed away.
It seemed to me like
it would feel like
the same thing to Aidan,
and I didn't want that.
Do you still feel that way?
I'm coming to terms
with it.
How is your relationship
with Mary Jo now?
We get along. We're civil
when we see each other.
And how about with Lori?
We're civil.
We have a friendship.
You hadn't seen each other
for quite sometime, right?
Mm-mm.Makes you sad?
Yeah.
He was the first guy
I like fell in love with
and I got pregnant by him.
Are you still
in love with him?
Yeah.
Did you know that?
You knew that.
I did.
Do you have any desire
to be in a relationship
with Lori?
Not as much as I did.
Does she need to just
get over you?
I would say yes.
I mean, she'll always
have my friendship.
Have you guys had
this conversation?
No.
It's an important
conversation to have.
You know, you need to know
where you're at.
Okay?
Do you have regrets
watching the episode?
You're pretty tough
on her.
No, I had every right
to be angry.
I really did.
And yet,
you feel supportive
of the decision
in retrospect.
In the end, yes.Yeah.
We weren't
on good terms.
So, I mean, it wouldn't
have worked.
In the long run.
How did you
come around?
I have a really big
support system at home.
My brother is my saving grace
in this whole situation.
Would you guys
provide any advice
to other teens
out there
who are in
a similar situation?
Consider the adoption.
Even you, Corey?
Now that--
yeah, now that, uh...
I-I'm so pleased
to hear that.
That's interesting.Now that I've been
through it,
I've really come around.
And I'm really happy
with the decision.
I mean, it's still not
what I pictured,
but I mean, even though
that I still have
that chance to see him.
Do you feel like
he'll have
a better life
with that family?
He will definitely have
more things that he needs.
Definitely.
And Lori, do you have
other advice
for other teens
who might be out there
in a similar position?
I would definitely
consider it.
I mean, there's so many people
that don't even know
that open adoption
is an option that they have.
It's been hard but,
in the long run,
it's been a good thing.Nice.
Congratulations, you guys.
A very touching story.Thank you.
It's very, very intense.
Very challenging.
Very courageous.
Okay, guys, thank you again
for being here.
Let's move on
to our next mom.
Now, it's a sad fact
that children born
to teen mothers are more likely
to grow up poor.
One girl who knows
all about that struggle
to stay financially afloat
is Nicole.
This is her story
being 16 and pregnant.
♪♪
First thing that
came in your head.
I was scared for you,
'cause I know it's
gonna be hard for you.
What made you like me?
The way you love me.
Your personality.Well, of course.
I can't stand
my mom.
You're an immature
16-year-old.
You know what?
You're a [bleep] bitch, Mom.
[woman]
Tyler...
Yo, that's real
respectful...
for a dad![bleep] you!
I think we need to go, guys.All right, let's go.
[shrieking, crying]
[baby crying]
He didn't go to sleep
until 8:00 this morning.
Well, you're not...
totally comfortable with her,
and it--
she feels it.
You guys are gonna be
skatin' at the skate park.
Yup.So you're gonna leave
the baby with me?
[grandmother]
Pisses me off.
[Tyler]
I'm sick of everyone
pickin' on us.
I don't feel
like a kid no more.
Me either.
Weird how something
so little can
change you, you know?
Mm-hmm.
[applause]
We're here now
with Nicole
and Brooklyn's daddy,
Tyler.
Hi, guys.
How are you?
Doin' good.How's Brooklyn doing?
She's gettin' big.She's getting big?
How old is she now?
Two months.Two months, yesterday.
All right.
Now, you guys, I--
I don't understand
how you're gonna
support this baby.
And the data is that
two thirds of families
started by young,
unmarried moms end up poor.
How are you guys gonna
try to turn out different?
She's in school now.
She just took her GED test.
She passed it, and right now
I got a job part-time.
I'm about to be
full-time at work.
So you're the only one
workin' right now?
Yeah.
And you're going
to school?
Well, um, I got expelled
four times, so...
What were you
expelled for?
[sighs] Friends.
Older friends.
Wrong crowd I don't
hang out with no more.
And you're only 16.
How is it to...
be a dad at 16?
Growin' up so fast?
If I didn't have a kid,
I would be on
a bad road again.
I would-- I'd probably
be in prison.
Like-- 'cause I've had
a bad history.
Havin' a baby has actually
cleaned me up a lot.
I'm not going
and doin' stuff anymore.
How is Tyler
as a dad?
Excellent.Excellent?
Yeah.He's completely
engaged.
He supports you.Yeah.
You don't feel alone.No.
What's your living
situation right now?
We're livin'
with my grandma,
and we're living
with her mom.
Both his grandma and my mom
help us out.
Help you out a little bit,
or they doin' the majority...
They do a lot.
They do a lot for us.
...they do the majority
of the childcare?
I would say
majority, yes.
They do help us out a lot,
I'm not gonna lie.
My grandma and her mom
are very great to us.
What would it
have been like
without your mom
and your grandma?
Hell.Would have been hell?
Yeah.
How's your guys'
relationship now?
It's great. I'm ready
to take it to the next level.
[chuckles]What does that mean?
I want her
to be my girl.
I got this for you,
baby.
[audience murmuring][chuckles]
I want you to be
my girl,
and I want you
to be with me forever.
[audience awws]
[laughter]
What do you say?
Yes.
[applause]I love you.
[applause continues]
Nicole, you just got engaged
in front of everybody.
How do you feel?
Good?[audience chuckling]
You're flushed.On national television.
I don't know what
to say.
Speechless?Yeah, I'm about to cry.
It's okay, baby.
I love you.
Do you love Tyler?I love him very much.
And I want to be with you
forever, too.
We will.
We plan on having six kids.
[gasps, grunts,
blows raspberry]
[light laughter]
How do you plan
to support six kids?
We--
we'll do it.
We wanted eight
at first.
Oh![laughter]
You've got to pay for college
for these eight kids.
We will.
If we win the lottery.
[laughter]
Exactly, it'll require
the lottery.
Are you guys still
sexually active?
Yes.How are you delaying
the onset
of six more kids?
Protection.With?
Condoms.In the meantime,
do you have the
"morning after" pill handy?
You know what
that is?Mm-mm. I don't have it.
It's a birth control--I don't really believe
in that, though.
Why?'Cause I feel like
it's abortion.
It's not abortion.
It works exactly
the same way
as the birth control pill
you're about to get on.
It prevents an egg
from being released.
Just 'cause you take it
after sex doesn't mean
it works any differently
than the pill
you take every day.
Okay?Yeah.
Congratulations, you guys.
Thank you for joining us.
Well, I'd like to thank
Nicole and all our moms
for chatting with me today.
And right after this break,
they'll come together
and talk to one another
for the very first time.
It's what we call
our Spotlight Session,
and it is coming up next.
[applause]
♪♪
Welcome back
to "Life After Labor."
I'm Dr. Drew,
and I am joined
by all ten of
our teenage mothers
who are here in the same place
for the very first time.
Before we let you guys
ask questions
of one another,
I've got a couple things
I want to ask.
Show of hands:
How many of you
have your own
biological fathers
in your life with you
presently?
Show of hands.
Three, interesting.
So how many expect
the father of your baby
to be in their life
when they're 16?
Hmm.
How many of you were
using birth control
properly when
you got pregnant?
Only one.[laughter]
All right, it's critical
for our viewers
to realize that birth control
not only helps
prevent pregnancy,
also condoms help prevent
sexually transmitted diseases.
Now, these moms
have been waiting
to ask questions
of one another,
so let's get right to it.
Who has a question
for whom?
I do.Jenelle, what do you got?
I got a question
for Nicole.
[both chuckling]
I would like to know,
why are you choosing
to still try
to be with Josh?
After all
he's done to you.
I'm not choosing
to be with him.
I'm choosing to possibly
work things out,
just because
I still love him
and it's for the benefit
of Lyle at the same time.
Anybody else have
a question?
I have one for Leah.Yeah.
Uh, how do you
handle working,
having your own place,
and raising twins?
I have a lot of help
watching them.
I don't like taking them
to a daycare,
so while I'm in school
most of the time
my grandparents
or my mom
will watch them
during the day
until I get home.
But otherwise,
it's really hard.
I'm completely stressed out
by the end of the day.
I have questions for
whoever wants to answer.
Now that you've
met everybody,
what's your feeling
about one another?
I think we all
have something
to relate to....to relate to.
Yeah.
Plus, I learned a lot.Yeah.
[Drew]
Are you guys gonna
stay in touch?
[all agreeing]
So you're gonna
support one another.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.Yeah.
Any surprises that
you've learned here,
being together?
Kailyn?
I'm surprised
how many girls
don't have their biological
dads in the picture.
I really thought
I would be singled out,
but I'm not alone.
It's a common risk factor
for teen pregnancy.
Other thoughts?
Things you'd like to share
with the world? Nicole.
I give a lot of credit
to Lori,
'cause she's strong enough
to do what she did.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
I'm glad you guys
support Lori.
Any advice you guys have
for young women out there
who are not pregnant?
Kail?
I would say, if you have
a rocky relationship
with your boyfriend,
don't think a baby's gonna
keep you guys together.
Well, my hope is that
people will see your stories
and learn from them,
I think.
Congratulations, you guys.
You're very courageous
to share these
stories with us.
We spent a lot of time talking
about these babies.
It's time we bring 'em out.
♪♪
[Drew]
Thanks again to all ten
of our moms for being here.
And thank you for watching.
I'm Dr. Drew, and we will
see you next time.
[applause]
Say bye-bye!
♪♪
♪ Oh these nine awful weeks ♪
♪ Don't know how I'm gonna
get through it all ♪
♪ I'm weak but
I'm strong enough to see... ♪♪