>> MY NAME'S LIZZIE.
I LIVE IN SMITHFIELD,
A SMALL CONSERVATIVE TOWN
ON THE COAST OF VIRGINIA,
WITH MY MOM AND OUR THREE DOGS.
OKAY, OH.
HEY, YO.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
BUT WE STILL HANG OUT TOGETHER.
>> YOU WON THAT ROUND.
>> I LOVE TO PARTY AND HAVE FUN
WITH MY FRIENDS.
THAT'S HOW I MET SKYLAR.
HE WAS SO CUTE,
I HAD TO HAVE HIM.
SKYLAR WORKS AT A THRIFT STORE
AND IS STUDYING TO BECOME
A PROFESSIONAL GLASSBLOWER.
NOW HE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
WE'VE BEEN DATING FOR
EIGHT MONTHS.
I LOVE BEING IN HIGH SCHOOL
AND PLAYING WITH THE MARCHING
BAND.
[chime dings]
BUT I CAN'T WAIT TO GO
TO COLLEGE, WHERE I'LL CONTINUE
TO PURSUE MY PASSION FOR MUSIC.
MAYBE I'LL EVEN PLAY IN THE
VIRGINIA ORCHESTRA ONE DAY.
A LOVING FAMILY,
A CUTE BOYFRIEND, GOOD GRADES,
THE MARCHING BAND:
I HAVE THE PERFECT LIFE.
BUT THAT'S ALL ABOUT TO CHANGE
BECAUSE...
[flute scale trilling]
I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
I WAS A JUNIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL
WHEN I GOT PREGNANT, BUT SINCE
THEN, I'VE DROPPED OUT TO BE
HOMESCHOOLED.
I LIVE AT HOME WITH MY MOM.
AFTER GETTING OVER THE INITIAL
SHOCK, SHE'S REALLY EXCITED
TO BE A GRANDMOTHER.
MOM?
MOM!
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> I CAN'T FIT IN MY PANTS.
[laughter]
THEY WON'T GO UP.
>> OH.
GOT A LITTLE BIGGER A LITTLE
QUICKER THAN YOU THOUGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT ABOUT THOSE STRETCHY
PANTS YOU PICKED UP?
YOU THINK MAYBE YOU OUGHT TO
BREAK THOSE OUT?
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO
WEAR THEM YET.
THESE ARE MY CUTE JEANS.
>> JUST TRY THE OTHER ONES ON.
>> STRETCHY JEANS.
THEY'RE NOT TOO BAD-LOOKING.
DO THEY LOOK BETTER?
>> OH, YEAH.
THOSE ARE NICE-LOOKING.
HOW DO THEY FEEL?
>> THEY HAVE THE LITTLE BAND.
>> [laughs]
I THINK WE'LL PROBABLY HAVE TO
GET YOU AT LEAST ANOTHER PAIR,
HUH?
>> MY MOM'S BEEN A LOT MORE
SUPPORTIVE THAN MY DAD.
HE'S STILL HAVING TROUBLE
COMING TO TERMS WITH MY
PREGNANCY.
>> I THOUGHT THAT YOU WERE ON
SOME SORT OF CONTRACEPTION.
>> I WAS.
>> THEN I FINALLY AGREED TO IT.
>> YEAH.
AND BEFORE WE COULD MAKE
THE APPOINTMENT...
>> COULD HAVE ABSTAINED
FOR A MONTH.
>> [chuckles mockingly]
>> I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT
YOU KNEW BETTER.
>> I WANTED FOUR KIDS.
I'M JUST GONNA SPACE THEM OUT
MORE NOW.
>> WELL, YOU ALSO WANTED TO GO
TO COLLEGE, AND YOU ALSO WANTED
TO GET A GOOD JOB.
>> I STILL WILL.
I SENT AN EMAIL TO THE VIRGINIA
SYMPHONY.
>> GOOD.
>> ASKING WHAT?
>> HOW YOU GO ABOUT BEING
A PART OF THE SYMPHONY.
THEY SAID IT'S JUST TRYOUTS.
>> WOULD HAVE BEEN A LOT EASIER
WITHOUT A BABY.
LET'S JUST PUT IT THAT WAY.
>> YUP.
I HOPE BEING PREGNANT WON'T GET
IN THE WAY OF MY DREAMS,
'CAUSE I'VE GOT A LOT PLANNED.
I KNOW ACHIEVING MY GOALS
WILL BE HARDER WITH A BABY,
BUT SKYLAR AND I ARE UP
FOR THE CHALLENGE.
[laughter]
FROM THE MOMENT WE MET,
WE'VE SPENT MOST OF OUR TIME
TOGETHER.
AND NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT,
SKYLAR IS MOVING IN WITH
MY MOM AND I FOR A WHILE,
SINCE WE PLAN TO LIVE HERE
ONCE THE BABY COMES.
THIS IS WHAT YOU HAVE TO LOOK
FORWARD TO, SKYLAR.
>> OH, OKAY.
>> OKAY.
MY MOM EVEN SAID WE CAN TURN
THE SPARE ROOM INTO A NURSERY.
I WANT EVERYTHING TO BE PERFECT
BY THE TIME THE BABY COMES,
SO WE BETTER GET STARTED.
[can clanking]
>> YOU WANT ME TO DO IT?
>> NO, I'VE GOT IT.
WOW.
WHAT COLOR DO YOU WANT TO PAINT
IT IF IT'S A GIRL?
>> I THINK WE SHOULD JUST
PAINT IT GREEN
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER.
>> AND DON'T FIND OUT THE SEX.
SO ARE YOU GONNA TEACH THE KID
GLASSBLOWING?
>> YEAH.
I GUESS YOU'RE GONNA DO FLUTE.
>> DOESN'T HAVE TO BE FLUTE.
>> THEY GOT TO LEARN TRUMPET
SO THEY CAN BE IN A SKA BAND.
>> OH, HECK, NO.
NO TRUMPET.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE TRUMPETS GIVE FLUTES
A LOT OF CRAP IN BAND.
BUT I'M NOT IN BAND ANYMORE,
SINCE THEY KICKED ME OUT
AFTER I STARTED HOMESCHOOLING.
I DON'T MISS PUBLIC SCHOOL,
BUT IT MAKES IT HARDER TO HANG
OUT WITH ALL MY BAND FRIENDS.
I MIGHT ACTUALLY GET
A COLOR COLOR.
THAT FEELS GOOD.
ALL MY MUSIC'S AT SCHOOL,
SO I HAVE TO GO PICK IT UP,
SO I HAVE, LIKE, NOTHING TO PLAY
EXCEPT MY SCALES.
>> THAT'S FUN.
>> OH, LOADS.
I MEAN, THAT'LL HELP ME PRACTICE
FOR WHEN I GO TRY OUT FOR
THE ORCHESTRA.
>> YEAH, YOU NEED TO,
'CAUSE YOU'RE SO GOOD.
>> WHY WERE YOU SO UPSET,
LIKE, WHEN I TOLD YOU ABOUT
ME BEING PREGNANT?
>> I FELT LIKE IT WASN'T WHAT
YOU REALLY WANTED AT THE MOMENT,
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE SO PRETTY,
AND YOU'RE SO SMART
AND, LIKE, DRIVEN.
>> AW.
>> YOU KNOW?
SO WHAT MADE YOU WANT TO KEEP
YOUR BABY?
>> DECIDE NOT TO GIVE IT UP
FOR ADOPTION?
>> YEAH.
LIKE, DID YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
>> NOT REALLY.
AND, LIKE, ABORTION,
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING I'M FOR.
DO YOU THINK I'M READY TO BE
A MOM?
>> OF COURSE.
>> DO YOU THINK SKYLAR'S READY
TO BE A DADDY?
>> NO.
>> WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
>> I'M SORRY.
OKAY, I THINK, LIKE,
ONCE A GIRL GETS PREGNANT,
YOU KNOW, SHE'S USUALLY THE ONE
WHO MATURES RIGHT AWAY
BUT NOT THE GUY.
>> YEAH.
BUT I ACTUALLY THINK SKYLAR'S
MATURING PRETTY QUICK.
HE EVEN CAME WITH ME TO MY
ULTRASOUND SO WE COULD FIND OUT
THE SEX OF OUR BABY.
WE'RE HAVING A GIRL
AND ARE NAMING HER SUMMER.
NOW THAT WE KNOW THE GENDER,
WE CAN GO AHEAD AND FINISH
THE NURSERY.
HOW HARD CAN PUTTING A CRIB
TOGETHER BE ANYWAY?
>> HMM.
IS THERE A SPECIFIC SIDE
I NEED TO PUT?
WHY DOES THAT LOOK WRONG?
I DON'T GET THAT PART.
SEE, THAT DOESN'T SEEM RIGHT
TO ME.
SOMEHOW I KNEW US PUTTING THE
CRIB TOGETHER WOULD TURN INTO
ME PUTTING THE CRIB TOGETHER.
>> [laughs]
UM, TEAMWORK.
YOU PUT IT TOGETHER, AND THEN
I GIVE YOU THE BABY TO PUT
IN IT.
>> SO ARE YOU AFRAID YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO GIVE UP ANYTHING?
>> I'M NOT GONNA LET JUST
HAVING A BABY STOP ME FROM
DOING WHAT I WANT TO DO
AND WHAT I LOVE.
>> WELL, THAT'S GOOD,
BECAUSE THEN IF YOU--
IF IT DID, I THINK YOU'D END UP
BEING RESENTFUL OF ME AND
POSSIBLY SUMMER.
>> EVERYONE THINKS I'M GONNA
HAVE TO GIVE SOMETHING UP.
I'M SURE I CAN STILL PLAY
IN THE VIRGINIA ORCHESTRA
AND BE A MOM.
>> NOW THAT THE CRIB IS DONE,
IT'S TIME TO START PLANNING
FOR OUR FUTURE.
>> OH, THAT'S PRETTY SWEET
RIGHT THERE.
>> WE NEED A TINY BABY PUMPKIN.
>> WHAT ABOUT THAT ONE?
>> LIKE THAT ONE.
>> THAT ONE?
>> SINCE SKYLAR ONLY WORKS
PART-TIME AT THE THRIFT STORE,
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO AFFORD A BABY.
THAT'S GONNA BE US IN,
LIKE, A YEAR.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
[giggles]
SO WHERE DO YOU WANT US TO BE
WITH OUR BABY NEXT YEAR?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I WISH WE HAD A PLACE
OF OUR OWN TO GO TO.
>> YEAH.
I CAN'T REALLY AFFORD THAT
RIGHT NOW, THOUGH.
>> I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT THE
MONEY, SINCE YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S WORKING.
>> I THINK--
>> WE'RE GONNA BE AT MY PARENT''
HOUSE FOR A WHILE.
>> YEAH, AT LEAST TWO YEARS.
>> SUCH A LONG TIME.
>> YEAH.
>> I GOT TO GET A MAMA PUMPKIN
AND A DADDY PUMPKIN AND GET YOUR
BUMPKIN TO WORK.
TWO YEARS OF LIVING AT MY MOM'S
HOUSE IS NOT EXACTLY THE PLAN
I WAS THINKING OF.
[cello music]
*
EVEN THOUGH I GOT PREGNANT
AT A YOUNG AGE, I'M TRYING HARD
NOT TO GIVE ANYTHING UP.
ONE THING I REFUSE TO CHANGE
ABOUT MY LIFE IS PLAYING MUSIC.
I USED TO MARCH IN THE HIGH
SCHOOL BAND WITH ALL MY FRIENDS,
SO NOW THAT I'M HOMESCHOOLED,
I JUST PRACTICE BY MYSELF.
[flute scale trilling]
AT LEAST SKYLAR STILL GETS
TO HANG OUT WITH HIS FRIENDS.
[guns popping]
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU WON.
>> DUDE, THAT WAS SWEET.
ARE WE GONNA BE ABLE TO HAVE
THIS GUY TIME AS WE NORMALLY DO?
>> YEAH.
>> I JUST HOPE IT DOESN'T
CHANGE.
I KNOW YOU'RE GROWING UP,
GONNA BE A DADDY.
>> BE A BIG BOY.
>> [chuckles]
>> SO DO YOU THINK YOU AND
LIZZIE ARE GONNA STAY TOGETHER
BECAUSE OF THIS?
>> I THINK WE'RE GONNA
STAY TOGETHER.
I ACTUALLY BEEN THINKING ABOUT
PROPOSING TO LIZZIE.
>> 'CAUSE SHE'S PREGNANT NOW,
OR WERE YOU PLANNING ON DOING
THIS BEFORE?
>> I THINK IT PROBABLY JUST SPED
UP THE PROCESS A LITTLE BIT.
I MEAN, I GUESS I HAVEN'T TALKED
TO HER DAD YET.
>> IS HE GONNA BEAT YOU UP
OR SOMETHING WHEN YOU TELL HIM?
>> NO, HE'S NOT GONNA
BEAT ME UP WHEN HE TELLS ME.
>> LIZZIE, YOU READY TO SEE US?
>> YES.
[gasps]
OH, YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
I REALLY STILL LIKE THAT DRESS
A LOT, A LOT.
>> CAN'T GIVE IT TO YOU,
SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO FIT IN IT.
>> I'LL TELL EVERYBODY THAT
YOU SAID HI.
>> OKAY.
>> YES.
>> I REALLY WISH YOU WERE COMING
TO HOMECOMING, THOUGH,
'CAUSE WE HAD SO MUCH FUN
LAST YEAR.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO
AND HAVE A BIG OLD BELLY,
LIKE, WHILE I'M TRYING TO
GRIND UP ON PEOPLE.
[laughter]
YOU WANT TO SEE THE DRESS
I'D WEAR?
>> both: YES.
>> OKAY, IT'S PRETTY.
THAT'S MY DRESS.
>> THAT IS SO PRETTY.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> I WISH YOU WERE GOING.
>> I DO TOO.
OH, WELL.
STUFF CHANGES.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M GONNA
WALK Y'ALL DOWNSTAIRS.
YOU'RE LATE FOR THE DANCE.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE Y'ALL LATER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU LOOK GORGEOUS.
AW.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE Y'ALL.
ALL RIGHT, DON'T GET PREGNANT.
>> both: WE WON'T.
>> BYE.
SINCE I'M NOT A PUBLIC SCHOOL
STUDENT ANYMORE, I HAVE TO MISS
OUT ON BEING IN OUR TOWN'S
HARVEST PARADE.
I'VE NEVER WATCHED THE PARADE
BEFORE.
>> IT'S NOT SO BAD.
>> IT'S NOT AS BAD AS I THOUGHT.
>> YEAH.
SO THIS IS THE FIRST YEAR
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN IN THE PARADE?
HOW MANY YEARS HAVE YOU BEEN
IN THE PARADE?
>> AT LEAST FIVE.
>> THAT'S A LOT.
[marching band percussion]
>> EVEN THOUGH THIS IS MY FIRST
YEAR NOT MARCHING WITH MY
BANDMATES, I'M GONNA TRY TO HAVE
A GOOD TIME.
LOOK AT CHELSEA DANCING.
>> CHELSEA.
>> [giggles]
CHELSEA!
SHE DIDN'T HEAR ME.
JESSICA!
VIRGINIA WOULDN'T EVEN SMILE
AT ME.
THAT'S REALLY SAD.
I GUESS PARADES AREN'T AS FUN
WHEN YOU'RE STANDING ON
THE SIDELINES.
BEING PREGNANT IS CAUSING ME
TO SACRIFICE SOME THINGS
AFTER ALL.
IT REALLY SUCKED NOT MARCHING
WITH THE BAND IN THE PARADE
YESTERDAY.
>> I GUESS I'LL TALK TO YOU
LATER.
I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> AW.
>> AND IT SUCKS EVEN MORE THAT
SKYLAR HAD TO LEAVE EARLY FOR
WORK TODAY.
I WAS HOPING WE COULD HANG OUT.
>> HEY, SKYLAR.
>> HEY, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> YOU TOO.
>> COME ON IN.
SO WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND?
>> I WAS...
WITH YOUR PERMISSION, I WAS
GOING TO ASK LIZZIE TO MARRY ME.
>> WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT,
AND I RESPECT THAT.
YOU KNOW, I'M IN NO HURRY
FOR YOU GUYS TO GET MARRIED.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO
BE MARRIED TO GET PREGNANT.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I WOULD HATE TO THINK
THAT YOU FEEL YOU HAVE TO GET
MARRIED 'CAUSE YOU HAVE A CHILD.
I DON'T CARE IF YOU GUYS
STAY TOGETHER.
IF YOU WANT TO TRY LIVING
TOGETHER, EVEN THAT'S OKAY.
BUT THE BIGGEST PROBLEM I HAVE
WITH YOU GUYS GETTING MARRIED
IS YOUR AGE.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE THE BABY'S
FATHER, YOU KNOW, WHETHER SHE
MARRIES SOMEBODY ELSE OR
WHATEVER.
>> I MEAN, I GUESS I SEE
THE POSSIBILITY OF US
NOT STAYING TOGETHER.
BUT I'M GONNA DO EVERYTHING
THAT I CAN TO KEEP US TOGETHER.
>> I'M ENTERING THE FINAL MONTHS
OF MY PREGNANCY,
AND THE REALITY OF BEING
A FUTURE MOM IS SINKING IN.
THIS LITTLE BABY GIRL'S ABOUT
TO POP OUT.
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE READY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE
A FABULOUS DADDY.
SO DO YOU THINK I'M GONNA BE
A GOOD MOM?
>> YEAH.
>> I WAS THINKING ABOUT THAT
LAST NIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW VERY MUCH
ABOUT KIDS.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL BE ABLE
TO TELL WHY THE BABY'S CRYING,
LIKE, IF IT'S HUNGRY
OR IF IT'S JUST GRUMPY
OR, I MEAN--
>> IT'S TIRED.
>> YEAH, IF IT'S TIRED.
THERE YOU GO.
I WAS ABOUT TO SAY,
'CAUSE I'LL KNOW IF THE DIAPER
NEEDS TO BE CHANGED.
THAT'S PRETTY EASY, BUT...
>> SO YOU PLAN ON
BREAST-FEEDING, RIGHT?
>> AS LONG AS I CAN, YEAH.
>> OKAY.
GOOD, 'CAUSE IT'S BETTER
FOR THE BABY...
>> AND IT'S CHEAPER.
>> THAN FORMULA.
EXACTLY, IT'S CHEAP.
>> IT'S CHEAPER.
SO DID YOU EVER THINK WHEN WE
MET THAT WE WOULD STILL BE
TOGETHER NOW HAVING THIS
CONVERSATION?
>> ABOUT BABIES?
>> YES.
>> NO.
I KNEW WE'D STILL BE
TOGETHER, THOUGH, 'CAUSE
I WANTED YOU, AND I GOT YOU.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND I GET WHAT I WANT.
>> WELL, I'M GLAD
THIS ACTUALLY TURNED OUT
THE WAY IT DID.
>> ME TOO.
>> MWAH.
>> OH.
I LOVE IT WHEN YOU DO THAT.
SKYLAR IS GONNA MAKE
A GREAT DAD AND HOPEFULLY
A GOOD HUSBAND ONE DAY TOO.
[lively rock music]
*
>> HEY, THERE.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU GUYS
TODAY?
>> I'M ACTUALLY HERE TO
PICK UP A RING.
>> ENGAGEMENT RING?
>> YUP.
>> AWESOME.
>> IT'S PREORDERED.
>> YOU THINK SHE'LL LIKE IT?
>> YEAH, I THINK SHE WILL.
I HOPE SO.
>> YOU HOPE SO?
>> THAT'S DEFINITELY WHAT
I WANTED.
>> DID YOU GET SOMETHING
WRITTEN INSIDE?
>> NO, I DIDN'T.
SHOULD I HAVE?
>> YEAH, YOU COULD HAVE SAID
SOMETHING LIKE, "ALL MY LOVE,"
MADE UP A NAME, GIVE HER
A PET NAME OR SOMETHING.
>> SHE EXPECTING IT AT ALL OR...
>> NO.
DON'T LOSE IT.
>> I'M NOT.
>> GONNA BURN A HOLE IN
YOUR POCKET NOW.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> * COMING DOWN
>> SKYLAR SURPRISED ME TONIGHT
BY ASKING ME TO DINNER AT
MY FAVORITE RESTAURANT.
SO WHY ARE WE GOING OUT
TO DINNER, BABE?
>> 'CAUSE I LOVE YOU.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YUP.
>> [giggles]
WELL, I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> * REACHING OUT
* TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
>> OH, YEAH, WHAT DID YOU THINK
WHEN YOU FIRST PICKED ME UP?
>> I LIKED YOUR EYEBROW
PIERCING.
I KNEW THAT.
AND I THOUGHT YOU WERE CUTE
WHEN WE HUNG OUT AND STUFF.
>> WE DID CLICK PRETTY FAST.
>> YUP.
WE SAT ON THE POOL TABLE
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR JUST GOING,
"WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE COLOR?
WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE MOVIE?"
>> [clears throat]
SO, LIZZIE, THERE'S A QUESTION
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> [giggles]
>> I LOVE YOU.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
>> YES.
[giggles]
YOU MAKE ME GIGGLE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> JUST LIKE YOU.
>> MM.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU MORE.
>> * WHAT CAN YOU DO
* WITH AN IMAGINARY HEART?
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO SHOW OFF
MY RING TO MY FRIENDS.
Y'ALL WANT TO SEE MY RING?
>> all: YES.
>> OH.
>> IT'S SO PRETTY.
>> I AM SO JEALOUS.
>> OH, THAT'S SO PRETTY.
>> IT'S BIG.
>> LIKE, HE COULDN'T HAVE PICKED
OUT A MORE PERFECT RING
IF I HAD DONE IT.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> I LOVE IT.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
>> YOU CAN'T?
>> WELL, I GUESS I CAN,
BUT STILL, IT'S KIND OF
UNEXPECTED.
>> LIKE, PERSONALLY, I WOULDN'T
WANT TO BE PREGNANT.
>> NOT MUCH YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT,
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL MAKE
THE BEST OF IT, RIGHT?
>> EXACTLY.
THAT'S HOW I LOOK AT LIFE NOW.
>> I'M GLAD EVERYTHING'S, LIKE,
WORKING OUT.
LIKE, IT COULD HAVE GONE IN
AN OPPOSITE DIRECTION AND BEEN
REALLY BAD AND JUST A MESS.
AND I'M REALLY GLAD, LIKE,
YOU'RE HAPPY.
>> YOU HAVE A LOT OF SUPPORT.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M EXCITED.
LIKE, I THINK EVERYTHING'S
GONNA GO GOOD, SINCE I FOUND--
OR I HAVE, LIKE, THE PERFECT
BOYFRIEND AND THE PERFECT RING
AND THE PERFECT FAMILY,
AND I DON'T KNOW.
I'M EXCITED ABOUT HAVING
A PERFECT BABY.
Y'ALL ARE ALL GONNA BE
AT MY WEDDING, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU TAKING THIS
SO WELL?
>> I HAVE THE SUPPORT
FROM Y'ALL AND HIS FAMILY
AND MY FAMILY, AND I KNOW
THAT WE CAN DO IT.
>> IT'S GOOD THAT YOUR PARENTS
SUPPORT YOU, THOUGH,
'CAUSE I KNOW MINE WOULDN'T.
>> YEAH.
[laughter]
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> MY FRIENDS ARE SO EXCITED
ABOUT THE ENGAGEMENT.
WISH I COULD SAY THE SAME
FOR MY DAD.
>> AND JUST THE FACT THAT
YOU HAVE A BABY DOESN'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO BE MARRIED.
>> IT'S NOT WHY I WAS
GONNA BE MARRIED.
>> YOU DON'T NEED TO RUSH
INTO IT.
>> WHEN DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
GET HITCHED, THEN?
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD WAIT
TILL IT'S RIGHT.
BUT YOU BOTH NEED TO GET THROUGH
WITH YOUR SCHOOL.
>> WHAT IF IT WAS RIGHT
RIGHT NOW?
>> WELL, THAT'S THE PROBLEM IS,
IT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
WHEN IT'S RIGHT AND WHEN
YOU THINK IT'S RIGHT.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU SHOULD GET
MARRIED WHEN YOU THINK IT'S
RIGHT.
>> I THINK IT'D BE RIGHT
WHENEVER WE DID IT.
>> WELL...
>> THERE IS NO WRONG TIME
FOR LOVE.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT MY DAD'S
SAYING, BUT I'M NOT GONNA LET IT
GET IN THE WAY OF WHAT I WANT.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE
WEARING AN ENGAGEMENT RING
AT 17.
I FIGURED IT WOULD JUST BE
MY BELLY RING.
YAY.
BUT NOW EVEN THAT HAS TO CHANGE.
MA?
>> YEAH, HONEY?
>> MY BELLY RING CAME.
>> DID IT, REALLY?
>> I GOT A PINK ONE.
>> OF COURSE.
>> OH.
>> THAT'S REALLY BIG.
>> OH, MY.
[laughs]
AND IT'S FLEXIBLE?
>> YEAH.
>> ISN'T THAT NEAT?
>> THAT'S CUTE.
MY PALE WHITE BELLY.
OW.
THAT WAS, LIKE, SHARP
AND POINTY AT THE TOP.
THAT LOOKS REALLY BIZARRE.
>> THAT LOOKS HUGE.
LOOKS LIKE A TOOTHPICK
WITH PINK DOTS ON THE END.
>> YOU CAN FEEL IT THROUGH
THE SKIN.
>> REALLY?
>> YAY.
THAT'S A RELIEF.
>> WELL, GOOD.
>> NOW THAT SKYLAR AND I ARE
ENGAGED, I CAN START TO SEE US
AS REAL PARENTS.
WE GOT THREE WEEKS AND TWO DAYS
LEFT.
>> YUP.
>> SO ARE YOU GETTING NERVOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> HAVING A BABY.
>> I MEAN, LIKE, THE LABOR PART
AND ACTUALLY HAVING IT
OR THE COMING HOME PART?
>> PROBABLY THE LABOR.
>> THE LABOR?
WHY ARE YOU NERVOUS
ABOUT THAT PART?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> [giggles]
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO DIE.
>> I HOPE I DON'T EITHER.
>> WHAT ARE YOU NERVOUS ABOUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HER COMING OUT GROTESQUE?
>> SHE'S OUR DAUGHTER.
SHE'S NOT GONNA BE EVEN
GROTESQUE IN THE SLIGHTEST.
>> OKAY.
>> I HOPE SHE'S NOT LIKE ME
VERY MUCH, IN THE BAD WAYS.
LIKE, MY MOM DIDN'T KNOW
ANYTHING I WAS DOING.
I HOPE I CAN KNOW WHAT
SHE'S DOING.
AND I HOPE SHE'S NOT DUMB
AND DOES THAT STUFF.
>> I DON'T WANT THAT EITHER.
>> ENOUGH WORRYING ABOUT
THE BABY.
IT'S TIME TO CELEBRATE.
MY MOM IS THROWING ME
A BABY SHOWER TODAY
AT SKYLAR'S HOUSE.
>> OH, YES.
JUST WHAT I WANTED.
>> WOW, THAT'S--
>> CUTE.
>> OH, SOCKS.
>> SOCKS, ALL RIGHT.
>> AW.
>> IT'S A BABY BLANKET.
>> AW, IT'S SO CUTE.
THANKS, Y'ALL.
>> THANKS, EVERYBODY.
>> I LOVE HIS PICTURE.
IT'S SO ADORABLE.
>> YES.
>> DO YOU WANT THIS,
OR DID YOU WANT SKYLAR'S FACE?
>> I'LL HAVE THE CORNER.
>> I WANT LIZZIE'S FACE.
SWEET.
>> LOOK AT THAT PRETTY BABY
ON THE CAKE.
>> [growls]
>> [whines] SKYLAR!
YOU'RE MEAN.
>> [chuckles]
>> OH, KISS ME AFTER YOU,
LIKE, SMASH MY FACE.
[laughter]
>> EVERYBODY COULD MOVE IN
THIS WAY, PLEASE.
>> ALL RIGHT, AS EVERYBODY
PROBABLY KNOWS, YOU KNOW,
A FEW MONTHS AGO, AFTER LIZZIE
GOT PREGNANT, SHE DECIDED THAT
SHE WASN'T GOING TO GO BACK
TO HIGH SCHOOL TO FINISH UP
HER LAST YEAR.
SHE DECIDED SHE WANTED TO DO
HOMESCHOOL, AND SHE WAS
CONFIDENT THAT SHE COULD DO IT,
AND I'M PROUD TO SAY THAT
SHE DID.
SO SHE'S NOW GRADUATED
FIVE MONTHS AHEAD OF THE REST
OF HER CLASS.
>> YAY.
>> AND SO TODAY WE ARE GIVING
HER HER DIPLOMA.
[cheers and applause]
>> THANK YOU.
>> THERE YOU GO.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THERE YOU GO, KIDDO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
DON'T YOU WANT TO GIVE A SPEECH?
YOU'RE THE VALEDICTORIAN
OF YOUR CLASS.
[laughter]
>> THE BABY SHOWER WAS GREAT,
BUT LATER THAT NIGHT, I GOT
SOME UNSETTLING NEWS.
WORD WAS GETTING AROUND THAT
SKYLAR HAD BEEN UNFAITHFUL TO ME
EIGHT MONTHS AGO AFTER PROM.
>> * WAKE UP
>> JOSH JUST TEXTED ME BACK,
AND HE SAID HE'S BEEN
HEARING [bleep] TOO.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> KRISTA AND SKYLAR,
SOUNDS LIKE THEY HOOKED UP.
I MEAN, SO SERIOUSLY, LIKE,
THINK ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, DO YOU--DO YOU THINK
SKYLAR WOULD CHEAT ON YOU?
>> LIKE, I DON'T THINK HE WOULD
'CAUSE WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR SO LONG, AND IF HE DID DO
ANYTHING BACK THEN, HE SHOULD
HAVE TOLD ME BY NOW.
>> I MEAN, WHAT IF HE DID?
LIKE, WHAT ARE--
I MEAN, ARE YOU GONNA EVER
TRUST HIM AGAIN?
>> I CAN'T ANSWER THAT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I ASSUMED IT WAS JUST
AN UGLY RUMOR, BUT WHEN
I CONFRONTED SKYLAR ABOUT IT,
EVERYTHING CHANGED.
>> I MADE A MISTAKE A WHILE AGO.
>> WAS IT WITH KRISTA?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T WANT THAT TO RUIN
WHAT WE HAVE TOGETHER,
'CAUSE I KNOW I REALLY DON'T
WANT TO LOSE YOU.
>> DO YOUR OTHER FRIENDS KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, ALL OF THEM?
>> THAT JUST MAKES ME LOOK
STUPID.
I DIDN'T EVER SEE YOU COMING
AND DOING THAT.
AND I JUST FEEL STUPID.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULDN'T FEEL
STUPID, BUT I UNDERSTAND.
>> IT MAKES ME FEEL
SELF-CONSCIOUS...
>> HONEY, YOU SHOULDN'T.
>> LIKE IT'S MY FAULT
AND I DID SOMETHING WRONG...
>> IT'S NOT.
>> WHICH LED YOU TO DO THAT.
>> THIS IS NOT YOUR FAULT.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
BUT YOU CAN HAVE YOUR RING BACK.
>> * I TORE YOUR HEART
* TO PIECES
>> I LOVE YOU.
I'M PROBABLY GONNA GO HOME NOW,
'CAUSE I'M SURE YOU DON'T WANT
ME STAYING HERE.
>> * PLEASE FORGIVE ME
>> * DAYLIGHT TURNS TO DARK
>> I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THE RUMORS WERE TRUE.
SKYLAR HAD BEEN UNFAITHFUL
TO ME.
I KICKED HIM
OUT OF MY MOM'S HOUSE.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO TALK
TO HIM RIGHT NOW.
MOM?
DID YOU REDO MY DOCTOR
APPOINTMENT?
THIS REALLY HURTS.
>> * FROM THE LIGHTS ABOVE
* STARS WILL FLY
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I WENT TO SLEEP LAST NIGHT,
I COULDN'T GET THE PICTURE
OUT OF MY HEAD,
AND SO I STARTED CRYING.
AND I TOOK ALL HIS STUFF,
AND I, LIKE, PUT IT IN A BOX,
AND I THREW IT IN THE CLOSET.
MY ROOM JUST GOT, LIKE,
DE-SKYLARIZED.
>> OH.
SO HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL TAKE TO GET OVER IT AND,
LIKE, MAKE HIM REDEEM HIMSELF?
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW,
'CAUSE HE DOESN'T, LIKE,
GET HOW THE LAST EIGHT MONTHS
I THINK ARE BASED ON LIES NOW
BECAUSE THE TRUST WAS A LIE.
BUT HE JUST HAS TO MAKE--
>> BUILD YOUR TRUST?
>> REBUILD THE TRUST, YEAH,
AND THEN START PROVING TO ME
THAT IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT
AND LAST FOREVER AND HE'S NEVER
GONNA DO ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
TO KEEP MY MIND OFF THE FACT
THAT SKYLAR CHEATED ON ME,
I'VE BEEN FOCUSING MORE ON
COLLEGE.
I'VE ALREADY ENROLLED IN TWO
CLASSES, WHICH TAKE UP MOST
OF MY TIME.
NOW THAT THERE'S THE POSSIBILITY
OF PARENTING WITHOUT SKYLAR,
I'VE DECIDED TO PUT MY DREAM
OF PLAYING IN THE VIRGINIA
ORCHESTRA ON HOLD FOR A MORE
STABLE CAREER AS AN ULTRASOUND
TECHNICIAN.
TODAY I'M MEETING WITH
A COLLEGE COUNSELOR TO MAKE SURE
I'M ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
>> YOU HAVE TO HAVE TAKEN
MEDICAL TERMINOLOGY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU HAVE TO HAVE AN "A"
OR A "B" IN BIO 141.
ALSO YOU HAVE TO HAVE AN OVERALL
GPA OF 3.0, AND YOU HAVE TO HAVE
SOME FORMAL ACCREDITED MEDICAL
EDUCATION, AND YOU HAVE TO PASS
YOUR EXAMS.
EACH OF THESE EXAMS COSTS $200,
AND EACH OF THESE EXAMS HAS
A NATIONAL PASS RATE OF
ABOUT 50%.
>> THIS SOUNDS LIKE A LOT
OF WORK.
I WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO DO IT
ON MY OWN.
I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT WHAT SKYLAR DID
AND HOW MUCH OUR BABY NEEDS TO
HAVE TWO PARENTS WHO LOVE HER.
EVEN THOUGH HE HURT ME,
I'M WILLING TO GIVE HIM
A SECOND CHANCE, 'CAUSE
I REALLY WANT THIS TO WORK,
NOT ONLY FOR ME BUT FOR SUMMER.
[line rings]
>> HEY.
CAN YOU COME OVER?
>> YEAH, I CAN.
>> OKAY, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD COME BACK.
>> I MISS YOU, AND I THINK
WE NEED TO WORK STUFF OUT.
BUT I STILL DON'T TRUST YOU.
>> I KNOW YOU DON'T TRUST ME,
BUT I'M GONNA DO EVERYTHING
I CAN TO MAKE IT BETTER.
>> YOU KNOW YOU'RE MY BEST
FRIEND?
>> YES, AND YOU'RE MINE.
>> I DIDN'T LIKE LOSING
MY BEST FRIEND.
>> I DIDN'T LIKE IT EITHER.
>> I'VE NEVER BEEN BEST FRIENDS,
LIKE, WITH A BOYFRIEND
OR ANYTHING BEFORE.
AND THAT MEANS MORE TO ME
THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
>> SO ARE YOU GONNA PUT BACK ON
YOUR RING?
OKAY.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT READY
TO PUT MY RING BACK ON,
I'M GLAD SKYLAR AND I
ARE TOGETHER AGAIN.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE EXCITED TO HAVE
A LITTLE GIRL TO PUT IN THERE.
>> SO DOES SKYLAR LIVE WITH YOU
AGAIN?
>> YEAH.
IT'S LIKE, IT WASN'T THE SAME
WITHOUT HIM THERE.
PLUS, I HATE SLEEPING
>> HE SEEMS LIKE HE'S CHANGED
FOR THE BETTER.
>> YEAH, BETWEEN WHEN WE FIRST
GOT TOGETHER AND, LIKE, NOW,
HE'S LIKE A DIFFERENT PERSON.
LIKE, HE DOESN'T STAY OUT
REALLY LATE, 'CAUSE HE'LL COME
HOME, AND WE'LL HANG OUT FOR
A COUPLE HOURS AND HAVE OUR TIME
THAT WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE VERY
MUCH OF ONCE THE BABY'S HERE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> SKYLAR MOVED BACK IN
JUST IN TIME,
'CAUSE A FEW DAYS LATER,
I WENT INTO LABOR.
>> YOU'RE DOING GREAT, BABY.
>> * SLOW YOUR BREATH DOWN
* JUST TAKE IT SLOW
* FIND YOUR HEART NOW
* WHOA, OH-OH-OH
>> IT HURTS.
>> * YOU CAN TRUST IN LOVE
* AGAIN
* WHOA, OH-OH-OH
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> * SLOW YOUR BREATH DOWN
>> OKAY, THE DOCTOR SAYS
IT'S TIME TO PUSH.
>> * WHOA, OH-OH-OH
>> AFTER ANOTHER HOUR
OF PUSHING...
[gasps]
SUMMER WAS BORN.
>> [crying]
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
[camera shutter clicks]
[baby cries]
>> OW, IT'S SO SORE.
SHE'S BEEN DOING THIS FOR,
LIKE, AN HOUR.
YES.
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN TO EAT
MY LUNCH YET.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> OR TAKE A SHOWER.
>> I'D DO IT FOR YOU,
BUT I CAN'T.
THE FIRST FEW ATTEMPTS AT
FEEDING HER WERE REALLY PAINFUL,
BUT BREAST-FEEDING IS CHEAPER
THAN BUYING BABY FORMULA,
SO I'M GONNA KEEP TRYING.
WE'RE BEING DISCHARGED FROM
THE HOSPITAL TODAY.
AW, SORRY IT'S A BUMPY RIDE.
>> SHE DOES SEEM TO BE
A MITE HUNGRY.
>> IS IT TIME TO EAT?
>> OW.
HEY, NO.
DON'T STOP ALREADY.
BABY GIRL COULDN'T HAVE
A BETTER DADDY.
SHE GOOD?
>> YOU'RE ACTING LIKE YOU'RE
STILL HUNGRY.
>> [playfully] STOP BEING
HUNGRY.
OW-HO-HO.
LITTLE GIRL.
THAT HURTS.
YOU'RE HUNGRY?
OW, OW, OW.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
BREAST-FEEDING SUMMER AT HOME
ISN'T GETTING ANY EASIER.
I THINK I'M GONNA SWITCH
TO FORMULA.
>> SO ARE YOU TOTALLY DONE
WITH BREAST-FEEDING?
>> YES, I AM.
I DON'T THINK IT'S SUPPOSED
TO HURT LIKE THAT.
IT DOESN'T HURT AS MUCH NOW,
BUT IT SURE IS EXPENSIVE,
ESPECIALLY ON TOP OF DIAPERS
AND OTHER BABY SUPPLIES.
AND WITH SKYLAR ONLY WORKING
PART-TIME HOURS AT THE THRIFT
STORE, MONEY IS TIGHT.
DO WE HAVE ANY MORE NEWBORN
DIAPERS IN THE CLOSET?
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THOSE PACKS
I JUST BOUGHT?
>> THEY'RE GONE.
>> ALREADY?
BUT NO, WE HAVE NO
NEWBORN DIAPERS.
>> AND HOW MUCH DID THAT PACK
OF HOWEVER MANY, 24, 48,
OR HOWEVER MANY YOU BOUGHT WAS?
>> IT WAS 12 BUCKS.
>> PLUS, HOW MUCH WAS IT FOR
THAT BIG BOX OF FORMULA WE GOT?
'CAUSE WE ONLY HAVE, LIKE,
ONE OR TWO OF THOSE LEFT.
>> IT WAS, LIKE, $33.
>> I THINK WE ONLY HAVE
ONE BIG BOX LEFT.
[baby hiccups]
WE WENT THROUGH THREE BIG BOXES
IN TWO WEEKS.
>> DAMN.
SINCE WE FIGURED YOU'D BE
BREAST-FEEDING, WE PROBABLY
SHOULD START WATCHING MONEY
EVEN MORE.
>> BEING MORE AWARE OF IT
THAN BEFORE.
MOST EXPENSIVE IS THE DIAPERS
AND THE FORMULA.
>> YEAH.
IT'S KIND OF EXPENSIVE.
>> YES, IT IS.
THAT'S WHERE ALL OUR MONEY'S
GONNA BE GOING.
>> IT'S OVER A DOLLAR--
IT'S, LIKE, A DOLLAR AN OUNCE
FOR FORMULA.
>> THAT MEANS YOU JUST DRANK $4.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE WORRYING
ABOUT HOW TO AFFORD DIAPERS
AT SUCH A YOUNG AGE.
LOOKS LIKE WE'LL BE SAVING UP
FOR OUR DREAM HOUSE FOR A LITTLE
LONGER THAN WE THOUGHT.
[baby crying]
>> [groans]
YOU, MY DEARIE, ARE FINE.
NOW, STOP IT.
TOMORROW IS MY FIRST DAY
BACK AT COLLEGE,
AND I REALLY NEED TO GET
SOME SLEEP.
BUT SUMMER'S STILL NOT SLEEPING
THROUGH THE NIGHT,
WHICH MEANS NEITHER AM I.
THIS IS WAY HARDER THAN
I THOUGHT.
>> SO YOU GOT SCHOOL TOMORROW,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> YUP.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL PROBABLY CRY
ON THE WAY TO SCHOOL.
I HAVE SEPARATION ANXIETY.
I DON'T LIKE PUTTING HER DOWN.
[sniffles]
I'M NOT LOOKING FORWARD TO
BEING AWAY FROM SUMMER TODAY.
LUCKILY, IT'S ONLY FOR
A COUPLE HOURS.
YOU READY FOR SCHOOL?
>> YEAH.
>> THIS ISN'T YOUR FIRST TIME
LEAVING SUMMER.
IT'S MY FIRST TIME.
DADDY WILL BE FINE.
MOMMY'S GOT A LONGER DAY.
SINCE SKYLAR IS WORKING
AFTER SCHOOL, MY MOM IS GONNA
WATCH SUMMER WHILE I'M GONE.
IF SHE GETS HUNGRY, IT'S
3 OUNCES, WHICH IS 1 1/2 SCOOPS.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT SHE JUST HAD A BOTTLE
TOO, SO SHE SHOULDN'T BE HUNGRY
FOR A COUPLE HOURS.
>> OKAY.
>> I'LL SEE YOU LATER,
BABY GIRL.
>> OKEYDOKEY.
COME ON, PUMPKIN.
OH, MY GOD.
HI.
GOOD MORNING.
>> * DOESN'T HELP TO KNOW
* THAT YOU ARE VERY
* SO FAR AWAY
* MY ONLY WISH IS IF
* YOU COULD APPEAR RIGHT HERE
* WITH ME
* I TRY TO KEEP MY MIND
* PREOCCUPIED
* BUT IT'S THE HARDEST THING
>> IT'S HARD TO CONCENTRATE
IN CLASS.
I CAN'T GET HOME FAST ENOUGH.
>> * I'LL NEVER LET YOU GO
>> [gasps]
HEY, BABY GIRL.
YOU GONNA HOLD MY HAND?
>> * I'M A LITTLE BABY
* SHORT AND STOUT
* HERE IS MY FOOTSIE
* HERE IS MY MOUTH
* WHEN I GET REAL HUNGRY
* GET MY CUP
* TIP ME OVER
* AND I SPIT UP
>> NOW COME HERE SO MAMA
CAN INSPECT YOUR HEAD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SAY, "BYE, DADDY."
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
BYE.
DADDY'S OFF TO WORK, SO WE HAVE
THE WHOLE DAY TO OURSELVES.
SKYLAR HAS AGREED TO WORK MORE
HOURS AT THE THRIFT STORE TO
HELP WITH OUR MONEY SITUATION.
[baby crying]
SHE WON'T STOP CRYING.
SKYLAR, MAKE HER STOP.
SAY, "I DON'T KNOW WHAT
SHE'S CRYING FOR."
>> I CAN'T EVEN HEAR YOU.
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER, THOUGH,
OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BYE.
IT GETS LONELY SOMETIMES
WITHOUT SKYLAR AROUND.
GOOD THING MY FRIEND SCOTTIE
IS COMING OVER TO SEE THE BABY.
>> SAYS, "I'M HAPPY NOW."
HOW OFTEN IS SKYLAR WORKING,
LIKE, DURING THE WEEK?
>> HE WORKS FIVE DAYS A WEEK.
>> DO YOU GUYS, LIKE,
STRESS ABOUT MONEY AT ALL?
>> LIKE, YEAH, WE DO.
BUT WE DO WANT TO, LIKE,
DO EVERYTHING ON OUR OWN.
[baby crying]
HI.
OH.
>> WHY IS SHE SAD?
>> WHAT ARE YOU SO FUSSY FOR?
DO YOU WANT TO STAND UP?
[baby bawling]
OH.
>> WELL, I'M GONNA GO.
>> WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
>> BYE.
>> WHY ARE YOU CRYING, LITTLE--
AW.
SKYLAR'S GOING TO SCHOOL
AND WORKING A LOT MORE NOW,
AND MY FRIENDS WON'T
HANG OUT AS MUCH.
AT LEAST I STILL HAVE SCHOOLWORK
TO KEEP ME BUSY.
YOU GONNA STAY ASLEEP SO MAMA
CAN WORK ON HOMEWORK?
WHAT SHOULD MAMA WRITE ABOUT,
HUH?
[smooching]
YOU GOT A LOT OF HAIR, GIRL.
YOU HAVEN'T LOST ANY YET.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAMA DOESN'T WANT
TO GO TO CLASS ANYMORE.
LET'S FORGET THE HOMEWORK,
AND I'LL HANG OUT WITH YOU.
[birds tweeting]
WHAT TIME DO YOU HAVE CLASS?
>> 11:00.
DO YOU HAVE CLASS AT
THE SAME TIME?
>> I HAVE CLASS FROM 11:00
TO 2:00.
BUT I DON'T THINK I'M GOING
TODAY, SO MOM DOESN'T HAVE
TO WATCH HER.
>> WHY AREN'T YOU GOING?
>> SO THAT I CAN BE WITH SUMMER.
I'D RATHER SPEND TIME WITH HER
THAN GO TO CLASS.
>> SO WHAT?
ARE YOU JUST NOT GOING ANYMORE?
>> NO.
I'M GONNA GO AND DROP OUT,
AND THEN I CAN STAY HOME ALL DAY
WITH MY BABY GIRL.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
BESIDES--I MEAN, INSTEAD OF
GOING TO TCC?
>> I'M GONNA FIND SOMETHING
TO DO, LIKE, SO I CAN GET--
LIKE, MAKE MONEY AND STUFF
BUT NOT BE AWAY FROM HER FOR
FOUR YEARS FOR A CAREER I DON'T
WANT TO DO.
AND MONEY COULD HELP RIGHT NOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT IT?
EVEN THOUGH I'M STILL
GONNA DO IT, LIKE, REGARDLESS.
>> SO IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER.
LIKE, IF THAT'S REALLY WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO.
I KNOW YOU DON'T LIKE TO,
LIKE, QUIT AT ANYTHING, SO...
WHEN ARE YOU DOING IT?
>> LIKE, TODAY.
>> BALANCING COLLEGE COURSES
AND BEING A MOM IS TOO HARD.
SO I'M ENROLLING IN A SIX-WEEK
TRAINING PROGRAM TO LEARN
MEDICAL BILLING
AND DROPPING OUT OF SCHOOL.
>> SO WHAT BRINGS YOU IN TODAY?
>> I WANTED TO DROP THE CLASSES
I'M IN NOW.
>> WHAT DRAWS YOU TO THAT
CONCLUSION?
>> I WAS KEEPING UP MY GRADES
AND EVERYTHING, BUT I WOULD JUST
RATHER RIGHT NOW SPEND MORE TIME
WITH HER THAN IN CLASS.
>> YEAH.
WOULD THERE BE ANY CHANCE
IF YOU JUST WANTED TO WITHDRAW
OUT OF ONE?
>> I'M JUST GONNA WITHDRAW
OUT OF ALL OF THEM.
>> OKAY, ONCE YOU SELECT
YOUR CLASSES, THEN YOU JUST HIT
"DROP" AGAIN.
OKAY.
>> MY CLASSES HAVE BEEN DROPPED.
>> LOOKS LIKE YOU DROPPED THEM.
>> SEE, YOU GOT MAMA TO CHANGE
HER WHOLE LIFE PLAN.
BUT I GUESS I'LL FORGIVE YOU.
DROPPING MY CLASSES SUCKED.
NOW I GOT TO TELL MY DAD.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
PURSE, GET IT TOGETHER.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON WITH SCHOOL?
>> I GOT A 3.5 OUT OF 4 POINTS
ON A ENGLISH ESSAY.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> YEAH, IT IS GOOD.
I'M DROPPING OUT, THOUGH.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE DOING SO WELL?
>> YEAH, I'M JUST GONNA DO
MEDICAL BILLING, 'CAUSE IT TAKES
SIX WEEKS TO GET IT, AND IT
MAKES A LOT OF GOOD MONEY.
>> AND YOU THINK THAT'S WHAT
YOU'RE GONNA WANT TO DO FOR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE?
>> DOESN'T MATTER IF I WANT
TO DO IT OR NOT.
I'M GONNA BE A MOMMY MOST
OF THE TIME.
>> YES, I KNOW.
BUT I'M CONCERNED ABOUT
FUTURE LIZZIE, THE ONE THAT'S
NOT GONNA BE HAPPY THAT SHE
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL.
>> OKAY, WELL, FUTURE LIZZIE
WILL BE HAPPY WITH SUMMER.
>> OH, YOU THINK THAT NOW,
BUT I'M TELLING YOU,
IN THE LONG RUN, YOU'RE GONNA
FIND OUT THAT'S NOT THE TRUTH.
I TOLD YOU YOU SHOULDN'T SIGN UP
FOR COLLEGE CLASSES SO SOON.
>> BUT I HAVE "A"s IN MY COLLEGE
CLASSES, SO IT'S OBVIOUSLY NOT
THAT I'M DOING BAD IN THEM.
>> BUT IT'S A LOT FOR YOU TO TRY
TO TAKE ON AT ONE TIME.
>> I COULD DO IT PERFECTLY FINE.
I JUST WOULD RATHER BE WITH HER
THAN GO TO CLASS AND HAVE HER.
>> BUT BEFORE YOU HAD HER,
YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD
HANDLE IT ALL.
SOMEDAY WHEN YOUR DAUGHTER
DECIDES SHE DOESN'T WANT TO GO
TO COLLEGE, YOU'LL UNDERSTAND.
>> I WANT HER TO BE HAPPY.
IF COLLEGE DOESN'T MAKE HER
HAPPY, THEN SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO.
>> BUT THE--
[clears throat]
I WISH, WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE,
I WAS NEARLY AS SMART AS YOU,
'CAUSE ALL THE THINGS THAT
I THOUGHT I KNEW TURNED OUT
TO BE WRONG.
>> IF SHE EVER FINISHES THIS
BOTTLE, DO YOU WANT TO GO
FOR A WALK?
>> SURE.
>> YOU GET TO GO IN YOUR
STROLLER.
ARE YOU DONE?
EVEN THOUGH SKYLAR IS
DISAPPOINTED THAT I DROPPED OUT
OF COLLEGE, HE STILL WANTS ME
TO BE HAPPY, AND SO DO I.
>> [groans]
>> SO HOW DO YOU LIKE
BEING A DADDY?
>> I LOVE IT.
>> REALLY, NOW?
>> YES.
>> BEST 19-YEAR-OLD DADDY
I KNOW.
>> [laughs]
WHY DO YOU THINK THAT?
>> BECAUSE YOU HELP ME IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
AND YOU TAKE HER WHEN I NEED
A BREAK, AND YOU FEED HER
AND PLAY WITH HER, AND Y'ALL
BOND SO FABULOUSLY.
>> * COULD YOU WAIT FOR A DAY?
>> BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
I HAD A BUNCH OF DREAMS:
TO GO TO MY SENIOR YEAR
AND DO ALL THE HIGH SCHOOL
THINGS LIKE HOMECOMING
AND SENIOR PROM,
AND MY BIGGEST DREAM WAS TO
PLAY THE FLUTE IN THE VIRGINIA
SYMPHONY.
AND THEN I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, AND THAT DREAM JUST
KIND OF DIED.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA OF
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
>> NOPE, JUST SOMETHING THAT
MAKES PRETTY GOOD MONEY.
AND I GUESS HAVING A BABY AT 17
TOTALLY FLIPPED ALL MY PLANS
FOR THE FUTURE.
I'M NOT IN COLLEGE ANYMORE.
I'M NOT GOING INTO MUSIC
ANYMORE.
I'M PROBABLY GONNA LIVE AT HOME
A LITTLE BIT LONGER INSTEAD
OF A DORM.
LET'S ASK DADDY IF HE'LL GO
MAKE YOU A BOTTLE.
I THINK THEY SHOULD BE DONE
IN THE DISHWASHER NOW.
AND IT'S BUMMED ME OUT
A COUPLE TIMES, BUT THEN I'LL
THINK ABOUT IT, AND I'LL THINK
OF SUMMER, AND IN MY MIND,
WHAT I'M DOING BEING A MOM
IS FAR MORE IMPORTANT THAN
JUST GOING OUT AND HAVING FUN.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN I WANT
SUMMER TO BE A MOM AT 17.
I WANT HER TO STILL GO TO
COLLEGE AND HAVE HER TEENAGE
YEARS.
>> SO HAVE YOUR DREAMS CHANGED
A LOT?
>> YEAH.
BEFORE HER, I WANTED TO BE,
LIKE, A MUSICIAN.
THE ROUGHEST PART ABOUT HAVING
A BABY RIGHT NOW IS JUST
WORRYING ABOUT MONEY,
BECAUSE I DON'T HAVE A JOB
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S FORMULA, $33;
DIAPERS, $20; GAS DROPS, $15;
WIPES, $7;
LOVING OUR DAUGHTER, PRICELESS.
IF I COULD GO BACK TO WHEN
IT ALL HAPPENED, I WOULD
DEFINITELY HAVE WAITED,
AND I WOULD HAVE JUST WANTED
TO WAIT, LIKE, FIVE YEARS.
>> HE MUST BE DOING GOOD WITH
SUMMER, OR LIZZIE WOULD BE
SAYING SOMETHING.
>> YEP.
>> SHE'S NOT ONE TO KEEP IT
TO HERSELF.
OF COURSE, IT GETS HARDER AND
HARDER AS THEY GET OLDER
AND OLDER.
>> IN THE FUTURE, EVERYTHING'S
NOT GONNA BE PERFECT.
WE'LL HAVE OUR PROBLEMS,
BUT I CAN ONLY SEE THEM
MAKING US STRONGER AS A COUPLE.
BUT RIGHT NOW, I'M FOCUSING
MOSTLY ON BEING A GOOD MOM.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> female announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT...
>> YOU THINK IT WILL HIDE
A PREGNANCY?
>> ARE YOU HIDING IN YOUR BAGGY
CLOTHES?
>> I JUST LOOK FAT RIGHT NOW.
>> NO, AS A FRIEND TO A FRIEND,
YOU LOOK PREGNANT.
>> THIS IS WHAT HE DOES.
HE SHUTS ME OUT.
>> YOU ARE THE FATHER
OF THAT CHILD.
>> IT WAS YOUR DECISION TO MAKE.
>> YEAH.
>> HER DECISION.
>> HER DECISION, JONATHAN?
>> [groaning]
OH, MY GOD.
YOU LEFT THE MILK OUT AGAIN.
>> SHUT THE [...] UP.
>> JOE!
[sobbing]
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW
* I'M GONNA GET THROUGH IT ALL
* AND I'M WEAK
* BUT I'M STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE