>> [giggles]
HI, I'M JORDAN.
I'M 17 YEARS OLD
AND FROM LANCASTER,
PENNSYLVANIA.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM,
TWO BROTHERS, AND LITTLE SISTER.
[hisses]
AFTER I GRADUATE HIGH SCHOOL
NEXT YEAR, I WANT TO GO TO
A TRADE SCHOOL AND GET CERTIFIED
AS A DENTAL HYGIENIST.
BUT FOR NOW, I LIKE TO HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS AT THE SKATING
RINK OR JUST CHILL AT THE POOL.
HEY, GIRL.
BUT I HAVEN'T SEEN THEM MUCH
THIS SUMMER BECAUSE I'VE BEEN
SPENDING SO MUCH TIME
WITH MY BOYFRIEND TYLER.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> [laughter]
TYLER'S KIND OF A LONER,
AND ISN'T VERY POPULAR
WITH THE KIDS AT SCHOOL.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
HE'S NOT AN ASS.
HE'S NOT A PERSON
TO CHEAT ON YOU.
>> JORDAN LIKES THOSE TYPE
OF BOYS SHE SAID.
THAT'S HER TYPE.
>> MY FRIENDS UNDERSTAND
WHY I LIKE TYLER,
BUT MY MOM DOESN'T GET IT.
>> I MEAN, I KNOW YOU LIKE HIM
OR WHATEVER,
BUT HE'S NOBODY THAT I WOULD
WANT TO HAVE AROUND ME.
>> SHE DOESN'T LIKE THAT
I'M DATING A WHITE GUY, AND SHE
WON'T EVEN LET HIM IN OUR HOUSE.
BUT I REALLY LOVE TYLER.
AND HE'S HERE TO STAY...
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
I'VE BEEN SLEEPING OVER
AT TYLER'S HOUSE
FOR THE PAST FEW WEEKS.
>> [blows raspberry]
>> [chuckles]
MY MOM DOESN'T LIKE IT
AND STILL FORBIDS TYLER
TO COME TO OUR HOUSE.
BUT SHE WORKS A GRAVEYARD SHIFT,
SO SHE'S LETTING ME STAY HERE
IN CASE I NEED TO GET TO
THE HOSPITAL AT NIGHT.
TYLER IS ALREADY OUT OF SCHOOL
FOR THE SUMMER.
AND I'M FINISHING MY LAST FEW
WEEKS OF JUNIOR YEAR FROM HOME.
SO WE'VE BEEN SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER.
REMEMBER SCIENCE CLASS
WHEN EVERYBODY WAS LIKE, "ARE
YOU GUYS DATING EACH OTHER?"
AND I WAS LIKE, "NO.
WHY WOULD I DATE TYLER?"
>> I WOULD, LIKE, TELL PEOPLE,
"YEAH, WE'RE DATING,"
'CAUSE I THOUGHT IF
I GOT EVERYONE THINKING WE WERE,
THEN YOU WOULD GO WITH IT.
>> [laughs]
NO.
>> LIKE, JUST THE WAY
YOU WOULD TALK TO ME, THE WAY
YOU WOULD BE AROUND ME, TO ME,
IT SEEMED LIKE YOU LIKED ME
BUT YOU WOULDN'T TELL ME.
LIKE, MOST PEOPLE JUST KIND OF
TALK TO ME A COUPLE TIMES
AND IT'S LIKE, WHATEVER.
'CAUSE I HONESTLY JUST DIDN'T
THINK GIRLS--OTHER GIRLS WOULD
REALLY THINK ABOUT ME LIKE THAT.
>> BUT YOU JUST WAS THE
BOYFRIEND I WOULD DREAM OF.
YOU JUST CATERED TO ME,
AND I DIDN'T HAVE TO ASK.
OR ANY TIME I CALLED YOU,
YOU PICKED UP YOUR PHONE.
>> BUT THEN, LIKE, THE MORE
AND MORE I WOULD BE WITH YOU,
MY HEART WAS SLOWLY
GOING TO YOU.
>> DID YOU EVER THINK ANYTHING
ABOUT ME BEING BLACK?
HIT YOU AT ALL?
>> TO ME, YOU'RE JUST
A CUTE GIRL AT SCHOOL
THAT WOULD ALWAYS GET--
LIKE, TALK TO ME.
>> DID IT BUG YOU AT ALL THAT
YOU COULDN'T COME TO MY HOUSE
BEFORE AND EVEN NOW?
YOU'RE, LIKE, THE FATHER
OF MY CHILD AND YOU STILL
CAN'T COME TO MY HOUSE.
>> IT DOES BUG ME.
>> I REALLY WANT ME AND TYLER TO
RAISE THIS BABY TOGETHER, BUT
MY MOM DOESN'T SEE IT THAT WAY.
>> SO WHAT ALL DO WE NEED?
ANY BABY STUFF SPECIFICALLY?
>> NO, WELL,
WE HAVE A PACK 'N PLAY.
SO WE HAVE ALL THE CLOTHES
AND STUFF.
>> SO YOU KNOW ONCE YOU HAVE HIM
THAT'S IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE COMING HOME.
I ALLOWED YOU THERE FOR SAFETY
REASONS SO THEY CAN GET YOU TO
THE HOSPITAL, BUT YOUSE ARE
COMING HOME, NO IF ANDS OR BUTS.
SO MAKE IT CLEAR WITH THEM
SO THEY'RE NOT SHOCKED.
>> WELL, HOW IS TY
GONNA SEE HIS BABY?
>> I DON'T REALLY SEE HIM
AS BEING A BIG PARTICIPATOR,
TO BE HONEST.
I REALLY DON'T WANT HIM HERE.
>> WHY NOT?
>> WELL, FOR STARTERS, HE'S
DIRTY, HE'S DIRTY-LOOKING, HE'S
DISRESPECTFUL, I DON'T LIKE HIM.
>> SO WHAT ABOUT
DURING THE NIGHT?
SO IT'S JUST ALL THIS
AND NOT TYLER?
TYLER CAN'T HELP IN,
PITCH IN OR ANYTHING?
IT JUST HAS TO BE UP TO US?
>> WHAT?
YOU WANT HIM TO COME HERE
AT NIGHT?
OH, HELL, NO.
YOU KNOW THAT'D NEVER, EVER--
YOU KNOW SHACKING UP
DON'T HAPPEN HERE.
AND I TOLD YOU BEFORE, WHEN YOU
HAVE THAT BABY, YOUR VISITS
AND STAYING OVER THERE BEFORE
YOU GIVE BIRTH IS GONNA STOP
IMMEDIATELY.
AS SOON AS WE
GET IN THE HOSPITAL.
YOU REMEMBER TYLER'S FACE THAT
DAY WHEN YOU TOLD ME OUTSIDE
ABOUT YOU--WHEN YOU GUYS
TOLD ME YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> DID YOU KNOW THAT WE WERE
GONNA TELL YOU?
>> I KNEW WHERE YOU WERE GOING
WITH IT, BECAUSE I STARTED
NOTICING THE BIGGER BRA SIZE
OR THE BOOB SIZE CHANGE,
YOUR SLEEPING CHANGE,
YOUR EATING CHANGE,
I NOTICED,
BUT I DIDN'T WANT TO NOTICE.
I KIND OF DIDN'T THINK YOU WOULD
GO THAT ROUTE WITH HIM.
SO I THINK IT WAS MY
RESPONSIBILITY TO PROBABLY
COME TO YOU TO GET YOU
ON A TYPE OF BIRTH CONTROL.
BUT ONCE YOU--I SEEN HIM,
I DEFINITELY DIDN'T THINK YOU
WOULD BE INTIMATE WITH HIM.
BUT YOU KNOW, I TOLD YOU
YOU HAD AN OPTION AT THE TIME,
AND THEN YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T
WANT TO GET RID OF IT.
>> NOT THAT I'M AGAINST
ABORTIONS, UM...
>> BUT THAT'S YOUR PREROGATIVE.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
THAT'S JUST WHAT I JUST--I JUST
PERSONALLY COULDN'T DO IT.
beep!
>> WHO'S IT FROM?
>> TY.
HE SAYS THAT HE'S HERE.
>> JUST MAKE SURE
HE STAYS OUT THERE.
>> THERE'S NO WAY THIS IS
GONNA WORK IF TYLER ISN'T EVEN
ALLOWED IN MY HOUSE.
HEY, TY.
>> HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WE RECENTLY FOUND OUT
WE'RE HAVING A BOY,
AND WE'RE NAMING HIM CHASE.
TYLER SAYS HE'S READY
TO BE A FATHER, BUT IF I LIVE
AT MY MOM'S HOUSE,
THAT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY.
LUCKILY, TYLER'S PARENTS HAVE
BEEN MORE SUPPORTIVE.
>> HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
>> WHAT'S UP?
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
>> TALK TO HER.
>> SO WHAT'S UP?
>> NEVER AGAIN.
I HATE GOING OVER THERE.
THERE'S ALWAYS SOME DRAMA.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> MY MOM.
[both laugh]
>> YOUR MOM HAPPENED.
>> YOUR MOM HAPPENS, YEAH.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW HOW EVERY TIME
I GO HOME, MOM'S ALWAYS LIKE,
"TY WON'T GET TO SEE THE BABY."
BECAUSE SHE HAS A PROBLEM
WITH TYLER, AND IT'S JUST
A HUGE CONFLICT.
>> WELL, WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I WANT TO STAY HERE; NOT GO
OVER THERE, 'CAUSE IF I GO OVER
THERE, SHE'S GONNA BE LIKE,
"ME, ME, ME, ME, ME.
MY, MY, MY, MY, MY.
MY WAY, NOT YOUR WAY."
>> [grumbles]
SHE JUST SEEMS LIKE THE KIND OF
PERSON WHO'S JUST GONNA TRY AND
TELL YOU HOW IT IS.
AND GONNA TRY AND CONTROL
HOW OUR SON IS RAISED.
SO--
>> WELL, YOU KNOW,
WE NEED YOU TO BE SURE OF
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT YOU ALREADY KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT.
>> I DEFINITELY WANT TO
STAY HERE.
>> AND YOU KNOW YOU HAVE
THAT OPTION, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I JUST DON'T HAVE, LIKE,
THE BALLS TO TELL MY MOM.
>> DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
AND WE'LL FIGURE IT ALL OUT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO
BE PREPARED THOUGH,
'CAUSE SHE IS GONNA BE MAD.
>> WELL, THANK YOUSE.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> DON'T FORGET,
YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOME.
>> ALWAYS WELCOME HERE.
YOU NEVER HAVE TO WORRY.
>> THANK YOU GUYS.
MY FEET HURT.
TYLER.
>> THE WAY I SEE IT,
YOUR MOM HAS A CHOICE HERE.
LIKE, SHE CAN BE ACCEPTING OF
YOUR DECISION TO BE HERE AND
JUST TRY TO BE THE GRANDMOTHER--
>> WHAT IF SHE GETS THE COPS
INVOLVED WHEN WE TELL HER THAT
WE'RE TAKING THE BABY HERE?
>> I'LL FIGHT HER TO THE DEATH.
LIKE, SHE IS NOT GONNA
KEEP MY SON AWAY FROM ME.
>> ARE YOU SCARED?
>> I'M NERVOUS, BUT I MEAN,
I'M NOT BACKING DOWN.
>> OUR BABY'S DUE IN LESS THAN
A MONTH, AND I'M A LITTLE
FREAKED OUT BY MY DECISION
TO LIVE AT TYLER'S HOUSE.
NOT ONLY AM I SCARED
TO TELL MY MOM...
>> TY.
>> BUT WE DON'T HAVE
ANY OF THE STUFF WE NEED
FOR WHEN THE BABY COMES HOME.
>> WHERE ARE WE GOING?
>> WE'RE GOING TO GET CLOTHES.
>> LIKE--
>> BABY CLOTHES.
>> ONESIES, BIBS.
>> ALL THAT GOOD STUFF.
>> LET'S GO.
>> TYLER, DO YOU HAVE
YOUR WALLET?
>> YEP.
>> TYLER ALREADY SPENT A LOT OF
HIS SAVINGS ON BABY SUPPLIES.
HE EVEN PAID $300
FOR THE CRIB I WANTED.
BUT ALL THAT STUFF
IS OVER AT MY MOM'S HOUSE.
AND SHE'LL NEVER
LET US TAKE IT TO TYLER'S.
SO I'M MEETING MY FRIEND EMILY
TO SHOP FOR SOME CLOTHES
AND MAYBE A BASSINET
FOR THE BABY TO SLEEP IN.
>> HEY, GIRL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
>> LIKE, CLOTHES.
I WANT NEWBORN STUFF.
I HAVE ALL THIS OTHER STUFF
FOR LATER ON, BUT--
>> JORDAN.
>> TYLER.
>> COME HERE.
>> BABE, WILL YOU LOOK AT THIS?
>> WHAT'S THIS?
>> THIS IS LIKE A BASSINET,
RIGHT?
>> I GUESS.
>> I THINK THERE'S A BASSINET
OVER HERE TOO.
>> YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
>> HOW MUCH IS IT?
>> DUCKIES.
>> THIS IS, LIKE, 55 BUCKS.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY?
LIKE, ISN'T THAT A BIT PRICEY?
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> IS THE BABY GONNA STAY
AT YOUR HOUSE, TYLER,
OR AT JORDAN'S?
>> YEAH.
HE'S STAYING WITH US.
>> MY MOM WANTS IT AT HER HOUSE.
>> IS YOUR MOM GONNA BE MAD
THAT, LIKE, HE'S GONNA STAY
WITH TYLER AND YOU GUYS?
>> YEAH.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE TYLER.
>> WHY DOESN'T SHE LIKE TYLER?
>> WHY DO YOU THINK?
>> YOU'RE WHITE.
>> OH.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> LIKE, WHEN I FIRST MET HER,
SHE KIND OF LOOKED AT ME LIKE,
"OH, YOU'RE WHITE?"
>> "HOW IS HE GONNA
RAISE A BLACK BABY?
I MEAN, LIKE, SOME KID'S GONNA
BE LIKE, 'YEAH, WHAT'S UP?'
AND HE'S GONNA BE LIKE,
'WHAT'S UP?'"
YOU KNOW?
[both laugh]
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> THE TRUTH IS, MY MOM
WASN'T THE ONLY ONE SURPRISED
WHEN WE GOT TOGETHER.
MY FRIENDS DIDN'T EXPECT IT
EITHER.
>> OKAY, NO OFFENSE, BUT...
[laughter]
I BET HER MOM--I WAS LIKE, "OH,
MY GOSH, WHAT DID YOUR MOM SAY?"
>> "I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THIS
WITH TYLER."
LIKE, EVERYBODY SAYS, "TYLER.
OH, MY GOSH, HIM?"
>> WATCH HIM TURN OUT
AS THE BEST DAD.
>> YEAH, I THINK HE WILL BE.
BUT MY MOM THINKS THAT
AS SOON AS I HAVE THE BABY,
WE'RE GONNA GO TO HER HOUSE.
IT'S A SMALL HOUSE--
>> IS SHE GONNA LET TY
SLEEP OVER AND STUFF?
>> NO.
NO.
NO, TY ISN'T EVEN ALLOWED
INTO THE HOUSE.
BUT WHEN I AM IN THE HOSPITAL,
I'M GONNA TELL HER
THAT I'M STAYING WITH TYLER.
>> DON'T YOU THINK--
YOU KNOW, IN THE DELIVERY ROOM,
THAT'S KIND OF LIKE--
>> THAT'S, LIKE, LAST MINUTE.
>> LAST MINUTE.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> THAT'S NOT PERFECT.
THAT'S THE WAY
TO START ARGUMENTS.
>> DON'T YOU THINK
SHE'S GONNA BE REALLY MAD?
>> REALLY MAD.
>> BUT THEN I COULD
KICK HER OUT OF THE ROOM.
>> DO YOU WANT ALL THAT CONFLICT
IN THE BABY ROOM THOUGH?
>> EXACTLY.
>> NO, NO.
YOU SHOULD JUST TELL HER NOW.
YOUR MOM WILL SEE IT BETTER
IF IT'S IN YOUR POINT OF VIEW
AND YOU TELL HER, LIKE,
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT IT.
>> SHE DON'T CARE.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW?
>> EXACTLY.
>> SHE TOLD ME...
SHE DIDN'T CARE.
I GUESS YOU HAVE GOOD POINTS
THOUGH.
>> LIKE, I UNDERSTAND
YOU'RE SCARED, BUT...
EITHER WAY, YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> I KNOW TELLING MY MOM
ABOUT OUR PLANS
IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
BUT I'M JUST TOO SCARED
OF HOW SHE'LL REACT.
>> SURPRISE!
>> OH, MY GOD.
WE WERE JUST LOOKING AT THIS.
>> WERE YOU?
>> YEAH.
OH, LOOK, IT HAS WHEELS, BABE.
>> DID YOU GUYS GET ANY CLOTHES
OR ANYTHING?
>> YEAH, WE BOUGHT A JACKET
'CAUSE WE'RE GONNA HAVE
THE JACKET THAT'S LIKE,
HIS SIZE RIGHT NOW.
>> DO YOU WANT TO TAKE YOUR
BASSINET IN AND SET IT UP?
>> I'M GLAD TYLER'S PARENTS
ARE WILLING TO SUPPORT US
WHILE WE LIVE HERE.
BUT I'M STARTING TO WORRY
ABOUT RAISING THIS BABY
WITHOUT ANY HELP FROM MY MOM.
MY MOM CALLED AND SAID SHE
NEEDED TO SEE ME TODAY.
I DON'T WANT TO GO,
BECAUSE THERE'S ALWAYS DRAMA
WHEN I'M OVER THERE,
BUT SHE SAID IT WAS IMPORTANT.
>> DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING?
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE JUST GOING OVER
TO HANG OUT?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN I COME IN
AND HANG OUT A LITTLE BIT?
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
NO.
THAT'S LIKE ASKING ME,
DO I WANT TO GO SKYDIVING
WITH YOU RIGHT NOW?
>> WELL, DO YOU THINK MAYBE
IF YOU TALK WITH YOUR MOM
THAT SHE WOULD--
>> NOPE.
>> THAT'S JUST SO JUST--
[sighs]
>> DOES THAT BUG YOU?
>> YEAH, IT DOES.
LIKE, YOU'RE HAVING MY KID.
I JUST HATE THIS.
I MEAN--
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
>> BYE.
>> all: SURPRISE!
>> DANG!
THIS IS PACKED!
[laughter]
OH, THIS IS SO NICE.
THANKS, MOM...
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> SO MUCH.
DON'T FALL OVER.
[indistinct speech]
HEY.
WHAT'S THIS BEHIND YOU?
>> IT'S A SET UP.
>> PRESENTS.
>> WHAT KATHY SET UP.
>> "IT'S SO NICE TO SHARE IN
THIS HAPPY TIME WITH YOU.
BEST WISHES TO BABY AND YOU."
OH, DANG.
SHE GOT ME THE SET?
OH, THAT'S A BIG BAG.
OH, YEAH?
>> SMELLING GOOD.
>> OH.
YES, I NEED THESE.
CAN NEVER GET TOO MANY DIAPERS.
OH, THAT IS SO CUTE.
LOOK AT THIS.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
>> SO WHEN YOU DUE?
>> MAY 29.
IT'S, LIKE, IN TWO WEEKS EXACT.
>> YOU'LL BE SITTING THERE
PUSHING A LOT.
PUSHING.
[all laugh]
>> I'M DEFINITELY GETTING
AN EPIDURAL.
>> AND TYLER, LIKE, I JUST THINK
YOU'LL BE WITH SOMEBODY CUTE.
[laughter]
CUTER, YOU KNOW.
>> I WAS LIKE, "THAT'S--
THAT'S HER BOYFRIEND?"
[laughter]
I MEAN, I MEAN, LIKE,
I SAY, OPPOSITES--YOU KNOW,
YOU GUYS ARE OPPOSITES,
BUT I GUESS OPPOSITES ATTRACT
IN THIS CASE.
[laughter]
>> I CAME OVER HERE TO TALK.
I'M GONNA GO GET MY GRUB ON.
I'M TIRED OF ALWAYS HAVING
TO STICK UP FOR TYLER,
WITH MY FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
I TRY NOT TO LET IT
BOTHER ME ANYMORE.
BUT SOMETIMES MY MOM
GOES TOO FAR.
>> SO WHAT'S THE--
WHAT'S THE WORD?
HOW'S IT GOING ON OVER THERE?
WHAT'S--
>> NOTHING.
NOTHING'S CHANGED.
>> WELL, YOU JUST MENTIONED THAT
SHE GOT YOU A BASSINET.
>> OH, YEAH.
UH, SHE SAID THAT SHE GOT IT
FROM--OH, I DON'T KNOW
WHERE IT WAS, BUT--
>> I DON'T CARE WHERE SHE GOT IT
FROM, BUT I MEAN, WHY DID JEN
GET YOU A BASSINET?
>> OH, FOR HER HOUSE.
>> OH.
IT AIN'T GONNA GET USED.
[laughter]
YOU BETTER TELL HER.
I DON'T WANT TO WASTE HER MONEY.
BECAUSE IT WON'T GET USED
OVER THERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> NOT SO GOOD WITH
THE CLEANLINESS LIKE I AM.
>> OH.
>> WHAT?
>> OOH.
>> NO, SHE JUST WANTS TO BE
MOMMY WHEN I HAVE THE BABY,
BASICALLY.
>> WELL, LET'S REMEMBER YOU'RE
MINE, AND WHAT'S YOURS IS MINE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, OKAY.
>> I CAN EVEN DECIDE
ON THE DRUGS YOU GET.
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
>> OKAY, THEN--
>> I HAVE TO SIGN PAPERS
FOR THAT.
>> OH, WE KNOW.
THEN JUST DROP IT THEN.
[indistinct speech]
>> IT'S NOT YOUR KID.
WHERE'S MY BAG?
>> BUT YOU'RE MY KID.
>> UM, HEY, JUST BE READY
TO COME GET ME 'CAUSE MY MOM'S
BEING HERSELF RIGHT NOW,
YOU KNOW.
SHE WANTS TO MAKE A BIG-ASS
SCENE ABOUT HOW BIG BOSS SHE IS,
AND HOW ALL THE POWER SHE HAS.
>> SHE DON'T WANT TO
CHALLENGE ME.
YOU KNOW I LOVE A CHALLENGE.
I LOVE A CHALLENGE.
YOU KNOW THAT.
>> ARE YOU LEAVING?
ARE YOU LEAVING?
>> YOU'RE LEAVING NOW?
>> YEAH.
BYE.
I DIDN'T SEE YOU--
>> YOU STILL HAVE FRIENDS HERE.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW
ANY OF THESE GIRLS.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
[scoffs]
SHE'S LIKE, "I'M LEAVING."
>> SHE ALWAYS DOES THIS [bleep].
ALWAYS MAKES A [bleep] BIG DEAL
OUT OF NOTHING.
YOU'RE GONNA INVITE ME OVER,
TALK [bleep] ABOUT ME,
MY BABY'S DADDY, AND LIKE--
>> SHE WAS TALKING [bleep]
ABOUT ME?
>> TY, COME ON.
IT'S--
>> YEAH, I KNOW, BUT LIKE,
AT THE BABY SHOWER--YOUR BABY
SHOWER WITH ALL YOUR FRIENDS.
>> SHE ALWAYS DOES THIS.
>> TYLER'S PARENTS COULD TELL
I WAS PRETTY UPSET AFTER
MY SURPRISE BABY SHOWER
YESTERDAY.
SO THEY WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED.
LIKE, IF NOTHING GOES HER WAY,
YOU KNOW, SHE WANTS TO PROVE
HOW BIG BOSS SHE IS.
SHE SAID, "YOU'RE GONNA NEED ME
FOR EVERYTHING,
FOR THE EPIDURAL.
YOU CAN'T EVEN GET THE EPIDURAL
UNLESS A PARENT
IS THERE TO SIGN FOR IT."
>> WELL, WHAT KIND OF MOTHER
CALLS UP HER DAUGHTER AND GOES,
"HA, HA, HA, YOU'RE GONNA NEED
MY SIGNATURE, AND I'M NOT
GONNA GIVE IT TO YOU.
TOO BAD, SWEETIE."
FOR A FREAKING EPIDURAL.
>> ONE THAT'S THREE CARDS SHY OF
A FULL DECK, IF YOU ASK ME.
>> SHE JUST THINKS THAT SHE'S
GONNA BREAK JORDAN AND JORDAN'S
GONNA CONFORM TO HER, AND
THAT'S THE WAY IT'S GONNA BE.
>> WHAT DO YOU PLAN ON DOING
WITH THE CRIB THAT TYLER BOUGHT
YOU THAT'S ALREADY OVER THERE?
>> I WANT TO GO GET IT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND HE BOUGHT IT FOR YOU.
HE DIDN'T BUY IT FOR YOUR MOM.
>> SHE THINKS SHE HAS POWER OVER
HER BECAUSE SHE HAS THIS CRIB.
AND WHEN ARE YOU GONNA TAKE AWAY
THAT POWER?
>> EVEN THOUGH WE HAVE A
BASSINET, I CAN'T JUST LET MY
MOM KEEP THE CRIB TYLER BOUGHT
FOR HIS BABY.
BUT IF WE'RE EVER GONNA SEE IT
AGAIN, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO TAKE
IT WHEN SHE'S NOT AROUND.
SO THE NEXT MORNING, WE DECIDED
TO GO GET IT BEFORE MY MOM GETS
HOME FROM THE GRAVEYARD SHIFT.
>> READY?
>> SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
MOVE FAST.
>> SO IS THE GAME PLAN
THE USUAL--
>> HURRY THE HELL UP
AND GET THERE.
>> I'M GOING AS FAST AS I CAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO GET THIS DONE.
>> DO YOU HAVE THE PIECES?
>> THE TOOLS?
>> YES.
>> YES, THEY'RE IN MY HAND.
>> PHEW.
>> [grunting]
>> TY.
I HAVE ANOTHER PIECE.
HURRY UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> HURRY UP.
GET IT DONE.
>> GOT THE OTHER BIG PIECE.
>> ONE MORE PIECE.
>> IS THAT--
THAT'S IT THEN, RIGHT?
>> THAT'S IT.
LET'S BOUNCE. HURRY UP.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S ROLL.
HIGH FIVE.
>> WE GOT THE CRIB.
YAY!
I LOVE THIS CRIB.
>> DON'T YOU FEEL LIKE
WE'RE HAVING A BABY NOW?
I THINK THERE'S MAGIC
ON THIS CRIB OR SOMETHING.
>> MAYBE KNOWING THAT
YOU GOT THIS FOR ME
MADE IT MORE VALUABLE.
>> EVEN IF SHE DOES TRY TO,
LIKE, PRESS CHARGES, WHATEVER,
I'M JUST GONNA BE LIKE,
"YOU SERIOUS?"
THAT'S MY MONEY
THAT PAID FOR IT.
>> I'M GLAD WE HAVE THE CRIB
AT TYLER'S HOUSE NOW.
BUT I'M SCARED OF WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN WHEN MY MOM
REALIZES IT'S GONE.
>> HI JORDAN.
>> HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I HAVE SOMETHING SO COOL
TO SHOW YOU.
ALL RIGHT, KEEP WALKING.
KEEP WALKING.
SMACK.
>> [laughs]
>> OKAY, NOW, OPEN UP YOUR EYES.
BOOM.
>> OH.
YOU GOT THE CRIB ALL READY.
IT LOOKS SO NICE.
>> THIS WAS IN MY HOUSE.
>> SO LIKE, IS ALL THE STUFF
FROM YOUR MOM'S HOUSE HERE?
>> NO, THIS IS WHAT HE BOUGHT.
>> WHAT DOES YOUR MOM THINK
ABOUT THE CRIB BEING HERE?
>> I HONESTLY DON'T THINK
SHE KNOWS YET.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> IT WAS IN MY ROOM.
>> [laughs]
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GONNA
HAPPEN WHEN YOUR MOM FINDS OUT?
>> I THINK SHE'S GONNA BE LIKE,
"I'M GONNA CALL THE COPS."
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
SHE ALWAYS DOES.
>> SHE SHOULDN'T CALL THE COPS
THOUGH.
>> WELL, THAT'S MY MOM.
[phone beeps]
OH, WOW.
I HAVE A VOICEMAIL
AND TWO MISSED CALLS.
>> WHO ARE THEY FROM?
>> MY MOM.
>> FIRST UNHEARD MESSAGE.
>> YOU [bleep] SLIMEBALL.
YOU MOVED THAT [bleep] CRIB OUT?
WHO CARRIED THE CRIB OUT?
I KNOW IT WASN'T YOU.
DID YOU HAVE TYLER IN MY HOUSE?
YOU'RE JUST TOTALLY
DISRESPECTFUL.
SEE, I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO BE NICE ABOUT THIS.
DO YOU REALLY THINK I WOULD...
>> NICE ABOUT WHAT?
>> LET THAT BABY MOVE IN THERE
SO YOU COULD PLAY HOUSE?
YOU'RE PUTTING A LOT OF PEOPLE
IN A BAD SITUATION.
NOW, YOU THOUGHT IT WAS TALK
AND TALK AND TALK.
NO, I'M GONNA SHOW YOU THE WALK,
WALK, THE REAL WALK.
BECAUSE THIS IS [bleep],
WHAT YOU JUST PULLED
WITH THAT LITTLE [bleep].
>> WOW.
>> YEP. OH, WELL.
ANYWAYS...
IT'S STRESSFUL.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> NOW I'M JUST GONNA
RELY ON TYLER.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I MEAN, LIKE,
SAY I NEVER TOOK THE CRIB
AND STAYED AT MY HOUSE.
THINGS WOULD BE THE SAME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SO WHY NOT TRY
A DIFFERENT METHOD?
I NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD
COME TO THIS
BETWEEN ME AND MY MOM.
I JUST CAN'T LET HER CUT TYLER
OUT OF MY LIFE.
[cell phone ringing]
>> MY DUE DATE IS JUST A WEEK
AWAY, AND I HAVEN'T ANSWERED
ANY OF MY MOM'S CALLS
SINCE SHE LEFT
THAT NASTY MESSAGE.
I FINISHED ALL OF
MY SCHOOL ASSIGNMENTS,
AND I'M OFFICIALLY A SENIOR.
SO I'M MEETING MY FRIENDS
AT THE LIBRARY TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT CLASSES WE'RE GONNA TAKE
NEXT YEAR.
>> HEY, GIRL.
>> HEY.
>> LOOK AT YOU GETTING ALL BIG.
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL
NEXT YEAR?
LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M GONNA GO TO THAT
TECH SCHOOL THAT YOU'RE IN.
>> THE CTC.
>> YEAH.
>> WHO'S GONNA TAKE CARE
OF THE BABY?
>> UM, I KNOW MY MOM'S GONNA
WANT TO.
>> DEFINITELY.
>> BUT IF SHE DOESN'T,
I DON'T HAVE A PLAN "B"
FOR THAT JUST YET.
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE BASICALLY
DEPENDING ON TY, RIGHT?
>> AT THE MOMENT, YEAH, I GUESS.
>> AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN REALLY
RELYING ON TYLER.
YOU'RE RELYING ON HIS PARENTS.
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS KIND OF, LIKE,
RELY ON HIS PARENTS.
SO THEN YOU'RE GONNA
GO BACK HOME.
>> DON'T YOU NEED A SECOND PLAN,
YOU THINK?
>> I DO.
>> I'M NOT HAVING A BABY.
>> I'M GRATEFUL FOR TY
AND HIS PARENTS,
BUT IT BUMS ME OUT THAT
ME AND MY MOM AREN'T TALKING.
AND I DOUBT SHE'LL EVER FORGIVE
ME FOR TAKING THAT CRIB
FROM HER HOUSE.
BUT WHEN I GOT BACK TO TYLER'S
HOUSE, MY MOM SENT ME AN EMAIL
APOLOGIZING FOR
THE VOICEMAIL MESSAGE
AND SAYING SHE WANTS TO
WORK THINGS OUT
WITH BOTH ME AND TYLER.
>> 'CAUSE WHEN I CAME HOME
FROM WORK AND I WENT IN THERE,
AND WHEN I SAW THE CRIB GONE,
AND THEN I CHECKED THE CLOSET
AND ALL THE BABY STUFF WAS GONE,
I FELT LIKE THERE WAS
A DAGGER IN MY BACK.
YOU KNOW, I JUST WAS SO CRUSHED.
I FELT LIKE I LOST A CHILD.
I MEAN, IT HURT.
IT'S A FEELING I DON'T WANT TO
EVER FEEL AGAIN.
I HAD NO IDEA YOU FELT THAT
STRONGLY ABOUT MOVING IN THERE
TO BE WITH HIM.
I DON'T--
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> I ALWAYS WANTED A HAPPY
FAMILY WITH BOTH OF THE PARENTS
AND THE CHILD.
I KNOW THAT YOU AND TYLER
DON'T GET ALONG,
AND I JUST KNEW THAT HE WASN'T
ALLOWED TO COME OVER.
I DIDN'T WANT TO, LIKE,
LOSE YOU AT ALL OR ANYTHING.
LIKE--
>> YOU WOULDN'T HAVE LOST ME.
YOU COULD NEVER LOSE YOUR MOM.
I WAS HURT.
BUT LOST?
NO, IT WOULD HAVE NEVER
BEEN THAT.
>> [sniffling]
>> THERE'S NOTHING THAT CAN
BREAK WHAT WE HAVE.
THERE'S JUST NOT.
WE'RE GONNA GO THROUGH THE UPS
AND DOWNS, BUT AT THE END OF THE
DAY, I'M ALWAYS THERE FOR YOU.
AND I TOLD YOU THAT.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT FOREVER.
BUT I GUESS THAT I'M OVER IT.
I'M JUST HAPPY YOU'RE HERE.
I JUST WANT TO
JUST MOVE FORWARD
AND JUST PUT THAT BEHIND US.
LIKE, I JUST WANT YOU
TO COME HOME.
>> I'M SO GLAD
MY MOM CAME AROUND
AND WE'RE WORKING THINGS OUT.
SHE PROMISED TO LET TYLER
COME OVER AND SEE THE BABY
ANY TIME HE WANTED.
WHEN I TOLD TYLER ABOUT IT,
HE WAS A LITTLE SKEPTICAL
OF HER INTENTIONS,
BUT AGREED TO COME OVER
AND HEAR WHAT SHE HAD TO SAY.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> HELLO.
MY PROPOSAL WAS THAT I WANTED
TO BASICALLY HAVE AN OPEN DOOR.
YOU KNOW, WHERE YOU CAN COME
AND VISIT AND BE A PART
OF THE BABY'S LIFE.
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO COME HERE.
I WORK THIRD SHIFT.
I'M SLEEPING DURING THE DAYTIME.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DEAL WITH ME.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU
WANT TO SEE THEM TWO.
>> AND THE WHOLE REASON WHY
I WAS GONNA MOVE TO YOUR HOUSE
WAS BECAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU WOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO SEE YOUR BABY.
>> ONLY--LIKE, I DID--
LIKE, I'M...
I AM A LITTLE HESITANT ABOUT IT.
'CAUSE TO ME, IT MAKES YOU LOOK
LIKE YOU JUST WANT THIS BABY
ALL TO YOURSELF.
>> I WANT TO MOVE
FROM TODAY FORWARD,
WITH A FRESH START WITH US.
BUT YOUR POINT IS,
I CAN JUST COME OVER--
>> ANY--IT'S OPEN.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I FEEL A LOT BETTER.
LIKE--
I CAN'T HAVE MY BABY DADDY AND
MY MOM NOT LIKING EACH OTHER
OR ALWAYS ARGUING,
JUST NOT GETTING ALONG.
IT JUST WASN'T RIGHT.
AND I WAS JUST SO UPSET.
I WAS EMOTIONALLY UPSET.
>> BUT THANKS FOR COMING.
I DO APPRECIATE IT.
I'M GLAD WE GOT IT OUT.
>> RIGHT.
ARE YOU COMING WITH ME
OR ARE YOU STAYING--
>> NO, I'M STAYING HERE
AND GET MY GRUB ON.
>> YEAH, WE'RE GOING OUT TO EAT.
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
>> I'LL SEE YOU.
>> LATER.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
AFTER EVERYTHING HER MOTHER'S
DONE, SHE'S GONNA DO
AN ABOUT-FACE AND GO OVER THERE
AND HANG OUT WITH HER
LIKE NOTHING HAPPENED?
>> YEAH, BUT JORDAN ACTUALLY
TOLD ME THE ONLY REASON WHY
SHE CAME HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE
WAS BECAUSE KELLY KEPT SAYING
I'M NOT GONNA BE ALLOWED
IN THE HOUSE.
BUT NOW THAT SHE'S ALLOWING ME
IN THE HOUSE, THAT'S WHY
SHE'S PLANNING ON GOING BACK.
SHE WANTS US TO FEEL WELCOME TO
GO OVER THERE.
>> IT'S A MATTER OF
WHETHER SHE REALLY MEANS IT.
THAT'S ALL WELL AND GOOD
IF SHE'S SERIOUS.
>> I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU,
I WAS GONNA SAY A FEW THINGS
OR ASK A FEW THINGS,
BUT I FELT UNCOMFORTABLE
WHILE BEING AT HER HOUSE.
>> I'M STILL--I'M A LITTLE BIT
CONCERNED AS TO HOW THIS
IS GONNA ALL PAN OUT.
>> THE ONLY THING THAT
I'M REALLY CONCERNED WITH NOW
IS THAT I'M GONNA END UP
NOT SEEING MY SON.
I WORRY THAT SHE'S GONNA LET HER
MOM TALK HER INTO DOING THINGS
THAT SHE WOULDN'T DO.
>> KELLY LIKES TO
CALL THE SHOTS.
AND THE WAY SHE'S BEEN
TRYING TO CALL IT,
IT'S NOT EXACTLY IN OUR FAVOR.
>> ALL RIGHT, NOW HOW ABOUT
LET'S START MEASURING
AND THEN CUTTING THE PIECES.
TODAY'S MY DUE DATE,
BUT I HAVEN'T HAD
ANY CONTRACTIONS YET.
I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE SLAPPING WATER ON ME.
TYLER HAS BEEN KIND OF DISTANT
SINCE OUR TALK, AND I CAN TELL
HE'S NOT HAPPY ABOUT MY DECISION
TO BRING THE BABY BACK HERE.
>> HOW'S EVERYTHING GOING
WITH YOU AND TYLER?
I KNOW THINGS KEEP CHANGING...
>> YEAH.
>> AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT, SO--
>> IT'S LIKE, I JUST THINK IT
HAS TO SINK IN.
WE'LL BE, LIKE, HAPPY, SAD--
>> HE'S EXPECTING YOU TO BE,
LIKE, YOU KNOW, OVER THERE,
HIS MOM, HIS DAD,
HIS GIRLFRIEND, HIS BABY.
AND THEN THE WALL
COMES TUMBLING DOWN
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, THAT WAS
NEVER, EVER MOM'S INTENTIONS.
WOW.
THIS IS SUPER HARD.
NOW I'M WORRIED WE'RE NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO CUT IT OFF.
[chime dings]
>> WE FINISHED MY BELLY CAST
JUST IN TIME,
BECAUSE LATER THAT MORNING...
[knocking]
MY WATER BROKE,
AND IT WAS TIME
TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
A COUPLE HOURS LATER, THE
CONTRACTIONS GOT EVEN WORSE.
SO I WAS HAPPY
TO GET AN EPIDURAL.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, EPIDURALS
DON'T TAKE AWAY THE PRESSURE.
WE WANT YOU TO BE ABLE TO FEEL
THAT SO WHEN IT COMES TIME
FOR US TO BE ABLE TO PUSH,
YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHERE TO PUSH.
>> OKAY.
I SERIOUSLY FEEL LIKE
IT'S COMING OR SOMETHING.
>> SHE GOT THAT STANK FACE ON.
[laughter]
>> SUDDENLY, I STARTED
TO FEEL A LOT OF PRESSURE.
AND MY DOCTOR SAID
IT WAS TIME TO PUSH.
>> SHE NEEDS HER GLASSES NOW.
CAN YOU SEE?
>> PULL FORWARD, PULL FORWARD.
>> LIKE YOU DID YOUR NECK, YEAH.
LIKE THAT.
PULL HARD.
KEEP PULLING.
NICE AND EASY.
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
KEEP COMING.
GOOD. THAT'S IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> KEEP COMING.
GOOD WORK. COME ON.
COME ON.
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
THAT'S IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> KEEP COMING.
KEEP PUSHING A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> HERE COMES THAT HEAD.
>> BIG, DEEP BREATHS.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE A MOMMY
IN A FEW MINUTES.
>> LET'S MOVE YOUR BOTTOM DOWN.
LET'S GET THESE FEET DOWN.
MOVE THESE FEET DOWN, MOVE DOWN.
>> WE'RE GONNA
SCOOT YOUR BUTT DOWN.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> OH, CRAMP, CRAMP.
>> PUSH. PUSH HARD.
>> THERE YOU GO.
PUSH, MAMA.
COME ON.
>> OH, LOOK AT HIM!
>> MAMA, YOU DID IT!
[baby wails]
>> TY, SEE YOUR BABY?
>> OH, JORDAN.
[baby wails]
>> [giggles]
[chime dings]
>> AFTER A COUPLE DAYS
IN THE HOSPITAL, ME AND CHASE
ARE READY TO GO HOME.
BUT I'M STILL REALLY SORE
FROM LABOR.
OKAY.
>> SORRY ABOUT THE BUMPS.
SORRY.
>> MY MOM HAS TO WORK TONIGHT,
SO TYLER WAS SUPPOSED TO COME
SPEND THE NIGHT AND HELP OUT,
BUT AT THE LAST MINUTE, HIS MOM
SAID HE HAD OTHER THINGS TO DO.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE THE PLAN WAS
FOR HIM TO SPEND THE NIGHT.
I EVEN CONFIRMED IT WITH HER.
I SAID, "YOU KNOW TYLER'S
SPENDING THE NIGHT."
SHE WAS LIKE, "OH, YEAH,
BUT HE GOT TO COME HOME
AND CLEAN HIS ROOM."
>> HE'S LIKE, "I KIND OF WANT TO
GO HOME, BUT--BUT--"
I WAS LIKE, "NO,
THEN, JUST GO HOME."
>> I DON'T GET IT.
I THINK SHE'S PROBABLY JUST MAD
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT
STAYING OVER THERE.
YOU'RE HOME, BOO-BOO!
LET'S GET HIM SET UP UPSTAIRS.
>> YEAH, OKAY.
OH, MY GOD,
MY BACK HURTS SO BAD.
>> OKAY, BUBBIE,
THERE'S YOUR MOMMY.
[baby coos]
WELL, I GOT TO GET READY TO GO
TO WORK, SO I'M HOPING YOU GUYS,
LIKE, PITCH IN.
TYLER RENEGED ON COMING OVER.
NO, I DON'T THINK HIS MOM WANTS
HIM TO COME...
I'M A COUPLE MINUTES AWAY.
JUST CALM DOWN WITH HIM.
I HAVE TO GO SOON.
DON'T BE SO FORGIVING.
I MEAN, PUT YOURSELF
IN HIS SHOES.
NEVER, RIGHT?
BE HONEST.
IT'S NOT ALL HIS MOTHER'S FAULT.
NOT THE CHOICE FOR TONIGHT.
>> MY MOM IS RIGHT.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
TYLER BAILED ON ME AND CHASE
ON OUR FIRST NIGHT HOME.
MY FIRST NIGHT HOME
WAS EXHAUSTING.
BETWEEN TAKING CARE OF CHASE
AND THE PAIN FROM LABOR,
I DIDN'T GET ANY SLEEP.
MY MOM WORKED ALL NIGHT, BUT
SHE TOOK CHASE FOR A WHILE WHEN
SHE GOT HOME TO GIVE ME A BREAK.
[door creaks open]
>> HEY, JORDAN.
[door creaks shut]
HOW'VE YOU BEEN DOING?
>> TAKING CARE OF CHASE.
SO HOW WAS SLEEPING LAST NIGHT--
BEING ABLE TO?
>> WAS CHASE KEEPING YOU UP?
>> YEP.
IT WOULD BE REALLY AWESOME
IF HIS DADDY COULD BE THERE.
>> WELL, JORDAN,
YOU SHOULD HAVE TOLD ME
THAT YOU WANTED ME THERE.
>> MM-MM, I WASN'T GONNA
TELL YOU TO COME HERE.
YOU SHOULD JUST
HAVE THAT DADDY INSTINCT.
AND JUST COME WHEN YOU WANT TO
SEE YOUR SON.
I'M GONNA WRAP THIS UP
AND GET CHASE.
>> WHEN I WENT HOME, BELIEVE ME,
I WAS UPSET 'CAUSE I THOUGHT
YOU DIDN'T WANT ME HERE.
[baby burps]
[gasps]
THERE'S A BURPIES.
>> [laughs]
>> I LOVE YOU, CHASE.
>> I KNOW TYLER EXPECTED
ME AND CHASE TO LIVE AT HIS
HOUSE, BUT HE NEEDS TO STEP UP
AND BE A DAD,
NO MATTER WHERE I'M LIVING.
[chime dings]
[baby wailing]
>> THINGS HAVEN'T GOTTEN
ANY EASIER
SINCE BRINGING CHASE HOME.
NIGHTS ARE THE WORST,
BECAUSE MY MOM IS AT WORK
AND MY BROTHERS AND SISTER
ARE ALL ASLEEP.
TYLER ALWAYS HAS AN EXCUSE
TO WHY HE DOESN'T CALL
OR COME OVER VERY OFTEN.
I KNOW HE AND HIS FAMILY FEEL
BURNED BY MY DECISION TO MOVE
BACK HOME, BUT I DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY THAT WOULD KEEP
THEM FROM VISITING CHASE.
SO I CALLED HIS PARENTS AND
INVITED THEM OVER, AND
SURPRISINGLY, THEY SAID YES.
>> HI.
>> HELLO.
>> HELLO, HOW ARE YOU?
>> ALL RIGHT; YOURSELF?
>> GOOD.
>> GET RID OF THE--HERE.
>> WELL, HELLO, SWEETHEART.
>> TOLD YOU.
HE NEEDS A HAIRCUT.
>> HELLO.
>> HE DEFINITELY
LIKES TO BE HELD.
>> SO I GUESS YOUR COMING HOME
HERE, IT'S A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
WE KIND OF THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE
COMING BACK TO OUR PLACE AND--
YOU KNOW, JUST KIND OF WONDERING
WHAT CHANGED YOUR MIND.
BROUGHT THIS LITTLE MUNCHKIN
WHO MIGHT BE GETTING HUNGRY.
DO YOU WANT TO GO BACK TO MAMA?
>> I'M GONNA TAKE HIM FROM YOU.
GRACIAS.
>> WE THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
HE WAS COMING BACK
AND HE WAS GONNA LIVE THERE
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT
YOU HAD LED US TO BELIEVE
AS WELL.
>> BUT--BUT LET'S GO BACK--
>> I THINK--
I THINK IT'S A LOT
OF MISUNDERSTANDINGS
AND A LOT OF ASSUMPTIONS
THAT DIDN'T COME TO FRUITION.
>> JUST TO BE HONEST WITH YOU,
I HAD NO DOUBT THAT
HE WAS COMING BACK HERE.
>> I PERSONALLY DON'T THINK
I MISLED ANYBODY ABOUT MY MOM.
'CAUSE MY INTENTIONS WERE
TO MOVE OVER, BUT I PERSONALLY
MADE A DIFFERENT DECISION.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST--
IT'S JUST I THINK TYLER'S
HAVING A HARD TIME TOO.
LIKE, HE'S--HE WAS EXPECTING YOU
TO COME BACK TO OUR HOUSE,
AND YOU KNOW,
WITH GETTING THE CRIB AND STUFF,
AND I THINK HE MIGHT BE
HAVING A HARD TIME.
>> TO ME, IT SEEMS LIKE
HE DOESN'T REALLY WANT TO
MEET HER HALFWAY HERE.
HE DOESN'T SHOW UP
A LOT OF THE TIMES OR--
>> DO YOU THINK TYLER THINKS
HE'S NOT NEEDED?
>> YOU GOT TO FIGURE, JORDAN,
HE WAS EXPECTING EVERYTHING
TO BE A LOT DIFFERENT, AND
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKED OUT.
SO IT'S A MAJOR ADJUSTMENT
FOR HIM.
>> HE'S NOT CALLING YOU AT ALL?
>> NO.
LIKE, YOU DON'T MAKE AN ATTEMPT
TO CALL, YOU DON'T MAKE AN
ATTEMPT TO TEXT, YOU DON'T MAKE
AN ATTEMPT TO REALLY COME HERE
AS OFTEN, SO YOU THINK I WOULD
JUST GIVE HIM TO YOU?
>> THE ONLY THING I CAN FIGURE
IS, HE'S JUST REALLY MAD
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T--
YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND.
YOU DIDN'T COME BACK THERE
WITH HIM.
WE'LL DEFINITELY TALK TO TYLER,
AND--
>> HE'LL COME AROUND.
IT'S JUST, HE'S YOUNG.
>> WELL, THANKS FOR LETTING US
HOLD HIM FOR A LITTLE BIT.
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SEE YOU, JORDAN.
>> BYE.
>> SEE YOU, LITTLE GUY.
>> TYLER'S PARENTS MUST HAVE
SAID SOMETHING TO HIM
ABOUT COMING AROUND MORE,
'CAUSE HE CALLED AND SAID
HE'D BE OVER IN A FEW MINUTES.
AND HE ACTUALLY SHOWED UP...
>> HELLO?
>> ABOUT FIVE HOURS LATER.
>> HEY.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED WITH
COMING HERE EARLIER?
>> MIKE WANTED TO GET THE
TRANSMISSION DONE.
>> OH.
>> AND WE FINALLY WERE ABLE TO
GET IT OUT AND GET A NEW ONE IN.
smooch!
I SAID I'D BE HERE TODAY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND HERE I AM.
>> I MEAN, I JUST KIND OF FEEL
LIKE IT'S ALWAYS GONNA
BE LIKE THAT.
LIKE YOU'RE GONNA BE LIKE,
"OH, I'M GONNA TAKE YOU OUT
TO A BASEBALL GAME."
AND HE'S GONNA BE WAITING
BY THE DOOR ALL DAY,
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA SHOW UP.
>> CAN I FEED HIM?
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS.
>> WHOSE FAULT IS THAT?
>> MINE, I GUESS.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
>> WELL, IT KIND OF IS,
CONSIDERING YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO DECIDED TO HAVE HIM HERE.
>> BUT IT'S NOT MY FAULT THAT
YOU HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
>> THIS IS WHY I JUST WANT TO
TAKE HIM OVER TO MY HOUSE
FOR A WHILE.
>> AND WHY DO YOU THINK I SHOULD
EVER FEEL COMFORTABLE ABOUT THAT
IF YOU MAKE NO ATTEMPT?
>> I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I DON'T ALWAYS FEEL COMFORTABLE
COMING HERE, LIKE--
>> WHY DO YOU FEEL LIKE--
>> IT'S NOTHING AGAINST YOU
OR CHASE,
IT'S JUST I JUST KIND OF--
>> BUT YOU NEVER CALL--
>> I UNDERSTAND THOUGH,
I SHOULD CALL.
>> BUT YOU STILL DON'T--
I MEAN--
>> YEAH, BUT I USUALLY
TRY TO TEXT YOU.
>> USUALLY?
SEE, THAT'S WHY I'M--LIKE,
IT'S REALLY HARD FOR ME TO SAY,
BECAUSE I EXPECTED
A LOT MORE FROM YOU.
I MEAN, I KNOW SOME GUYS
WOULDN'T GIVE A [bleep]
ABOUT THEIR KID.
AND NOT TO CALL.
WHY WOULDN'T YOU CALL?
>> I'LL CALL YOU TONIGHT.
>> MM, OKAY.
YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE YOU NEVER DO.
[baby whimpers]
I KNOW TYLER FEELS UNEASY
AT MY HOUSE...
[chime dings]
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
HE WOULD USE IT AS AN EXCUSE
TO IGNORE ME AND CHASE.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU POOPED.
YES, I'LL MAKE SURE
THAT THEY'RE ALL WARM.
MM-HMM.
WOW.
WHAT DID YOU EAT?
YOU STINKERS.
I DID NOT FEED YOU THAT.
I'M STILL TRYING TO GET USED TO
THIS MOMMY THING.
STRETCH.
GOOD BOY.
I'VE DEFINITELY HAD LOTS OF
PRACTICE DOING THINGS ON MY OWN.
TYLER HASN'T STOPPED BY
IN A COUPLE OF WEEKS,
AND AT THIS POINT, MY FAMILY
DOESN'T WANT HIM COMING AROUND
AT ALL ANYMORE.
[cell phone ringing]
HELLO?
>> JORDAN...
>> ABOUT WHAT THOUGH?
THAT'S NOT MY PROBLEM,
BUT OKAY.
GET HERE QUICK, 'CAUSE MY MOM
HAS TO GO TO WORK
AND SHE'S WATCHING CHASE.
WHO IS IT?
>> IT'S ME.
CAN I COME IN?
>> COME IN.
>> CAN I SEE CHASE FIRST?
>> OKAY, WHAT TIME IS IT, TY?
>> 9:00.
>> OKAY, YOU COULD HAVE HIM ALL
DAY; NOT WHILE HE'S SLEEPING
AT NIGHT.
>> I JUST WANTED TO SEE HIM
REAL QUICK.
>> WELL, YOU COULD SEE HIM
ALL DAY TOMORROW.
HE'S SLEEPING RIGHT NOW.
YOU WANT TO GO WAKE HIM UP
NOW WHEN HE'S UP ALL NIGHT?
>> I'M NOT GONNA WAKE HIM UP.
I JUST WANT TO LOOK AT HIM.
I JUST WANT TO BE ABLE
TO SEE HIM.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM IN A WHILE.
>> THAT'S NOT MY FAULT.
YOU WERE ABLE TO COME HERE
ANY OTHER DAY; NOW YOU WANT TO
COME INSIDE MY HOUSE
AND START DEMANDING STUFF.
>> I JUST WANT TO SEE HIM FOR--
>> YES, ANY OTHER TIME DURING
THE DAY, YOU CAN COME OVER
WHENEVER.
>> [bleep].
YOU NEVER TELL ME [bleep].
>> OKAY, SO YOU'RE GONNA COME UP
IN MY HOUSE AND START CUSSING,
RIGHT?
>> SURE.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN LEAVE.
>> [bleep] YOU ALL.
>> [indistinct shouting]
NO, GUYS!
JORDAN, GO GET THE BABY.
JORDAN, I PUT HIM IN THE BOPPIE.
YO, MIKE!
I'M NOT PLAYING.
I'M TELLING YOU AND DOMINIC, NO.
YOU AIN'T READY FOR THAT.
LET'S GO.
YOU IS NOT READY FOR THAT.
BUT YOU SHOULD BE READY
WHEN YOU TALK THAT BIG TALK.
>> [sighs]
>> THIS IS REALLY IT.
THIS IS THE END OF US.
I BELIEVE THAT HE WANTS NOTHING
TO DO WITH CHASE
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T COME AROUND
FOR CHASE.
HE DOESN'T--HE HASN'T
GOTTEN CHASE ANYTHING
SINCE HE WAS BORN.
HE DOESN'T THINK
HE HAS TO DO ANYTHING.
LIKE, I WANT TO GET FULL
CUSTODY OF CHASE.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD.
WHAT DOES HE DO FOR HIM?
AND I MEAN, AS FAR AS COMING TO
VISIT HIM, JUST BRINGING HIM
STUFF OR BUYING HIM STUFF
OR JUST--
>> I MEAN, LIKE NEVER ONCE--
I NEVER SAID "NEVER COME"
OR ANYTHING.
>> WE DIDN'T, BUT I'M
AT THE POINT WHERE I'M GOOD
THAT HE DOESN'T.
>> I JUST CAN'T TAKE ANOTHER
HEARTBREAK RIGHT NOW.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH
FOR ME AND CHASE.
I GOT TO FOCUS ON CHASE.
MY FOCUS SHOULD NOT EVER BE
ON A MAN OVER MY CHILD.
>> SO, LIKE, ARE YOU GOING TO
SCHOOL NEXT YEAR?
>> I'M DROPPING OUT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S UP TO YOU WHAT YOU DO.
I JUST WANT TO SEE YOU SUCCEED
FOR YOUR SON.
>> BEING A MOM AND GOING TO
SCHOOL, IT'S NOT A GOOD MIX,
AND I CAN'T DO THOSE THINGS
WITH CHASE.
SO I GOT TO TAKE ONE STEP
AT A TIME INSTEAD OF
THINKING I CAN DO ANYTHING.
THIS WHOLE SITUATION IS TOUGH.
IT REALLY WOKE ME UP.
LIKE, DON'T GET PREGNANT.
DON'T THINK THAT
YOU'RE INVINCIBLE,
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT.
>> SO YOU THINK YOUR MOM
IS OFF DRUGS AND STUFF?
>> I DON'T THINK
SHE STOPPED DRINKING.
>> IT'S NO SECRET
THAT I HAVE A DRUG ADDICTION.
>> TELL MAMA ALL ABOUT IT.
>> CAN I HOLD MY GRANDBABY NOW?
>> NO, I'M HOLDING HIM NOW.
>> GIMME THE BABY.
>> I DON'T WANT MY BABY TO
BE AROUND SOMEBODY LIKE THAT.