>> [giggles]
OKAY, I'M DONE.
I'M DONE.
I'M MILLINA.
I'M 17, AND I LIVE IN HARRISON
TOWNSHIP, MICHIGAN,
RIGHT OUTSIDE OF DETROIT.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
AND I USED TO LIVE WITH MY MOM,
BUT SHE STRUGGLES WITH DRUG
ADDICTION, AND HAS BEEN IN
AND OUT OF JAIL FOR THE PAST
FIVE YEARS.
MY DAD CAN BE LOTS OF FUN.
>> "DAD, CHECK ME OUT.
I'M JAMMIN'."
>> [giggles]
BUT HE'S PRETTY FLAKY
AND CAN'T REALLY AFFORD
TO SUPPORT ME,
SO NOW MY LITTLE BROTHER MOSES
AND I LIVE WITH MY GRANDMA,
WHO TAKES REALLY GOOD CARE
OF US.
>> WOW, LET'S CELEBRATE.
>> I'M NOT PICKING THOSE UP.
BUT HAVING A TROUBLED FAMILY
HASN'T BEEN EASY ON ME.
I WENT THROUGH A PRETTY
REBELLIOUS PHASE WHEN I DROPPED
OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL,
AND STARTED SPENDING A LOT
OF TIME IN THE RAVE SCENE.
AND THAT'S WHERE I MET
MY BOYFRIEND TREVOR.
>> STOP.
>> [giggling]
WE'RE SO ALIKE,
IT'S ALMOST CREEPY.
WHAT SHIRT ARE YOU WEARING?
>> SAME ONE AS YOU.
>> [laughing] THAT IS SO...
AND WE LOVE TO STAY OUT
TILL THE SUN COMES UP.
BUT OUR ALL-NIGHTERS
ARE ABOUT TO GET MUCH LESS FUN,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
I'M SEVEN MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND TREVOR AND I DECIDED
TO NAME OUR SON KAYDEN.
MY MOM HAS BEEN IN JAIL
ON A DRUG POSSESSION CHARGE
FOR MY WHOLE PREGNANCY.
I'M HOPING THAT SHE GETS
RELEASED INTO A REHAB FACILITY
IN TIME FOR MY DUE DATE.
BUT UNTIL THEN, ALL WE CAN DO
IS TALK ON THE PHONE.
>> THIS CALL WILL BE RECORDED
AND SUBJECT TO MONITORING
AT ANY TIME.
YOU MAY BEGIN SPEAKING NOW.
>> HELLO?
I GOT THE 3-D ULTRASOUND
DONE.
>> DID YOU?
>> I GOT THIS BEAR,
AND YOU SQUEEZE IT,
AND IT HAS KAYDEN'S HEARTBEAT
IN IT.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> AW.
>> HEY, LISTEN.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO HEAR IT, THOUGH.
[heartbeat whooshing]
>> [squeals]
I FEEL LIKE THE WORST MOM.
>> YOU'RE NOT, MAMA.
I CAN'T SEND PICTURES ANYMORE,
CAN I?
>> NO.
BECAUSE HER COURT DATE'S
THE 18TH.
>> NEXT TIME WE GO TO COURT,
THEY'RE HAVING THEIR ARGUMENT
AND THEY'RE HAVING THEIR
VERDICT.
>> I'M NOT GONNA BREAK.
I'M GONNA LET IT MAKE ME
STRONGER.
I'M NOT THAT PERSON
WHEN I'M NOT ADDICTED,
YOU KNOW, WHEN I'M CLEAN.
>> MOM, I DON'T LOOK DOWN ON
YOU.
I DON'T LOOK AT YOU DIFFERENTLY.
YOU ARE MY MOM.
I'M ALWAYS GONNA LOVE YOU.
YOU MESSED UP.
>> I'VE GOT ONE MINUTE.
WE GOT ONE MINUTE REMAINING.
HONEY, I'M SO SORRY.
>> I'M SORRY, MAMA.
I LOVE YOU.
>> [automated voice] GOOD-BYE.
>> BYE.
WITH EVERYTHING THAT'S GOING
ON WITH MY MOM,
WITH HER BEING IN JAIL
AND WITH HER HAVING
ALL OF HER COURT DATES
AND ME WANTING TO HAVE
MY MOM THERE,
IT'S REALLY HARD FOR ME
TO PUT MY 100% FOCUS
ON KAYDEN WHEN I'M DISTRACTED.
>> I DON'T--I CAN'T BLAME YOU.
I MEAN, IT'S YOUR MOM.
BUT I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND,
LIKE, THAT'S A GROWN WOMAN.
SHE MAKES HER OWN DECISIONS.
SHE GETS HER OWN CONSEQUENCES.
AND NOW THIS IS YOUR TIME
TO START YOUR OWN
DECISION-MAKING.
>> RIGHT.
WITH MY MOM, SHE'D GO
AND SHE'D PROMISE THINGS,
AND THEN SHE WOULDN'T DO IT.
AND YOU'VE PROVED TO ME
THAT I CAN TRUST YOU.
BUT IT'S JUST THE FACT
THAT THERE'S STILL THAT LITTLE
TEENY, LIKE, DEVIL ON MY
SHOULDER GOING,
"EVERY TIME YOU TRUST SOMEBODY,
THEY LET YOU DOWN."
>> RIGHT.
>> WELL, I MEAN, LIKE, THE ONLY
WAY WE CAN REALLY WORK ON IT
AND MOVE FORWARD IS IF
YOU LET THAT GO.
I'M NOT THOSE PEOPLE.
>> IT'S JUST THE FACT OF,
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
SO I'M HOPING FOR THE BEST,
BUT EXPECTING THE WORST.
>> RIGHT.
IT'S GONNA BE ROUGH,
TO SAY THE LEAST.
WE GOT TO KEEP STRONG,
KEEP DOING HARDER
AND WE GOT TO KEEP GOING FURTHER
WITH EVERYTHING WE CAN DO
PRODUCTIVELY TOWARDS
KAYDEN'S FUTURE.
>> WHAT'S A BRISKET?
IS IT LIKE A BISCUIT
WITH A "R"?
>> NO, IT'S LIKE--
IT'S KIND OF, LIKE, SHREDDED
AND IT'S GOT BARBECUE SAUCE
IN IT.
>> OKAY.
I GOT ALL EXCITED.
I SEEN BARBECUE SAUCE
AND WAS LIKE, "AH."
>> YOU AND YOUR WEIRD PREGNANCY
FOOD CRAVINGS.
>> [chuckles]
>> WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
WHEN YOU FOUND OUT
THAT YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> UM, I WAS REALLY WORRIED.
I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO THINK.
JUST KIND OF LOOKING BACK NOW,
I THINK OF ALL THE THINGS
I COULD HAVE DONE DIFFERENTLY.
AND BEFORE THEN, I WAS TOTALLY
AGAINST GETTING ON BIRTH
CONTROL TOO.
BECAUSE I KNEW A LOT OF PEOPLE
THAT HAD A LOT OF DIFFERENT
ISSUES WHEN THEY STARTED
THAT THEY DIDN'T HAVE BEFORE.
AND I WAS LIKE,
IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN TO ME.
WELL, GUESS WHAT?
IT DID.
>> WELL, ARE YOU GONNA DO
SOME RESEARCH ON SOME BIRTH
CONTROL FOR AFTER KAYDEN'S MORE?
>> YEAH.
AND I DON'T WANT ANOTHER
"UH-OH."
[laughs]
>> ONCE KAYDEN'S BORN,
AND YOU'VE HAD A FEW MONTHS
TO RECUPERATE,
ARE YOU GONNA WANT TO GO BACK
OUT AND PARTY LIKE THAT AGAIN?
>> I MEAN, SOMETIMES I DO
MISS IT.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO GET INVOLVED
WITH THE DRUGS, AND I DON'T
WANT TO GET INVOLVED
WITH THE DRINKING,
BECAUSE I DON'T EVER WANT
KAYDEN TO HAVE TO DEAL WITH
WHAT ME AND MO DEALT WITH.
MY MOM GOT US TAKEN AWAY
FROM HER.
SO I DON'T EVER WANT HIM
TO HAVE TO GO THROUGH THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK ABOUT
EVERY LITTLE THING THAT COULD
GET HIM TAKEN AWAY FROM ME.
I OVERTHINK IT.
LIKE, I'M LIKE, WELL, WHAT IF
SOMEBODY RANDOMLY CALLED
PROTECTIVE SERVICES
'CAUSE THEY GET MAD AT ME--
>> WELL, THAT'S COMPLETELY
NORMAL.
IT'S COMPLETELY NORMAL.
SO DON'T FEEL BAD ABOUT
OVERTHINKING THINGS.
YOU JUST WANT TO DO BETTER
THAN YOUR MOM DID.
>> THINGS WITH TREVOR ARE GOOD,
BUT I HAVE A HARD TIME
WITH HIS MOM, TINA,
BECAUSE SHE'S REALLY EMOTIONALLY
UNSTABLE, AND SHE HAS
A HEALTH CONDITION THAT CAUSES
SEIZURES.
SHE'S ALSO REALLY JUDGMENTAL
OF MY MOM'S SITUATION.
BUT I TRY NOT TO SAY ANYTHING,
BECAUSE IT'S IMPORTANT TO TREVOR
THAT WE GET ALONG.
SO THIS IS, LIKE, A 3-D
ULTRASOUND.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE'S HIS HEAD?
>> THIS IS HIS HEAD RIGHT HERE.
>> IS THAT--WHERE'S HIS PENIS?
>> IT'S NOT ON THERE.
>> THIS IS JUST HIS HEAD.
>> YEAH, THIS IS JUST HIS HEAD.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'RE READY
FOR A BABY, YOU GUYS?
AS A COUPLE, YOU NEED TO DECIDE
WHAT YOU NEED TO DO
TO PLAN THIS BABY.
>> RIGHT.
WELL, I THINK, LIKE, WHEN THE
BABY FIRST COMES,
WE'RE GONNA KIND OF BALANCE
HIM BETWEEN BOTH--
WE'RE GONNA COME OVER HERE,
WE'RE GONNA GO TO MY HOUSE.
AND THEN, I MEAN, EVENTUALLY,
I MEAN, WE HAVE TALKED ABOUT
GETTING OUR OWN PLACE.
IT'S NOT A ANYTIME SOON THING,
BUT IT'S--
>> ONE DAY.
FUTURE GOALS.
>> RIGHT.
>> IT'S A LOT OF WORK
TO RAISE A BABY.
I KNOW.
I RAISED TWO BABIES BY MYSELF.
>> RIGHT.
AND I'M REALLY GRATEFUL
THAT I'M NOT IN THIS BY MYSELF,
THAT I DO HAVE TREVOR
TO HELP ME AND--
>> I TOLD YOU THAT I WOULD BE
HERE TO TAKE CARE OF THIS BABY.
YOUR MOM WASN'T ANY HELP.
THAT'S WHY SHE'S NOT HERE,
OKAY?
BUT I'M HERE FOR YOU.
AND I'LL CONSUME MY MYSELF
HELPING YOU.
>> THANK YOU--
>> AND I WILL ENJOY EVERY MINUTE
OF IT.
>> BUT WHEN YOU'RE HAVING
A SEIZURE, YOUR HANDS GO NUMB
AND EVERYTHING.
DOES THAT EVERY CONCERN YOU
WITH, LIKE, HOLDING THE BABY
OR ANYTHING, THAT--
ARE YOU EVER WORRIED ABOUT THAT?
>> NO.
>> NO?
>> IF I'M NOT OKAY,
I WOULD SAY I WASN'T OKAY,
AND I WOULD CALL SOMEONE
TO HELP ME.
IT'S HARD HAVING A BABY.
AND YOU THINK YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE GLAD I'M THERE.
>> WELL, I'M--
>> NOT SAYING WE DON'T WANT
YOU THERE.
>> WE AREN'T SAYING THAT WE
DON'T WANT YOU THERE.
WE'RE NOT SAYING THAT--
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE A HUGE PART
OF KAYDEN'S LIFE.
YOU'RE HIS GRANDMA.
>> I HAVE CONCERNS ABOUT
TINA WANTING TO TAKE CARE
OF KAYDEN.
BUT MY MOM ISN'T HERE TO HELP
OUT, AND I KNOW NAN DOESN'T
WANT ANYMORE RESPONSIBILITIES.
CURRENTLY, THIS IS THE ONLY
HOUSE THAT'S ACTUALLY STABLE.
BUT I KNOW THAT YOU'RE--
HE'S GONNA BE CRYING,
AND YOU'RE GONNA WANT THAT--
>> YEAH, I'M GONNA SAY,
"MILLINA, YOU BETTER GET UP
AND DO SOMETHING WITH THIS
CHILD."
>> RIGHT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO RAISE
YOUR CHILD.
I THINK IT'S A DAY-BY-DAY.
I'LL NEVER SAY,
"WELL, YOU'VE GOT TO GO
AND YOU'VE GOT TO GO TO TAKE
THE BABY TO TINA'S
OR HAVE TREVOR TAKE THE BABY."
I'M NOT GONNA DO THAT TO YOU.
>> WITH TINA'S PHYSICAL
AND MENTAL ISSUES,
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
LEAVING HER WITH THE BABY
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, WE'VE WATCHED
HER DROP THINGS,
WE'VE WATCHED HER FALL, WE'VE--
WHAT HAPPENS IF SHE GOES
AND SHE FALLS WITH THE BABY?
ANOTHER THING IS, TINA GOES
AND SHE'S LIKE, "OH," YOU KNOW,
SITTING THERE TALKING BADLY
ABOUT MY MOM.
>> DON'T DO ANYTHING YOU DON'T
FEEL COMFORTABLE.
YOU STILL HAVE THE RIGHT
TO SAY NO.
ASIDE FROM HER PHYSICAL
IS HER BEING IRRATIONAL
AND THREATENING AT TIMES.
THIS IS WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT
BEFORE YOU HAVE A CHILD.
>> I KNOW THAT STAYING WITH NAN
FULL-TIME IS MY BEST OPTION,
BUT I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
TREVOR AND I ARE ON
THE SAME PAGE.
SO WHAT ARE THINKING
IN TERMS OF BABY-RELATED--
LIKE, ARE YOU SCARED?
WHAT'S...
>> I MEAN, I'M REALLY NERVOUS
ABOUT HIM, BUT I'M REALLY
EXCITED TO MEET HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO,
BUT, YOU KNOW, WE'LL FIGURE
THAT OUT.
>> I'M JUST FREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, BEFORE WE'RE LIKE,
OKAY, WELL, WE HAVE THIS
AMOUNT OF TIME,
WE HAVE THIS AMOUNT OF TIME.
WE'RE PRETTY MUCH OUT OF TIME
NOW.
AND IT'S JUST, LIKE, THE FACT
OF, WE DON'T REALLY HAVE
A GAME PLAN.
LIKE, WE HAVE AN IDEA OF WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO,
BUT WE REALLY DON'T HAVE THE,
"OKAY, THIS IS WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN."
>> I MEAN, LIKE, I HAVE,
LIKE, SOME OF THE PREPARATIONS
FOR, LIKE, THE DAY OF
AND, LIKE, YOU KNOW, A PLAN,
BUT IT'S MORE AFTER THAT
WHICH I NEED TO REALLY
FIGURE OUT.
>> I FEEL LIKE MY HOUSE
WOULD BE A BETTER ENVIRON--
OR A BETTER PLACE FOR HIM
BECAUSE THERE'S MORE SPACE.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'S GONNA BE TOUGH.
BUT, I MEAN, I WOULD COME STAY
OVER SO THAT, LIKE, YOU COULD
SLEEP IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
NIGHT.
AND I'M SURE YOU'LL BE
EXHAUSTED.
AND I'LL BE HAPPY TO TAKE CARE
OF HIM AND CHANGE HIS DIAPER
AND ALL THAT.
>> YOU DON'T SOUND TOO THRILLED
ABOUT THAT.
>> I THINK HE'D BE BETTER OFF
AT MY HOUSE.
BUT THAT'S MORE FOR SELFISH
REASONS.
[doorbell rings]
>> HI, HALEY.
HOW YOU DOING, HONEY?
>> HEY, NAN, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
MILLINA'S IN HER ROOM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MILLINA.
>> OH, HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M DOING GOOD.
WORKED ALL DAY.
TOUCH MY BABY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> MY MOM HAS A COURT DATE
TOMORROW AT 8:15 IN THE MORNING.
>> ARE YOU GOING
TO THE COURT DATE?
>> I'M PLANNING ON GOING.
THE ATTORNEY REALLY BELIEVES
THAT SHE CAN GET A WHOLE CASE
THROWN OUT.
AND IF SHE CAN LEAVE ON THAT,
HE'S GONNA SAY, "OKAY,
WE'RE GONNA RELEASE YOU,
AND YOU NEED TO BE INTO
A PROGRAM IN X AMOUNT OF TIME."
>> IF THAT HAPPENS,
AT LEAST SHE'LL BE HERE
FOR KAYDEN.
>> IF SHE DOES GOOD,
SHE'LL BE ABLE TO COME HOME
ON WEEKENDS.
I THINK THIS LAST TIME
THAT SHE RELAPSED
REALLY HAD A BIG EFFECT
ON HER, BECAUSE SHE FELL INTO--
SHE FELL DOWN A RABBIT HOLE
SO QUICK.
YOU KNOW, SHE GOT INVOLVED
WITH IT, AND JUST, HER PROBLEM
GOT SO BAD SO FAST.
LIKE, THIS WAS, LIKE--
I THINK THIS WAS LAST YEAR.
LIKE, LOOK AT HER FACE.
SHE JUST LOOKS SO HAPPY.
AND THEN IT'S HARD TO WATCH
HER GO FROM THAT, AND SEE HOW
SHE WAS, TO THIS.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD TO LOOK AT.
LIKE, I MEAN,
I'VE DEALT WITH IT FOR A WHILE
TO JUST FAKE A SMILE
AND TELL EVERYBODY I'M OKAY,
BUT IT'S GETTING HARDER.
>> YOU KNOW, YOUR MOM,
NO MATTER WHAT, IS YOUR MOM,
AND SHE'S THE BEAUTIFUL PERSON
THAT YOU SEE IN THE FIRST
PICTURE.
AND SHE'S MADE MISTAKES.
AND SOMETIMES SHE'S GONNA SEEM
UGLY AND BEATEN DOWN,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
SHE DOESN'T LOVE YOU.
>> IT JUST--I--
IT KIND OF--IT HURTS REALLY BAD.
>> YEAH, MOMS AREN'T REALLY
REPLACEABLE.
> I'M REALLY SCARED ABOUT
THE WHOLE SITUATION.
I JUST DON'T REALLY KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE IT.
NAN AND TREVOR BOTH HAVE WORK
TODAY, SO I'M GOING TO MY MOM'S
COURT DATE BY MYSELF,
AND I'M SUPER NERVOUS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YES.
>> HE'S GONNA ARGUE
THE MOTION?
>> HAVE HER SHOW UP AT 9:30.
>> IT REALLY SUCKS THAT MY MOM'S
GONNA BE IN JAIL WHEN THE BABY
COMES.
TREVOR'S BEEN BUSY AT HIS
FAST FOOD JOB, AND I'M TRYING
TO SPEND MORE TIME WITH MY DAD.
I HOPE THAT I CAN RAISE A BABY
BETTER THAN I CAN THROW
A FRISBEE.
I FEEL LIKE...
AFTER MOM GOES THROUGH THIS
YEAR-LONG PROGRAM,
I MEAN, I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH HER BEING AROUND THE BABY,
ALONE WITH THE BABY,
UNTIL SHE PROVES TO ME
THAT SHE'S OKAY.
WHAT TYPE OF RELATIONSHIP
DO YOU WANT TO HAVE
WITH THE BABY?
>> I KNOW I'VE HAD PROBLEMS
IN THE PAST WITH SEVERAL
THINGS--DRUGS, ALCOHOL.
YOU KNOW, SCREAMING,
YELLING.
ABUSE.
AND, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT LIKE
THAT ANYMORE.
LUCKILY, I WENT TO THERAPY
AND IT WORKED.
I THINK THAT YOU AND TREVOR
WILL BE ALL RIGHT IF YOU STAY
AWAY FROM ALL US GROWN-UPS.
AND I DON'T SO MUCH MEAN ME.
I MEAN THE LADIES.
>> WITH TREVOR'S MOM,
I'M WORRIED, LIKE--
SHE GOES AND SHE HAS STROKES,
AND WE WATCH HER DROP THINGS
REPEATEDLY.
>> LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
I KNEW THAT TREVOR'S MA
WAS BAD NEWS WITHIN
THE FIRST FIVE MINUTES.
>> I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
SAYING, "HERE'S MY KID.
YOU CAN BE ALONE WITH HIM,
WATCH HIM."
>> RIGHT.
WHY TAKE A CHANCE?
>> LIKE, I WANT THE BABY
TO BE ABLE TO HAVE
A MORE STABLE LIFE THAN I DID.
>> YEAH.
>> OH?
WHEN?
>> WHAT'D SHE SAY?
>> SO WHAT IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
>> SO SHE'S MOVING IN
WITH THESE PEOPLE WHO ARE
OPENING UP THEIR BASEMENT
TO OUR FAMILY.
BUT, YEAH, I GUESS SHE
WANTS TO INCLUDE YOU IN ON IT.
>> OKAY.
SHE WANTS TO MOVE
YOU, HER, ME, AND KAYDEN
TO THIS LADY'S HOUSE?
>> IT'S THREE TIMES THE SIZE
OF OUR HOUSE.
>> DO YOU WANT MY HONEST
THOUGHT PROCESS,
OR DO YOU WANT ME TO SUGARCOAT
IT?
>> I'LL TAKE THE HONESTY.
>> LIKE, I'D BE FINE WITH COMING
OVER AND STAYING THE NIGHT,
YOU KNOW, BUT MOVING IN?
DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE WITH THAT
AT ALL.
>> RIGHT.
>> I'M, LIKE, 100% SICK
OF JUST BITING MY TONGUE,
AND I DON'T APPRECIATE IT
WHEN SHE'S SITTING THERE
BADMOUTHING MY MOM.
>> I WANT YOU TO BE THERE
BECAUSE I LIKE BEING CLOSE
TO YOU, I LIKE BEING ABLE
TO COME HOME FROM WORK
AND SPEND TIME WITH YOU.
I THINK, YOU KNOW, WHAT WOULD
PROBABLY BE, LIKE, NOT THE BEST
IDEA, BUT FIRST STEP, I GUESS,
IF YOU WOULD LIKE,
YOU COULD COME OVER TOMORROW,
AND MAYBE YOU GUYS COULD
SIT DOWN.
AND I GUESS YOU COULD TRY TO
TALK TO HER, BECAUSE IT'S NOT
GONNA GO AWAY.
>> FINE.
I'LL COME OVER AND I'LL TALK
TO HER.
>> YEAH, THAT'S ALL I WANT.
I JUST WANT YOU TO TALK TO HER.
IF IT DOESN'T WORK OUT,
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
>> WE'RE MOVING.
>> I HEARD.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE
THAT YOU GUYS ARE MOVING?
>> WELL, UM...
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS,
SHE'S GOT A 2,000-SQUARE-FOOT
BASEMENT SHE HAS REMODELED
FOR US.
>> THAT'S COOL.
>> AND YOU ARE COMING TOO?
>> I'M OKAY WITH,
YOU KNOW, COMING AND STAYING
THE NIGHT.
BUT I JUST DON'T THINK
FULLY I'M READY TO JUST
MOVE OUT.
>> I WON'T ALLOW YOU TO HAVE
THE BABY OR YOURSELF
IN AN ENVIRONMENT
THAT WOULD HARM YOU OR THE BABY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> YOUR MOM'S GOT PROBLEMS.
PEOPLE I KNOW THAT WENT TO JAIL
CAME OUT OF JAIL,
DID THE SAME AMOUNT OF DRUGS
THEY DID WHEN THEY WERE IN JAIL,
AND DIED.
>> BUT MY THING IS JUST,
I WOULD LIKE YOU TO HAVE
AN OPEN MIND ON THAT THERE
IS A CHANCE SHE CAN DO BETTER.
>> AND IF YOU'RE NOT
DISAPPOINTED, AND SHE STEPS UP
AND SHE'S A MOM TO YOU
AND A GRANDMOTHER TO YOU,
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
OKAY?
BUT I HAVE NO RESPECT FOR HER.
AND I'M SORRY.
AND I THINK THAT'S FAIR.
>> AND I UNDERSTAND WHY--
WHY THAT'S YOUR--
>> OKAY, MY KIDS CAME FIRST.
THEY ALWAYS CAME FIRST.
YOU DON'T NEED TO WORRY ABOUT
A GROWN WOMAN THAT DOESN'T
GIVE A [bleep] ABOUT HERSELF.
I FEEL THIS IS THE BEST
ENVIRONMENT FOR THE BABY.
>> I FEEL THAT IT'S NOT.
I DON'T THINK THAT I WILL EVER
100% FULLY FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH YOU BEING ALONE
WITH THE BABY.
BECAUSE--
>> GOOD.
>> I'VE SEEN PERSONALLY
EVERYTHING THAT YOU'VE GONE
THROUGH.
YOU HAVE STROKES.
NOT YOUR FAULT.
BUT WHAT IF YOU WERE TO BE ALONE
WITH THE BABY AND HAVE ONE?
DO YOU SEE WHERE I'M COMING
FROM OR NOT REALLY?
>> NOPE.
>> IT DOESN'T WORRY YOU AT ALL
THAT YOU COULD POSSIBLY--
>> NO, BECAUSE I KNOW WHEN
I'M HAVING A STROKE, MILLINA.
THAT'S WHY I'M LIVING WITH MY
FRIEND.
MY FRIEND WANTS TO TAKE CARE
OF ME.
IT'S YOUR KID.
DO WHAT YOU WANT WITH IT.
>> I'M TRYING TO
TALK TO YOU AND HAVE YOU--
>> YOU WERE HONEST.
>> AND I DON'T--
>> YOU WERE HONEST ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T NOT WANT YOU AROUND
THE BABY.
>> HEY--
>> I DO.
I JUST DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE--
>> HEY, DO YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE BEEN NOTHING BUT THE BEST
[bleep] MOTHER IN THIS
[bleep]DAMN WORLD.
>> I'M NOT SAYING THAT YOU'RE
A BAD MOM, TINA.
>> THERE IS NOBODY IN THIS WORLD
THAT WOULDN'T TRUST ME
WITH THEIR [bleep] BABY.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT RIGHT
[bleep] NOW!
>> I'M NOT SAYING I DON'T TRUST
YOU WITH HIM.
I'M SAYING I DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH YOU BEING ALONE
WITH HIM.
>> THERE'S NOBODY IN THIS WORLD
THAT WOULDN'T TRUST ME
WITH THEIR [bleep] BABY ALONE!
>> NOW, I TRIED TO TALK TO YOU.
BUT CLEARLY--
>> NO, YOU'VE JUST TOLD ME
WHERE I STAND.
YOU DON'T TRUST ME ALONE
WITH YOUR BABY.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEEDED TO SAY.
>> I'VE TRIED TO TELL YOU THAT
BEFORE.
>> GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR MOM!
I HOPE SHE CAN HELP YOU!
>> AFTER THINGS GOT SO CRAZY
WITH TINA, TREVOR THOUGHT
IT'D BE BEST FOR HIM TO STAY
THERE AND SMOOTH THINGS OVER
WITH HER.
TREVOR'S MOM WENT COMPLETELY
APE[bleep] ON US.
SHE WAS LIKE, "BY THE WAY,
WE'RE MOVING THIS WEEK."
AND SHE GOT THERE
AND TALKED [bleep]
ABOUT MY MOM.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU JUST DON'T
BRING UP THAT SUBJECT TO HER.
YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE--
>> NO, I DON'T BRING IT UP.
SHE DOES.
>> I WOULD JUST--
I WOULD JUST TELL HER.
"YOU KNOW, I'D REALLY FEEL
UNCOMFORTABLE TALKING
ABOUT THIS RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW, CAN WE TALK ABOUT
SOMETHING ELSE?"
>> RIGHT, SO I TOLD HER THAT
I DIDN'T FEEL COMFORTABLE YET
MOVING IN.
SHE COMPLETELY BLEW UP.
>> BUT WHAT DOES HE SAY?
>> HE'S TRYING TO MAKE UP
WITH HIS MOM.
>> IT WOULD BE BETTER IF HE WAS
HOME WITH YOU.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> IT'S A SHAME BECAUSE THAT IS
TREVOR'S MOM, YOU KNOW,
AND NO MATTER WHAT HE SAYS,
SHE BROUGHT HIM INTO THIS WORLD.
HE LOVES HER.
>> RIGHT.
>> HE WANTS THAT ACCEPTANCE
FROM HER.
>> I'M DONE TRYING TO GET HER
TO LIKE ME.
I'M DONE TRYING TO CREATE
A RELATIONSHIP WITH HER.
I AM DONE TRYING.
IF I DECIDE, NO, HE'S NOT
GOING OVER THERE,
I'M KEEPING HIM,
THE ONLY WAY THAT HE CAN HAVE
ANY SAY IN IT IS IF HE TAKES
ME TO COURT.
I HOPE TREVOR CAN UNDERSTAND
THAT IT MIGHT BE A WHILE
BEFORE I CAN DEAL WITH HIS
MOM AGAIN.
I WANT TO TALK TO HIM
ABOUT IT, BUT IT MIGHT HAVE
TO WAIT, BECAUSE I STARTED
HAVING CONTRACTIONS.
NAN, COME HERE!
>> I'M HERE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> UM, I'M PRETTY SURE
IT'S TIME TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU, FIVE MINUTES
APART?
>> YEAH, BETWEEN TWO AND FIVE.
I'M PRETTY MUCH READY.
I TEXTED TREVOR ON THE WAY
TO THE HOSPITAL,
AND HE'S MEETING US THERE.
I AM IN SO MUCH PAIN RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW, MO.
YEAH, IT'S GONNA SUCK.
THE DOCTORS MEASURED ME
AT 4 CENTIMETERS
AND ADMITTED ME.
I'M REALLY SAD THAT MY MOM'S
NOT HERE, AND IT GOT REALLY
UNCOMFORTABLE WHEN I FOUND OUT
THAT TINA WAS IN THE WAITING
ROOM.
>> I HATE NOT KNOWING ANYTHING
AND SITTING HERE.
>> I DON'T GIVE A HELL WHO IT
IS.
I WILL KICK ANYBODY THE [bleep]
OUT THAT MAKES THIS ANY MORE
STRESSFUL FOR ME THAN IT HAS
TO BE.
[breathing rhythmically]
AND AFTER HOURS OF PAINFUL
CONTRACTIONS, IT WAS TIME
TO PUSH.
>> * TAKE IT ALL IN
* TAKE IT ALL IN
* NEVER FORGET THIS NIGHT
* THIS IS WHAT LOVE'S *
* ALL ABOUT
>> I GOT HOME A FEW DAYS AGO,
AND TREVOR'S BEEN TRYING
TO GET ME TO TAKE THE BABY
OVER TO HIS HOUSE TO SEE
HIS MOM.
BUT EVEN THOUGH I LET TINA
MEET KAYDEN BRIEFLY
AT THE HOSPITAL,
I'M WORRIED THAT IF I GO OVER
THERE, SHE COULD HAVE ANOTHER
CRAZY OUTBURST.
SO I FINALLY GOT THE BABY
ASLEEP.
>> ABOUT TIME.
TIRED?
>> I'M EXHAUSTED.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T GET THIS.
I REMEMBER WHEN I USED TO STAY
UP ON A DAILY BASIS FOR FUN.
[laughs]
>> NO MORE.
>> NOW I'M JUST LIKE--
>> SLEEP'S FUN.
>> YEAH, I'M JUST LIKE,
LET ME SLEEP.
>> WELL, JUST THINK:
HE WENT THROUGH THE MOST
GRUESOME, HORRIFIC MOMENT
OF HIS LIFE
THAT HE'LL NEVER REMEMBER.
>> YEAH, BUT THEN WHEN HE GETS
OLDER, IF HE'S ANYTHING
LIKE HIS DAD, HE CAME OUT
OF A WOMAN--HE'S GONNA SPEND
THE REST OF HIS LIFE TRYING
TO GET BACK IN ONE.
>> NOT ANYMORE.
[snickers]
AFTER WHAT I SAW, I'M GOOD.
>> WAS IT REALLY THAT BAD?
>> MM-HMM.
AFTER WATCHING YOUR PRETTY
VAGINA GO FROM A VAGINA
TO STARGATE AND A BABY COME
FLYING OUT, IT KIND OF CHANGES
THE BALL GAME.
[cell phone chiming]
HELLO?
YES, LET ME CALL YOU BACK
IN A FEW.
LOVE YOU TOO.
BYE.
>> WHO WAS THAT?
>> MY MOTHER.
>> IS SHE OKAY?
>> YEAH, SHE'S FINE.
>> OH, SHE SOUNDED LIKE
SHE WAS UPSET.
>> NO, SHE'S FINE.
SINCE SHE MOVED OUT OF THE
HOUSE, AND SINCE KAYDEN WAS
BORN, MOM IS...
DOING BETTER
AND SHE'S REALLY TRYING
TO GET RID OF ALL THE,
YOU KNOW, NEGATIVE THINGS
THAT HAVE HAPPENED
AND TRYING TO MOVE PAST
THEM ALL.
>> EVEN THOUGH SHE'S,
LIKE, BETTER, THOUGH, LIKE,
I'M SO KIND OF WORRIED
SHE'S GONNA FREAK OUT AGAIN.
>> RIGHT, BUT, I MEAN,
RIGHT NOW SHE
SEEMS LIKE HER OLD SELF AGAIN.
SO, I MEAN, THE ONLY WAY
YOU CAN REALLY, YOU KNOW,
MAKE THE ASSESSMENT YOURSELF
IS BY SEEING HER YOURSELF.
>> I DON'T WANT HER TO SEE
THE BABY TILL HE GETS A LITTLE
BIT OLDER.
>> WELL, HOW LONG ARE WE
TALKING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M TRYING TO COME UP
WITH A SOLUTION THAT'S GOOD
FOR EVERYBODY, AND IT SEEMS
LIKE IT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOU.
>> I NEVER SAID THAT.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
I KNOW WHAT YOUR PLANS ARE.
>> IT'S REALLY HARD TO DEAL
WITH ALL OF THE SITUATIONS
AT ONE TIME, SO I'M JUST KIND OF
TRYING TO FOCUS ON KAYDEN
AND THEN FOCUS ON EVERYTHING
ELSE.
I GOT KISSES.
SINCE TREVOR AND NAN ARE BOTH
WORKING A LOT, I'M ALONE
WITH KAYDEN MOST OF THE TIME.
AND IT MAKES ME REALLY WISH
MY MOM WERE AROUND TO HELP.
HI, PUMPKIN.
OH, NO.
YOU'RE WET.
YOU GOT LOTS AND LOTS
OF POO-POOS IN THERE.
>> YOU MAY BEGIN SPEAKING NOW.
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
>> HI, MAMA.
>> HEY, PUMPKIN.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> UM, I MISS YOU.
>> UM, I MISS YOU TOO.
>> I HATE BEING AWAY FROM YOU.
>> [chuckles]
THE BABY IS SLEEPING ON ME.
>> AW, I WANTED TO SEE HIM
BE BORN SO BAD.
[baby coos]
>> [laughs]
>> AW, I HEARD HIM.
AW.
>> HE SAYS HELLO.
>> HELLO, BABY.
>> HE SAYS, "HMM."
[giggles]
>> I JUST CAN'T WAIT FOR THIS
TO BE OVER.
>> WHEN--ONCE YOU GO TO REHAB,
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG
IT'S GONNA TAKE YOU
TO BE ABLE TO GET VISITS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT DEPENDS ON WHAT THEY--
YEAH, IT DEPENDS ON WHERE
THEY SEND ME.
IT DEPENDS--IT DEPENDS
ON SO MUCH--
>> [automated voice] REMAINING.
>> OH, MY GOD, IT ALWAYS GOES BY
SO FAST.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I LOVE YOU?
>> A LOT.
>> I REALLY DO.
>> I LOVE YOU, TOO, MOM.
>> SORRY I MESSED UP EVERYTHING.
>> YOU KNOW, MOM, JUST...
YOU GOT TO JUST MAKE SURE
THAT YOU GET [bleep] TOGETHER.
RIGHT, I LOVE YOU, MAMA.
>> I LOVE YOU, SWEETHEART.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
I GIVE HIM KISSES.
WE'RE GONNA--
>> HUGS AND KISSES.
>> I'M GONNA TRY TO COME
TO YOUR COURT DATE, DEPENDING.
YOU KNOW, IF I SHOW UP
A LITTLE BIT LATER--
>> I THINK IT'S--
[automated voice interrupts]
>> ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
BYE-BYE.
I'M REALLY SAD ABOUT MY MOM'S
SITUATION, AND IT'S NOT HELPING
THAT TINA KEEPS BLOWING UP
MY PHONE, TRYING TO GET ME
TO BRING THE BABY OVER THERE.
[phone clicking]
WHY AM I SUPPOSED
TO DROP EVERYTHING I'M DOING
TO RUSH OVER TO THE PHONE
AND MAKE SURE THAT YOUR MOM'S
NOT PISSED OFF AT ME.
I DON'T EVEN ANSWER THE PHONE
LIKE THAT TO MY FAMILY.
I DIDN'T CALL BACK BECAUSE,
GOD FORBID, I TAKE A LITTLE
BIT OF TIME TO MYSELF
WHILE THE BABY'S SLEEPING.
I WENT AND I GOT HIS [bleep]
FINISHED.
I DYED MY HAIR.
I TOOK A SHOWER.
I ATE SOME FOOD.
I FEEL LIKE, IF YOU AND I--
OUR RELATIONSHIP WOULD WORK
IF OUR FAMILIES STAYED
THE [bleep] OUT OF IT.
'CAUSE IT'S LIKE, YOU AND I
ARE FINE UNTIL EVERYBODY ELSE
STEPS IN.
APPARENTLY YOU.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I GUESS
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
>> TODAY IS MY MOM'S COURT DATE,
AND EVEN THOUGH IT'S FREEZING
OUT, I'M TAKING KAYDEN WITH ME
SO THAT SHE CAN SEE HIM.
>> COURT'S BACK IN SESSION.
PLEASE BE SEATED.
>> I'M HERE, YOUR HONOR.
>> PEOPLE VS. KUKULA.
>> READY, YOUR HONOR.
>> TODAY IS THE DATE AND TIME
SET FOR SENTENCING.
>> GOOD MORNING, YOUR HONOR.
MAY IT PLEASE THE COURT,
REGINA TRIPLETT ON BEHALF
OF MS. KUKULA, WHO'S STANDING
TO MY RIGHT.
TODAY IS THE DAY AND TIME
SCHEDULED FOR SENTENCING.
WE'RE ASKING THE COURT
FOR AN EXPEDITED REHAB
TO INPATIENT SO THAT SHE
CAN GET THE TREATMENT
THAT SHE NEEDS.
>> RIGHT.
DO YOU WISH TO SAY ANYTHING
BEFORE I SENTENCE YOU?
>> I'VE HAD A LOT OF TIME
TO THINK, AND I'VE BEEN
THROUGH SOME HORRIBLE THINGS
AS AN ADDICT.
I REGRET A LOT OF THINGS
RIGHT NOW,
THINGS THAT WILL LAST FOREVER.
MY GRANDSON WAS BORN.
AND I WASN'T THERE FOR THAT.
EXCUSE ME.
NOT THERE FOR MY CHILDREN
THE WAY I SHOULD BE.
AND I'VE LET DOWN A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
I NEED TO GET HELP,
AND I NEED TO GET IT RIGHT
THIS TIME.
>> WELL, IF YOU GET OUT OF JAIL,
WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO?
>> I WANT TO GO INTO AN
INPATIENT REHAB.
I WANT TO GET BETTER SO BAD.
NOT JUST FOR FAMILY,
BUT FOR MYSELF.
I KNOW I'M CAPABLE OF BETTER.
I NEED HELP.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA
SENTENCE YOU...
TO 200 DAYS IN MACOMB COUNTY
JAIL.
>> I CAN'T.
I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
>> I UNDERSTAND,
BUT I HEARD THIS SPEECH
A MILLION TIMES.
A LOT OF TIMES, A LOT OF PEOPLE,
THEY GO IN THE FRONT DOOR
OF THE INPATIENT,
THEY GO OUT THE BACK DOOR.
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, AND GOOD LUCK.
>> I'M REALLY BUMMED
THAT MY MOM'S GONNA BE AWAY
FOR SO LONG.
I USED TO HAVE TREVOR
TO LEAN ON WHEN THINGS WENT
DOWNHILL, BUT EVER SINCE OUR
FIGHT ABOUT HIS MOM LAST WEEK,
HE WON'T EVER ANSWER MY CALLS.
>> YOUR CALL HAS BEEN FORWARDED
TO AN AUTOMATIC VOICE
MESSAGE SYSTEM.
>> ARE YOU ALREADY FREAKING OUT
AWAY FROM THE BABY?
>> YEAH.
I WANT TO CALL NAN RIGHT NOW
AND JUST BE LIKE, "HEY,
IS HE OKAY?"
>> [chuckles]
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU GOT OUT WITHOUT THE BABY?
>> NEVER.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> YEAH.
>> [laughing] OH, MY GOD.
>> YOU'VE BEEN SPENDING
SO MUCH TIME THINKING ABOUT
YOUR MOM AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
HAVE YOU EVEN, LIKE, THOUGHT
ABOUT MAYBE, LIKE, GOING BACK
TO SCHOOL OR--
>> I WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL,
BUT IF THAT CAN'T BE FIGURED
OUT, I'M DEFINITELY GONNA GET
MY G.E.D.
NOW WE JUST GOT TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT TO DO WITH TREVOR.
>> HOW OFTEN DOES HE EVEN
SEE KAYDEN?
>> HE HASN'T COME OVER.
>> LIKE, AT ALL?
>> I THINK MAYBE ONCE OR TWICE.
>> WHAT?
THAT'S AWESOME.
DO YOU EVER BRING KAYDEN OVER
TO TREVOR'S?
>> WELL, THE LAST TIME I WENT
OVER THERE, HIS MOM
COMPLETELY FREAKED.
AND THEN SHE STARTED SCREAMING
AND YELLING.
AND I DON'T WANT KAYDEN AROUND
THAT.
THERE'S NO COMMUNICATING WITH
HER.
IT'S ALWAYS HER.
>> SHE'S JUST LIKE--
LIKE, SHE DOESN'T ACTUALLY
LISTEN TO YOUR INPUT.
SHE JUST--
>> IT'S HER WAY OR--
>> THE HIGHWAY?
>> YEAH.
THE WAY YOU JUST DESCRIBED
HOW HIS MOM ACTS,
I DON'T GET WHY TREVOR
WOULDN'T, LIKE, WANT
TO, LIKE, LEAVE THAT
AND, LIKE, COME AND STAY
WITH YOU AND HIS SON.
>> YOU KNOW, HE'S NOT COMING
OVER.
IT'S MORE, "YOU COME OVER."
IT'S LIKE WE'RE BEST FRIENDS
THAT GOT DRUNK, HAD AN "UH-OH,"
AND NOW WE HAVE A BIG "UH-OH."
I JUST WANT HIM TO BE THERE
FOR HIS KID.
>> EXACTLY.
>> KAYDEN CAME DOWN WITH A COLD
AFTER I TOOK HIM TO THE
COURTHOUSE.
[baby crying]
>> YOU'RE LIKE THE LONE RANGER
OVER HERE, EH?
>> YEAH.
AND I DON'T LIKE HOW DISTANT
TREVOR AND I HAVE BECOME.
I'M RUNNING OUT OF OPTIONS.
[door squeaking]
>> OH, HI, HANDSOME.
>> [chuckles]
YEAH, COME TO DADDY.
>> HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
I'M IN LOVE WITH HIM.
>> AW.
>> YOU DON'T REALLY REALIZE
HOW HARD IT IS ACTUALLY
TAKING CARE OF HIM.
I'M DOING IT ALL BY MYSELF NOW.
IT'S LIKE, HOW OFTEN HAVE
WE SEEN EACH OTHER?
>> I KNOW I WAS SUPPOSED
TO, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
BE OVER MORE, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, LIKE, I THINK HE'S
BETTER OFF HERE.
IT'S JUST, HERE THERE'S MORE
PEOPLE TO HELP YOU.
>> YOU ARE ALWAYS WELCOME
TO COME HERE.
AND I HAVE ACCOMMODATIONS
FOR THE BABY HERE.
>> I FEEL LIKE IF YOU'RE
GONNA GO AND NOT BE NICE TO ME,
WHY WOULD I WANT TO BE AROUND?
>> I HAVE NEVER--
>> WHY WOULD I WANT MY CHILD--
>> I HAVE NEVER NOT BEEN NICE
TO YOU.
[baby crying]
I FEEL LIKE I DIDN'T GET
A CHANCE TO BOND WITH
MY GRANDCHILD,
AND THAT IT'S--
YOU'RE NOT SHARING.
I DON'T FEEL YOU'RE SHARING.
>> BUT I WASN'T GONNA TAKE
HIM OUT WHILE HE WAS SICK.
I WAITED UNTIL HE GOT BETTER,
AND THEN WE CAME OVER.
>> SOUNDS LIKE A LOT OF EXCUSES.
>> IT'S NOT EVEN EXCUSES.
IT'S WHAT'S ACTUALLY GOING ON.
>> HE WENT TO SEE YOUR MOTHER.
>> AND THAT'S WHERE HE GOT SICK.
>> OKAY, WELL, WAS THAT
A GOOD CHOICE?
>> WELL, I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT BABY HAS NO IMMUNE SYSTEM.
I WOULD NEVER HAVE DONE THAT.
>> YEAH, BUT THAT WAS THE ONLY
WAY HE COULD HAVE SEEN MY MOM,
SO I BROUGHT HIM--
>> SEND THEM A PICTURE.
>> YOU CAN'T.
>> SHE PUT HERSELF THERE.
>> SEND A POSTCARD.
>> YOU CAN'T SEND PICTURES.
>> I AGREE WITH TINA.
>> SHE PUT HERSELF THERE.
>> SHE DID IT TO HERSELF.
>> AND QUIT ENABLING--
>> YEAH.
>> I'M NOT ENABLING ANYTHING.
>> HE'S IN THE SAME PREDICAMENT
AS HE'S IN THERE.
>> DON'T BE MAD AT THE BABY.
>> I'M NOT. I'M BURPING HIM.
>> CAN I HOLD THE BABY
AND BURP HIM?
>> IT'S A LOSING SITUATION--
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO MAKE YOU
ANGRY.
I'M TRYING TO TALK TO YOU.
TALK TO ME.
>> I DON'T EVEN--
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY.
>> DO YOU WANT TO TALK
PRIVATELY TO ME?
>> NO, IT'S JUST, I SERIOUSLY
DON'T...
>> MILLINA, I WANT TO HELP YOU,
AND OFFERING YOU MY LOVE.
I UNDERSTAND YOU DIDN'T HAVE
A LOT OF LOVE, MILLINA,
AND I'M OFFERING YOU MY LOVE.
THAT'S ALL.
I JUST HAVE EVERYBODY GANGING UP
ON ME.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> IT REALLY HURTS
THAT NOBODY UNDERSTANDS
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
NOT EVEN TREVOR.
>> HOLA.
>> [laughs]
>> WHAT'S BUGGING YOU?
>> I HATE HOW PEOPLE CHANGE.
>> SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I MEAN, I'M TRYING TO MAKE
EVERYBODY HAPPY, AND...
SEEMS LIKE IN THE END,
EVERYONE'S MISERABLE.
>> OUR RELATIONSHIP SHOULDN'T
BE ABOUT EVERYBODY ELSE.
SHOULD BE ABOUT THE THREE OF US.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
[baby cooing]
>> HERE.
COME ON.
>> WHAT IS IT THAT YOU WANT?
>> I WANT YOU TO SPEND MORE
TIME WITH KAYDEN.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
IT'S NOT ABOUT ME.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOUR MOTHER.
THE CHOICES THAT I MAKE
HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH ANYTHING
EXCEPT FOR WHAT I THINK
IS IN HIS BEST INTEREST.
AND THEN I GET BITCHED AT
WHEN I DO WHAT'S BEST FOR HIM.
AND I GET TALKED DOWN TO
AND I GET CALLED MEAN NAMES.
I MEAN, IF YOU CAME TO MY HOUSE,
AND EVERY SINGLE TIME
YOU CAME TO MY HOUSE,
NAN SAT THERE AND TOLD YOU
EVERYTHING THAT WAS WRONG
WITH YOU, WOULD YOU WANT
TO COME OVER?
>> NO.
>> I MEAN, WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
YOU ACTUALLY FELT LIKE
WE WERE TOGETHER.
[baby hiccupping]
>> MM, THE DAY KAYDEN WAS BORN.
>> EXACTLY.
[baby hiccupping]
>> RIGHT NOW I THINK
WE SHOULD STOP WORRYING
ABOUT YOU AND I...
AND JUST KIND OF WORK ON
WORKING TOGETHER FOR KAYDEN.
COME HERE, YOU.
I THINK WE JUST NEED
TO TAKE A STEP BACK
AND FOCUS ON THIS LITTLE GUY.
[baby crying]
WHAT?
>> DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE GONNA
BE HERE MORE FOR HIM?
>> NO, I'M GONNA COME AROUND
AS MUCH AS I CAN.
[baby cooing]
>> THIS ISN'T HOW I WANTED
IT TO BE WITH TREVOR,
BECAUSE I...
DIDN'T WANT KAYDEN
TO GROW UP IN A BROKEN HOME.
IN THE BEGINNING, IT WAS
LIKE ME AND TREVOR WERE ON
THE SAME TEAM.
BUT NOW IT'S MORE SO LIKE,
INSTEAD OF FIGHTING TOGETHER,
WE'RE FIGHTING WITH EACH OTHER.
>> CAN I HAVE A HUG?
>> BEFORE I HAD KAYDEN,
I WAS ALWAYS AT THE CLUB.
I WAS ALWAYS NOT MAKING
THE BEST DECISIONS.
BUT NOW THAT I HAVE KAYDEN,
I HAVE TO THINK OF,
WHAT AM I DOING RIGHT NOW,
AND HOW IS IT GONNA AFFECT
NOT ONLY ME, BUT KAYDEN?
[mid-tempo rock music]
*
>> * I NEED MY PEOPLE
* YEAH, I NEED MY PEOPLE
>> AS FAR AS SCHOOL GOES,
HAVING MY SON, IT JUST MAKES IT
THAT MUCH HARDER.
I DO PLAN TO AT LEAST GO
AND GET MY G.E.D.
ME HAVING AN EDUCATION
WILL HELP KAYDEN IN A LOT
OF WAYS.
>> THIS CALL WILL BE RECORDED
AND SUBJECT TO MONITORING
AT ANY TIME.
>> HI, PUMPKIN.
>> MY MOM USED TO BE
A REALLY GOOD MOM.
SHE JUST GOT CAUGHT UP
IN DRUGS.
>> IT WOULD BE NICE
IF I COULD GET, LIKE,
A DAY OUT, YOU KNOW,
AND HOLD THE BABY.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT THAT KAYDEN
NEVER HAS TO FEEL THE THINGS
THAT I FELT.
>> * AND I NEED MY PEOPLE
*
>> YOU BEING SORRY.
DON'T BE LIKE MY DAD.
I'M NOT GONNA BE THE ONLY ONE
TAKING CARE OF HIM FINANCIALLY.
>> I WILL BRING EVERYTHING
TO YOUR HOUSE WHEN I FEEL LIKE
IT'S NECESSARY.
>> IT'S NECESSARY NOW.
I WANT TO SEE HIM DO GOOD.
I REALLY, TRULY DO,
FOR THE BABY.
[baby crying]
BUT YOU GOT TO OWN UP
TO WHAT YOU DID WRONG.
>> YOU BE WRONG TOO.
>> I'M LEAVING.