>> OHHH.
HI, I'M ALLIE.
I'M 16 YEARS OLD.
I JUST STARTED MY SENIOR YEAR OF
HIGH SCHOOL, AND I'M SO READY TO
MAKE THE MOST OF MY LAST YEAR
BEFORE I GRADUATE.
SENIOR IS KIND OF BRUTAL,
BUT, LIKE, I LIKE IT.
I LIVE IN PASADENA, TEXAS,
BUT I'M NO TEXAN.
I HATE TEXAS.
TWO YEARS AGO, WHEN MY DAD
MOVE FROM NEW JERSEY TO TEXAS,
I HAD TO GO WITH HIM, BECAUSE AT
THE TIME, MY MOM COULDN'T AFFORD
TO HAVE ME STAY WITH HER.
LEAVING MY MOM BEHIND WAS HARD,
BUT AT LEAST WE TALK ALL THE
TIME.
>> HI.
I'VE MADE A FEW NEW FRIENDS
HERE, AND SINCE I STARTED DATING
MY BOYFRIEND JOEY, TEXAS HAS
GOTTEN A LITTLE BETTER.
HE'S ONLY A SOPHOMORE, BUT HE'S
ON THE FOOTBALL TEAM, SO I CAN
OVERLOOK THAT ONE SMALL FLAW.
GO, JOEY.
WE GOOF AROUND AND HAVE A LOT OF
FUN TOGETHER, BUT THINGS ARE
ABOUT TO GET SERIOUS, BECAUSE
I'M PREGNANT.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
EVERYONE MADE FUN OF ME FOR
DATING A SOPHOMORE, BUT NOW THAT
I'M FIVE MONTHS PREGNANT,
ALL ANYONE NOTICES IS MY BELLY.
>> I REMEMBER WHEN YOU FIRST
HANDED ME THAT PREGNANCY TEST.
IT CAME OUT POSITIVE.
I WAS, LIKE, SO SHOCKED.
WE WERE, LIKE, GOING OUT FOR,
LIKE, A MONTH OR TWO.
>> LIKE, TWO MONTHS.
WELL, WHEN WE FOUND OUT, IT WAS,
LIKE, THREE MONTHS, 'CAUSE WE
DIDN'T KNOW AT FIRST.
I NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD HAPPEN,
'CAUSE I WAS ON THE PILL OR
WHATEVER, AND I MISSED A
COUPLE OF DAYS, BUT IT'S NOT
LIKE YOU ASK, LIKE, WHEN YOU'RE
IN THAT MOMENT, NO ONE STOPS
AND--WELL, NOW I'M GONNA STOP
AND THINK, BUT, LIKE, IT'S NOT
LIKE YOU ASK, "HEY, DID YOU MISS
YOUR PILL TODAY?"
>> YEAH, YOU DON'T THINK THAT.
>> YEAH, BECAUSE THEN THE
MOOD'S JUST, LIKE, PBBT AFTER
THAT.
SO MANY PEOPLE IN SCHOOL ASKED
ME, LIKE, THEY'RE LIKE, "OH,
SINCE YOU GUYS ARE HAVING A
BABY, ARE YOU GETTING MARRIED?"
LIKE, IS THAT, LIKE, A RULE,
IF YOU HAVE A KID YOU HAVE TO
GET MARRIED?
I WAS LIKE, "NO."
I'D RATHER YOU WANT TO GET
MARRIED, LIKE, 'CAUSE WE LOVE
EACH OTHER.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE I DON'T WANT
TO RUSH INTO THINGS, LIKE,
GIVE IT TIME.
>> WELL, DON'T YOU THINK WE'RE
RUSHING INTO THINGS NOW?
>> YES, BUT THE MARRIAGE--
>> YEAH, THAT'S A CHOICE.
ARE YOU SCARED?
>> YES, I'M SCARED.
>> I'M SCARED.
[laughs]
NONE OF MY FRIENDS ARE IN ANY OF
MY CLASSES THIS SEMESTER.
LET ME GET THE DOOR FOR YOU
LADIES.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> AND NOW THAT I'M STARTING TO
SHOW, THEY WANT TO KNOW HOW IT'S
GOING.
>> LIKE, HOW DOES IT FEEL IN
SCHOOL, LIKE, YOU KNOW,
HOW YOU HAVE A BIG BELLY?
LIKE, IS EVERYONE ALWAYS
STARING?
LIKE, DO THEY TALK ABOUT YOU AND
STUFF?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW IF PEOPLE
TALK ABOUT ME, BUT PEOPLE STARE.
GIRLS WHO STARE LIKE THAT, I'M
LIKE...
>> [laughs]
>> DOING THE EYEBROW THING.
>> YEAH, I LOOK AT THEM LIKE,
"HELLO."
>> BUT YOURS DOESN'T LOOK THAT
BIG--
>> EXACTLY.
THAT'S WHY PEOPLE ARE LIKE, "IS
SHE OR IS SHE NOT?"
>> I TOLD MY MOM, AND MY MOM WAS
LIKE, "OH, GET AN ABORTION,"
RIGHT AWAY.
>> WHAT?
>> AND THEN I TOLD MY DAD,
AND THEN MY DAD DIDN'T TALK TO
ME FOR, LIKE, A WEEK, AND AFTER
A WEEK, HE WAS LIKE, "YOU GET
ADOPTION OR GET OUT."
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
WHY WOULD YOUR PARENTS KICK YOU
OUT WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT?
>> I WOULD NEVER KICK OUT MY
KID.
>> EXACTLY.
>> LIKE, I CAN'T GO TO MY MOM'S.
IF I GO TO MY MOM'S HOUSE, THEN
ME AND JOEY ARE NOT TOGETHER,
'CAUSE SHE'S IN NEW JERSEY.
YEAH.
>> HOW DOES JOEY FEEL ABOUT ALL
THIS, LIKE, BEING A DAD?
>> HE SAID HE'S READY NOW.
IF YOU ASK HIM, "ARE YOU READY
TO BE A PARENT?"
"YEAH, I'M READY TO BE A
PARENT."
IT'S LIKE, "NO, YOU'RE NOT."
[laughter]
JOEY ISN'T READY FOR A LOT OF
THINGS, AND NEITHER AM I.
WE DEFINITELY AREN'T READY TO
LIVE TOGETHER WITH JOEY'S
PARENTS, BUT THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE
TO DO, BECAUSE AFTER I TOLD MY
DAD I WAS PREGNANT, I HAD TO
MOVE OUT.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME THAT MY
BABY HAS BOTH PARENTS, SO GOING
TO MY MOM'S IN NEW JERSEY WASN'T
AN OPTION.
MY ONLY CHOICE IS TO LIVE WITH
JOEY'S PARENTS, WHICH MAKES ME
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I CAN TELL
JOEY'S MOM REALLY DOESN'T WANT
ME TO BE THERE.
>> I MET HER ONE DAY, AND THEN
THE NEXT TIME WAS, "SHE'S
PREGNANT."
I MEAN, RIGHT THERE WE WENT.
>> HOW'D YOU FEEL WHEN I TEXTED
YOU SAYING ALLISON WAS PREGNANT?
>> I WAS LIKE, "OH, NO.
WHAT THE HECK IS WRONG WITH
JOEY?"
WHAT DID YOU FRIENDS THINK,
JOEY?
>> THEY THOUGHT I WAS JOKING.
>> MM-MM.
>> EVERYBODY WAS SAYING I'M
SCREWED.
>> YOU'RE SCREWED?
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
I TOOK CARE OF A BABY, WENT TO
SCHOOL, HELPED HER, AND WORKED.
IT SUCKS.
>> ABORTION OR ADOPTION,
IS THAT AN OPTION?
DID Y'ALL EVER THINK ABOUT IT?
>> NOPE.
>> DIDN'T?
>> NEVER.
>> I DON'T REALLY BELIEVE IN
THAT.
>> MY MOM AND DAD DO.
>> WHAT ARE Y'ALL GONNA DO AFTER
THE BABY'S BORN?
WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
>> LIKE, WITH WHAT?
>> WHERE ARE Y'ALL GONNA BE
STAYING AT?
>> HOPEFULLY, EVERYTHING GOES
GOOD.
>> WHEN I MOVED IN TWO MONTHS
AGO, JOEY WARNED ME THAT
HIS MOM HAS STRUGGLED WITH DRUGS
FOR A LONG TIME,
WHICH MEANS WE NEVER KNOW WHAT
SHE'S GOING TO SAY OR DO.
>> COME INSIDE.
DAMIEN, GET IN.
I TOLD YOU.
I DONE TOLD YOU I DIDN'T WANT TO
SEE HIM.
I KNEW THIS WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
I NEED A FIX.
>> JOEY AND I SPEND A LOT OF
TIME WISHING WE HAD OTHER
OPTIONS.
>> SLOW DOWN.
I'M FAT AND PREGNANT.
>> [laughs]
>> I KNOW IT'S YOUR MOM, BUT SHE
KIND OF DOES AFFECT THE BABY.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT IS SHE'S, LIKE, NOT CLEAN
AROUND HIM OR SOMETHING,
HOWEVER YOU SAY THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE YOU KNOW HOW SHE GETS
ANGRY?
WHAT IF SHE DOES SOMETHING AND
HURTS HIM?
>> YEAH, SHE GETS ANGRY EASILY.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T WANT HIM IN A PLACE
THAT'S NOT SAFE FOR HIM.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE.
I'D RATHER BE IN PASADENA
WITH YOUR GRANDMA.
>> YEAH, IT'S MUCH MORE SAFER IN
PASADENA.
[sighs]
>> PASADENA IS ONLY 20 MINUTES
AWAY, AND WE'D LIKE TO LIVE WITH
JOEY'S GRANDMA,
BUT SHE FEELS THERE ISN'T ENOUGH
ROOM FOR ALL OF US.
STILL, IT'S GOOD TO GO OVER
THERE JUST TO VENT.
I'M GONNA FAIL HIGH SCHOOL.
I'M NOT EVEN GONNA GRADUATE IF
WE STAY OVER THERE.
THERE'S PEOPLE COMING IN AND
OUT, LIKE, 1:00 IN THE MORNING,
LIKE, 2:00 IN THE MORNING, LIKE,
AND THEY'RE ALL--CONSTANT
YELLING.
>> SHE YELLS ALL THE TIME.
>> THEY BOTH YELL, AND THEN WHEN
SHE GOES TO BED, THE WHOLE HOUSE
HAS TO SHUT UP, OR SHE'LL HAVE A
FIT.
>> WHAT?
>> JOEY COULD HAVE THE TV UP A
LITTLE.
SHE'LL TEXT JOEY, "TURN DOWN
THAT F-ING TV, BLAH, BLAH,
BLAH."
LIKE, IT'S JUST NOT GOOD.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S ALWAYS TALKING BAD
ABOUT MY DAD.
LIKE, "OH, YOUR DAD DOESN'T DO
NOTHING FOR Y'ALL, BLAH, BLAH,
BLAH," AND I'M LIKE, "NEITHER
DO YOU."
>> DRUGS HAVE REALLY JUST MESSED
UP HER MIND.
SHE STILL DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT IT TAKES TO BE A PARENT.
YOU THINK THAT $5 HERE AND A
HAMBURGER IS A PARENT?
IT'S NOT EASY, YOU BRING A
BABY IN THE WORLD.
IT'S NOT EASY AT ALL.
>> IT'S NOT EASY, BUT HIS
PARENTS DO THIS LITTLE EXTRA
STRESSING.
WHILE JOEY'S GRANDMA HASN'T
OFFERED TO TAKE US IN, SHE IS
TRYING TO HELP US BY BRINGING
EVERYONE TOGETHER AT HER PLACE
TO DISCUSS A PLAN FOR WHEN THE
BABY COMES.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA DO SCHOOL
WHEN YOU HAVE THE BABY?
ARE YOU GONNA BE HOMEBOUND OR
WHAT?
>> DAY CARE.
>> THAT BABY IS NOT GOING TO DAY
CARE.
>> WELL, THEN, WHO'S GONNA TAKE
CARE HER?
WE ALL WORK.
>> WELL, MY FRIEND WAS TELLING
ME ABOUT THIS PLACE THAT SHE PUT
HER BABY WHEN IT WAS BORN.
IT WAS, LIKE, ONE MONTH, AND IT
WAS RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO OUR
SCHOOL.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S A DAY CARE?
>> YEAH, SHE GETS IT THERE FOR
FREE, 'CAUSE HER AND HER
BOYFRIEND ARE BOTH IN SCHOOL.
>> YOU TRUST DAY CARES?
YOU TRUST DAY CARES?
>> WELL, THERE ARE GOOD DAY
CARES.
THERE ARE GOOD DAY CARES.
>> MOTHER, YOU DIDN'T EVEN LIKE
ME TO PUT MY KIDS IN DAY CARE,
SO DON'T EVEN TRY IT.
>> WHO?
>> YOU.
>> 'CAUSE AT THAT TIME, IT WAS
BAD.
THINGS ARE DIFFERENT.
NOW THEY HAVE CAMERAS.
WELL, THAT'S THE ONLY OPTION
THEY HAVE.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOUR DAD?
IS HE GONNA HELP YOU OUT IN ANY
WAY?
>> WHAT, WITH THE BABY?
YEAH, HE SAID HE WOULD.
NOW HE'S STARTING TO COME
AROUND.
>> IT REALLY JUST PISSED ME OFF
WHEN HER DAD WAS LIKE, "WELL,
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO LIVE UNDER
THE BRIDGE SOMEWHERE, 'CAUSE
YOU'RE NOT LIVING WITH ME."
>> OH, NO.
>> HE DID THROW YOU OUT OF THE
HOUSE.
HE TOLD YOU YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
I DIDN'T GET RID OF HER WHEN SHE
CAME OUT PREGNANT.
"OH, GET OUT OF THE HOUSE.
YOU NEED TO LEAVE NOW."
THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
REGARDLESS, THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
WE TAKE CARE OF OUR OWN.
I'M SORRY.
>> YEAH, WE DO.
WE DO.
>> I DON'T LIKE WHEN YOUSE ALL
TALK ABOUT HIM BAD, BUT HE DID
DO THAT BAD, SO I JUST TAKE IT.
>> HE'S MY DAD.
>> WELL, YEAH, THAT'S--I MEAN,
I UNDERSTAND THAT, BECAUSE YOU
DON'T HAVE NOBODY HERE.
YOU'RE ALONE HERE.
THE THING ABOUT IT IS THAT Y'ALL
ARE GONNA FINISH SCHOOL.
Y'ALL ARE GONNA GO OUT AND GET A
CAREER, AND THAT'S THE BEST
THING THAT Y'ALL CAN DO.
>> I WANT TO STAY TO RAISE THE
BABY WITH JOEY, BUT I'M NOT SURE
HIS MOM'S HOUSE IS THE BEST
PLACE TO DO IT.
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
I'M 6 1/2 MONTHS PREGNANT, AND
WITH ALL THE STRESS OF LIVING AT
JOEY'S, I CAN'T WAIT FOR PHONE
CALLS WITH MY MOM.
>> WHEN ARE YOU GONNA COME?
>> YEAH, BUT ARE YOU GONNA COME,
LIKE, AFTER HE'S BORN?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BYE.
SCHOOL ISN'T JUST IMPORTANT TO
MY MOM.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME TOO.
GRADUATING ON TIME AND WITH GOOD
GRADES IS A MUST.
THE BABY IS DUE RIGHT AROUND MY
CHRISTMAS BREAK, SO AS LONG AS I
CAN STAY ON TRACK, I'LL ONLY
HAVE ONE SEMESTER LEFT AFTER
HE'S BORN.
KEEPING UP WITH GRADES WHILE I'M
PREGNANT IS STRESSFUL, BUT AT
LEAST THERE ARE FUN PARTS OF
BEING A SENIOR, LIKE THE
HOMECOMING DANCE.
>> WE'RE GONNA DANCE EVERY DANCE
THAT WE POSSIBLY CAN, OKAY?
>> [laughs]
>> THIS IS OUR LAST HOMECOMING
NOT AS PARENTS YET.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DANCE.
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU EMBARRASSED, LIKE,
PEOPLE WILL LOOK AT US?
>> NO, I JUST--
>> OR ARE YOU EMBARRASSED 'CAUSE
YOU THINK I'LL MAKE FUN OF YOU?
>> PROBABLY.
YEAH, THAT.
>> I WOULD NEVER MAKE FUN.
DON'T BE NERVOUS.
I CAN'T DANCE THAT GOOD.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DANCE AT
ALL.
WHEN SOMEONE, LIKE, TRIES TO
FORCE ME TO DANCE,
I WILL JUST, LIKE, RUN OFF.
>> [laughs]
>> I'VE NEVER DANCED.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO FORCE
YOU.
LIKE, IF YOU REALLY DON'T WANT
TO, WE DON'T HAVE TO, BUT I DO
WANT TO A LITTLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THIS IS OUR FIRST DANCE
TOGETHER.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME YOU'VE EVER
SEEN ME IN A DRESS.
YOU KNOW THAT?
>> YEAH.
ARE YOU ALMOST FINISHED?
I'M PUTTING ON MY SHOES.
HOPEFULLY, MY PREGNANT SELF CAN
WALK IN THESE.
>> NICE.
>> [laughs]
THANKS.
>> YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
>> THANKS.
YOU WANT TO HELP ME ZIPPER THIS
NOW?
[laughs]
STOP.
YOU'RE MAKING ME BLUSH.
DANCING IS SO FUN, EVEN IF I
HAVE A BIG BELLY.
FOR ONCE, I WANT TO FORGET
ABOUT THE STRESSES OF LIVING
WITH JOEY'S FAMILY AND JUST BE A
TEENAGER.
JOEY AND I USUALLY MEET UP AFTER
SCHOOL JUST TO HANG OUT, BUT
TODAY I HAVE A CHECKUP WITH THE
DOCTOR.
SINCE NEITHER OF US CAN DRIVE,
THAT MEANS A BUS RIDE AND A LONG
WALK.
>> AHH, FINALLY, A CAR.
>> NO, YOU NEED TO LEARN HOW TO
DRIVE FIRST.
HOW WOULD YOU EVEN GET A CAR?
WE NEED JOBS.
THAT'S WHAT WE NEED.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO IF
YOU GO INTO LABOR AT SCHOOL?
>> IF IT HAPPENS IN SCHOOL, THAT
WOULD BE COOL.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THEN PEOPLE WILL TALK
ABOUT IT.
"HEY, YOU KNOW THAT GIRL?
HER WATER BROKE TODAY IN CLASS.
IT WAS NASTY."
I CAN JOKE ABOUT MY WATER
BREAKING IN SCHOOL, BUT THE
TRUTH IS, I'M REALLY NERVOUS
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> HI, ALLISON.
HI, JOEY.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS DOING TODAY?
>> I'M GOOD.
JUST WAITING.
>> SO WHAT I WANT TO DO IS KIND
OF TALK TO YOU TODAY ABOUT SOME
QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS THAT YOU
MIGHT HAVE ABOUT LABOR.
>> WHEN MY WATER BREAKS, IS IT
GONNA BE, LIKE, IT'S NOT GONNA
BE, LIKE, A PUDDLE, RIGHT,
OR WHAT HAPPENS?
DOES IT JUST LOOK LIKE I PEED
MYSELF OR WHAT?
>> WELL, YOUR WATER BREAKING CAN
HAPPEN A LOT OF DIFFERENT WAYS.
IT MIGHT BE A HUGE GUSH.
IT MIGHT JUST BE LITTLE
TRICKLES.
SOMETIMES IT DOESN'T BREAK AT
ALL AT HOME.
I HAVE TO BREAK IT IN LABOR.
IT'S JUST KIND OF A MYSTERY.
YOU DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
[laughter]
>> I WENT TO REGISTER AT THE
HOSPITAL, AND THEY TOLD ME I
COULD HAVE AS MANY PEOPLE AS I
WANT IN THE ROOM.
HOW MANY PEOPLE DO YOU ALLOW?
>> WELL, DO YOU HAVE A RULE?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I DON'T WANT HIS MOM IN
THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> SHE'S, LIKE, A LOUD WOMAN.
I DON'T WANT HER IN IT.
>> SO YOU HAVE TO TELL ME,
AND YOU HAVE TO TELL YOUR NURSES
WHAT'S GONNA MAKE THIS THE BEST
EXPERIENCE FOR YOU,
AND WE WILL DO EVERYTHING WE
CAN.
>> THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
I WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT WHO TO HAVE IN THE
DELIVERY ROOM, BUT JOEY'S MOM IS
SO UNPREDICTABLE AND EXPLOSIVE.
IT'S REALLY MAKING ME THINK
ABOUT THE KINDS OF PARENTS I
WANT US TO BE.
I WANT TO BE A GOOD MOTHER,
LIKE, KIND OF FUN, BUT ALSO,
LIKE, I WANT TO BE A LITTLE
STRICT WITH HIM.
I THINK I'LL BE A LITTLE STRICT,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT HIM TO TURN
OUT LIKE US,
AND I WANT US BOTH TO BE THERE.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO TURN OUT
WITH ONE PARENT, AND I DON'T
WANT HIM TO GET A GIRL PREGNANT
WHEN HE'S A TEENAGER.
LIKE, I DON'T WANT HIM--I'LL
PROBABLY BE STRICT.
SO ARE YOU SCARED?
>> I'M PROBABLY GONNA BE SCARED
ABOUT NOT BEING A GOOD ENOUGH
PARENT.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW HOW
PEOPLE SAY YOU PARENT HOW YOUR
PARENTS PARENTED?
AND OUR PARENTS, UH....
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS HARDER THAN IT SHOULD
BE, RIGHT?
I DON'T WANT TO BE LIKE OUR
PARENTS.
LIKE, EVENTUALLY, THEY JUST
GAVE UP ON US.
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP ON HIM.
>> ME NEITHER.
JOEY AND I KNOW WE'RE HAVING A
BOY, AND WE DECIDED TO NAME HIM
AYDENN.
MY MOM JUST SENT ME A CHECK FOR
A LITTLE BIT OF MONEY,
SO WE'RE EXCITED TO START
GETTING SOME CUTE BABY STUFF.
DO YOU WANT TO GET A STROLLER
LIKE THIS OR A STROLLER LIKE--
>> I WANT A BIG STROLLER.
>> I LIKE THIS BLUE ONE.
HOW MUCH IS IT?
>> WHOA, $300 FOR THIS.
>> I LIKE THIS.
>> HOW MUCH IS IT?
>> UH...$12.
>> $12?
WE ONLY GOT, LIKE, $20.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE NEED A LOT OF MONEY TO
SUPPORT A BABY.
>> EVERY TIME I'M IN SCHOOL,
PEOPLE ALWAYS TELL ME STUFF LIKE
THAT.
"DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH IT COSTS
FOR A BABY PER YEAR?"
>> WHICH ONES DO YOU WANT TO
GET?
>> HOW MUCH IS THIS ONE?
>> THIS ONE'S $5.50.
>> GET THAT ONE.
>> $4.50.
>> LET'S GET THOSE TWO.
>> $10.82.
>> YOU KNOW HOW MUCH IS LEFT ON
THERE?
>> $10.
>> I NEED A WALLET.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF WE
NEED.
>> IT'S SCARY TO THINK ABOUT HOW
MUCH WE NEED, AND WITH THE BABY
COMING IN THREE MONTHS, WE HAVE
A LOT TO FIGURE OUT.
>> I'LL GET THE BIBS.
>> JOEY'S MOM HAS BEEN ON EDGE
LATELY AND WANTS THE PLACE TO
HERSELF FOR THE WEEKEND.
JOEY'S GRANDMA HAS AGREED TO LET
US STAY WITH HER FOR A COUPLE
DAYS, WHICH IS JUST FINE WITH
ME.
>> MAN, GRANDMA DOESN'T HAVE NO
TEA?
SHE ALWAYS HAS TEA.
GET SOME WATER BEFORE WE GO.
OH, MAN, IT'S TOO HOT.
[sighs]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
>> NOTHING.
>> ALLISON, GET ME A BANANA,
PLEASE, IF YOU DON'T MIND.
>> HERE, DAMIEN.
GIVE IT TO YOUR MOM.
I'M NOT GETTING UP.
>> AND DON'T THROW IT AT HIM
LIKE THAT.
>> I DIDN'T THROW IT AT HIM.
>> YES, YOU DID.
>> IT DIDN'T HIT HIM.
>> BUT IT HIT THE COUCH.
>> IT DIDN'T HIT HIM, THOUGH.
>> BUT I WASN'T THROWING IT AT
HIM.
>> YOU GET ON MY NERVES,
ALLISON, SOMETIMES.
YOU REALLY DO.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> WELL, THEN, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU CAN GO STAY WITH YOUR MOM
AND YOUR DADDY.
>> YOU TOLD ME I COULD STAY IN
YOUR HOUSE, BUT YOU DON'T TAKE
CARE OF US.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE OVER HERE.
>> SO.
WHY SHOULD I TAKE CARE OF YOU?
YOU AIN'T MY DAUGHTER.
YOU ARE NOT MY DAUGHTER, GIRL.
THAT'S MY SON, AND MY SON
DON'T THROW [bleep] IN MY FACE,
SO [bleep] YOU, BITCH.
YOU HEAR THAT?
GET THE [bleep] OUT.
GET OUT.
>> GET OUT OF HERE, MAN.
>> NO.
[bleep] HER.
YOU [bleep].
WHAT WRONG WITH YOU, [bleep]
HITTING ME?
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> GET THE [bleep] OUT OF HERE.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO.
>> YOU MOTHER[bleep].
DON'T YOU EVER CALL ME.
YOU HEAR THAT?
EVER.
[bleep] YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOUR MAMA DIDN'T WANT YOU,
AND YOUR DADDY DIDN'T WANT YOU.
YOU'RE HERE BECAUSE NOBODY'S
AROUND FOR YOU.
YOU DON'T EVER HIT ME IN MY
[bleep] MOUTH.
I'M GONNA PRESS CHARGES ON YOUR
BITCH[bleep].
>> I DIDN'T EVEN HIT YOU.
>> I'LL [bleep] YOU UP AND
[bleep] HER UP TOO.
I DON'T GIVE A [bleep] IF SHE'S
PREGNANT.
MOM, I GOT IT ON WITH ALLISON.
YOUR [bleep] GRANDSON [bleep]
POPPED ME IN MY MOUTH BECAUSE OF
THAT LITTLE BITCH.
SO WHAT?
I'M A DOPE FIEND, BITCH.
WHAT?
AT LEAST I SEE MY KIDS.
WHAT'S YOUR [bleep] PARENTS'
PROBLEM, HUH?
THEY DON'T EVEN DO DRUGS, AND
THEY DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU.
I'M TIRED OF IT.
>> WELL, THEN, GET OUT.
>> NO, [bleep] YOU.
THIS IS MY MOTHER'S [bleep]
HOUSE.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE NOT AROUND
EITHER; GO.
>> I DON'T GIVE A [bleep].
>> YOU KNOW, WE CAN CALL THE
POLICE ON YOU: CHARGING ON A
PREGNANT GIRL.
>> DID I TOUCH HER?
SHE DIDN'T DO--I DIDN'T TOUCH
HER.
>> YEAH, MAYBE YOU CAN GO AWAY.
>> NO.
I'VE DONE A LOT FOR YOU.
YEAH, I WAS A [bleep] DRUG
ADDICT, BUT I STRUGGLED FOR YOU
ASS.
I WASN'T A [bleep] BAD MOTHER,
AND YOU'RE GONNA TURN MY BACK
FOR THAT BITCH?
IF GOD WOULD HAVE TOLD ME THE
FUTURE, I WOULD HAVE SAID, "YOU
KNOW WHAT?
ABORT THAT CHILD.
ABORT IT."
I WANT HER OUT.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED TO STEP FOOT
IN MY [bleep] HOUSE, AND I
MEAN THAT, JOEY.
[bleep] YOU.
I'M DEAD TO YOU NOW.
>> COME ON.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
>> DID YOU HIT HER?
>> NO.
>> WELL, SHE WAS CHARGING AT
YOU.
>> I KNOW.
SHE'S A CRAZY BITCH.
THAT'S WHY.
>> WHATEVER.
I DON'T CARE.
>> * MOVE SLOW *
* WE DON'T HAVE NO PLACE TO GO *
>> AFTER JOEY'S MOM'S FREAK OUT,
I NEEDED TO HEAR MY MOM'S VOICE.
SHE WAS REALLY UPSET WHEN SHE
HEARD WHAT HAPPENED.
>> YEAH.
NOW.
>> I CAN'T JUST LEAVE.
>> YES, YOU CAN.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
I LOVE YOU, AND I WILL TALK TO
YOU LATER, OKAY?
>> OKAY, I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> I FEEL SO TORN.
GOING BACK TO NEW JERSEY WOULD
BE THE EASY ANSWER, BUT JOEY
IS TOO YOUNG TO LEAVE HOME,
AND I WANT MY BABY TO HAVE BOTH
PARENTS.
WE NEED JOEY'S GRANDMA TO HELP
US FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> SHE JUST STARTED SAYING THAT
I PUNCHED HER.
>> WELL, YOU ALREADY KNOW SHE'S
GONNA SAY THAT.
SHE'S A DRAMA QUEEN, BUT...
>> HIS MOM TEXTED HIM, "I DON'T
WANT EITHER OF YOU AT MY HOUSE,"
LIKE, TEXTING JOEY, "STAY OUT OF
MY HOUSE."
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS--I DON'T KNOW.
AND Y'ALL CAN JUST STAY WITH ME
UNTIL Y'ALL CAN GET BACK--
UNTIL Y'ALL CAN GET ON YOUSE
FEET.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, MAYBE I CAN DO
IT FOR A YEAR,
UNTIL Y'ALL CAN GET IT TOGETHER.
>> IT'S SUCH A RELIEF THAT
JOEY'S GRANDMA SAID WE COULD
STAY WITH HER.
I WISH WE COULD SETTLE IN RIGHT
AWAY, BUT ALL OF OUR STUFF IS
STILL AT HIS MOM'S HOUSE.
>> HIKE.
>> SINCE WE AREN'T GOING TO GET
OUR STUFF UNTIL THE END OF THE
WEEK, JOEY'S USING THIS TIME TO
PLAY FOOTBALL WITH FRIENDS,
BUT I HAVE TO FOCUS ON SCHOOL,
BECAUSE MY DUE DATE IS ONLY TWO
MONTHS AWAY.
>> SO ARE YOU GONNA MISS OUT ON
ANYTHING, LIKE, THIS YEAR?
>> WHY, BECAUSE THE BABY OR
WHATEVER?
>> ARE YOU SCARED OF MISSING OUT
ON ANYTHING?
>> I'M NOT GONNA MISS OUT ON
ANYTHING SENIOR YEAR.
I CAN'T HAVE THAT.
I WON'T MISS OUT ON PROM,
BUT, LIKE, HE'LL BE THERE,
SO HE'LL PROBABLY BE CRYING,
PROBABLY TAKE AWAY FROM MY FUN
WITH MY FRIENDS.
SO I WON'T MISS OUT ON ANYTHING,
BUT I'LL MISS OUT ON, LIKE,
DOING THE TEENAGE THING.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO WITH
SLEEPING HABITS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN IT'S BORN, I'M WORRIED THAT
MY GRADES ARE GONNA GO DOWN A
LITTLE.
ALL MY CLASSES SO FAR, THEY
SEEM, LIKE, I GOT IT,
BUT PRE-CAL, I HAVE TO STAY
AWAKE TO GET IT,
SO THAT'S THE CLASS I'M WORRIED
ABOUT.
AND WHEN THE BABY'S BORN, I'M
GONNA MISS, LIKE, WEEKS.
THAT'S THE ONLY THING I'M
WORRIED ABOUT.
I DON'T WANT MY SCHOOLWORK TO
SLIP.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO GET USED TO
IT.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO,
REALLY.
WHAT CAN I DO, TAKE ENERGY
DRINKS?
[laughter]
>> Y'ALL READY?
WELL, LET'S GET IT OVER WITH.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO FACE THE
DRAMA EVENTUALLY REGARDLESS.
Y'ALL GOT TO GO OVER THERE AND
GET YOUR STUFF.
>> YEAH.
>> EITHER SHE GONNA COME OUT AND
CAUSE A SCENE AND--
IT WILL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> WE GAVE JOEY'S MOM SOME TIME
TO CALM DOWN, BUT NOW WE HAVE TO
GO GET HER STUFF.
SOME OF JOEY'S FAMILY IS HERE TO
HELP, BUT I'M FEELING REALLY
NERVOUS.
>> WHAT'S WRONG, ALLISON?
>> NOTHING.
>> YOU LOOK ALL DEPRESSED, MAN.
DON'T LET IT GET TO YOU, MAN.
Y'ALL GONNA GET YOUR STUFF RIGHT
NOW.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT ANY
TROUBLE.
>> EHH, SHE AIN'T GONNA START NO
>> I WON'T.
>> NO, SHE WON'T.
>> THERE AIN'T GONNA BE NO
TROUBLE, MAN.
>> WHEN WE GOT THERE, JOEY'S
GRANDMA WAS ALREADY IN THE
HOUSE, AND HIS MOM WAS OUTSIDE
WAITING FOR US.
>> ARE YOU GETTING OFF, OR ARE
YOU STAYING IN?
>> I'M GETTING OFF.
IT'S MY CRAP.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> THAT'S YOUR SON RIGHT THERE.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> WELL, YOU NEED TO CARE.
>> NO, I DON'T CARE.
HE SAT THERE, AND HE TALKED
DOWN ON ME.
>> YOU--YOU SHOULD CARE
REGARDLESS.
>> [bleep] YOU.
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU WANT TO SIT THERE...
>> HEY, HEY, HEY, NO.
>> AND TELL ME LIKE THAT THAT I
COULDN'T SEE THE BABY?
>> HEY.
>> THAT'S FINE, JOEY.
>> YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
>> WHY DID YOU START [bleep]?
JUST GET EVERYTHING OUT OF
THERE.
DANG.
>> YOU COULD TAKE THAT
GOD[bleep] ATTITUDE OUTSIDE,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE IN MY HOUSE.
GET YOUR [bleep] ASS OUT OF MY
[bleep] HOUSE, GIRL.
TAKE YOUR ASS IN THERE.
>> OH, YOU'RE SO MATURE, MOM.
>> OH, YES, I AM.
I AM.
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
>> THE WORLD KNOWS THAT I'M A
PILL-POPPING ADDICT--
BUT WHO THE HELL IS SHE TO THROW
IT IN MY FACE?
>> ALLISON, GET IN THE TRUCK.
>> NEVER ONCE DID I THROW IT IN
HER FACE ABOUT HER PARENTS.
WHO THE HELL GOT YOU YOUR
MEDICAID.
I DID.
WHEN NOBODY WANTED YOU--
WHEN NOBODY WANTED YOU,
I TOOK YOU IN, AND YOU'RE OVER
THERE NOW BUDDY-BUDDY WITH MY
MOTHER, WHO DIDN'T WANT YOU?
I DID A LOT FOR YOU ASS,
ALLISON, A LOT.
YOU TORE MY SON AWAY FROM ME,
AND ME AND MY SON HAD A
RELATIONSHIP LIKE THIS.
>> WELL, YOU NEVER HAVE TO SEE
ME AGAIN AFTER TODAY, OKAY?
>> AND I'M STILL GONNA SLEEP
GOOD, ALLISON.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> YOUR MOTHER SLEEPS GOOD, AND
YOUR DADDY SLEEPS GOOD.
>> OKAY, BUT YOU NEVER HAVE TO
SEE ME.
I PROMISE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SEE ME OR SEE
YOUR SON, NOT SEE ME OR MY KID.
I PROMISE.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA USE THAT
BABY WITH ME, 'CAUSE I STILL
SLEEP GOOD AT NIGHT.
>> OKAY, SLEEP GOOD.
>> COME ON INSIDE.
GET INSIDE.
>> PUT THE [bleep] BABY STUFF IN
THE BACK.
I'M TIRED OF HER ASS,
CRAZY [bleep] BITCH.
>> WE ALMOST GOT EVERYTHING.
WE COULD HEAD BACK IN A MINUTE.
>> ALL THIS FAMILY DRAMA ISN'T
MAKING THIS PREGNANCY ANY
EASIER.
>> LET'S GO.
THE THING IS THAT Y'ALL GOT YOUR
STUFF.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> GETTING OUR STUFF BACK WAS
REALLY DIFFICULT.
I'M SO RELIEVED THAT JOEY'S
GRANDMA TOOK US IN.
IT'S BEEN EASIER KEEPING UP
WITH SCHOOL.
AND EVEN THOUGH HER OLD OFFICE
IS A LITTLE CRAMPED, IT'S A
MILLION TIMES BETTER THAN IT WAS
AT JOEY'S MOM'S HOUSE.
SOON THIS IS GONNA BE OUR BABY
RIGHT HERE.
WE SHOULD PRACTICE.
WOULD YOU WANT TO SLEEP WITH HIM
IN BED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HOW ABOUT WE SLEEP WITH HIM
WHEN HE'S SIX OR SEVEN MONTHS?
NOT WHEN HE'S A NEWBORN.
>> [sighs]
>> READY TO GO TO BED?
>> I'M SLEEPY.
I LOVE YOU.
smooch!
>> WITH AYDENN COMING SOON, WE
STILL HAVE A LOT TO LEARN ABOUT
TAKING CARE OF A NEWBORN.
SO YOU READ THE BABY BOOK MORE
THAN ME.
WHAT, LIKE, WHAT DO YOU THINK WE
NEED TO KNOW, BESIDES HOW TO
FEED IT AND WHAT TIME?
I KNOW THERE'S, LIKE, TIMING TO
FEED HIM.
>> YOU GOT TO CHANGE A DIAPER.
HAVE YOU EVER CHANGED A DIAPER?
>> YOU HAVE?
>> MY BROTHERS AND SISTERS.
WE COULD DEMONSTRATE IT
ON KITTY.
HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S IN FOR THE
CHALLENGE.
>> [laughs]
OKAY, HOLD ON.
LET ME GET THE DIAPER.
LAY HIM DOWN.
READY?
READY, KITTY?
>> GET HIM.
>> OKAY.
YOU GOT FAT, KITTY.
YOU CAN'T EVEN FIT IN NEWBORN
DIAPERS.
HE'S KICKING.
NOW I GOT HIS FEET.
I WON'T BE THIS ROUGH WITH
OUR KID.
I PROMISE.
YOU UNDO THIS THING, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, AND YOU JUST STRAP
IT ON.
>> IT STICKS?
>> YES.
>> IT DOESN'T FEEL STICKY.
OKAY.
OW, HE'S NAILING ME.
>> NICE.
HE LOOKS SEXY.
>> WHAT A CUTE KITTY.
HOW DOES HE LOOK?
>> HE LOOKS GOOD.
LET'S SEE IF HE CAN WALK IN IT.
PUT HIM ON THE BED.
[laughter]
YEAH, HE'S SEXY.
>> BYE.
WHAT A WASTE OF A DIAPER.
[wolf howling]
HALLOWEEN IS HERE, AND IT'S ONE
OF MY FAVORITE HOLIDAYS.
HEY!
YOU SEE THAT?
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO LET BEING
PREGNANT KEEP ME FROM HAVING FUN
TONIGHT.
WE'RE AWARE OF OUR AGE.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> HEY.
TRICK OR TREAT?
>> YOU GOT A PUMPKIN.
>> OH, COOL.
YOU GET DOUBLE.
>> THANKS.
>> AT EIGHT MONTHS PREGNANT, I'M
GETTING TIRED AND UNCOMFORTABLE.
SO INSTEAD OF GOING OUT TO PARTY
WITH OUR FRIENDS, JOEY AND I ARE
CALLING IT A NIGHT.
>> SEE YOUS LATER.
>> AT LEAST WE GOT A LOT
OF CANDY.
>> WHY?
>> IT'S BEEN TWO WEEKS SINCE
WE'VE HEARD FROM JOEY'S MOM.
BUT SUDDENLY, SHE STARTED
CALLING NONSTOP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SHE SAYS SHE'S SORRY AND HAS
SOMETHING EXTREMELY IMPORTANT TO
TELL US.
JOEY CONVINCED ME TO GO OVER AND
TALK TO HER, BUT I'M NOT SURE
IT'S SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
I DON'T WANT TO GO HERE.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SET FOOT IN
HER HOUSE AGAIN.
>> UM...
I'M GOING TO A REHAB.
>> WHEN ARE YOU GOING?
>> MONDAY.
SO I'M GONNA BE GONE FOR ABOUT
FIVE DAYS DETOX.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
>> IT'S WHEN YOU'RE REALLY BAD
ON SOMETHING, LIKE--
>> OPIATES.
I'VE BEEN TAKING THEM FOR, LIKE,
WHAT, TEN YEARS?
I'VE BEEN HOOKED ON THEM.
AND MY ADDICTION IS ALREADY
TOO BAD.
>> HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
BE THERE?
>> BASICALLY ABOUT 35 DAYS I'LL
BE GONE.
I HAVE TO THOUGH.
IT WAS ALREADY TO A POINT WHERE
I DIDN'T GIVE A [bleep] WHAT
ANYBODY THOUGHT.
YOU KNOW THAT.
SO I WANT TO AT LEAST BE CLEAN
AND SOBER FOR AT LEAST THE BABY
AND FOR THE KIDS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HOPEFULLY YOU LIVE UP TO IT.
>> I KNOW.
I'VE TRIED IT BEFORE.
>> WHAT'S SO DIFFERENT ABOUT
THIS TIME?
>> I DON'T--WELL, BECAUSE.
THIS TIME IT'S DIFFERENT BECAUSE
I WANT TO DO IT.
I'M READY.
MY BODY IS JUST WORN
OUT ALREADY.
TEN YEARS IS A LONG TIME TO BE
TAKING PILLS.
>> JOEY'S MOM SEEMS SINCERE
ABOUT TRYING TO CHANGE,
BUT SHE'S SAID THIS BEFORE.
SO I HOPE THIS TIME IN REHAB
WILL HELP HER BECOME THE PARENT
WE NEED HER TO BE.
[chime dings]
WHILE JOEY'S MOM IS OFF IN
DETOX, WE HAVE TO SPEND THE
MONTH GETTING EVERYTHING FOR
THE BABY.
SO FOR THE NEXT FEW WEEKS, ALL
WE'RE GOING TO DO IS CLEAN, SET
UP, AND DECORATE.
IT'S BEEN A FEW WEEKS SINCE
JOEY'S MOM LEFT FOR DETOX.
WE HAVEN'T HEARD FROM HER, BUT
SHE'S DUE BACK SOON.
THIS IS MY LAST WEEK OF SCHOOL
BEFORE CHRISTMAS BREAK.
I REALLY HOPE THE DOCTOR SAYS
I'LL HAVE THE BABY NEXT WEEK SO
I WON'T MISS MUCH SCHOOL.
>> HELLO, ALLISON.
>> HI, JOEY.
HOW YOU GUYS DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> HOW HAVE YOU BEEN FEELING
THIS WEEK?
>> FINE, JUST NORMAL.
>> SO HOW'S SCHOOL GOING?
>> GOOD, IT'S OUR LAST WEEK TILL
THE BREAK.
>> ISN'T THAT EXCITING?
ARE YOU READY FOR CHRISTMAS?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, WELL, YOUR MEASUREMENT
IS BETTER THIS WEEK.
DID YOU EAT A LOT?
[laughter]
>> MY PANTS DON'T BUTTON
ANYMORE.
>> THEY'RE NOT BUTTONING
ANYMORE?
ARE YOU WEARING MATERNITY
CLOTHES?
>> NO. [laughs]
>> IN THE 40s.
OKAY. SOUNDS GOOD.
OKAY, SO WE'RE 39 WEEKS.
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU GETTING TIRED OF THE
WHOLE THING?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, THIS IS THE POINT
WHERE, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE READY TO
DELIVER.
SO WE'RE GONNA DELIVER YOU
THIS WEEK.
SO YOU GET TO BE INDUCED
THE WAY I HAVE IT SET UP IS THAT
YOU'LL GO IN THURSDAY EVENING.
>> OKAY.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL ON
THURSDAY.
OKAY, AND WHAT TIME DO YOU GET
OUT OF SCHOOL?
>> 2:30.
>> SO I'M THINKING MAYBE
9:00-ish WOULD BE A GOOD TIME.
SO WHAT YOU DO IS, YOU'LL GO TO
LABOR AND DELIVERY AT 9:00.
YOU'LL HAVE ALL YOUR BAGS.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GO HOME THAT
NIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE THERE, OKAY,
UNTIL YOU HAVE A BABY.
>> OKAY.
>> EXCITED?
>> YES.
[laughter]
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT, JOEY,
YOU EXCITED?
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL SEE YOU GUYS.
BYE-BYE.
>> BYE.
THANK YOU.
>> UH-HUH.
>> OH, JESUS.
IT'S NOT A LOT OF NOTICE, BUT
KNOWING THAT I'M GETTING INDUCED
GIVES MY MOM A CHANCE TO GET
HERE FOR THE BIRTH.
ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE TO COME?
>> WHY NOT THOUGH?
>> I WISH YOU COULD COME TOO.
THAT, LIKE, UPSETS ME THAT
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE THERE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> YEAH.
I HAVE TO GO NOW.
>> YEAH, I'M OKAY.
OKAY, SO--
>> OKAY.
>> BYE.
>> I'M TWO DAYS AWAY FROM BEING
INDUCED, AND JOEY'S MOM IS BACK
FROM DETOX.
>> HEY, IT'S ABOUT TIME!
>> HEY, BABY.
>> HEY.
>> HEY, ALLIE.
>> HI.
NOW THAT I KNOW MY MOM WON'T BE
THERE, I'M REALLY GOING TO NEED
SUPPORT FROM JOEY'S FAMILY.
>> SO ARE YOU KIND OF SAD THAT
SHE'S NOT COMING?
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU GET THE CHEERLEADERS
OVER HERE.
>> I WOULD BE SAD TOO.
>> YEAH, WELL, SHE'S GOT US.
SO SHE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT IT.
I THINK IT'S NICE THAT EVERYBODY
CAN GET ALONG NOW.
AND JUST--YOLANDA HAS TO CONTROL
HER TEMPER, 'CAUSE A COUPLE OF
MONTHS AGO IT WAS A DISASTER.
I FEEL LIKE NOW IT'S
THE TIME JUST TO, YOU KNOW, JUST
PUT THAT IN THE PAST.
KEEP GOING, BECAUSE NOW YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE A GRANDCHILD.
YOU KNOW, AND REGARDLESS OF WHAT
HAPPENED, YOU KNOW, WE'RE ALL A
FAMILY.
AND IF FAMILY DOESN'T STICK
TOGETHER, THEN WHO'S GONNA STICK
TOGETHER?
WHO'S GONNA DO IT IF IT'S NOT
FAMILY?
>> JOEY'S MOM SEEMS EXCITED
ABOUT THE BABY COMING.
AND SINCE SHE REALLY WANTS TO,
IT'S THE FIRST TIME I ACTUALLY
FEEL OKAY ABOUT HER BEING IN THE
DELIVERY ROOM.
READY? COME ON.
>> NO.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE.
>> YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE,
OKAY.
>> ARE YOU DILATED OR ANYTHING?
>> OH.
>> OKAY, WHEN YOU DO YOU THINK
THE BABY IS GONNA COME?
>> I SAY PROBABLY NOON TOMORROW.
>> [gasps]
OH, GOSH.
THAT'S TOO LONG.
>> I SAY MAYBE ABOUT 4:00 IN THE
MORNING.
MAYBE EVEN BEFORE THAT.
>> I GUESS HE WANTS TO LIVE
IN THERE.
>> WOULD YOU WANT TO COME OUT?
I WOULDN'T EITHER.
I'D BE THERE FOREVER.
>> I'VE BEEN LYING HERE FOR FOUR
HOURS ALREADY, AND NOTHING IS
HAPPENING YET.
BUT AT LEAST MY MOM IS KIND OF
KEEPING ME COMPANY BY TEXTING ME
A LOT.
>> HI.
>> HELLO.
>> HOW'S IT GOING?
>> I'M ALL RIGHT.
>> SO I'M GONNA BREAK YOUR
WATER.
WE'RE GONNA START YOUR PITOCIN.
THIS IS GONNA GET EVERYTHING
STARTED A LITTLE BIT MORE.
YOU'LL FEEL A LITTLE BIT OF
PRESSURE, AND THEN YOU MIGHT
FEEL THE FLUID COMING OUT.
OKAY.
>> UGH.
>> OKAY, I'M SORRY.
SO ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS LET US
KNOW WHEN YOU'RE READY FOR SOME
MEDICINE.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THEN WE CAN ALWAYS GET
THAT EPIDURAL WHEN YOU'RE READY.
OKAY?
>> YOU TALKED TO YOUR MOM?
YOU TEXTED HER, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
EVERY TIME SOMETHING NEW HAPPENS
I TELL HER.
TEXTING WITH MY MOM HELPS A
LITTLE, BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME AS
HAVING HER HERE.
[groaning]
>> YOU MISSED IT ALL.
>> I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO WAKE YOU
UP, BECAUSE Y'ALL THE ONES
HAVING THE BABY.
ARE THEY GETTING STRONGER?
>> ARE THEY GETTING STRONGER?
>> [whimpering]
>> SO SHE CAN SQUEEZE YOUR HAND.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
THAT WILL MAKE HER AGGRAVATED.
>> [whimpering]
>> DOES YOUR BACK HURT A LOT?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WANT ME TO RUB IT
FOR YOU?
IT'S RIGHT HERE, HUH?
>> YEAH.
OH, GOD.
>> HEY, ALISON.
YOU WANT TO GO AHEAD AND GET THE
EPIDURAL?
>> ALL RIGHT, A LITTLE BIT OF A
STICK HERE.
LOTS OF PRESSURE.
>> OKAY, HOW'S THAT?
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> OVER THE NEXT FIVE TO TEN
MINUTES YOUR CONTRACTIONS WILL
START TO BOTHER YOU A WHOLE
LOT LESS.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
>> SO YOU'RE FIVE CENTIMETERS
AND 90%.
YOU'RE MOVING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> OH, JUST IMPATIENT.
>> "GET AYDENN OUT!"
>> OH, GOD.
>> IS THAT EXCITING?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S GONNA
BE BORN.
>> I KNOW.
HE'S RIGHT DOWN THE DOOR.
'CAUSE I ALWAYS DO THAT WITH MY
DADS.
>> WHERE DO I CUT IT THOUGH?
>> WELL, I'LL SHOW YOU.
THERE'S TWO CLAMPS.
I KNOW YOU CAN'T CUT ANYTHING
IMPORTANT OFF.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> YOU OKAY, JOEY?
>> JOEY, IF YOU'RE GONNA PASS
OUT, WE'RE GONNA GET YOU A
STOOL.
>> YEAH, YOU CAN.
>> IF YOU FEEL BETTER WITH
HOLDING HER HAND, YOU CAN HOLD
HER HAND.
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I DON'T WANT TO PASS OUT
HERE.
>> COME ON.
JUST HOLD IT AND PUSH.
>> all: ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> OKAY, ALLISON, COME ON.
>> all: ONE, TWO, THREE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
ALL RIGHT, GIRL.
>> OH, HE'S COMING.
>> OKAY, YOU'RE VERY,
VERY CLOSE.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> PUSH, PUSH!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HI!
[baby gurgling]
>> RIGHT BETWEEN THESE TWO.
[baby squawks]
>> HI BABY.
>> IT'S OUR FIRST MORNING WITH
AYDENN, AND EVERYBODY WENT HOME
TO SLEEP.
>> HAVE YOU CHANGED HIS DIAPER
RECENTLY?
>> YEAH. WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
WE DID, LIKE AN HOUR AGO?
COMING IN, WE KNEW NOTHING ABOUT
TAKING CARE OF A BABY.
SO WE'RE TRYING TO LEARN AS MUCH
AS WE CAN WHILE WE'RE STILL IN
THE HOSPITAL.
>> YOU WANT TO CHECK THE DIAPER
FIRST?
>> YES.
>> OKAY, YOU GUYS WANT TO DO IT?
>> [squeaking]
>> OH, HE IS WET.
OKAY, SO THIS LITTLE YELLOW
STRIP ON THE DIAPER WILL TURN
GREEN WHEN HE'S WET.
THAT JUST TELLS YOU
AUTOMATICALLY.
>> I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
>> YEAH, HE WON'T GET SO SOILED
THAT HE LEAKS THROUGH HIS
DIAPER.
>> DO WE WIPE HIM, OR NO?
>> JUST USE LIKE WET GAUZE
AROUND HIM, AND THEN YOU CAN
WIPE HIS BOTTOM WITH A WIPE.
>> GOT IT.
HOW DO YOU--I DON'T--
HOW DO YOU TAKE HIM IN A BATH
AND STUFF?
>> OKAY, YOU ACTUALLY DON'T WANT
TO SUBMERGE HIM.
THE LITTLE PINK BASIN THAT YOU
HAVE, FILL IT UP HALFWAY.
AND YOU CAN KIND OF SIT
HIM IN IT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND YOU WANT TO SPONGE BATHE
HIM UNTIL THE UMBILICAL CORD
FALLS OFF.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU KNOW, HE'S NOT GONNA
BREAK, YOU KNOW.
>> THEN YOU BATHE HIM ONCE
A DAY?
>> WE BATHE EVERY OTHER NIGHT.
>> GOT IT.
>> OKAY?
>> IT'S COLD.
OH, HI!
MY FRIENDS ARE EXCITED TO SEE
THE BABY.
AND I'M HAPPY TO SHOW HIM OFF.
WANT TO HOLD HIM?
>> YES.
>> GET HIS HEAD.
YOU THINK HE LOOKS LIKE ME?
>> YEAH, HE HAS YOUR CHEEKS.
>> [crying]
>> AW, WE GOT A CRYER.
>> OH, YEAH, HE'S A BIG CRYBABY.
SHH, SHH, SHH.
>> HOW'S IT GONNA FEEL TO TAKE
HIM HOME?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SCARED.
AT LEAST WE GET THE CHRISTMAS
BREAK OFF FOR ME TO PREPARE
MYSELF FOR WHEN WE HAVE TO BACK
TO SCHOOL.
>> WHAT DOES YOUR DAD THINK
ABOUT THIS?
DID HE SHOW UP, CALL, TEXT?
>> I JUST SENT HIM A PICTURE.
>> DID HE REPLY BACK?
>> HE'S LIKE, "SO YOU HAD THE
BABY."
>> DO YOU THINK HE'S GONNA COME
SEE HIM?
>> HE DIDN'T ASK WHAT HOSPITAL
I'M AT.
>> THAT'S MESSED UP.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT IS.
HOW WAS YOUR LABOR?
LIKE, WHO ALL WAS THERE?
>> WELL, LIKE, HE WAS THERE, HIS
MOM.
>> AFTER YOU TOLD ME A BILLION
TIMES--
>> THAT SHE'S NOT GONNA BE
THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE DIDN'T FLIP OUT OR
ANYTHING?
>> SHE WAS ACTUALLY PRETTY GOOD.
SHE WAS QUIET, AND SHE WAS LIKE,
SUPPORTIVE OF MY LEFT LEG.
>> [laughs]
>> SHE WAS GOOD.
YOUR GRANDMA'S ON HER WAY UP.
>> I KNOW.
>> HOW DO Y'ALL FEEL ABOUT
TAKING THE BABY HOME?
>> I'M SCARED.
>> YOU'RE SCARED?
I'M SCARED.
I'D BE SCARED TOO.
>> YOU'RE SCARED FOR US?
>> NERVOUS.
>> I'M EXCITED AND NERVOUS TO
GO HOME, BECAUSE IT MEANS WE
HAVE TO START DOING THIS ALL ON
OUR OWN.
>> ALL RIGHT, AYDENN.
WELL, AT THE HOSPITAL YOU HAD
THE NURSES.
YOU HAD EVERYBODY.
NOW IT'S JUST Y'ALL.
YOU TWO!
>> IT'S GOING TO BE JUST THE TWO
OF US ONCE JOEY'S GRANDMA GOES
BACK TO WORK.
AND WE STILL HAVE A LOT
TO LEARN.
IS HE HUNGRY?
DOES HE HAVE A WET DIAPER?
>> [screaming]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T CHECKED HIS DIAPER.
HE SMELLS THOUGH.
OH, YEP.
>> HELLO?
THAT'S WHY HE'S FUSSY.
DUDE, WHY ARE YOU JUST STARING
AT IT?
>> DON'T BE SCARED TO WIPE,
JOEY.
THE NURSES IN THE HOSPITAL MADE
LOOK IT SO EASY, BUT HE'S
SO LITTLE.
I WORRY ABOUT DOING THE
WRONG THING.
I FEEL BAD.
>> [screaming]
>> I FEEL BAD.
>> I DON'T WANT TO PUT HIM IN.
>> [screaming]
>> I DON'T WANT TO TAKE HIM
A BATH.
CAN HE JUST STAY DIRTY?
>> [screaming and crying]
>> I KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE A
LONG NIGHT WITH FEEDING AND
DIAPER CHANGES.
JOEY SAID HE'D HELP OUT, BUT
IT LOOKS LIKE HE HAS OTHER
PLANS.
[yawning]
>> [fussing]
>> SHH.
SHH.
AT LEAST ONE OF US GOT
SOME SLEEP.
>> BE GOOD.
WITH JOEY BACK AT SCHOOL AND HIS
GRANDMA AT WORK, IT'S HARD
TAKING CARE OF AYDENN ALL DAY BY
MYSELF.
STAY RIGHT HERE.
MY PLAN IS TO STAY AT HOME UNTIL
THE BABY IS SIX WEEKS OLD.
THEN I CAN GO BACK TO SCHOOL AND
HE CAN GO TO DAY CARE, WHICH I
GET FOR FREE BECAUSE I'M A HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENT.
BECAUSE JOEY HAS FOOTBALL AFTER
SCHOOL, HE COMES HOME LATE A
LOT.
AFTER DOING HIS HOMEWORK, HE
DOESN'T SEEM INTERESTED IN
HELPING OUT WITH THE BABY.
I KNOW YOU'RE HUNGRY.
YOU PROBABLY HAVE A WET DIAPER.
BEING AT HOME ALL DAY, I MISS MY
FRIENDS, SO IT'S NICE WHEN WE
CAN MEET UP AFTER SCHOOL.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
I'M GONNA GO UP THIS LITTLE RAMP
THING, OKAY?
WOW.
HE'S THERE.
NO, HE'S WAITING FOR ME TO OPEN
THE DOOR.
I HAVE THE KEY.
HE DOESN'T.
I WISH I COULD SAY JOEY IS
HELPING OUT MORE, BUT THAT'S NOT
THE CASE.
OH, I'LL GET HIM.
HE HASN'T BEEN HELPING A LOT.
HE'S PISSING ME OFF, REALLY,
'CAUSE HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
IF I ASK HIM, HE GIVES ME A HARD
TIME, BUT HE STILL DOES IT.
BUT I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO ASK.
IT'S LITTLE THINGS, BUT WHEN
SOMEONE DOES SOMETHING LITTLE
TOO MUCH, THAT'S WHEN IT STARTS
TO TURN, LIKE, BIG.
LIKE, "COME ON."
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S NOT READY FOR THE
RESPONSIBILITY, AND IT'S A
LITTLE LATE TO NOT BE READY,
'CAUSE HE'S ALREADY HERE.
LIKE, IF HE CAN'T BE
RESPONSIBLE, I DON'T WANT TO
BE WITH SOMEBODY WHO'S NOT
RESPONSIBLE.
>> WOULD YOU GO TO JERSEY IF IT
DIDN'T WORK OUT?
>> I DON'T WANT THAT TO HAPPEN.
LET ME SEE HOW HE ACTS WHILE I
GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
LIKE, HE'S USING THE EXCUSE.
"I GOT TO DO SCHOOLWORK.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING."
AND I TELL HIM, "WHAT ABOUT WHEN
I GO BACK TO SCHOOL?"
HE'S LIKE, "I GUESS I'LL HELP
AT NIGHT."
>> LIKE, "YOU GUESS?"
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"YOU GUESS"?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I FEEL CONFUSED AND FRUSTRATED.
I HOPE WHEN MY MOM GETS HERE SHE
CAN HELP ME FIGURE THINGS OUT.
MY MOM'S WEEKEND VISIT IS
FINALLY HERE, AND JOEY'S PARENTS
ARE TAKING ME TO THE AIRPORT
WHILE HE'S IN SCHOOL.
OH, HER PLANE JUST LANDED.
>> TELL HER TO WAIT AT THE GATE,
NOT TO MOVE.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN EACH OTHER FOR
A YEAR.
NOW THAT I'M A MOM, I'M
REALIZING HOW MUCH I NEED MY
MOM'S HELP AND ADVICE.
READY TO SEE GRANDMA?
>> HI!
>> MOMMY!
[heartfelt rock music]
* *
>> YEAH, OF COURSE I DO!
HE'S SO TINY.
HI, AYDENN!
HI.
YOU ARE SO ADORABLE.
>> WANT TO GO GET YOUR BAGS?
>> YEAH.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
>> OKAY.
>> HI, YOLANDA, IT'S SO NICE TO
MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> I'M LAUREN.
HI, HI, HI, HI.
>> HOW WAS YOUR FLIGHT?
>> IT WAS A REALLY GOOD FLIGHT.
IT REALLY WAS, YEAH.
>> THAT WAS GOOD.
THAT WAS GOOD.
>> YOU'LL HAVE YOUR BAG IN
A MINUTE.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME MY MOM IS
MEETING JOEY.
>> IT'S SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
YOU'RE SO CUTE!
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU ARE SO CUTE.
>> [squawking]
[laughter]
[burps]
>> UH-OH.
>> HE JUST BURPED.
IT'S NICE THAT MY MOM IS FINALLY
ABLE TO MEET EVERYONE, BUT SHE
SEEMS MORE FOCUSED ON
FIGURING OUT WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH JOEY.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO, OR
WHAT WOULD YOU SETTLE TO DO?
>> PROBABLY LIKE FAST FOOD OR
SOMETHING.
[laughs]
I'M CONFUSED.
I CHANGE MY CAREER LIKE ALMOST
EVERY WEEK.
JUST ASK HER.
LIKE, ONE WEEK I WANT TO BE A
LAWYER.
ONE WEEK I WANT TO BE A NURSE.
ONE WEEK I WANT TO BE--
>> JUST DO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
'CAUSE IF YOU DON'T--
>> I STILL WANT TO GET A DEGREE
THOUGH.
>> YOU CAN STILL DO THAT.
>> GRADUATE AND GET A DEGREE.
>> HI.
THIS IS MY MOM.
>> HI!
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU TOO.
>> SO DID YOU SEE YOUR
GRANDBABY?
>> HE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> ISN'T HE?
HE JUST ATE, HUH?
>> YEAH, HE ATE AT 4:00.
>> HE DID POOP, THOUGH, I THINK.
>> OH, HE POOPED?
WHY DIDN'T YOU CHANGE IT?
>> OH, MY BABY.
HE POOPED?
NO WONDER HE'S CRYING.
>> JOEY KNEW HE POOPED.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
>> WELL, HOW COME YOU HAVE HIM
LIKE THAT?
YOU KNOW HE'S CRYING
'CAUSE HE'S POOPED.
>> I SAID HE SMELLED LIKE A
WHILE AGO.
>> THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU CHANGE
HIM A WHILE AGO?
>> YEAH!
>> GOING TO CHANGE HIM.
IT REALLY SUCKS THAT JOEY CAN'T
FIGURE OUT HOW TO BE A PARENT.
AND I KNOW MY MOM IS GOING TO
WANT TO TALK ABOUT
THE SITUATION.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL THOUGH?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT JOEY?
>> LIKE, I LOVE HIM, OBVIOUSLY.
I DON'T KNOW--
>> DO YOU REALLY?
WOULD YOU BE WITH HIM NOW IF IT
WASN'T FOR HIM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OKAY, YOU ANSWERED MY
QUESTION.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, AYDENN'S ONLY A MONTH
OLD, AND I'M ALREADY GETTING
SICK OF HIS STUPID EXCUSES.
>> WELL, WHAT ARE HIS EXCUSES?
>> ANYTIME HE DOES SOMETHING FOR
AYDENN, IT'S 'CAUSE I ASKED.
>> BUT OTHERWISE HE JUST DOESN'T
DO ANYTHING?
>> NOT REALLY.
>> FOR YOU TO FEEL LIKE THAT,
IT'S JUST GONNA BE A MATTER OF
TIME BEFORE YOU'RE JUST GONNA
SAY, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE."
>> I THINK MYSELF STUCK IN TEXAS
FOR A WHILE.
>> YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT STUCK
IN TEXAS.
IF YOU'RE THAT UNHAPPY, WE CAN
HAVE YOU HOME WITHIN 24 HOURS.
>> DO YOU THINK ME AND JOEY WILL
STAY TOGETHER?
>> HONESTLY, NO.
>> WELL, HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
WE'LL MAKE IT THEN?
>> I THINK YOU KNOW.
I THINK YOU KNOW WHAT THE END
RESULT IS GONNA BE.
IT'S IN YOUR HEAD.
THERE'S STILL THAT PERCENTAGE
WHERE I COULD BE WRONG.
I DON'T KNOW EVERYTHING.
BUT BECAUSE OF HOW THINGS ARE
AND BECAUSE YOU REALLY HAVEN'T
STARTED TO...
>> LIVE?
>> LIVE.
>> YEAH.
>> HONESTLY, I THINK JOEY'S VERY
SWEET.
I THINK HIS FAMILY IS
VERY SWEET.
BUT I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE SO
FRUSTRATED AND DONE WITH IT.
I THINK IN SIX MONTHS YOU'RE
GONNA BE GOING INSANE.
[chime dings]
>> MY MOM IS MAKING A LOT
OF SENSE.
THE WHOLE REASON FOR STAYING IN
TEXAS WAS TO RAISE THE BABY
WITH JOEY.
BUT IF HE'S NOT GOING TO STEP UP
AND BE A DAD, THEN I'M NOT SURE
WHILE I'M STILL HERE.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> AW, BYE.
>> MY MOM COULD ONLY COME FOR
THE WEEKEND BECAUSE OF WORK, BUT
I WISH SHE DIDN'T HAVE TO LEAVE
SO SOON.
>> MY MAKEUP FEELS SMUDGED
AGAIN.
>> A LITTLE.
>> I REALLY WANT YOU TO COME...
>> TO JERSEY?
>> TO JERSEY.
WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU.
>> OKAY.
JUST A PHONE CALL AWAY.
BYE.
>> I LOVE HAVING HER HERE, AND
SHE'S THE ONE PERSON WHO
UNDERSTANDS ME.
IT'S HARDER THAN EVER TO SAY
GOOD-BYE WHEN THINGS ARE SO UP
IN THE AIR.
IT'S BEEN SIX WEEK SINCE I'VE
HAD THE BABY,
AND IT'S TIME FOR ME TO GO BACK
TO SCHOOL.
SO IT'S MORE IMPORTANT THAN EVER
THAT JOEY STEPS UP AND HELPS ME
TAKE CARE OF AYDENN.
ARE YOU GONNA HELP ME TONIGHT,
SINCE I GO TO SCHOOL?
>> WAKE ME UP.
>> NO!
WAKE YOURSELF UP.
EVEN LIKE WHEN I'M HERE WITHOUT
SCHOOL, I ONLY GET A LITTLE BIT
OF SLEEP.
BUT AT LEAST I CAN TAKE A RANDOM
NAP DURING THE DAY.
I CAN'T DO THAT NOW, 'CAUSE
I HAVE TO GO TO SCHOOL.
SO I NEED YOUR HELP MORE.
THAT WAY WE BOTH GET THE SAME
AMOUNT OF SLEEP.
>> I HELP YOU.
I FEED HIM, CHANGE HIM.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> YES, I DO.
>> YOU DON'T CHANGE HIM.
>> I CHANGE--WELL, I CHANGE
HIS DIAPER.
>> NO, YOU DON'T.
>> YES, I DO.
>> WHEN?
>> SOME--AT TIMES.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHY DON'T YOU BURP HIM?
>> [fussing]
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
HI, BABY.
HERE.
I THINK WE SHOULD JUST KEEP
TAKING TURNS WHEN IT'S TIME
FOR FEEDING.
AND I DON'T ALWAYS GET
THE 3:00 A.M., OKAY?
>> OKAY.
IT SOUNDS GOOD.
>> [cooing]
>> WHY DO YOU LOOK AT ME WHEN HE
DOES THAT?
SOMETIMES YOU GET HOME, AND
YOU'RE LIKE...
SO ARE YOU REALLY GONNA BE ABLE
TO HELP? REALLY?
>> I'M GONNA HAVE TO, LIKE, PUSH
MYSELF TO DO IT.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO?
>> I AM GOING TO.
>> OKAY.
I BELIEVE YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA FAIL THIS YEAR.
YOU SWEAR?
>> I SWEAR.
[alarm droning]
>> IT'S MY FIRST DAY BACK AT
SCHOOL.
I USED TO GET UP EARLY TO GET
MYSELF READY, BUT NOW I HAVE TO
GET AYDENN READY FOR DAY CARE.
>> SORRY, BABY.
>> [fussing]
>> HE'S SO FUSSY.
>> IT'S 'CAUSE HE JUST FINISHED
EATING AT, LIKE, 4:45.
>> OH, HE DID?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE GETTING DRESSED
ALREADY?
>> YEAH, I'M GONNA GET DRESSED,
BECAUSE--
>> LET ME FINISH DRESSING HIM,
AND YOU GET DRESSED.
>> OKAY.
IT'S ONLY A DAY AFTER OUR TALK,
AND JOEY IS ALREADY FORGETTING
THAT HE PROMISED TO HELP.
>> OH, YOU'RE NOT GETTING READY?
>> I AM, BUT LOOK--I HAVE TO
FINISH HIS STUFF BEFORE I EVEN
TOUCH MYSELF.
WE HAVE TO GO NOW, JOEY.
COME ON.
I'M NOT GONNA BE LATE TO SCHOOL
EITHER.
GO.
IT'S FUN BEING WITH ALL MY
FRIENDS AGAIN, BUT GETTING BACK
INTO THE SWING OF THINGS AT
SCHOOL IS HARD.
AND SO IS BEING AWAY FROM AYDENN
ALL DAY.
ONCE I PICK HIM UP FROM DAY
CARE, I HAVE HOURS OF HOMEWORK
TO DO.
AND IF JOEY'S STILL AT PRACTICE,
THERE'S NO ONE TO WATCH THE
BABY.
>> [gurgling]
>> OH, GOD.
IT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH KEEPING
UP WITH SCHOOL IF I'M THE ONLY
ONE PARENTING.
SO I DECIDED TO TALK TO JOEY'S
GRANDMA WHEN SHE GOT HOME
FROM WORK.
>> I UNDERSTAND IT'S FRUSTRATING
HE DON'T WANT TO CHANGE, HE
DON'T WANT TO DO.
BUT IT'S JUST--THAT IS PART OF
BEING A PARENT.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW I'D HAVE TO DO
IT LIKE 24-7 BY MYSELF.
>> I THINK THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
>> HUH?
>> I THINK YOU HAVE TO ADAPT TO
BEING A MOTHER.
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO ADAPT TO
BEING A FATHER, AND IN BETWEEN,
Y'ALL ARE GONNA HAVE TO ADAPT
TOGETHER IN THE RELATIONSHIP.
'CAUSE AT FIRST IT WAS ALL CUTE.
"OOH, I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE BABY
TO GET HERE."
DIDN'T Y'ALL JUST SAY, "OOH,
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HIM."
AND NOW?
"UGH."
>> IF I'M LIKE, "CAN YOU JUST
HOLD HIM REAL QUICK?" HE'S LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD.
WHY?"
WHEN HE SAYS STUFF LIKE THAT,
I'M LIKE, "OH, MY GOSH."
>> YOU AND JOEY WERE BARELY
DATING, BARELY BEGUN DATING
WHEN YOU BECAME PREGNANT.
THAT'S ANOTHER BIG MISTAKE,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE YOUR RELATIONSHIP--WHERE
IT'S AT.
YOU KNOW, AND THEN YOU BRING A
BABY IN THE WORLD.
Y'ALL ARE BOTH FRUSTRATED,
BECAUSE YOU WEREN'T PREPARED TO
WHAT WAS GONNA COME.
AND WITH BOTH OF YOU FRUSTRATED,
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK IN A
RELATIONSHIP.
THAT WILL NOT WORK.
SO YOU'RE FRUSTRATED AT HIM, AND
HE'S FRUSTRATED WITH YOU.
RAISING A CHILD IS NOT EASY.
IT'S NOT EASY.
SO IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU AND JOEY
ARE NOT GETTING ALONG, THEN
Y'ALL NEED TO TALK ABOUT IT,
'CAUSE OTHERWISE, IT AIN'T
GONNA LAST.
>> JOEY'S GRANDMA IS RIGHT.
I HAVE TO TELL HIM HOW I FEEL.
HOW COME WHEN I ASK YOU TO DO
SOMETHING, YOU COMPLAIN, OR YOU
JUST DON'T DO IT FOR HIM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LOOK, I KNOW YOU LOVE HIM AND
ALL, BUT YOU JUST DON'T WANT TO
DO THE DIRTY WORK.
>> TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH, I'M
KIND OF LAZY.
>> THAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
YOU'RE LAZY?
I'M LAZY TOO.
BUT I GET MY ASS UP, BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT ANYTHING BAD TO
HAPPEN TO HIM.
YOU DON'T CARE.
LIKE, YOU LET HIM SIT IN THIS
DISGUSTING DIAPER UNTIL SOMEONE
TELLS YOU TO CHANGE HIM.
>> NO, I DON'T.
I JUST FORGET.
>> HOW DO YOU FORGET?
>> MOST OF THE TIME IT'S BECAUSE
I'M FEEDING HIM AND I DON'T
REALIZE HE HAS A DIRTY DIAPER.
>> YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO
MAKE HIS BOTTLES.
THAT'S HOW MUCH YOU DON'T PAY
ATTENTION TO, LIKE, WHAT HE EATS
AND STUFF.
'CAUSE YOU TELL ME YOU'LL SHAPE
UP, AND YOU WON'T.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA KEEP ON DOING
WHAT YOU'RE DOING UNTIL I START
RESENTING YOU, 'CAUSE THAT'S
WHAT'S STARTING TO HAPPEN,
'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
DOING ANYTHING.
AND I DON'T EVEN NEED YOU TO DO
ANYTHING FOR ME.
I WANT YOU TO DO SOMETHING
FOR HIM.
BUT YOU DON'T EVEN WANT TO
DO THAT.
LIKE, YOU JUST LIKE HIM THERE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> NOTHING.
>> YOU WANT YOUR LIFE TO BE
REGULAR.
>> NO.
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
>> NO, I DON'T.
DON'T GO TO CONCLUSIONS.
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> THERE'S NOTHING--
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE TIME TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> YES, YOU DO.
IF YOU WANT TO GO BACK TO YOUR
IMMATURE WAYS, WE COULD GO.
I TELL YOU THAT ALL THE TIME.
WE DON'T NEED TO BE HERE.
YOU COULD GO RIGHT BACK TO YOUR
NORMAL LIFE.
PRETEND IT NEVER HAPPENED.
OKAY?
YOU WANT THAT TO HAPPEN?
'CAUSE THAT'S HOW IT SEEMS YOU
WANT IT TO HAPPEN.
YOU THINK WE'RE GONNA WORK IF
YOU KEEP ACTING LIKE THIS? HMM?
>> NO.
>> THEN WHY DO YOU KEEP ACTING
LIKE THAT?
HMM?
HELLO?
>> I'M LOSING HOPE THAT JOEY
WILL EVER CHANGE.
THE LESS HE HELPS WITH AYDENN,
THE MORE I THINK ABOUT
WALKING AWAY.
>> THINGS WITH JOEY HAVE GONE
FROM BAD TO WORSE SINCE OUR
LAST TALK.
HE'S REALLY MAD AT ME, AND HE
STARTED SLEEPING ON THE COUCH.
>> HOW ARE THINGS GOING WITH
JOEY?
>> HE'S LIKE, "I'M JUST ALWAYS
MISERABLY WITH YOU."
I WAS LIKE, "WHY AM I EVEN
HERE?"
I WAS LIKE, "WHY AM I
EVEN HERE?"
>> HE'S LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW."
I'M LIKE...
>> WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE HE TOLD
YOU HE'S MISERABLE WITH YOU.
>> IT'S JUST NOT WORKING.
AT FIRST IT STARTED--I THINK THE
REASON I STOPPED PAYING
ATTENTION TO HIM, 'CAUSE HE
WOULDN'T HELP WITH AYDENN.
LIKE, IT JUST STARTED
TO FADE AWAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S LIKE, "THIS KID CANNOT
GROW UP."
>> YEAH, IT'S LIKE IT'S BEEN
GOING ON FOR A WHILE, SO--
>> YEAH, BASICALLY SINCE AFTER
TWO WEEKS OF AYDENN BEING BORN.
THAT'S WHEN IT STARTED
GETTING BAD.
>> THAT LONG ALREADY?
>> YEAH.
I LIKE, DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW MUCH
MORE I CAN TAKE OF JOEY'S CRAP.
>> DO YOU WANT TO BREAK UP, OR
I MEAN, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING
ABOUT IT?
>> LIKE, I REALLY DIDN'T
WANT TO.
BUT LIKE, I'M GETTING TIRED OF
TRYING AND GETTING NO FEEDBACK
ON MY TRYING.
>> WELL, IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
YOU KNOW YOU CAN CALL ME, TEXT
ME, WHATEVER.
>> OKAY, I APPRECIATE IT.
I'M GONNA GO.
>> NO PROBLEM. OKAY.
THE NEXT DAY AT SCHOOL, JOEY
STARTED SENDING ME CRAZY TEXTS.
BUT TODAY'S BEEN, LIKE,
HORRIBLE.
LIKE, HE'S BEEN SENDING ME
THESE ALL DAY.
>> WHAT IS HE TELLING YOU?
>> HE'S LIKE, "WHY CAN'T THINGS
BE LIKE THEY USED TO BE?
YOU NEVER HAVE TIME FOR
ME ANYMORE.
ALL YOU DO IS GET MAD AT ME
ABOUT THE BABY.
YOU'RE NEVER HAPPY.
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST BE HAPPY
BEING WITH ME?"
>> SO HE'S JEALOUS OF THE BABY?
>> THAT'S KIND OF WHAT IT SOUNDS
LIKE, RIGHT?
AND THEN HE SAYS I MAKE HIM
MISERABLE ALL THE TIME.
I GUESS HE THOUGHT EVERYTHING
WILL BE THE SAME, AND IT'S LIKE
TOTALLY DIFFERENT THAN HE
THOUGHT, BECAUSE IT IS TOTALLY
DIFFERENT THAN I THOUGHT TOO.
AND I THINK I'M JUST DONE TRYING
TO MAKE IT WORK.
>> SO HAVE YOU TEXTED HIM BACK?
>> I'M ABOUT TO TEXT HIM
RIGHT NOW AND TELL HIM, LIKE,
I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
AND I DON'T THINK IT'S GOOD FOR
AYDENN.
I JUST HOPE IT'S THE RIGHT THING
TO DO.
BUT I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT
AYDENN.
I JUST WANT AYDENN TO BE OKAY.
>> YOU THINK YOU'LL REGRET THIS
AT ALL?
>> I HOPE NOT, BUT I CAN'T TAKE
THIS ANYMORE.
IT'S DONE.
IT'S BEST FOR EVERYBODY,
I THINK.
BEFORE PICKING UP THE BABY FROM
DAY CARE, I WENT HOME TO TALK TO
JOEY FACE-TO-FACE.
>> NOW YOU WANT TO LEAVE NOW?
WHAT ARE YOU?
YOU'RE FRIGGING UNGRATEFUL.
YOU HAD IT GOOD HERE.
YOU HAD AT LEAST SOMEBODY WHO
CARED FOR YOU.
>> PLEASE STOP, OKAY?
YOU KNEW WE WERE DOING BAD.
YOU EVEN TOLD ME.
YOU SENT ME LITTLE NASTY TEXT
MESSAGES ABOUT HOW WE'RE GONNA
DO BAD.
"WATCH, WE'RE GONNA BREAK UP.
SOMETHING BAD IS GONNA HAPPEN
TO YOU," ALL THIS BULL[bleep].
YOU TELL ME I'M SO UNGRATEFUL?
>> YES, YOU ARE.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> HOW AM I UNGRATEFUL?
>> I TRIED TO PROVIDE YOU WITH
EVERYTHING.
I TRIED TO PUT A ROOF OVER
YOUR HEAD.
I STOOD BY YOU.
>> YOU THINK I NEVER STOOD
BY YOU?
>> I STOOD BY YOU EVEN WHEN YOU
WERE PREGNANT.
>> JOEY, WHEN I WAS PREGNANT I
WAS GONNA GO TO JERSEY.
I KEPT TELLING MY MOM, "NO, NO,
I WANT TO STAY WITH HIM."
YOU NOTICE I GOT PISSED AT YOU
WHEN YOU STOPPED TAKING CARE OF
AYDENN.
>> TAKING CARE--I WAS TRYING.
JUST BECAUSE IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE NIGHT--DOESN'T MEAN [bleep].
I TRIED.
I TRIED FEEDING HIM.
>> GOOD JOB TRYING TO FEED HIM.
>> I TRIED CHANGING HIS DIAPER.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, YOU TRIED?
>> I EVEN TRIED TO VOLUNTEER TO
GIVE HIM A BATH.
>> GOOD, VOLUNTEER EVERY ONCE
A WEEK.
>> I TRIED EVERY DAY.
>> 'CAUSE HE DOESN'T NEED TO
TAKE A BATH EVERY DAY OR EAT
EVERY THREE HOURS.
>> I TRIED EVERY DAY.
WHEN DID WE BECOME SO
BROKEN, HUH?
>> WHEN YOU STOPPED TAKING CARE
OF AYDENN.
>> 'CAUSE OF THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> [sniffling]
>> * AND SO I'LL GO MY WAY *
* I DON'T KNOW *
* WHAT'S LEFT TO SAY *
* WHEN YOU LOOK BACK *
* ON THIS YEARS FROM NOW *
* WILL YOU ASK YOURSELF? *
* WILL YOU WONDER HOW *
* YOU COULD LET MY LOVE *
* OUT FROM YOU? *
* 'CAUSE WHEN I'M GONE *
* I WON'T LOOK BACK AT ALL *
* WHEN I'M GONE *
* I WON'T LOOK BACK AT *
* I WON'T BE TROUBLE *
* WHEN I'M GONE *
* I WON'T LOOK BACK AT ALL *
* *
[phone trilling]
>> HELLO?
>> HEY, ME AND JOEY JUST
BROKE UP.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> UM, I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU THINK IT'S COOL IF I COME
STAY WITH YOU?
>> YEAH.
UM, YOU WANT ME TO GO
PICK YOU UP?
>> YEAH, I'M OUTSIDE HIS HOUSE.
>> OKAY, I'M ON MY WAY.
>> OKAY.
>> BYE.
I DON'T THINK JOEY WAS READY FOR
A BABY.
I THINK ONCE HE WAS BORN IT KIND
OF HIT HIM LIKE, "WHOA, THIS IS
A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITY."
AND HE DIDN'T TAKE UP TO HIS
RESPONSIBILITIES.
SO I DON'T THINK HE WAS READY
AT ALL.
>> HEY.
I THINK JOEY THOUGHT OUR
RELATIONSHIP WOULD BE THE SAME,
LIKE HOW IT WAS BEFORE I WAS
PREGNANT, WHILE I WAS PREGNANT,
AND WHEN AYDENN WAS BORN.
>> YEAH, RIGHT NOW?
>> YEAH.
PARENTING IS VERY HARD.
BUT I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA
BE EASY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE ME,
JOEY, AND THE BABY.
SO WE'D TAKE TURNS.
I NEVER GET SLEEP.
IT'S VERY EXPENSIVE, AND I'M BY
MYSELF NOW.
IT'S NOT ANYTHING I THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE.
>> YOU GOT IT?
YOU GOT EVERYTHING?
I'M GONNA GET YOUR BAG.
>> I'M SO CLOSE TO FINISHING
HIGH SCHOOL.
AND I THINK I COULD DEAL WITH
STAYING IN TEXAS FOR A COUPLE
MORE MONTHS, BECAUSE IF I GO
TO NEW JERSEY, I'LL HAVE TO STAY
BACK AND BE A SENIOR AGAIN;
RATHER THAN STAYING HERE, I'LL
GRADUATE THIS YEAR.
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
>> I'M AT ASHLEY'S HOUSE.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO STAY HERE
TO GRADUATE.
>> I WOULD PREFER YOU HERE.
>> I WOULD PREFER TO BE THERE
TOO, BUT I'M NOT GONNA FAIL
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> BETTER NOT.
>> I AM VERY EXCITED TO GO HOME
AND BE WITH MY MOM.
I CAN'T WAIT TILL GRADUATION.
I WILL LEAVE THAT DAY TO GO WITH
MY MOM AND TO JERSEY.
JOEY CAN STILL SEE AYDENN
WHENEVER HE WANTS.
BUT IT'S UP
TO HIM IF HE WANTS TO SEE AYDENN
OR NOT, NOT ME.
I USED TO THINK THAT THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING FOR AYDENN WAS
TO MAKE SURE HE HAD TWO PARENTS.
THAT'S WHY I STAYED HERE.
AND WHAT I ALWAYS TOLD JOEY.
BUT I THINK THAT'S CHANGED,
BECAUSE I THINK THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING...
HI, SWEETIE.
ABOUT HAVING A CHILD IS MAKING
SURE THAT THEY'RE STABLE,
HAPPY, AND OKAY,
EVEN IF THAT MEANS HAVING ONE
PARENT AROUND.
>> announcer: NEXT WEEK, ON THE:
>> WE'D LIKE TO WELCOME OUR TEN
TEENAGE MOMS HERE.
>> I JUST REALIZED I DIDN'T,
LIKE, FEEL FOR HIM WHAT YOU
SHOULD FEEL FOR SOMEBODY.
WHY AM I CRYING SO MUCH?
>> HOW'D YOU GET A HICKEY ON
YOUR NECK?
>> I TOLD YOU. A GIRL.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU HAD SEX WITH
ANOTHER GIRL.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> BROKEN.
>> YOU FEEL BROKEN?
>> 'CAUSE WE'RE JUST
FALLING APART.
>> JOEY, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
US BRINGING THE BABY OUT?
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM IN MONTHS.