>> [laughs]
I'M JORDAN.
I'M FROM BALTIMORE, MARYLAND.
I WAS ALWAYS THE POPULAR GIRL
AT SCHOOL,
AND NEVER MISSED A PARTY.
REMEMBER HOW TAN I GOT?
>> YOU GOT REALLY TAN.
>> WE DANCE.
>> WHEN I MET MY BOYFRIEND DEREK
OVER A YEAR AGO ON TWITTER,
WE GOT SERIOUS REALLY QUICKLY.
WE SPEND ALL OUR TIME TOGETHER.
>> I LOVE YOU, BUG.
>> I LOVE YOU.
DEREK GOT A COLLEGE SCHOLARSHIP,
AND MY DAD AND STEPMOM EVEN LET
HIM MOVE IN WITH US BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T HAVE A PLACE TO STAY.
I JUST GRADUATED FROM HIGH
SCHOOL, AND ALWAYS DREAMED OF
JOINING THE ARMY.
BUT NOW ALL OF OUR PLANS ARE
GONNA CHANGE,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
DEREK AND I ARE HAVING A
DAUGHTER, AND WE DECIDED TO NAME
HER GENEVIEVE, EVIE FOR SHORT.
SHE'LL BE HERE IN SEVEN WEEKS,
AND WE HAVE A LOT TO FIGURE OUT.
AFTER I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, DEREK DROPPED OUT OF
COLLEGE AND STARTED WORKING.
BUT THEN HE LOST HIS JOB.
MY PARENTS GOT MAD AND KICKED
HIM OUT, AND I WENT WITH HIM.
I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO THEM SINCE.
>> THIS IS [bleep].
>> FOR THE PAST THREE WEEKS,
WE'VE BEEN BROKE AND HOMELESS.
DEREK HASN'T GOTTEN ANOTHER JOB
YET.
HEY, I'VE BEEN WONDERING IF I
COULD STAY WITH YOU GUYS
JUST FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE ANYWHERE
TO STAY RIGHT NOW.
WE'VE BEEN COUCH SURFING
WITH FRIENDS.
ALL WE HAVE IS EACH OTHER
AND OUR BEAT-UP OLD MINIVAN
THAT WE CALL BERTHA.
I HATE LIVING OUT OF THIS CAR.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE STAYING WITH
DEREK'S FRIEND PATRICK,
BUT WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
A BETTER OPTION.
>> AWAKE?
>> YES, I'M AWAKE.
>> IS SHE AWAKE IN THERE?
>> YEAH.
SHE'S HUNGRY.
[groans]
THERE'S NOTHING IN THERE.
>> UM...
>> NO.
>> THERE'S BANANAS.
>> OH, YEAH.
I GUESS I'LL EAT A BANANA.
YOU KNOW, WE CAN PROBABLY ONLY
STAY HERE A COUPLE MORE NIGHTS,
'CAUSE WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR,
WHAT, A BUNCH ALREADY?
>> I HATE HAVING ALL MY STUFF
IN MY TRASH BAGS.
>> IT'S NOT WORKING.
WE ARE BASICALLY HOMELESS.
I'M FURIOUS ABOUT WHEN MY DAD
KICKED US OUT.
YOUR JOB WAS SEASONAL,
AND YOU TOLD HIM THAT.
>> BUT HE ALWAYS OVERREACTS...
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> SO IT'S NOT LIKE IT WASN'T
EXPECTED.
>> I'M REALLY MAD ABOUT
THE WHOLE SITUATION.
OUR LIVES WOULD BE SO DIFFERENT
IF I DIDN'T GET PREGNANT.
MAYBE WE SHOULD'VE BEEN
A LOT MORE CAREFUL.
>> THAT'S YOUR FAULT.
>> MY FAULT?
YOU KNEW THAT I WAS NOT ON
BIRTH CONTROL.
>> I HATE CONDOMS.
I DON'T LIKE THE WORD.
I DON'T LIKE THE IDEA.
IT'S LIKE PUNISHMENT.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT IS.
WE CAN'T AFFORD THIS ONE.
SHE'S COMING IN TWO MONTHS.
IF WE'RE HERE, WHERE ARE WE
GONNA PUT HER, ON THE FLOOR?
ONCE TIME GETS CLOSER,
IT'S NOT GONNA FLY ANYMORE.
IF I WAS TO GO INTO LABOR,
WHERE THE HECK ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO BRING HER HOME?
>> I KNOW.
I'LL DO MY PART.
I'M GONNA LOOK FOR A JOB.
>> DEREK AND I ARE RUNNING OUT
OF PLACES WHERE WE CAN BOTH
STAY, AND SOMETIMES I NEED
A BREAK FROM PATRICK'S.
LUCKILY, MY FRIEND SUGAR
WILL ALWAYS COME PICK ME UP,
SO I CAN CRASH AT HER HOUSE.
>> ALL RIGHT, SHOW ME WHERE
YOU SLEEP.
>> ON THE--
RIGHT THERE.
ON THE FUTON.
>> IS THAT EVEN COMFORTABLE
FOR YOU?
>> YEAH, THAT'S--
>> ARE YOU OKAY WITH THAT?
>> YEAH.
DOESN'T BOTHER ME.
>> WHERE DO YOU EVEN KEEP
YOUR CLOTHES AT?
>> WELL, IT WAS IN BAGS
RIGHT THERE, BUT THERE'S CLOTHES
ALL OVER THE FLOOR NOW.
>> OH.
SO WHAT DID YOU GUYS DO
LAST NIGHT, SINCE, YOU KNOW,
YOU SEEM ALL TIRED?
>> THIS RIGHT HERE.
>> THE FUNNY THING IS,
THEY'RE NOT KIDDING.
THIS IS WHAT THEY DO.
>> THIS IS WHAT YOU GUYS REALLY
DO.
>> I ATE SOME NASTY HOT DOGS
AND FELT REALLY SICK TO MY
STOMACH.
>> OH, THEY WERE--IT WAS KINDA--
>> IT WAS DISGUSTING.
>> WHERE'S YOUR JOB, DEREK?
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU GOT A JOB.
>> YEAH, I'M A PROFESSIONAL
VIDEO GAME PLAYER.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD ACTUALLY,
LIKE, GO AND GET A JOB,
JUST, MAYBE.
>> I SHOULD, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> WELL, HOW SOON--
YOU KNOW, THE BABY'S DUE IN,
LIKE, A MONTH AND A HALF NOW.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING NERVOUS?
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE NOT GETTING BOTHERED
BY IT RIGHT NOW?
>> I MEAN, IT IS WHAT IT IS.
>> HONESTLY, DEREK, YOU NEED
TO STEP UP MORE.
SHE HAS NEEDS.
SHE REALLY NEEDS HELP.
>> SHE DOES?
>> YEAH.
AND I KNOW YOU CAN'T REALLY
SEE THAT, BECAUSE YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THE GAME RIGHT NOW,
BUT SHE DOES.
>> YOU NEED HELP, BABY?
>> STEP UP AND SAY YOU NEED
HELP.
>> YES.
>> SHE NEEDS HELP.
SHE NEEDS MORE HELP.
>> I DO.
>> SHE NEEDS TO EAT MORE.
SHE NEEDS TO HAVE A BED.
SHE NEEDS TO HAVE HELP
WITH MONEY.
DON'T YOU WANT BETTER FOR YOUR
KID?
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING THAT DEREK
ISN'T TAKING PARENTHOOD
SERIOUSLY.
I'M GLAD I HAVE SUGAR'S SUPPORT,
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE SHE GOT
PREGNANT AROUND THE SAME TIME
AS ME.
BUT SHE ENDED UP MAKING
A DIFFERENT DECISION.
>> WHEN YOU FIGURED OUT YOU WERE
PREGNANT, WHAT WAS YOUR FIRST
REACTION?
>> I CRIED IN THE OFFICE.
WHEN THEY CALLED ME BACK THERE,
AND THE WOMAN, SHE WAS LIKE,
"YEAH, YOU'RE PREGNANT."
>> HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
AN ABORTION?
>> I KNOW I COULDN'T DO THAT.
>> WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
I JUST DECIDED TO GET AN
ABORTION, BECAUSE I FELT LIKE,
IN A SENSE, I WAS STILL A KID,
AND IT WAS KIND OF LIKE,
I DON'T FEEL LIKE I CAN HANDLE
THAT TYPE OF PRESSURE YET.
>> YEAH, BUT I WASN'T GONNA BE,
LIKE, "OH, YOU MADE THE WRONG
DECISION."
'CAUSE NOW I SEE THAT, YOU KNOW,
YOUR LIFE STILL GETS TO MOVE
FORWARD, AND I'M MOVING FORWARD
IN A DIFFERENT DIRECTION.
IF I COULD GO TO COLLEGE
RIGHT NOW, BELIEVE ME, I WOULD.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS
HAVE GROWN MORE CLOSER,
OR APART, SINCE ALL THIS HAS
BEEN GOING ON?
>> CLOSER, ACTUALLY.
WITH ALL THIS MOVING AROUND,
I WISH I COULD JUST FIND
SOMEWHERE TO STAY, LIKE,
LONG-TERM.
PATRICK, LIKE--
I DON'T MIND STAYING THERE
AT ALL,
BUT IT'S LIKE,
HE HAS A LOT OF HIS FRIENDS
COME OVER AND STUFF LIKE THAT,
AND THEN I'M PREGNANT,
SO I NEED TO SLEEP EARLIER
THAN ALL OF THEM.
AND IF WE'RE IN THE LIVING ROOM
AND THEY'RE ALL TRYING TO HANG
OUT IN THE LIVING ROOM,
I'M FALLING ASLEEP AND I JUST
FEEL RUDE.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE YOU HERE
ALL THE TIME, HONESTLY,
BUT IT'S KIND OF LIKE MORE
OF A RESPECT THING, YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T THINK MY MOM WILL
WANT, LIKE, SOME GUY JUST
SLEEPING ON THE COUCH EVERY
NIGHT, BECAUSE--
>> YEAH, OF COURSE.
NO, I UNDERSTAND.
>> YOU KNOW.
>> I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OH, GOD.
>> SO YOU READY FOR BED?
>> YES.
>> HOW'S IT FEEL SLEEPING
IN A BED NOW?
>> GREAT.
>> * OH, OH
* OH, OH, OH, OH
>> IT WAS NICE SPENDING THE
NIGHT AT SUGAR'S,
BUT DEREK AND I NEED A PERMANENT
PLACE TO GET READY FOR THE BABY.
THE ONLY PEOPLE I'M SPEAKING TO
FROM MY FAMILY RIGHT NOW
ARE MY GRANDMOTHER AND AUNT.
I REALLY HOPE THEY CAN
HELP US OUT.
>> IT'S HUGE.
>> I KNOW.
>> GOTTEN BIGGER SINCE THE LAST
TIME.
SO HOW YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> HAVE YOU SPOKEN TO YOUR DAD
LATELY?
>> NO.
NOT SINCE I LEFT.
I GET WHY, IN HIS MIND,
MY DAD ASKED DEREK TO LEAVE.
THAT'S NOT A LOGICAL REASON
TO ME, BUT, WHATEVER.
IT'S NOT MY HOUSE.
BUT FOR YOU TO GET MAD AT ME--
YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT MARRIED,
FINE, BUT HE'S THE FATHER
OF MY CHILD...
>> RIGHT.
>> WHO LOVES ME AND LOVES
THE BABY AND IS WILLING TO BE
THERE FOR ME.
AND YOU WANT ME TO WALK AWAY
FROM HIM TO BE WITH--
TO STAY WITH YOU.
>> THAT'S MY SON,
AND I HATE TO SEE HIM DO THIS
TO YOU.
>> RIGHT NOW WE HAVE NO MEANS
OF SUPPORTING A BABY.
I HAVE NO BANK ACCOUNT,
'CAUSE I NEVER NEEDED ONE,
SO I HAVE NO MONEY SAVED UP
WHATSOEVER.
HIS IS IN THE NEGATIVE.
>> I GOT PAID TODAY.
I CAN GIVE YOU SOME MONEY
FOR GAS OR--
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO HAVE
TO DO THAT.
>> BUT YOU'RE STILL GONNA TAKE
SOME MONEY TONIGHT TO PUT GAS
IN THAT CAR.
GOT IT?
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> 'CAUSE IT WILL HELP.
>> I MEAN, THINGS ARE GOING
TO BE ROUGH.
THEY ARE, YOU KNOW.
I'VE BEEN THERE, DONE THAT.
>> WOULD WE BE ABLE TO STAY
HERE?
>> DO--
>> WE--WE CAN'T.
THERE'S NO ROOM.
WE WISH YOU COULD STAY HERE.
IT'S JUST TOO--TOO MUCH.
I JUST WISHED IT WAS BETTER
FOR YOU.
>> YEAH, WELL, IT'S NOT GONNA
BE, SO I JUST GOT TO MAKE
THE BEST OUT OF IT.
>> OUR DAUGHTER WILL BE HERE
IN SIX WEEKS,
AND AFTER GETTING TURNED DOWN
BY MY GRANDMOTHER, DEREK DECIDED
TO REACH OUT TO HIS DAD,
WHO LIVES IN TEXAS,
TO SEE IF HE HAS ANY OPTIONS.
>> WANT TO GO IN THERE?
>> YEAH, IT'S PROBABLY WARM.
>> HI, DAD.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> NOTHING'S REALLY CHANGED
SINCE YOU LEFT.
WE STILL DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHERE TO GO OR WHERE TO STAY.
>> I KNOW IT UPSETS YOU THAT
I MADE THE SAME MISTAKE AS YOU.
>> FOR REAL, DAD.
DO YOU HAVE ANY--
WHAT CAN WE DO?
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?
>> WE CAN'T DO THAT.
>> BUT WE ALSO--
>> MY MEDICAL INSURANCE DOESN'T
SWITCH OVER.
>> I DON'T THAT HER MEDICAL
INSURANCE WILL SWITCH OVER.
>> I'M GONNA CALL HER AND SEE
WHAT--SEE WHAT SHE HAS TO SAY.
ALL RIGHT, DAD, WELL,
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
>> FEEL WEIRD STAYING WITH
SOMEONE I'VE NEVER EVEN MET.
>> BETTER THAN A BACK SEAT.
WE CAN'T GO TO TEXAS.
CAN'T KEEP STAYING AT PATRICK'S.
>> WHAT IF SHE'S, LIKE,
A PSYCHO?
>> YOU THINK DAD WOULD OFFER US
TO GO STAY SOMEWHERE THAT WASN'T
SAFE?
>> NO.
>> RIGHT.
I'VE KNOWN HER SINCE I WAS
A LITTLE BOY.
>> I'M JUST SAYING...
>> SHE'S NOT GONNA--
>> SHE COULD THROW US OUT
LIKE OTHER PEOPLE HAVE.
>> NO.
JORDAN, YOUR PARENTS ARE UNIQUE.
THEY ARE ONE-OF-A-KIND.
SHE'S NOT GONNA DO THAT TO US.
>> WELL...
BEGGARS CAN'T BE CHOOSERS.
>> YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> SINCE WE'VE RUN OUT OF
OPTIONS,
DEREK CALLED TRACY,
AND SHE INVITED US OVER TO TALK.
[knock on door]
HI.
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> WHY DON'T WE JUST, UM,
GO HEAD OVER TO THE DINING ROOM
AND SIT DOWN SO WE CAN TALK.
>> OKAY.
>> SO I'M REALLY GLAD YOU GUYS
COULD COME OVER TODAY.
I'VE BEEN TALKING TO YOUR DAD,
DEREK, ABOUT YOUR GUYS'
SITUATION.
NOW WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN STAYING?
>> WE'VE BEEN SLEEPING ON
FLOORS,
MATTRESSES ON THE GROUND.
JUST ANYWHERE.
THIS WHOLE SITUATION HAS BEEN
STRESSFUL FOR HER,
AND SHE CAN'T REALLY--
>> YEAH.
>> CAN'T REALLY PUT HER THROUGH
TOO MUCH MORE.
>> NO.
AS A YOUNG WOMAN, YOU NEED
SOMEONE ELSE IN YOUR CORNER--
ANOTHER WOMAN FIGURE.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE YOUR MOM,
BUT I'VE HAD THREE KIDS.
I'VE BEEN PREGNANT THREE TIMES,
SO--
>> DO YOU NEED ANYTHING FROM US?
OBVIOUSLY, I WANT TO GET A JOB.
>> I'M NOT GONNA SAY,
"I NEED THIS MUCH MONEY
EVERY MONTH FOR YOU TO BE HERE."
>> RIGHT.
>> I--UNTIL YOU GUYS GET ON
YOUR FEET, I WILL DO WHATEVER
I CAN DO, AS LONG AS YOU GUYS
RESPECT ME AND RESPECT,
YOU KNOW,
MY CHILDREN AND THEIR HOME.
>> EVERYBODY IN THE HOUSE, YEAH.
>> THAT'S REALLY, REALLY
GENEROUS OF YOU,
AND I'M REALLY APPRECIATIVE
OF IT.
>> I KNOW IT'S NOT A BEDROOM,
BUT I WANTED TO OFFER YOU
MY LIVING ROOM.
I HAVE TWO TWIN MATTRESSES...
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT YOU COULD PUT TOGETHER.
>> DO YOU NEED ANY TIME TO,
LIKE, THINK THIS OVER,
OR CONTEMPLATE IDEAS?
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE SOLD.
>> YEP.
>> LOOK AT HER BIG, GIANT SMILE.
SHE'S LIKE, "YES."
LET'S GO LOOK AT IT REAL QUICK
AND JUST SEE IF WE CAN FIGURE
OUT WHERE WE'RE GONNA PUT
THINGS, OR WHATEVER.
HERE'S THE ROOM.
I WAS THINKING,
IF YOU GUYS WANT TO PUT, LIKE,
THE SEATING AREA OVER THIS WAY
AND THEN YOU COULD PROBABLY
PUT THE BED--YOUR BED, LIKE,
OVER HERE.
>> YEAH, IN THE CORNER.
>> WE CAN MOVE THINGS AROUND,
LIKE--
>> ALTHOUGH BABY STUFF DOES
TAKE UP A LOT, SO, YEAH.
>> WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
>> A LOT BETTER THAN BEING
ON THE FLOOR.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S MY LITTLE BOY.
>> HE'S LIKE, "WHAT THE HECK?"
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
>> ALL RIGHTY,
WE'LL CALL YOU LATER.
>> YEP.
>> THERE'S HARDENED DOG POOP.
>> YOU'RE IN CHARGE OF THAT ONE,
HOMEY.
>> EW.
OH...
>> THE DOG POOP IS SO HARD.
IT'S BEEN BACK HERE PROBABLY
FOR YEARS.
>> WE DON'T NEED HER PICKING UP
DOG POOP AND EATING IT.
WE'LL GET THIS AREA CLEANED,
WE'LL PUT THE BEDS HERE,
AND THEN...
SWEEP, VACUUM, MOP.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DEFINITELY
FEBREZE AND SPRAY.
>> IT'S BETTER THAN THE FLOOR.
>> IT IS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO SUCK IT UP
AND MAKE SACRIFICES.
>> * OH, OH, OH, OH
* OH, OH
>> [gasps]
MY NAIL ALREADY CHIPPED.
>> NO!
>> LOOK AT IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT?
DO YOU AND DEREK STILL DO IT?
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> DO YOU?
>> I CHOOSE NOT TO.
>> I HEARD, LIKE, SOME PEOPLE,
LIKE, WHEN THEY'RE PREGNANT,
LIKE, THEY WANT IT MORE.
CAN YOU GET PREGNANT
WHILE YOU'RE PREGNANT?
>> WHAT?
NO.
>> OH.
>> ARE YOU SENSITIVE ABOUT
THE WAY YOUR BODY LOOKS?
>> YES.
I HAVE MY BIG OL' BELLY, AND--
>> MAKES EVERYTHING DIFFICULT.
>> IT'S JUST--YEAH.
>> IS THERE ANYTHING YOU'RE
SUPER EXCITED ABOUT?
>> JUST HAVING HER THERE.
'CAUSE IT'S LIKE, YOU GET
SO USED TO HAVING SOMEONE
IN YOUR STOMACH, LIKE--
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE IT'LL GIVE
YOU CLOSURE, LIKE YOU HAVE
A FAMILY THAT'S, LIKE,
ALL TOGETHER?
>> YEAH, AS LONG AS WE GET
EVERYTHING TOGETHER BEFORE
SHE COMES.
>> YOU DEFINITELY WANT
A BABY SHOWER, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, AND I THINK EVERY
PREGNANT PERSON WANTS A BABY--
LIKE, IT'S A BIG DEAL.
>> ME AND MY MOM--
WE DEFINITELY WANT TO DO ONE
FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU DESERVE
ONE.
I THINK IT'LL HELP YOU A LOT,
BECAUSE YOU REALLY HAVE,
YOU KNOW, NOTHING RIGHT NOW.
>> I'D LOVE THAT.
THANK YOU.
AND I HONESTLY DON'T EVEN WANT
TO INVITE MY DAD OR MY MOM.
I REALLY DON'T CARE AT ALL.
I REFUSE TO TALK TO THEM
EVER AGAIN.
>> * OUT ON THE STREETS
*HELD OUT HIS HAND *
* AND DROPPED TO HIS FEET
>> [grunts]
>> WE HAVE THE TABLE READY
FOR YOU TO MAKE THE FAVORS.
>> I'M REALLY, REALLY THANKFUL
AND HAPPY THAT YOU GUYS HAVE
MADE IT, YOU KNOW, THIS MUCH
EASIER, THAT NOW WE WILL HAVE
STUFF THAT WILL HELP OUT,
BECAUSE WE HAVE LITERALLY
NOTHING RIGHT NOW.
>> WE'RE GLAD TO REALLY HELP
YOU.
WE REALLY ARE.
>> SO HOW ARE THINGS AT TRACY'S,
JORDAN?
>> I MEAN, I'M NOT REALLY
COMPLAINING, BECAUSE IT'S A LOT
BETTER NOW THAT WE ACTUALLY HAVE
AN AREA TO SLEEP ON.
THIS WILL NOT BE A PERMANENT
SITUATION.
THERE'S NOT EVEN ENOUGH ROOM.
>> ONCE THE BABY SHOWER'S DONE,
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
FINANCIALLY AFTER THAT?
>> DEREK'S JUST GONNA START
LOOKING FOR A JOB
SO HE'S AT LEAST WORKING.
>> START LOOKING FOR A JOB?
HE HASN'T STARTED?
IF DEREK GETS SCARED,
HE'S GONNA PROBABLY RUN TO HIS
DAD.
>> AND THEN I'M SCREWED.
>> WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN IF DEREK
DOESN'T COME THROUGH?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T WORK RIGHT NOW.
NOBODY'S GONNA HIRE ME.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU DO FOR MONEY
TO FEED THE BABY AND CLOTHE IT?
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANOTHER
OPTION, YOUR BABY DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING.
WHAT DO OTHER GIRLS DO
IN YOUR SITUATION?
BECAUSE LIVING IN SOMEONE ELSE'S
HOME IS NOT ALWAYS THE BEST
THING.
>> THEY EITHER GO TO A HOMELESS
SHELTER, BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT'S
THERE, AND THEN THEY HAVE TO GO
TO SOUP KITCHENS AND STUFF
LIKE THAT.
>> LIKE, I'M REALLY PISSED OFF,
BECAUSE SHE'S THINKING HER ONLY
OPTION RIGHT NOW...
>> YEAH.
>> IS A HOMELESS SHELTER.
>> AND THAT'S REALLY MAKING
ME IRRITATED.
YOU DO HAVE ANOTHER OPTION.
IT'S FOR DEREK TO WORK.
AND HE'S NOT WORKING.
>> IT'S STRESSFUL ENOUGH
BEING A TEENAGER ON TOP OF
HAVING YOUR FIRST BABY,
AND THEN NOT HAVING A STABLE
PLACE WHERE YOU KNOW YOU'RE
GONNA LIVE ON TOP OF ALL OF
THAT.
>> DON'T BE AFRAID.
I WANT HER TO BE STRONG, AND--
>> SHE IS STRONG.
SHE MADE IT THIS--SHE MADE IT
THIS FAR WITHOUT FREAKING OUT.
>> I WANT HER TO BE STRONG,
BECAUSE I KNOW SHE CAN DO IT.
THAT'S WHY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
LISTEN, I'M HERE ANYTIME YOU
WANT TO TALK TO US, OKAY?
>> OUR DAUGHTER WILL BE HERE
IN THREE WEEKS.
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE NOT READY,
AND DEREK HASN'T LOOKED FOR
A JOB, I'M REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT BECOMING A MOM.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK SHE'S GONNA
LOOK LIKE?
>> YOU.
>> AND THE FIRST THING WE ARE
SEEING IS THAT SHE HAS A LOT
OF HAIR.
>> LOOK AT HER.
SHE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
SHE'S GOT YOUR NOSE
AND YOUR CHIN.
>> JAY-Z LIP.
>> SHE DOESN'T HAVE A JAY-Z LIP.
>> [laughs]
>> SHE'S CHEWING.
THEY ACTUALLY DRINK THEIR FLUID
WHEN THEY'RE DOING THAT.
AND FLUID IS PEE,
IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
>> EW, EVIE, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> WELL, MOST OF US TURN OUT
NORMAL, SO.
SHE'S MAYBE ABOUT 8 1/2 POUNDS.
>> [scoffs]
MAN.
>> WHAT?
>> OKAY.
BRING YOUR PICTURES UP
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
>> OKAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> I WONDER WHAT THAT MEANS,
THAT HER HEAD'S A LITTLE BIT
BIGGER.
>> SHE'S GOT A BIG HEAD.
LIKE MOMMY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO PUSH A BIG
ROUND HEAD OUT.
I KNOW THIS IS GONNA BE AWFUL
FOR ME.
I'M GONNA WANT TO DIE.
>> IT'LL BE OKAY.
>> NOT REALLY READY FOR HER
TO COME YET.
SHE NEEDS TO STAY IN THERE
UNTIL SHE'S SUPPOSED TO COME,
'CAUSE WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
READY YET.
WE'RE NOT GONNA GET EVERYTHING
AT THE BABY SHOWER.
>> BUT WE'LL GET A LOT MORE
THAN WHAT WE HAVE.
>> YEAH, WE WILL.
I'M SERIOUS.
AND WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO,
JUST STAY LIVING WITH TRACY?
>> YEAH, WE'RE NOT GONNA HAVE
A CHOICE.
>> OH, GOD, SHUT UP.
WE CAN'T LIVE AT TRACY'S
FOREVER.
YOU NEED TO START LOOKING
FOR A JOB.
'CAUSE WE'RE NEVER GONNA GET
ANYWHERE IF WE DON'T HAVE MONEY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> SO NOW YOU'RE PISSED OFF,
SO--
DO YOU WANT TO SAY SOMETHING?
>> SO COMPLAINING TO ME
IS GONNA DO WHAT?
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
>> SO WHAT IS IT ABOUT?
>> HER.
>> * I'M GETTING OVER *
>> THERE'S SO MUCH UNCERTAINTY
AND ALL THIS OTHER CRAP.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S FAIR
FOR HER.
[melancholy piano music]
*
>> * HOURS AGO
>> AFTER THE ULTRASOUND,
DEREK PROMISED ME THAT
HE'D START LOOKING FOR A JOB
SO WE CAN FINALLY GET SOME MONEY
COMING IN.
>> ALL RIGHTY.
LET'S WARM UP.
>> [shivering]
[engine sputters]
WHY ISN'T IT TURNING ON?
[starter clicking]
DOES SHE HAVE GAS?
>> YEAH, BABE.
THAT'S THE BATTERY.
>> DID YOU LEAVE THE LIGHTS ON?
>> NO, THE LIGHTS ARE OFF.
>> YOU ALWAYS LEAVE THE LIGHTS
ON.
WHAT DO WE DO?
[starter clicking]
ASK HIM, ASK HIM.
>> HEY, EXCUSE ME.
YOU DON'T HAPPEN TO HAVE
A PAIR OF JUMPER CABLES, DO YOU?
>> I MIGHT, ACTUALLY.
[engine turns over]
>> YOU GOT IT!
[engine sputters]
>> DANG.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL HAVE TO FIGURE SOMETHING
OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH THOUGH.
IT WAS WORTH A TRY.
THINGS WILL TURN AROUND FOR US.
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU THOUGH.
>> I'M ROOTING FOR YOU GUYS.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
THANK YOU.
>> WE CAN'T BE WITHOUT A CAR.
>> YOU KNOW, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET TO STEPPIN'.
BABE.
>> IT'S, LIKE, A MILE...
>> WELL...
>> IN THE COLD.
>> WE'RE LOSING DAYLIGHT,
I'M FREEZING COLD,
AND I WOULD LIKE TO GO HOME,
SO WE NEED TO START WALKING,
AND WE CAN TALK ABOUT IT WHEN WE
GET IN THE HOUSE,
WHERE IT'S WARM.
>> I THINK MY FINGERS ARE FROZEN
OFF.
BERTHA WAS THE ONE THING WE HAD.
>> WE KNEW SHE WAS GONNA DIE,
AND IT JUST SO HAPPENS THAT
SHE DID.
>> NOW HOW THE HECK ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO GET TO DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENTS?
>> MISS TRACY.
>> WHAT HAPPENS IF I GO IN LABOR
AND MISS TRACY'S NOT HERE?
NOW WE DON'T HAVE A CAR.
HOW ARE YOU GONNA GET A JOB?
HOW ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO GET
TO THE JOB?
HA, THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
I'M NOT STRESSING ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW, BECAUSE I HAVE OTHER
THINGS TO BE WORRIED ABOUT.
>> LIKE WHAT?
SHE'S GOING TO BE HERE.
I HATE THAT YOU'RE SO RELAXED
ABOUT IT.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU.
>> EXACTLY--
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE AN [bleep].
AFTER ABANDONING OUR MINIVAN,
IT GOT IMPOUNDED.
DEREK STILL HASN'T FOUND A JOB,
AND WE'VE BEEN STUCK INSIDE
TRACY'S HOUSE FOR THE LAST
FEW DAYS.
YOU SAID YOU WERE GONNA LOOK
ONLINE FOR JOBS.
ARE YOU GONNA DO THAT TODAY?
>> MM-HMM, YEAH.
>> ARE YOU GONNA DO IT
WHILE I DO LAUNDRY?
OKAY, JUST KEEP LOOKING
ON YOUR PHONE.
>> IF I SAID I WAS GONNA
DO IT TODAY,
THEN I'M GONNA DO IT TODAY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DO YOUR OWN DAMN LAUNDRY THEN.
WHY ARE YOU SO ANGRY?
HMM?
>> YOU NONSTOP NAG
AND QUESTION AND ANNOY.
>> IF YOU DID STUFF THE FIRST
TIME, I WOULDN'T HAVE TO NAG YOU
ABOUT IT.
>> YOU NAG ABOUT THE DUMBEST
[bleep].
>> WELL, I THINK I HAVE A RIGHT
TO BE STRESSED OUT.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE YOU SAID
BEFORE THE BABY CAME
EVERYTHING WILL BE SITUATED,
AND IT'S NOT.
>> WHAT'S NOT SITUATED?
>> NOTHING'S SITUATED.
YOU'RE LIVING IN SOMEONE ELSE'S
LIVING ROOM.
THERE'S NO ROOM FOR THE BABY.
>> WE'RE LIVING IN SOMEBODY'S
LIVING ROOM.
IT'S TOUGH [bleep].
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO?
THERE ISN'T NOWHERE TO GO.
WE CAN'T GO TO YOUR PARENTS'
HOUSE.
ACCEPT THE SITUATION AND DEAL
WITH IT.
FIGURE [bleep] OUT.
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO.
>> STOP YELLING AT ME.
>> ARE YOU FRUSTRATED BECAUSE
YOU FEEL LIKE IT'S MY FAULT
THAT WE'RE IN THIS SITUATION?
>> NO, I MEAN, I CAN LEAVE
AT ANY POINT IN TIME
THAT I WANT TO LEAVE.
>> YOU CAN'T DO THAT WHEN
THE BABY COMES.
>> WHY?
>> YOU CAN'T JUST LEAVE.
>> YOU'RE STUCK HERE.
I'M NOT.
>> * THAT'S HOW WE START *
* TO MATTER
*
* ONE OF US LEADS
* ONE OF US FOLLOWS
>> I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM DEREK
SINCE HE STORMED OUT,
AND I'M REALLY HURT BY WHAT
HE SAID.
>> HI, BABY.
ARE YOU DONE ARGUING?
>> ARE WE DONE ARGUING?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE WHO LEFT.
NOT ME.
>> I HAD TO.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING.
>> I CAN'T DEAL WITH YOU
SOMETIMES.
>> WELL, WHAT DID YOU MEAN WHEN
YOU SAID THAT I'M STUCK HERE
BUT YOU CAN LEAVE AT ANYTIME?
>> IF I WAS GOING TO LEAVE,
WHEN YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE
PREGNANT, I WOULD'VE LEFT.
I WOULD NEVER WALK OUT ON YOU
AND EVIE.
>> MAYBE I NEED TO STRESS
A LITTLE LESS,
BUT YOU SHOULD STRESS
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> WHO SAID I'M NOT STRESSED?
>> YOU DON'T SHOW IT.
>> RIGHT.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO PUSH YOU.
SHE'S GONNA BE HERE VERY SOON,
AND WE'RE NOT IN THE BEST
SITUATION FOR HER.
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK FOR A JOB.
I WILL LOOK ONLINE FOR A JOB.
>> IT JUST STRESSES ME OUT.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL--
>> AND THEN SHE HAS TO RELY
ON BOTH OF US.
>> YOU GUYS ARE VERY IMPORTANT
TO ME.
I'M NOT GOING AWAY.
>> IF YOU SAY SO.
SINCE WE STILL NEED BABY STUFF,
I'M REALLY HAPPY SUGAR AND HER
MOM ARE THROWING US A SHOWER.
>> COME IN.
>> SURPRISE!
>> HEY.
>> HEY!
>> HI EVERYBODY.
>> COME ON IN AND SEE ALL YOUR
STUFF.
>> HI.
>> I MISS HANGING OUT WITH YOU.
>> I KNOW.
I MISS A LOT.
>> WE WERE TOGETHER, LIKE,
ALL THE TIME.
YOU PRACTICALLY LIVED AT MY
HOUSE.
>> EVERY SINGLE WEEKEND.
>> NO, REALLY.
>> SO HOW'S SCHOOL GOING?
>> IT'S GOING GOOD.
YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO PROM.
I'M WEARING A PINK PROM DRESS.
>> OH, YOU'RE GONNA LOOK
SO PRETTY.
YEAH, ALL I DO NOW IS MOTHERLY
THINGS, LIKE THE LAUNDRY
AND CLEAN THE HOUSE AND--
HAD TO GROW UP, I GUESS, SO--
>> ALL RIGHT, PRESENT TIME.
>> OH, THE CLOTHES ARE MY
FAVORITE PART.
>> OH, THAT'S NICE.
>> LOOK.
THEY'RE VERY SUMMERY.
>> OH, I LIKE THE HAT.
>> CAN'T BELIEVE WE GOT
ALL THIS STUFF.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
WE DIDN'T HAVE, LIKE, ANYTHING.
>> IT MEANS A LOT.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> WE NEEDED IT.
>> I'M GLAD THAT WE FINALLY
HAVE SOME STUFF FOR EVIE.
DEREK EVEN SEEMS TO BE GETTING
SERIOUS ABOUT FINDING A JOB,
WHICH IS GREAT,
BECAUSE I'M SICK OF RELYING
ON HANDOUTS.
>> IS IT OKAY IF I USE YOU
AS A REFERENCE FOR JOB
APPLICATIONS?
>> UM, ON ONE CONDITION--
THAT YOU GET YOUR HAIR CUT.
YOU LOOK LIKE A DIRTY Q-TIP.
HERE'S THE MONEY FOR IT
RIGHT NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> MM-HMM, THANK YOU.
>> MUCH BETTER.
BUT BEFORE DEREK COULD GO IN
FOR AN INTERVIEW,
I STARTED FEELING SOMETHING
STRANGE.
DEREK!
>> BABY!
>> COME HERE.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I THINK I'M LEAKING.
>> LET ME SEE.
>> SEE?
>> EW, WHAT IS THAT?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE PEE,
BUT IT'S CLEAR.
AND IT KEEPS SOAKING MY
UNDERWEAR.
>> CALL MISS TRACY.
>> HERE WE GO.
>> WE'RE HAVING A BABY.
>> WHEN I ARRIVED AT THE
HOSPITAL,
MY DOCTOR CONFIRMED THAT I WAS
LEAKING AMNIOTIC FLUID,
SO HE DECIDED TO INDUCE ME
RIGHT AWAY.
LET ME TELL YOU,
THESE CONTRACTIONS ARE NOT FUN.
>> THINK YOU'RE BREATHING WRONG.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO BREATHE
THEN, GENIUS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LIKE THE...
[breathing rhythmically]
>> COME ON, DON'T DO--
[laughter]
>> NO, I DON'T WANT MY PARENTS
HERE.
OUCH.
THIS THING HURTS.
>> WHAT?
>> THE I.V.
IT HURTS.
STOP.
LIKE, YOU GOT TO THINK--
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DO, BECAUSE I GET PERIOD
CRAMPS.
THESE ARE JUST TEN TIMES WORSE.
THEY'RE GETTING WORSE.
LIKE, WAY WORSE.
AFTER NINE HOURS OF LABOR,
THE NURSE SAID IT WAS FINALLY
TIME TO START PUSHING.
[groaning]
>> PUSH, BABY, PUSH!
>> AND THE NEXT THING WE KNEW,
EVIE WAS HERE.
[baby crying]
>> WELCOME TO THE WORLD.
>> WE'RE BRINGING EVIE HOME
TODAY.
SEEING AS MY PARENTS AREN'T
AROUND, I'M GLAD I HAVE DEREK'S
HELP.
>> HI, BABY MUNCH.
HI.
>> IT'S GONNA BE WEIRD
WHEN WE GO HOME NOW,
'CAUSE WE HAVE HER NOW.
BEFORE IT WAS JUST ME AND YOU.
>> HI.
>> OH, LOOK AT YOU.
>> HI, HOW ARE YOU?
>> IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> YOU TOO.
>> OH, YOU'RE ADORABLE.
SHE LOOKS LIKE BOTH OF YOU.
>> YEAH, SHE REALLY DOES.
A BEAUTIFUL BABY.
>> OKAY, EVERYBODY SAY CHEESE.
>> HOW MANY PEOPLE DOES IT TAKE
TO CHANGE A DIAPER?
>> I KNOW, RIGHT.
>> IT TAKES A VILLAGE.
>> OH, THERE'S A BABY.
SO ARE YOU EXCITED TO BRING
LITTLE BABY HOME?
>> YEAH.
I'M READY FOR HER TO BE HOME.
WE'RE HERE.
>> THERE WE GO.
>> HI, PUMPKIN.
>> WELCOME HOME, PRINCESS.
>> IF I HAVE TO FEED HER
EVERY HOUR, I'M NOT GONNA BE
ABLE TO DO ANYTHING ELSE.
OH, WHOA.
OH, MY GOSH.
>> OH, [bleep] THAT.
>> EVEN THOUGH WE'RE STAYING
IN SOMEONE ELSE'S LIVING ROOM,
I'M GRATEFUL WE HAVE A ROOF
OVER OUR HEADS.
>> SHE'S SMILING.
>> DO YOU GUYS HAVE ANY LAUNDRY
IN THE WASH, BY ANY CHANCE?
>> WE DO.
>> CAN YOU GO CHANGE IT, PLEASE?
>> HI, PEANUT.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> SORRY.
[baby cries]
>> SHE'S HUNGRY.
>> WELL, GET THE BOTTLE.
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> DEREK, SHE SAID, "EXCUSE ME."
>> OH, CRAP.
I DIDN'T EVEN HEAR HER.
[clanking]
[baby crying]
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT THE
HECK WE'RE GONNA DO WITH HER.
SHE CAN'T SLEEP IN THE BED
WITH US.
[baby crying]
>> YOU'RE GOING IN THE CRIB
TONIGHT.
[baby crying]
>> CAN I HOLD HER NOW?
>> NO.
>> YES.
>> DEREK--
>> 'CAUSE THIS IS THE PROBLEM.
ANY TIME YOU HEAR HER MAKE
A PEEP, YOU WANT TO JUST SCOOP
HER UP.
NO, LET HER CRY.
[baby crying]
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I DON'T LIKE WHEN SHE CRIES.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
>> SHE--IT'S GOOD FOR HER
TO CRY.
IT'S OKAY FOR HER TO CRY.
[baby crying]
>> [blows raspberry]
I MEAN, SHE'S JUST GONNA KEEP
GETTING UP AND CRYING
BECAUSE SHE'S HUNGRY.
THAT'S NOT FAIR TO ME.
WHEN AM I EVER SUPPOSED TO SLEEP
IF I HAVE TO FEED HER EVERY
FREAKIN' 30 MINUTES.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE THAT WANTED
TO BREAST PUMP.
>> WE HAVE NO MONEY FOR FORMULA,
SO I HAD TO PUMP.
[baby crying]
SHE'S HUNGRY.
>> 'CAUSE SHE DOESN'T EAT.
>> YOU WANT TO KEEP FEEDING HER,
THEN KEEP FEEDING HER.
>> THIS IS EXTREMELY STRESSFUL.
[baby crying]
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HOLA.
WHAT'S UP?
>> I GOT SOME STUFF
AT THE STORE.
I GOT THE KOOL-AID THAT YOU LOVE
AND I GOT THESE FOR YOU...
>> OH, MY GOSH, THANK YOU.
>> SO YOU CAN STOP LEAKING
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I GOT SOME KIND OF BAD NEWS
TODAY.
THE LANDLORD SAID THAT
AT THE END OF MY LEASE
HE'S SELLING THE HOUSE.
SAYS HE'LL GIVE ME 30 DAYS
TO GET OUT.
>> DAMN.
>> I DON'T HAVE, LIKE,
A FAMILY TO FALL BACK ON
WHERE I CAN GO, OR--
>> YEAH.
>> I'M JUST, LIKE, FREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW 'CAUSE I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
WHEN I'M IN A BAD MOOD
AND I COME HOME AND SEE YOU
PLAYING A VIDEO GAME,
AND I'M LIKE, "UH, DID HE TRY
TO FIND A JOB TODAY?"
HAVE YOU HEARD ANYTHING?
>> NOT REALLY.
IT'S KIND OF DEPRESSING.
>> I KNOW YOU JUST HAD A BABY,
BUT I HAD THREE JOBS WHEN I HAD
MY FIRST KID.
I CAN IMAGINE AS A NEW PARENT
YOU'D WANT TO BE ABLE TO PROVIDE
FOR YOUR CHILD YOURSELF.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE
WE WOULD END UP.
>> * ONLY YESTERDAY
[cell phone chimes]
>> HI, DAD.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> NOTHING.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU THAT TRACY
TOLD US SHE'S GETTING KICKED OUT
BY HER LANDLORD, SO WE DON'T
REALLY HAVE ANYWHERE TO GO.
WE'RE BACK TO BEING HOMELESS.
>> 15 SECONDS OF PLEASURE,
AND IT GOT YOU NINE MONTHS
OF TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT--
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO NEXT.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY ADVICE
FOR US?
>> YEAH.
DON'T HAVE NO MORE KIDS.
STRAP IT UP.
COVER YOUR MAN.
PUT A HAT ON.
WHAT--WEAR A JIMMY.
I MEAN, HOW ELSE YOU WANT ME
TO SAY IT?
WHY DON'T Y'ALL JUST COME DOWN
TO TEXAS WITH ME?
>> HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO GET THERE?
WE DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
>> I'LL SEND YOU MONEY
TO CATCH A PLANE.
AND YOU CAN WORK WITH ME.
I'LL TEACH YOU HOW TO DO CABLE,
AND THEN YOU CAN MAKE SOME
MONEY.
BUT AT LEAST YOU'LL BE WORKING,
'CAUSE YOU GOT TO SUPPORT
YOU AND YOUR FAMILY.
>> YEAH.
>> I COULD EVEN GET JORDAN
A JOB.
SHE CAN BE A DISPATCHER
FOR MY JOB.
COME DOWN HERE,
AND WE'LL BE FINE.
WE'LL MAKE IT TOGETHER.
>> SO WE'D HAVE OUR OWN ROOM
FOR US AND THE BABY?
>> YEAH, IT'S A TWO-BEDROOM.
WHY WOULD YOU NOT WANT
TO DO THAT?
YOU GOT TO BE MORE
RESPONSIBLE, DEREK.
YOU GOT TO GET A BACKBONE,
JORDAN.
YOU GOT TO STOP WAITING
FOR HAND-ME-OUTS, DEREK.
I'MA HELP Y'ALL,
BUT Y'ALL GOT TO HELP Y'ALL SELF
TOO.
ALL RIGHT, LOVE Y'ALL.
>> BYE.
I NEED TO THINK THIS OVER.
I'M GONNA GO GET THE LAUNDRY
AND START FOLDING IT.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR DWAYNE'S OFFER,
BUT I'M NOT SURE IF I'M READY
FOR THIS MUCH CHANGE.
>> * AND DON'T BE AFRAID *
* TO SETTLE NOW
* SHE'S LOOKING FOR WAYS *
* TO TEACH YOU
* AND DON'T BELIEVE *
*IN MY DREAMS NOW *
[dog barks]
>> READY FOR OUR WALK?
>> YES
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M READY.
>> SO HOW'S MOTHERHOOD BEEN?
>> UM, IT'S INTERESTING.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT BUSY, BUT I ALWAYS FEEL
BUSY, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> JUST BECAUSE OF HER?
>> YEAH.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I ALWAYS HAVE
STUFF TO DO.
LAUNDRY AND DISHES
AND WASHING BOTTLES.
AND IT'S TIME CONSUMING NOW.
>> EVERY TIME I GO SOMEWHERE,
I'M LIKE, THIS SUCKS, 'CAUSE,
LIKE, JORDAN'S NOT WITH ME.
>> I KNOW.
I MISS BEING A TEENAGER.
I REALLY DO.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
ABOUT IT.
>> I WOULD TOO.
>> I WAS LOOKING AT, LIKE,
OLD PICTURES AND STUFF,
AND IT'S, LIKE, DEPRESSING.
I'M TERRIFIED OF GETTING
PREGNANT AGAIN.
>> YOU ARE?
>> LIKE, I'M TERRIFIED.
I DON'T WANT ANOTHER BABY.
SO I HAVE SOME NEWS,
AND I THINK THAT WE MIGHT BE
MOVING TO TEXAS.
SINCE MISS TRACY'S GONNA BE
GETTING KICKED OUT,
WE HAVE NOWHERE TO GO.
>> WOW.
THAT'S STUPID.
>> IT WASN'T MY FIRST CHOICE,
TO GO TO TEXAS.
BELIEVE ME.
BUT DEREK HAS A GUARANTEED JOB
WORKING FOR A CABLE COMPANY
WITH HIS DAD.
>> DEREK SHOULD'VE BEEN HERE
THIS NINE MONTHS SAVING UP
FOR WHEN THE BABY WAS BORN
TO BE ABLE TO LIVE WHERE YOU
WANT TO LIVE.
NOW YOU HAVE TO GO ALL THE WAY
TO A DIFFERENT STATE
AND YOU HAVE TO LIVE
OFF HIS DAD NOW.
LIKE, AREN'T YOU TIRED OF LIVING
OFF OF PEOPLE?
>> YEAH, BELIEVE ME, I AM.
I'M GONNA TRY TO MAKE THE BEST
OF IT FOR HER.
>> ARE YOU GONNA MENTION TO YOUR
PARENTS AT ALL THAT YOU'RE
MOVING TO TEXAS?
>> I--NO.
I'M JUST NOT READY TO REALLY
FORGIVE THEM.
>> IF YOU GO TO TEXAS...
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND YOU AND DEREK GET INTO
A FIGHT OR SOMETHING HAPPENS,
IF YOU NEED SOMEONE TO GO TO,
THERE'S NO ONE TO GO TO THERE.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU KNOW I'M ALWAYS HONEST
WITH YOU.
I'M NOT GONNA LIE TO YOU.
I LOVE YOU TO DEATH.
BUT YOU COULD'VE HAD EVERYTHING
FOR YOU HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> DEREK COULD'VE HAD THE MONEY.
YOU COULD'VE HAD
THE PICTURE-PERFECT FAMILY
YOU WANTED.
>> YEAH.
>> AND NOW YOU GOT TO BE
ALL MESSED UP.
AND HONESTLY,
I DON'T SEE HIM STEPPING UP.
I THINK YOU HAVE WAY TOO MUCH
FAITH IN HIM AT THIS POINT...
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN HE'S NOT PROVING
ANYTHING.
>> * I'M NOT SURE *
* THIS MAGIC'S GONNA WORK *
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> * OH, LOVE
*
* GET IN MY HEAD
>> PUT THAT TONGUE AWAY.
>> * SET THE WORLD ON FIRE
>> AFTER TALKING TO SUGAR,
I NEED TO KNOW WHETHER DEREK
IS REALLY GONNA BE THERE FOR US
IF WE MOVE TO TEXAS.
>> * COLOR ME RED
*SET THE WORLD ON FIRE *
>> SO I REALLY THINK THAT WE
NEED TO MAKE A DECISION ABOUT
IF WE'RE REALLY GONNA MOVE
TO TEXAS OR NOT.
>> WELL, DO YOU WANT TO GO?
>> I MEAN, IT'S NOT MY FIRST
CHOICE.
>> WELL, WHAT'S YOUR FIRST
CHOICE?
>> LIVING HERE IN AN APARTMENT.
>> THAT'S NOT A CHOICE AT ALL.
THAT'S NOT EVEN AN OPTION.
>> WELL, WE ONLY HAVE REALLY
ONE OPTION.
IT FEELS LIKE NOW WE'RE BACK
TO BOUNCING FROM HOUSE TO HOUSE.
>> THAT'S WHY WE SHOULD GO
TO TEXAS.
BECAUSE THERE'S A HOME
THAT WE WOULD BE STAYING AT.
YOU'LL HAVE YOU'RE OWN ROOM,
WHICH YOU KEEP SAYING YOU WANT.
IT'S DEFINITELY BETTER THAN
STAYING HERE.
>> YEAH, WHEN I WAS TALKING
TO SUGAR, SHE BROUGHT UP,
IF WE DON'T WORK OUT,
OR WHATEVER,
WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO.
>> THAT'S STUPID.
THAT'S 'CAUSE SHE'S NEGATIVE.
SHE LIKES TO THINK ABOUT
ALL OF THE NEGATIVE THINGS
THAT COULD POSSIBLY HAPPEN.
>> I MEAN, YOU HAVE SAID BEFORE
THAT YOU CAN JUST REALLY LEAVE
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
SO IF WE GO TO TEXAS,
HOW DO I KNOW YOU'RE NOT JUST
GONNA GO OUT OR DO STUFF
AND LEAVE?
>> AND MISS OUT ON THIS?
THERE'S NOTHING I'D RATHER
BE DOING.
>> IT JUST FEELS UNSTABLE.
>> EVERYWHERE WE GO IS UNSTABLE.
WHERE HAVE WE BEEN IN THE LAST--
WE HAVEN'T EVEN BEEN IN ONE
PLACE FOR MORE THAN THREE
MONTHS.
YOU JUST HAVE TO BE PATIENT.
IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN OVERNIGHT.
>> I KNOW.
I MEAN, I WANT A GOOD SITUATION
FOR HER TO GROW UP IN.
I DON'T WANT HER TO BE BOUNCING
BACK AND FORTH LIKE I HAD TO.
>> WE'LL JUST HAVE TO WORK
HARDER TO MAKE SURE THAT SHE
DOESN'T HAVE A--
HAVE TO GROW UP THE WAY WE DID.
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK THIS IS ONE BIG STEP
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOU WANT TO GO TO TEXAS?
SHE SAID YES.
>> I THINK IT'S OUR ONLY OPTION.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD GO.
[humming]
>> BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
I WAS REALLY FUN AND OUTGOING
AND I HAD A LOT OF FRIENDS,
WENT TO PARTIES
AND DID TEENAGE STUFF.
LITTLE PEANUT.
I DO NOT STILL FEEL LIKE
A TEENAGER.
I FEEL LIKE I'M TEN YEARS OLDER
THAN WHAT I AM.
I--IT'S JUST WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
>> * OH, SING
* SING MY SOUL
>> I HAD A HOME.
I HAD NICE THINGS.
I HAD A CAR.
I HAD EVERYTHING I WANTED.
AND THEN IT WAS JUST GONE.
THAT IS ONE OF THE WORST
SITUATIONS THAT I CAN IMAGINE.
>> I TOLD YOU SHE POOPED.
I'M NOT CHANGING IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I JUST PUT MY HAND IN POOP.
>> [laughs]
>> DEREK IS VERY CAREFREE,
AND THAT'S VERY FRUSTRATING
'CAUSE I NEED HIM TO STEP UP
TO THE PLATE AND TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY.
[baby cries]
I WORRY THAT HE IS NOT GONNA
PURSUE AN ACTUAL CAREER
AND IS NOT GONNA SAVE MONEY.
IT SCARES ME MORE NOW
BECAUSE GENEVIEVE IS ACTUALLY
HERE, SO SHE'S GONNA NEED
MORE THINGS, AND WE HAVE NO
MONEY TO GET HER THOSE THINGS.
>> WE GOT TO PUT OUR CLOTHES
IN HERE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY SUITCASES.
IT'S A LEAP OF FAITH TO JUST
PACK UP EVERYTHING AND MOVE
TO TEXAS WITH DEREK,
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW ANYONE ELSE
OTHER THAN HIM AND HIS DAD.
BYE, MARYLAND.
FOR US AND OUR FAMILY,
IT'S JUST BETTER FOR US TO GO.
SO I CAN'T REALLY THINK ABOUT
BEING SAD ABOUT LEAVING.
>> * OH, OH
* WHEN I COME BACK
* COME BACK
>> I DO NOT REGRET GENEVIEVE,
BUT I DO REGRET HAVING HER
AT SUCH A YOUNG AGE.
I REGRET BEING STUPID.
USE PROTECTION.
BIRTH CONTROL.
DO WHATEVER YOU CAN SO YOU DO
NOT GET PREGNANT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'LL KEEP IN TOUCH.
>> OKAY.
>> NOBODY THINKS THAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS GONNA
HAPPEN TO ME,
BUT THEN I WAS PREGNANT
WHILE BEING HOMELESS.
>> * OH, SING
* SING MY SOUL
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
THE FUTURE HOLDS FOR MYSELF
AND GENEVIEVE AND DEREK.
>> * OH, SING
*OH, SING MY SOUL *
* AS ALL THE YEARS FORETOLD
* TO HEAR
* THE RINGS THAT CHANGE
* AND, OH, SING
* OH, SING MY SOUL
>> SINCE YOU'RE NOT THE FATHER,
I DON'T THINK YOU GUYS WILL
LAST.
>> IT'S REALLY AWKWARD FOR ME
BEING PREGNANT WITH SOMEBODY
ELSE'S BABY.
I HATE SEX.
THAT'S JUST WHAT HAPPENS.
>> YOU AND MAUWI AIN'T NEVER
EVEN BEEN INTIMATE, RIGHT?
>> RIGHT.
I'M PUTTING ON A CHASTITY BELT.
>> THAT'S EXTREMELY FRUSTRATING,
'CAUSE NOBODY TOLD YOU
YOU WOULD POP UP PREGNANT.