>> OOH!
IT'S SO PRETTY.
[chime dings]
HI, I'M MYRANDA.
I'M 17, AND I LIVE IN
SAN AUGUSTINE, TEXAS.
I'M AN HONORS STUDENT IN
MY JUNIOR YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL
AND A SHORTSTOP ON THE
SOFTBALL TEAM.
I LOVE PLAYING SPORTS WITH
MY FRIENDS AND GOING TO PARTIES,
AND THAT'S HOW I MET MY
BOYFRIEND, ERIC.
YOU WERE BEING ALL SWEET.
HE HOPES TO PLAY PRO BASEBALL
ONE DAY.
MY PARENTS SPLIT UP
WHEN I WAS YOUNG, AND MY MOM
WASN'T AROUND MUCH WHILE I WAS
GROWING UP.
[chime dings]
SHE'S STILL DEALING WITH
SOME PERSONAL PROBLEMS,
SO SHE LET ME MOVE INTO ERIC'S
GRANDMOTHER'S HOUSE AFTER
WE'D BEEN DATING FOR SIX MONTHS.
I REALLY LIKE LIVING WITH HIM,
BUT BEING AROUND HIS GRANDMOTHER
CAN GET ON OUR NERVES.
>> Y'ALL GET UP OUT OF THAT BED.
YOU BETTER MAKE IT UP TOO.
>> I REALLY LOVE ERIC
AND HOPE WE'LL BE TOGETHER
FOREVER BECAUSE...
I'M PREGNANT.
ERIC AND I HAD ONLY BEEN
TOGETHER FOR THREE MONTHS BEFORE
I GOT PREGNANT, BUT WE'RE BOTH
COMMITTED TO OUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> MWAH!
>> EVEN THOUGH WE'RE NERVOUS
ABOUT BEING PARENTS, I THINK
WE'LL BE ABLE TO MANAGE
TOGETHER.
>> YOU REMEMBER HOW WE MET?
>> WELL, I REMEMBER
WE WERE IN THE POOL,
AND YOU WERE TRYING TO FLIRT
WITH ME, BUT THEN YOU, LIKE,
THREW ME.
>> AND YOU STARTED LIKING ME.
>> NO, YOU STARTED LIKING ME.
>> NO, IT WAS THE OTHER WAY
AROUND.
>> [giggles]
>> ARE YOU READY TO HAVE A BABY?
>> NO.
>> TAKE CARE OF IT?
>> I'M NOT READY AT ALL.
I'M ONLY 17.
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE READY TO BE
A DADDY?
>> OH, HELL NO.
[laughter]
I GET TIRED WATCHING
OTHER PEOPLE'S BABIES, SO...
>> YOU SEE OTHER PEOPLE WITH
BABIES, AND YOU'RE LIKE,
"OH, HOW CUTE."
AND THEN WHENEVER YOU HAVE YOUR
OWN, YOU'RE LIKE, "OH, CRAP."
[laughter]
WE RECENTLY FOUND OUT
WE'RE HAVING A GIRL AND ARE
NAMING HER KAYLEE.
WHEN MY MOM FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, SHE WAS REALLY UPSET.
SHE STRUGGLED WITH ADDICTION
IN THE PAST, SO WE WERE NEVER
REALLY CLOSE WHEN I WAS GROWING
UP, AND BEING PREGNANT ONLY
MAKES VISITING HER MORE AWKWARD.
I'M GONNA GO STAY THE NIGHT
WITH MOM.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS SO.
>> I THINK SHE'S BEEN OFF DRUGS,
BUT I DON'T THINK SHE STOPPED
DRINKING.
>> [sighs]
WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN TALK SOME
SENSE INTO HER WHEN YOU
GO DOWN THERE.
>> I'VE TRIED TALKING SENSE
INTO HER SINCE I WAS 12.
>> WELL, MAYBE NOW THAT YOU'RE
PREGNANT, SHE'LL LISTEN.
>> I DOUBT IT.
IF SHE EVER DOES IT AGAIN,
SHE'S NOT GONNA BABYSIT
OR ANYTHING.
I CAN'T HAVE MY CHILD
AROUND SOMEBODY WHO DOES
STUFF LIKE THAT.
MY MOM SAYS SHE'S BEEN SOBER
FOR SEVERAL MONTHS NOW,
EVER SINCE HER LAST TIME
IN REHAB, BUT WE HAVEN'T REALLY
DISCUSSED MY PREGNANCY YET.
>> MY FIRST THOUGHTS WERE,
"OH, MY GOD, THAT'S IT."
LIFE'S OVER.
I MEAN, I'M SORRY.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT
YOUR FEELINGS.
I JUST...
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO BE
PREGNANT.
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND IS,
WHY WEREN'T YOU TAKING THE PILL?
>> I WAS OFF FOR, LIKE, A MONTH.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK?
YOU WEREN'T GONNA GET PREGNANT?
>> YEAH.
>> [scoffs]
WE HAVEN'T EVEN DISCUSSED
THE FACT ON--ARE WE GONNA
DROP OUT OF SCHOOL
AND GO GET A G.E.D.?
>> I'M GONNA GET MY G.E.D.
>> [sighs] MYRANDA...
SOMETIMES I WONDER IF IT'S
MY FAULT, BECAUSE I SHOULD
HAVE BEEN A BETTER PARENT.
AS A MOTHER, YOU FEEL LIKE
IT'S...
YOU FEEL LIKE IT'S YOUR FAULT,
THAT YOU COULD HAVE DONE MORE.
I THINK I JUST KNOW HOW HARD
IT'S GONNA BE FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S NO WAY YOU'RE
GONNA BE ABLE TO GET OUT AND
GET A PLACE AND--WITH YOU
AND THE BABY AND ERIC.
NO JOBS.
EVERYTHING'S DIFFERENT NOW.
EVERYTHING HAS CHANGED.
NOTHING IS--NOTHING IS HOW
IT USED TO BE.
[sighs]
>> MY MOM ISN'T MAKING THINGS
EASIER, AND FINANCES ARE GONNA
BE TIGHT, SO I'M GLAD WE CAN
STAY AT ERIC'S GRANDMOTHER'S
HOUSE.
SHE'S RAISED ERIC SINCE HE WAS
YOUNG AND HAS BEEN LETTING US
LIVE HERE FOR FREE.
I'M HOPING SHE'LL KEEP HELPING
US OUT WHEN THE BABY COMES,
BECAUSE ERIC IS ONLY WORKING
PART-TIME THIS SUMMER
AND STARTS HIS COLLEGE CLASSES
IN THE FALL.
>> HOW DID YOU GET HER PREGNANT,
MAN?
>> I DIDN'T WEAR A CONDOM.
I WAS THINKING WITH MY PENIS.
I DIDN'T CARE.
>> YOU READY FOR THIS BABY
TO COME AND EVERYTHING?
>> YEP.
>> WHERE YOU GETTING ALL YOUR
MONEY FROM AND EVERYTHING
FOR, LIKE--
>> MY JOB.
I GOT $700 SAVED UP RIGHT NOW,
AND AS LONG AS I SAVE UP
EVERY WEEK AFTER I--
ON MY JOB, I SHOULD HAVE PLENTY.
>> I FEEL WORTHLESS, 'CAUSE
IT'S, LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I CAN'T
DO NOTHING, EXCEPT FOR LAUNDRY,
AND THEN MY STOMACH'S
IN THE WAY, SO IT'S LIKE--
I CAN'T GET THEM.
I FEEL WORTHLESS.
IT'S HARD.
>> I CAN SEE YOU HAVING A KID.
I CAN'T SEE ERIC.
>> THREE!
[laughter]
>> LIKE, RAISING--
>> LIKE, AS A DAD.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I CAN SEE HIM GOING IN
THE ROOM--"MYRANDA!
GET YOUR KID!"
>> [laughs]
I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT WAS THE SCARIEST THING
WHEN YOU FOUND OUT YOU WERE
PREGNANT?
>> SCARIEST THING WAS TELLING
MY MOM, AND THEN WHENEVER
WE HAD TO TELL NANNY,
THAT WAS PRETTY SCARY.
>> I FIGURED THAT'S WHAT
YOU'D SAY FIRST.
>> MY HEART WAS RACING.
[sighs]
EVER SINCE ERIC'S GRANDMOTHER
FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT,
SHE HASN'T BEEN GIVING US
MUCH PRIVACY.
>> WHAT ARE Y'ALL DOING?
>> GET OUT.
>> I HOPE THAT'S ALL Y'ALL ARE
DOING, IS WATCHING TV,
BUT I GUESS IT'S A LITTLE BIT
TOO LATE ANYWAY.
>> AND SINCE ERIC WOULD RATHER
PLAY VIDEO GAMES THAN HELP OUT
AROUND THE HOUSE...
>> YOU AIN'T GONNA WASH
THAT DISH.
YOU DIDN'T WASH IT.
>> I JUST WASHED IT.
>> YOU JUST RINSED IT OUT.
>> THERE'S A DISHWASHER.
>> NANNY IS ALWAYS ON OUR CASE.
>> WE NEED TO TALK.
WHEN I FIRST FOUND OUT THAT
YOU GUYS WERE PREGNANT...
[sighs]
I WAS SICK.
I FELT LIKE I WAS GONNA
THROW UP.
IF Y'ALL HADN'T HAVE BEEN
SO DUMB AND STUPID AND WOULD
HAVE USED SOME BIRTH CONTROL--
ERIC!
LIKE...
>> WHY AM I SUPPOSED TO BE
THE ONE WITH BIRTH CONTROL?
>> DID I NOT TELL YOU, "ERIC,
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE CONDOMS"?
IT DON'T MATTER IF SHE'S ON
BIRTH CONTROL.
AND MYRANDA, SHE QUIT TAKING
THE STUPID THINGS.
>> I RAN OUT.
AND I MISSED A DAY.
THEN I MISSED SOME MORE DAYS.
>> Y'ALL GOING, "BLAH,
BLAH, BLAH."
IT'S YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
YOU TEND TO IT.
>> WELL, WE DIDN'T THINK
IT'D HAPPEN.
>> [scoffs]
THAT'S--MM.
BOTH OF Y'ALL, MORE OR LESS,
JUST RUINED EACH OTHER'S LIVES.
>> YOU'RE ANNOYING, YOU KNOW...
>> I'M ANNOYING.
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS NAGGING AT ME
FOR DUMB THINGS.
>> YOU HAVE NO IDEA, NO IDEA,
NONE.
>> SEE, THAT'S WHY YOU MAKE ME
MAD SOMETIMES.
YOU SAY YOU KNOW EVERYTHING.
>> I KNOW A HECK OF A LOT MORE
THAN YOU KNOW.
OH, Y'ALL THINK Y'ALL KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING,
AND Y'ALL DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
WHERE YOU GONNA LIVE?
>> WE'LL COME HERE TO--
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
IT'S NOT GRANDMA DAY CARE.
I DONE BEEN THERE, DONE THAT.
NO MORE.
BABIES HAVING BABIES.
MM.
[chime dings]
>> I REALLY THOUGHT WE WERE
GOING TO BE ABLE TO LIVE HERE
ONCE THE BABY COMES...
[door slams]
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE I WAS WRONG.
>> IT REALLY SUCKS THAT
ERIC'S GRANDMOTHER ISN'T GOING
TO LET US LIVE HERE,
'CAUSE THE BABY IS DUE IN JUST
TWO MONTHS.
I'D RATHER JUST MOVE SOMEWHERE,
IF WE COULD.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW
IF WE COULD AFFORD AN APARTMENT,
UNLESS WE HAD ROOMMATES.
>> I DON'T WANT ROOMMATES.
>> EXACTLY.
SO WE COULDN'T AFFORD
AN APARTMENT.
>> WHAT ABOUT...
>> HOW MUCH WOULD THE RENT BE?
>> WELL, SHE ACTUALLY SAID
WE WOULDN'T HAVE TO PAY RENT.
WE'D ONLY HAVE TO PAY
THE ELECTRICITY BILL.
>> IT'S A BIG STEP,
LIVING ON OUR OWN WITH A BABY.
WE'LL HAVE TO LEARN A WHOLE LOT
THAT WE'RE NOT EVEN READY FOR.
>> I THINK IT'S OUR BEST BET.
>> THE HOUSE WAS VERY CLOSE
TO ERIC'S GRANDMOTHER'S PLACE,
AND WE'RE GONNA CHECK IT OUT
THIS WEEK.
>> AH, I DON'T EVEN LIKE
THE BOOKSTORE.
>> SUMMER IS NEARLY OVER,
AND TODAY WHILE MY FRIENDS ARE
GETTING READY FOR SENIOR YEAR,
I HAVE TO START STUDYING
FOR MY G.E.D.
ERIC IS GONNA TAKE PART-TIME
CLASSES AT A LOCAL COMMUNITY
COLLEGE, SO HE'LL BE AROUND
TO HELP ME GET READY.
I'M GONNA SIT RIGHT HERE.
>> WANT ME TO ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS?
WHAT'S TWO PLUS TWO?
>> THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
ON A G.E.D.
>> WELL, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
SKIPPING YOUR LAST YEAR OF
HIGH SCHOOL?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET TO PLAY
SOFTBALL.
>> I COULD.
>> OH, YEAH?
HOW?
>> JUST NOT IN THE SCHOOL.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA DO THAT
WITH THE BABY?
GO TO PRACTICE EVERY DAY?
YOU STILL GOT TO GO TO PRACTICE.
>> THERE'S NOT PRACTICE.
>> JUST 'CAUSE IT'S NOT IN
SCHOOL DON'T MEAN YOU WON'T
HAVE PRACTICE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT YOUR
PLAN IS FOR SCHOOL, COLLEGE,
NOTHING.
>> I KNOW.
BUT A YEAR AND A HALF,
SHE'LL BE ABLE TO, YOU KNOW,
MOVE AROUND MORE, AND SHE WON'T
BE AS, YOU KNOW, HARD TO TAKE
CARE OF.
>> YEAH, BUT I'M GONNA BE DOING
ONLINE CLASSES FOR PROBABLY
THE FIRST TWO SEMESTERS.
>> I'M REALLY STARTING TO WORRY
ABOUT BEING ABLE TO FOCUS
ON SCHOOL WHILE I'M TAKING CARE
OF A BABY.
AND BECAUSE MY MOM HASN'T GIVEN
THE BEST ADVICE IN THE PAST,
ERIC'S AUNT TAMMY AGREED
TO TALK TO ME.
I MEAN, THERE'S, LIKE, SO MANY
THINGS I PROBABLY NEED,
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW ABOUT IT.
>> THERE'S A TON OF STUFF
YOU NEED FOR A BABY.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> [laughs]
EVERYTHING.
>> LIKE, WHAT ARE THE MAIN
THINGS, THOUGH?
>> DIAPERS AND WIPES
AND MEDICINE--IN CASE
THEY HAVE DIAPER RASH--
LITTLE NOSE SUCKERS
FOR THEIR LITTLE BOOGERS.
>> EW.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND SO NASTY.
I'VE JUST BEEN THINKING ABOUT
A LOT OF THINGS.
LIKE, A LOT OF THINGS ARE ON
MY MIND RIGHT NOW--
MY MOM AND THEN WHENEVER
ERIC STARTS SCHOOL.
>> THEN YOU'RE GONNA BE
BY YOURSELF.
THAT'S PROBABLY THE MAIN THING,
RIGHT?
>> IT IS.
I'M JUST GONNA BE
A LONELY WOMAN.
>> WELL...
>> I'M HOPING IT WON'T BE
TOO BAD, SINCE THE HOUSE WE
MIGHT MOVE INTO IS RIGHT AT
THE EDGE OF ERIC'S GRANDMOTHER'S
PROPERTY.
WE JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE
IT'S READY FOR A BABY.
[rattling]
>> OH, THERE.
>> [groans]
>> IT USED TO BE NICE.
>> EW!
GROSS.
THAT'S NASTY.
>> WE MIGHT GET A NEW STOVE.
>> WE GOT TO GET A REFRIGERATOR.
[sighs]
>> WE GOT TO GET
AN AIR CONDITIONER TOO.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S NASTY.
>> WHERE'S THE BABY GONNA GO?
>> [sighs]
I DON'T KNOW.
EW.
>> YOU KNOW Y'ALL GOT
A LOT OF WORK TO DO HERE.
>> YOU LIKE OUR NEW HOUSE?
[chuckles]
>> WELL, NOT RIGHT NOW.
IT'S A LOT OF WORK THAT'S GOT
TO BE DONE ON THIS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU CAN'T DEPEND ON SOMEBODY
TO COME IN HERE AND DO IT
FOR YOU.
>> IT'S JUST NASTY.
>> Y'ALL GOT A LOT OF WORK TO
DO, AND YOU AIN'T GOT VERY LONG
TO DO IT.
YOU BETTER GROW UP FAST,
BOTH OF YOU.
[sighs]
>> [sighs]
[chime dings]
>> MY DUE DATE IS SIX WEEKS
AWAY, SO ERIC AND I ASKED SOME
FAMILY AND FRIENDS TO HELP US
GET THIS HOUSE READY AS FAST
AS WE CAN.
[thud]
[clattering]
>> EW.
>> READY?
>> YEP.
>> [grunts]
ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> SINCE WE HAVE LITTLE SAVINGS
AND ERIC ONLY MAKES $150 A WEEK,
SOME OF HIS RELATIVES ARE
PITCHING IN SOME MONEY
TO HELP US GET NEW APPLIANCES.
>> THERE ARE, LIKE,
A MILLION BEES UP HERE.
>> WE GOT A LOT DONE,
BUT THIS HOUSE IS STILL
A LONG WAY FROM BEING FINISHED.
PLUS, WE STILL NEED TO PICK UP
SOME LAST-MINUTE BABY SUPPLIES.
[line ringing]
SINCE FINDING OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, MY MOM SAID SHE WAS
GONNA BE AROUND A LOT MORE
THAN IN THE PAST.
SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO COME VISIT
AND TAKE US TO MY ULTRASOUND
APPOINTMENT AND THE BABY STORE,
BUT I'VE TRIED CALLING HER
EVERY DAY THIS WEEK AND STILL
CAN'T SEEM TO REACH HER.
>> YOUR CALL HAS BEEN FORWARDED
TO AN AUTOMATIC VOICE MESSAGE
SYSTEM.
>> SO ERIC'S GRANDMOTHER DECIDED
TO TAKE US SHOPPING FOR THE BABY
INSTEAD.
>> SUCH A GENTLEMAN.
>> OKAY, THIS IS OUR STROLLER
ROOM.
THIS STROLLER RIGHT HERE
COMES IN TONS OF DIFFERENT
COLORS, AND IT'S $679.
>> SIX?
>> WOW.
>> $679.
>> DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU NEEDED
AN INFANT SEAT?
>> THOSE ARE JUST FOR INFANTS,
AND THOSE RUN AROUND $180.
>> BABY STUFF IS EXPENSIVE
NOWADAYS.
>> I KNOW. IT IS.
>> MM.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT IS.
>> I'M GONNA KEEP LOOKING
AROUND.
WHERE'S ERIC?
ERIC?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> [laughs]
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> REALLY?
WE DIDN'T GET HERE TO SLEEP.
GET UP, LAZY.
>> I'LL GET UP WHEN I HAVE TO
GET UP.
>> GET UP, ERIC.
COME ON.
YOU GOT TO LOOK TOO.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> TODAY I'M GETTING OUT
OF THE HOUSE TO SPEND SOME TIME
WITH MY FRIENDS WHILE
I STILL CAN.
MY BEST FRIEND, KRISTIAN,
IS TAKING ME AND SOME OF THE
OTHER GIRLS ON THE SOFTBALL TEAM
TO THE BATTING CAGES.
>> HI.
>> HEY.
[bat strikes]
>> OW!
>> THERE WE GO.
[thump]
>> DOES THIS MAKE YOU MISS
SOFTBALL?
>> A LITTLE BIT, YEAH.
>> OH!
[laughter]
>> PLEASE, BE CAREFUL.
>> BE CAREFUL, PLEASE.
[laughter]
SHE'S MAKING ME NERVOUS.
>> OH, IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
IT'S JUST A BALL.
>> YOUR BELLY MIGHT GET
IN THE WAY.
IT'S FRICKIN' HUGE.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO, LIKE,
SCOOT BACK SUPER FAR
AND LEAN SUPER FAR.
>> DON'T GET THAT CLOSE!
[bat strikes]
>> PLEASE, DON'T FALL.
[machine fires]
[fence rattles]
>> OH!
>> I WASN'T READY.
WHOO!
>> THAT'S NOT HURTING YOU
OR ANYTHING?
>> IT'S STARTING TO HURT MY SIDE
A LITTLE BIT.
[laughs]
>> JUST BE CAREFUL.
>> [grunts]
OW.
>> I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO STOP.
>> WHAT?
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
>> YOU'RE SCARING US.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE SCARING ME.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YOU GO SIT DOWN.
>> YEAH, YOU GO SIT DOWN.
>> [sighs]
WHEW.
IT WAS GREAT TO HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS,
BUT THE NEXT DAY, I GOT
SOME TROUBLING NEWS.
[chime dings]
MY MOM HAD STARTED DRINKING
AGAIN.
SHE GOT INTO A HUGE FIGHT
WITH HER HUSBAND, WADE,
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND SPED OFF IN HIS CAR.
>> YEAH, THEY FOUND HER.
THEY TOOK HER TO A HOSPITAL.
AND THAT HOSPITAL SAID THEY'RE
GONNA SEND HER TO SOME REHAB.
AND I KNEW SHE WAS GONNA RUN OFF
AND DO DRUGS, LIKE SHE DID,
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
SHE'S DONE IT...
>> COUNTLESS TIMES.
>> MULTIPLE TIMES.
SHE ONLY THINKS ABOUT HERSELF
AND DOESN'T CARE ABOUT ME
OR HER GRANDCHILD OR ANYTHING.
>> WHEN SHE GETS DONE WITH
REHAB, SHE'S GONNA TRY
TO COME BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> I GUESS JUST, THIS TIME,
I CAN'T BE AS SOFTHEARTED
LIKE I USUALLY AM,
AND TELL HER...
SHE CAN'T BE AROUND THE BABY.
I DON'T WANT MY BABY TO BE
AROUND SOMEBODY LIKE THAT.
>> ME NEITHER.
>> YEAH.
[chime dings]
>> I'M PRETTY DISAPPOINTED THAT
MY MOM IS BACK IN REHAB,
BUT I CAN'T REALLY SAY
I'M SURPRISED.
>> SO WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO IS GET
A COUPLE OF PICTURES HERE.
>> AREN'T YOU EXCITED, ERIC?
>> YEAH.
I GUESS SO.
[heartbeat pulsing]
>> THERE'S THE BABY'S HEARTBEAT.
SEE, THAT'S AN ELBOW.
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT.
>> HAND IS UP HERE.
>> AW.
>> THERE'S THIS EYE.
YEAH, SEE HER LITTLE FINGERS?
>> WHO DO YOU THINK SHE LOOKS
LIKE, NANNY?
>> SHE GOT YOUR MOUTH.
GOT A BIG MOUTH.
[laughter]
>> THERE, THERE'S HER TONGUE.
>> OH!
>> OH, LOOK AT THAT.
>> AW, HOW CUTE.
>> SHE'S LAZY IN THERE.
>> HEY, SHE TAKES AFTER YOU,
ERIC.
>> YEAH.
>> DOES IT FEEL MORE REAL TO
Y'ALL, NOW THAT YOU ACTUALLY
SEE HER MOVING AND HER FACE?
>> THE CLOSER AND CLOSER IT GETS
TO THE POINT WHERE SHE'S
ACTUALLY COMING, IT'S, LIKE,
MORE AND MORE YOU REALIZE.
>> UH-HUH.
MAKE YOU REALIZE IT IS REAL.
DO YOU WISH YOUR MOM
WAS HERE, MYRANDA?
>> NO.
[chuckles]
NO, I DON'T GIVE A RAT'S BUTT
ABOUT MY MOM ANYMORE.
[pins clattering]
I'D RATHER HANG WITH MY FRIENDS
THAN WORRY ABOUT MY MOM.
>> WHATEVER.
[laughter]
>> IT'S THE SAME.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> IT IS.
>> HAVE TO CARRY HER--
CARRY HER AROUND IN A LITTLE
CAR SEAT, BRING HER EVERYWHERE
YOU GO.
>> YEAH.
>> AH!
MY FEET HURT.
THEY'RE SWOLLEN.
>> WELL, THEY'RE GONNA BE
SWOLLEN WORSE THAN THAT.
Y'ALL GOT A LOT TO DO,
DON'T YOU?
I'M SORRY, BUT I HATE IT.
>> YEAH, WELL, GOOD THING
YOU'RE NOT LIVING HERE, HUH?
>> THIS IS GONNA BE Y'ALL'S
HOUSE.
YOU SHOULD BE EXCITED
TO GET IT DONE.
Y'ALL WASN'T LISTENING
TO ANYTHING I SAID.
>> WE GOT TO GET THIS HOUSE DONE
BEFORE THE BABY GETS HERE.
>> AND GET IN HERE.
>> SO I WON'T HAVE TO LISTEN
TO THE BABY CRY ALL NIGHT.
THERE'S A LOT OF WORK THAT'S GOT
TO BE DONE.
AND TIME'S A-TICKIN'.
>> TODAY IS MY BABY SHOWER.
MY MOM GOT OUT OF REHAB
LAST NIGHT, AND EVEN THOUGH
I'M NOT READY TO SEE HER,
MY AUNT TAMMY INVITED HER
ANYWAY, SO IT'S KIND OF
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> OH!
>> OH, THAT'S--
>> GOD!
>> I WANT HER TO MOVE
SO I CAN FEEL IT.
I HAVEN'T FELT IT YET.
OH!
>> SEE?
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> HURRY UP, MYRANDA.
YOU GOT A BUNCH OF PRESENTS
TO OPEN.
>> NANNY!
>> I'M GONNA GET TIRED
STANDING UP HERE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
HAVE A BABY CAT.
>> HOW HAVE YOU BEEN FEELING?
YOU HURTING ANY?
>> EVERY NOW AND THEN,
SHE PUSHES DOWN ON ME.
>> SO PRESSURE?
YOU'RE HAVING A LOT OF PRESSURE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> MYRANDA, IT'S NO...
UM, SECRET THAT I HAVE
A PROBLEM, AND I HAVE STRUGGLED
MY WHOLE LIFE WITH ALCOHOLISM
AND A DRUG ADDICTION.
BUT I'VE JOINED AN INTENSIVE
OUTPATIENT PROGRAM WHERE I GO
THREE DAYS A WEEK, AND I'LL STAY
WITH THAT PROGRAM FOR AS LONG
AS THEY TELL ME I NEED TO STAY
WITH IT, WHICH WILL PROBABLY BE
AT LEAST A YEAR, IF NOT MORE,
SO...
BUT I HAVE A LOT OF ISSUES
AND A LOT OF PROBLEMS THAT
I HAVE TO DEAL WITH,
AND I'VE NEVER WANTED TO FACE
THEM OR DEAL WITH THEM,
BUT IT'S TIME THAT I DO.
SO THAT'S WHERE I'M AT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A MAJOR THING,
SO YOU CAN SPEND AS MUCH TIME
WITH YOUR GRANDBABY AS YOU CAN.
>> YES.
>> JUST, HOPEFULLY, YOU DON'T
HAVE, LIKE, ONE OF THOSE MOMENTS
AGAIN, WHERE YOU LEAVE WHILE
YOU'RE TRYING TO WORK ON IT,
LIKE BEFORE.
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT...
I AM 100% COMMITTED, SO THAT
I CAN SEE MY GRANDBABY BEING
BORN, OKAY?
I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA LET ME IN
THE DELIVERY ROOM WHEN YOU'RE
HAVING THE BABY, RIGHT?
>> I GUESS.
>> ME AND ERIC AND YOU.
I THINK THAT'S THE BEST THREE
THAT SHOULD BE IN THERE.
>> I APPRECIATE MY MOM'S
APOLOGY, BUT SINCE I'VE HEARD IT
ALL BEFORE, I'M NOT SURE
THIS TIME WILL BE DIFFERENT.
>> YOU THINK ERIC'S GONNA HANDLE
THE DELIVERY ROOM OKAY?
>> UH...
[laughter]
I HAVE NO IDEA HOW HE'S GONNA
REACT.
THE DOCTOR SAID, "YOU CAN ONLY
HAVE TWO PEOPLE IN THE LABOR
ROOM."
SO I FIGURED YOU AND ERIC
COULD BE THE ONES.
YOU WANT TO BE IN THE LABOR ROOM
WITH ME?
>> YEAH, I WILL.
SO YOU DECIDED NOT TO HAVE
YOUR MOM IN THERE?
>> YEAH, I HAVEN'T TOLD HER YET,
THOUGH.
>> UH-OH.
>> WELL, SEE, I FIGURED--
BOYFRIEND AND MY BEST FRIEND.
>> AUNT KRISTIAN.
>> [laughs]
>> SHE'S PROBABLY NOT GONNA
TAKE THAT VERY WELL.
SHE WANTED TO BE IN THERE BAD.
>> IT'S NOT HER BABY ANYWAY.
>> HER BABY IS HAVING THE BABY,
THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
BUT SINCE I CAN ONLY HAVE TWO,
SHE'LL JUST HAVE TO GET OVER
THAT.
[chime dings]
IT'S GONNA BE HARD TO TELL MY
MOM, BUT I THINK NOT HAVING HER
AT THE HOSPITAL IS WHAT'S BEST.
>> I HAVEN'T DECIDED WHEN
I'M GOING TO TELL MY MOM I DON'T
WANT HER IN THE DELIVERY ROOM,
AND I'M TRYING TO STAY FOCUSED
ON GETTING MY G.E.D., ESPECIALLY
NOW THAT MY FRIENDS ARE BACK
IN SCHOOL, AND ERIC IS STARTING
HIS COMMUNITY COLLEGE CLASSES.
>> ARE YOU HAPPY THAT ERIC'S
GOING TO COLLEGE, OR DOES IT--
>> YEAH, I'M REAL HAPPY.
I THINK THAT'S A GOOD THING,
'CAUSE HE'S TRYING TO SUPPORT ME
AND WHEN SHE COMES AND...
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE HE MAKES A LOT
OF MONEY A MONTH, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> MAYBE, LIKE, $150 A WEEK.
>> YOU GET LONELY BEING...
>> YEAH, I GET REAL LONELY.
>> DO YOU MISS SCHOOL OR...
>> YEAH, I'M GETTING, LIKE,
REAL TIRED OF NOT BEING ABLE
TO SEE MY FRIENDS.
IF I COULD, I WOULD GO BACK
TO SCHOOL.
I JUST...
LIKE, I'M ALWAYS FEELING SO
SICK AND NAUSEOUS ALL THE TIME.
IF I COULD TAKE ALL OF THIS
BACK, I WOULD.
BUT I CAN'T TAKE IT BACK.
MY DUE DATE IS ONLY TWO WEEKS
AWAY, SO I ASKED ERIC'S FAMILY
TO HELP US PUT THE FINISHING
TOUCHES ON OUR NEW HOUSE.
TODAY, WE CAN FINALLY MOVE IN,
BUT I'M SO PREGNANT, I CAN'T
REALLY HELP MUCH.
SO I'M GLAD KRISTIAN AND MY
FRIENDS SHOWED UP.
>> ONE MORE TRIP.
>> THIS IS NOT FUN AT ALL.
>> CAN Y'ALL, LIKE, GO
A LITTLE FASTER, ESPECIALLY
THIS ONE?
>> OH, I GOT TO GET MY XBOX.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING.
>> THAT STUPID XBOX.
>> I THINK I'LL JUST
PUT IT IN HERE.
[grunts]
>> OH, IS THAT YOUR BABY?
>> NO, IT'S JUST EASIER
TO CARRY.
>> DON'T DROP HER.
>> MM-HMM.
[rain pattering]
>> RUN!
>> MY DUE DATE IS NEXT WEEK,
AND I STILL HAVEN'T TOLD MY MOM
ABOUT MY DECISION NOT TO HAVE
HER IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
SO I INVITED HER OVER
'CAUSE I REALLY CAN'T WAIT
MUCH LONGER.
>> MM.
I MEAN, I TOLD HER I HAD
TO TALK TO HER ABOUT SOMETHING,
BUT I NEVER TOLD HER WHAT.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT
TELLING HER?
>> NERVOUS.
KIND OF SCARED OF HER REACTION.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT ANYBODY.
>> IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
[gravel crunching]
I THINK I HEAR SOMEBODY
PULLING UP.
>> HOW'S MY BABY DOING?
>> SHE'S DOING GOOD.
>> BOTH MY BABIES.
[laughs]
>> HEY.
>> HI, HONEY.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
LOVE YOU.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
HEY, THERE, PRETTY.
>> [laughs]
>> [sighs]
YOU KNOW HOW I WENT TO THE
DOCTOR THE OTHER WEEK?
>> MM-HMM.
>> SHE SAID, "YOU CAN ONLY HAVE
TWO PEOPLE IN THE LABOR ROOM."
>> SO THAT'S GONNA BE ERIC
AND YOUR MOM.
>> NO.
>> WHAT?
>> IT'S GONNA BE ERIC
AND KRISTIAN.
>> KRISTIAN?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY?
>> I DON'T WANT CONFLICT.
>> YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S GONNA BE CONFLICT?
>> YES, I DO.
>> YOU DON'T WANT ME
IN THE ROOM.
JUST BE HONEST.
DOES ANYTHING THAT I'VE DONE
IN MY PAST HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE DECISION YOU MADE
TO HAVE HER IN THE ROOM
INSTEAD OF ME IN THE ROOM?
>> YOU KNOW, WHENEVER YOU MISSED
MY 3-D ULTRASOUND,
I KIND OF DID HAVE THAT FEELING
INSIDE ME THAT I DIDN'T WANT
YOU TO BE THERE, BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, I COULDN'T RELY ON YOU
TO BE THERE.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE THERE.
YOU WEREN'T.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
>> AND I WAS JUST REAL UPSET
AND MAD AT THAT POINT.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, WHEN THE BABY COMES...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT JUST BRINGS UP PAST MEMORIES.
>> I'M JUST SORRY THAT I EVER
PUT YOU IN THE POSITION
TO BE IN THE POSITION
THAT YOU'RE IN.
I PUT YOU IN THAT POSITION
THAT YOU HAD TO MAKE
THAT KIND OF DECISION.
[sniffles]
WE'RE GONNA GET BETTER.
THINGS ARE GONNA GET BETTER.
[sniffles]
DON'T CRY.
>> [sobs]
>> TELLING MY MOM WAS EVEN
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD
BE, BUT I'M GLAD I DID IT,
'CAUSE TWO DAYS LATER, I WOKE UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
IN REALLY BAD PAIN.
SO ERIC DROVE ME TO THE
HOSPITAL, AND I TEXTED KRISTIAN
TO MEET US THERE.
>> YOU NEED TO GET SOME SLEEP.
[monitor pulsing]
>> ERIC, ONCE THEY BREAK
HER WATER, THE BABY'S HEAD
IS BASICALLY...
>> THIS IS SO WEIRD.
I FEEL LIKE I'M PEEING MYSELF.
>> MY CONTRACTIONS WERE GETTING
REALLY INTENSE, SO I ASKED
THE DOCTOR FOR AN EPIDURAL.
[vomiting]
>> IT'S A GOOD THING.
>> [groans]
>> I'M JUST CHECKING FOR
A CONTRACTION.
>> AFTER WHAT SEEMED LIKE
AN ETERNITY, IT WAS FINALLY
TIME TO PUSH.
>> PUSH.
PUSH, PUSH...
>> COME ON, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> THERE WE GO.
HARDER, HARDER, HARDER.
THAT'S IT.
>> [groans]
>> THERE YOU GO.
GOOD JOB.
AND AGAIN.
PUSH.
TWO, THREE, FOUR.
>> SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
BLOW OUT.
OKAY.
>> KEEP GOING, MYRANDA.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE A MOM.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> [groans]
[baby cries]
>> THERE WE GO!
TELL MAMA ALL ABOUT IT.
[baby crying]
YEAH, THERE'S MAMA.
>> SO SWEET.
>> THERE'S YOUR MAMA.
>> YOUR MAMA.
>> OKAY.
LET ME GET HER OVER HERE
AND GET HER CLEANED UP.
[baby cries]
>> OH!
>>  'CAUSE ALL THAT YOU ARE
IS ALL I NEED
'CAUSE ALL THAT YOU ARE
>>  YEAH, ALL THAT YOU ARE
IS ALL I NEED
>> female announcer: GET ANSWERS
TO YOUR SEX AND RELATIONSHIP
QUESTIONS AND TIPS ON HOW TO
TAKE CONTROL AT:
>> AFTER SPENDING TWO DAYS
IN THE HOSPITAL, IT WAS TIME
TO BRING KAYLEE HOME.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET YOU INSIDE.
[Kaylee fusses]
>> I GOT YOU.
>> HEY.
>> HEY, I WANT TO COME
AND SEE THE BABY.
I AIN'T GOT TO HOLD HER YET.
OH...
>> THE WHOLE FAMILY WAS THERE
TO GREET US.
>> [kissing]
>> EVERYONE EXCEPT MY MOM.
>> SHE SMILED AT ME.
WHENEVER I TOOK HER,
SHE SMILED AT ME.
>> I JUST CHANGED HER.
>> WELL, HONEY, YOU MIGHT AS
WELL GET READY.
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE THAT
FOR AT LEAST THE FIRST--
THERE SHE GOES AGAIN.
>> I HEARD THAT ONE COME OUT.
LOOK AT HER.
NOW I KNOW WHAT THE POOPY FACE
IS.
[passing gas]
>> OOH, GIRL!
YOU ARE A STOUT ONE TOO.
[laughter]
>> BLAH.
[Kaylee fussing]
>> NOW THAT THE WELCOME PARTY
IS OVER, I HOPE ERIC AND I
CAN HANDLE BEING PARENTS
ON OUR OWN.
>> IT SAYS "FOUR" RIGHT THERE.
>> [whines]
I CAN'T SEE THAT.
>> HERE, FOUR.
[Kaylee fussing]
I ONLY GET TO SLEEP ABOUT
THREE HOURS A NIGHT.
>> ERIC'S BEEN HELPING AS MUCH
AS HE CAN, BUT SINCE HE HAS TO
GO BACK TO WORK AND SCHOOL,
I'M GONNA BE ON MY OWN
MOST OF THE TIME.
[Kaylee fussing]
>> MM?
>> MM-MM.
[Kaylee fussing]
>> WHAT DO YOU NEED,
LITTLE GIRL?
I'M GETTING STIR-CRAZY
BY MYSELF.
PST-PST-PST-PST.
I REALLY MISS ERIC
AND MY FRIENDS.
MY MOM KEEPS TEXTING,
BUT I'M STILL NOT READY
FOR HER TO BE AROUND KAYLEE.
[door creaks open]
I'M GETTING TIRED OF STAYING
IN THAT HOUSE.
IT'S A LITTLE-BITTY HOUSE.
LIKE, WHEN IT'S JUST
ME AND KAYLEE,
LIKE, I ALWAYS FEEL LONELY.
>> Y'ALL NEED TO GO OUT TO EAT
ONE DAY OR SOMETHING.
>> WELL, WE WOULD, BUT WHAT
WOULD I DO WITH KAYLEE?
NANNY WORKS ON WEEKENDS,
AND THE ONLY PERSON TO WATCH
KAYLEE IS MY MOM,
AND I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
BECAUSE MY MOM HAS BEEN STAYING
SOBER AND STICKING TO HER
TREATMENT, ERIC AND I DECIDED
TO LET HER VISIT AND SEE HER
GRANDDAUGHTER.
>> CAN I HOLD MY GRANDBABY NOW?
>> NO, I'M HOLDING HER NOW.
>> GIVE ME THE BABY.
YOU GET HER ALL NIGHT.
>> MM.
>> YOU GET HER ALL NIGHT.
[chuckles]
OH, THAT'S AMAZING.
OH, YEAH, SHE'S GRABBING
MY FINGER.
OH, IT JUST REMINDS ME SO MUCH
OF WHEN YOU WERE THIS LITTLE.
LOOK AT WHAT YOU DID, MYRANDA.
LOOK.
YOU DID THAT, MOM.
OH, THANK YOU, GOD.
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
>> OH, SHE'S COLD.
SHE'S SHIVERING.
YOU SEEM LIKE YOU DON'T WANT
YOUR MOM TO WATCH HER.
>> I GUESS I'M JUST SCARED
FOR HER TO WATCH HER,
'CAUSE OF HOW I'VE GROWN UP
WITH HER.
>> YOU WANT GRANDMA
TO WATCH YOU?
I THINK YOU SHOULD TRUST
YOUR MOM MORE.
>> YEAH.
[sighs]
I GUESS.
I KNOW GETTING OUT OF THE HOUSE
WITH ERIC WILL BE GOOD FOR ME,
BUT I'M STILL PRETTY NERVOUS
ABOUT LEAVING KAYLEE ALONE
WITH MY MOM.
YOU WANT TO WATCH KAYLEE
TONIGHT?
>> OF COURSE.
I'D BE HAPPY TO WATCH HER.
WHAT ARE Y'ALL GONNA DO?
>> WE'RE JUST GONNA GO EAT.
>> GONNA GO OUT TO EAT TOGETHER.
>> RIGHT DOWN THE ROAD.
>> I'D BE HAPPY TO WATCH HER.
>> HERE YOU GO.
>> JUST MAKE SURE YOU BURP HER
GOOD, 'CAUSE SHE'S GONNA HAVE
TO EAT HERE SOON.
>> ALL RIGHT...
>> I KEEP ALL OF HER STUFF
UP IN THAT TOP CABINET.
FORMULA IS IN THE LITTLE
CONTAINER, AND THEN MAKE SURE
YOU WARM HER BOTTLES UP.
IT HELPS HER STOMACH.
>> OKAY.
>> FOUR OUNCES, TWO SCOOPS.
>> A SCOOP OF THE POWDER?
>> TWO SCOOPS.
AND WHEN YOU CHANGE HER,
DON'T PUT POWDER ON HER,
BECAUSE IT CAKES UP,
AND IT'S NOT GOOD.
>> OKAY.
I CAN HANDLE THAT.
I GOT YOU.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> THANK YOU.
[bell rings]
>> DOES IT FEEL GOOD TO FINALLY
GET OUT OF THE HOUSE?
>> YEAH, BUT I'M STILL A LITTLE
NERVOUS ABOUT LEAVING KAYLEE.
I MISS HER ALREADY.
FEELS GOOD TO GET OUT, THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> CALLING MOM.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> I FORGOT TO TELL HER
TO GIVE KAYLEE THE GAS DROPS
EVERY TIME SHE FEEDS HER.
[line ringing]
>> YOUR CALL HAS BEEN FORWARDED
TO AN AUTOMATIC VOICE MESSAGE
SYSTEM.
[beep]
>> IT'S WEIRD THAT SHE'S
NOT ANSWERING.
>> I KNOW.
KIND OF WORRIES ME.
>> MAYBE SHE DON'T HAVE
NO SERVICE FOR HER PHONE THERE.
>> WE GET PERFECT SERVICE
AT OUR HOUSE.
THAT'S NO EXCUSE.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT IF SHE'S SICK
AND SHE DOESN'T KNOW IT?
>> WELL...
>> WHAT IF SHE'S CHOKING
AND SHE CAN'T HELP HER?
>> WELL, JUST TRY NOT TO THINK
ABOUT IT LIKE THAT.
>> I WORRY ABOUT THEM THINGS
WHEN I'M WATCHING HER.
>> TRYING HER AGAIN?
[phone beeps]
[line ringing]
>> YOUR CALL HAS BEEN FORWARDED
TO AN AUTOMATIC--
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> HURRY.
>> I'M TRYING.
[car beeping]
>> MY MOM ISN'T PICKING UP
HER PHONE, AND IT'S MAKING ME
THINK SOMETHING IS WRONG.
[door creaks open]
>> HEY.
>> HOW'S THE BABY?
>> SHE'S GOOD.
SHE'S LAYING DOWN--
>> I'M GONNA GO IN THERE
AND CHECK ON HER.
>> YEAH, SHE'S IN HER BED.
[Kaylee coos]
I COULD HEAR MY PHONE
RINGING QUITE A BIT OVER THERE
WHEN I HAD THE BABY.
I JUST COULDN'T GET UP
TO GO GET IT.
I KNEW IT WAS PROBABLY YOU
CALLING.
I DIDN'T WANT TO WORRY YOU,
BUT--WERE YOU THAT WORRIED?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, SHE'S FINE.
YOU KNOW I WOULD DO NOTHING--
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING--
TO HURT THAT BABY.
>> EVEN THOUGH, YOU KNOW,
I'M STILL A TEENAGER,
I STILL FEEL LIKE I SHOULD BE
THE ONE TO WATCH HER
AND TAKE CARE OF HER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> HAVE YOU GOTTEN BETTER WITH
YOUR THOUGHTS ON ME WATCHING
THE BABY--YOU KNOW, TRUST?
>> I GUESS NOW THAT SHE'S HERE,
IT'S HARDER THAN I THOUGHT
TO LET PEOPLE WATCH HER.
>> YOU GOT TO BUILD UP THAT
TRUST, NOT BE SO STRESSED
OR WORRIED ABOUT IT.
CALL ME.
"MOM, CAN YOU COME OVER
AND HELP ME FOR A LITTLE WHILE?"
CALL ME.
THAT'S WHAT I'M HERE FOR.
I WANT TO BE HERE FOR THAT,
OKAY?
>> I STILL WORRY.
SINCE IT'S MY DAUGHTER,
I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO TAKE CARE
OF HER, AND I KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S UNDERSTANDABLE.
>> I WANT TO TRUST MY MOM
WITH ALL MY HEART,
BUT IT'S JUST REAL HARD,
ESPECIALLY, YOU KNOW, EVERYTHING
THAT SHE'S DONE IN THE PAST.
I PRAY THAT MY TRUST FOR HER
WILL BUILD IN TIME,
BUT IT'S NOT UP TO ME;
IT'S UP TO HER.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE
THAT HARD TO HAVE A BABY.
BUT WHEN SHE WAS BORN,
IT FINALLY HIT ME THAT THERE'S
SO MUCH MORE THAN JUST FEEDING
HER AND PUTTING HER TO BED.
[Kaylee crying]
I HAVE NO JOB.
ERIC HAS A VERY LOW INCOME JOB.
I JUST WISH HE WAS AROUND MORE
TO HELP WITH KAYLEE AND
THE HOUSE, BECAUSE WE'RE
GETTING THROUGH BARELY.
I'M HAPPY THAT I HAVE HER,
BUT I'M ALSO SAD THAT I HAVE
HER, BECAUSE I JUST WISH
I COULD HAVE HAD A BETTER LIFE
FOR HER THAN IT IS NOW.
>> WHAT IF SHE WORE
A BASEBALL HAT?
[laughter]
>> WHENEVER KAYLEE GETS TO BE
16, I'LL TELL HER, "I DON'T
WANT YOU TO END UP LIKE I DID.
IF YOU'RE GONNA BE SEXUALLY
ACTIVE, USE PROTECTION."
I'LL TELL HER THAT.
>> LOOK AT HER HOLDING
THAT BALL.
LOOK AT HER.
THERE YOU GO.
>> YAY!
I DON'T REGRET HAVING KAYLEE,
BUT I DO WISH THAT I WOULD HAVE
WAITED TO ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW,
HAVE SEX.
[laughs]
I REALLY DO.
>> I WAS KIND OF HOPING THAT,
FOR THE FIRST FEW MONTHS AT
LEAST, WE COULD BE HERE
TOGETHER.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE WAY
THAT HE TREATS YOU SOMETIMES.
YOU [bleep] USE US.
>> THAT'S WHY I DON'T LIKE
STAYING HERE; IT'S 'CAUSE
I'M NOT WELCOME.
[baby crying]
>> I KNOW!