My name is Nicole.
I'm 16 years old, and I'm
from Longwood, Florida.
I've got a ton of friends,
and my house is definitely
the place to come hang.
We're going to prank call.
Oh, no.
[laughing]
My dad died when I was two.
So my mom raised me on her own,
and it was just the two of us.
Until Tyler showed up.
He's almost 16, and he's
the love of my life.
He and my mom get to
hang out a lot
because he
dropped out of school.
All right, all right.
There's friction between Tyler
and his parents
so his grandma took him in.
And Grandma wins.
[laughing]
-Phoebe, do you want corn?
-Yeah.
Tyler grew up
with a single mom,
so he filled in as daddy
for his two little sisters.
It's just
his nature to be nurturing.
Just be safe,
if you need me, call me.
All Tyler's experience
with kids will come in handy
because... I'm pregnant.
[rock music]
[music playing]
OK, what happened in school
today, you guys?
It's really boring,
I miss seeing you.
My sophomore year is on hold
until after the baby comes.
So I don't see my friends
as often as I used to.
So when did you find out
you were, like, pregnant?
Like, did you just
take tests, or--
I took seven.
ALLIE: Seven?
You weren't sure the
first three worked?
I peed on a stick.
And then I gave it to--
[laughing]
I gave it to my mom because I
was too nervous to look at it.
Were you on birth control?
ALLIE: Oh.
-You weren't using condoms?
-Nope.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
ALLIE: Well, that's
what happens.
Oh, yeah.
It's just, like, unreal.
It should feel
unreal for you, too.
Aren't you nervous?
I was freaking out
because the first thing
that popped in my
head was Tyler,
what is he going to think?
As soon as I told him,
I thought he was going
to walk out, and just leave.
But he didn't.
]NICOLE] In fact, Tyler is more
committed than ever.
-Come on, Macy.
-Go and say hi to mommy.
Mm, I want a kiss from you,
not the dog.
[blowing air on belly]
He wants
to be an example to our baby
and get back to school
before she arrives.
The baby will be
born in January,
and then I go back in March.
-Do you miss it?
-Yeah.
I miss my friends.
I miss going to school, too.
-I feel you.
-Do you? Really?
I don't want to
just be nothing.
I want Brooklyn to
have a good life.
We're having a girl,
and we're naming her Brooklyn.
She's moving.
Oh, I felt it.
As a kid, Tyler was shuttled
back and forth between
his mom and dad's house.
He started failing school
and got expelled when he was 13.
I know he'll go back someday.
But for now, we've got a
ton of time to hang out.
Baby, do you remember
the first time we met?
Do you?
Yeah, it took me all
night to ask you out.
I was so nervous.
And I was like, oh, my God.
He is cute!
I can't help it.
What made you like me?
Well, your personality
when I got around you
because I was the only one
that could break you
out of your shell.
Yeah, my mom
couldn't even do that.
Yeah, and just your smile.
And the way you love me.
What made you like me?
Everything.
Give me some details.
Your personality.
Well, of course.
-Your looks.
- I know.
The way you treat me,
the way you protect me.
[laughing]
-You're going to kill yourself.
-Nah.
Awesome.
There's
a lot to love about Tyler,
but he does have a nasty habit.
He promised to quit smoking
once Brooklyn comes.
He's also going to
have to get a job.
Tyler definitely has skills.
He wants to grow up
and be a chef.
He also thinks he can get work
as a mixed martial arts fighter
and has plans to tour
as a professional skateboarder.
[music playing]
But for now, all I know is
we're going to have to get
some help from our families.
So you're getting two
pancakes, sausage,
scrambled eggs with American
cheese and onions,
and a side of hash browns.
-And then a biscuit, please.
-And a biscuit.
She's eating for two.
She got a little
baby in the belly.
She doesn't stop eating.
You ought to see her.
WAITRESS: No?
-Oh, my God.
I'm lucky my mom
loves Tyler as much as I do.
And she definitely didn't react
like the average mom
when she found out
I was pregnant.
What did you think
when you first found out?
The first thing that
came in your head.
To be honest with you,
I was happy for you.
But I was scared for you
because I know
it's going to be hard for you.
He's got to get a job someday.
You've got to find something.
I could be a mechanic,
I could be a landscaper.
-I could do all sorts of stuff.
-A professional skateboarder.
[TINA] Seriously--
I want you to teach
Brooklyn how to skate.
You don't realize how
hard it's going to be.
You think it's going to be easy.
You think it's going
to be a piece of cake.
Ever--
Here's your drinks
to go and I'll be back.
Oh, let's see what
we're paying today.
-Geez.
-What?
It's expensive, this is the most
I've ever spent here.
That you spent?
Well, no, uh, that
we've ever spent here.
You got to start
saving some money
because you're not going
to get much out of me.
I just want to be
able to support them.
I'm ready for Brooklyn.
I can't wait.
And yours was
the most expensive.
Really?
I've got to get
this checked out.
Can I ask a question?
Am I, like, reading this wrong?
It doesn't make sense.
This adds up to $30 with
the $6 and the two 10?
What's that?
It looks like you
charged me twice.
WAITRESS: Ma'am, it's right.
Is that--
That's your sausage, hash
browns, scrambled eggs.
Oh, that's my mine.
-You mean-- but what's that?
-That was her--
Oh, that's hers?
Everybody keeps telling us
that love
doesn't pay the bills.
We know that's true,
'cause my mom does, for now.
She's even managed to scrape
together enough
to buy Tyler
a cake for his 16th birthday.
The boys have gathered at
our house to celebrate.
Tyler.
Of course,
Tyler hasn't woken up yet.
What do you want to do
for your birthday today?
-Any ideas?
-I'm not getting up.
Get up, boy.
Come on, you're 16,
we've got to do something.
What did we
do for your birthday?
-Nothing.
Well, you're pregnant,
you got a baby, that's enough.
That's for him.
That's not from you.
I haven't had
a birthday party in years.
TINA: I couldn't afford
anything, Nicole, you know that.
Let's go to the
skate park today.
-Do you guys want to go?
-Sure.
[music playing]
I got him a cake.
Do you think he's
going to like it?
Yeah.
Happy birthday, Tyler,
happy birthday to you.
He might be 16, but he acts
like he's five sometimes.
-Always.
-Age is just a number.
Are we still going to come
here when Brooklyn's born?
Yeah, he's going to
teach her to skate.
A lot of people don't understand
why my mom is so unconditionally
supportive of me and Tyler.
What's wrong?
It's all right to be
nervous and everything.
I was, with you.
Extremely.
When I was 10 months old,
my mom gave birth
to a baby who died.
And I think that makes her
more open to my being pregnant.
Emily was born prematurely.
She lived, like, three hours.
Your father was
crying and crying,
and he fell to the floor,
he passed out.
I didn't--I never
told you that.
She died in my arms,
on my birthday.
And then your dad turns
around and dies on my birthday
in '95, a year to the day
that Emily was born.
I definitely want
to take a picture
so he can be there
for her birth.
He's going to be
a grandpa, you know?
He really--I think he'd
be there for you, too.
You know that,
he'd really support you.
You know?
And--and I know he'd love
the hell out of Tyler.
Sorry.
I just wish he was here
to see all of this,
to be a part of it.
[sniffing]
Our baby's due
in two months.
I just can't wait for
her to get here, man.
And Tyler's still
looking for work.
I applied for them, too.
-Did you?
-Yeah, online.
But they don't pay you [bleep].
It's $6.50 an hour.
Still, it's money.
People
say Tyler lacks motivation.
But I have no doubt about
his ability to be a good dad.
You guys ready to eat?
Here, baby girl.
All I have
to do is watch the way
he takes care
of his two little sisters.
Let me put some
butter in here for you.
Are you excited for the baby?
-Yeah.
-You are?
So you guys ready to be an aunt?
-Nah.
-Why?
-That's not true.
-No, that's not true.
I'm not going to love
the baby more than you.
I'm just going to
love it just as much.
Oh!
What are you going to do when
you see that baby
for the first time?
I'm going to
pinch it's cheeks.
I'm going to go like this.
[laughing]
So is mommy happy
that I'm having a baby?
-Tell the truth.
-No.
-No?
-What she say?
-No, she's mad.
She said you're too--
you're a big baby.
What else did she say?
Nana!
Go ahead, tell us,
we want to here.
Nah.
-Oh, come on.
-Come on!
She says you should get a job.
I'm just telling you.
Mommy was
pissed, wasn't she?
Oh, she still is.
Just give her time to get used
to it, and she'll come around.
It's not really the point
of getting used to it.
The thing is,
this was their choice
and we have to deal with it, no
matter whether we agree with it
-or not.
-Yeah.
And I couldn't imagine
never supporting a child.
Tyler's lucky
his grandma has his back.
[NELL] Touch the belly there.
He left
his mom's house two years ago.
And he had nowhere else to turn.
Put the shirt down.
What was one of the reasons
you came to stay here?
I don't want to talk about it.
I can't stand it
when you guys fight.
God, my hair was
about to start falling out
when I was living there.
Tyler's mom had him
when she had just turned 17.
When Tyler's little
sisters came,
and his mom's
marriage fell apart,
she couldn't handle
Tyler on her own.
Deep down, I know he hurts
about his family situation.
But now he gets to start
a brand new one with me.
[guitar music]
Tomorrow's my baby shower.
So my girls are coming to sleep
over and start the party early.
-Prank call Tyler.
-Prank call Tyler, Kayla.
-It'd be funny.
-What do I say?
Act like a guy.
Tell him you want to fight
him and he'll get fired up.
-Oh, yeah.
-Just do it, do it, do it.
[phone ringing]
[TYLER] Hello?
Hey, is this Tyler?
This is Oscar.
[TYLER] i
Yeah, this is Oscar.
Yeah, I heard you wanted
to take it down, man.
I heard
you wanted to beat it.
[laughing]
Yeah.
All right,
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Bye.
[laughing]
You got him into it!
You can go on the internet
and prank call prostitutes.
[laughing]
My name is Harmony and I'm 23
years old, give me a call.
-All right.
-Call.
[phone ringing]
[HARMONY] Hello?
Hi, yes, for my
boyfriend's birthday,
I'm very interested
about getting him a girl.
Can you help me out?
OK, well, he's very
into the Spider-Man.
So what if I can get you,
but dressed up as like a guy?
HARMONY [ON PHONE]: OK.
[laughing]
I started getting
sharp pains in my stomach
And at seven months pregnant,
I don't think
I should be feeling this.
I have to go to
the bathroom, so--
Is she OK?
[phone ringing]
[TINA]
Babe, are you OK?
Mom, I got
really bad cramps.
It's right under my belly.
It really hurts, really bad.
[music playing]
I'm going to the hospital.
Tyler's grandma and my mom want
to take me to get checked out.
Oh, my gosh.
[music playing]
All right?
All right, let's go.
Get in the truck.
Nicole, what's going on?
They hurt,
now it's like really bad.
Be careful!
Call me.
TINA: OK.
[music playing]
Canceling
my sleepover was a bummer,
but at seven months pregnant,
I'm way more worried about
the pains in my lower belly.
[pensive music]
After four hours
in the hospital,
the doctors had
to give me a shot
to keep me
from going into preterm labor.
At least I got released in time
to get over to my baby shower.
[upbeat music]
[cheering and applause]
I want a hug.
My mom was able
to set up the party
at her friend's
retirement complex.
Hey, it's a girl baby.
Isn't that cool?
So heavy!
Hello, Allie.
JJ!
Responsible
parents, sucking helium.
Oh, look,
Tina's doing it, too.
Allie!
Oh, Allie!
Tyler's mom showed up.
We were both
surprised to see her.
-OK.
-Did you get cake?
So we can go soon.
Breanna.
Hello!
Oh, I still sound funny.
That is adorable.
Oh, that's cute!
Everyone
was having a good time,
and we got some necessary stuff.
Oh, that baby's going
to have so many clothes.
But one person
didn't seem that happy for us.
-Who's that from?
-Rattler!
Thank you,
that's very cute.
My son just turned 16.
He's going to be a dad,
and I just want to smack
them both upside the head.
[groans]
He's seen me struggle with
the girls his whole life.
And here he does--
That's what's got me--
And who's that from?
-Aunt Becky.
-Thank you, Aunt Becky.
Marissa, thank you!
It's a bib.
I'm ready to go home.
This is just too much.
Thank you!
[laughing]
Thank you so much.
[laughing] That he's 16?
Going to have a baby?
Out of school?
Smokes cigarettes
stays up all night?
Yo, this thing is soft.
Tyler's no angel.
I expected more from him.
Mom, you're missing
all of that outside.
I'm watching.
I love you, baby.
I'm going out for a cigarette.
I hope Mom's around
for a long time
because that baby's
going to need it.
No.
Don't even go there.
Because you just--you'll
say something to piss me off,
and I'll just piss you off.
Nicole, I told her
her life was over.
No more free time.
It's not the baby's fault.
Ah, [bleep] bitch.
Boy, aren't
we getting a little--
Yeah, because I hate
that [bleep]..
-You bring it up every time.
-You brought it up.
No, you brought
the [bleep] up.
-Don't even go there.
-Yeah.
Go back inside.
You're an immature 16-year-old.
You're a [bleep] bitch, Mom.
Yo, that's real
respectful for a dad.
[bleep] you.
Oh, he's pathetic.
Hey, Tyler,
come here for a minute.
I want to leave.
I swear, I can't stand my mom.
Tell me everything.
She was like--she was like,
she goes, you're a 16-year-old
-that's immature--
-Why?
--and don't know
how to raise a kid.
And I was like, really?
Well, that's why I left
her house at 11 years old.
Give him a good ass beating,
because that's what he needs.
You need to go tell
your brother bye
because it'll be
a long time before you
see or talk to him again.
Go.
I love you so much.
Remember that, OK?
I love you.
I don't want to
talk to her no more.
I'm sick of her.
I want her out of my life.
Tyler's mom had
him when she was a teenager.
So if anybody should understand
where we're at, it's her.
We don't need more drama.
What we need is support.
Oh!
[upbeat music]
Tyler hasn't gotten
over the blow out with his mom.
But I think her
calling him a slacker
is having an effect on him.
-So what's up, man?
-Been chillin', school.
I haven't been to school
in like, four years, man.
Yeah.
I need a change,
stay out of trouble.
-You need to go back to school.
-I know.
I miss, like, being
able to go to school
and have something
to do during the day
because you have nothing
to do during the day.
Yeah. I know.
Like, that's why
I sleep all day.
But I definitely
want to go to school.
-I want to go. I--
-You better.
Tyler always told me he
was going to graduate someday.
And days before he was due to be
a dad, he enrolled in a program
to complete his GED.
Now that I'm so close to my due
date, contractions have started
and I'm getting
really uncomfortable.
I'm trying to get this whole
labor thing moving along.
She's anxious.
Nicole, you want to get
your jacket and let's go?
Let's go start walking.
You need to be active.
My doctor
said that keeping on my feet
might kick start labor.
I can't run no more.
10 jumping jacks.
One, two.
Let's go, come on, girl.
Come on.
[upbeat music]
I've also been told
that some weird diets
can get labor going.
AI Steak Sauce
and macaroni and cheese.
I'm about to throw up.
I drank Castor oil,
and nothing happened.
It just gave me diarrhea.
[laughing]
Have you dilated at all?
I had Tyler check.
[laughing]
But he didn't know
what to look for,
so it didn't really work out.
We're going to put her
in my car with the bass all
the way up so when
the baby starts,
like, jiggling and dancing, it's
going to wiggle its way out.
Hey, do you know any
place that has speed bumps?
If you go fast over a speed
bump, it causes labor.
-And it wrecks your car.
-Let's do it.
[tires screeching]
-You ready?
-Yeah.
[laughing]
-That was a good one.
-Right here.
-OK. I just got a pain.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God!
Let's do it again!
The speed
bumps didn't work either.
I guess we'll just have to wait
for nature to take its course.
[guitar music]
Can I shoot pool right now?
No.
Yeah.
You need to be walking around.
Grandma, don't you think
shooting pool's good for her?
It wouldn't hurt you.
[crack]
However odd Tyler's theory
sounded,
my contractions
started getting
intense and closer together.
-You got to.
-I can't.
-One more. Just one more, baby.
I'll rack them and everything.
I want to see you break.
[crying]
I think we need to go, guys.
All right.
Let's go.
[upbeat music]
Where do you want
your father's picture?
How about on the window?
[pensive music]
[grunts] Baby!
[laughing]
I wasn't laughing for long.
[pensive music]
I always saw myself as tough,
but the pain got worse
than I could ever imagine.
The doctor came in about 15
minutes ago, broke her water,
and said now it should
start progressing.
And they got her
on a ball right now,
and she's crying really bad.
[sobs]
Well, the nurse said it could
be any time up to 12 hours.
[sobbing]
[pensive music]
[gasping and groaning]
Come on, breathe.
You're doing good.
Come on.
[grunting]
[squeals and cries out]
Oh, my God.
Deal with this a little bit
longer.
Come on.
It's all right.
You're about
to get the epidural
and it's just going to go by
so fast.
Finally,
I was dilated enough
to get an epidural.
After 12 hours at the
hospital, the nurse
finally came in with good news.
I talked to the doctor.
He is on his way down.
He doesn't want to wait, and
it's time to start pushing.
-This is it, kiddo.
-Oh, my God!
You'll have the baby
in the next 30 minutes.
I can't wait.
Tyler, you're
going to be a daddy.
TINA: I can't wait to have
this baby here, honey.
I can't wait until she
just, whoosh, hello, baby.
Go ahead and pull
those legs back.
OK.
So on the next contraction
here, what I want to do is--
right now is-- and big push,
come on, push, push, push.
This is it.
Push.
Come on, keep pushing.
Push, push.
Head's out.
[groaning]
Hey, they just
did one push already
and the baby's
head's already down.
-Well, hurry up and get there.
-Yes.
That's what the
doctor just said.
Please don't pass out.
[laughing]
Come on,
push, push, push.
[pensive music]
♪  I think I'd
Love to believe you then ♪
♪  You're lost because you are ♪
You hear it?
[crying]
Nine pounds?
-Nine pounds, six ounces.
-Oh, my God!
I was happy so many people
showed up to meet Brooklyn.
The one person I was surprised
to see was Tyler's mom.
She didn't say much,
but just the fact
that she showed up said a lot.
Well, she was born today.
What's today?
January 17.
[music playing]
You sure got a cute little baby.
That's Baby Brooklyn.
[upbeat music]
It's great to see
Tyler's mom getting along
for the last couple of days.
And now the doctor says we're
ready to take Brooklyn home.
She's smiling.
[laughing] That's cute.
[music playing]
-How you feeling, baby girl?
-I'm fine.
She's awake now.
She's looking around.
[laughing]
She say, where am I. What
is this contraption on me?
Tyler and I are nowhere
near having a place of our own.
Our plan for now, is to
go back and forth from
my mom's to Tyler's grandma's.
Baby girl.
Yes, this is daddy's house.
This is home, bud.
Hey you.
Uh oh.
What?
-We got to change her.
-OK.
I'm pretty sure.
You want me to change her?
-If you want to.
-No, do you want to?
-Go ahead.
-You sure.
I'd ask you if you
want me to change her,
but I know you're going
to do it. So I won't ask.
-Do you want to do it?
-No, go ahead.
You're the mother.
You need to do it.
-She's wet, right?
-No.
It feels wet, though.
Yep.
Is she getting a little red?
Mm-mm.
The nurse said that she
looks fine down there.
OK.
She looks red to me.
But it's up to you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Come on, baby.
Put your leg down.
Yeah, I know.
This mom
thing is all brand new for me.
I'm glad some experienced
adults came over to help us.
-See the baby
-How are you, mama?
-You see Tyler's baby?
-How you doing?
You ready for a bath?
Well-well.
Have you given her bath yet?
No we're doing it right now.
I'm gonna watch you
guys do it first.
Amy is going to show you how.
Oh, yep.
See, I knew you weren't
going to like this.
[baby crying]
Oh my God.
Let's get them fingers.
Yes.
Oh my goodness.
She don't like this at all.
Oh, baby girl.
I don't like that.
[baby crying]
You're supposed to
get over here and help.
It's all right.
[baby screaming]
-OK.
-Get a diaper.
I'm sorry.
All right, mommy
can do it because I
don't want you being mad.
I don't want to hurt her.
You're not going
to hurt her, honey.
Just pull her little legs
up and get me a shirt.
Here.
You need some help, babe?
-Get her little arms here.
-I'm trying. I'm trying.
Take this
and push it down.
Yeah, but, grandma,
it's stuck on her back.
Well, we don't--no,
you get the arms in first--
OK, grandma.
--then you
pull them back down.
I have a headache.
-You want a cigarette?
-No.
I just quit.
-Smoking? You're done?
-Yeah.
-I quit cigarettes.
-No more? For the baby?
Yeah.
I don't want smoke
around her and Nicole
said it would be a good idea.
I asked him to quit.
Think I'm gonna
call off school today
because Brooklyn was born.
Tyler followed through
and re-enrolled for his GED.
But I guess his first day
of school in over four years
will have to wait.
Hi, is Miss Weaver there?
Hi, this is Tyler, um, I
was calling to tell you, um,
I wouldn't be able
to make it today
because my daughter
was just born.
So is that all right though?
Thank you.
Bye.
Tyler
only missed one class
and he's motivated
to get his education
because he's got a new job and
he's starting at the bottom.
And nobody expected it
would come from his mom.
She hooked him up
with the nursing home
where she works
after she found out
that he went back to school.
How is things
with Nicole and the baby?
Good.
Grandma?
Fine.
Other than staying on
your ass when she needs to?
On everything.
Well, you--
you're only 16, bud.
I know but I'm doing everything
right. I go to school.
Yes, you went back to school.
I go to work.
I don't do nothing wrong.
Just put your
priorities first.
I do.
-Finish school.
-I'm going to.
-Go to college.
-I am.
And get a good
paying job to take care
of you, Nicole, and Brooklyn.
Tyler might not be that excited
about his new line of work
but we'd be screwed if his
mom didn't help us out.
What made you come
around to talk to Tyler
again, after what happened?
-At the baby shower?
-Yeah.
Well, I missed him.
Thought about Tyler every day
even though he's a butt-head.
And I'm proud of Tyler
that he's gone back
to school, which you need to.
I am.
But, you're
always welcome here.
OK.
Even though you
guys should've waited.
Yeah.
No more kids for quite
a while like in your 20's.
You know me and
Tyler want six?
You'll change
your mind quickly.
I'm glad Farrah's proud to have
a grandkid and I'm going
to respect her wish to not give
her a bunch more anytime soon.
The cool thing about my mom is
that she doesn't mind looking
after Brooklyn once in a while.
OK, we'll be back.
How about we watch TV?
Now that Tyler's working
and going to school,
we don't want our lives
to come to a complete stop.
I didn't crash.
I won.
She's content, now.
She's in grandma's lap.
All right.
Y'all gonna clean this mess up?
I'm going to bed.
Goodnight.
Come on, sweetheart.
Come on.
What would you do
if I wasn't here?
Even though I'm supposed to be
back in two months,
school seems like a
million miles away.
My mom helps when she can.
She's not even drinking much.
And Tyler and I are learning
the ropes with Brooklyn.
So when things get
to be too much--
-Grandma.
-Yes?
We're staying here tonight.
We know we can always move
on to Tyler's grandma's.
Is it time
for you to wake up?
Yeah.
Are you going to
open those eyes?
Tyler.
Are you going to get up?
I'm going to put
some earplugs in.
Why?
So I can't hear you.
All right.
Just snoozing away.
He's never going to get up.
When grandma spent,
we give Tyler's mom some
time with her granddaughter.
Are you eating with us?
We'll be back.
Whatever.
Mom, can you help
me change her diaper?
She went poop.
Everybody seems cool about
pitching in with childcare,
so I didn't see the harm
in accepting the help.
But I think shuttling
our kid around
is starting to upset Farrah.
What are we talking about?
-The house hopping--
-Oh God.
It's not oh God, Tyler.
Don't get all pissy.
We're not
doing nothing wrong.
She wants
one stable home.
No. She has a home
and she knows the home.
You need
to think about her.
Yeah, she's fine.
We're doing everything
in our will to help her.
Well, a lot of
people think different.
Well, that's a lot of people.
That's their own opinions.
It's what the world's
full of, drama.
I think everybody's
just concerned.
They want her to have stability.
We are stable.
It's just not fair
for her to be bounced.
Really?
She comes first before
going out, shooting pool--
[bleep] you say.
Well, your freedom is done.
Both of y'all.
I'm sick of
everyone picking on us.
You see Tyler
wouldn't be getting upset
if none of this wasn't true.
I knew she was gonna
[bleep] deal about that.
It's just like every
time I come over there
she's got something to
start with me about.
She's kind of saying that we
never have the baby, I guess.
I didn't do nothing wrong.
But we do go back
and forth a lot.
Like, I'm agreeing with that.
We do.
Tyler was bounced from house
to house when he was a kid
and it was rough on him.
We don't want the same
for Brooklyn.
To find out what you can
do to prevent pregnancy
go to itsyoursexlife.org.
We're letting things cool off
between Tyler and his mom,
so we're staying at my mom's
for a couple of days.
She's at work,
so we're on our own.
Tyler's as helpful as he can be
but between his school schedule
and his new job, I'm alone
caring for Brooklyn tonight.
[baby crying]
I know I should get her to
sleep but she's the boss of me
and she just doesn't
want to go down.
[knocking on door]
Hey, beautiful.
I miss the girls, but now all
I want to do is sleep.
She's so big.
Aw.
You want her?
Come here, baby.
Hey.
So, how's it been
since you've been home?
It's so
completely different.
Everything's on
Brooklyn's time now.
Does she have a schedule
yet or is it whenever?
Yeah, it's whenever.
How are you going to
take care of Brooklyn
and still go back to school?
It's going to be really tough.
It's like no sleep at all
if you had to go to school.
If I want to get an
education to help raise her
then that means no sleep then.
I have to do it.
So are you home
alone during the day?
Yeah.
Tyler's at work?
Friends don't just
stop by like they used to?
No.
I don't feel like
a teenager anymore.
-Look.
-She's smiling.
-Hey, what's up, guys?
Give me my baby.
Hi, sweetheart. Hi.
How was she all day?
I didn't go to sleep
until 8:00 this morning.
-8 o'clock? Why?
-No.
Because she was up.
All night?
What are you doing?
You know what it is?
You being a new mom.
You're still uncomfortable.
Well, you're not totally
comfortable with her
and she feels it.
I'm not being mean.
I'm just saying you guys need to
start coming around more often.
You guys are going to be
a skating at the skate park?
So you going to
leave baby with me?
-Why don't you say it?
-What?
You guys are going
to leave her with me.
Yeah.
OK.
So, we're bringing
the baby with us?
No.
Hi, Brooklyn.
Hi.
It's nice
to have help from our families
but this is me and Tyler's baby
and we're going to have to
give up some of our freedom
to do what's best for her.
Where do you want her to
grow up at your house or mine?
I want to get our own place.
So it's not at your house
or my house.
It's our house.
We just gotta save up.
And then she can go visit
grandmas' on the weekends.
Yep.
Are you excited to
take her back here
when she's old enough to play?
Yeah. She'll be running
all over the place.
Daddy, push me. Push me.
She'll be like teach me
how to do a back flip.
I'm teaching
her how to do one.
-OK, when she was 20.
-No. When she's five.
-No.
-Yeah.
If she's
anything like you,
she's going to be a handful.
Why don't you just
kiss me down here.
No.
He's hitting me.
Yeah.
Don't jump on the table.
I'm starting to realize
that my mom is right.
It's going to take time for
us to learn how to be parents.
My first
thought when I found out
I was pregnant was like
once I had the baby Tyler
would be gone
and I would be stuck
a single mom like most girls.
He could've left me when he
found out I was pregnant,
but he chose not to
and he chose to stick
with me through the hard times.
For you, baby.
Usually, a day is
just being home with the baby.
It's not going out
with my friends
anymore like it used to be.
I'm on baby time now and I
don't get to do what I want,
when I want.
You don't want daddy to win?
Think I'm
going to have to fight
pretty hard to make sure I'm
motivated to go to school.
I think if we waited
and I went to college
first everything would
have been a little easier.
I want to Brooklyn
to go to school.
And I want her to
wait to have kids
because I don't want her to
go through the hard times
that I've been
through when I was 16.
She's like, honey,
you're having twins.
I was like--
-Twice the amount of diapers.
-Twice the everything.
Whether you want
to face it or not,
you two have two kids for
the rest of your life.
COREY: You have to
face you have a family.
LEAH: How long was we together
before we got pregnant?
Not very long at all,
but does that matter?
Was I in love?
No I wasn't.
Do I think you
picked him over me?
Yeah, I do.
Jealousy is going
to split us up.
-Why are you crying?
-[Leah screaming]
-What did I [bleep] do?
-You make me insane!