>> DO IT PRETTY.
[chime dings]
HI, I'M KIANNA,
AND I'M FROM FORT WORTH, TEXAS.
I'M GONNA BE A SENIOR THIS YEAR,
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M TOTALLY
FOCUSED ON SCHOOL, I LOVE
HANGING OUT WITH MY FRIENDS
AND HAVING FUN.
[laughter]
I LIVE WITH MY MOM AND DON'T
TALK TO MY DAD.
WELL, I HAVEN'T CLEANED
UPSTAIRS.
>> YOU NEED TO GET IT TOGETHER.
>> WE DON'T ALWAYS GET ALONG
'CAUSE SHE'S SO TOUGH ON ME.
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE IN TEXAS,
MY FAVORITE SPORT IS FOOTBALL,
SO IT ONLY MAKES SENSE THAT
TWO MONTHS AGO, I STARTED DATING
MY BOYFRIEND, ZAK.
HE'S AN AWESOME FOOTBALL PLAYER.
EVEN THOUGH WE LIVE IN DIFFERENT
TOWNS AND GO TO DIFFERENT
SCHOOLS, WE SOMEHOW
MAKE IT WORK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I LOVE YOU.
>> YEAH?
>> LIKE ME, ZAK LIVES WITH
HIS MOM AND DOESN'T TALK
TO HIS DAD.
OH!
>> OH, YEAH.
>> EVEN THOUGH HE'S ONLY 15
AND I'M 17, WE TOTALLY
GET EACH OTHER.
>> OH!
>> ZAK DOES ACT HIS AGE, THOUGH,
AND HE JOKES AROUND A LITTLE
TOO MUCH AT TIMES.
BUT HE'S GOING TO HAVE TO GROW
UP SOON BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
IT'S A MONTH BEFORE SCHOOL
STARTS, BUT TODAY IS THE FIRST
FOOTBALL GAME OF THE YEAR.
EVEN THOUGH WE GO TO DIFFERENT
SCHOOLS, I'M EXCITED TO WATCH
ZAK PLAY.
IT'S THE DIXIE BELLES.
>> WHO CARES?
>> I CARE.
THINGS ARE DEFINITELY DIFFERENT
NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT.
I'M TRANSFERRING TO A NEW SCHOOL
FOR MY SENIOR YEAR TO HELP ME
GRADUATE EARLY, AND I'M BUMMED
I HAVE TO GIVE UP MY FAVORITE
SCHOOL ACTIVITIES.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S GONNA MAKE ME CRY,
'CAUSE I WANT TO DANCE,
'CAUSE THAT'S ALL I WANTED TO DO
THIS YEAR, IS BE ON DIXIE BELLES
AND PLAY SOFTBALL.
[sighs]
>> WHY DO YOU LIKE DANCING
SO MUCH?
>> I CAN SHOW MY PERSONALITY OFF
WITH IT.
>> WHAT PERSONALITY?
[laughter]
>> SHUT UP.
[cheers and applause]
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OH, FUMBLE!
[whistle blasts]
>> OH, THERE HE IS!
>> WHOO!
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
DO WE WAVE OUR HANDS
OR ANYTHING?
[laughs]
[whistle blasts]
ZAK LIVES 30 MINUTES AWAY
AND DOESN'T HAVE HIS LICENSE
YET, SO THIS IS ONE OF THE FEW
WEEKNIGHTS WE GET TO SEE
EACH OTHER.
IT'S, LIKE, TWO MONTHS SINCE
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER, BUT WE'RE
HAVING A BABY NOW, YOU KNOW?
>> I WAS SHOCKED.
MY FIRST THOUGHT WAS,
"I'M YOUNG."
I'M 15.
YOU 17.
[chuckles]
>> 'CAUSE IT'S LIKE,
ONE NIGHT OF FUN
CAN RUIN EVERYTHING.
LIKE, I DIDN'T TAKE MY BIRTH
CONTROL FOR THREE DAYS.
WHO KNEW THAT JUST THREE DAYS
COULD MAKE OUR LIVES CHANGE
FOREVER, YOU KNOW?
I'M STILL GETTING USED TO
THE FACT THAT I'M PREGNANT,
BUT I'M GLAD ZAK IS STICKING
BY ME.
[chime dings]
MY MOM, ON THE OTHER HAND,
WAS FURIOUS WHEN SHE FOUND OUT.
SHE HAD ME WHEN SHE WAS
A TEENAGER AND RAISED ME
ON HER OWN.
SO SHE KNOWS WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE YOUNG AND PREGNANT.
>> I TOOK STEPS TO PREVENT THIS
FROM HAPPENING,
AND I EXPECTED FOR YOU TO BE
MATURE ENOUGH TO COME TO ME
AND SAY, "I NEED HELP."
'CAUSE I HAVE TOLD YOU
OVER AND OVER HOW HARD IT IS
TO BE A TEEN MOM.
I DIDN'T WANT THIS FOR YOU.
>> I KNOW THAT, AND I DIDN'T
EITHER.
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, HOW COME YOU NEVER DID
COME AND TALK TO ME ABOUT
THIS WHOLE PREGNANCY THING?
>> I WASN'T GONNA HAVE NOTHING
TO TELL YOU AT FIRST, THOUGH,
'CAUSE I WAS GONNA TAKE CARE
OF IT MYSELF.
>> TAKE CARE OF IT HOW?
>> I WAS GONNA TAKE CARE OF IT.
>> SO YOU WEREN'T GONNA
HAVE THE BABY?
YOU WERE GONNA TERMINATE
THE PREGNANCY OR WHAT?
SO WHY DID YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND?
>> I FELT LIKE I COULDN'T DO IT.
WELL, I KNEW I COULDN'T DO IT,
SO THEN MAYBE ADOPTION.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT ADOPTION?
>> YEAH, NO.
>> YOU DON'T SOUND SURE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I MEAN, YOU STILL HAVE TIME
TO THINK ABOUT ADOPTION.
>> I'M DUE IN TWO MONTHS,
SO I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH
MORE TIME.
I FOUND OUT WE'RE HAVING A BOY,
AND ZAK IS REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT IT.
OH, LOOK AT THE COW.
BUT THE CLOSER MY DUE DATE GETS,
THE MORE I THINK ADOPTION MIGHT
BE THE BEST CHOICE FOR US.
WHEN I THINK ABOUT IT,
I'M LIKE, "I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO TAKE CARE OF HIM, AND I'M NOT
GONNA MAKE IT.
I'M NOT GONNA GRADUATE.
I'M NOT GONNA BE A VET."
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW I'LL BE
ABLE TO ACCOMPLISH IT, BECAUSE
MONEY-WISE, LIKE, EVERYTHING
JUST COMES TO MY MIND LIKE THAT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
ABOUT THIS?
>> NOW I'M JUST CONSIDERING
ADOPTION.
>> LIKE, DID YOU TELL ZAK YET?
>> NOT YET.
LIKE, ZAK DOESN'T THINK ABOUT
THAT KIND OF THINGS,
'CAUSE HE'S 15.
HE JUST THINKS, "OH,
IT'S A BABY, AND EVERYTHING
IS GONNA BE OKAY."
BUT IT'S NOT.
WE'RE BOTH GONNA HAVE
TO GET JOBS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO STAY
IN SCHOOL, BECAUSE THE BABY
IS GONNA NEED BETTER.
I DON'T WANT HIM GROWING UP
WITH NOTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
THERE ARE A LOT OF REASONS
WHY ADOPTION COULD BE
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD TO TALK TO
ZAK, BECAUSE HE'S SO EXCITED
ABOUT THE BABY.
>> WHAT'S UP? WHAT'S UP?
>> HEY.
>> YOU WANNA TALK?
>> YEAH.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
DOING ADOPTION.
>> FOR REAL?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU AIN'T SAID NOTHING
ABOUT THAT.
>> WELL, I THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
>> WELL, WHY DO YOU WANT TO DO
ADOPTION?
>> I FEEL LIKE ADOPTION WILL
GIVE HIM A BETTER LIFE
AS WELL AS US.
WE COULD CONTINUE TO GO
TO SCHOOL.
WE CAN GET THE EDUCATION
THAT WE NEED.
>> HE'S NOT GONNA--
>> GO TO COLLEGE AND GET
A GOOD JOB.
>> WHY YOU THINK HE GONNA
STOP THAT?
>> BECAUSE WE'RE STRUGGLING.
AND IF WE'RE STRUGGLING,
HE'S GONNA STRUGGLE.
HE'S GONNA GROW UP
WITH NO MONEY.
HE'S GONNA GROW UP NOT HAVING
WHAT HE NEEDS.
>> NOT NECESSARILY.
I GREW UP JUST FINE.
MY MAMA RAISED THREE KIDS
BY HERSELF, WORKING TWO JOBS,
ONE JOB.
SHE DID IT BY HERSELF.
>> OKAY, SHE'S WORKING.
WE'RE NOT WORKING.
>> I THINK THE MAIN REASON THAT
I WANT HIM IS BECAUSE MY DAD
NEVER WAS AROUND.
>> I'M JUST SAYING,
THERE'S A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
>> OH, YEAH.
A LOT FOR YOU TO THINK ABOUT?
>> NO, THERE'S A LOT FOR
BOTH OF US TO THINK ABOUT.
>> I'M BUMMED THAT ZAK IS SO
AGAINST THE IDEA OF ADOPTION.
I KNOW HE HAS HIS REASONS,
BUT I DON'T THINK HE REALIZES
HOW HARD PARENTING IS.
ZAK DOESN'T WANT TO DO ADOPTION,
LIKE, POINT-BLANK, PERIOD.
HIS DAD WASN'T THERE FOR HIM,
SO HE'S LIKE, "I DON'T WANT
MY KID TO BE RAISED WITHOUT
A FATHER, BECAUSE I KNOW
HOW IT FEELS."
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S JUST
TALKING OR IF HE'S FOR REAL.
>> DOES HE HAVE HIS LICENSE
OR ANYTHING?
>> NO, HE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE
HIS PERMIT YET.
>> HAS HE EVEN TRIED TO, LIKE,
START LOOKING FOR A JOB
SINCE, LIKE, HE FOUND OUT
THAT YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> NO, HE HASN'T.
HE'S 15, SO HE CAN'T REALLY
GET A JOB.
>> BUT IF HE DOESN'T AGREE
WITH ADOPTION, HE SHOULD REALLY,
YOU KNOW...
>> TRY TO MAKE ME CHANGE MY MIND
AND KEEP EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
>> TRY TO PROVE TO YOU THAT
YOU CAN MAKE IT.
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS A WAY, THOUGH.
>> HE'S JUST GONNA HAVE TO,
LIKE, SUCK IT UP AND GET
THE JOB.
EVEN IF HE DOESN'T LIKE IT,
I MEAN, STILL BRING
SOMETHING IN.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GONNA BE
ABLE TO GO TO SCHOOL, GRADUATE,
AND THEN GO TO COLLEGE,
GET MY VETERINARY MEDICINE
LICENSE AND ALL THAT
WITH A BABY.
I DON'T THINK HE'S REALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT IT AND HOW
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE.
I THINK HE'S JUST THOUGHT ABOUT
THE FACT THAT HE HAS A CHILD
NOW.
HE JUST HASN'T THOUGHT, LIKE,
"OH, WELL, I'M GONNA HAVE
A BABY, SO I NEED TO DO THIS
AND THIS AND THAT."
HE HASN'T THOUGHT FORWARD.
WITHOUT ZAK'S SUPPORT,
I DON'T KNOW HOW I'LL DECIDE
ABOUT ADOPTION.
PLUS, I'M STARTING A NEW SCHOOL
TODAY, AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO TELL THEM.
HOW SHOULD I DO MY MAKEUP?
AT LEAST I'M GONNA DO
MY EYEBROWS.
>> LEAVE THEM ALONE.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA BRING
ATTENTION TO YOURSELF.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GONNA
HAPPEN NOW THAT YOU'RE SO BIG?
DO YOU THINK PEOPLE ARE GONNA
STARE AT YOU?
>> MAYBE A LITTLE BIT.
>> I WAS ALWAYS EMBARRASSED.
I DIDN'T WANT PEOPLE TO KNOW
I WAS PREGNANT.
>> YEAH, IT'S GONNA BOTHER ME.
I CHOSE TO SWITCH TO A NEW
SCHOOL BECAUSE IF I DECIDE
TO KEEP THE BABY, THEY HAVE
FREE DAY CARE.
[groans]
THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL
IS SUPPOSED TO BE AWKWARD
BUT EVEN MORE SO WHEN YOU'RE
PREGNANT.
>> OKAY, I'M MRS. LUMSDEN.
AND TODAY FOR AN ICEBREAKER,
WE'RE GONNA DO THIS LITTLE
ACTIVITY.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO MOVE AROUND
SOME.
OKAY, WHO WILL GRADUATE
THIS YEAR?
OKAY, I WILL NOT ASK YOU
TO DO THIS TODAY--DOESN'T MEAN
YOU'RE SAFE ALL YEAR--
BUT WHO CAN DO A CARTWHEEL?
CLIFF?
OH, I DEFINITELY WON'T
ASK YOU TO DO A CARTWHEEL.
>> [giggles]
[school bell rings]
EVEN THOUGH SCHOOL WAS AWKWARD,
AT LEAST I HAVE ONE FRIEND HERE
WHO DOESN'T MAKE ME FEEL
SELF-CONSCIOUS.
>> DID YOU FEEL WEIRD, LIKE,
WHEN YOU WALKED IN?
DID YOU SEE PEOPLE, LIKE,
LOOKING AT YOU?
>> AT FIRST, I WAS LIKE...
PEOPLE WERE STARING AT ME
AND JUST, "OH, MY GOD.
SHE'S PREGNANT."
>> EVERYBODY WILL BE LOOKING
AT YOU.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> I HATE CRAP LIKE THAT.
>> I'M GLAD MY FIRST DAY
OF SCHOOL IS BEHIND ME,
BUT ZAK AND I STILL NEED TO
FIGURE OUT WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
ABOUT THE BABY.
IS IT NASTY?
>> MM-MM.
>> SO HOW DO YOU FEEL NOW?
>> MMM...NOTHING.
ARE YOU STILL CONSIDERING
ADOPTION?
>> YEAH.
I'M JUST CONSIDERING MY OPTIONS.
I KNOW I CAN'T PROVIDE HIM
WITH WHAT HE ACTUALLY NEEDS
ALL THE WAY.
>> HE GONNA HAVE TOYS.
HE GONNA HAVE WHAT HE NEEDS.
>> TOYS?
WHAT IS TOYS?
HE NEEDS PAMPERS AND--
>> HE GONNA HAVE PAMPERS.
THAT'S NO--
>> I MEAN, WIPES AND BOTTLES.
>> YOU KNOW HE'S GONNA HAVE
ALL THAT, MAN.
>> ARE YOU GONNA GET A JOB?
>> I'M ONLY 15, AND YOU ACT LIKE
IT'S EASY TO GET A JOB AT 15.
>> I MEAN--
>> YOU JUST LOOKING
FOR EXCUSES TO GIVE HIM UP?
>> NO, I'M TRYING TO TALK
TO YOU.
>> OKAY, WELL, I'M LISTENING.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA BE AROUND
WHEN YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL
AND FOOTBALL PRACTICE
AND BASKETBALL?
>> OKAY, SO WHAT?
YOU JUST WANT ME TO GIVE IT
ALL UP?
>> NO, THAT'S--I'M SAYING THAT--
HOW AM I GONNA BE ABLE TO DO
WHAT I NEED TO DO?
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO GIVE UP
MY BABY, BUT I WANT TO GRADUATE,
AND I WANT TO GO TO
A UNIVERSITY.
>> SO YOU JUST GONNA TAKE
THE EASY WAY OUT?
>> ADOPTION'S ACTUALLY NOT
THAT EASY.
YOU STILL HAVE ALL THAT
EMOTIONAL STRESS THAT IT'S GONNA
PUT YOU THROUGH, GIVING YOUR
BABY AWAY TO SOMEBODY.
>> YOU ALWAYS HAVE A CHOICE.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU CHOOSE TO DO,
THAT'S WHAT YOU CHOOSE TO DO.
YOU MIGHT GONNA REGRET IT
ONE DAY WHEN YOU GROWN.
>> [sniffles]
I'M NOT SURE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I WANT TO DO
ADOPTION STILL, THOUGH.
HONESTLY.
>> AFTER TALKING TO ZAK,
I'M MORE CONFUSED THAN EVER
ABOUT WHETHER I SHOULD CHOOSE
ADOPTION, AND WE NEED TO MAKE
A DECISION SOON, BECAUSE I'M DUE
IN JUST SEVEN WEEKS.
>> WHY ISN'T ZAK HERE?
>> HE COULDN'T LEAVE SCHOOL.
>> KIANNA?
>> WARM JELLY.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S YOUR BABY'S
HEART BEATING.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR IT?
>> YES.
[monitor warbling]
OH...
>> [laughs]
THERE'S YOUR BABY'S FACE.
CAN YOU SEE IT?
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S LOOKING RIGHT AT US.
THAT'S HIS LITTLE NOSTRILS
AND HIS LIPS.
OH, THERE HE GOES,
STICKING HIS TONGUE OUT.
>> OH!
[laughter]
LOOK AT HIS NOSE.
>> IT'S YOURS.
[laughter]
>> I KNEW IT.
LOOK AT HIS LIPS.
THEY'RE SO POUTY.
>> THEY'RE LIKE...
>> THEY'RE GONNA BE BIG.
[laughter]
SEEING THESE PICTURES MAKES ME
REALIZE HOW HARD IT WOULD BE
TO CHOOSE ADOPTION.
BUT BEFORE WE MAKE OUR DECISION,
I NEED TO SEE IF I CAN REALLY
COUNT ON ZAK TO HELP SUPPORT
THE BABY.
WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO.
>> I JUST WANT TO RAISE MY SON.
>> IF WE DECIDE TO KEEP
THE BABY, I JUST--
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'LL DO IT
EXACTLY.
>> I WOULD BE A BETTER DAD
THAN MY DAD WAS.
I HAVE FIVE MEMORIES THAT
I CAN THINK OF OF MY DAD
OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD.
WITH MY SON, I WANT TO BE AROUND
FOR HIM.
I WANT HIM TO HAVE
LOTS OF MEMORIES WITH ME,
NOT JUST FIVE.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHERE YOU'RE
COMING FROM.
LIKE, I REALLY DO.
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LET HAVING
A BABY RUIN MY DREAMS
AND MY GOALS FOR LIFE.
I DON'T WANT TO JUST GRADUATE
HIGH SCHOOL OR DROP OUT
AND JUST WORK AT MCDONALD'S
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
I HONESTLY DON'T.
I WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL,
AND I WANT TO BECOME
A VETERINARIAN.
>> LIKE I SAID, I'D HELP YOU
IN ANY WAY I CAN.
I'LL GET A JOB.
>> ARE YOU WILLING TO GIVE UP
FOOTBALL, THE THING THAT
YOU LOVE THE MOST?
>> I'D--I'D BE SAD I'M MISSING
OUT ON MY LAST TWO YEARS
OF FOOTBALL, BUT I'D GIVE UP
ANYTHING.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE
SOMEBODY ELSE RAISE MY SON.
>> IF YOU'RE SERIOUS ABOUT
KEEPING THE BABY AND YOU JUST
DO EVERYTHING THAT YOU HAVE SAID
THAT YOU'RE GONNA DO FOR ME,
THEN I'M WILLING TO KEEP
THE BABY, IF YOU'RE GONNA
SIT HERE AND HELP ME.
>> YEAH, I'M GONNA DO MY--
>> I MEAN, DON'T JUST TELL ME
YOU ARE, AND THEN YOU BAIL OUT
WHEN IT GETS HARD OR SOMETHING.
>> I WON'T.
>> I THINK WE CAN DO IT.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD,
AND IT'S GONNA BE A BIG
STRUGGLE, BUT WE CAN DO IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
[chime dings]
>> I'M RELIEVED WE MADE
THE DECISION TO RAISE OUR BABY
TOGETHER.
IT WON'T BE EASY, ESPECIALLY
SINCE ZAK LIVES SO FAR AWAY
AND DOESN'T HAVE A CAR,
BUT I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
NOW THAT WE MADE A DECISION,
I CAN FINALLY FOCUS ON SCHOOL...
>> THAT BELLY IS SLOWING
YOU DOWN.
>> AND I'M EXCITED TO TELL
MY FRIENDS.
>> SO WHAT'S GOING ON WITH
YOU AND ZAK?
>> WE'RE NOT GONNA DO ADOPTION.
>> WHY AREN'T YOU GONNA DO
THE ADOPTION?
>> 'CAUSE I DECIDED I WANT
MY SON.
>> WHAT MADE YOU DECIDE THAT
YOU WANTED HIM?
>> I THINK IT WAS JUST TIME.
OVER TIME, I WAS LIKE,
"I DON'T WANT TO DO IT."
AT FIRST, I MEAN, I WAS
IN BETWEEN IT, AND, LIKE,
I DIDN'T REALLY CARE,
BUT NOW I'M LIKE,
"I WANT TO KEEP HIM."
AND I NEEDED TO MAKE UP MY MIND,
BECAUSE IT'S NOT THAT LONG.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA PAY
FOR THE BABY?
>> I HAVE, LIKE, $130.
IT'LL BE ENOUGH FOR TWO BOXES
OF DIAPERS.
>> [sighs]
>> I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
WE NEED MONEY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> ZAK AND I ARE GONNA HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT HOW WE'RE GONNA
BE ABLE TO AFFORD THIS BABY.
I'M HOPING MY MOM WILL
BE WILLING TO HELP OUT,
BUT I HAVEN'T TOLD HER ABOUT
OUR DECISION TO PARENT YET,
AND I'M WORRIED ABOUT HOW
SHE'LL REACT.
I'M NOT DOING ADOPTION.
>> SO WHAT MADE YOU CHANGE
YOUR MIND?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST CHANGED MY MIND.
>> THAT'S FINE.
IT'S YOUR BABY.
YOU CAN CHOOSE TO DO WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO WITH YOUR OWN CHILD.
YOU JUST REALIZE IT'S GONNA BE
A STRUGGLE FOR YOU, AND YOU'RE
JUST GONNA DO WHATEVER YOU CAN
TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU CAN DO
THE BEST YOU CAN.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I THINK Y'ALL GOT A LOT
OF TALKING TO DO.
HMM.
AND Y'ALL DON'T HAVE
A LOT OF TIME.
SO I MEAN, DO YOU HAVE
A PRIORITY LIST OF WHAT YOU
EXACTLY NEED RIGHT NOW
AND WHAT YOU CAN DEAL WITH
FOR LATER?
>> NO, WE--
>> OKAY, Y'ALL NEED TO COME UP
WITH A PLAN HERE OF EXACTLY
WHAT YOU NEED.
HOW MUCH DO Y'ALL HAVE
TO CONTRIBUTE TO ANY OF THIS?
>> I'M NOT SURE YET.
I HAVE $130 SOMETHING, THOUGH.
>> $130 IS NOT GONNA GO
VERY FAR.
Y'ALL GOT TO REALIZE THERE'S
GONNA BE TIMES COMING UP THAT
WE WON'T ALWAYS BE ABLE TO HELP.
I'M ALREADY IN THE HOLE
WITH KIANNA GOING TO THE DOCTOR.
Y'ALL MADE THIS SITUATION,
SO I DON'T WANT TO BE
A FINANCIAL RESPONSIBILITY
ON ME.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY
BEING A KID WITH A KID.
IT'S HARD.
IT'S A STRUGGLE.
I DID IT, SO I KNOW THAT
YOU CAN DO IT.
BUT LIKE I SAID,
IT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT.
>> TALKING TO MY MOM MADE ME
REALIZE THAT WE NEED TO START
GETTING READY FOR THIS BABY.
MY NEW SCHOOL OFFERS DAY CARE,
SO THAT'S TAKEN CARE OF,
AND WE EVEN PICKED OUT A NAME,
KAY'DEN.
WE'VE BOTH APPLIED FOR JOBS,
BUT WE HAVEN'T HEARD BACK.
MY SCHOOL HAS A PARENTING CLASS
FOR ALL THE PREGNANT STUDENTS,
AND I HAVE AN INTERESTING
HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENT.
>> HEY, KIANNA.
>> HI.
>> TODAY'S YOUR BIG DAY.
IT'S YOUR BABY DELIVERY HERE.
HERE'S YOUR GIRL.
>> YEAH.
>> HERE IN THE BABY, IT'S GOT
THE COMPUTER IN IT, AND IT
RECORDS EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS.
>> OKAY.
>> TAKE CARE OF THE BABY
LIKE IT WAS A REAL LIVE BABY.
IF YOU FAIL, YOU'LL STILL
PASS THE CLASS.
I'LL BE VERY WORRIED ABOUT
YOUR REAL BABY.
>> [laughing] YEAH.
>> I'M GONNA PUT THIS ON YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> THIS MEANS YOU'RE A MOMMY
FOR THE WEEKEND.
>> OKAY.
>> THERE'S YOUR BABY.
>> THANK YOU.
[mechanical crying]
OKAY...
THERE'S A LOT TO REMEMBER
WITH THIS BABY.
MAYBE IT WILL TEACH US
WHAT WE'RE GONNA NEED TO DO
AS PARENTS.
>> SO ARE WE REALLY TAKING THIS
TO THE RESTAURANT?
>> I HAVE TO.
IT'S MY GRADE.
>> WE SHOULD LEAVE THAT THING
IN THE CAR.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE THAT BAD,
ZAK.
>> LEAVE THE PHONE ON CALL.
>> NO, NO.
>> WHEN IT START CRYING,
WE JUST RUN OUT TO THE CAR.
>> NO, WE HAVE TO TAKE HIM--
TAKE HER WITH US.
>> NO, I'M JUST PLAYING.
CAN I HAVE A KISS?
[smacking lips]
[mechanical crying]
OH, MY GOD.
I GOT HER.
[mechanical crying]
>> HOLD HER HEAD.
>> I'M HOLDING--[chuckles]
>> [laughs]
>> STOP.
[mechanical crying]
>> ROCK HER.
>> ROCK HER?
[mechanical crying]
IT'S NOT WORKING.
>> OKAY, NOW TRY THE BOTTLE.
>> THERE WE GO.
YOU WANNA--
>> HOLD IT!
>> I MEAN, SHE'S STANDING UP.
IT'S NOT--
>> NO.
[mechanical crying]
>> OH, MY FOOD FELL TOO.
ALL RIGHT...
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'RE READY
TO HAVE A REAL BABY?
>> NO.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> ARE YOU?
>> I'LL BE READY.
>> I'M GLAD ZAK'S TRYING
TO TAKE CARE OF THIS PLAY BABY,
BUT I HOPE HE DOES A BETTER JOB
WITH OUR SON.
MY DUE DATE IS THREE WEEKS AWAY,
AND MY FEET ARE GETTING
VERY SWOLLEN.
I HAVE MY WEEKLY CHECKUP TODAY,
SO HOPEFULLY THE DOCTOR
WILL BE ABLE TO HELP ME.
>> HI, KIANNA, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> MY FEET HURT.
>> GO AHEAD AND LEAN BACK
FOR ME.
I WANT TO FEEL HOW SWOLLEN
YOUR LEGS ARE.
WOW.
OKAY.
GIRLS THAT ARE REALLY YOUNG
WHEN THEY GET PREGNANT
CAN BE AT RISK FOR LOTS OF
DIFFERENT COMPLICATIONS DURING
THE PREGNANCY.
YOU KNOW, THE CONCERN IS,
WITH ALL THE SWELLING
YOU'RE HAVING IN YOUR LEGS,
IS WHETHER OR NOT YOU'RE TRYING
TO GET PREECLAMPSIA.
>> MM-HMM.
>> SO WHAT IS PREECLAMPSIA?
>> WHAT THAT IS, IS A CONDITION
WHERE IT AFFECTS YOUR BLOOD
PRESSURE, AND IT MAKES YOU HAVE
PROTEIN IN YOUR URINE.
WOMEN SOMETIMES GET REALLY
SWOLLEN.
AND THE THING THAT'S DANGEROUS
ABOUT IT IS THAT IT CAN BE
DANGEROUS FOR YOUR BABY.
SO I THINK THAT PROBABLY
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS LET YOU DO A 24-HOUR
URINE COLLECTION AT HOME, OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WE'RE GONNA SEND YOU HOME
WITH A JUG.
YOU NEED TO KEEP IT IN A COOL,
DARK PLACE, LIKE THE FRIDGE.
>> [laughing] OKAY.
>> LABEL IT.
I KNOW.
IT'S KIND OF GROSS, HUH?
>> SO AM I ABLE TO GO TO SCHOOL?
>> NOT YET.
FIRST, WE NEED TO HAVE YOU DO
MORE LAB TESTS.
AND WE'LL DECIDE IF WE NEED
TO ADMIT YOU TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> OKAY.
>> BUT LET'S MAKE SURE YOUR
KIDNEYS ARE WORKING OKAY
AND MAKE SURE THAT THAT'S
DOING OKAY.
BUT I THINK WE CAN DO THAT
WHILE YOU'RE AT HOME, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
I'M JUST SCARED FOR EVERYTHING.
I DON'T WANT TO BE ADMITTED
INTO THE HOSPITAL.
[pan sizzling]
AFTER WE LEFT, THE DOCTOR CALLED
MY MOM AND TOLD HER THEY WERE
TESTING ME, AND IF I SHOW SIGNS
OF PREECLAMPSIA, THEY MIGHT HAVE
TO INDUCE LABOR.
>> I ASKED HER, I SAID,
"WILL THEY INDUCE HER
AUTOMATICALLY?"
AND SHE SAID THAT IT'D JUST
DEPEND ON HOW YOU DID.
IT'S NOT EVEN THAT, 'CAUSE,
YOU KNOW, IF THEY HAVE TO INDUCE
YOU, THAT MEANS THE BABY
IS GONNA BE HERE EARLIER THAN
WHAT WE WANTED.
WE DON'T HAVE THE CRIB.
I MEAN, WE NEED EXTRA
BOTTLES AND DIAPERS.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE GONNA BE RUSHING
TO TRY TO GET ALL THIS STUFF.
THAT'S WHAT WORRIES ME.
YOUR DOCTOR SAID SHE WANTED
TO PUT YOU ON HOMEBOUND,
'CAUSE YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
ON BED REST.
>> I KNOW...
I GOT TO USE THE RESTROOM.
>> GO PEE IN YOUR JUG, KIANNA.
>> IT'S GETTING HEAVY.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE A HILLBILLY.
YOU LITERALLY HAVE A PEE POT.
>> EW...
YEAH, THAT'S IN YOUR
REFRIGERATOR.
FOR THE NEXT 24 HOURS, WHILE
EVERYONE ELSE IS AT SCHOOL...
crash!
I HAVE TO STAY ON BED REST
AND FILL UP THIS JUG.
HELLO?
I KNOW YOU JUST CALLED ME,
BUT I GOT TO USE THE RESTROOM.
I'M GONNA CALL YOU BACK
WHEN I'M DONE.
[water running]
MOM, IT'S GETTING HEAVIER
AND HEAVIER.
>> THANK YOU FOR EXPRESSING THAT
TO ME.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO SEE:
A JUG FULL OF PEE.
[toilet flushing]
>> IT'S TIME TO BRING THIS JUG
BACK TO THE DOCTOR AND MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING IS HEALTHY,
BUT I HAVE TO WAIT TWO DAYS
FOR THE RESULTS.
THANK YOU.
BYE.
[phone ringing]
HELLO?
>> HI, IS THIS KIANNA?
>> YES, THIS IS HER.
>> HI, KIANNA.
I'VE JUST RECEIVED SOME OF YOUR
RESULTS FROM THE URINE TEST,
AND IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE STILL
AT RISK FOR PREECLAMPSIA,
AND SO BECAUSE OF THAT
AND THE RISK TO YOU
AND POSSIBLY THE BABY,
I THINK IT'S BEST AT THIS TIME
THAT WE DON'T WAIT ANY FURTHER,
AND WE WOULD LIKE TO JUST
INDUCE YOU.
>> MM, OKAY.
WHEN WILL I BE INDUCED?
>> WELL, I WOULD LIKE YOU
TO COME TO THE HOSPITAL
THIS AFTERNOON.
>> OKAY.
>> BYE.
>> I'M SHOWING SIGNS
OF PREECLAMPSIA, WHICH COULD
PUT ME AND MY BABY AT RISK.
SO EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT DUE
FOR THREE WEEKS, MY DOCTORS
ARE INDUCING LABOR TONIGHT.
AY-YI-YI.
>> ARE YOU SCARED?
>> YEAH, I'M SCARED AND NERVOUS.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SCARED ABOUT?
>> ON TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE,
ZAK BROKE HIS ARM DURING
FOOTBALL PRACTICE.
IT COULDN'T HAVE COME
AT A WORSE TIME.
THE DOCTORS ARE GIVING ME
PITOCIN TO GET THE PROCESS
STARTED.
>> DOING OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WANNA SQUEEZE
MY BROKEN HAND?
>> I DON'T THINK
IT'S GONNA HELP.
I'M STARTING TO FEEL
CONTRACTIONS, AND THEY
REALLY HURT.
>> IS IT COMING BACK?
>> MM-HMM.
THE PAIN IS GETTING WORSE,
BUT THE BABY IS STILL NOT READY
TO COME OUT.
THE PAIN WON'T GO AWAY
AT THE BOTTOM.
IT HURTS.
>> JUST BREATHE.
>> TAKE DEEP BREATHS.
>> YEP.
>> TRY TO SQUEEZE
THAT BABY DOWN.
SQUEEZE THAT BABY DOWN.
>> I WANT A C-SECTION
AND GET IT OVER WITH.
>> [laughs]
>> THIS WILL PROBABLY BE
THE ONLY TIME I'LL SAY,
"KIANNA, YOU WANT SOME DRUGS?"
'CAUSE YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
IT'LL MAKE IT FEEL
SO MUCH BETTER.
>> [sighs]
>> SO YOU WANT ME TO CALL
FOR PAIN MEDICINE?
WE'RE READY FOR PAIN MEDICINE.
WE NEED IT.
THANK YOU.
>> THE MEDICINE IS HELPING
WITH THE PAIN, BUT IT'S ALSO
MAKING ME KIND OF LOOPY.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU OKAY?
>> MY HEAD FEELS LIKE IT'S FREE.
[laughter]
>> WHAT DID Y'ALL DONE GIVE
THIS GIRL?
COME ON NOW.
>> LIKE I'M FLOATING.
I FEEL LIKE I'M FLOATING.
>> CAN I GET SOME OF THAT?
[laughter]
>> THE DOCTOR SAID I'M STILL NOT
DILATED ENOUGH TO START PUSHING.
SO MY MOM WENT HOME OVERNIGHT,
BUT I'M GLAD ZAK STAYED WITH ME.
>> DID YOU SLEEP?
>> NOT REALLY.
>> NEITHER DID I.
>> I'M ONLY AT 1 CENTIMETER.
I'M NOT PROGRESSING, SO...
[monitor buzzing]
I THOUGHT I'D BE FARTHER ALONG
BY THE TIME MY MOM CAME BACK
IN THE MORNING, BUT I'M STILL
NOT DILATED ENOUGH, AND I'M
GETTING REALLY FRUSTRATED.
>> THIS IS SUCH A SLOW PROCESS,
TRYING TO HAVE THIS BABY.
YOU'RE ONLY 4 CENTIMETERS
DILATED,
AND WE GOT TO GET TO A 10.
WE STILL GOT A LONG ROAD TO GO.
>> AFTER A FEW MORE HOURS
WITH NO PROGRESS, THE DOCTOR
SAID THE BABY MIGHT BE IN
DANGER.
SHE WANTS TO DO AN EMERGENCY
C-SECTION.
>> WE'RE GONNA--JUST TO BE
SURE--PREPARE FOR A C-SECTION,
OKAY?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA FEEL
ANYTHING, OKAY?
YOU'LL FEEL PEOPLE TOUCHING YOU.
YOU'LL FEEL PRESSURE.
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
>> DO YOU UNDERSTAND
WHY THEY'RE DOING THIS?
BECAUSE THE BABY IS KIND OF
IN DISTRESS, OKAY?
AND SO HIS HEART RATE
WAS DROPPING, AND HE CAN'T PASS
THROUGH THE CANAL.
AND SO HE WAS HAVING A LOT
OF SWELLING IN HIS HEAD
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT DILATING.
YOU'RE STAYING AT 4, OKAY?
SO WE CAN'T PUT HIM AT RISK
ANYMORE.
SO THE BEST THING IS FOR US
TO JUST GO AHEAD AND HAVE
A C-SECTION, OKAY?
>> Y'ALL READY?
ANYBODY WANTS TO JOIN IN?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU READY, KIANNA?
SO WE'RE BELIEVING TONIGHT,
LORD GOD, THAT YOU'RE GONNA GIVE
HER THE STRENGTH AND THE BABY
THE STRENGTH.
IN JESUS NAME, AMEN.
>> all: AMEN.
[mellow guitar music]
* *
>> * SUN SHINES *
* ALWAYS *
* *
* BESIDE YOU *
* AND INSIDE YOU *
* *
>> CAN YOU SEE HIM?
>> NOT YET.
>> * HEART BEAT *
>> 21:36.
[baby crying]
>> I HEAR HIM!
* *
[baby crying]
HE LOOKS LIKE ME?
WHO HE LOOK LIKE?
>> HE'S JUST GOT YOUR NOSE.
>> HE'S GOT A LOT OF HAIR.
* *
[chime dings]
>> RECOVERING FROM A C-SECTION
TAKES LONGER THAN WITH REGULAR
CHILDBIRTH, SO I COULDN'T GO
HOME RIGHT AWAY.
BUT IT GAVE ME A CHANCE
TO BOND WITH KAY'DEN,
AND IT GAVE MY MOM AND ZAK
SOME TIME TO GET THINGS READY
AT THE HOUSE.
>> SO, ZAK, ARE YOU READY
FOR KAY'DEN TO COME HOME?
>> YES, MA'AM.
>> HE'LL SAY, "MY DADDY
DID THIS."
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS,
AND I'M FINALLY ABLE TO LEAVE
THE HOSPITAL.
>> YOU GOT HIM OKAY?
YOU NEED ANY HELP?
>> I GOT IT.
>> OKAY, SWEETIE.
PUT YOUR SEAT BELT ON.
>> IT'S ON.
OW, THIS HURTS.
>> I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I'M TRYING NOT TO--
I MEAN, IT'S THE ROAD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO--
>> THIS TRUCK--MOM!
>> WHAT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> QUIT SCREAMING, KIANNA.
>> DID YOU NOT SEE THIS TRUCK
WAS MOVING?
>> I SEE IT.
HE WAS JUST PUTTING
HIS SIGNAL ON.
CALM DOWN.
[laughs]
>> I'M REALLY NERVOUS ABOUT
BRINGING KAY'DEN HOME.
ZAK IS IN SCHOOL ALL DAY,
AND I DON'T FEEL READY TO BE
ALONE WITH THE BABY.
GO SLOW!
>> OH...
I'VE GOT TO GET READY
TO GO TO WORK.
YOU GOT HIM?
>> YEAH.
OKAY, WELL, SEE YOU TONIGHT.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> BYE.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S JUST ME AND YOU.
JUST ME AND YOU, BUDDY.
I'M BUMMED THAT I'M ALONE
ON MY FIRST DAY HOME
FROM THE HOSPITAL,
BUT ZAK AND MY FRIENDS ARE
COMING OVER AFTER SCHOOL.
>> OH, WOW.
THAT BABY'S TINY.
>> I KNOW.
HE'S REALLY LITTLE.
>> SO WHEN ARE YOU GONNA COME
BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> I DON'T KNOW YET.
>> HEY.
>> HOW WAS IT IN THE HOSPITAL
ALL THOSE DAYS?
>> HORRIBLE.
>> DID ZAK, LIKE, BRING YOU
FOOD, OR DID HE...
>> MY MOM DID AND HIS MOM.
HE STAYED THERE ALL WEEKEND.
[knocking at door]
>> YOUR DADDY'S HERE.
>> WHEN DID YOU GET
YOUR HAIR CUT?
>> TODAY, INSTEAD OF GOING
TO SCHOOL.
>> SO, NO, YOU GOT YOUR HAIR CUT
BEFORE YOU CAME OVER HERE,
BASICALLY.
MM-MM, NO.
[laughter]
>> OOH, THEY'RE FIGHTING
OVER THE BABY.
OH, MY GOD.
[both squealing]
[baby crying]
>> HE GOT A NASTY DIAPER.
>> HE DO?
>> YEAH.
[baby crying]
GONNA FIX IT A LITTLE...
>> PULL IT DOWN SOME.
IT'S ON HIS CORD.
>> TELL 'EM TO BE QUIET.
YOU GOOD.
>> OKAY, WELL, WE BETTER
GET GOING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> BYE, HONEY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> BYE, ZAK.
>> I WANT TO MAKE THE MOST
OF MY TIME WITH ZAK.
HE HAS TO RELY ON HIS MOM
FOR RIDES, SO I WON'T SEE HIM
AGAIN TILL THE WEEKEND.
ARE YOU GONNA FEED HIM, ZAK?
>> WHO?
>> KAY'DEN.
>> YES.
>> NO, HE'S NOT HUNGRY.
>> I GOTTA GO.
>> YOU'RE WEIRD.
OVER THE FIRST WEEK,
I HAD TO GET USED TO TAKING CARE
OF KAY'DEN ALL BY MYSELF.
IT'S SO EXHAUSTING, AND I REALLY
WISH I HAD SOME HELP.
>> HELLO?
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WILL YOUR MAMA BRING YOU
OVER HERE?
>> I DOUBT IT.
SHE DON'T GET OFF UNTIL LATE.
>> OKAY.
YOU READY?
>> [fussing]
>> YEAH, IT'S COLD.
I KNOW.
I HAVE ANOTHER MONTH BEFORE
I GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
I DON'T WANT TO FALL BEHIND,
BUT KEEPING UP WITH MY HOMEWORK
WHILE TAKING CARE OF A NEWBORN
ISN'T EASY.
[baby crying]
AH...
AND AT NIGHT, IT ONLY GETS
HARDER...
NO, NO, NO.
AND LONELIER.
I'M GONNA PUT YOU TO SLEEP.
[baby grunts]
[baby crying]
COME ON.
NO, DON'T DO THAT.
[phone playing hip-hop song]
HELLO?
>> HELLO?
>> MMM...
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I WAS ASLEEP--WAKE UP...
>> WHAT YOU SAY?
>> I'M TIRED.
>> BYE.
THIS IS WAY HARDER THAN
I WAS EXPECTING, AND I'M GOING
TO NEED MORE HELP FROM ZAK.
>> HOW'S IT BEEN GOING
WHEN I BE AT SCHOOL?
>> IT'S KIND OF HARD.
I WAKE UP THREE TIMES A NIGHT
AT LEAST.
I PROBABLY LOSE FIVE HOURS
OF SLEEP.
IT'S TIRING.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN LISTENING TO ME.
>> I SWEAR TO GOD,
I HEARD YOU.
>> THEN WHY ARE YOU NOT TALKING?
>> I AM, GIRL.
I'M PLAYING WITH KAY'DEN.
[baby crying]
SAY, "MOMMY, CHILL OUT.
MOMMY, CHILL OUT."
OOH, BOY, THAT'S WHY YOU CRYING.
>> ZAK, IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
>> YEAH, IT IS THAT BAD.
>> ZAK, KEEP THE DIAPER--
KEEP THE DIAPER UNDER THERE.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO STAY UNDER
HIS BUTT UNTIL YOU'RE DONE.
DO YOU NOT KNOW HOW TO DO THIS,
ZAK?
>> I'M NOT USED TO IT.
ALL DONE.
>> LOOK, IT'S BAD.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY IT SMELLED
LIKE POOP TO ME.
>> ZAK...
>> [buzzes lips]
>> I THINK, WHEN I GO BACK
TO SCHOOL, IT'S GONNA GET HARDER
THAN IT IS NOW, BECAUSE YOU KNOW
HOW I'M ALREADY TIRED?
I'M SCARED.
>> MAYBE HE HAS BROWN EYES.
>> ZAK, YOU'RE NOT LISTENING
TO NOTHING I'M SAYING!
>> I CAN MULTITASK.
>> IT'S NOT EASY.
>> I KNOW.
NOTHING'S EVER EASY.
>> I'M WORRIED THAT ZAK DOESN'T
REALLY UNDERSTAND HOW HARD
IT'S GOING TO BE FOR ME
TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
AND TO MAKE THINGS WORSE,
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN COUNT ON MY MOM'S SUPPORT.
>> KIANNA, THESE ARE THE ONLY
BOTTLES THEY HAD.
THESE LITTLE THINGS
ARE EXPENSIVE.
THAT LITTLE BIT OF TUB OF MILK
WAS $12.
HOW MUCH IS ALL THAT TOGETHER
THAT YOU OWE ME?
>> IT'S, LIKE, $25, $30.
>> WHAT DO YOU PLAN ON DOING?
YOU LOOKING FOR A JOB OR WHAT?
>> YEAH.
>> FIND A JOB TO GET YOU SOME
REAL MONEY COMING IN.
>> OKAY, I CAN DO THAT, MOM.
>> YOU TELL ME THAT,
BUT YOU HAVEN'T DONE IT YET,
AND YOU WASTED ALL THIS TIME.
>> WHY DO YOU KEEP SAYING THAT?
>> 'CAUSE I'M NOT BELIEVING YOU.
Y'ALL NEED TO STAY FOCUSED
AND NOT BE LOSING PRIORITIES
HERE.
>> I DECIDED AGAINST ADOPTION
BECAUSE I THOUGHT I COULD
HANDLE IT WITHOUT ZAK
BEING AROUND MUCH.
I DON'T REGRET KEEPING KAY'DEN,
BUT I CAN'T DO THIS WITHOUT
MORE HELP.
>> IT'S TOUGHER THAN I THOUGHT
NOT HAVING ZAK AROUND DURING
THE WEEK, AND IT'S ABOUT TO GET
EVEN HARDER, BECAUSE TODAY,
I'M GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
HELLO.
MAMA HAS TO GET READY.
KAY'DEN IS GOING TO DAY CARE
WHILE I'M IN CLASS.
IT'S GOING TO BE REALLY HARD
TO BE APART FROM HIM ALL DAY.
>> GOOD MORNING.
HI.
>> MWAH!
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, WE PROMISE
TO TAKE GOOD CARE OF HIM.
>> I KNOW.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE GREAT
TO SEE MY FRIENDS TODAY,
BUT I'M EXHAUSTED, AND IT'S HARD
TO ADMIT HOW OVERWHELMED I FEEL.
>> HOW ARE THINGS GOING AT HOME?
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> DO YOU SLEEP OFTEN?
>> I TRY.
>> YOU GOT TO SLEEP WHEN
KAY'DEN SLEEPS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WITH ALL THE DIAPER BUYING
AND FOOD, WHERE DO YOU GET,
LIKE, THE MONEY TO DO ALL THAT?
>> MY MOM HELPS OUT A LOT.
AND THEN, LIKE, SHE DOESN'T
HAVE MONEY AS IT IS, AND SHE
STILL DOES IT.
>> IS ZAK NOT HELPING HER
WITH IT OR ANYTHING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BUT HE SHOULD BE.
>> SO ARE YOU HAPPY?
>> IT'S NOT THE SAME
AS IT USED TO BE.
IT'S DIFFERENT.
IT'S NOT MISERABLE OR NOTHING.
BUT I WISH THAT ZAK WAS AROUND
MORE.
>> YEAH.
>> NOW THAT I'M BACK IN SCHOOL,
IT'S EVEN MORE IMPORTANT
FOR ZAK TO HELP ME OUT
WITH THE BABY.
HOPEFULLY THIS TIME,
HE'LL LISTEN TO ME.
DURING THE WEEK, I WISH YOU WERE
THERE, BECAUSE IT'S HARDER
THAN WHEN YOU'RE NOT THERE.
LIKE, MY DAYS ARE HARDER,
BECAUSE I WAKE UP EARLIER,
LIKE, AT 6:00, AND I FEED
KAY'DEN, AND SOMETIMES,
AFTER I FEED HIM, HE DOESN'T
WANT TO GO BACK TO SLEEP.
SO I'M SITTING THERE
TRYING TO MAKE HIM GO TO SLEEP.
I JUST THINK THAT, LIKE,
I GET MAD SOMETIMES
BECAUSE I'M TIRED,
BECAUSE OF ALL THE THINGS
THAT I'M DOING AT THE HOUSE
BY MYSELF, AND THAT MAKES ME
ANGRY.
>> I HELP OUT THE WAY I CAN.
>> I KNOW YOU HELP OUT
THE WAY YOU CAN.
>> IF I COULD BE THERE
EVERY DAY...
>> YOU WOULD BE THERE.
>> YEAH.
SO IT'S NOT LIKE I'M NOT DOING
NOTHING AT ALL.
>> I KNOW, BUT THEN EVEN THOUGH
IT'S JUST ME AND THE BABY,
I WISH THAT YOU COULD BE THERE
WITH US 24/7 TOO, LIKE,
SO WE COULD BE A FAMILY,
INSTEAD OF JUST BEING A FAMILY
JUST ON THE WEEKENDS.
>> * AS I WALK *
* ABOVE THE PAIN *
* I CAN FEEL YOU *
* WALKING WITH ME *
* CARRYING ME *
>> I HOPE THAT IN THE FUTURE,
THAT ME AND ZAK, WE CAN STAY
TOGETHER AND WE CAN RAISE
KAY'DEN HOW HE SHOULD BE RAISED.
>> "DADDY'S CHANGED ME WEIRD."
>> [laughs]
HE WANTS TO BE HERE FOR THE BABY
BECAUSE HE KNOWS HOW HARD IT IS
WITHOUT A FATHER.
WITH ZAK NOT HAVING A JOB,
IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE HE CAN'T
REALLY SUPPORT US FINANCIALLY.
HE IS NOT ABLE TO SIT THERE
AND GIVE US MONEY, SO I FEEL
LIKE HE NEEDS TO GET A JOB
AS SOON AS HE CAN.
>> HE'S 16.
IS HE LOOKING FOR A JOB
FOR SURE?
DO YOU SEE HIM FILL THINGS OUT?
>> NOT YET.
SINCE HAVING THE BABY, MY LIFE
HAS CHANGED IN MANY WAYS.
BASICALLY, I AM ON MY OWN.
>> YOU DO HAVE SEVERAL ABSENCES
SO FAR FROM THIS SCHOOL YEAR
ALREADY.
HOPEFULLY YOUR ATTENDANCE
WILL BE A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
>> YEAH, IT WILL.
MY MAIN GOAL RIGHT NOW
IS TO GRADUATE HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I DON'T WANT HAVING A BABY
TO STOP ME FROM GRADUATING.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S HARD FOR ME
TO SIT HERE AND WAKE UP EVERY
MORNING AND GO TO SCHOOL
AND WORK VERY HARD,
I'M GONNA DO IT REGARDLESS.
I DO WISH THAT ME AND ZAK
WOULD HAVE WAITED
OR BEEN MORE RESPONSIBLE,
SO THAT WE COULD STILL HAVE
OUR TEENAGE LIVES.
I MISS YOU.
LIKE, IT WAS ALWAYS ME AND YOU
ALL THE TIME.
NOW IT'S, LIKE, I DON'T EVEN GET
TO REALLY SEE YOU OR TALK
TO YOU.
I WASN'T READY TO HAVE A BABY.
I DON'T THINK MY LIFE
WAS IN PLACE IN ORDER
FOR ME TO HAVE A BABY.
>> YOU LOOK SO TIRED.
WHY ARE YOU SO TIRED?
>> 'CAUSE I AM TIRED.
BEEN UP ALL DAY.
I HOPE THAT I CAN ACHIEVE
MY GOALS LIKE GOING TO COLLEGE,
GETTING MY VETERINARY MEDICINE
LICENSE, STAYING WITH ZAK,
AND RAISING A GOOD, HEALTHY BOY.
JUST CONTINUE TO WORK HARD
IN LIFE AND MAKE THE BEST OF IT.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> SO I'M GUESSING YOU'RE MOM
WASN'T REALLY HAPPY ABOUT IT.
>> NO, SHE WASN'T HAPPY AT ALL.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU GIVE
THE CHILD UP FOR ADOPTION.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE IDEA.
>> KIDS SHOULD NOT HAVE KIDS.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE A BABY
IN LESS THAN 24 HOURS.
OH, MY GOD.
>> I DO EVERYTHING AROUND HERE.
>> YOU TAKE OUT TRASH.
>> SHUT UP.
GOD, YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
>> HE NEEDS TO STEP UP AND BE
A BETTER DAD.
>> THE ONLY REASON WE STAY
TOGETHER IS BECAUSE OF HER.