[chime dings]
>> HEY, I'M LINDSEY.
I'M 16, AND I LIVE
IN RENO, NEVADA.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM
AND SHARE A ROOM
WITH MY YOUNGER SISTER,
RICKI LEE.
THE PLACE IS SO SMALL THAT WE
EVEN HAVE TO SHARE A BED.
>> I ALSO HAVE TWO OLDER
SISTERS, DALLAS AND LACEY.
AND EVEN THOUGH
THEY DON'T LIVE WITH US,
WE HANG OUT ALL THE TIME.
>> [laughs]
>> I'M REALLY CLOSE WITH MY MOM,
BUT SHE CAN BE KIND OF
HARD ON ME.
>> THAT'S WAY OVER YOUR PRICE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> THAT'S MY POINT.
>> I'VE BEEN WITH MY BOYFRIEND,
FOREST, FOR THREE YEARS,
AND WE'VE DEFINITELY HAD
OUR ISSUES.
WE'VE BEEN ON,
THEN OFF...
WELL, IF HE DOESN'T CALL ME
BACK, I'LL BE REALLY UPSET.
THEN ON AGAIN.
BUT WE'RE DOING OKAY NOW,
EXCEPT HE DOESN'T HAVE A JOB.
AND I WISH HE'D GET HIS ACT
TOGETHER.
I'M STARTING MY SENIOR YEAR OF
HIGH SCHOOL IN THE FALL...
[chime dings]
AND I PLAN ON GOING TO COLLEGE
AND BECOMING A POLICE DETECTIVE.
BUT THAT'S NOT MY ONLY DREAM.
I'M ALSO TRAINING TO BECOME A
PROFESSIONAL CAGE FIGHTER
AND A MODEL.
BUT ACHIEVING ALL MY DREAMS IS
ABOUT TO GET A LOT HARDER,
BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
I'M ON SUMMER BREAK.
AND SINCE THE BABY IS DUE
IN FOUR MONTHS, I'VE BEEN
WORKING LONG HOURS AT A
FAST-FOOD RESTAURANT
TO SAVE MONEY.
SO IT'S NICE WHEN I HAVE
A DAY OFF.
[laughter]
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED?
HOW'D YOU GET PREGNANT?
>> WELL, YOU HAVE SEX.
>> YOU KNOW, THE REASON WHY THEY
MAKE CONDOMS IS SO THAT WAY YOU
CAN DO IT WITHOUT
ENDING UP WITH A...
>> both: BABY.
>> WE WOULD USE THEM A LOT.
LIKE, WE REALLY DID.
AND THEN--
>> YOU GUYS JUST STOPPED?
>> LIKE, WE--ONE TIME, WE DID IT
BEFORE WITHOUT A CONDOM,
AND WE NEVER GOT PREGNANT.
SO I KIND OF THOUGHT THAT I
COULDN'T GET PREGNANT FOR
SOME REASON.
>> THAT ONE TIME--
>> WHATEVER IT DID, CHANGED
YOUR WHOLE ENTIRE LIFE.
>> YEAH.
SO THEN I JUST TOLD FOREST,
AND HE WAS JUST LIKE,
"ARE YOU SERIOUS?"
FOREST TOLD ME
TO GET AN ABORTION.
>> HOW'D YOU FEEL?
YOU PROBABLY, LIKE, BROKE DOWN,
HUH?
>> WHEN I GOT HOME AND I WENT
TO SLEEP, I, LIKE, CRIED.
IT'S SO SCARY.
YOU JUST CAN'T HELP IT.
>> ARE YOU SCARED HE'S NOT GONNA
BE THERE?
>> I KNOW HIM.
HE'S A BIG TEDDY BEAR.
YEAH, IF YOU'RE GROWN
ENOUGH TO MAKE ONE--
>> STICK IT IN, YOU BETTER BE
GROWN ENOUGH TO--
>> STICK IT OUT.
[laughter]
>> OR SOMETHING.
>> MY MOM WAS DEVASTATED WHEN
SHE FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT.
AND LIKE FOREST, SHE WANTED ME
TO GET AN ABORTION.
BUT NOW THAT I'M FIVE MONTHS
ALONG, SHE'S COMING AROUND AND
DOING HER BEST TO BE SUPPORTIVE.
>> I WANTED YOU TO HAVE AN
ABORTION, LINDSEY,
BECAUSE I WANT YOU TO DO MORE.
>> WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
>> I WANT YOU TO BE ABLE TO
REACH YOUR GOALS.
YOU WANT TO BE A DETECTIVE.
IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
>> SEE, YOU'RE JUST DOUBTING ME
ALL THE TIME, SO WHATEVER.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO DOUBT YOU.
I'M TRYING TO MAKE YOU REALIZE
HOW HARD IT'S REALLY GONNA BE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> BUT YOU ACT LIKE IT'S ALL
IMPOSSIBLE, AND YOU JUST MAKE IT
SEEM LIKE IT'S YOUR WAY
OR THE HIGHWAY.
>> LINDSEY, IF IT WAS MY WAY OR
THE HIGHWAY, I WOULDN'T BE
SUPPORTING YOU LIKE I HAVE THE
LAST COUPLE OF MONTHS.
IT DOES FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA BE
HAVING THE BABY, BECAUSE I KNOW
I'M GONNA END UP TAKING CARE OF
IT A LOT MORE THAN I WANT TO.
>> WELL, THEN YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
LIKE, YOU--
>> BUT THAT'S THE THING,
LINDSEY.
I KNOW I WILL, BECAUSE THAT'S
WHO I AM.
>> I KNOW, BUT IF YOU'RE GONNA
JUST BITCH ABOUT ME AND TELL ME
ALL THE NEGATIVE ASPECTS EVERY
TIME I TALK ABOUT IT, THEN I
DON'T HAVE TO BE HERE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE HERE.
I COULD LEAVE.
>> YOU ARE 16 YEARS OLD.
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU GO OUT
ON YOUR OWN AND BE WORRIED ABOUT
YOU.
>> I KNOW MY MOM WANTS ME TO
STAY WITH HER, BUT THAT'S NOT
GONNA BE EASY IF SHE KEEPS
MAKING ME FEEL GUILTY ABOUT MY
DECISION.
ALSO, MY MOM'S HOUSE IS REALLY
SMALL AND ABOUT A HALF HOUR AWAY
FROM FOREST, WHICH MAKES IT
REALLY HARD FOR US TO SPEND TIME
TOGETHER.
[chime dings]
WHEN I TOLD FOREST I WAS KEEPING
THE BABY, HE WAS REALLY UPSET.
AND WE BROKE UP FOR A FEW
MONTHS.
BUT NOW WE'RE BACK TOGETHER,
AND HE'S STARTING TO GET USED TO
THE IDEA OF BEING A DAD.
WE EVEN PICKED OUT A NAME FOR
HER, ANIYAH.
SO WHEN I FIRST TOLD YOU I WAS
PREGNANT, YOU WERE,
LIKE, FURIOUS.
YOU WANTED NOTHING TO DO WITH ME
AND ALL THAT.
AND ALL YOU WANTED WAS ME TO
GET OUT OF YOUR SIGHT AND FOR ME
TO GET AN ABORTION.
>> IT SEEMED AS IF YOU GOT
PREGNANT TO KIND OF TIE ME DOWN.
AND I DIDN'T THINK IT'D BE
HEALTHY AT ALL FOR OUR
RELATIONSHIP, IF WE WERE TRYING,
FOR ME TO FELT FORCED INTO
SOMETHING THAT, LIKE--
THAT WASN'T EVEN THERE YET.
>> I REALLY DID NOT THINK IT
WOULD HAPPEN, AND THEN,
WHEN WE LEAST EXPECTED IT,
IT HAPPENED.
JUST--IT'S SO EASY FOR EVERYBODY
ELSE TO SAY, "OH, YEAH.
JUST GO GET AN ABORTION."
AND IT'S LIKE,
"LIKE, WHO ARE YOU TO TELL ME TO
GET AN ABORTION?"
>> WELL, EVERYONE WAS JUST
FREAKED OUT TRYING TO MAKE THE
SMARTEST DECISION FOR YOU.
>> BUT REALLY, IT'S MY LIFE, AND
I KNOW IT DOES HAVE, LIKE--
HAVE A BIG EFFECT ON OTHER
PEOPLE.
>> AT FIRST, I WAS SO SCARED,
I DIDN'T WANT TO THINK ABOUT IT.
AND THEN I KIND OF GOT
USED TO IT.
AND THEN MY GRANDMA AND MY AUNT
BROUGHT OVER SOME, LIKE,
BABY CHAIRS.
AND THEN IT REALLY HIT ME AGAIN.
AND I WAS SCARED.
I ALMOST WANTED TO FAINT.
>> WELL, IF YOU JUST TRY
AND WE BOTH PUT IN AN EFFORT,
THEN WE COULD BE HAPPIER.
YAY!
>> I GUESS I GOT TO START BUYING
DIAPERS RIGHT NOW.
>> SO THEN WE DON'T HAVE TO BE
ALL STRESSED.
>> AND GET TO BUY CLOTHES,
ALL THAT.
>> AW, YAY!
[giggles]
IT'S NICE TO SEE FOREST AT LEAST
A LITTLE EXCITED ABOUT
THE BABY FOR ONCE.
BUT IT'D BE EVEN BETTER IF HE'D
STEP UP AND GET A JOB.
[chime dings]
I'VE HAD TO MAKE SACRIFICES TOO.
I USED TO SPEND MY SUMMERS
TRAINING FOR CAGE FIGHTING
MATCHES AND HANGING WITH
FRIENDS, BUT IT'S TOTALLY
DIFFERENT NOW THAT I'M PREGNANT.
>> WATCHING THE BASEBALL GAME.
WHOO!
[laughs]
ARE YOU STILL CAGE FIGHTING?
>> NO, RIGHT NOW I CAN'T,
BECAUSE IT'S TOO MUCH OF A RISK.
SO AS MUCH AS I WANT TO STILL
CONTINUE CAGE FIGHTING, I NEED
TO PUT IT ON HOLD FOR AWHILE.
AND THE BABY COMES FIRST.
AND AS MUCH AS, LIKE, I WANT TO
GO PRO AS SOON AS I'M 18,
NOW THAT'S PUT OFF, LIKE,
ANOTHER YEAR OR TWO.
>> SO WHAT DID YOUR TRAINER SAY
WHEN YOU GOT PREGNANT
AND HAD TO STOP?
>> UM, I ACTUALLY HAVEN'T EVEN
TOLD MY TRAINER YET.
>> YOU'RE STOPPED?
>> YEAH, I--'CAUSE HE'S LIKE A
FATHER FIGURE TO ME, AND I WAS,
LIKE, AFRAID OF WHAT
HE WOULD SAY.
>> ARE YOU EVER GONNA TELL HIM?
>> WELL, I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO
TELL HIM, BECAUSE ONCE I START
TRAINING AGAIN, I THINK IT WOULD
BE WAY MORE AWKWARD IF I JUST
SHOW UP WITH, LIKE,
A LITTLE BABY.
AND THEY'RE GONNA BE LIKE,
"WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
AND WHAT IS THAT BABY?"
I DON'T WANT HIM TO THINK I JUST
FLAKED OUT AND GAVE UP.
I CAN'T CAGE FIGHT.
I CAN'T HUNT.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING THAT I
NORMALLY WOULD DO.
>> THAT SUCKS.
>> OH, I'M GONNA GET TEARS
IN MY EYES.
>> DON'T.
THEN I'M GONNA CRY.
STOP IT.
I'M SERIOUS, STOP.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE TALKING
ABOUT IT, BECAUSE IT'S, LIKE,
STILL EMOTIONAL.
[sniffles]
>> MY MOM KNOWS HOW SAD I'VE
BEEN ABOUT MISSING OUT ON CAGE
FIGHTING, SO SHE'S CONVINCED ME
TO GO OUT TONIGHT
AND SEE A MATCH.
THE SHIRT LOOKS FINE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO WHEN
YOU GET THERE?
ARE YOU GONNA SAY HI TO THE
OTHER GUYS THAT YOU TRAIN WITH
AND EVERYTHING?
>> NO.
>> NO? WHY NOT?
>> I'M NOT TALKING TO ANYBODY.
>> LINDSEY, THEY'RE GONNA
SEE YOU.
YOU CAN'T HIDE.
YEAH, I THINK YOU SHOULD JUST
ACT LIKE LINDSEY
AND NOT BE ASHAMED.
>> I'M NOT ASHAMED.
I WANT TO BE THE ONE
TO TELL RICK.
>> I JUST THINK YOU'RE BEING
UNREALISTIC.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TURN THIS
INTO AN ARGUMENT.
>> I'M NOT TURNING IT
I'M JUST TRYING TO MAKE YOU
FACE THE FACTS.
>> OKAY, WELL--
>> YOU NEED TO STOP GETTING MAD.
IT'S NOT YOUR MOM'S FAULT THAT
SHE KEEPS ASKING YOU THAT
QUESTION.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SAID YOU DON'T WANT
SOMEONE ELSE TO TELL HIM,
AND THAT'S WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN, DUDE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> LIKE, HE DOES NOT NEED TO
WORRY ABOUT ME BEING PREGNANT.
THAT IS SO RUDE.
>> I THINK HE'D BE MORE EXCITED
TO SEE YOU THAN WORRIED ABOUT
YOU BEING PREGNANT.
>> NO, IF HE SAW ME PREGNANT,
TRUST ME, HE WOULD NOT BE
EXCITED TO SEE ME.
[chanting "Diesel"]
I DIDN'T RUN INTO ANYONE FROM MY
FIGHTING DAYS, BUT NOW I REALLY
MISS TRAINING.
AND MY MOM KEEPS REMINDING ME
THAT THE LONGER I KEEP MY
PREGNANCY A SECRET, THE HARDER
IT'S GONNA BE FOR ME
TO START UP AGAIN.
>> ALL I'M SAYING IS THAT YOU
ARE STILL A KID.
AND I THINK YOU NEED TO RESPECT
AND APPRECIATE YOUR MOM A LITTLE
BIT MORE.
>> NEVER MIND.
THIS IS JUST TURNING INTO
AN ARGUMENT.
THAT'S WHY I HATE TALKING
TO YOU.
>> SO...
>> THE CONVERSATION'S OVER.
>> YEAH, THE CONVERSATION
IS OVER.
AND WE'RE GONNA BE HAVING
ANOTHER CONVERSATION SOON.
>> WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
WHY DO YOU GET ALL MAD?
MY MOM'S BEEN ON MY CASE LATELY,
SO I'VE BEEN SPENDING A LOT OF
TIME AT FOREST'S HOUSE.
AND SOMETIMES, I FEEL LIKE IT
WOULD MAKE SENSE FOR ME TO JUST
LIVE HERE.
>> WHY ARE YOU DOING THE DISHES?
>> BECAUSE I'M NESTING.
>> I'M, LIKE, PREPARING FOR THE
BABY.
SO IT'S CRAZY HOW OUR
RELATIONSHIP HAS BEEN,
THIS WHOLE TIME THAT I'VE BEEN
PREGNANT--
>> YEAH.
>> EVERY--EVERY DAY, LIKE,
EVERY HOUR, I WAS JUST--
I JUST KEPT, LIKE, PICTURING US
LIKE A LITTLE HAPPY FAMILY.
AND I WAS LIKE, "I KNOW
WE CAN DO IT."
IF I MOVE IN, I THINK IT'LL BE
THE BEST THING FOR OUR FAMILY.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BENEFIT US A
LOT, ESPECIALLY MONEY-WISE.
>> YEAH, BECAUSE THEN WE WON'T
HAVE TO BUY TWO OF EVERYTHING.
>> DIAPERS FOR ME,
DIAPERS FOR YOU.
>> AND JUST, IT'S UNSTABLE
FOR ME.
>> YEAH.
>> AND ANIYAH.
I DON'T WANT ANIYAH TO--
>> BE GOING BACK AND FORTH.
>> YEAH, LIKE, I WANT HER TO
KNOW SHE HAS A HOME.
IT'S A BIG STEP
TO MOVE OUT OF MY HOME
WITH A GUY,
WITH A BABY FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> WELL, NOW THAT ANIYAH IS IN
THE PICTURE,
IT'S EVEN MORE IMPORTANT.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE A STRONG
FAMILY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> NOT ONE THAT JUST--
>> BACK AND FORTH AND DON'T KNOW
IF WE WANT TO BE TOGETHER.
>> ALWAYS...
>> both: FIGHTING.
>> YEAH.
WELL, THERE'S A LOT MORE PROS...
>> THAN CONS.
REGARDLESS OF WHERE I'M GONNA
LIVE, WE HAVE TO START FIGURING
OUT WHAT WE NEED FOR ANIYAH.
>> DO YOU NEED ANY ASSISTANCE?
SO HOW MUCH ARE YOU LOOKING
TO SPEND?
>> UM, I THINK FOR, LIKE, ALL
THE SLEEPING MATERIAL,
I'D SPEND, LIKE, $200.
>> AND THAT'S GONNA BE TOUGH TO
GET INTO.
>> OKAY, SO I'VE BEEN TAKING
NOTES, LIKE, TO SEE--
TO GET ORGANIZED.
AND THE BASSINET WOULD BE
$25 TO $80, THE CRIB ABOUT $200,
THE STROLLER, $60,
THE CLOTHES, $55,
AND THE PLAY SEAT
ABOUT $60.
>> MM-HMM.
AND THEN YOU WOULD NEED THE,
UM, CAR SEAT AS WELL.
>> OH, YEAH, DEFINITELY.
AND CAR SEATS, HOW MUCH?
>> BETWEEN $100 AND $200,
DEPENDING.
>> JUST ON A LITTLE CAR SEAT?
>> YEAH.
[laughs]
>> OH, WOW.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
SO ALMOST, LIKE, $500
JUST FOR THAT STUFF.
IT'S A LOT MORE THAN I PLANNED
TO SPEND JUST ON THAT.
NOW I NEED TO WORK MORE,
A LOT MORE.
[laughs]
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT.
GETTING READY FOR THE BABY IS
GOING TO COST WAY MORE THAN I
THOUGHT.
AND MY PAYCHECK FROM WORK ISN'T
REALLY GONNA CUT IT.
SO FOREST AND I ARE GONNA HAVE
TO WORK TOGETHER.
>> WHAT DO WE STILL NEED
FOR THE BABY?
ARE YOU LOOKING AT, LIKE,
THE CRIB, OR WHAT?
>> WELL, WE STILL NEED A LOT
ACTUALLY, LIKE, A LOT,
ALMOST EVERYTHING.
WE HAVE THE MONEY TO GET
THE CRIB, SO THAT'S THE NUMBER
ONE THING WE NEED TO GET.
WE NEED MORE CLOTHES, BOTTLES.
THERE'S A LOT.
>> OH, WE GOT A LOT OF STUFF TO
STILL BUY.
>> AND TIME IS ALMOST UP.
>> OH, NO.
HOW MUCH LONGER,
TWO MORE MONTHS?
>> YEAH.
THAT'S IF WE'RE LUCKY.
YOU HAVE TO GET A JOB,
BECAUSE...
I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO WORK
FOR SIX WEEKS AFTER
THE BABY'S BORN.
>> YEAH.
I'M GLAD FOREST IS WILLING TO
GET A JOB, AND IT MAKES ME FEEL
GOOD ABOUT MOVING IN WITH HIM.
BUT I'M NOT SO SURE MY FAMILY IS
GOING TO LIKE IT.
SO I'M THINKING OF TO MOVE IN
WITH FOREST.
>> WHY DO YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
>> MY ROOM IS KIND OF TOO SMALL
AT MOM'S HOUSE TO HAVE A CRIB
AND A BASSINET AND EVERYTHING
ELSE YOU NEED FOR A BABY.
AND THEN ON TOP OF THAT,
WE'RE GONNA NEED TO HAVE DOUBLE
OF EVERYTHING.
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE WE'RE HAVING
TWINS.
SO WHY NOT JUST LIVE TOGETHER
AND BE ABLE TO BUY ONE OF
EVERYTHING WE NEED?
>> SO HAVE YOU TOLD MOM YOUR
PLANS, WHAT YOU'RE WANTING
TO DO?
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> YOU BETTER TELL MOM SOON.
>> I'M ALREADY GONNA HAVE
STRESS OF A BABY AND COMPLETING
SCHOOL AND EVERYTHING ELSE.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR SOMEBODY
BITCH ABOUT ME AND MY DAUGHTER
LIVING SOMEWHERE.
>> DOES FOREST HAVE A JOB YET?
IS HE LOOKING FOR JOB?
>> YEAH, HE NEEDS TO GET A JOB.
>> YOU CAN'T TAKE CARE OF A BABY
AND YOURSELF FROM WORKING AT
MCDONALD'S.
I HOPE THAT, YOU KNOW, THE BABY
WILL MAKE HIM REALIZE THAT THIS
IS REAL LIFE, AND YOU DO HAVE TO
STEP UP, BUT THAT'S NOT ALWAYS
THE CASE.
>> I JUST WANT THINGS TO WORK
OUT SO MUCH THAT, LIKE--
I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE A FEELING THEY WILL.
>> IT'S BEEN A WEEK SINCE FOREST
SAID HE'D GET A JOB, AND HE
STILL HASN'T STARTED LOOKING.
IT'S FRUSTRATING, BECAUSE I'VE
BEEN WORKING A LOT OF LONG
SHIFTS, SOME OF THEM STARTING
AT 6:00 A.M.
[chime dings]
AND WHILE I'M SEVEN MONTHS
PREGNANT AND WORKING, FOREST
WOULD RATHER LAY AROUND ALL DAY.
AND I'M STARTING TO GET A LITTLE
WORRIED.
THANK YOU FOR DINNER, DORA.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
FOREST ASKED ME IF HE COULD--
>> WE SHOULD.
>> IT'S JUST NICE HAVING
YOU HERE.
IT'S--AND THE HELP.
YOU HELP ME WITH THE DISHES.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
I ENJOY BEING HERE.
I KNOW, LIKE, I'VE BEEN THE ONLY
ONE WORKING.
ARE YOU GONNA GET A JOB?
>> YES, I'M GONNA GET A JOB,
BUT--
>> NOT NOW.
NOT UNTIL HE'S DONE WITH SCHOOL.
I DON'T WANT HIM WORKING AND
GOING TO SCHOOL AND BEING A DAD
AND TRYING TO DO HOMEWORK.
I THINK THAT'S TOO MUCH
ON HIS PLATE.
SO...
>> I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE WORKING
AT FAST-FOOD, FLIPPING BURGERS
OR ANYTHING, BECAUSE...
>> BUT I MEAN, AT LEAST
I BRING HOME A CHECK.
>> BUT THAT'S ALSO WHY
YOU CAN LIVE HERE,
BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU--
>> WELL, YEAH--
>> SO THAT YOU CAN STAY IN
SCHOOL, AND YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORK.
>> AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THE
THING IS--IS WE'RE GONNA, WHAT?
STRUGGLE A LITTLE BIT UNTIL THE
TIME I GET A JOB IN SUMMER,
AND THEN I'LL HAVE, LIKE,
DIPLOMA.
I CAN GET A GOOD JOB
AND NOT JUST SOMETHING STUPID.
I CAN ACTUALLY GET THE MONEY TO
SUPPORT A FAMILY,
NOT JUST SOMETHING THAT CAN HELP
OUR FOOD ON THE TABLE.
>> I'M REALLY NOT HAPPY THAT
FOREST ISN'T GOING TO GET A JOB.
[chime dings]
AND AFTER I LEFT HIS HOUSE, WE
ARGUED ON THE PHONE FOR AWHILE.
AND IT ENDED WITH HIM
HANGING UP ON ME.
IT SUCKS THAT WE'RE FIGHTING
AGAIN AFTER WE WERE DOING SO
WELL FOR AWHILE.
AND THE TIMING COULDN'T BE ANY
WORSE, BECAUSE LATER THAT NIGHT,
SOMETHING FELT WEIRD.
MOM!
>> WHAT?
>> COME DOWN HERE.
>> WHAT'S UP, SWEETHEART?
>> I THINK I'M HAVING
CONTRACTIONS.
LET'S GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
OKAY?
HERE, HONEY.
>> [groans]
MY DUE DATE IS TWO MONTHS AWAY,
SO I'M REALLY WORRIED,
AND FOREST WON'T ANSWER
HIS PHONE.
[line ringing]
WHEN I TOLD THE HOSPITAL STAFF
I WAS HAVING CONTRACTIONS,
THEY ADMITTED ME.
AND IT'S REALLY SCARY TO THINK I
MIGHT GO INTO LABOR THIS EARLY.
>> SIT DOWN.
AND DO THIS.
NOW I'M FINALLY GETTING
NERVOUS.
>> [sighs]
THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE 61 DAYS
LEFT.
FOREST HASN'T CALLED YET.
>> I'M STILL IN THE HOSPITAL
WAITING TO FIND OUT IF THESE
CONTRACTIONS MEAN I COULD BE
GOING INTO LABOR EARLY.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU?
HOW--DO YOU FEEL CRAMPY?
>> YEAH, AND I FEEL HOT.
AND I JUST DON'T FEEL GOOD.
>> OKAY.
SO YOU'RE AT RISK
FOR PRETERM LABOR.
SO I'M GONNA MONITOR YOUR BABY,
SEE IF YOU'RE HAVING ANY
CONTRACTIONS, AND WE'LL GET YOU
THAT SHOT.
>> TOMORROW?
>> TOMORROW, YEAH.
>> WHAT EXACTLY IS,
LIKE, THE SHOT?
WHAT IS IT--
>> IT'S CALLED BETAMETHASONE.
AND IT'S A STEROID.
AND IT'S USED TO HELP DEVELOP
THE BABY'S LUNGS.
IF YOU DELIVER BEFORE 36 WEEKS,
THERE IS THE CHANCE THAT YOUR
BABY'S LUNG MIGHT NOT BE MATURE.
>> MY FEELINGS ARE HURT.
THE DOCTORS ARE WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT'LL HAPPEN IF I HAVE THE
BABY THIS EARLY, AND THEY WANT
TO KEEP ME OVERNIGHT.
MY MOM HAD TO LEAVE FOR WORK.
AND FOREST STILL HASN'T CALLED
ME BACK.
IN THE MORNING, MY CONTRACTIONS
HAD MOSTLY STOPPED,
AND I WAS FEELING BETTER.
BUT I'M STILL PRETTY FRUSTRATED
ABOUT FOREST NOT SHOWING UP.
>> HE HASN'T TRIED CALLING OR
TEXTING YOU OR ANYTHING?
>> NO.
HE OBVIOUSLY DOESN'T CARE.
WELL, WHATEVER HE'S DOING,
IT'S--NOTHING IS MORE IMPORTANT
THAN HIS CHILD.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
>> SHE HAS TO GET A SHOT TO
MAKE HER LUNGS DEVELOP FASTER,
BECAUSE SHE COULD COME ANY DAY
NOW.
LIKE, DOES HE NOT CARE THAT THIS
COULD AFFECT--
>> MAYBE HE'S RUNNING FROM IT.
LIKE, SINCE IT'S GETTING SO MUCH
CLOSER TO THE TIME,
HE'S GETTING MORE AFRAID.
>> YEAH, WELL, GROW THE [bleep]
UP.
SO...
>> SORRY.
OKAY.
GIVE YOU THE SHOT.
ALL RIGHT, MY DEAR, ROLL OVER.
>> OW.
>> RIGHT NOW, LINDSEY, DON'T PUT
YOUR HAND BACK THERE.
>> OW.
>> GOOD TO GO.
YOUR INSTRUCTIONS ARE BED REST--
>> ONLY UP TO SHOWER.
>> NO SCHOOL.
UP TO SHOWER, UP TO EAT,
KIND OF BASIC.
YOU'LL BE ON THE COUCH.
WE'RE NOT GONNA TAKE ANY CHANCES
WITH YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
>> I'M READY TO GO.
SINCE MY MOM HAD TO WORK, MY
SISTER DALLAS CAME TO DRIVE ME
HOME.
>> BUT I'M SERIOUS.
LIKE, WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU
AND FOREST?
>> THE OTHER DAY WHEN I WENT TO
THE HOSPITAL, HE DIDN'T EVEN
RETURN MY CALL.
LIKE, I LEFT HIM A VOICEMAIL.
I TEXTED HIM.
AND I CALLED HIM ABOUT HOW I WAS
IN THE HOSPITAL.
HE NEVER EVEN CALLED TO ASK WHY
I WAS THERE OR ANYTHING.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> HE HASN'T BEEN
THERE TO HELP ME.
HE HASN'T CALLED TO SEE IF I'M
OKAY, IF I NEED ANYTHING.
>> WHAT AN ASS[bleep].
>> I WORK MY ASS OFF.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A JOB.
I'M THE PREGNANT GIRLFRIEND
GOING TO WORK AT, LIKE,
5:00 IN THE MORNING,
AT 12:00 AT NIGHT,
NOT EVEN GETTING OFF UNTIL THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
AND I GET NOTHING IN RETURN.
LIKE, I'M KIND OF JUST, LIKE,
DONE IN A WAY.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
I REALLY DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BE WITH HIM AT ALL,
'CAUSE THAT'S [bleep] UP.
LIKE, YOU DESERVE WAY
BETTER THAN THAT.
LIKE, YOU'RE HAVING HIS KID, AND
HE'S NOT EVEN...
THAT'S SO MESSED UP.
IT'S LIKE HE DOESN'T APPRECIATE
YOU AT ALL.
>> TODAY WAS SUPPOSED TO BE MY
FIRST DAY BACK AT SCHOOL, BUT
BECAUSE I'M ON BED REST, I HAVE
TO DO ALL MY WORK ONLINE.
>> SO DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA
BE ABLE TO DO THE MATH ONLINE,
OR ARE YOU GONNA NEED HELP,
SWEETHEART?
>> I CAN DO IT.
IT ALSO MEANS I CAN'T GO TO
WORK, WHICH REALLY SUCKS,
BECAUSE NOW I'M NEVER GONNA BE
ABLE TO SAVE UP FOR ALL THE BABY
STUFF WE NEED.
AND FOREST STILL HASN'T EVEN
CALLED TO SEE HOW I'M DOING.
>> AT THE TONE,
PLEASE RECORD YOUR MESSAGE.
[phone beeps]
>> OKAY, WELL, SINCE YOU CAN'T
BE MATURE AND TALK ABOUT THIS
AND BE CIVIL LIKE YOU SAY--
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN CALL ME BACK
WHEN I HAD TO GO TO THE
HOSPITAL.
AND YOU'RE NOT EVEN TRYING TO
GET A JOB, SO YOU'RE REALLY
UNMOTIVATED, AND YOU NEED TO GET
YOUR [bleep] TOGETHER.
AND UNTIL THEN,
I'M NOT IN YOUR LIFE.
AND I'M DONE.
[sad instrumental music]
* *
>> OKAY.
THINGS ARE SO BAD WITH FOREST,
AND IT'S MAKING ME MISS
MY OLD LIFE.
BUT WHEN I FINALLY GOT A TEXT
FROM FOREST APOLOGIZING,
IT WAS HARD TO IGNORE.
HE SAID HE MISSES ME AND WAS
JUST FREAKING OUT ABOUT US
BECOMING PARENTS.
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M ON BED REST,
I AGREED TO GO OVER THERE AND
HEAR WHAT HE HAD TO SAY.
HI.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> I REMEMBER, I WAS IN THE
HOSPITAL, BECAUSE I STARTED
GETTING CONTRACTIONS,
SO I HAD TO GO.
AND THEN, THEY HAD TO GIVE ME A
SHOT, BECAUSE I COULD HAVE HAD
HER WAY EARLY.
AND SHE WOULD HAVE BEEN IN
THE ICU.
>> YOU--I KNOW YOU THINK IT WAS
ALL BAD ON YOU, BUT HERE I AM.
AND IT'S LIKE, "OH, I'M GONNA BE
A FATHER NOW.
LIKE, JUST BEING FOREST,
YOU HAVE TO GROW UP NOW."
FOREST, IT'S LIKE,
"HERE'S YOUR KID."
AND SO WHEN I DID DITCH YOU AT
THE HOSPITAL, IT WASN'T BECAUSE
I WAS TRYING TO BE MEAN OR
ANYTHING, BUT I FELT
I CAN GROW UP ON MY OWN TOO.
>> I JUST WANTED YOU TO BE THERE
FOR ME.
>> WELL, I AM SORRY.
AND I WANT TO HAVE A GREAT
FAMILY, SO...
DO YOU WANT TO WORK ON THIS
AND GET BACK TOGETHER?
>> AS LONG AS WE TREAT EACH
OTHER WITH RESPECT.
>> OKAY.
>> AND THAT'S THE ONLY WAY I
COULD BE WITH YOU.
>> WE SHOULD TRY
AND MAKE THINGS WORK.
IT IS GONNA BENEFIT, LIKE, US
BEING AROUND EACH OTHER AND YOU
LIVING HERE AND RAISE A DAUGHTER
IN A HEALTHY FAMILY.
>> I'M GLAD FOREST SEES WHAT HE
DID WAS WRONG AND WANTS US TO BE
TOGETHER AS A FAMILY.
SO I THINK IT'D BE BEST IF I
LIVED WITH HIM ONCE THE BABY
COMES.
>> HEY, HONEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> WELL, I AM GOING TO
MOVE IN WITH FOREST.
>> WHEN?
>> AS SOON AS THE BABY'S BORN.
LIKE, I'LL MOVE IN WITH THEM
AT THEIR HOUSE.
>> AND WHY DO YOU THINK THAT'S
SUCH A GOOD IDEA?
>> I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
WE RAISE ANIYAH AS A FAMILY.
I WANT FOREST AND I TO WORK ON
OUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> SO I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT--
AFTER THE BABY'S BORN, DO YOU
THINK HE'S GONNA HELP?
DO YOU THINK HE'S GONNA BE
RESPONSIBLE?
BECAUSE SO FAR, I MEAN, OFF AND
ON, HE'S BEEN PRETTY
IRRESPONSIBLE.
>> HIM NOT COMING TO THE
HOSPITAL WITH ME, YOU KNOW, THAT
WAS NOT OKAY AT ALL.
>> DID HE SAY HE WAS SORRY AND
HE WAS GONNA STEP UP AND
BE RESPONSIBLE?
>> YEAH, HE SAID THAT.
>> STILL, IT'S HARD.
WHEN I WORK, I'M NOT GONNA BE
ABLE TO SEE YOU AND ANIYAH
HARDLY AT ALL.
>> I MEAN, I KIND OF HAVE TO
GROW UP.
I'M NOT GONNA BE WITH YOU
FOREVER.
>> YEAH, LINDSEY, I WANT TO TELL
YOU THIS.
YOU'RE PREGNANT RIGHT NOW,
AND SOMEDAY, WHEN ANIYAH IS 17
YEARS OLD, I PRAY SHE'S NOT
DOING THIS TO YOU,
BECAUSE IT'S HARD.
YOU'RE STILL MY BABY.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S A GREAT
IDEA.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHERE MY MOM'S
COMING FROM, BUT MY MIND'S MADE
UP.
AND A FEW HOURS LATER...
MY WATER JUST BROKE, AND I'VE
BEEN HAVING CONTRACTIONS,
AND I'M IN A LOT OF PAIN.
I'M GOING TO THE HOSPITAL RIGHT
NOW.
>> OH, NO, I AM POSITIVE.
I'M ONLY 36 WEEKS, SO I'M
NERVOUS THAT ANIYAH'S LUNGS
WON'T BE FULLY DEVELOPED.
BUT WHEN I GOT TO THE HOSPITAL,
THERE WAS NO DOUBT THAT I WAS IN
LABOR, SO THEY ADMITTED
ME RIGHT AWAY.
>> SO YOU'RE NOT QUITE 36 WEEKS.
SO YOU'RE A LITTLE EARLY TOO.
>> [panting]
smooch!
>> ON A SCALE FROM ONE TO TEN,
TEN BEING THE WORST,
WHAT'S YOUR PAIN LEVEL AT?
>> WELL, I MEAN, LIKE, RIGHT
NOW, IT IS REALLY, REALLY BAD.
>> RIGHT, 'CAUSE YOU'RE HAVING
A CONTRACTION.
>> [panting]
>> WHAT ARE YOU WANTING TO DO
FOR PAIN MANAGEMENT?
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
>> YOU HAVEN'T THOUGHT ABOUT IT?
OKAY.
>> [panting]
OW.
NO, DON'T TOUCH ME.
>> OKAY.
>> PLEASE, DON'T TOUCH ME.
I LOVE YOU.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
BUT PLEASE DON'T TOUCH ME.
>> THE BABY IS NICE AND LOW.
AND SHE IS 6 TO 7 CENTIMETERS.
>> AFTER FIVE HOURS OF LABOR,
ANIYAH WAS FINALLY BORN
PERFECTLY HEALTHY.
[sentimental instrumental music]
* *
>> * THANK YOU, MY CHILD *
>> YOU'RE SO ADORABLE.
I JUST LOVE YOU.
>> * LITTLE STRANGER GIRL *
* YOU ARE HOME TONIGHT *
>> MY BABY.
I'M SO GLAD THAT FOREST WAS BY
MY SIDE THROUGH THE WHOLE THING.
>> HI, ANIYAH.
[giggles]
>> I'M STARTING TO FEEL LIKE I
CAN TRUST HIM A LITTLE MORE NOW.
>> [laughs]
>> FOREST'S MOM DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO MISS TOO MUCH SCHOOL,
AND ANIYAH HAS TO GET SOME TESTS
DONE TO MAKE SURE SHE'S OKAY.
SO MY MOM CAME BY TODAY TO KEEP
ME COMPANY WHILE I FILL OUT SOME
OF THIS HOSPITAL PAPERWORK.
[yawns]
>> SO WHAT ARE YOUR
PLANS, HONEY?
>> TO GO HOME AND SLEEP.
>> YEAH, BUT WHERE ARE YOU
GOING, TO FOREST'S?
>> YES.
>> THAT'S SO FAR OUT THERE.
I WON'T BE ABLE TO BE WITH YOU
AS MUCH AS I WANT.
>> WELL, MOM, I DON'T NEED HELP.
OH, YOU--IF THIS IS NOT
FILLED OUT BY THE TIME--
>> DID YOU FILL OUT WHAT YOU
COULD?
THIS DOESN'T REALLY MAKE ANY
SENSE THAT I'M FILLING OUT THESE
PAPERS FOR YOU WHEN YOU'RE NOT
LIVING WITH ME AND IT'S FOR YOUR
CHILD AND NOT MY CHILD.
SO THIS DOESN'T REALLY MAKE
ANY SENSE.
>> BUT IT'S BECAUSE I'M NOT 18,
SO SINCE I'M NOT 18, LEGALLY,
YOU GUYS ARE STILL IN CHARGE OF
ALL OF MY BILLS.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, LINDSEY?
YOU THINK YOU'RE AN ADULT.
AND YOU THINK YOU CAN DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT TO DO.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TIME TO REALLY
STEPPING UP AND BEING
RESPONSIBLE AND DOING SOMETHING,
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
>> JUST WITH THOSE PAPERS!
>> NO, AND THAT'S MY POINT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> FOR MONTHS, I HAVE ASKED YOU
TO FILL OUT WHAT YOU COULD ON
THESE PAPERS, BECAUSE YOU'RE THE
ONE HAVING THE BABY.
>> YOU'RE JUST BEING RUDE TO ME.
>> OKAY, I'M DONE.
I'M DONE.
HERE, FINISH FILLING OUT YOUR
PAPERS.
THIS IS YOUR BABY.
YOU DECIDED TO DO THIS.
>> I'VE ALREADY HAD TO FILL
STUFF OUT.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I ASK YOU TO DO ONE THING
FOR THIS WHOLE NINE MONTHS.
>> LINDSEY, HOW MUCH HAVE I DONE
FOR YOU THROUGHOUT THIS WHOLE
PREGNANCY?
YOU NEED TO BE AN ADULT.
>> JUST GO!
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT!
JUST GO!
>> IF YOU THINK THAT YOU'RE OLD
ENOUGH TO HAVE A BABY, YOU NEED
TO BE OLD ENOUGH TO READ THE
PAPERS AND FILL THEM OUT.
>> LEAVE! GO!
>> SORRY.
>> SHUT UP!
>> [sighs]
DONE.
DONE, DONE, DONE.
I'M OVER IT.
>> I WISH MY MOM AND I COULD GET
ALONG AND THAT SHE COULD
UNDERSTAND WHY I WANT TO LIVE
WITH FOREST.
BABE, ANIYAH LOOKS SO CUTE
RIGHT HERE.
>> IT'S YOUR NEW HOME, ANIYAH.
>> YOU LOOK SO CUTE, BABY GIRL.
LET'S CHANGE HER DIAPER.
THERE WAS NO ROOM.
DONE!
>> PUNKIN'.
>> I'M GLAD FOREST'S FAMILY IS
WILLING TO HELP OUT.
>> WELL, I COULD TAKE ONE DAY
OFF OF WORK.
>> NO, I'M NOT ASKING
YOU TO DO THAT.
>> I'LL MISS SCHOOL.
>> NO.
>> BABE, YOU CAN'T EVEN CHANGE
HER DIAPER BY YOURSELF.
>> YES, I CAN.
>> BUT EVEN THOUGH HIS MOM
DOESN'T WANT HIM TO GET A JOB,
WHAT I HAVE SAVED ISN'T GONNA BE
ENOUGH.
[baby crying]
I'M SO TIRED, ANIYAH.
I'M SO TIRED.
ALMOST DONE?
>> [yawns]
>> FOREST GETS UP REALLY EARLY
IN THE MORNING FOR SCHOOL
EVERY DAY.
>> BYE, BABE.
>> AND I SPEND THE REST OF MY
DAD HOME WITH THE BABY DOING
SCHOOLWORK ONLINE.
AND IT GETS REALLY LONELY.
MY FRIENDS ALL LIVE AT LEAST A
HALF HOUR AWAY.
AND NONE OF THEM SEEM INTERESTED
IN MAKING THE DRIVE OUT HERE TO
MEET ANIYAH.
[chime dings]
IT'S DEPRESSING TO THINK THAT
JUST A YEAR AGO, I WAS ON MY WAY
TO BECOMING A PROFESSIONAL CAGE
FIGHTER AND HAD TONS OF FRIENDS.
AND NOW IT'S ALL FALLING APART.
I WANT TO START GETTING MY LIFE
BACK ON TRACK.
SO I'M GONNA TRY AND MAKE THINGS
BETTER WITH MY MOM.
>> HI, HONEY.
>> HELLO, MOM.
>> HOW ARE YOU, SWEETIE?
>> YOU WAKING UP?
HI, BABY.
>> CAN I HOLD HER?
>> MM-HMM.
YOU WANT THE BOTTLE?
>> YOU KNOW, I WASN'T READY, BUT
I WOULDN'T TRADE IT FOR ANYTHING
IN THE WORLD.
ANYWAY, I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED AT THE HOSPITAL
AND EVERYTHING.
>> ME TOO.
>> IT WAS UGLY.
IT WAS SUCH A BEAUTIFUL
EXPERIENCE BEING THERE THROUGH
THE BIRTH AND THEN, ALL OF A
SUDDEN, IT JUST ALL WENT TO
HECK, YOU KNOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I DON'T FEEL GOOD ABOUT THAT
AT ALL, BUT HOPEFULLY WE CAN
MOVE ON FROM HERE.
YOU THINK?
>> WELL, I'M WILLING TO WORK ON
US.
>> ME TOO.
BECAUSE I LOVE YOU, AND I LOVE
THIS GRANDDAUGHTER
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
AND I WANT TO BE A PART OF BOTH
OF YOUR LIVES.
>> YOU ARE AND ALWAYS WILL BE.
AFTER DINNER, MY MOM SUGGESTED
THAT WE GO SEE MY TRAINER,
BECAUSE I'VE REALLY BEEN MISSING
CAGE FIGHTING.
I'M REALLY SCARED.
>> COME ON.
DO YOU WANT ME TO WALK IN IN
FRONT OF YOU OR BEHIND YOU?
>> YEAH, IN FRONT.
>> OKAY.
>> KEEP THAT HAND UP WHEN
YOU KICK.
HOLY MOLY.
WHO'S THIS HERE?
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER IN FOREVER.
>> I KNOW.
THAT STRANGER, HUH?
THE STRANGER.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR NAME AGAIN?
>> [laughs]
OH, NO, DON'T CRY.
YOU'LL MAKE ME CRY.
STOP IT.
>> I MISS LINDSEY.
>> I MISS YOU.
>> THIS IS ANIYAH.
>> ANIYAH.
>> THIS IS LINDSEY'S BABY.
>> IT'S WHY I'M BRINGING THE
BABY, 'CAUSE I WANT TO LIKE--
I MISS THE GYM.
AND I MISS YOU.
THIS HAS BEEN THE REASON I
HAVEN'T BEEN HERE.
AND I WANTED TO TELL YOU, BUT IT
WAS JUST SO HARD.
LIKE, EVERY TIME I WOULD DRIVE
BY, I JUST WANTED TO COME, BUT
THEN I WAS, LIKE, JUST SO SCARED
OF WHAT YOU WOULD,
LIKE, SAY, AND...
[sniffles]
>> WELL, YOU CAN TELL ME STUFF.
YEAH, THAT MAKES ME FEEL BAD.
YOU COULD HAVE COME BY AND...
>> HERE YOU GO, SWEETIE.
>> SO DO YOU THINK IF I WORK MY
BUTT OFF, I COULD STILL GO PRO
LIKE WE HAD PLANNED?
>> WELL, I MEAN, IT'S GONNA
BE HARD.
THAT'S THE ONE THING YOU HAVE TO
UNDERSTAND.
I THINK YOU CAN GO PRO FOR SURE.
>> YAY.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE ONE OF THE
TOUGHEST GIRLS I'VE MET.
>> SEE, ANIYAH?
YOU CAN BE HERE WATCHING ME.
>> [laughs]
>> WHEN YOU OPEN YOUR EYES,
IF YOU EVER PLAN ON IT.
I AGREED TO START TRAINING FOUR
DAYS A WEEK.
BUT I'M GOING TO HAVE TO FIGURE
OUT HOW TO MAKE IT WORK ON TOP
OF MY ALREADY HECTIC SCHEDULE.
I WANTED TO HAVE A LITTLE BREAK.
>> OH.
IS IT HARD FOR YOU?
WHAT DO YOU DO EVERY DAY?
>> I'M, LIKE, UP ALMOST ALL
NIGHT WITH THE BABY.
AND THEN I TAKE CARE OF HER
ALL DAY.
>> ARE YOU GONNA WANT TO GET
BACK INTO CAGE FIGHTING?
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY.
THAT'S--I WANT TO BECOME
A PROFESSIONAL.
BUT I'M GONNA HAVE TO PAY
FOR IT.
>> HOW MUCH DOES CAGE
FIGHTING COST?
>> 80 BUCKS.
>> 80 BUCKS...
>> A MONTH.
>> A MONTH?
SO THERE'S ANOTHER BILL ON TOP
OF EVERYTHING.
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE A LOT, BUT
IT'S GOING TO BE HARD IF YOU
DON'T HAVE MONEY COMING FROM
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
WHY ISN'T FOREST WORKING?
>> THERE'S NOBODY THERE PUSHING
HIM TO MOVE FORWARD.
LIKE, I TELL HIM MY PART, AND
HIS MOM BACKS HIM UP.
HIS MOM DOESN'T MAKE HIM
GET A JOB.
>> IF I WERE FOREST, I WOULD BE
VERY EMBARRASSED.
>> I'M JUST WORRIED...
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU SHOULD
BE DOING EVERYTHING.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
[baby fussing]
>> IT'S OKAY, MAMA.
HOW WAS IT, SEEING TRAINER
AGAIN--RICK?
>> IT WAS REALLY GOOD, ACTUALLY.
IT FELT LIKE KIND OF A BIG
RELIEF OFF ME.
IT'S GIVEN ME SO MUCH MORE
MOTIVATION TO, LIKE, REALLY GET
BACK INTO CAGE FIGHTING, BECAUSE
I WANT TO GO PRO
WHEN I TURN 18.
>> WHEN DO YOU GO TO TRAINING?
>> EVERY OTHER DAY.
>> EVERY OTHER DAY?
>> YEAH.
>> SO MONDAY, WEDNESDAY,
AND FRIDAY?
>> AND SATURDAY.
>> AND SATURDAY?
>> YEAH.
>> DANG.
>> IT'S JUST CRAZY HOW FAST
MONEY GOES BY, LIKE,
WITH DOCTOR BILLS.
WE'RE GONNA NEED KIND OF A LOT.
I KNOW, LIKE, YOU WANT TO GET A
JOB AS SOON AS YOU GRADUATE.
IS IT JUST 'CAUSE YOU WANT TO
CONCENTRATE ON SCHOOL?
>> I KNOW IF I JUGGLE SCHOOL AND
WORK, I'M GONNA F--
MESS UP IN SCHOOL.
>> I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT STRESSING ABOUT SCHOOL.
BUT IT'S ALSO STRESSFUL
FOR ME TOO.
I HATE HAVING TO ASK PEOPLE FOR
MONEY.
AND PLUS, I WANT TO HELP OUT A
LOT AROUND HERE.
SO YOU ONLY WANT ME TO WORK.
>> IF YOU DO, BALANCE IT GOOD.
>> MY SCHEDULE IS GOING TO BE
WATCH ANIYAH ALL DAY,
DO SCHOOL ALL DAY,
YOU COME HOME,
I GET READY TO GO TO TRAIN.
THEN THE DAYS THAT I DON'T
TRAIN, YOU COME HOME, I GET
READY, YOU TAKE ME TO WORK.
AND THEN YOU PICK ME UP AT
MIDNIGHT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE WATCHING
HER A LOT.
FOREST DOESN'T WANT TO GET A JOB
UNTIL HE GRADUATES.
IT'S NOT OKAY.
BUT HE'S STUCK BY MY SIDE
AND ANIYAH'S SIDE.
>> IT'S OKAY, BABY.
[laughs]
>> HOW ARE YOU GUYS?
HI, HONEY.
>> HI, MOM.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> IT FELT GOOD TO MAKE UP WITH
MY MOM.
WE REALLY LOVE EACH OTHER.
AND WE'VE JUST BEEN THROUGH SO
MUCH TOGETHER.
I LIKE THAT YOU COME OVER, BUT I
WISH YOU COULD COME OVER MORE.
MY FIRST TIME BACK AT CAGE
FIGHTING WAS PRETTY INTENSE.
>> BEEN AWHILE, HUH?
>> YEAH, IT'S LIKE I ALMOST
FORGOT WHAT TO DO.
>> LET'S GO, LINDSEY.
>> ONE YEAR OF NO TRAINING PUT
ME BACK SO FAR.
MY GOAL IS TO JUST GET BACK IN
SHAPE 100% SO THAT I CAN BECOME
THE FIGHTER I WANT TO BE.
I KNOW THAT I GOT MYSELF INTO A
LOT WITH HAVING TO BE A MOM 24/7
AND STILL TRY TO BECOME A
PROFESSIONAL CAGE FIGHTER.
I WOULD DO ANYTHING TO BE OUT OF
SCHOOL ALREADY AND HAVE A CAREER
AND HAVE MY OWN HOME.
I JUST WISH I WOULD HAVE WAITED.
[chime dings]
>> ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT.
>> I KNOW WHAT'S BEST.
>> AND WHAT IS THAT?
>> ADOPTION.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO NOT TRY.
>> WOULD YOU BE ABLE TO?
>> I CAN'T ON MY OWN.
MATT!
>> WHAT?
>> YOU ARE NOTHING!
AND GO HANG OUT
WITH YOUR CRACKHEAD FRIEND.