>> THAT'S WHAT YOU KEPT SAYING.
[chime dings]
HI, I'M SABRINA.
I'M 17 YEARS OLD AND GREW UP
IN LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA.
MY PARENTS SPLIT UP WHEN I WAS
A KID, AND AFTER LIVING WITH MY
DAD FOR THE LAST TEN YEARS,
I DECIDED I WANTED TO BE NEAR MY
MOM, SO AFTER MY JUNIOR YEAR,
I PACKED MY THINGS AND MOVED ALL
THE WAY ACROSS THE COUNTRY
TO FRANKLIN, TENNESSEE.
THERE'S SO MUCH MORE, LIKE,
NATURE OUT HERE.
IT'S A LOT DIFFERENT HERE,
AND MY MOM'S HOUSE IS ALWAYS
HECTIC, BECAUSE SHE HAS
THREE LITTLE KIDS.
>> DON'T HIT ME.
>> NO.
>> SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
>> SO ME AND MY SISTER REBECCA
LIVE NEARBY
AT OUR GRANDPARENTS' HOUSE,
WHERE THERE'S MORE SPACE.
WHY DOES YOUR HAIR OR MY HAIR
ALWAYS END UP IN MY SPAGHETTI?
>> IT'S YOUR HAIR.
>> MY SISTER AND I ARE REALLY
CLOSE, BUT I MISS MY FRIENDS
BACK IN CALIFORNIA...
>> HELLO?
>> ESPECIALLY MY BOYFRIEND,
IMAN.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR A COUPLE
OF YEARS, AND MOVING AWAY HAS
BEEN KIND OF HARD ON OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
BUT NOW IMAN IS THINKING
ABOUT MOVING TO TENNESSEE TO BE
WITH ME.
>> I CAN'T SAY "I-MAN" VERY--
>> IMAN, NOT "I-MAN."
>> SEE?
I DON'T KNOW HIM AT ALL.
>> THINGS WILL DEFINITELY BE A
LITTLE AWKWARD IF HE MOVES HERE,
BUT I'M DETERMINED TO MAKE IT
WORK, BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
LIVING HERE IN TENNESSEE IS SO
MUCH DIFFERENT THAN MY LIFE BACK
IN CALIFORNIA, BUT I REALLY
MISSED HAVING MY MOM AROUND
WHEN I WAS A KID.
MADRE!
AND AFTER I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, I KNEW I NEEDED HER
MORE THAN EVER.
I WISH WE COULD LIVE TOGETHER,
BUT I GUESS THIS IS THE NEXT
BEST THING.
>> WHEN YOU WENT WITH YOUR DAD,
WHEN YOU WERE AROUND SEVEN,
IT'S BECAUSE I WAS HAVING
LOTS OF PROBLEMS.
I WASN'T STABLE ENOUGH TO TAKE
CARE OF YOU.
>> WHEN I WAS LITTLE, I
REMEMBER, LIKE, I'D ALWAYS WANT
TO BE WITH YOU AND STUFF, BUT,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, IN SOME WAYS,
I THINK IT WAS, LIKE,
BEST FOR ME TO BE THERE,
BUT A LOT OF TIME, I JUST
WANTED TO BE WITH YOU.
>> YOUR DAD DID THE BEST THAT
HE KNEW HOW.
YOU KNOW, HE SHOULDN'T HAVE
GAVE YOU SO MUCH FREEDOM.
DID YOUR DAD TALK TO YOU ABOUT
BIRTH CONTROL EVER?
>> NO, WE NEVER EVEN TALKED.
I LEARNED, LIKE, WHAT SEX WAS,
LIKE, IN THE SEX ED CLASS,
'CAUSE IT WAS, LIKE, MANDATORY
TO TAKE.
>> I KNOW I'VE TALKED TO YOU
ABOUT IT.
I KNOW I'VE TOLD YOU STUFF--
THAT YOU'RE NOT READY.
>> YOU GUYS, LIKE, ALWAYS TOLD
ME TO PREVENT IT, BUT, LIKE,
IN THE CLASS, THEY ACTUALLY
SHOWED ME, LIKE, WHAT IT WAS.
>> WE JUST TOLD YOU NOT TO,
INSTEAD OF ACTUALLY TELLING YOU
WHAT IT WAS AND WHY YOU
SHOULDN'T DO IT.
WE JUST TOLD YOU, "DON'T."
I MEAN, WE ALL MAKE OUR
MISTAKES, AND NOBODY'S PERFECT
AS PARENTS, AND YOU'RE GOING TO
LEARN THAT TOO.
IT SURPRISES ME THAT YOU MADE
THOSE TYPE OF DECISIONS, BUT IT
DOESN'T MAKE YOU A BAD PERSON,
AT ALL.
IT JUST--YOU DID SOMETHING,
AND NOW YOU GOT TO PAY THE
CONSEQUENCES.
>> EVEN THOUGH I DON'T LIVE WITH
HER, IT'S NICE FINALLY HAVING MY
MOM AROUND TO TALK TO.
[chime dings]
GROWING UP IN A BROKEN HOME
WAS REALLY PAINFUL, AND I'M
DESPERATE FOR MY BABY TO HAVE
BOTH PARENTS IN ITS LIFE.
I WAS NERVOUS ABOUT MOVING SO
FAR AWAY FROM IMAN AFTER I GOT
PREGNANT, BUT HE PROMISED ME HE
WAS SAVING HIS MONEY AND WOULD
MAKE IT TO TENNESSEE BEFORE THE
BABY CAME.
BUT I'M DUE IN SIX WEEKS,
AND IMAN STILL DOESN'T HAVE
HIS PLANE TICKET.
HELLO?
>> WHERE YOU AT?
>> I'M IN MY BACKYARD.
>> MY SISTER.
>> DID HE BUY THE TICKETS YET?
>> NO, HE'S WAITING TO BUY THEM.
>> OH.
WHEN DOES, LIKE, HE PLAN ON
COMING OUT HERE?
>> NOT TILL THE DAY OF--LIKE, MY
DUE DATE, AUGUST 26TH, RIGHT?
IS THAT WHEN YOU'RE COMING OUT?
>> WHAT IF IT COMES EARLY, AND
HE'S GOING TO MISS EVERYTHING?
>> [sighs]
WHY CAN'T YOU JUST COME,
LIKE, EARLIER?
>> A FAMILY THING.
>> SO THAT'S MORE IMPORTANT THAN
HIS FAMILY THAT HE MADE?
>> ARE YOU EXCITED TO COME OUT,
OR DO YOU NOT WANT TO COME OUT
ANYMORE?
>> WHERE IS IMAN GOING TO STAY
WHEN HE GETS OUT HERE?
>> HE'S--WELL, HE WAS GOING TO
STAY OVER HERE.
[laughs]
>> HE'S NOT TAKING MY ROOM.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IT'S GOING
TO BE LIKE, LIKE, WHEN YOU COME
OUT HERE?
>> WELL, ONCE YOU KNOW WHEN
YOU'RE GETTING OUT,
THEN TELL ME.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
NONSENSE.
[laughs]
>> SOMETIMES I, LIKE--IT JUST
MAKES ME THINK, LIKE, HE'S
REALLY STUBBORN, AND HE'S NOT
WILLING TO GIVE UP THAT MUCH
FOR YOU.
>> LIKE, HE TELLS ME SO MUCH
THAT HE IS, AND I WANT TO
BELIEVE HIM, BUT...
>> I THINK, FOR ME, IN THE
BEGINNING WHEN IMAN MOVES OUT
HERE, IT'S GONNA BE, LIKE, A
LITTLE WEIRD AND UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> I KNOW MY SISTER IS WORRIED
THAT THINGS WILL CHANGE WHEN
IMAN MOVES HERE, BUT I'M HOPING
WE CAN ALL MAKE IT WORK AND BE
A FAMILY.
DOES A SPATULA WORK TO GET
SPAGHETTI OUT?
OH, I GUESS SO.
>> WHEN'S "E-MAN" COMING?
DO YOU KNOW FOR SURE?
[both laugh]
I MEAN "I-MAN"?
SORRY, SABRINA, I HAVEN'T GOT
USED TO THE NAME YET.
>> I THOUGHT HE SHOULD HAVE BEEN
HERE BY NOW.
>> YEAH, I DO TOO.
>> IT'S GONNA BE A LOT MORE
DIFFERENT WITH THE BABY HERE.
>> UH-HUH.
>> NOISY.
>> YEAH, BECAUSE ONCE THE BABY
COMES, IMAN'S COMING TOO.
SO IT'S GONNA GO FROM FOUR
PEOPLE AT THE TABLE TO SIX.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT HOW
LONG YOU MIGHT BE HERE?
>> LIKE, RIGHT AFTER I GRADUATE,
WE'RE GONNA LOOK INTO, LIKE,
OTHER PLACES.
>> I THINK IT'S GONNA BE KIND OF
HARD ON YOU TO RENT AN APARTMENT
FOR, YOU KNOW, $1,000 A MONTH,
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU FIRST START
OUT.
>> IT'S AWESOME THAT MY
GRANDPARENTS ARE BEING SO COOL,
BUT IF THEY'RE GONNA LET IMAN
MOVE IN WITH US, I NEED TO KNOW
HE'S GOING TO HELP SUPPORT
OUR BABY.
[line ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> HI.
>> SO WHAT'S UP?
>> LIKE, WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS
WHEN YOU COME OUT HERE?
>> SO DO YOU HAVE MONEY SAVED
UP, OR ARE YOU SPENDING IT?
>> SO YOU'RE NOT GONNA SAVE
ANYTHING FOR THE BABY?
CAN WE JUST...
OH, GOD.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> BYE.
>> UGH.
IMAN PROMISED ME HE'D START
SAVING HIS MONEY AND GET HERE IN
TIME FOR THE BABY, BUT TIME IS
RUNNING OUT.
>> WHAT YOU DOING?
>> TRYING TO CHECK IF IMAN'S
ONLINE.
>> IS HE?
>> NO.
>> ARE YOU JUST GOING TO CALL
HIM THEN, I GUESS?
>> NO.
AFTER OUR TALK LAST NIGHT,
I'M WORRIED ABOUT IMAN MAKING
IT TO TENNESSEE IN TIME FOR
THE DELIVERY.
[chime dings]
SCHOOL STARTS RIGHT AROUND MY
DUE DATE, AND I'M GONNA NEED HIS
HELP WITH THE BABY TO HAVE ANY
CHANCE OF GRADUATING THIS YEAR.
>> ARE YOU LOOKING FORWARD TO
SCHOOL, WITH YOUR BABY
AND WHATNOT?
>> IN SCHOOL, I WOULD HAVE THAT
DAY CARE, SO DURING THE DAY,
SHE'S GONNA BE, LIKE, WITH ME
AT THE SCHOOL.
I DON'T WANT TO JUST, LIKE,
LEAVE HER WITH MOM OR GRANDMA
ALL THE TIME.
>> I THINK I'M CONCERNED ABOUT
YOU GETTING TOO FAR BEHIND IN
YOUR SCHOOLWORK WHILE YOU'RE NOT
AT SCHOOL.
YOU MIGHT NOT HAVE TIME TO
ACTUALLY DO IT, WITH THE BABY.
>> WELL, NEWBORNS SLEEP A LOT.
>> THEY ALSO WHINE A LOT AND
POOP A LOT.
>> LIKE, I'M GONNA GET THE TUTOR
FROM THE SCHOOL.
JUST A CERTAIN COUPLE OF HOURS,
JUST SO I CAN GET MY STUFF AND
KEEP ON TRACK, AND THEN GO BACK
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
OH, AND I HAVE TO GET FITTED
FOR MY CAP AND GOWN.
LIKE, THE GOWN IS GONNA BE,
LIKE, FIVE TIMES AS BIG ON ME.
>> ARE THEY SERIOUSLY GONNA
MEASURE IT WITH THE BELLY?
>> I'M LIKE, "SUBTRACT."
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
THAT HUGE WHEN YOU'RE--
>> I'M LIKE, "MEASURE HER."
IT'S HOT IN HERE, MOM.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
I JUST THINK YOU'RE NOT FEELING
GOOD TODAY.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M SWEATING
TO DEATH.
MY DUE DATE IS LESS THAN A MONTH
AWAY, AND I STILL DON'T HAVE
EVERYTHING I'LL NEED FOR WHEN
THE BABY COMES HOME.
>> EVEN THAT CONSIGNMENT SALE
THAT WE WENT TO OVER HERE IN
FRANKLIN, THOSE CRIBS WERE,
LIKE, $300 TO $400.
>> I KNOW.
AS SOON AS I FOUND OUT I WAS
HAVING A GIRL, MY MOM AND
SISTER WANTED TO GO SHOPPING,
BUT SINCE IMAN IS STILL TRYING
TO SAVE UP FOR A PLANE TICKET,
IT'S UP TO ME TO BUY EVERYTHING
WE NEED.
THE BABY NEEDS A TRAMPOLINE,
MOM.
>> THE BABY NEEDS A TRAMPOLINE.
>> THOSE ARE EXPENSIVE.
I ALMOST FORGOT.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED SOME PADS
FOR YOUR--
YOUR BOOBS ARE GONNA START
LEAKING AFTER THE BABY AND
PROBABLY BEFORE THE BABY.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S GROSS.
>> SO--BUT YOU'RE GONNA
NEED PADS.
I ALMOST FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
>> THAT'S NOT NORMAL.
>> ARE YOU JUST PREPARED,
MENTALLY, FOR THE BABY TO COME
NOW OR...
>> NO.
[laughs]
>> WHAT IS THE NAMES YOU'RE
THINKING ABOUT FOR THE BABY?
>> REMEMBER, I TOLD YOU I WAS
THINKING ABOUT AUDREY?
>> AUDREY?
NO, I DON'T LIKE AUDREY.
>> TOO BAD.
>> AND IT'S GONNA HAVE IMAN'S
LAST NAME?
>> YEAH.
>> IT IS?
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED TO HIM.
>> BUT HE'S THE FATHER
OF THE BABY.
>> I THINK THAT IF HE SAVED THE
MONEY ENOUGH AND HE WAS
RESPONSIBLE ENOUGH TO SAVE
ENOUGH MONEY TO GET OUT HERE--
>> TO SEE THE BABY.
>> TO SEE THE BABY, THEN HE
DESERVES TO HAVE THE BABY NAMED
AFTER HIM.
DO YOU AGREE WITH ME?
>> YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT I THINK TOO.
LIKE, IF HE'S NOT GOING TO COME
OUT HERE AND EVERYTHING AFTER,
LIKE, ALL THESE MONTHS OF HIM
SAYING THAT HE'S COMING OUT
HERE, THEN--
>> WELL, HE CAN'T JUST COME OUT
HERE LAST-MINUTE EITHER.
>> I FEEL SAD, BECAUSE I'M NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO SPEND AS MUCH
TIME WITH YOU.
>> WHAT ARE YOU UPSET ABOUT,
BECCA LEE?
>> THAT I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO
SPEND TIME WITH MY SISTER,
HANG OUT AND DO FUN STUFF
LIKE WE ALWAYS DO.
IMAN'S ALWAYS GOING TO BE THERE
TO DO STUFF WITH HER.
>> I FEEL LIKE EITHER--IF IMAN
WAS HERE OR NOT, I WOULD STILL
WANT YOU AROUND ALL THE TIME
AND EVERYTHING.
[sniffling]
IF IMAN DOESN'T COME, I'M STUCK
RAISING THIS BABY ALONE, AND IF
HE DOES, I'M WORRIED ABOUT HOW
REBECCA WILL REACT.
>> YOU CAN'T HARDLY LIFT
YOUR BELLY.
YOU HAVEN'T DROPPED YET.
>> ALL THE STRESS HAS BEEN
KEEPING ME UP AT NIGHT, AND MY
FEET HAVE GOTTEN HUGE.
>> SHE'S BEEN SWELLING LATELY,
AND I'VE BEEN WORRIED ABOUT
HER SWELLING.
>> ACTUALLY, SWELLING IS NORMAL
IN PREGNANCY.
IT'S WHEN IT'S IN COMBINATION
WITH HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE--
123 OVER 68.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
[heart beating on ultrasound]
>> HELLO.
HOW YOU DOING?
>> I'M GOOD.
>> FEELING ALL RIGHT?
WHAT'S NEW?
>> SWELLING.
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHY THAT IS?
>> I'M PREGNANT?
>> YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
EVERYTHING'S ON TRACK.
YOU SHOULD BE GOOD TO GO.
THE BABY'S MOVING PLENTY.
>> WELL, AND THEN HER BIRTH
CONTROL AFTER, PROBABLY
AN I.U.D. WOULD BE BEST.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WOULD DO,
IF IT WAS ME.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> AN I.U.D. THAT LOOKS LIKE
A LITTLE ANCHOR, KIND OF...
FFT!
>> [laughs]
YEAH, THERE YOU GO,
A LITTLE ANCHOR.
>> LITTLE ANCHOR.
>> SO HOW MANY PEOPLE CAN
ACTUALLY BE IN THE ROOM?
>> I DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S
A REAL HOSPITAL POLICY.
I MEAN, YOU OBVIOUSLY DON'T WANT
A DOZEN PEOPLE IN THERE.
IT GETS KIND OF CRAZY.
BUT YOUR IMMEDIATE FAMILY,
MOST OF THE TIME, WE'RE FINE.
YOU DON'T WANT IT TO
BE A CIRCUS.
THIS IS YOUR MOMENT.
THIS IS ABOUT YOU, SO I WOULD
JUST HAVE THE PEOPLE IN THERE
YOU WANT.
>> OKAY.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> I KNOW I'LL HAVE MY MOM
AND SISTER WITH ME IN THE
DELIVERY ROOM.
>> OOH, ICE CREAM.
>> AND IF I CAN JUST MAKE IT
TO MY DUE DATE, IMAN MIGHT BE
THERE TOO.
SO IMAN JUST CALLED ME, LIKE,
TWO SECONDS AGO.
>> DID YOU TALK TO HIM OR...
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M AT THE ICE CREAM--
GELATO PLACE...THING.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
>> WHY NOT?
>> OKAY.
>> HANG UP.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
>> THAT WAS RUDE.
>> [crying]
>> DID ANYTHING HAPPEN TO MAKE
HIM MAD OR...
>> NO, LIKE, I HAVEN'T EVEN
TALKED TO HIM, LIKE...
>> WHY IS HE BEING LIKE THAT
TO YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S NEVER LIKE THAT.
>> MAYBE HE'S SCARED OF THE
RESPONSIBILITIES.
>> HE'S LIKE,
"OF COURSE I'M SCARED.
LIKE, AREN'T YOU SCARED OF
BEING A MOTHER?"
>> I'M LIKE, "YEAH, IT'S SCARY,"
BUT IT'S, LIKE, WHAT I HAVE
TO DO.
>> DO YOU THINK, IF HE DOESN'T
COME, YOU GUYS WILL TRY TO MAKE
IT WORK OR...
JUST THAT'S IT?
>> IF HE'S NOT GONNA COME,
THEN I DON'T THINK WE'LL BE
TOGETHER ANYMORE.
[laughter]
>> I'VE BEEN SO WORRIED ABOUT
IMAN GETTING HIS PLANE TICKET
THAT I HAVEN'T FELT LIKE HANGING
OUT WITH ANY OF MY FRIENDS
IN A WHILE.
>> SO HOW DO YOU LIKE TENNESSEE
SO FAR?
>> I'M NOT USED TO IT.
AND SINCE EVERYBODY IS ABOUT TO
GO BACK TO SCHOOL, AND I'M ABOUT
TO HAVE A BABY, I WON'T BE
SEEING THEM MUCH AFTER TODAY.
>> WE'RE GONNA GO LOOK IN THERE
FOR BABY CLOTHES.
>> OH, LOOK, BABY NAMES.
>> AUDREY!
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
>> SAY, "TENNESSEE," INSTEAD
OF "CHEESE."
[laughter]
>> SO WHERE ARE WE GOING NOW?
>> WE SHOULD GO DO SOME ARTS
AND CRAFTS.
ARE YOU GUYS READY TO MAKE SOME
FINE ARTS?
>> SO, LIKE, ARE YOU READY
FOR THE BABY TO COME?
>> SOME DAYS IT'S LIKE, "OKAY,
I'M READY.
WHEN IS IT COMING?"
AND THEN OTHER DAYS, IT'S LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD."
>> DID YOU EVER THINK ABOUT,
LIKE, ABORTION OR ADOPTION?
>> I DIDN'T THINK OF ABORTION
AT ALL.
I KNEW I WANTED TO KEEP IT.
BUT IT WAS STILL, LIKE, YOU
KNOW, IN MY MIND, LIKE,
"OH, WHAT IF..."
IT WAS ALWAYS IN THE BACK OF MY
MIND, LIKE, HOW MY LIFE WOULD
BE, LIKE, IF I DIDN'T HAVE HER
AND, LIKE, HOW IT WOULD CHANGE
WITH HER THERE.
>> YEAH.
HOW DO YOU THINK THAT, LIKE,
THAT'S GONNA CHANGE, LIKE, YOURS
AND REBECCA'S RELATIONSHIP?
>> WELL, IT'S JUST GONNA BE
DIFFERENT.
>> HOW DOES SHE FEEL ABOUT IMAN
COMING OUT AND MOVING IN
WITH YOU GUYS?
>> SHE--SHE ACTS LIKE SHE
DOESN'T EVEN WANT HIM TO COME.
>> REALLY?
>> BECAUSE SHE'S LIKE, "HE'S NOT
GONNA GET HIS TICKET."
>> YEAH.
>> YES, HE IS.
DESPITE WHAT MY SISTER THINKS...
[chime dings]
I STILL HOPE IMAN WILL COME
THROUGH FOR ME AND OUR BABY.
AND LATER THAT NIGHT, HE CALLED
AND SAID HE BOUGHT A TICKET.
HIS FLIGHT'S NOT TILL NEXT WEEK,
SO I JUST HAVE TO MAKE IT TO MY
DUE DATE, BUT THE NEXT MORNING,
I WOKE UP FEELING DIZZY AND WITH
A BADLY SWOLLEN FOOT.
MY MOM CALLED THE DOCTOR, JUST
TO, LIKE, LET HIM KNOW, LIKE,
HOW, LIKE, MY FOOT IS, LIKE,
REALLY SWOLLEN.
SO HE JUST WANTED ME TO GO IN
TO MAKE SURE EVERYTHING WAS OKAY
AND STUFF.
NO, HE TOLD ME TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
I DON'T WANT TO GO INTO LABOR
BEFORE IMAN GETS HERE, BUT WHEN
I GOT TO THE HOSPITAL, THE NURSE
SAID I WAS SHOWING SIGNS OF
PREECLAMPSIA.
>> A LOT OF TIMES WITH
PREECLAMPSIA, PATIENTS COME IN,
AND THEY'RE FINE, THEY'RE FINE,
THEY'RE FINE, AND THEN THEY WAKE
UP ONE DAY, AND THEIR NOSE IS
PUFFY, AND THEY HAVE THE WORST
HEADACHE OF THEIR LIFE, AND THEY
JUST SAY, "I JUST FEEL HORRIBLE.
I'M VOMITING."
I'M GOING TO CALL DR. LODGE AND
SEE WHAT HE WANTS TO DO, AND I
WILL COME IN IN A COUPLE MINUTES
AND LET YOU KNOW WHAT HE SAID.
>> THANK YOU.
>> OKAY, SO HE'S DECIDED TO
DELIVER YOU, OKAY?
IT'S TIME TO STAY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
>> HER BOYFRIEND'S NOT HERE
FROM CALIFORNIA YET, SO SHE'S
SO UPSET.
HE COMES THURSDAY.
HE'S GONNA MISS IT.
LET'S CALL HIM, HONEY.
>> HELLO?
>> OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE SHAKING
SO BAD.
WE'RE HAVING A BABY.
>> [crying]
MM-HMM.
>> SO I'M GOING TO NEED TO START
AN I.V.
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
OKAY, ONE, TWO, THREE.
WE'LL START THAT PITOCIN.
>> IS SHE GOING TO START
BEING IN PAIN NOW BECAUSE OF
THAT STUFF?
>> SHE WILL START FEELING
SOME CRAMPING.
IT'LL BE A GRADUAL THING.
>> [exhales]
>> YOU WONDERED WHAT
A CONTRACTION FELT LIKE,
AND NOW YOU KNOW.
>> OW, IT HURTS MY BACK.
THE CONTRACTIONS STARTED GETTING
REALLY PAINFUL, SO I DECIDED TO
GET AN EPIDURAL.
>> ALL RIGHT, SWEETIE, SO WHAT
WE'RE GONNA HAVE YOU DO IS,
YOU'RE GONNA SIT UP
FACING TOWARDS ME.
OKAY, IT'S GONNA FEEL LIKE
A LITTLE TWINGE.
TAKE A BIG DEEP BREATH.
DULL, ACHY PRESSURE.
LOTS OF PRESSURE, THOUGH.
GREAT JOB.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
YOU CAN RELAX.
HEAD ON BACK.
YOU MIGHT NOTICE YOUR LEGS ARE
GOING TO START TO GET WARM,
TINGLY, MAYBE A LITTLE HEAVY
HERE IN THE NEXT FEW.
I PROMISE IT'LL WORK ITS WAY UP
TO YOUR BELLY.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY?
>> HEY, SWEETIE.
>> HI.
>> I'M GONNA CHECK YOU, OKAY?
>> SHE'S THERE?
>> WELL, YEAH, YOU'RE COMPLETE.
THE HEAD'S RIGHT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO
LET HIM KNOW THAT YOU ARE
COMPLETE, AND WE'LL START
PUSHING.
>> SHE'S RIGHT THERE.
>> DID YOU TEXT IMAN?
>> I TEXTED HIM ALREADY.
>> SO WHO'S YOUR LEG HOLDERS?
>> ME AND LAURA?
>> DON'T PUSH HER LEGS BACK,
OKAY, JUST SUPPORT THEM.
YOU FEEL ONE NOW?
OKAY, SO GRAB YOUR LEGS.
PULL THEM BACK.
PUSH.
TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT.
>> IT'S COMIN'.
IT'S COMIN'.
>> KEEP PUSHING.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S PUSH
THE BABY OUT.
>> PUSH, BABY.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> OH, GOOD.
THERE SHE IS.
OH, MY GOD.
>> JUST BREATHE.
>> [crying]
>> HI.
[sobbing]
>> THERE SHE IS.
[baby crying]
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, SHE'S TURNING PURPLE.
SHE'S TURNING PURPLE.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE HER OVER
HERE FOR JUST A SECOND, OKAY?
>> SHE'S PURPLE.
[crying stops]
>> I WAS SO HAPPY TO BE DONE
WITH LABOR, BUT WHEN AUDREY
SUDDENLY STOPPED CRYING, I COULD
TELL SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
>> WE NEED NICU NOW.
>> NOW!
>> THEY'RE HERE.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
>> OH, MY BABY.
GOD, LORD, JESUS!
>> THEY TOOK AUDREY TO INTENSIVE
CARE RIGHT AFTER SHE WAS BORN,
AND I'M WAITING TO HEAR IF
SHE'S OKAY.
I CAN'T STOP SHAKING.
>> IT'S A LITTLE SCARY.
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
MY BEST GUESS WOULD BE THAT THE
BABY GOT SOME FLUID IN THE BACK
OF ITS THROAT, MAYBE DOWN--
THAT WENT INTO ITS LUNGS.
IT ALL HAPPENED VERY QUICKLY.
SO SHE'S JUST GONNA GO TO NICU.
THEY'RE GONNA WATCH HER FOR
A LITTLE BIT.
I KNOW IT WAS A LITTLE BIT
SCARY.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE BACK.
>> I HAVE TO CALL PEOPLE NOW.
HELLO?
THE BABY CAME.
SHE, LIKE, STOPPED BREATHING
FOR A LITTLE BIT.
WHERE'D YOU GUYS GO,
TO THE NICU?
>> YEAH.
>> THEY'RE GONNA KEEP HER
DOWN THERE.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THEY THINK SHE MIGHT
HAVE A LUNG INFECTION.
JUST SOME KIND OF--SHE'S GONNA
BE FINE, BUT THEY'RE GONNA
PROBABLY KEEP HER
FOR A FEW DAYS.
MY CHEST HURTS.
>> MY FIRST NIGHT IN THE
HOSPITAL WAS THE SCARIEST
OF MY LIFE, BUT I WAS SO
RELIEVED TO HEAR THAT AUDREY WAS
GONNA BE OKAY.
>> SO WE'RE GONNA GO DOWN
AND SEE THE BABY IN THE NICU.
>> I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE
HER HERE.
I CAN'T WAIT TO FINALLY SEE HER,
BUT I CAN'T BRING HER HOME YET,
BECAUSE THE DOCTORS WANT TO KEEP
HER AT THE HOSPITAL FOR A COUPLE
OF DAYS, JUST TO BE SAFE.
>> ARE YOU REALLY UPSET,
SABRINA?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, AT LEAST WE KNOW SHE'S
HEALTHY NOW.
OKAY.
>> AUDREY.
MOM'S BABY.
>> HI, AUDREY.
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL.
SHE WANTS TO WAKE UP, BUT SHE'S
JUST SO TIRED.
>> SO DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT GOING HOME?
>> NO.
>> I KNOW IT'S HARD.
I KNOW IT'S HARD.
THERE'S NOTHING HARDER THAN
LEAVING YOUR BABY.
IT'S OKAY, SABRINA.
DO YOU HAVE PICTURES OF HER?
YOU'VE GOT PICTURES ON YOUR
PHONE.
ALL RIGHT.
AND I HAVE YOUR NUMBER, SO I'LL
CALL YOU IF ANYTHING HAPPENS.
>> BYE, BEAUTIFUL GIRL.
[chime dings]
>> LEAVING AUDREY AT THE
HOSPITAL WAS REALLY HARD, BUT AT
LEAST SHE'LL BE HOME BY THE TIME
HER DAD ARRIVES NEXT WEEK.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M GONNA SKYPE IMAN.
>> RING.
>> HI.
>> OH, HI.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE TALKING TO YOU, NOT HER.
>> I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
>> HOW'S THE BABY?
>> SHE'S FINE.
>> SHE'S EATING PROPERLY NOW
AND ALL THAT GOOD STUFF?
>> NO.
LIKE, SHE ATE TWO TIMES TODAY,
AND THAT'S IT.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M FINE.
ARE YOU EXCITED TO SEE THE BABY
OR WHAT?
>> YES, I AM, ACTUALLY.
I'M VERY EXCITED.
>> WHEN ARE YOU COMING?
>> POSSIBLY THURSDAY OR FRIDAY.
MOST LIKELY THURSDAY--
MOST LIKELY THURSDAY.
>> WHY, "OR FRIDAY"?
>> JUST IN CASE I CAN'T GET
A TICKET OR ANYTHING.
>> SO YOU STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN
IT YET?
>> NO, I HAVE NOT.
BUT I WILL.
>> [crying]
>> HE JUST HUNG UP.
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO HIM.
HE'S BEEN SAYING THAT HE HAD
HIS TICKET.
HE TOLD ME THURSDAY, SO I TOLD
EVERYBODY ELSE THURSDAY.
>> YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
HE LIED?
>> YEAH.
AND HE WAS JUST LIKE, "OH, WELL,
I DIDN'T EVEN GET MY TICKET
YET," SO I DON'T EVEN THINK
HE'S GOING TO GET IT.
>> I'M UPSET.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU JUST HAD A BEAUTIFUL
BABY, HIS BEAUTIFUL BABY.
WHY IN THE HELL DID HE KEEP IT
FOR THE LAST SECOND, KNOWING
THAT HE WAS HAVING A BABY?
I DON'T WANT YOU TO HURT, BUT
WHAT'S GOING TO MAKE IT EASIER
IS AUDREY.
AND YOU THINK MAYBE NOT, BECAUSE
IT'S GOING TO REMIND YOU OF HIM,
BUT, NO, BECAUSE YOU'LL BE SO
BUSY TRYING TO TAKE CARE OF HER
THAT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE
TIME TO DWELL OVER HIM.
I THINK THIS WOULD BE A GOOD
CHANCE TO START CLEAN.
>> AFTER A FEW EXTRA DAYS
IN THE HOSPITAL, IT'S TIME TO
TAKE AUDREY HOME.
>> IS SHE ASLEEP?
>> YEAH.
>> SHE IS?
I'M REALLY SAD IMAN ISN'T HERE
TO WELCOME HER.
IT LOOKS LIKE I BETTER GET USED
TO DOING THINGS ON MY OWN.
I'M KIND OF SCARED TO GO IN,
MOM.
>> HI, GUYS.
DON'T TOUCH HER.
>> FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME A KISS,
'CAUSE I'M GONNA GO--
TAKE THE KIDS AND GO.
LOVE YOU.
>> COME ON.
OH, YOU PEED.
LET'S EAT.
[baby crying]
SHH.
THERE YOU GO.
>> BABY HERE?
BABY'S HERE.
>> SHE WAS JUST AWAKE
A SECOND AGO.
>> AW!
AWW...
AUNTIE BECCA WANTS BABY.
OH, HOW CUTE.
I'M ONLY THE SECOND PERSON TO
HOLD BABY, RIGHT AFTER MOM,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> SO FAR, AS WE KNOW IT, YOU'RE
GOING TO BE RAISING BABY AUDREY
AS A SINGLE MOM?
>> THAT'S HOW IT IS RIGHT NOW.
I JUST WANTED HIM TO BE HERE
TO HELP OUT AND STUFF.
HI.
[baby fussing]
[baby crying]
OHH.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
AUDREY WAKES UP EVERY COUPLE OF
HOURS AT NIGHT, SO I'M
COMPLETELY EXHAUSTED.
AND NOW THAT SCHOOL HAS STARTED,
MY TEACHERS ARE SENDING ALL OF
MY WORK HOME UNTIL I'M READY
TO GO BACK.
[baby crying]
OH, WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
IT'S SO HARD TO STAY ON TOP OF
IT ALL.
>> GET TO IT.
I TAKE BABY!
>> LUCKILY, MY SISTER WATCHES
AUDREY FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS
EVERY NIGHT SO I CAN GET MY WORK
DONE, BUT I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK
HOW MUCH EASIER THIS WOULD ALL
BE IF IMAN WERE HERE TO PITCH
IN.
>> DO YOU THINK I'D BE HELPING
AS MUCH IF, LIKE, IMAN WAS HERE?
LIKE, I'D BE ABLE TO?
>> I THINK YOU WOULD.
YOU WOULD JUST KICK HIM OUT.
>> I DO GET UPSET, BECAUSE I SEE
YOU SAD AND HURT LIKE THAT.
IT'S ANNOYING.
IT MAKES ME ANGRY.
>> FROM HOW I KNEW HIM, EVEN THE
BIG THINGS, HE WOULD ALWAYS COME
THROUGH WITH IT.
AND THEN, LIKE, NOW THAT HE'S
NOT HERE, LIKE, THAT WAS
SOMETHING TOTALLY DIFFERENT,
AND I WAS, LIKE, SHOCKED.
>> HE KIND OF KEEPS FLAKING OUT.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE IF I TELL
HIM, "JUST DON'T COME OUT HERE,"
THEN, LIKE, IN THE FUTURE,
I'LL GET BLAMED FOR IT, LIKE,
BY HER OR SOMETHING.
[chime dings]
I KNOW MY FAMILY WANTS ME TO
GIVE UP ON IMAN AND JUST MOVE ON
WITH MY LIFE, BUT HE KEEPS
TEXTING ME THAT HE'S TRYING TO
FIND A WAY TO TENNESSEE.
PLUS, I NEED HIS HELP MORE THAN
EVER, BECAUSE I'M ABOUT TO GO
BACK TO SCHOOL, AND MY PLANS TO
HAVE AUDREY THERE WITH ME
JUST FELL THROUGH.
THEY CALLED ME FROM THE SCHOOL
AND TOLD ME THAT THEY WEREN'T
GONNA HAVE A SPOT FOR THE BABY
TILL JANUARY.
>> AREN'T YOU REALLY UPSET ABOUT
THAT?
>> YEAH, BECAUSE I WANTED HER TO
COME TO SCHOOL WITH ME AND
STUFF, SO I COULD SEE HER, LIKE,
A LOT IN THE DAYTIME.
>> SO WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
WITH BABY-FACE?
>> I GUESS I'LL JUST...
>> DO YOU THINK IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN DIFFERENT IF IMAN WAS
THERE?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE THEN I WOULDN'T
HAVE TO, LIKE, ASK YOU GUYS TO
WATCH THE BABY.
>> I THINK HE'S JUST BEEN
PROMISING YOU AND PROMISING YOU
THINGS, AND HE HASN'T CAME
THROUGH ON ONE OF THOSE THINGS
YET.
>> IT'S BEEN ONE THING.
>> WHAT?
>> THAT HE HASN'T CAME OUT.
>> YEAH, BUT HOW MANY TIMES DID
HE PROMISE TO COME OUT ALREADY?
I THINK YOU NEED TO JUST THINK
ABOUT IT SOME MORE, AND I THINK
YOU SHOULD MOVE ON AFTER THAT.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO DO IT
BY YOURSELF.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE HER BY YOURSELF.
>> I DON'T KNOW--YOU KEEP
TELLING ME TO MOVE ON.
IT'S GETTING ANNOYING.
>> WELL, I HAVE TO TELL YOU
THE TRUTH.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING.
[baby crying]
>> DOO-DOO-DOO.
HEY.
>> MY DAUGHTER AND MY GIRL
LIVE HERE.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> I AM--I'M--I MEAN, I AM
EXCITED, BUT I THINK I'M MORE
NERVOUS THAN ANYTHING.
[baby crying]
>> NAH, SHE DOESN'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
>> SHE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING?
>> RIGHT NOW, SHE THINKS I'M
AT HOME, SLEEPING.
>> YEAH.
A LOT OF THINGS ARE FLOWING
THROUGH MY HEAD RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, YOU WANT TO LEARN?
OKAY.
HISTORY.
DO YOU KNOW HISTORY?
>> WHAT YOU DOING?
>> MY HOMEWORK.
>> ARE YOU TIRED?
>> YEAH.
[sighs]
DO YOU WANT TO DO IT FOR ME?
>> IF I'M NOT GONNA DO MY
HOMEWORK, WHY WOULD I DO
YOUR HOMEWORK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
DID YOU SEE MY ESSAY I WROTE IN,
LIKE, 20 MINUTES, AND I DIDN'T
EVEN READ THE BOOK?
>> GOOD JOB, CHEATER.
[doorbell rings]
>> OH, IS THAT MOM?
>> WHAT?
MOM'S NOT COMING.
>> WHO IS IT?
>> HI.
>> HEY.
>> WHO IS IT?
>> HI.
>> SURPRISE.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> I'M SHAKING RIGHT NOW.
I'M ALL NERVOUS.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I MISS YOU.
MAY I?
SHE LIKE BEING SNUGGLED?
>> YES.
YOU'RE FREEZING.
>> I MISSED YOU.
>> I MISSED YOU TOO.
[laughter]
WHERE ARE WE SITTING DOWN AT?
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO GO TO MY
ROOM SO YOU GUYS CAN TALK.
>> I THINK IT'S VERY COOL I GET
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
BUT I MISSED EVERYTHING, AND
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I WANT TO MAKE UP FOR LOST TIME,
FOR THINGS I COULDN'T DO.
HOW IS SHE AT NIGHT AND ALL
THAT STUFF?
>> SHE SLEEPS THROUGH THE
NIGHTTIME.
>> VERY NICE.
ANYTHING ELSE I SHOULD KNOW?
SO I GOT TO DO THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GONNA WALK ME THROUGH IT?
>> YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO CHANGE
A DIAPER?
>> NO, WHY WOULD I CHANGE
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I'VE NEVER HAD A KID BEFORE.
>> SHE DIDN'T POOP.
SHE ONLY PEED.
>> YES!
YOU WANNA GIVE ME THIS LEG?
YEAH.
[baby fussing]
OH, THERE IT IS.
>> DID HE DO GOOD?
[baby fussing]
OH, THAT'S A NO.
>> THAT'S CODE NAME FOR "GOOD."
I TOLD YOU.
THAT'S CODE NAME FOR,
"MOM BETTER FEED ME."
THAT'S WHAT THAT'S CODE FOR.
>> NO, YOU'RE DOING HER BOTTLE.
>> UGH.
>> SHE DRINKS 4 OUNCES.
>> SO TWO SCOOPS.
>> YEAH.
PRECISION.
[baby fussing]
AM I FEEDING HER TOO?
HI.
>> MOVE YOUR HAND.
>> YOU NEVER THOUGHT I'D COME,
DID YOU?
>> IT'S, LIKE, WEIRD TO SEE YOU
EVEN HERE TODAY.
>> COME AND EAT.
>> IMAN TOTALLY CAUGHT ME OFF
GUARD BY SHOWING UP, BUT HIS
TIMING IS PERFECT.
I'M GOING BACK TO SCHOOL
TOMORROW, AND SINCE THERE'S NO
ROOM AT THE DAY CARE ON CAMPUS,
I WAS RELYING ON MY GRANDPARENTS
TO WATCH AUDREY ALL DAY, SO
THEY'RE HAPPY HE'S HERE TOO.
>> I'M REALLY SURPRISED THAT YOU
GOT HERE, SO...
THIS REALLY IS A BIG SURPRISE
TO US.
WELL, I HEARD THAT HE'S
GONNA STAY.
IS THAT TRUE?
ARE YOU GONNA STAY NOW?
>> I'M HERE INDEFINITELY,
FOR RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S WHY I BOUGHT A ONE-WAY
TICKET HERE.
>> OH, THAT'S GOOD.
>> SO I'M KIND OF HERE FOR GOOD.
>> WHATEVER.
IF IT PAYS--YOU KNOW, IF IT PAYS
AN HOURLY WAGE CONSISTENTLY,
I'LL DO IT.
I DON'T WANT TO JUST BE HERE
AND JUST BE DEAD WEIGHT.
I WANT TO BE HERE AND TRY TO
BE PRODUCTIVE.
LIKE, THE MAIN THING IS, I WANT
HER TO FINISH SCHOOL.
THAT'S WHAT I'M REALLY PUSHING.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> I'LL BEND OVER BACKWARDS TO
MAKE SURE SHE GETS HER STUFF
DONE, YOU KNOW?
>> I THINK IMAN MADE A GOOD
IMPRESSION WITH MY GRANDPARENTS,
BUT REBECCA DIDN'T SEEM
THRILLED.
I WAS SO EXCITED FOR OUR FIRST
DAY OF SCHOOL TOGETHER, BUT THE
NEXT MORNING, SHE SAID SHE
DIDN'T FEEL GOOD AND WAS
STAYING HOME.
BEING IN SCHOOL AGAIN WAS
REALLY WEIRD.
I WAS DEAD TIRED, DIDN'T KNOW
MY WAY AROUND, AND DIDN'T KNOW
ANYBODY IN MY CLASSES.
AND BECAUSE REBECCA STAYED
AT HOME, I DIDN'T HAVE ANYONE
TO EAT LUNCH WITH.
I COULD BARELY WAIT FOR IMAN AND
AUDREY TO COME PICK ME UP, BUT
THEN MY DAY JUST GOT WORSE.
>> REBECCA DIDN'T GO TO SCHOOL
TODAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU KNOW THIS
OR IF THEY'RE LYING TO YOU, BUT
I GOT SOME OTHER NEWS FOR YOU.
>> WHAT?
>> SHE UNENROLLED TODAY.
SHE UNENROLLED
FROM SCHOOL TODAY.
>> TODAY?
>> TODAY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> SHE TOLD ME THAT SHE'S MOVING
OUT TO LIVE WITH HER MOM.
YOU OKAY?
YOU GONNA MISS YOUR SISTER?
YOU ALL RIGHT, BABY?
YOU WANT TO CALL YOUR MOM
OR YOUR SISTER OR ANYTHING
LIKE THAT?
>> NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO THEM.
>> SO NOBODY TOLD YOU NOTHING,
OBVIOUSLY.
YEAH, THAT'S PRETTY MESSED UP.
>> [crying]
>> YOU WANT ME TO TAKE HER?
>> MY MOM AND REBECCA KEPT
CALLING ME TO TALK, BUT I
WOULDN'T PICK UP.
[crying]
>> WE LOVE YOU VERY MUCH.
>> I DIDN'T.
WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
YOU THINK WE JUST DID THIS
BEHIND YOUR BACK OR SOMETHING?
AND I DO ALL THIS STUFF FOR HER,
AND SHE JUST LEAVES ME.
JUST GET OUT, PLEASE!
[crying]
>> female announcer: DON'T
GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
[baby crying]
>> ARE YOU AWAKE?
I DIDN'T GET MUCH SLEEP
LAST NIGHT.
AUDREY WAS UP A LOT, AND I SPENT
MOST OF MY TIME THINKING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED WITH MY SISTER.
I'M HAPPY IMAN IS HERE, BUT I'M
USED TO DEPENDING ON REBECCA FOR
SO MANY THINGS, AND I'M WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT IT'S GONNA BE LIKE
NOW THAT SHE'S GONE.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FEEL HURT THAT I HAD TO
HEAR IT FROM IMAN AND NOT,
LIKE, YOU OR IMAN OR ANYBODY.
>> I PLANNED ON TELLING YOU.
>> LIKE, I WENT TO SCHOOL, AND I
COME HOME, AND IT'S LIKE YOU'RE
MOVING OUT, ALREADY GONE.
WHEN DID YOU DECIDE THAT YOU
WERE GOING TO MOVE OUT?
LIKE, YOU ALREADY HAD IT
PLANNED?
OR WAS IT JUST, LIKE...
>> HMM.
I WANT TO BE WITH MOM TOO,
BUT I JUST CAN'T NOW, BECAUSE
OF IMAN AND THE BABY AND
EVERYTHING, SO...
YOU WERE JUST, LIKE, MY CLOSEST
FRIEND AND EVERYTHING.
NOW THAT MY SISTER LEFT, I FEEL
LIKE WE'RE NOT AS CLOSE AS WE
WERE BEFORE.
IT'S KIND OF SAD, BECAUSE I
STILL THOUGHT ME AND HER WOULD
BE BEST FRIENDS AND REALLY CLOSE
AND TELL EACH OTHER EVERYTHING,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
>> I KNOW YOU GUYS WERE, LIKE,
SUPER CLOSE, BEST FRIENDS.
AND NOW SHE'S, LIKE, GONE.
LIKE, I WOULD WANT TO CRY.
>> YEAH, I CRIED, LIKE, THAT
WHOLE NIGHT.
MAYBE IT WAS, LIKE, EVERYTHING
ALTOGETHER, AND THEN PLUS IMAN
WAS COMING OUT.
SHE PROBABLY DIDN'T BELIEVE
HE WAS GONNA COME OUT, AND THEN
HE CAME, AND SHE WAS LIKE, "OH."
>> READY TO TAKE A BATH?
>> I THINK IMAN'S A GREAT DAD.
HE'S TAKING CARE OF HER ALL DAY,
ALL NIGHT.
HE KNOWS HER CRIES.
HE KNOWS WHEN TO FEED HER,
WHEN TO JUST HOLD HER,
WHEN TO BURP HER,
WHEN TO CHANGE HER.
>> YOU ACTUALLY LIKE ME BEING
HERE, HELPING YOU OUT?
>> YES.
>> YEAH?
ARE YOU SURE?
YOU'RE NOT LYING TO ME?
>> NO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A TOUGH JOB.
IT'S A VERY TOUGH JOB, ACTUALLY.
>> I KNOW.
ARE YOU GOING CRAZY?
NOW THAT I'M A MOM, IT'S A LOT
OF RESPONSIBILITY AND HARD WORK
THAT I HAVE TO DO, AND IT'S JUST
STRESSFUL SOMETIMES, BECAUSE
WHEN SHE'S CRYING, AND YOU DON'T
KNOW WHY SHE'S CRYING...
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S KIND OF HARD.
WELL, IT IS HARD.
AND IT'S STRESSFUL TRYING TO
GRADUATE ON TIME.
I'M HOPING AFTER I GRADUATE HIGH
SCHOOL, THAT I'M GOING TO GO TO
COSMETOLOGY SCHOOL, AND IMAN'S
GOING TO BE IN SCHOOL BY THEN
AND HAVE HIS JOB.
>> HE HAS TO WORK.
HE'S GOT A BABY.
HE'S GOT RESPONSIBILITY NOW.
HE CAN'T AFFORD TO STAY HOME
BABYSITTING ANYMORE.
HE CAN'T JUST SIT AROUND AND
WAIT FOR JOBS TO CALL HIM.
>> LIKE, IF I COULD GO BACK AND
STUFF, I WOULD JUST WAIT TO HAVE
SEX UNTIL I WAS OLDER AND JUST
MATURE ENOUGH, BECAUSE THEN YOU
END UP WITH HEADACHES EVERY DAY,
NOT SLEEPING, JUST A LOT OF
GROWING UP AND RESPONSIBILITY
THAT YOU DON'T WANT UNTIL
LATER ON, AND IT'S JUST
REALLY HARD.
BUT, IN THE END, LIKE, ME AND
IMAN ARE HAPPY.
AND THE BABY'S ALWAYS HAPPY,
NO MATTER WHAT, SO THAT'S ALL
THAT MATTERS.
[chime dings]
>> PEOPLE ALWAYS STARE AT ME
LIKE THEY'VE NEVER SEEN
A PREGNANT PERSON BEFORE.
>> I'LL HELP AS MUCH AS I CAN,
DEVON, BUT I'M NOT GONNA RAISE
THIS CHILD.
[baby crying]
>> IT SUCKS TO MOVE AWAY FROM
YOUR FAMILY.
YOU DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GO AWAY.