>> [laughs]
HI, I'M JORDAN, AND I'M FROM
ST. LOUIS, MISSOURI.
DO I REALLY WANT TO WEAR THIS,
THOUGH?
>> I DON'T KNOW. IT'S CUTE.
>> THE FIRST THING EVERYONE
NOTICES ABOUT ME IS MY IDENTICAL
TWIN SISTER, JESSICA,
BECAUSE WE DO EVERYTHING
TOGETHER...
GET IT OFF.
GET READY TOGETHER,
GO TO SCHOOL TOGETHER,
HANG OUT WITH OUR BEST FRIEND,
ELLIE, TOGETHER...
[laughter]
AND EVEN EAT TOGETHER.
PEOPLE CAN TELL US APART,
THOUGH, BECAUSE,
BEING SIX MINUTES OLDER,
I'M THE MATURE ONE.
>> WHY ARE THERE SO MANY
PICTURES OF YOU?
>> FIRSTBORN.
THEY LIKE ME BETTER.
[giggles]
OUR PARENTS DIVORCED RIGHT AFTER
WE WERE BORN.
>> I'VE HAD IT!
>> AND RAISING TWIN BABIES
ON HER OWN WAS MORE THAN
OUR MOM COULD HANDLE.
SO MY GRANDPARENTS OFFICIALLY
ADOPTED US WHEN WE WERE
NINE YEARS OLD, AND WE'RE MUCH
CLOSER TO THEM THAN OUR REAL
PARENTS.
>> DRIVE CAREFUL.
SEAT BELT.
[school bell rings]
>> WHEN WE WERE ONLY 15,
WE LEFT NORMAL HIGH SCHOOL LIFE
BEHIND FOR GOOD TO BECOME
MODELS.
>> OKAY, JORDAN, YOU LOOK DOWN.
>> EVEN THOUGH MY GRANDMA
TRAVELED WITH US AS OUR TUTOR,
I WOULD GET HOMESICK
IF WE WERE AWAY TOO LONG,
ESPECIALLY AFTER I MET
MY BOYFRIEND, BRIAN,
AT A LOCAL BASEBALL GAME.
HE'S A CUTE, SMART,
HARDWORKING PROM KING
WHO THINKS I'M THE QUEEN
OF HIS WORLD.
THE ONLY PROBLEM IS, SINCE BRIAN
CAME INTO THE PICTURE,
THINGS HAVEN'T BEEN THE SAME
WITH MY SISTER.
I TRY TO MAKE BOTH OF YOU HAPPY.
IT'S SO FRICKIN' HARD, THOUGH.
SOMEHOW, THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
ALONG...
>> YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
>> BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
MY GRANDMA IS BASICALLY LIKE
MY MOM, AND SHE WAS NOT HAPPY
THAT I GOT PREGNANT, AND NOW,
SEVEN MONTHS LATER, SHE IS STILL
GIVING ME THE SAME LECTURE.
>> YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND THAT
THE DECISIONS THAT YOU TWO MADE,
IT'S NOT ONLY AFFECTING YOU TWO.
IT AFFECTS EVERYONE,
ALL YOUR FAMILY.
>> I KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
>> I KNOW YOU ARE.
BUT A LOT OF CHANGES--
>> WELL, I CAN'T CHANGE IT NOW.
>> NO, YOU CAN'T.
BUT IT'S STILL AFFECTING
EVERYONE.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> I HAVE A BUMP RIGHT HERE.
IT HURTS, BUT...
>> YEAH, THAT'S PART OF MAKING
THOSE KIND OF DECISIONS.
HAVING SEX IS BASICALLY WHAT
IT'S FOR, IS REPRODUCING.
>> YEP.
>> NOW WE HAVE A BABY
ON THE WAY, AND YOUR LIFE
WILL BE ALTERED.
>> YEAH, TRUE.
>> YOU NEED TO GET READY
FOR SCHOOL.
>> MY SISTER AND I WERE
HOMESCHOOLED WHILE WE WERE
MODELING, BUT WHEN I GOT
PREGNANT, WE BOTH STOPPED
AND ENROLLED IN G.E.D. CLASSES,
BECAUSE WE ALWAYS DO EVERYTHING
TOGETHER.
WANT TO FRENCH BRAID MY HAIR?
GRANDMA WAS LECTURING ME
ON HOW IF I COULD GO BACK
AND RETHINK OF MY CHOICES,
LIKE, OF HAVING SEX,
WOULD I?
AND STUFF...
BUT I JUST KIND OF
BLOCK HER OUT.
>> I THINK THAT'S KIND OF MEAN.
>> WHY?
>> I KNOW HE'S, LIKE, A MISTAKE
OR WHATEVER, BUT HE'S HERE NOW.
>> YEAH, BUT HE'S NOT GONNA
BE CALLED A MISTAKE.
>> OKAY, HE WAS AN ACCIDENT.
>> A SURPRISE.
>> IS IT BAD TO SAY I HOPE
YOU GO INTO LABOR WHEN BRIAN'S
NOT THERE?
>> HEY, JESSIE, THAT'S MEAN.
>> I WANT TO BE THE PERSON...
>> I'M SURE BRIAN DOES TOO,
FOR HIS BABY.
>> IT'S MY NEPHEW.
WHEN HE HAS A NEPHEW,
HE WILL UNDERSTAND.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, I'LL SEE YOU
AFTER SCHOOL, OKAY?
>> IT'S GONNA BE WEIRD
NOT GOING WITH YOU, THOUGH,
TO CLASS.
>> YOU HAVE ELLIE.
SHE GOES TO CLASS.
>> OKAY, I'LL JUST REPLACE YOU
WITH ELLIE.
>> YOU DO ANYWAYS.
>> WHATEVER.
THAT'S 'CAUSE YOU REPLACED ME
WITH BRIAN.
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> JORDAN.
>> I DON'T.
>> OKAY, WHO DO YOU SPEND
MOST OF YOUR TIME WITH?
BRIAN.
WHO DO YOU ALWAYS TALK TO?
WHO DO YOU TELL YOUR SECRETS TO?
BRIAN.
>> WHAT SECRETS DO I HAVE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SCARED IT'S NOT GONNA BE
THE SAME WITHOUT YOU,
'CAUSE I HAD YOU THERE
THE WHOLE TIME, WITH ME.
>> I KNOW.
>> I WOULD MISS THAT.
>> CAN I SEE HERE
WHAT YOU ARE DOING TODAY?
>> YEAH, THE WORK SHEETS
YOU GAVE ME YESTERDAY.
>> OKAY.
>> WHEN WILL I, LIKE, BE ABLE
TO TAKE MY G.E.D.?
>> OKAY, HERE ARE YOUR SCORES.
MATH WAS YOUR LOWEST.
>> YEAH, I WAS HAVING
A REALLY HARD TIME FOCUSING.
>> WERE YOU?
OKAY, GOT A LITTLE BIT OF WORK
TO DO, BUT HANG IN THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> KEEPING ON TRACK WITH SCHOOL
WITH THE BABY COMING IS GOING
TO BE HARD, BUT AT LEAST I HAVE
A REALLY SUPPORTIVE BOYFRIEND.
I'LL HAVE A 20-OUNCE
WEDDING CAKE.
GETTING PREGNANT WAS A BIG
SURPRISE FOR US BECAUSE
I WAS ON THE PILL.
WE LEARNED TOO LATE THAT
I HADN'T TAKEN IT LONG ENOUGH
FOR IT TO WORK.
>> IT'S GONNA BE WEIRD
NOT SEEING YOU PREGNANT,
'CAUSE YOU'VE BEEN PREGNANT FOR,
LIKE, THE MAJORITY OF OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
[chuckles]
I DON'T REALLY REMEMBER
WHAT IT WAS LIKE.
>> WELL, I WAS 30 POUNDS
LIGHTER.
>> I THINK IT WAS RIGHT AFTER
I ASKED YOU OUT, LIKE,
I SAW THE MODELING PICTURES
OF YOU, AND I WAS, LIKE,
SHOWING THEM OFF TO EVERYBODY.
I WAS LIKE, "YEP,
I'M DATING A MODEL.
NO BIG DEAL."
I DO REMEMBER, THOUGH, LIKE,
WHEN I FIRST ASKED YOU OUT,
THINKING LIKE, "WOW.
WE WOULD MAKE A REALLY
BEAUTIFUL BABY."
[laughter]
EXCEPT NOT AS SOON.
MAYBE A COUPLE YEARS FROM NOW.
>> LIKE FOUR.
>> OR SEVEN.
>> YEAH.
>> I REMEMBER BACK WHEN YOUR
GRANDMA, LIKE--IF I WAS OVER
AT YOUR HOUSE, WE WEREN'T
ALLOWED TO--
>> SHARE A BLANKET.
OR SHE'D ALWAYS GET MAD
IF SHE SAW US, LIKE,
EVER KISS OR ANYTHING.
>> OH, I REMEMBER THAT ONE TIME
I KISSED YOU IN MY KITCHEN,
AND SHE WAS RIGHT THERE,
AND I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE IT,
AND SHE LOOKED AT ME ANGRY.
I WAS LIKE...
OOPS!
>> SHE WAS LIKE, "I DON'T WANT
YOU KISSING HIM, BECAUSE KISSING
JUST LEADS TO OTHER THINGS."
>> YEAH, THAT'S--
AIN'T THAT THE TRUTH?
TODAY IS MY BABY SHOWER,
AND MY SISTER IS THROWING ME
A PARTY AT ELLIE'S HOUSE.
>> EVERYBODY, THEY'RE COMING,
OKAY?
>> WE STILL NEED A LOT OF STUFF
FOR THE BABY, BUT WE ALREADY
DECIDED HIS NAME IS GOING
TO BE...
>> all: NOAH!
[laughter]
>> FIRST GAME, WE'RE GONNA PLAY
MUSIC, AND YOU'RE JUST ALL GONNA
PASS THE BOTTLE AROUND.
>> DON'T LET IT GET ME.
DON'T LET IT GET ME.
[laughter]
THE GIRLS ARE FEEDING THE GUYS,
AND YOU'RE GONNA BE BLINDFOLDED.
>> OH, GOSH, THIS IS GONNA
BE ALL OVER.
[laughter]
>> AH, THAT'S HIS EYE!
>> YEAH!
>> YAY!
>> DIAPERS.
>> AT LUNCH, AT SCHOOL ONE DAY,
I WAS LIKE, "BRIAN IS HAVING
A BABY, WHAT?"
>> I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT IT,
'CAUSE I HEARD BRIAN TALKING
ABOUT IT, AND THEN I ASKED
ETHAN, AND EVERYONE WAS KEEPING
IT A SECRET.
>> UM, I WAS, LIKE, TWO WEEKS
LATE, SO WE WENT AND GOT A TEST.
I TOLD BRIAN TO GO LOOK--
>> YEAH, YOU DIDN'T EVEN
TELL ME.
YOU WERE LIKE, "OH, MY GOD.
GO LOOK AT THE TEST."
>> HIS FACE WAS WHITE.
>> I DON'T THINK IT REGISTERED
FOR A COUPLE MONTHS.
TILL I TOLD MY GRANDMA.
[laughter]
>> ARE YOU--DO YOU PLAN ON
MOVING IN TOGETHER SOON?
>> WHEN NOAH COMES?
>> THAT'S A TOUCHY SUBJECT.
>> WHAT I THINK IT IS,
JESSIE IS FEELING LEFT OUT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK BRIAN, LIKE,
GETS IN THE WAY SOMETIMES.
SORRY, BRIAN.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO.
THINGS ARE TENSE BECAUSE
MY SISTER THINKS BRIAN
IS EDGING HER OUT.
SO WHEN I ASKED MY GRANDMA
IF HE COULD MOVE IN, SHE SAID
SHE WOULD HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT IT.
BUT IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT TO US
THAT WE GET TO LIVE TOGETHER,
BECAUSE BRIAN IS GIVING UP
GOING AWAY TO COLLEGE
SO WE COULD BE A FAMILY.
HE NOW WORKS AT A RESTAURANT
AND WILL GO TO A COMMUNITY
COLLEGE NEARBY IN THE FALL.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT BRIAN
MOVING IN?
>> I HAVE.
MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS,
IS THIS GONNA BE TOO MUCH
PRESSURE ON BOTH OF YOU?
AND YOU'RE GONNA BE TRYING
TO GO TO SCHOOL.
>> I GUESS THE WAY I LOOK AT IT
IS, IF I LIVED HERE AND HELPED
TAKE CARE OF NOAH, THEN WE COULD
SUPPORT EACH OTHER EMOTIONALLY.
I THINK IT WOULD BE
A LOT EASIER.
>> YEAH, I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
GUYS TO BE TOGETHER BECAUSE
OF NOAH.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE WITH BRIAN
JUST 'CAUSE OF NOAH.
>> EVEN IF, LIKE, I DON'T LIVE
HERE, I STILL THINK THAT
THIS IS A REALLY GOOD PLACE
FOR NOAH TO BE, 'CAUSE YOU HAVE
A REALLY STRONG SENSE OF FAMILY.
[voice breaks] AND I NEVER
REALLY GREW UP WITH THAT.
I WANT NOAH TO ALWAYS HAVE
A STRONG RELATIONSHIP WITH ME.
>> WELL, AND THAT'S WHAT
I WANT TO SEE YOU TWO GROW INTO.
I THINK ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT HAS CONVINCED ME THE MOST
THAT YOU GUYS ARE REALLY
DEDICATED TO ONE ANOTHER--
AND I CAN SEE HOW MUCH
YOU LOVE ONE ANOTHER.
SO, BRIAN, YOU CAN MOVE IN.
>> HMM!
>> BUT ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT REALLY STILL BOTHERS ME IS,
I HAVE JESSICA HERE, AND I HAVE
TO THINK ABOUT, HOW IS THIS
GOING TO AFFECT HER?
>> YEAH.
I'M RELIEVED MY GRANDMA IS GOING
TO LET BRIAN MOVE IN, BUT I AM
NOT LOOKING FORWARD TO TELLING
MY SISTER.
[tapping at door]
>> ARE YOU READY FOR SCHOOL?
>> YEP.
>> YEAH.
>> OKEYDOKEY, GUYS.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
>> I'M EXCITED THAT BRIAN
IS MOVING IN NEXT WEEK,
BUT NOW I'VE GOT TO TELL
MY SISTER.
SO, J...
>> HMM?
>> I TALKED TO GRANDMA,
AND SHE SAID BRIAN CAN MOVE IN.
>> [sighs]
WHEN?
>> IN, LIKE, A WEEK OR SO.
>> HE'S GONNA BE THERE NOW
ALL THE TIME.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> HE'S GONNA BE IN YOUR ROOM
ALL THE TIME, SO I'M NOT GONNA
BE ABLE TO JUST, LIKE,
GO DOWN THERE AND LAY IN
YOUR BED WITH YOU.
>> I'LL COME LAY IN YOUR BED
WITH YOU.
>> THESE...
>> BRIAN IS MOVING HIS STUFF
OVER TODAY.
>> I THINK WE'VE GOT IT ALL.
>> I'LL GRAB THE LITTLE BOX.
AND EVEN THOUGH HIS MOM'S
DISAPPOINTED THAT HE'S NOT
GOING AWAY TO COLLEGE,
SHE'S HAPPY THAT HE'S
STEPPING UP AS A DAD.
>> YOU GONNA BE READY FOR THAT?
ALL HIS SMELLY CLOTHES IN THERE?
>> THEY'RE NOT SMELLY.
IT WAS NICE KNOWING YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU SOMEDAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I LOVE YOU.
[laughter]
>> I'M HAPPY BRIAN AND I
ARE GOING TO BE LIVING TOGETHER
BECAUSE THE BABY IS DUE
IN SIX WEEKS.
BUT THIS IS A BIG CHANGE
FOR MY SISTER.
HERE, THIS IS YOUR TOP DRAWER.
>> MY UNDIES.
>> HEH-HEH-HEH.
>> WELL, I DON'T REALLY WANT
TO GO THROUGH YOUR CLOTHES,
SO I'M GOING UPSTAIRS.
>> GOOD.
>> JESSIE, YOU MEAN YOU DON'T
WANT TO FOLD HIS BOXERS?
>> NO.
MOVE DOWN.
>> WHO?
>> EVERYBODY SHARE.
>> YOU.
>> JESSIE IS WANTING TO SIT.
>> MOVE IT.
>> [laughs]
SO, JESSIE, HOW ARE YOU DEALING
WITH BRIAN BEING IN THE HOUSE
AND...
>> I MEAN, IT'S GONNA BE
A LOT DIFFERENT.
>> IT'S PROBABLY NEVER GONNA
BE THE SAME.
>> ALL RIGHT, I HAVE TO GET
IN THE SHOWER.
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
YOU STINK.
>> BRIAN...
>> I'M GONNA GET IN THE SHOWER
TOO, JORDAN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M GONNA TURN IT ALL THE WAY
UP SO JESSIE GETS NO HOT WATER.
>> SHE'LL KILL YOU.
>> I WILL HURT YOU.
>> NOW THAT BRIAN'S MOVED IN,
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT THAT
I KEEP SPENDING TIME WITH
MY SISTER.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN BACK HERE
SINCE LAST SUMMER.
>> YEAH, I LIKE BEING WITH
JUST ME AND YOU.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME WHEN
WE BOTH HAVEN'T BEEN DOING
THE SAME THING.
>> I KNOW.
YOU'RE GONNA BE A MOM.
>> WELL, ONE DAY, WHEN YOU'RE
A MOM, THEN WE'LL BE DOING
THE SAME THING.
>> OR IF YOU WOULD HAVE STUCK
WITH MODELING, WE'D BE DOING
THE SAME THING.
>> JESSICA, SERIOUSLY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA PUT
ON THE OUTSIDE?
>> I'M GONNA MAKE THIS
FOR BRIAN.
>> NOT EVERYTHING IS ABOUT
BRIAN, JORDAN.
>> YOU PICK ON HIM A LOT.
>> HE PICKS ON ME.
>> BECAUSE YOU DO IT BACK.
>> YOU'RE ALWAYS DEFENDING HIM.
>> IT'S HARD FOR YOU TO
UNDERSTAND, 'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
IN THIS SITUATION.
>> UM, IT'S HARD FOR YOU TO
UNDERSTAND, 'CAUSE YOU'RE NOT
IN MY SITUATION.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO TELL YOU.
[baby crying]
>> THERE'S YOUR FUTURE.
>> SHUT UP.
IT'S TIME FOR MY WEEKLY CHECKUP.
EVEN THOUGH THINGS AREN'T
PERFECT AT HOME, I'M HAPPY
THAT BRIAN AND MY SISTER
ARE COMING WITH ME,
BECAUSE I WANT BOTH OF THEM TO
BE THERE IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
>> I COULD GO DOWN TO
THE FOOD COURT.
>> ME AND BRIAN CAN GO
EXPLORING.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO EXPLORING
WITH YOU.
YOU'RE MEAN TO ME.
>> YOU'RE MEAN TO ME.
>> OH, MY GOSH, YOU TWO...
>> [humming]
>> BRIAN...
>> WHAT IS THIS?
>> YOU KNOW, EVERY TIME WE COME
IN HERE, YOU PLAY WITH STUFF.
>> YEAH, YOU ACT LIKE A CHILD.
>> WHY WOULD THEY LEAVE IT
ALL OUT IF THEY DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO PLAY WITH IT?
>> OH, MY GOSH, BRIAN,
REALLY, STOP.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> WHO GAVE NOAH HIS "Y"
CHROMOSOME?
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW IT WASN'T
ANOTHER GUY?
>> OKAY, JESSIE, SHUT UP.
[knocking at door]
>> ALL RIGHT, JORDAN,
IT LOOKS WONDERFUL.
YOU'RE OUT OF HERE.
>> SO I WAS THINKING, LIKE,
YOU KNOW HOW YOU PLAN ON HAVING,
LIKE, YOUR SISTER IN THE ROOM
WHEN YOU HAVE THE BABY?
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, I KIND OF JUST WANT IT
TO BE ME AND YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BOND
WITH YOU WHEN YOUR, LIKE, SISTER
IS ALWAYS THERE.
>> WELL, I MEAN, I WANT HER
TO BE THERE.
I MEAN, LIKE, IT'S HARD
BECAUSE, LIKE, WE'RE SO CLOSE.
>> BUT IT'S GONNA TAKE AWAY
SOME OF THE SPECIALNESS FOR ME
IF SHE'S IN THE ROOM.
>> I--WELL, I CAN TALK TO HER.
BUT I DON'T WANT HER, LIKE,
TO HATE ME.
>> SHE'S NOT GONNA HATE YOU,
JORDAN.
>> WELL, LIKE, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND, LIKE, HOW CLOSE
WE WERE.
>> I DO UNDERSTAND, BUT I THINK
IT WOULD BE BETTER FOR HER
TO REALIZE NOW THAT'S SHE'S NOT
GONNA BE THE NUMBER ONE PERSON
IN YOUR LIFE ANYMORE.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHERE BRIAN
IS COMING FROM, BUT I REALLY
DOUBT MY SISTER WILL SEE IT
THE SAME WAY.
>> DO YOU FEEL READY?
>> YEAH, KIND OF.
JUST NERVOUS ABOUT LABOR.
>> I KNOW.
>> I WATCHED THE LABOR VIDEO.
>> I HOPE YOU DON'T HAVE TO HAVE
A C-SECTION, 'CAUSE THEN
I CAN'T BE IN THERE.
>> JESSIE...
BRIAN WANTS JUST ME AND HIM.
HE WANTS IT TO BE, LIKE,
A PRIVATE MOMENT.
>> SERIOUSLY?
YOU GUYS ARE JERKS.
>> JESSIE--
>> NO, LIKE, I DO SO MUCH STUFF
FOR YOU, AND THEN YOU'RE
GONNA SAY I'M NOT GONNA
BE IN THE ROOM.
>> I WANT YOU IN THE ROOM.
I'M SAYING BRIAN DISCUSSED
ME AND HIM--
>> BRIAN DOESN'T WANT ME
IN THE ROOM.
>> BECAUSE HE FEELS THAT IT'S,
LIKE, THE LAST MOMENT ME AND HIM
WILL JUST, LIKE, BE TOGETHER.
>> OKAY, FINE.
HAVE YOUR LAST MOMENT.
>> JESS?
>> YOUR LIFE PRETTY MUCH
REVOLVES AROUND HIM.
>> NO, IT DOESN'T.
>> YEAH, IT DOES.
>> NO, IT REVOLVES AROUND
MY BABY.
>> WELL, MAKE YOUR DECISION.
>> MY SISTER IS REALLY UPSET
THAT BRIAN DOESN'T WANT HER
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM,
AND THINGS IN THE HOUSE
ARE EVEN MORE TENSE.
>> SO YOU GUYS DOING OKAY?
>> WELL, I WAS MAD.
>> YEAH, I KNOW, AND I DON'T
WANT YOU MAD AT ME.
>> I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE JUST MAD.
>> I'M HURT.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, 'CAUSE I DON'T SEE
WHY THINGS SHOULD CHANGE.
>> THEY NEED TIME FOR
THE THREE OF THEM TO BOND
TOGETHER AS A FAMILY.
>> IT'S JUST HARD FOR BRIAN
BECAUSE BRIAN'S NEVER DONE
ANY FAMILY INTERACTION,
LIKE, HOW ME AND YOU WERE
ALWAYS TOGETHER.
>> HE JUST HAS TO GET USED
TO IT.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA LOSE ME.
>> YOU NEED TO MEET ME
IN THE MIDDLE.
LIKE, YOU GUYS ARE SO CLOSE.
IT'S HARD FOR ME AND JORDAN
TO BE AS CLOSE.
>> SO, JESSIE, HOW ARE YOU DOING
WITH ALL THIS NOW?
>> I AM GONNA GIVE YOU SPACE.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO, LIKE,
GIVE ME, LIKE, A TON OF SPACE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO UNDERSTAND,
LIKE, I JUST GOT TO MEET BRIAN
IN THE MIDDLE TOO, BECAUSE IF
I DO EVERYTHING I WANT,
HOW IS THAT FAIR TO BRIAN?
>> YEAH.
>> I HOPE WE CAN WORK THIS OUT,
BECAUSE THE LAST THING I WANT
TO DO IS HURT MY SISTER.
YOU HAVE TO WORK ALL THE WAY
TILL 8:00?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M GONNA MISS YOU.
MY DUE DATE IS ONLY
A MONTH AWAY.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> BRIAN IS WORKING AS MUCH
AS POSSIBLE BEFORE HE STARTS
COLLEGE, AND I'M TRYING TO TAKE
THE G.E.D. BEFORE I GIVE BIRTH.
>> YOU NERVOUS?
>> A LITTLE NERVOUS BECAUSE
I THINK IT WOULD BE EASIER
IF I DID IT NOW INSTEAD OF WHEN
HE'S, LIKE, HERE.
>> I'M VERY GLAD WE DON'T HAVE
THAT TIMELINE.
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW HOW
YOU DO IT, JORDAN.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE
WITH SCHOOL IF YOU HADN'T HAVE
ENDED UP PREGNANT?
>> I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE GONE
BACK INTO MODELING.
>> YEAH.
>> I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE JUST
BEEN HAVING, LIKE, FUN
AND, LIKE, DOING THE COLLEGE
EXPERIENCE.
>> YEAH.
JESS, HAVE YOU DECIDED WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I WANT TO BE A CAKE BAKER
AND OPEN MY OWN SHOP
OR CONTINUE WITH MODELING
OR BE A DENTAL HYGIENIST
OR AN ULTRASOUND TECHNICIAN.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> JEEZ.
>> I HAVE OPTIONS.
AMIE WANTS TO GO GET SNOW CONES.
DO YOU WANT TO GO?
>> YEAH.
YOU WANT ONE?
>> NO, THANKS.
>> WELL, WE'LL BRING YOU BACK
ONE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> SEE YA.
IT'S OBVIOUS MY SISTER
IS STILL HURT.
SHE'S SPENDING MORE TIME
WITH HER FRIENDS AND ISN'T
EVEN COMING TO MY DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT TODAY.
[coughing]
>> THINK YOU CAN MAKE IT
TO THE HOSPITAL?
>> YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA HAVE
TO PULL OVER SOON.
[coughing]
[gagging and vomiting]
>> YOU ALL RIGHT, BABE?
>> OH, MY GOD.
UGH, IT LOOKED LIKE SOUR CREAM.
ICK.
>> SOUR CREAM?
>> YEAH, I DRANK A GLASS
OF MILK.
>> EW.
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> HI.
>> HI, THERE.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> BEEN THROWING UP ALL MORNING.
>> OKAY.
SO I THINK YOU PROBABLY JUST
NEED TO KEEP TAKING YOUR
MEDICINE.
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S CHECK HIS HEARTBEAT.
[monitor pulsing]
PERFECT, 145.
YOU'RE MEASURING
VERY APPROPRIATELY.
>> OKAY.
>> SO AGAIN, LET'S JUST REVIEW
THE REASONS TO COME IN:
IF YOU START BLEEDING
OR IF YOUR WATER BREAKS.
OKAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE-BYE.
>> THIS BABY REALLY IS
COMING SOON.
AND IT'S MAKING ME REALIZE
THAT NOT HAVING MY SISTER HERE
JUST DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
I'VE DECIDED I WANT MY SISTER
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
>> WE TALKED ABOUT IT.
>> BUT I WANT HER IN THE ROOM.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE SHE'S MY TWIN SISTER,
AND I WOULD LIKE HER TO, LIKE,
BE THERE AND SUPPORT US.
>> SUPPORT US?
I'M THERE.
I HAVE PLENTY--
>> I'M PUSHING A BABY OUT.
I WANT HER THERE TO SUPPORT ME.
>> OKAY, WHAT ABOUT WHAT I WANT?
>> EITHER WAY, ONE OF US
ISN'T GONNA GET WHAT THEY WANT,
AND I WANT HER THERE,
AND I WANT HER TO TAKE PICTURES
AND VIDEO.
>> SOMETIMES YOU GOT TO MAKE
SACRIFICES.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT YOU BEING
IN THE ROOM WHEN I GIVE BIRTH.
>> WELL, BRIAN DOESN'T WANT ME
THERE, OBVIOUSLY.
JERK.
>> WELL, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
OVER THIS WAY EITHER.
>> UM, I UNDERSTAND PERFECTLY.
>> YOU'RE NOT A TWIN.
>> WHY CAN'T YOU JUST, LIKE,
REALIZE THAT SHE'S BEEN THROUGH,
LIKE, EVERYTHING WITH ME?
>> BUT HOW IS THE MOMENT
SUPPOSED TO BE SPECIAL BETWEEN
ME AND YOU IF EVERYBODY
IS IN THE ROOM?
>> IT'S STILL GONNA BE SPECIAL.
WHAT, YOU WANT ME TO SAY
NO ONE CAN BE IN THE ROOM?
OH, MY GOSH.
>> ALL RIGHT, SHE CAN BE
IN THE BIRTH ROOM.
>> AND YOU'RE GONNA BE MAD AT ME
ABOUT IT.
>> OKAY, EITHER WAY, SOMEONE
IS GONNA BE MAD.
YOU SAID IT.
I GUESS IT'S BETTER
THAT I'M MAD.
>> EVEN THOUGH BRIAN WAS UPSET
ABOUT ME WANTING MY SISTER
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM,
HE GOT OVER IT QUICK.
POOR LITTLE GUY.
AND I'M GLAD, BECAUSE THIS BABY
IS DUE ANY MINUTE.
>> IT'S NICE TO HAVE TIME
OFF WORK.
>> FINALLY GET TO SPEND
SOME TIME WITH YOU.
>> IT'S GONNA BE THE LAST TIME
WE GET TO HANG OUT, JUST ME
AND YOU, BEFORE THE BABY
IS BORN.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> NO ANYBODY BUT ME AND YOU.
>> [giggles]
I LIKE IT WHEN WE HANG OUT
ALONE TOO.
>> [kissing sounds]
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I COULD GO INTO LABOR
AT ANY MOMENT, AND I'M TOO
UNCOMFORTABLE TO EVEN LEAVE
THE HOUSE.
>> I WISH YOU WERE ACTUALLY
GOING TO THE GAME.
>> YEAH.
IT'S TOO HOT, THOUGH.
>> DO YOU WISH YOU WERE GOING
JUST TO HANG OUT WITH EVERYBODY?
>> LIKE YOU USED TO.
>> YEAH.
I USED TO BE OUT, LIKE,
ALL THE TIME WITH YOU GUYS.
>> OH, YEAH.
IT'S PROBABLY TIME FOR US TO GO.
>> SEE YA.
>> OKAY, BYE, JORDAN.
>> BYE.
>> IT'S A GOOD THING
I DIDN'T GO TO THE GAME
WITH MY SISTER BECAUSE I'M
HAVING THE WORST BACK PAIN.
I'M HAVING, LIKE, CONTRACTIONS,
LIKE, FIVE MINUTES APART,
AND IT'S CAUSING MY BACK
TO HURT, LIKE, MY PELVIS AREA.
>> WELL, IF THEY'RE
UNCOMFORTABLE AND THEY'RE THAT
REGULAR, YOU PROBABLY NEED
TO GO ON IN.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
>> BYE-BYE.
>> BYE.
MY SISTER IS STILL OUT,
SO I TEXTED HER THE NEWS
THAT WE WERE HEADING
TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> JUST REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT, BABE.
>> THERE YOU GO, DEAR.
>> HELLO.
>> SO WHAT WE'LL DO IS,
WE'LL DO A QUICK EXAM.
SO YOU ARE 3 CENTIMETERS.
SO LET ME GO JUST GIVE
DR. DAY A CALL, AND SOMEONE
WILL BE RIGHT BACK.
[knocking at door]
>> AM I GONNA HAVE MY NEPHEW?
>> SHE'S REALLY CLOSE.
>> I FEEL LIKE CRYING.
[laughter]
>> J?
WILL YOU REBRAID MY HAIR?
>> WE HAD A SMALLER...
>> HOW'D YOU LIKE TO HAVE
A BABY TONIGHT?
>> [gasps]
>> WE'D LOVE TO.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> SO THEY'RE GONNA COME IN
AND START YOUR I.V.s.
RIGHT NOW, WE'RE JUST GONNA
DO THE PITOCIN THING AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, SO YOU'RE GONNA NOTICE
THAT YOU'RE GONNA START FEELING
A LITTLE MORE CRAMPY IN ABOUT
20, 30 MINUTES, OKAY?
>> HOW OFTEN DO PEOPLE POOP
DURING LABOR?
>> [laughs]
>> QUITE OFTEN.
WE'LL HIDE IT.
>> GOOD.
>> ANOTHER CONTRACTION?
>> BREATHE.
>> IT HURTS.
>> I KNOW IT DOES.
JUST BREATHE, SWEETHEART.
BREATHE.
>> [sobbing]
>> JORDAN, YOU HAVE TO BREATHE.
>> I AM TRYING.
>> COME ON, BABE.
>> SHUT UP.
>> I'M COMING, I'M COMING.
YES, MA'AM?
>> I'M FEELING A LOT MORE
PRESSURE.
>> OKAY, COOL.
ON THIS CONTRACTION,
I JUST WANT YOU TO TRY
AND BREATHE THROUGH IT
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
ARE YOU HAVING ONE NOW?
OKAY, SO FOCUS ON THE PANTING.
I NEED DR. DAY CALLED
AND DR. WOOD CALLED.
>> JORDAN, LOOK AT THE CAMERA.
>> [whimpers]
>> IT'S OKAY, BABY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> [sobbing]
>> YOU'RE DOING OKAY.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> LOOK AT ME.
YOU'RE DOING FANTASTIC, SWEETIE.
>> YOU GOT IT.
>> HANG IN THERE.
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER, OKAY?
YOU'RE DOING FANTASTIC.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE, SWEETIE.
>> OKAY, WELL, WHEN YOU HAVE
A CONTRACTION, WE'RE JUST GONNA
TAKE A BIG, DEEP BREATH IN
AND THEN JUST BEAR DOWN.
>> [gasping]
HE'S, LIKE, THERE.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I'M PUSHING.
>> THAT'S OKAY, PUSH A LITTLE.
>> BRIAN, GRAB MY LEG.
>> HERE WE GO.
BIG BREATH IN.
>> HOLD THESE KNEES.
>> AND JUST PUSH.
>> [exhaling]
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> GOOD.
>> KEEP GOING, GOOD.
>> A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> [gasps]
>> TAKE A BREATH.
TAKE A BREATH.
BIG, DEEP BREATH AND HOLD IT.
>> [moaning]
>> KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING.
DO IT AGAIN, READY?
>> TRY ONE MORE.
>> GO, COME ON, JORDAN.
>> GO, BABY, GO.
>> [wails]
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> COME ON, NOAH, PLEASE.
COME OUT.
>> HI.
>> HEY.
>> YOU READY?
>> YES.
[moaning]
>> GRAB BEHIND YOUR LEGS,
PULL THEM BACK, WAY BACK.
>> THERE YOU GO, PERFECT.
PUSH, COME ON, JORDAN.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> GOOD JOB.
LET IT OUT.
>> [gasps]
>> READY?
LET IT OUT.
AND GO, GO.
COME ON, YOU CAN DO IT.
>> GOOD JOB, JORDAN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> LOOK DOWN, LOOK DOWN,
LOOK DOWN.
>> [yells]
[all talking at once]
[Noah cries]
>> DAD, YOU TAKE THE SCISSORS
HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[Noah cries]
OHH...
I LOVE YOU.
HI, OPEN YOUR EYES.
HI.
GO WITH HIM.
>> YOU WANT ME TO STAY WITH YOU?
>> [cries]
[laughter]
>> WANT TO HOLD HIM?
>> HEY, BABY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ISN'T HE SO CUTE?
>> YES.
HEY.
>> YOU'RE A MOMMY.
THERE YOU GO.
>> YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM, JESSIE?
>> YEAH.
>> BRIAN IS TAKING THE WHOLE
WEEK OFF FROM WORK.
I'M REALLY HAPPY THAT HE AND
MY SISTER GOT ALONG SO WELL
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
HELLO.
>> HI.
>> I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
I WAS DOING THIS RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
OKAY, WE'RE GONNA HAVE YOU PUT
YOUR LEFT HAND UNDER YOUR
BREAST, AND WE AIM THE NIPPLE
TO HIS NOSE.
NOW YOU HAVE TO SUCK, BUDDY.
>> FEELS LIKE HE'S PULLING
ON MY BOOB.
>> YEAH.
>> GOOD STUFF.
>> HELLO.
>> HAVE YOU CHANGED HIS DIAPER
YET OR IS THIS THE FIRST TIME?
>> I HAVEN'T YET.
>> FIRST TIME?
>> YEP.
I HEARD YOU HAD TO PUT
HIS BOY PARTS A CERTAIN WAY.
>> OKAY, I CAN HELP YOU
WITH THAT.
>> YOU JUST...
>> OOP.
[laughter]
>> AND IS HE--
>> both: OHH!
>> SO A TRICK YOU CAN DO IS,
TAKE THAT DIAPER, THIS TOP PART,
AND WIPE THE REST OF THAT DOWN.
>> POOR LITTLE GUY.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOOKS PERFECT.
>> HE LOOKS LIKE A CATERPILLAR.
>> A LITTLE BURRITO.
>> OR, LIKE, A COCOON.
>> HI, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
YOU GONNA OPEN YOUR EYE?
>> HERE, BRIAN, GET IN IT TOO.
[phone camera clicks]
HOW WAS THE DELIVERY?
>> INTENSE.
YOU COULD SEE HIS HEAD COMING
OUT, AND THEN SHE'D STOP
PUSHING, AND IT WOULD GO
BACK IN.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> IT WAS WEIRD.
[Noah squeals]
I LOVE IT WHEN HE FUSSES.
HE DOESN'T REALLY DO IT,
BUT HE GIVES, LIKE,
THE WEAKEST LITTLE, "EHH."
[laughter]
>> WELCOME TO PARENTHOOD.
>> TODAY, WE GET TO BRING NOAH
HOME, SO MY SISTER AND GRANDMA
ARE GETTING THE HOUSE READY,
AND MY COUSINS ARE COMING OVER.
>> LOOK AT HIM ALL STRAPPED IN.
>> [groans]
HEY.
HE JUST WOKE UP.
>> NOAH, WE'RE SO CLOSE TO HOME.
>> I LOVE YOU, BRI.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> [cries]
>> UH-OH.
[Noah screaming]
>> HE'S LOOKING AROUND.
>> LOOK AT HER.
>> HI.
>> HE'S LOOKING AROUND.
>> HI, NOAH.
>> ARE YOU TIRED OR WHAT?
ARE YOU JUST EXCITED TO BE HERE?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE HE'S ADJUSTING
VERY WELL.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GONNA GO
UPSTAIRS.
WE'LL TALK TO YOU
AFTER A WHILE.
>> [crying]
>> [yawns]
[belches]
[crying]
>> NOAH WON'T STOP CRYING,
NO MATTER WHAT WE DO.
WHAT?
>> [crying]
>> WHAT?
>> [belches]
>> YOU KNOW YOU SHAKE
THE WHOLE BED.
>> I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
EVEN WITH BRIAN HERE
TO HELP, ALL THIS CRYING
AND NO SLEEP IS ALMOST MORE
THAN I CAN HANDLE.
>> [crying]
>> [shushing]
>> HEY.
LET ME CHANGE HIS DIAPER.
>> OKAY, TEACH ME.
>> WELL, YOU'RE--HOLD ON.
YOU'RE REALLY COLD.
>> WE'RE ABOUT TO CHANGE
HIS DIAPER.
>> I'M GONNA GO SHOW HER HOW.
[shushing]
NO.
>> YOU'RE SO TINY.
>> YOUR HANDS ARE PROBABLY COLD,
J.
>> ARE THEY?
>> YES, THEY'RE FREEZING.
HOLD ON.
I'M GONNA NEED BRIAN'S HELP.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO HOLD
HIS FEET, LIKE, FIRM.
REMEMBER LIKE SHE SAID?
>> [screams]
>> BABE, HOLD HIS HAND.
>> SORRY.
NOAH, GET THAT ARM DOWN.
>> [sighs]
WHY ARE YOU SO CRABBY TODAY?
>> I'M NOT CRABBY.
>> YEAH, YOU ARE.
>> YOU DON'T NEED ME.
>> I DO NEED YOU.
I SHOULD HAVE--IT'S HARD
TO USE EVERYONE'S HELP,
BECAUSE I HAVE BRIAN
WHO HAS TO LEARN IT FIRST.
>> OKAY.
I'M NOT GONNA HELP YOU ANYMORE.
I DON'T CARE.
>> NO, YOU DO CARE.
WHY ARE YOU CRYING SO MUCH?
>> HOW WOULD YOU FEEL?
WHAT IF IT WAS ME THAT HAD
THE BABY AND I HAD MY BOYFRIEND
LIVING HERE AND YOU DIDN'T
NEED ME?
>> I DO NEED YOU, JESSICA,
BUT I HAVE TO BE A MOM FIRST.
>> OKAY, BE A FRICKIN' MOM.
>> AND LEARN HOW TO DO IT
MYSELF.
I CAN'T USE YOU EVERY SECOND.
>> SHE DOESN'T EVEN TRY TO,
LIKE, UNDERSTAND THAT WE'RE
TRYING TO BE PARENTS HERE.
>> I'M NOT PART OF HER PICTURE
ANYMORE.
[sobs]
>> WHAT AREN'T YOU HAPPY ABOUT?
>> EVERYTHING IS CHANGING.
I FEEL LIKE SHE ALWAYS STILL
WANTS TO BE MY NUMBER ONE
PERSON, BUT I'M NOT ALLOWED
TO BE HERS ANYMORE.
>> IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
>> I JUST WANT IT TO GO BACK
TO JUST ME AND HER.
[sobs]
[crying]
>> MY SISTER IS REALLY UPSET,
AND NOAH IS BEING FUSSY
AND WON'T EAT.
I'VE HARDLY SLEPT, AND IT'S ALL
JUST GETTING TO BE TOO MUCH.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
HIS MOUTH IS, LIKE, SO DRY.
HE NEEDS MOIST IN THERE.
JUST GIVE HIM, LIKE,
A LITTLE BIT OF FORMULA.
>> YEAH, TRY THAT FIRST.
[Noah fusses]
[water running]
>> YOU GUYS DOING OKAY?
>> HIS, LIKE, MOUTH
IS REALLY DRY.
>> WHERE'S HE AT?
>> [crying] IN THERE.
>> IN WHERE?
>> IN THE ROOM.
>> HONEY, DON'T CRY.
HE'S GONNA BE OKAY.
>> [sobbing] I, LIKE, CAN'T GET
ANY MILK IN HIS MOUTH, SO HE'S,
LIKE, REALLY DRY.
>> OKAY, BUT JUST RELAX.
>> I FEEL HORRIBLE.
>> HONEY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO FEEL
HORRIBLE.
HI, BABY.
HI, BABE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> NO, HE WON'T STOP CRYING
BECAUSE HIS MOUTH IS SO DRY.
>> HE'S FINE.
HE CAN'T EAT 24/7.
>> BUT HE WON'T HARDLY EAT.
NOTHING IS COMING OUT.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE FEEDING
SO OFTEN.
>> [shushes]
>> YOU'RE HIGHLY STRESSED OUT
RIGHT NOW.
THAT STOPS YOUR FLOW OF MILK.
>> BABE.
>> YOU HAVE TO CALM DOWN
JUST A LITTLE BIT.
HOW ABOUT IF YOU SIT DOWN HERE
AND CALM DOWN?
CAN I TAKE HIM UPSTAIRS
FOR A FEW MINUTES?
>> YEAH.
>> JUST GIVE YOU A LITTLE
SEPARATION.
[Noah screams]
LET'S GO.
>> YEAH.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
[shushing]
>> IT'S NOT EASY, BABE.
>> WELL, I FEEL LIKE
A HORRIBLE MOM.
LIKE, WHAT IF YOU WERE THE ONE
TRYING TO FEED HIM?
AND IT WASN'T HAPPENING.
>> I'M TRYING TO HELP.
>> YEAH, BUT HE HASN'T
HARDLY EATEN.
>> COME HERE.
>> IS HE CRYING STILL?
>> NO, GRANDMA IS HOLDING HIM.
JORDAN, HE'S FINE.
IT'S NOT BECAUSE HE'S HUNGRY--
>> BUT, SEE, HE WAS CRYING
FOR ALMOST, LIKE, THREE HOURS.
>> YEAH, BUT HE JUST DOESN'T
KNOW WHAT HE WANTS.
SOMETIMES THEY JUST NEED TO CRY.
>> IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> IS MY MAKEUP ALL MESSED UP?
>> NO.
JUST THIS EYE.
>> IT MEANS A LOT THAT MY SISTER
IS HERE FOR ME, EVEN AFTER
OUR FIGHT.
WHERE'S THAT DAMN BURP RAG?
>> WILL YOU CALM DOWN?
>> HE'S, LIKE, SPITTING UP
ALL OVER THE PLACE, AND I DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHERE IT IS.
>> YOU HAD IT.
DON'T YELL AT ME.
>> I KNOW.
I'M JUST REALLY GETTING
FRUSTRATED.
[Noah crying]
WEEK AFTER WEEK, IT'S BEEN MORE
OF THE SAME.
[Noah sneezes]
BLESS YOU.
THERE'S BEEN VERY LITTLE SLEEP
AND LOTS OF NOAH CRYING.
>> [crying]
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> TO SCHOOL.
>> WHILE MY SISTER GETS TO GO
TO SCHOOL AND HANG OUT
WITH OUR FRIENDS,
I'M STUCK AT HOME.
BRIAN HAS BEEN GOING TO WORK
AND IS NOW STARTING COLLEGE.
>> I GOT TO GET GOING.
>> REALLY?
>> LOVE YOU.
>> NOAH CRIES AND SPITS UP
CONSTANTLY.
>> [coughs]
>> I'M GONNA USE YOUR TOWEL.
LIKE THAT.
HEY?
[Noah fussing]
I'M STARTING TO WORRY
THAT SOMETHING MIGHT BE WRONG
WITH NOAH.
SO I MADE A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT
SO WE CAN FIND OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON.
>> ARE YOU GONNA DRIVE JORDAN
TO THE DOCTOR?
BECAUSE I HAVE CLASS.
>> YEAH, I'LL TAKE HER.
>> JUST MAKE SURE YOU TELL THEM,
LIKE, HE'S BEEN SCREAMING
FOR FIVE WEEKS.
I GOT TO GET GOING.
>> GOOD-BYE, BRIAN.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> I'M GLAD THINGS ARE BETTER
WITH MY SISTER BECAUSE I REALLY
NEED HER, ESPECIALLY WHEN BRIAN
IS NOT AROUND.
LIKE, I LOOK AT EVERYONE ELSE'S
BABY, AND THEIR BABIES ARE ALL,
LIKE, HAPPY AND DON'T CRY
VERY MUCH.
AND HE, LIKE, SCREAMS IN PAIN
AND DOESN'T SMILE VERY MUCH,
EXCEPT FOR IN HIS SLEEP.
I'M GONNA FIX WHATEVER IS WRONG
WITH YOU.
WHEN NOAH GOT CHECKED OUT,
WE LEARNED THAT HE HAS SEVERE
ACID REFLUX.
ACID REFLUX HAPPENS WHEN
WHATEVER YOU EAT GETS PUSHED UP
OUT OF YOUR STOMACH AND UP INTO
YOUR THROAT, AND IT REALLY
HURTS, WHICH IS WHAT'S MAKING
HIM CRY CONSTANTLY.
THEY SENT US TO THE HOSPITAL
IMMEDIATELY TO GET HIM
MEDICATION THROUGH AN I.V.,
AND THAT WAS SCARY ENOUGH THAT
I NEEDED EVERYONE BY MY SIDE.
[Noah crying]
[monitor beeping]
I HATE SEEING HIM CRY BECAUSE
HE'S IN PAIN OR HE'S GOT
A NEEDLE IN HIS ARM.
[Noah crying]
LIKE, WHEN HE FIGHTS ME
LIKE THIS...
>> THE MEDICINE FINALLY
KICKED IN, AND NOAH STARTED
TO CALM DOWN, BUT WE'RE STILL
NOT EXACTLY SURE WHAT'S
GOING ON.
HELLO.
>> HI.
[Noah crying]
OH, NOAH.
BABIES WITH REFLUX ARE PROBABLY
GONNA BE A LITTLE BIT MORE
HIGH-MAINTENANCE OR HIGH-NEEDS
BABIES THAN BABIES WITHOUT
REFLUX.
BUT WE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO MAKE IT BETTER, OKAY?
HE'S NOT GONNA BE, LIKE,
SO EASY, BUT WE SHOULD
MAKE IT BETTER, SO THAT
YOU'RE NOT CONSTANTLY DEALING
WITH A BABY WHO IS UNHAPPY
AND FUSSY AND CRANKY.
>> THANK YOU.
THE NEXT MORNING, THE DOCTOR
DISCHARGED NOAH.
THANK YOU.
>> GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
>> SHE RECOMMENDED A NEW
FORMULA, AND WE HAVE TO GIVE
HIM MEDICINE, BUT I'M SO
RELIEVED THAT HE'S OKAY.
BRIAN AND I ARE STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO BALANCE
PARENTING WITH HIS SCHOOL
AND WORK.
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> TAKING CARE OF THE BABY.
HE'S VERY CRABBY.
>> HA.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M STUDYING IN THE LIBRARY.
>> WHEN WILL YOU BE HOME?
>> UM, I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I HAVE TO WORK TONIGHT,
SO PROBABLY LATE.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'LL TALK
TO YOU LATER.
TEXT ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> BYE.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD JUST,
LIKE, TAKE ADVANTAGE OF, LIKE,
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE.
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE
ALL THOSE OPTIONS.
>> WELL, DON'T WORRY.
I WILL TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF ALL MY OPTIONS FOR YOU.
>> JUST, LIKE, DON'T MESS IT UP.
>> I KNOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO.
>> BETTER NOT, OR I'LL WHUP YOU.
[laughs]
THE PAST, LIKE, YEAR OF MY LIFE
HAS BEEN, LIKE, CRAZY.
I THOUGHT BEING A MOM...
OH, IT WON'T BE HARD.
I'LL WAKE UP A COUPLE TIMES
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
NO, 'CAUSE NOAH HAS ACID REFLUX,
SO IT'S, LIKE, A COLICKY BABY
ALL DAY LONG.
IT'S HARD NOT SEEING BRIAN,
'CAUSE HE'S WORKING ALL DAY
AND GOING TO SCHOOL ALL DAY.
I KNOW HE'S DOING IT FOR ME
AND NOAH.
>> CAN YOU SMILE?
SMILE.
>> HE DOES SUCH A GOOD JOB.
LIKE, THAT'S A TRUE MAN
RIGHT THERE.
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT,
IT WAS BEYOND STRESSFUL,
BALANCING JESSICA AND BRIAN,
TRYING TO, LIKE, EVEN MY TIME
OUT WITH BOTH OF THEM.
>> AW, ARE YOU UPSET?
>> TELL HIM TO STOP,
BEFORE I GET A KNIFE
AND STAB HIM.
>> IT WAS, LIKE, ONE OF THE
HARDEST NINE MONTHS OF MY LIFE.
FEELING NAUSEOUS...
IT WAS JUST VERY DIFFICULT--
AND WATCHING MY BODY CHANGE
SO MUCH, 'CAUSE YOU GET
STRETCH MARKS.
IT'S NOT FUN.
>> SO LET'S TALK ABOUT
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
FOR BIRTH CONTROL.
>> OKAY.
>> DID YOU HAVE ANYTHING
IN MIND?
>> I JUST WANTED TO GET
ON THE PILL, AND I'LL STICK
WITH THAT FOR A VERY LONG TIME
AND MAKE SURE I DO IT EXACTLY
RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, IF YOU SKIP A PILL
HERE AND THERE, YOU KNOW,
YOU'RE REALLY SETTING YOURSELF
UP FOR SOME ACCIDENTS.
>> YEAH, NO MORE OF THOSE.
>> SO--OKAY, GOOD.
>> I LOVE BEING A MOM,
EVEN THE SCREAMING, THE REFLUX,
ALL OF THE TIME BEING IN
THE HOSPITAL.
I DON'T REGRET ANY OF IT.
I MEAN, HE'S WORTH IT,
BUT I WISH I WAS OLDER,
I ALREADY HAD MY EDUCATION
TAKEN CARE OF.
I WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ALL THAT.
I GAVE UP JUST, LIKE, FREEDOM.
LIKE, I GAVE UP MODELING.
I GAVE UP NOT PLANNING
FOR MY FUTURE.
LIKE, HE WAS BORN, AND IT WAS
PRETTY MUCH PLANNED OUT FOR ME.
NOAH.
>> * BUT IT'LL FLY YOU
* LIKE A KITE
* IT'LL THROW YOU
* TO THE GROUND
* BUT THAT'S THE BEST THING
* I HAVE FOUND
>> IS IT SCARY KNOWING
TWO ARE COMING?
>> YEAH, IT SCARED ME WHEN
I FIRST FOUND OUT.
>> YOU'RE ONLY 16 YEARS OLD.
AND IF HE DOESN'T GET THAT,
WE'RE GONNA CONTINUE
TO BUMP HEADS.
YOU NEED TO MEET ME HALFWAY!
>> THEY'RE NOT YOUR KIDS.
I DON'T HAVE TO MEET YOU
HALFWAY.
>> THIS IS SOMETHING YOUR DAD
SHOULD BE HELPING OUT ON.
>> DO YOU WANT OUT OF THIS
RELATIONSHIP, JENNIFER?
>> YEAH, I DO.
THAT'S CALLED KIDNAPPING!
THINK ABOUT YOUR KIDS, JOSH!
YOU WILL NEVER SEE THEM AGAIN!