>> SIX HIGH SCHOOL GIRLS,
SIX TEENAGE PREGNANCIES,
SIX BABIES BROUGHT INTO THE
WORLD AS YOU WATCH FROM HOME.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE TO GIVE BIRTH
ON MTV?
HOW HAS LIFE CHANGED SINCE THE
CAMERAS STOPPED ROLLING?
AND WHAT DOES THE FUTURE HOLD
FOR THESE YOUNG WOMEN AND THEIR
CHILDREN?
THEY'RE ALL HERE READY TO ANSWER
THESE AND MANY MORE OF YOUR
QUESTIONS.
THIS IS THE 16 AND PREGNANT
FINALE SPECIAL: LIFE AFTER
LABOR.
[Filligar's Sunflower Kid]
*
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
* DON'T KNOW HOW
* I'M GONNA GET THROUGH IT ALL
[cheers and applause]
>> I'LL CLAP FOR YOU GUYS.
AND WELCOME TO A VERY SPECIAL
SHOW, AS THE ENTIRE CAST OF
16 AND PREGNANT COMES TOGETHER
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
I'M DR. DREW, AND OVER THE NEXT
HOUR, WE'RE GONNA GET DEEP
INSIDE EACH MOTHER'S STORY.
WE'RE GONNA TALK IN-DEPTH WITH
AMBER, WHITNEY, MACI, CATELYNN,
FARRAH, AND EBONY,
AND THEIR MAIN SUPPORTERS.
THEY'RE IN THE BUILDING AS WELL.
WHICH OF THE FAMILY MEMBERS
STEPPED UP, AND WHICH STEPPED
OUT?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO STAY TUNED
TO SEE WHO'S HERE.
BUT FIRST, I'VE GOT SOME
QUESTIONS FOR YOU GUYS.
IMAGINE THAT.
MACI, WHAT'S THE HARDEST PART
ABOUT BEING A MOM?
>> WELL, I THINK THE HARDEST
PART ABOUT BEING A TEEN MOM IS
BEING YOUNG AND HAVING TO GROW
UP WITHIN NINE MONTHS AND HAVING
TO BE READY AND LOSE FRIENDS AND
GAIN FRIENDS AND WORRY ABOUT
PEOPLE AND WHAT THEY'RE SAYING,
AND THEN, BEING A MOM IS JUST
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
YOU'RE GONNA GET YOUR ENERGY,
HOW YOU'RE GONNA DO THIS,
HOW YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THAT,
HOW YOU'RE--JUST EVERYTHING.
YOU JUST HAVE TO GET EVERYTHING
INTO ONE LITTLE PACKAGE IN NINE
MONTHS.
>> YOU HAVE TO LET GO OF YOUR
YOUTH AND BECOME A GROWN-UP,
BOOM.
>> RIGHT, IN A SECOND.
>> AND YOU HOPE YOUR PARTNER
KEEPS UP WITH THAT.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND, AMBER, LABOR WAS TOUGH,
RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH.
[laughter]
>> HOW BAD WAS IT?
>> WELL, THEY DIDN'T SHOW
EVERYTHING EXACTLY ON THE SHOW.
I PUKED 51 TIMES DURING IT.
>> BUT WHO'S COUNTING?
>> THE NURSE WAS COUNTING.
[laughter]
>> EBONY, MOTHERHOOD'S TOUGH AT
ANY AGE.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE DOING IT
THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL?
>> IN YOUR SENIOR YEAR, YOU WANT
TO PARTY, AND YOU'RE DONE WITH
HIGH SCHOOL NOW, AND I WAS
PREGNANT FROM THE START TO THE
END OF MY SENIOR YEAR.
>> WELL, BEFORE WE GET GOING,
LET'S LOOK AT A QUICK LOOK BACK
AT SIX INCREDIBLE STORIES.
HERE'S WHAT WENT DOWN ON THIS
SEASON OF 16 AND PREGNANT.
>> MOM!
>> WHAT?
>> I THINK MY WATER JUST BROKE.
>> SHE'S 16 YEARS OLD.
SHE'S A BABY.
>> I JUST CANNOT HANDLE THIS.
>> PUSH, PUSH.
>> IF I GAVE HER UP FOR
ADOPTION, LIKE, I HAD GIVEN
SOMEBODY, LIKE, AN AWESOME GIFT.
>> I AM A TEENAGER.
YOU DON'T CARE.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME.
>> WE CAN'T STAND IT HERE
ANYMORE.
>> TOMORROW, Y'ALL NEED TO MOVE.
>> ALL THAT BABY NEEDS IS LOVE.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT ALL A BABY
NEEDS IS LOVE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT PARENTING.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HAVING
A BEAUTIFUL SITUATION RIGHT
NOW, HUH, FARRAH?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I HAVE TO DEAL
WITH YOU; YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
>> HOLD HIM, AND HE WILL STOP
CRYING.
>> NO, I'LL LEAVE, PERIOD.
>> THEN LEAVE.
>> [crying] LIKE, I'M JUST THE
ONE THAT GREW UP TOO FAST.
AND I WANT HIM TO GROW UP TOO.
>> WELL, I JUST FEEL LIKE
EVERYBODY IS STARING AT ME,
BECAUSE I HAVE A BEACH BALL
UNDER MY SHIRT.
>> I KNOW THAT YOU GUYS CAN
PROVIDE FOR HER A LOT
MORE THAN I CAN.
I JUST WANT HER TO HAVE
BETTER THAN WHAT I HAD.
>> IF WE DIDN'T HAVE A KID,
WE WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
>> I AM HERE WITH ONE OF OUR
TEEN MOMS AND HER MOM AS WELL.
FARRAH, DEBRA, WELCOME TO THE
SHOW, GUYS.
[cheers and applause]
SO, FARRAH, FROM CHEERLEADER TO
MOM, I MEAN, WHAT WAS THAT
TRANSITION LIKE FROM HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENT TO PARENT?
>> IT WAS A BIG TRANSITION.
IT WAS A LOT FOR ME TO GET USED
TO, BUT IT WAS NECESSARY,
AND I THOUGHT I WAS ALLOWED
PLENTY OF TIME, I GUESS, THE
NINE MONTHS WAS PLENTY OF TIME
FOR ME TO DO IT.
>> WERE THERE FRIENDS THERE TO
SUPPORT YOU?
>> I DID HAVE SOME FRIENDS THAT
WERE THERE TO SUPPORT ME.
I STILL HAVE SOME OF THOSE
FRIENDS, BUT LOTS OF THEM,
UNFORTUNATELY, I DON'T TALK TO
ANYMORE.
>> SOUNDS PAINFUL.
>> NO.
>> NOT PAINFUL.
>> YOU DON'T WANT SOMETHING THAT
HOLDS YOU BACK IN LIFE.
>> AND THE BABY, SOPHIA, HOW'S
SHE DOING?
>> GREAT.
SHE'S GROWING.
SHE'S FOUR MONTHS NOW.
>> FANTASTIC.
WELL, LET'S TAKE A LOOK BACK AT
FARRAH'S JOURNEY ON 16 AND
PREGNANT.
>> EVERYBODY AT EVERY SCHOOL
IS SAYING THE RUMORS.
NONE OF THE GIRLS KNOW
BESIDES YOU AND COURTNEY, SO...
>> YOU'RE THAT POPULAR, FARRAH.
>> AND YOU KNOW THEY JUDGE YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE A SINGLE MOM.
>> THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
LEADERS.
>> CHEER "LEADERS," NOT CHEER
"FOLLOWERS."
>> AFTER YOU HAVE THE BABY,
YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA BE ALL
PUFFED UP.
>> NO, I PLAN ON NOT BEING
THAT PUFFED UP.
I'M SO SORRY EVERYONE HAS
TO LOOK AT MY CROTCH RIGHT NOW.
I JUST CANNOT HANDLE THIS.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> [crying]
>> OH, SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> HOW MUCH WOULD YOU HELP A
LITTLE BIT?
>> PROBABLY NOT TOO MUCH.
>> THAT IS SERIOUSLY JUST
PISSING ME OFF.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HAVING
A BEAUTIFUL SITUATION RIGHT
NOW, HUH, FARRAH?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I HAVE TO DEAL
WITH YOU; YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
>> SO, DEBRA, THE SMACK:
PEOPLE AROUND HERE ARE CALLING
THAT "THE SMACK HEARD AROUND THE
WORLD."
IS IT OKAY TO HIT YOUR KIDS?
DO YOU WANT FARRAH TO HIT
SOPHIA?
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW THAT I
ACTUALLY HIT HER.
I WAS DRIVING DOWN THE ROAD KIND
OF FAST, AND I HIT SOMETHING.
>> DO YOU REGRET YELLING AT HER?
>> NO.
>> YOU DON'T REGRET YELLING AT
HER.
>> NO, I THINK THAT IT'S--AS A
PARENT, IF YOU LOVE YOUR CHILD,
YOU HAVE TO TELL THEM WHEN--WHEN
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH ON SOMETHING.
YOU HAVE TO--YOU'RE THERE TO
GUIDE THEM.
IT DOESN'T MEAN YOU'RE
OVERBEARING, AS I'VE BEEN
CALLED, BUT IT MEANS THAT YOU
HAVE TO LOVE THEM--
>> OVERBEARING?
IS YOUR MOM OVERBEARING?
>> SHE'S MY MOM.
SHE DOES--
>> IS YOUR MOM OVERBEARING?
>> I WOULD SAY NO.
>> NO.
>> NO, DR. DREW, NO.
>> OKAY.
[laughter]
WELL, YOU DIDN'T HAVE A BABY
DADDY, BUT YOU HAD YOUR MOMMY.
>> YES.
>> WAS THAT HELPFUL?
>> YES, I WOULD PREFER IT BE
WITH MY MOM THAN THE BABY DADDY,
SO I WAS VERY LUCKY IN THAT
SENSE.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU WATCH
THE SEGMENT, YOU SEE A LOT OF
DRAMA WITH YOU GUYS.
IS THAT WORKING OUT BETTER NOW?
IS IT...
>> WHEN I WATCH THE OTHER GIRLS
WITH THEIR BABY DADDIES,
IT SEEMED LOTS OF DRAMA KIND OF
WITH THAT, THOUGH, TOO.
>> IT'S TRUE.
IT PUTS A LOT OF STRESS ON
RELATIONSHIPS.
WELL, THROUGHOUT TODAY'S SHOW,
WE'RE GOING TO BE TAKING
QUESTIONS FROM OUR STUDIO
AUDIENCE AS WELL AS VIEWERS AT
HOME.
JESSICA HERE IN THE AUDIENCE HAS
A QUESTION FOR FARRAH.
>> HI, FARRAH, I'M JESSICA.
I CAN REALLY RELATE TO YOU,
BECAUSE I WAS A SINGLE TEEN MOM
AND HAD TO JUMP BACK INTO THE
DATING SCENE AT ONE POINT,
SO I WAS WONDERING, HAVE YOU
BEEN GOING ON ANY DATES, OR DO
YOU CURRENTLY HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
>> MM, I WISH I COULD FIND A
MAN.
[laughter]
>> DEBRA, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT FARRAH DATING?
>> WELL, I THINK SHE'S GOT SO
MANY OTHER PRIORITIES RIGHT NOW,
BUT I TOLD HER THAT IF SHE WANTS
TO DATE, AND IF SHE FINDS
SOMEBODY THAT IS FLEXIBLE ENOUGH
TO UNDERSTAND HER SCHEDULING AND
SO FORTH DEMANDS, I NEED TO MEET
HIM.
WE NEED SOMEBODY REAL.
WE DON'T NEED ANY STORIES OR
WANNABES.
WE NEED SOMEBODY THAT'S
ABSOLUTELY A REAL PERSON.
>> SOMEBODY WHO LOVES FARRAH?
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
>> AND SOPHIA.
YOU HAVE TO LOVE THE WHOLE
PACKAGE.
>> YEAH, IT IS A PACKAGE,
INCLUDING ME.
[laughter]
>> THANK GOD, OF COURSE.
>> WELL, THERE'S SOMETHING I
WOULD LIKE TO ADD.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING A LOT ABOUT
THE TOUGH CHOICES THAT COME
WITH TEEN PREGNANCY:
WHETHER OR NOT TO STAY IN
SCHOOL, WHAT TO DO ABOUT YOUR
CAREER, ABORTIONS, ADOPTION,
SO MUCH MORE.
BUT IF PREVENTION OCCURS
AND TEENS ARE SMART ABOUT HOW
THEY CONDUCT THEMSELVES, THESE
IMPOSSIBLE DECISIONS DO NOT HAVE
TO BE THEN MADE, SO LEARN MORE
ABOUT PREVENTION BY LOGGING ON
TO 16ANDPREGNANT--
THAT'S THE NUMBER--
16ANDPREGNANT.MTV.COM--
AND STAY IN CONTROL OF YOUR
LIFE.
BUT FOR NOW, WE'LL PAUSE FOR
SOME COMMERCIALS, AND WHEN WE
RETURN, WE'LL BE JOINED BY
BENTLEY'S MOM, MACI.
MACI TOLD HER MOTHER SHE WAS
PREGNANT--GET THIS--VIA A
TEXT MESSAGE.
BUT TODAY SHE WAS KIND ENOUGH TO
JOIN US IN PERSON.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[applause]
>> AND WELCOME BACK.
I AM DR. DREW, AND THIS IS
THE 16 AND PREGNANT FINALE
SPECIAL: LIFE AFTER LABOR.
NOW, FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A
GENERATION, TEEN PREGNANCIES ARE
ON THE RISE IN THIS COUNTRY, AND
ONE HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT WHO GOT
PREGNANT AT THE TENDER AGE OF 16
JOINS ME HERE TODAY.
MACI, THANK YOU FOR COMING.
SO WHAT'S IT BEEN LIKE?
HOW HAS THE ADJUSTMENT BEEN WITH
THE BABY?
>> IT'S CRAZY.
YOU'RE BUSY ALL THE TIME, 24-7.
YOU NEVER GET A BREAK.
YOU HAVE TO PACK THINGS,
AND YOU CAN'T FORGET ANYTHING,
OR YOU'RE IN BIG TROUBLE,
AND RELATIONSHIPS ARE HARD,
AND MONEY IS HARD, AND JUST
EVERYTHING.
IT'S A HUGE CHANGE FROM BEING
16 TO BEING 16 AND A MOM.
>> CAN YOU UPDATE US ON BENTLEY?
HOW'S HE DOING?
>> HE'S WONDERFUL.
HE'S EIGHT MONTHS OLD, AND HE
JUST STARTED CRAWLING, LIKE, A
WEEK AND A HALF AGO.
HE HAS NO TEETH.
HE JUST DECIDED NOT TO GET ANY,
I GUESS.
[laughter]
HE SLEEPS THROUGH THE NIGHT,
WHICH IS AWESOME.
I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S AWESOME.
HE HAS THE BEST PERSONALITY,
AND IT'S JUST A REALLY FUN AGE
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S AWESOME.
>> NICE, WELL, WE'LL TALK ABOUT
BENTLEY'S FATHER, RYAN,
IN A MINUTE--LET ME AT HIM--
BUT FIRST, HERE'S A QUICK TRIP
DOWN MEMORY LANE.
>> [crying]
>> IT'S YOUR TURN.
>> CAN'T YOU JUST HOLD HIM TILL
I GET DONE WITH MY HOMEWORK?
>> I DON'T THINK HE WAS,
LIKE, READY TO HAVE A KID YET.
>> AND I WASN'T READY EITHER,
BUT I GREW UP BECAUSE I HAD TO.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OKAY.
>> SO YOU DON'T THINK RYAN WILL
COME BY?
>> WHY DON'T YOU TEXT HIM?
>> YOU WANT ME TO TEXT HIM?
>> YEAH, HIS MOM--
>> NO, 'CAUSE THEN I'LL BE
THE WITCHY MOTHER-IN-LAW.
>> SO?
>> [laughs]
>> HOLD HIM, AND HE WILL STOP
CRYING.
>> NO, I'LL LEAVE, PERIOD.
>> THEN LEAVE.
I MEAN, I DON'T THINK IF WE
WERE IN THIS SITUATION,
WE WOULD BE THIS UNHAPPY
RIGHT NOW.
>> NO, IF WE DIDN'T HAVE A KID,
WE WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
>> OKAY, WELL, I DON'T WANT YOU
TO STAY HERE BECAUSE YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU HAVE TO.
>> WELL, MACI, AT ONE POINT,
YOU SAID YOU FELT LIKE YOU HAD
TWO BABIES.
>> MM-HMM.
>> RYAN?
>> YES.
>> IS HE STILL--YOU STILL HAVE
TWINS?
>> UM...
IT'S GETTING BETTER.
I'VE GOT TWO DIFFERENT-AGED
TWINS.
>> OH, HE'S STILL BEHAVING LIKE
A LITTLE CHILD.
>> WELL, NO.
HE'S GOTTEN A LOT BETTER.
IT TOOK HIM--IT TOOK HIM A WHILE
TO ADJUST FROM BEING AN ONLY
CHILD TO BEING A FATHER.
I DON'T THINK I HAD AS MUCH
PATIENCE FOR HIM AS I SHOULD
HAVE, BUT, I MEAN, HE'S STILL
NOT PERFECT, BUT HE'S DEFINITELY
GETTING THERE.
HE'S DOING A WHOLE LOT BETTER,
AND I THINK SEEING THE SHOW
HELPED CHANGE HIM A LOT.
HE FINALLY REALIZED HOW SELFISH
HE WAS BEING, SO HE'S DOING A
LOT BETTER NOW.
>> SO REALLY ACTUALLY VIEWING
YOUR PROGRAM IS WHAT BROKE
THROUGH TO HIM AND GOT HIM TO
STEP IT UP A BIT?
>> I THINK HIS PARENTS AND MY
PARENTS BOTH SAW THE PROBLEMS WE
WERE HAVING, AND HIS DAD, I
THINK, WAS KIND OF DISAPPOINTED
IN THE WAY HE WAS ACTING,
BECAUSE HIS PARENTS DIDN'T RAISE
HIM TO BE THAT WAY, AND SO HIS
DAD HAD TO TALK TO HIM A FEW
TIMES, AND AFTER SEEING THE
SHOW, I THINK IT ALL JUST
FINALLY GOT TO HIM, AND HE
REALIZED EVERYTHING.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU GIVEN UP TO BE
A TEEN MOM?
>> EVERYTHING.
YOU GIVE UP YOUR SOCIAL LIFE.
YOU GIVE UP HAVING TO FIGURE OUT
HOW YOU'RE GONNA GRADUATE HIGH
SCHOOL.
YOU GIVE UP YOUR SENIOR PROM.
YOU GIVE UP YOUR ATHLETICS AT
SCHOOL.
YOU GIVE UP ALMOST EVERYTHING,
BUT TO GAIN SOMETHING ELSE.
>> I KNOW THE PEOPLE THAT STUDY
SINGLE MOMS ALWAYS SAY THE ONE
THING THEY WANT TO GIVE THEM IS
A SUPPORTIVE PARTNER.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHERE IS YOUR SUPPORTIVE
PARTNER?
>> UM...
NOW, IT'S RYAN, BUT AT FIRST,
IT WAS JUST ME.
[laughs]
[exhales]
UM--
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WANT TO TALK TO THAT YOUNG
MAN.
WHERE IS HE?
>> HE'S HERE.
>> CAN I TALK TO HIM?
>> MM-HMM.
>> CAN YOU GET HIM FOR ME?
>> [laughs]
RYAN, YOU CAN COME OUT.
[laughter]
[applause]
>> [whispers]
>> NO.
[audience awws]
[light laughter]
>> [sniffles]
>> WHERE WERE YOU?
>> I WASN'T THERE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> GOT SCARED.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU JUST TOOK OFF?
>> I MEAN, I WAS THERE, BUT I
WASN'T THERE.
I DIDN'T--
>> HE WAS THERE IN A SENSE
THAT--
>> DON'T RESCUE HIM.
>> I--WELL, I--
>> DO NOT RESCUE HIM.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO.
>> HANG ON.
>> OKAY.
>> LET'S TAKE A BREAK, BUT DO
NOT GO ANYWHERE, BECAUSE LATER
IN THE SHOW, WE HAVE AN
EMOTIONAL REUNION WITH CATELYNN
AND BABY CARLY, WHEN THE
16 AND PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL
RETURNS.
[applause]
BABY WESTON HAS SOME MEDICAL
ISSUES.
>> YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT HIM NOW KNOWING THAT HE
HAS SOMETHING WRONG WITH HIM.
>> IT'S BETTER WITHOUT A CONDOM.
>> DON'T LISTEN TO THAT.
[cheers and applause]
[applause]
>> AND WELCOME BACK TO
16 AND PREGNANT: LIFE AFTER
LABOR FINALE SPECIAL.
I'M DR. DREW.
LET'S GET INTO IT HERE.
DO YOU NEED TO MAKE AN APOLOGY
TO MACI?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> WELL, I WANT TO HEAR IT
MYSELF.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> FOR NOT HELPING.
>> OKAY.
>> FOR BEING THERE...
>> AREN'T YOU P.O.'D?
>> ME?
YEAH.
>> TELL HIM.
>> I'M PISSED OFF.
[laughter]
>> HOW COME?
>> BECAUSE IN A WAY,
WHENEVER I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, YOU HAVE TO GIVE UP SO
MUCH.
YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH
EVERYTHING, AND YOU CAN'T BE
WEAK, OR IT WILL KILL YOU.
YOU CAN'T BE WEAK AT ALL.
EVERY PART OF STRENGTH IN YOUR
BODY HAS TO COME OUT,
AND IT'S EASIER WHEN YOU'RE
DOING IT WITH SOMEONE,
AND I HAD TO BE STRONG BY
MYSELF, AND I DIDN'T HAVE
ANYBODY TO TALK TO, BECAUSE I
COULDN'T TALK TO MY BEST
FRIENDS, BECAUSE THEY HAD NO
IDEA WHAT I WAS GOING THROUGH.
NOBODY DID.
NOBODY KNOWS AT ALL, AND...
>> YOU DIDN'T CARE?
>> I WAS JUST ANGRY.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> I MEAN, I COULDN'T TALK TO
HER.
SHE COULDN'T TALK TO ME.
I MEAN, WE DIDN'T GET ALONG.
IT WAS, LIKE--IT WAS HORRIBLE,
SO, I MEAN, I GUESS I TOOK IT
OUT ON BOTH OF THEM.
>> CAN YOU TRUST HIM NOW?
>> MM-HMM.
I CAN.
>> SHOULD SHE?
>> YEAH.
>> HAVE YOU DONE ANYTHING
TO HELP HER FEEL MORE
SECURE?
>> [exhales]
SHE'S GOT A RING.
>> SO YOU'RE GONNA GET MARRIED?
>> MM-HMM.
[audience awws]
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
OKAY, I'M GONNA BUST YOUR BALLS
A LITTLE MORE.
YOU SAID SOMETHING PRETTY AWFUL
AT ONE POINT, WHICH IS THAT YOU
WOULDN'T BE TOGETHER IF IT
WEREN'T FOR BENTLEY.
YOU STILL FEEL THAT WAY?
>> NO, BUT AT THE TIME, I MEAN,
IT WAS JUST--WE JUST ARGUED AND
FOUGHT CONSTANTLY, AND, I MEAN,
THAT WAS--I MEAN, THE ONLY
REASON WHY...
>> HE'S SAYING, IF WE HADN'T
HAVE HAD BENTLEY, AND WE FOUGHT
AND ARGUED LIKE THAT, WE WOULD
NOT HAVE BEEN TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, WE WOULDN'T HAVE WASTED
THE TIME TRYING.
I MEAN, WE WOULD HAVE JUST--
>> RIGHT, BUT--
>> WELL, IT'S AN IMPORTANT
POINT, BECAUSE IT'S SOMETHING
THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE DO, IS,
THEY GO, "SCREW IT.
I'M OUT OF HERE."
BUT YOU STAYED IN, AND YOU
FORGED SOMETHING.
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING GOING NOW,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
>> I MEAN, WE HAVE EACH OTHER
AND BENTLEY.
>> DO YOU LOVE MACI?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YOU LOVE RYAN?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HAPPY GETTING MARRIED?
>> RYAN.
>> I MEAN, I DIDN'T KNOW WHO YOU
WERE ASKING.
>> YOU TOOK AT BEAT THERE, DUDE.
THEY ANSWER IS, "YES, I'M
DELIGHTED."
WE HAVE PAUL IN THE AUDIENCE,
WHO'S GOT A QUESTION FOR US.
PAUL?
>> HI, GUYS.
I'M JUST WONDERING IF YOU EVER
CONSIDERED ABORTION.
>> MM, THAT'S A HEAVY QUESTION.
>> NO.
>> NEVER.
>> NOPE.
>> RYAN.
>> NO.
>> HUH?
>> NO, NEVER.
>> WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE--WHO ARE YOU ASKING?
>> BOTH OF YOU.
WHEN I ASK QUESTIONS, YOU'RE
BOTH ENTITLED TO ANSWER.
WHY NOT?
>> IT'S JUST NOT FOR ME.
I--I DON'T KNOW.
I--AS SOON AS I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, I DIDN'T CRY.
I DIDN'T FREAK OUT.
I WAS JUST LIKE, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
HERE WE GO.
LET'S GO."
ADOPTION OR ABORTION JUST--
>> SO ADOPTION WAS AN OPTION
FOR YOU.
>> THEY'RE OPTIONS, BUT NEITHER
ONE OF THEM WERE OPTIONS FOR ME,
NOT FOR--NOT FOR THE SUPPORT I
HAD FROM MY FAMILY, AND AT THE
TIME, THE RELATIONSHIP THAT WE
DID HAVE, AND IT JUST--WE COULD
DO IT.
>> DID YOU WANT TO GET PREGNANT?
>> NO.
>> IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
>> YES.
>> BUT YOU WERE UP TO THE
CHALLENGE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY, HAVE YOU GIVEN UP A LOT
TOO, RYAN?
WE'VE HEARD THE MOMS KEEP
TALKING ABOUT HOW MUCH THEY'VE
GIVEN UP.
HAVE YOU GIVEN UP A LOT?
>> I MEAN...YEAH,
BUT I DON'T THINK I'VE GIVEN UP
AS MUCH AS SHE HAS.
>> I THINK THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE HEARD YOU SAY THAT.
>> WELL, GUYS, MACI AND RYAN,
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
THANK YOU FOR SITTING THROUGH
THE GRILLING, RYAN.
>> THANKS FOR MAKING ME CRY...
>> I BEG YOUR PARDON.
>> THE WHOLE TIME.
>> I'M SORRY, BUT IT'S REAL.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
I MEAN, THIS IS YOUR LIFE,
AND IT'S A GOOD SITUATION,
RIGHT?
>> THAT YOU WANT TO BE IN WHEN
YOU'RE 30.
[laughter]
>> OKAY, WELL, THANK YOU FOR
BEING HERE.
MACI IS GOING TO ANSWER MORE
QUESTIONS DURING OUR SPOTLIGHT
SESSION, WHEN ALL THE TEEN MOMS
GET A CHANCE TO FACE EACH OTHER
FOR THE FIRST TIME AND ASK
ANYTHING THEY WANT.
THAT'S GONNA BE INTERESTING.
WHEN THE 16 AND PREGNANT
FINALE SPECIAL RETURNS,
WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT BABY LEAH
AND SEE HOW HER PARENTS, AMBER
AND GARY, ARE COPING.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO THE
16 AND PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL:
LIFE AFTER LABOR.
NOW, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
NEARLY 3 OUT OF EVERY 10
AMERICAN GIRLS WILL BECOME
PREGNANT BEFORE THEY TURN 20.
WE HAVE THE HIGHEST RATE OF TEEN
PREGNANCY AMONGST ALL
INDUSTRIALIZED NATIONS,
AND ON 16 AND PREGNANT,
WE MET SIX YOUNG WOMEN WHO
UNEXPECTEDLY BECAME MOMS
THEMSELVES.
ONE OF THOSE NEW MOMS IS AMBER
HERE WITH THE MAN IN HER LIFE,
GARY.
HI, GUYS.
>> HI.
[applause]
>> HOW IS BABY LEAH DOING?
>> SHE'S DOING GREAT.
SHE LOOKS COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
THAN WHEN SHE WAS BORN.
>> SHOCKING.
>> OH, YEAH.
SHE'S SO MUCH BIGGER,
AND SHE'S BEEN CRAWLING,
AND SHE SAYS "MAMA, DADA,
BABA," AND...
>> SHE HAS FOUR TEETH AND TWO
MORE COMING IN.
>> FOUR TEETH.
IT'S, LIKE, A LITTLE RABBIT
TEETH.
IT'S SO CUTE.
>> BEFORE WE TALK FURTHER,
LET'S REVISIT YOUR EXPERIENCE
ON 16 AND PREGNANT.
>> DID YOU JUST BUY THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW MUCH WAS IT?
>> IT WAS, LIKE,
A COUPLE HUNDRED DOLLARS.
>> THAT'S MONEY WE COULD BE
SAVING UP FOR THE BABY.
>> GARY, WHEN IT COMES TO
PRIORITIES, THE FAMILY'S FIRST.
YOUR LITTLE TOYS GOT TO WAIT.
>> WHY DID YOU TELL YOUR MOM
ABOUT THE PS3?
YOU SAID YOU WOULDN'T.
IT MAKES ME LOOK LIKE AN ASS
WHEN I WORKED OVERTIME.
>> BECAUSE YOU ARE AN ASS FOR
DOING IT.
YOU DON'T CARE.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME.
I WANT A C-SECTION.
>> [crying]
>> DOES SHE COME WITH ANY
INSTRUCTIONS?
>> SHUT UP, GARY.
>> THE DADDY GUIDE.
I DON'T NEED NO DADDY GUIDE.
>> AT LEAST THEY'RE NOT MARRIED.
>> YEAH, NO KIDDING.
>> I'M GONNA PROPOSE.
>> OOOH.
>> THAT'S $21.40.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR RETURN
POLICY ON THEM IS?
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULD
MARRY ME.
[laughter]
>> SORRY.
>> $21.40?
>> HEY, IT'S THE ONE SHE WANTED.
IT REALLY IS, TRULY, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> NO, NO, IT WASN'T.
WE WERE WALKING AROUND WAL-MART
ONE DAY, AND SHE SAW IT,
AND SHE LIKES REALLY FLASHY
RINGS, AND I HADN'T PLANNED
ON PROPOSING TO HER,
AND THEN, LIKE, AN OPPORTUNITY
PRESENTED ITSELF.
>> GARY.
>> WHAT?
>> OKAY, GO AHEAD.
>> $21.40 ON THE RING.
[laughter]
$400 ON THE--
>> $500.
>> $500 ON THE GAME CONSOLE.
>> TO BE EXACT, IT WAS $480.
>> DUDE, DUDE, WHAT--
PRIORITIES STRAIGHT?
>> NO, IT'S JUST I WAS THINKING,
LIKE, IF I WAIT FOR THE
FINANCES, LIKE, OKAY, YEAH, I
SHOULD HAVE MAYBE BOUGHT A MORE
EXPENSIVE RING AND MAYBE NOT
BOUGHT THE PS3...
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T
MATTER HOW MUCH THE RING WAS.
>> BUT...BECAUSE I LOVE YOU,
AND THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
I LOVE HER, AND MY...
[applause]
MY LOVE GOES FURTHER THAN $21.
>> [laughs]
>> YOU KNOW, IF I COULD--
I'D BUY HER ANYTHING IF I
COULD, BUT...
>> OKAY, THE FACT THAT YOU GOT
PREGNANT AS A TEENAGER,
DOES THAT CHANGE YOUR THINKING
ABOUT CONTRACEPTION AND
UNPROTECTED SEX?
>> YEAH, COMPLETELY.
IF WE DON'T HAVE CONDOMS OR
ANYTHING, WE DO NOT HAVE SEX.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S SO HARD TO BE YOUNG AND
HAVE A BABY, BECAUSE YOU DON'T
GET TO DO WHAT YOU USED TO DO.
>> I RECOMMEND GETTING THE
INDUSTRIAL-SIZED BOX.
>> HOLD ON.
[laughter]
BUT--BUT THAT MAKES YOU SAD,
RIGHT?
YOU LOST A LOT.
>> IT DOES MAKE ME SAD THAT I
DID LOSE SOME OF THE EXPERIENCES
THAT I COULD HAVE HAD.
>> BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T USE A
CONDOM.
>> BECAUSE OF--YES, BECAUSE
OF...
>> EVERY TIME.
>> I--FOR SOME REASON--
>> WAS IT JUST ONE TIME, OR WAS
IT--
>> NO, WE HADN'T BEEN USING A
CONDOM BASICALLY THE WHOLE TIME.
>> WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WERE YOU TRYING TO GET
PREGNANT?
>> NO, I DON'T--I KNOW IT SOUNDS
SO STUPID, AND IT IS.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
I REALLY DON'T.
AND ONE OF THE THINGS WAS,
WELL, HE DIDN'T FEEL IT.
>> IF WE DIDN'T HAVE A CONDOM,
I WAS LIKE, "LET'S DO IT
ANYWAY," YOU KNOW.
>> YEAH, THAT'S HOW IT WAS.
>> HE DIDN'T WHAT?
>> NO, NO.
[laughter]
>> HE DIDN'T FINISH.
IS THAT WHAT YOU SAID?
>> NO, HE COULDN'T FEEL.
>> OH, YEAH, SO--
>> WHAT?
>> YOU KNOW HOW GUYS SAY--
>> NO, IT'S BETTER WITHOUT A
CONDOM.
>> GUYS DON'T LIKE CONDOMS, SOME
GUYS.
>> IT'S NOT--WELL, OBVIOUSLY,
IT'S NOT BETTER IF YOU DON'T
WANT TO GET PREGNANT.
I MEAN--
>> WELL, IN THAT FACT, IT AIN'T.
THERE'S--YOU'VE GOT TO LOOK AT
THE DIFFERENT FACTORS.
FOR PLEASURE, IT'S BETTER
WITHOUT A CONDOM.
FOR NOT KEEPING PROTECTION,
IT'S BETTER WITH A CONDOM, SO...
>> GARY, NO, DON'T LISTEN TO
THAT.
[laughter]
>> BUT--BUT THE "FOR HIS
PLEASURE" COST YOU YOUR
CHILDHOOD AND YOUR YOUTH.
>> I DON'T WANT TO PUT IT ALL ON
HIM, BECAUSE IT WAS MY FAULT
TOO.
I COULD HAVE SAID NO, LIKE WE DO
NOW.
I COULD HAVE SAID, "NO, IF WE
DON'T HAVE SOMETHING, THEN LET'S
NOT DO IT," BUT I DIDN'T,
SO IT'S BOTH OF OUR FAULTS,
BUT WE'RE LIVING.
WE'RE DOING A GOOD JOB.
I THINK WE'RE GREAT PARENTS.
WE'RE NOT PERFECT.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T REALLY THINK
ANYBODY IS, BUT I THINK WE'RE
GOOD PARENTS.
I DO.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT OTHER KIDS
TO KNOW ABOUT THIS?
>> I DON'T WANT THEM TO THINK
THAT WE'RE TRYING TO
GLAMORIZE...
>> TEEN PREGNANCY.
>> TEEN PREGNANCIES, 'CAUSE
IT'S NOT GLAMOROUS.
I THINK THAT THIS SHOW SHOWS ALL
DIFFERENT PEOPLE, ALL DIFFERENT
STORIES, DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS,
AND IT SHOULD PORTRAY TO EACH
ONE OF YOU GUYS AND REALLY,
YOU KNOW, IT SHOULD HIT EVERY
ONE OF YOU GUYS A SOFT SPOT
SOMEWHERE, AND, YOU KNOW, SO YOU
UNDERSTAND THAT, "YOU KNOW, I
NEED TO WAIT."
>> WELL, THANK YOU, GARY AND
AMBER, FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE WILL HAVE MORE WITH AMBER
DURING THE SPOTLIGHT SESSION,
WHEN ALL THE TEEN MOMS GET A
CHANCE TO FACE EACH OTHER FOR
THE FIRST TIME AND ASK ANYTHING
THEY WANT.
THAT'S GONNA BE INTERESTING,
TO SAY THE LEAST, AND PLUS,
WE'LL HAVE ALL THE BABIES HERE
ON THE STAGE TOGETHER, SO STAY
TUNED FOR THAT.
OH, YES.
WHEN WE RETURN, WE'LL CHECK IN
WITH EBONY AND JOSH.
THERE WAS A TIME WHEN JOSH
WAS--HE WAS LITERALLY KISSING
EBONY'S FEET,
BUT YOU THINK BABY JOCELYN MIGHT
HAVE CHANGED ALL THAT?
STAY TUNED TO FIND OUT.
THE 16 AND PREGNANT FINALE
SPECIAL RETURNS RIGHT AFTER
THIS, SO DON'T GO AWAY.
[applause]
WE HAVE AN EMOTIONAL REUNION
WITH CATELYNN AND BABY CARLY.
>> CAN I HOLD HER?
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
SHOULD WE BRING OUT THE BABIES?
>> together: YES.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND
PREGNANT: THE LIFE AFTER LABOR
FINALE SPECIAL,
WITH THE ENTIRE CAST OF
16 AND PREGNANT COMING TOGETHER
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME.
NOW, IN A LITTLE BIT, WE'RE
GONNA TALK TO CATELYNN AND TYLER
ABOUT THEIR DECISION TO OPT FOR
ADOPTION.
WE ALSO HAVE SOMETHING VERY
SPECIAL IN STORE FOR THEM, WHICH
YOU CANNOT AFFORD TO MISS.
HANG IN FOR THAT.
BUT FIRST, I'M JOINED BY BABY
JOCELYN'S PARENTS, EBONY AND
JOSH.
HI, GUYS.
>> HEY.
>> HELLO.
>> SO...
[applause]
DID I HEAR RIGHT THAT YOU'VE GOT
SOME NEWS FOR US?
>> WE HAD A BABY.
>> WOW, THAT IS ASTONISHING.
>> NO, WE GOT MARRIED ON THE
25TH.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU FEELING OKAY ABOUT THAT,
JOSH?
>> YEAH, IT WAS ALL RIGHT.
YOU UP...
[laughs]
YOU UP TO BEING A HUSBAND AND A
DAD?
>> YEAH, AND NOW WE'VE GOT A
WHOLE FAMILY COMPLETE.
>> A WHOLE FAMILY.
>> THIS WAS A GOOD DECISION, YOU
THINK?
>> YEAH, IN THE LONG RUN IT IS,
YEAH.
[laughter]
>> AND, EBONY, HAS JOSH STEPPED
UP AND GROWN UP?
>> BIG-TIME, BIG-TIME.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> HE REALLY HAS, YES.
>> HAS HE?
TELL ME HOW.
>> WELL, THE ONLY THING HE
DOES NOT DO IS, HE DOES NOT
CHANGE POOPIE DIAPERS, BECAUSE
SOMETHING SO BEAUTIFUL MAKES
SOMETHING EXTREMELY STINKY.
I MEAN, THE WORST POOPIE DIAPERS
YOU EVER SMELLED, SO...YEAH,
WE CAN'T KEEP HER IN AN ENCLOSED
ROOM.
>> EVERYTHING ELSE, THOUGH:
HE'S ON TOP OF THINGS.
HE'S NOT SLEEPING WHILE HE'S
TAKING CARE OF THE BABY.
HE'S ATTENTIVE TO YOU.
HE'S SUPPORTIVE.
>> YES, HE IS.
HE IS ALL OF THE ABOVE.
>> EXCELLENT.
WELL, BEFORE WE MOVE ON,
LET'S TAKE A LOOK BACK AT
EBONY'S EXPERIENCE BEING
16 AND PREGNANT.
>> PROM'S IN APRIL.
THE BABY IS DUE IN MAY.
I CAN'T FIT IN THIS DRESS.
>> MAYBE IF HE HAD KEPT IT IN
HIS PANTS AND NOT KNOCKED
SOMEBODY UP, IT WOULDN'T HAVE
BEEN THIS WAY.
>> PUSH.
>> LOOK AT HOW CUTE SHE IS.
>> [crying] LIKE, I'M JUST THE
ONE THAT GREW UP TOO FAST.
AND I WANT HIM TO GROW UP TOO.
SO I HAD TO SACRIFICE GRADUATING
AND GOING INTO THE AIR FORCE.
YOU'RE HER FATHER, AND YOU NEED
TO ACT LIKE IT.
>> I DO ACT LIKE I'M HER FATHER.
WHAT THE [bleep] ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'VE BEEN WORKING MY ASS OFF
JUST TO GRADUATE, AND THEN I
GOT TO WORRY ABOUT
ENLISTING INTO THE AIR FORCE,
SO I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO
SEE YOU GUYS THAT MUCH AT ALL.
SACRIFICES.
>> JOSH, SOMETHING THAT JUMPS
OUT AT ME, YOUR POOR MOM:
BEEN TALKING TO YOU ABOUT SEX
SINCE YOU WERE TEN.
[laughter]
WH-WH-WH-WHAT?
HELP ME UNDERSTAND THAT.
DID SHE NOT MENTION IN ANY OF
THOSE SEX TALKS--SHE DIDN'T
MENTION CONDOMS?
>> NO, SHE DID,
AND I WAS JUST STUPID AND DIDN'T
LISTEN, I GUESS.
>> YES.
>> WHOSE IDEA WAS IT TO HAVE SEX
THE FIRST TIME WITHOUT A CONDOM?
>> DO YOU REMEMBER THAT?
>> YEAH, IT WAS PROBABLY JUST
HEAT OF THE MOMENT.
>> IT WAS A HEAT-OF-THE-MOMENT
THING.
LIKE, YOU'RE JUST--I CAN'T EVEN
EXPLAIN IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
[laughter]
>> IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
[laughs]
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW FOR
CONTRACEPTION?
>> I'M ON BIRTH CONTROL.
I HAD A LITTLE SHOT.
>> DEPO-PROVERA SHOT.
>> YES.
>> SURE, THAT ONE.
>> YOU'VE MADE SOME HUGE
SACRIFICES.
>> YES.
>> YOU DIDN'T WALK AT
GRADUATION.
>> NO.
>> YOU DIDN'T JOIN THE AIR
FORCE.
>> NO, BUT I HAVE--LIKE, THIS
IS HOW I SEE IT.
IF ONE DOOR CLOSES, THEN ANOTHER
ONE OPENS, AND I CAN'T JOIN THE
AIR FORCE RIGHT NOW.
IT'S JUST PUT OFF UNTIL LATER.
I'M GOING TO COLLEGE IN THE
FALL, AND--
>> DID YOU GRADUATE?
>> IT'S A COLLEGE OPTIONS
PROGRAM, AND YOU FINISH YOUR
HIGH SCHOOL CREDITS ALONG WITH
THE COLLEGE CREDITS, AND SO IT'S
A THING THAT MY SCHOOL DOES FOR
ME.
>> I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON IN YOUR HEAD
THERE, JOSH, BECAUSE YOU'VE HAD
TO GIVE UP A LOT TOO.
>> YEAH, IT IS REAL HARD TO
LOSE YOUR YOUTH, BECAUSE, I
MEAN, BEFORE ALL THIS HAPPENED,
I WAS JUST HAVING A BLAST WITH
MY LIFE, AND ONCE SHE GOT
PREGNANT, AND AFTER JOCELYN WAS
BORN, IT TOOK ALL THAT AWAY,
BECAUSE WE CAN'T DO AS MUCH,
BECAUSE WE HAVE TO SIT THERE
WITH HER AND TAKE CARE OF HER,
SO IT DEFINITELY PUTS A STRAIN,
BUT I DON'T LOOK AT IT AS IT
TAKES AWAY MY LIFE.
IT JUST--OR MY LIFE OR MY
DREAMS--IT JUST PUTS IT ON HOLD
WHILE I TAKE CARE OF MY
RESPONSIBILITIES FOR NOW.
>> DID EBONY HELP BRING YOU
AROUND TO THAT...GENTLY?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> YEAH, GENTLY BUT FIRMLY?
>> YES.
>> NOT GENTLY AT ALL.
JUST--
>> JUST FIRM.
[laughter]
>> A MEMBER OF THE AUDIENCE
NAMED NATIA HAS A QUESTION.
NATIA?
>> HEY, EBONY, I JUST WANTED
TO KNOW WHAT IT WAS REALLY LIKE
GOING TO PROM WHILE BEING
PREGNANT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS REALLY FUN.
I HAD TO SIT DOWN A LOT, BECAUSE
I WAS FAT, BUT, I MEAN,
YOU HAVE THIS--I WAS SO HUGE.
I WAS VERY BIG.
I MEAN, I STILL DANCED, THOUGH,
AS YOU GUYS SAW.
I HAD A BLAST AT PROM.
>> DO YOU STILL HAVE PLANS TO
JOIN THE AIR FORCE, JOSH?
>> OH, YES, I'VE BEEN FILLING
OUT THE PAPERWORK RIGHT NOW,
AND I JUST HAVE TO TURN
EVERYTHING IN, AND THEY'LL GIVE
ME MY DATE TO GO IN, SO...
>> I CAN'T STAND BEING AWAY
FROM HIM, BUT IF I'M FOCUSED ON
SCHOOL WORK, AND THEN HE CALLS
ME, THEN I'LL BE OKAY, BUT I'LL
STILL MISS HIM.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, EXCELLENT.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
THANK YOU, EBONY AND JOSH,
FOR JOINING US, AND
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE MARRIAGE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> LATER, WE'RE GONNA HEAR FROM
YOU AGAIN, BUT FIRST, LET'S STEP
ASIDE FOR A BREAK, AND THEN
WE'LL RETURN WITH CATELYNN AND
TYLER.
NOW, THEY CHOSE ADOPTION FOR
BABY CARLY, AND WE'VE GOT A HUGE
SURPRISE IN STORE.
TRUST ME, YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS
WHAT'S COMING UP NEXT, SO WE'LL
BE RIGHT BACK.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO 16 AND
PREGNANT: LIFE AFTER LABOR,
THE FINALE SPECIAL,
HOSTED BY ME, DR. DREW.
NOW, LISTEN, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
THERE ARE 730,000 TEEN
PREGNANCIES EVERY YEAR IN
AMERICA.
ABOUT HALF OF THOSE PREGNANCIES
RESULT IN THE BIRTH OF A LIVE
CHILD, YET ONLY ABOUT 1% OF
THOSE BABIES ARE ADOPTED, 1%.
ONE COUPLE THAT KNOWS ALL ABOUT
THE OPTION TO ADOPT JOINS ME
NOW.
CATELYNN AND TYLER, WELCOME TO
THE SHOW.
>> HI.
>> HI, GUYS.
NOW, YOU GUYS MADE A VERY, VERY
DIFFICULT DECISION TO OPT FOR
ADOPTION, AND REALLY, THEY
AGONIZED OVER IT UNTIL THE VERY
LAST MINUTE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK BACK AT
CATELYNN'S PREGNANCY AND THE
IMPOSSIBLE MOMENTS THAT
FOLLOWED.
>> THERE'S SCARY THINGS ABOUT
ADOPTION, BUT, I MEAN, LIKE,
PARENTING, LIKE, I MEAN,
THAT'S EVEN SCARIER.
>> I THINK ADOPTION WOULD BE
THE BEST OPTION.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA END UP
GOING THROUGH WITH IT?
>> NO, I DON'T AGREE WITH IT.
YOU CAN CHANGE YOUR MIND
ANYWAYS.
>> IF I GAVE HER UP FOR
ADOPTION, LIKE, I HAD GIVEN
SOMEBODY, LIKE, AN AWESOME GIFT.
>> AND I KNOW THAT YOU GUYS CAN
PROVIDE FOR HER A LOT
MORE THAN I CAN.
I JUST WANT HER TO HAVE
BETTER THAN WHAT I HAD.
>> ALL THAT BABY NEEDS IS LOVE.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT ALL A BABY
NEEDS IS LOVE.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT PARENTING.
>> I WANT YOU TO OPEN YOUR EYES,
AND I WANT YOU TO LOOK.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE.
>> THERE SHE IS.
>> WE CAN DO THIS.
>> SHE WANTED TO, UM,
SEE HER REAL QUICK
AND JUST HOLD HER AND...
>> THIS IS NOT AN EASY THING
TO DO.
SHE'S JUST REALLY GONE NOW.
>> YEP.
>> SORRY.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I'M FINE.
>> SUCH A COURAGEOUS DECISION,
BOTH OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HOW DID YOU DO IT?
>> UM...
>> HER.
>> YEAH, JUST WHEN YOU LOOK AT
HER, LIKE, AND YOU HOLD HER,
AND YOU JUST KNOW THAT YOU'RE
DOING IT FOR HER,
AND IT JUST MADE ME WANT TO DO
IT 100 TIMES MORE.
JUST HOLDING HER.
JUST LOOKING AT HER, 'CAUSE, I
MEAN, THEY'RE SO INNOCENT.
>> BUT I SAW YOU GET KIND OF
AMBIVALENT ABOUT IT.
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO LET HER GO.
>> WELL, YEAH, I DIDN'T.
IT WAS REALLY--IT WAS HARD,
BUT, I MEAN, YOU'VE JUST GO TO--
YOU'VE GOT TO KIND OF PUSH
YOURSELF, BECAUSE IT'S THE BEST
THING FOR HER, AND THAT'S ALL
YOU CAN THINK ABOUT IS HER.
YOU CAN'T THINK ABOUT YOURSELF.
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT AT 17?
WHERE DID YOU COME TO THAT--
>> BECAUSE WHEN YOU HAVE A KID,
IT'S NOT--IT'S NOT JUST, "OKAY,
WELL--
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU ANYMORE.
>> IT'S NOT, YOU KNOW--
>> YEAH, BUT AT 17, EVERYTHING'S
ABOUT YOU.
>> I KNOW, BUT--
>> NO, BUT YOU CAN'T--WHEN YOU
HAVE A BABY, THAT'S NOT ABOUT
YOU.
YOU CAN'T...
>> YOU'VE GOT TO GROW UP.
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU UNDERSTAND HOW
EXTRAORDINARY THAT IS THAT YOU
GUYS WERE ABLE TO DO THAT?
>> WELL, I HEAR IT A LOT, BUT...
[laughter]
>> IT DIDN'T SEEM EXTRAORDINARY
TO YOU.
>> NO, IT DIDN'T.
>> NO.
>> IT SEEMED NATURAL.
>> YEAH.
>> MM-HMM.
>> TYLER, I KNOW YOU HAD A LOT
OF MIXED FEELINGS ABOUT IT,
AND YOU HAD A FAMILY THAT WAS
TELLING YOU SOMETHING COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> HOW AT 17 DO YOU GET THE--
DO YOU HAVE THE COURAGE AND THE
STRENGTH TO STAND UP TO YOUR OWN
FAMILY?
>> MY DAUGHTER.
SHE GAVE ME THE STRENGTH,
THE COURAGE.
>> I TOLD YOU YOU GUYS TAKE MY
BREATH AWAY, YOUR STRENGTH AND
YOUR COURAGE.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST INCREDIBLY
DIFFICULT WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
>> YEAH, IT'S NOT EASY.
>> IT'S THE HARDEST THING.
>> YEAH, IT'S THE HARDEST THING
I'VE EVER DONE IN MY LIFE.
>> AND YET IT'S THE RIGHT
THING...
>> YEAH.
>> FOR YOUR DAUGHTER, FOR CARLY.
>> CARLY'S HER NAME, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'VE GIVEN CARLY--WHAT HAVE
YOU GIVEN HER AS A RESULT OF
YOUR SACRIFICE?
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> A CHANCE AT LIFE...
>> A CHANCE, YEAH, AWESOME
PARENTS, A BEAUTIFUL HOME,
A BEAUTIFUL FAMILY, HUGE FAMILY.
THAT--SHE IS SURROUNDED BY
SO MUCH LOVE, IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
>> WHAT DID YOU HAVE GROWING UP?
>> A SINGLE MOM, MOVING ALL
THE TIME.
>> WAS SHE A TEEN PARENT TOO?
>> WELL, SHE, I MEAN, SHE WAS
19, BUT THAT'S--
>> NINE..."TEEN."
>> YEAH, AND MOVING ALL THE
TIME AND JUST--IT WASN'T--
I MEAN, I'M NOT GONNA SAY IT WAS
BAD, 'CAUSE I DIDN'T HAVE A
HORRIBLE LIFE, BUT, I MEAN, IT
COULD HAVE BEEN BETTER, SO...
>> YOU CERTAINLY WANTED BETTER
FOR YOUR CHILD.
>> YEAH, I DIDN'T WANT HER TO
HAVE WHAT WE HAD.
>> YEAH, WE WANTED MORE.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU TELL KIDS
THAT THINK TO THEMSELVES, "WELL,
I'M NOT GONNA LET MY KID HAVE
WHAT I HAD.
I'M GONNA DO A BETTER JOB,
AND I'M GONNA RAISE THEM"?
AND IT'S REALLY THE SAME STUFF
YOUR DAD WAS TELLING YOU.
>> WELL, I MEAN, YOU CAN DO IT.
LIKE, YOU REALLY CAN DO IT,
BUT, I MEAN...
>> AT WHAT COST?
>> YEAH, EXACTLY, AT WHAT COST?
>> YOU KNOW, WHAT--THE KIND OF
LIFE THAT YOUR CHILD IS GONNA
LIVE, OR, YOU KNOW,
NOBODY CAN REALLY PREDICT THE
FUTURE, BUT--
>> YOU CAN SAY THAT YOU'RE
GONNA BE A GOOD MOM, AND YOU'RE
GONNA DO THIS, AND YOU'RE GONNA
DO THAT, BUT, I MEAN, AFTER A
YEAR, IT GETS OLD.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL NOW SEEING
ALL THE OTHER MOMS WITH THEIR
BABIES?
>> WELL, UM...I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETIMES I THINK, LIKE...
>> WE COULD HAVE DONE IT.
>> YEAH, I THINK THAT WE COULD
HAVE DONE IT, AND, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE, LIKE, YOU SEE WITH ALL
OF THEM, THEY'RE JUST, LIKE,
EVERYBODY'S OOHING AN AHHING
ALL OVER THEM, AND WE DON'T HAVE
NOTHING, AND IT'S LIKE, "OKAY,"
BUT THEN YOU'VE GOT TO STOP
YOURSELF, AND YOU'VE GOT TO BE
LIKE, "NO, THIS IS WHY WE DID
IT, YOU KNOW.
IT'S NOT ABOUT US.
IT'S ABOUT HER."
SO YOU'VE GOT TO JUST THINK
ABOUT HER, NOT YOURSELF.
>> I FEEL SO PASSIONATELY THAT
PEOPLE LIKE YOU NEED TO BE
HONORED AND...BECAUSE IT JUST--
IT'S SO DIFFICULT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, LET'S STEP
ASIDE FOR A BREAK, AND THEN
WE'VE GOT A HUGE SURPRISE IN
STORE.
TRUST ME, YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS
WHAT'S COMING UP NEXT, SO
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[applause]
HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN SINCE
YOU'VE SEEN CARLY?
>> FIVE WEEKS AGO.
>> SO FIVE WEEKS AGO WAS THE
LAST TIME YOU SAW HER.
>> YEP, MY HEART'S RACING.
>> WELCOME BACK.
I'M DR. DREW, AND THIS IS THE
16 AND PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL:
LIFE AFTER LABOR.
SHORTLY AFTER CARLY WAS BORN,
HER ADOPTIVE MOM TERESA GAVE
CATELYNN--GAVE YOU A BRACELET.
IS THAT RIGHT?
IS THAT BRACELET--
>> YEAH, I WEAR IT EVERY DAY.
>> OKAY, THIS WAS A SYMBOL OF
THE BOND BETWEEN THE THREE OF
YOU.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THIS CLIP,
WHERE SHE DOES GIVE YOU THAT
BRACELET.
>> OKAY.
>> THE LITTLE GIRL...
HI.
HI, CATELYNN.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
[gasps]
HI, BABY GIRL.
[laughs]
HERE, I'LL PULL THE CARD OUT.
I'LL GIVE THIS TO YOU,
AND THEN I CAN KIND OF
FURTHER EXPLAIN IT.
>> IT'S PRETTY.
>> I LIKE THAT.
>> WHAT DOES IT SAY?
[giggles]
>> OH.
"ALWAYS IN MY HEART."
>> I HAVE ONE TOO.
AND WE HAVE ONE FOR CARLY
TOO.
AND, UM...
SO THE PLAN IS THAT I WILL
ALWAYS BE WEARING MINE,
AND YOU CAN BE WEARING YOURS,
AND THEN WHEN SHE'S OLD ENOUGH,
WE'LL GIVE HER HERS AS WELL
TO WEAR.
WE'RE JUST SO GONNA BE LINKED
FOR LIFE, AND WE JUST CAN'T
THANK YOU ENOUGH FOR,
UM...
FOR THIS GIFT.
>> I'M NEVER GONNA TAKE IT OFF.
>> I'M NEVER GONNA TAKE MINE OFF
EITHER.
>> THAT MEANS SO MUCH.
>> THAT'S PRETTY INTENSE, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, IT IS.
[laughs]
>> HOW LONG HAS IT BEEN SINCE
YOU'VE SEEN CARLY?
>> FIVE WEEKS AGO.
>> SO FIVE WEEKS AGO WAS THE
LAST TIME YOU SAW HER.
>> YEP, THEN SHE WENT HOME.
>> YOU MISS HER?
>> OH, I MISS HER A LOT.
>> YOU BOTH THINK ABOUT HER
A LOT.
>> I MISS HER LIKE CRAZY.
>> MM-HMM, I THINK ABOUT HER
EVERY DAY.
THERE'S NOT A DAY THAT SHE DOES
NOT PASS MY MIND.
>> EVERY SINGLE DAY.
I GOT A FRAME OF, LIKE, OUR
FACES, AND THEY'RE TOUCHING,
AND, LIKE, NOT--SIDE-TO-SIDE
OUR NOSES ARE TOUCHING, AND
I GOT IT, AND I PUT IT IN A
REALLY NICE FRAME AND JUST HUNG
IT OVER MY DRESSER, AND SO EVERY
DAY, I WAKE UP, AND I CAN JUST
LOOK AT IT.
>> YEP.
>> AND I KEPT HER BABY
BLANKET, SLEEP WITH IT EVERY
NIGHT AND PUT IT OVER MY PILLOW.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE LIVES A FAIR DISTANCE
FROM WHERE YOU ARE, A PLANE RIDE
AWAY, SO IT'S NOT SOMETHING YOU
CAN EASILY GO TO SEE HER.
>> MM-MM.
>> WELL, ALTHOUGH THESE GUYS
KNOW ABOUT THIS, WHAT YOU ALL
DON'T KNOW IS THAT TERESA AND
BRANDON ARE HERE WITH CARLY.
[audience oohs]
AND--OOH, YEAH.
AND SO THIS IS ACTUALLY AN
OPPORTUNITY TODAY FOR REUNITING
YOU GUYS WITH CARLY...
>> YEAH.
>> AND GETTING A CHANCE TO SAY
HI TO TERESA AND BRANDON.
>> MY HEART'S RACING.
>> YOUR HEART'S--BUT YOU
WANT--YOU'RE GOOD WITH THIS.
YOU WANT TO DO THIS.
>> YEAH, I WANT TO.
>> THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY--
>> OH, MY GOSH, YES.
>> YES, THIS IS AN OPEN
ADOPTION.
THIS IS A CHANCE TO MAKE ONE OF
THOSE VISITS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> SOMEBODY'S FOOTING THE BILL
FOR YOU.
[laughter]
>> SO, TYLER, ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> YES.
>> SHOULD WE BRING THEM OUT?
>> YEAH, COULD WE?
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S BRING THEM OUT.
[applause]
>> GO GET IT.
GO GET IT.
>> HI, YOU GUYS.
>> HOW YOU BEEN?
>> I'M DOING GOOD.
>> 40 DAYS.
>> HI, TERESA.
>> HI, BRANDON.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD, HOW ARE YOU GUYS?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> I'M, LIKE, SHAKING.
>> [laughs]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> HI, OH, SHE'S SO CUTE.
SHE STILL LOOKS THE SAME.
>> DOES SHE LOOK BIGGER?
>> THAT'S THE FIRST THING I
WANTED TO KNOW WAS, "WHAT DO YOU
THINK?
DOES SHE LOOK THE SAME?
DOES SHE LOOK DIFFERENT?"
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S A LITTLE BIGGER.
>> SHE LOOKS A LITTLE BIT
BIGGER.
>> SHE'S A LITTLE BIGGER.
>> HER HAIR STILL STICKS
STRAIGHT UP ON THE TOP OF HER
HEAD.
[laughter]
>> OOOH, CAN I HOLD HER?
GOT IT?
>> [whining]
>> UH-OH.
OOOH, YOU'RE STILL SO LITTLE.
>> [laughs]
>> HI, CARLY.
>> OKAY, GUYS, YOU WANT TO TAKE
A SEAT?
>> YEAH.
[laughs]
>> YOU CAN COME OVER HERE, BABE.
>> WHERE?
>> IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER.
>> SO CUTE.
>> OH.
[audience awws]
>> SHE'S HIDING.
>> SHE'S SHY.
>> GET THOSE LIGHTS OUT OF MY
EYES.
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
>> SAY HI.
[laughs]
[laughter]
SHE DOESN'T--SHE'S JUST, LIKE...
>> TYLER, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
PUSH HER HAIR DOWN, NOT PUT IT
UP.
>> WELL, I LIKE IT UP.
>> SHE LIKES HER LITTLE MOHAWK.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE WILL BE COMING
BACK WITH MUCH MORE AFTER THIS,
SO DON'T GO AWAY.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO LIFE AFTER
LABOR: THE 16 AND PREGNANT
FINALE SPECIAL.
I'M DR. DREW, AND WE ARE IN THE
MIDDLE OF REALLY AN AMAZING
REUNION: BABY CARLY AND HER
ADOPTIVE PARENTS, TERESA AND
BRANDON, GET TO SEE CARLY'S
BIOLOGICAL PARENTS FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE LEAVING THE HOSPITAL.
TERESA'S GOT CARLY RIGHT NOW,
BEAUTIFUL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ISN'T SHE?
>> NOW, YOU FOUR CHOSE A
SEMI-OPEN ADOPTION.
HELP US UNDERSTAND WHAT THAT IS.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, THE CLOSED
ADOPTIONS THAT PEOPLE THINK OF
ARE REALLY RARE THESE DAYS,
SO WITH A SEMI-OPEN ADOPTION,
BIRTH PARENTS HAVE AN
OPPORTUNITY TO CHOOSE THEIR
ADOPTIVE PARENTS, AS CATELYNN
AND TYLER LOOKED AT PROFILES AND
CHOSE US, AND THEN BIRTH PARENTS
ALONG WITH THE ADOPTIVE PARENTS
HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO KIND OF
DECIDE WHAT THEIR RELATIONSHIP'S
GONNA LOOK LIKE GOING FORWARD.
>> WE CAN'T TALK ABOUT HER
WITHOUT TALKING ABOUT YOU ALL,
SO...
[laughter]
EVERYBODY HEARS ABOUT YOU ALL
AND THE BRAVE DECISION YOU MADE
AND OUR RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU
EVERY TIME THEY ASK ABOUT CARLY.
>> YEAH.
>> WE LOVE TO TELL THEM ABOUT
YOU.
>> AND I ALSO MISSED--I DIDN'T
REALLY HEAR--I HEARD HOW YOU
FELT ABOUT THESE TWO WHEN YOU
WERE LOOKING AT THEIR PICTURES,
BUT I DIDN'T HEAR EITHER OF YOU
TELL THEM.
>> WHAT I THINK ABOUT THEM?
>> YEAH, THE PARENTS.
>> I ABSOLUTELY LOVE YOU GUYS.
>> WONDERFUL.
>> SERIOUSLY, YOU GUYS ARE,
LIKE, SERIOUSLY, LIKE, A SECOND
FAMILY TO ME.
I MEAN, 'CAUSE--AND IT'S JUST
AMAZING, LIKE, EVEN HOW YOU
LEFT ME THAT MESSAGE YESTERDAY,
AND YOU WERE LIKE, "WE'RE
ETERNALLY GRATEFUL FOR YOU, AND
WE LOVE YOU," AND IT'S JUST,
LIKE, EVERY TIME I TALK TO YOU
GUYS, YOU GUYS JUST...
BRING ME UP MORE AND MORE.
IT'S, LIKE...
THEY'RE JUST--AND BOTH, LIKE,
SHE'S STILL HERE.
YOU GUYS ARE TAKING GREAT CARE
OF HER, AND YOU LOVE HER, AND...
>> SHE WOULDN'T HAVE HAD SUCH
GOOD PARENTS, YOU KNOW, IF IT
WASN'T FOR YOU GUYS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THESE
TWO, TERESA?
>> WE HAVE JUST SO LONGED FOR
THIS BABY, AND IT'S THE MOST
INCREDIBLE GIFT THAT ANYBODY
COULD EVER GIVE US, AND, YOU
KNOW, LIKE I SAY, I DON'T KNOW
IF I'LL EVER BE ABLE TO TELL YOU
ENOUGH HOW MUCH WE LOVE YOU
AND HOW GRATEFUL WE ARE THAT YOU
MADE SUCH A HARD AND BRAVE
DECISION, AND WHAT WE JUST LOVE
ABOUT BOTH OF YOU GUYS IS THAT
CARLY IS GONNA GROW UP KNOWING
THAT YOU MADE THIS DECISION
BECAUSE YOU LOVED HER AND
BECAUSE YOU WANTED A BETTER LIFE
FOR HER, AND SHE IS SWEET AND
WONDERFUL AND--AND JUST HAS SO
MUCH OF BOTH OF YOU GUYS IN HER
ALREADY, AND WE LOOK, AND WE
DEBATE ON WHO SHE LOOKS LIKE
AND WHO SHE'S GONNA BE LIKE,
AND IT'S JUST A PRECIOUS GIFT.
>> IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU GUYS,
I DON'T KNOW HOW WE WOULD HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO DO THIS.
>> OR HOW WE'D BE RIGHT NOW
EITHER.
>> I DON'T--YOU KNOW, I CAN'T
PICTURE HER WITH ANYBODY--ANY
OTHER FAMILY BESIDES YOU GUYS.
YOU GUYS ARE PERFECT.
>> YOU'RE EVERYTHING THAT WE'VE
WANTED.
>> EVERYTHING THAT WE'VE WANTED.
YOU KNOW, IT JUST SEEMED LIKE
THE MOST PERFECT MATCH.
>> WE'VE GOT QUESTIONS FROM AN
AUDIENCE MEMBER.
IS SOMEBODY NAMED ERIN OUT
THERE?
ERIN, WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR
THESE GUYS?
>> HI, GUYS.
I JUST WANTED TO KNOW WHAT
ADVICE YOU WOULD GIVE TO YOUNG
PARENTS WHO ARE ALREADY IN THE
ADOPTION PROCESS.
>> DEFINITELY, IF YOU DON'T HAVE
A SUPPORTIVE FAMILY, LIKE I
DIDN'T, I WOULD DEFINITELY GET
SOME COUNSELING, BECAUSE IT'S
NOT EASY.
IT'S REALLY NOT EASY, BUT YOU
JUST HAVE TO--THE WHOLE TIME
YOU'RE GOING THROUGH IT, YOU
HAVE TO KNOW.
YOU HAVE TO, LIKE, PREPARE
YOURSELF FOR THAT DAY WHEN YOU
HAVE TO, LIKE, HAND YOUR CHILD
OFF, BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE TO DO
IT.
THAT'S WHAT HELPED ME OUT A LOT,
BECAUSE, I MEAN, IT GAVE ME A
LOT OF STRENGTH, SO...
>> AND WHILE YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH THE ADOPTION PROCESS,
JUST CONSTANTLY THINK ABOUT YOUR
BABY...
>> YOU'VE GOT TO THINK ABOUT
HER, YEAH.
>> AND NOBODY ELSE.
>> RACHEL, WHERE ARE YOU?
YOU'VE GOT A QUESTION.
>> THIS QUESTION'S FOR BRANDON
AND TERESA.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE MEETING
CATELYNN AND TYLER FOR THE FIRST
TIME?
>> WELL, MEETING THEM FOR THE
FIRST TIME WAS NERVE-RACKING,
BUT THE MOMENT THEY KIND OF
WALKED IN THE DOOR, IT WAS,
YOU KNOW, IT WAS PRETTY AMAZING.
I MEAN, WE JUST FELT LIKE WE
KIND OF MADE THIS CONNECTION
WITH YOU ALL, AND, BUT YEAH, WE
JUST FELT LIKE, AS WE SAID, I
MEAN, THERE'S KIND OF ALWAYS
THIS LITTLE BIT IN THE BACK OF
OUR HEADS OR OUR MINDS THAT WE
KNEW THAT YOU COULD CHANGE YOUR
MIND.
AGAIN, YOU ALL DID A GREAT JOB
OF REASSURING US.
I MEAN, YOU WERE COUNSELING US
IN A SENSE ABOUT, "NO, NO, CALM
DOWN.
IT'S OKAY."
>> I WAS LIKE, "DON'T BE
AFRAID."
>> YEAH, YOU WERE GOOD AT THAT.
SO THERE WAS ALWAYS THIS LITTLE
BIT OF, YOU KNOW, CONCERN IN THE
BACK OF OUR MINDS, BUT WE KIND
OF JUST DECIDED EARLY ON,
IF WE'RE HOLDING BACK, THAT'S
GONNA SHOW THROUGH.
WE'RE GONNA FEEL IT.
THEY'RE GONNA NOTICE IT,
AND THAT CAN'T BE THE WAY IT IS.
WE JUST KIND OF HAVE TO GO
FORWARD AND PUT YOURSELF OUT
THERE AND JUST, YOU KNOW, GO
FOR IT AND JUST BELIEVE THAT
IT'S GONNA MOVE THROUGH.
>> WE'VE GOT AMANDA IN
THE AUDIENCE.
SHE HAS A QUESTION.
>> I KNOW THAT BOTH YOUR PARENTS
HAD ISSUES WITH YOUR DECISION
FOR ADOPTION.
I WAS WONDERING HOW THEY'RE
DEALING WITH IT NOW.
>> MY MOM'S WARMING UP TO IT A
LOT MORE NOW, 'CAUSE SHE
MISSES ME, 'CAUSE I HAVEN'T BEEN
HOME IN, LIKE, SEVEN WEEKS.
>> WHERE ARE YOU LIVING?
>> I'VE BEEN STAYING AT TYLER'S.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> YEAH, WHAT, STAYING IN MY
HOUSEHOLD WITH DRUNKS AND LOUD
MUSIC AND PARTYING?
NO, NO THANKS.
>> AND YOU WERE EXPOSED TO ALL
THAT, THOUGH.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, THE FUNNY THING
HUMANS DO IS, THEY USUALLY
RE-CREATE THE THING THAT WERE
PROBLEMATIC IN THEIR PAST.
THEY USUALLY DON'T KNOW TO BREAK
THE CYCLE.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, MY WHOLE LIFE, I'VE
BEEN ALWAYS WATCHING OVER MY
MOM AND PRACTICALLY RAISING
MY TWO-YEAR-OLD BROTHER
BY--LIKE, PRACTICALLY RAISING
HIM, LIKE, HIS WHOLE LIFE,
EVEN THOUGH HE'S ONLY TWO, BUT
STILL, SO I'VE SEEN A LOT OF
STUFF, AND I JUST THINK IT MAKES
YOU GROW UP REALLY FAST.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY PARTING
MESSAGES FOR CARLY OR TERESA OR
BRANDON?
>> I'M GONNA MISS HER, BUT WE
ALWAYS SAY THAT IT'S NOT A
GOOD-BYE.
IT'S A SEE YOU LATER.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> RIGHT?
>> SEE YOU LATER...
>> EXACTLY.
>> TILL NEXT TIME.
>> YEP, SEE YOU LATER.
>> WELL, THIS IS CLEARLY AN
EMOTIONAL DAY FOR THE FOUR OF
YOU, AND WE THANK YOU ALL FOR
BEING HERE.
LET'S STEP ASIDE FOR A BREAK,
AND THEN WE'LL RETURN WITH
WHITNEY AND WESTON AND THE BIRTH
OF THEIR BABY BOY.
[applause]
>> SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> THIS REALLY MADE ME GROW UP
SO MUCH, AND IT WAS KIND OF
SCARY.
>> SHOULD WE BRING OUT THE
BABIES?
>> together: YES.
>> LET'S DO IT.
BABIES?
>> WELCOME BACK.
LET'S REVISIT ANOTHER
UNFORGETTABLE STORY FROM THIS
SEASON.
OF COURSE, I'M TALKING ABOUT
WHITNEY AND WESTON AND THE BIRTH
OF THEIR BABY BOY.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE
EVERYBODY IS STARING AT ME,
BECAUSE I HAVE A BEACH BALL
UNDER MY SHIRT.
>> WHITNEY CAN'T BEND DOWN
AND TIE HER SHOE HERSELF?
>> SHE'S USED TO BEING WAITED ON
HAND AND FOOT.
>> [groaning]
THIS BABY'S READY TO BE BORN,
I THINK, SO...
YOU'VE GOT TO BURP HIM, CHANGE A
DIAPER, AND COOK,
AND MAKE SURE THE HOUSE
IS CLEAN AND THE LAUNDRY'S DONE.
THIS IS WHAT GROWING UP
IS ALL ABOUT.
>> I'M TIRED OF Y'ALL
NOT DAMN DOING ANYTHING.
>> WE DON'T DO ANYTHING?
WE CAN'T [bleep] STAND IT
HERE ANYMORE.
>> Y'ALL NEED TO MOVE.
>> TO BE HONEST, I JUST DON'T
THINK WE CAN AFFORD IT.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> WHITNEY AND WESTON, WELCOME
TO THE SHOW.
>> THANKS.
>> SOMEBODY MADE A COMMENT THAT
YOU WERE A BABY HAVING A BABY,
THAT YOU COULDN'T EVEN TIE YOUR
OWN SHOES.
>> I CAN TIE MY OWN SHOES.
>> DID YOU GROW UP?
>> I GREW UP A LOT.
>> HOW?
>> JUST--I USED TO JUST BE
SILLY ALL THE TIME.
JUST MAKING JOKES AND ALWAYS
JUMPING AROUND, AND I NEVER
CARED ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE BUT
MYSELF, AND THEN THIS HAS BEEN
A--REALLY A WAKE-UP CALL.
>> ONE OF THE MOST IMMATURE
KINDS OF THINKING PEOPLE CAN
HAVE IS SORT OF MAGICAL
THINKING, LIKE, "THIS ISN'T
GONNA HAPPEN TO ME.
I'M INVINCIBLE.
I'M NOT GONNA GET PREGNANT."
WERE YOU THINKING LIKE THAT?
>> YEAH, I DEFINITELY WAS.
I MEAN--
>> WERE YOU READY TO HAVE SEX
EVEN?
>> UM...
I THINK I WAS, BUT I DON'T--
>> REALLY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THAT'S MAYBE THE MORE
HONEST ANSWER, BECAUSE
SOMEBODY WHO'S READY TO HAVE SEX
WOULD PLAN CONTRACEPTION,
WOULDN'T THEY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I'M NOT--I'M NOT INTENDING TO
MAKE YOU FEEL GUILTY, BUT IT IS
WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE.
A BABY'S HAD A BABY.
YOU ALL RIGHT WITH THAT?
>> [laughs]
I MEAN, I GUESS I WAS LIKE THAT
BEFORE, BUT...
[exhales]
I'M SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> BUT IT'S REALLY MADE ME GROW
UP SO MUCH, AND IT'S KIND OF
SCARY TO THINK HOW EVERYTHING
USED TO BE, AND NOW, IT'S, LIKE,
THE BIGGEST CHANGE, AND IT
JUST ALL HAPPENED SO FAST,
AND, I MEAN, I'M HAPPY ABOUT IT,
AND I GUESS IT'S WHAT I NEEDED.
>> TO GROW UP?
MY UNDERSTANDING IS BABY WESTON
HAS SOME MEDICAL ISSUES.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW'D YOU FIGURE THAT OUT?
HOW'D YOU COME TO UNDERSTAND
THAT?
>> UM...
HE JUST--WHEN HE WOULD EAT, HE
WOULD ALWAYS THROW UP, SO HE
WASN'T GAINING THAT MUCH WEIGHT,
BUT THEY COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT WAS.
>> DID HE HAVE TO BE
HOSPITALIZED?
>> YEAH, FOR ABOUT A WEEK AND A
HALF, AND THEN HIS--THEN THEY
NOTICED THAT HIS LIVER WAS
SWELLING UP.
>> ENLARGED, SO MY
UNDERSTANDING IS, HE HAS
SOMETHING CALLED
ALPHA-1 ANTITRYPSIN DEFICIENCY,
WHICH IS A GENETIC DISORDER.
WHAT'S IT GONNA MEAN FOR HIM?
>> WELL, HE CAN'T PLAY SPORTS
WHEN HE GETS OLDER OR ANYTHING
LIKE THAT, AND--
>> HE CAN'T SMOKE CIGARETTES
WHEN HE GETS OLDER.
>> YEAH, MM-HMM.
>> ONE OF THE ASPECTS OF
ALPHA-1 ANTITRYPSIN IS,
THEY GET EMPHYSEMA, IF THEY
SMOKE, REALLY BAD.
>> MM-HMM.
>> MM?
>> OKAY, NO SMOKING.
DO YOU GUYS SMOKE?
>> I DO.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO STOP.
>> YES, SIR.
>> BECAUSE BABIES WHOSE PARENTS
SMOKE BECOME ADULTS THAT SMOKE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY?
IS HE THRIVING, THOUGH,
OTHERWISE NOW, DOING OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> BUT BOY, WHAT A SCARY THING
TO GO THROUGH.
>> IT IS.
LIKE, BEFORE, YOU REALLY DON'T
THINK THAT NOTHING'S GONNA BE
WRONG, AND THEN YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT HIM NOW
KNOWING THAT HE HAS SOMETHING
WRONG WITH HIM, AND I'M SCARED
THAT IF--WHEN HE GETS OLDER,
AND HE WANTS TO JUST BE LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE AND PARTY, YOU
KNOW, WITH HIS FRIENDS, AND HE
CAN'T DRINK OR ANYTHING LIKE
THAT.
>> I WILL TELL YOU, IF--AGAIN,
IF YOU ARE THE KIND OF PARENT
THAT DOESN'T DRINK AND DOESN'T
SMOKE, IT'S MUCH LESS LIKELY
THAT HE WILL.
>> I MEAN, I DON'T.
>> AS YOU FOUND OUT MAYBE FROM
SOME OF THESE STORIES AND SOME
OF YOUR PEERS, IT REALLY DOESN'T
MATTER SO MUCH WHAT THE PARENTS
SAY.
IT'S MORE ABOUT HOW THEY LIVE
THEIR LIVES.
>> MM-HMM.
>> MM?
>> WESTON, YOU'RE DOING SUCH A
GREAT JOB AS A DAD.
WHERE DO YOU GO FOR SUPPORT?
>> UM...
MY MOM HAS ALWAYS BEEN THERE
FOR ME, AND SHE'S ABOUT THE ONLY
PERSON, OTHER THAN WHITNEY, OF
COURSE, THAT I COULD GO TO WITH
ANYTHING.
IT WOULDN'T MATTER WHAT IT WAS.
>> SO YOUR MOM.
DO YOU HAVE ANY PEERS, ANY
OTHER--ANY OTHER FRIENDS?
>> NOT REALLY.
I DON'T REALLY HANG OUT WITH
ANYBODY OR TALK TO ANYBODY.
>> WESTON, IF YOU WERE TALKING
TO A GROUP OF 15-YEAR-OLDS OUT
HERE WHO WERE THINKING ABOUT
HAVING SEX, THOUGHT IT WAS A
COOL THING, WHAT WOULD YOU TELL
THEM?
>> THINK AGAIN.
TAKE EXTRA PRECAUTIONS AFTER THE
PRECAUTIONS.
I MEAN...
>> PRECAUTIONS ON PRECAUTIONS.
>> YES.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAD TO
GIVE UP YOUR DREAMS?
>> IN--IN SOME WAY, I FEEL LIKE
I'M GONNA BE MORE SUCCESSFUL
NOW, BECAUSE IT'S KIND OF MADE
ME TAKE THAT PUSH THAT--BECAUSE
I KNOW I HAVE TO DO THIS
TO SUPPORT HIM AND TO DO
EVERYTHING, AND I THINK IF I
WOULDN'T HAVE, I WOULD HAVE JUST
BEEN LIKE, "OH, I CAN DO THIS
LATER, AND I CAN HAVE FUN
RIGHT NOW."
>> SO EVEN THOUGH IT'S HARD,
THERE'S BEEN SOME--SOME REAL
GOOD THINGS HAVE COME OUT OF IT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY, WELL, THANK YOU, GUYS.
THANK YOU.
WE'RE GONNA STEP ASIDE FOR ONE
LAST BREAK, AND WHEN WE RETURN,
WE'RE COMING BACK WITH WHAT
WE'RE CALLING THE SPOTLIGHT
SESSION, WHEN THE TEEN MOMS COME
TOGETHER ON THIS STAGE AND ASK
THE QUESTIONS THEY WANT
ANSWERED.
PLUS, WE'RE GONNA MEET THE REAL
STARS OF THIS SHOW: THE BABIES.
DON'T MOVE.
WE'RE COMING RIGHT BACK.
[applause]
>> WE'RE BACK.
I'M DR. DREW, AND THIS IS LIFE
AFTER LABOR: THE 16 AND
PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL.
AND WE'RE JOINED NOW BY THE
ENTIRE CAST, ALL SIX MOMS,
AND I KNOW THESE YOUNG WOMEN
HAVE QUESTIONS FOR ONE ANOTHER,
SO LET'S GET RIGHT TO THAT.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION FOR ALL THE
GIRLS.
SO I KNOW WE'VE TOUCHED ON
THAT--PROTECTION,
AND I'D LIKE TO KNOW JUST HOW
MANY OF US DIDN'T USE CONDOMS
WHEN WE GOT PREGNANT.
>> SHOW OF HANDS.
HOW MANY PEOPLE DID NOT USE
PROTECTION?
>> I DID SOMETIMES, SOMETIMES
NOT, SO...
>> IT'S LIKE WEARING YOUR SEAT
BELT.
YOU'VE GOT TO WEAR IT ALL THE
TIME....
>> YEAH.
>> ALL THE TIME.
SO NOBODY PRACTICED ANY
CONTRACEPTIVE.
>> NOPE.
>> I DID, BUT IT STOPPED.
>> YEAH, IT STOPPED AFTER A
WHILE, SO...
>> YEAH.
>> WHO'S PRACTICING
CONTRACEPTION NOW?
EVERYBODY--OH...
>> I DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
IT.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
[laughter]
>> UM, I HAVE A QUESTION FOR
YOU.
I DON'T KNOW HIM, SO I'M NOT
GONNA SAY ANYTHING, BUT JUST
FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN ON THE SHOW,
IT JUST HURT MY FEELINGS.
JUST THE WAY THAT HE TREATED
YOU AND THE THINGS THAT HE SAID
TO YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> I JUST WANT TO KNOW, HAS HE
ALWAYS BEEN LIKE THAT, OR WAS IT
JUST--
>> NO.
>> WHEN WE FIRST STARTING
DATING, I--I NEVER REALLY
HAD A BOYFRIEND BEFORE,
AND HE WAS MY FIRST BOYFRIEND,
AND I DIDN'T GIVE MY ALL TO HIM,
BUT HE DEFINITELY GAVE HIS ALL
TO ME.
IT WENT GOOD AND THEN BAD AND
BACK TO GOOD.
>> WHAT ARE YOU THINKING,
CATELYNN?
>> WHAT AM I THINKING?
NOTHING, 'CAUSE IT JUST--I JUST
KIND OF FELT BAD FOR HER,
BECAUSE IF--I MEAN--
>> ONE THING YOU'VE GOT TO HAND
TO HIM: HE WAS HONEST.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, THAT'S A GOOD
THING THAT IT'S HONEST, BUT JUST
WHEN I WATCHED, AND I HEARD HIM
SAY THAT, LIKE, THAT, LIKE,
CRUSHED MY HEART.
LIKE, I WAS, LIKE, AND THEN YOU
JUST, LIKE, SAT THERE, AND YOU
WERE JUST LIKE, "OH, WELL, THEN
YOU NEED TO LEAVE," AND I WAS
JUST, LIKE, I FELT SO BAD FOR
YOU, BECAUSE IF TYLER WERE TO
SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT TO ME, I
MEAN, I WOULD JUST--
>> IT'S REALISTIC.
HE WAS REALISTIC.
HE WAS HONEST.
>> RIGHT, THAT'S JUST HOW IT
WAS.
>> DO YOU GUYS FEEL SUPPORTIVE
OF ONE ANOTHER?
>> COMPLETELY.
>> YOU LOOK AT EACH OTHER, AND
YOU--
>> I FEEL LIKE THE FIRST TIME I
SAW EVERY ONE OF THEM, I WAS
LIKE, "THEY'RE, LIKE, MY BEST
FRIENDS."
>> ALREADY.
>> SHE JUST CAME UP TO ME AND
HUGGED ME, MACI.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW HER, AND SHE
WAS JUST, LIKE, HUGS ME,
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, HI."
[laughter]
>> WHEN I WATCHED YOUR SHOW, I
JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE SO STRONG,
AND NOW THAT I'VE MET YOU AND
BEEN AROUND YOU, I THINK THAT
WHEN YOU GET OLDER AND YOU DO
HAVE A BABY, YOU'RE GONNA BE AN
AWESOME MOM.
>> YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME CRY.
>> YOU'RE JUST LIKE US.
YOU COULD DO IT.
>> THANKS.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> WE HAVE AN AUDIENCE QUESTION
FROM BECKY.
>> HI, GUYS.
FROM WATCHING THE SHOW, I
NOTICED THAT MOST OF YOU CHOSE
NOT TO BREAST-FEED YOUR BABIES,
AND I WAS JUST WONDERING HOW YOU
CAME TO THAT DECISION.
>> WHO WANTS TO ANSWER THAT?
PEOPLE HAVE GRAVE MISCONCEPTIONS
ABOUT BREAST-FEEDING.
>> CAN I ANSWER THAT?
>> PLEASE.
>> I BREAST-FED FOR A TOTAL OF
TWO WEEKS, AND WHAT GETS PEOPLE
ABOUT BREAST-FEEDING, YOUR--
OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> IT HURTS.
YOUR BOOBS ARE SO ENGORGED WITH
MILK.
LIKE, YOU HAVE TO CONSTANTLY
PUMP, AND YOU DRIP, AND...
>> THERE'S JUST BODY LEAKING
EVERYWHERE.
>> LEAKING FLUIDS, LIKE I SAID.
>> YEAH, I MADE THE DECISION
TO BREAST-FEED, AND I WAS GOING
TO UP TO THE DAY WHEN I HAD
LEAH, AND ALL MY FAMILY WOULD
COME IN, AND THEY ALL WERE LIKE,
"OH, IT HURTS SO BAD," AND THEY
JUST SCARED ME OUT OF IT, BUT I
WAS GOING TO DO IT, AND BY THE
TIME I ACTUALLY MADE THE
DECISION TO, I WASN'T DEVELOPING
ENOUGH MILK TO, SO...
>> SO YOU HAVE TO PRODUCE ENOUGH
MILK.
YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE TO TOLERATE
THE PAIN, AND THEN THE BABY HAS
TO COOPERATE.
>> together: RIGHT.
>> DID ANYBODY HAVE A
COOPERATIVE BABY?
ANYBODY?
>> SOPHIA COOPERATED, BUT I
QUIT.
>> AFTER HOW LONG?
>> A LITTLE LESS THAN A WEEK,
AND SO...
>> BECAUSE...
>> IT WAS JUST TOO MUCH.
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FOUND IT TIRING.
>> IT IS.
>> SO...
>> IT'S PRETTY COMPLICATED,
BREAST-FEEDING.
IT'S MUCH MORE THAN THE
SORT OF THE "ROMANTIC NOTION"
THAT PEOPLE HAVE ABOUT IT.
>> THEY GET SO HARD.
>> THEY GET HARD, AND THEY HURT.
>> IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN, BUT,
LIKE, THE ONLY THING THAT
RELIEVED ME WAS IN THE SHOWER.
>> together: YEAH.
>> THE SHOWER, OH, YES.
>> IT WAS--IT FELT LIKE BRICKS.
[laughter]
>> SIMONE IS OUT IN THE AUDIENCE
STANDING BY WITH A QUESTION.
>> MY QUESTION IS, NOW THAT YOU
GUYS HAVE HAD CHILDREN,
WHAT MESSAGES WOULD YOU POSSIBLY
LIKE TO TEACH THEM IN THE FUTURE
ABOUT TEENAGE PREGNANCY,
CONTRACEPTION, AND
RELATIONSHIPS?
>> BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN A TEEN
PARENT, IT'S MORE LIKELY THAT
YOUR CHILDREN COULD BE AT RISK
FOR TEEN PARENTING.
>> THAT'S A STATISTIC?
>> MM-HMM, AND SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA TELL YOUR KIDS?
HOW ARE YOU GONNA LIVE YOUR
LIFE?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO TO TRY TO
ENCOURAGE THEM MAYBE NOT TO DO
THE SAME THING?
>> YOU'VE JUST GOT TO TALK TO
THEM.
MY PARENTS DIDN'T TALK TO ME
ABOUT ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
>> I MEAN, IF I HAD A DAUGHTER
OR EVEN IF I HAD A SON, I'D BE
BUYING HIM CONDOMS, EVEN IF I
DIDN'T THINK HE WAS HAVING SEX.
JUST SO HE KNOWS THAT, "YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO USE THESE.
THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
DO," OKAY, YOU KNOW, AND THEN,
MAYBE, YOU KNOW, TURN AROUND AND
TELL HIM OUR STORIES, HOW OLD WE
WERE AND HOW HARD IT WAS AND
JUST EVERYTHING YOU WENT
THROUGH, AND IT MIGHT SCARE THEM
A LITTLE BIT, BUT THAT'S A GOOD
THING.
>> JUST TALK TO THEM.
LET THEM KNOW.
>> DISCUSSING CONSEQUENCES...
>> together: YEAH, RIGHT, YES.
>> YEAH, YOU'VE GOT TO REALLY BE
VERY CLEAR ABOUT THE
CONSEQUENCES OF THE CHOICES YOU
MAKE.
>> together: MM-HMM, EXACTLY.
>> NOW, IT'S BEEN A GREAT SHOW,
AND I WANT TO HONOR ALL OF YOU.
YOU'RE JUST REALLY, INDEED,
LOVELY, STRONG, AMAZING YOUNG
WOMEN, EACH AND EVERY ONE OF
YOUR STORIES.
THANK YOU FOR SHARING IT WITH
US.
>> together: THANK YOU.
>> BUT TONIGHT WOULD NOT BE
COMPLETE WITHOUT A VISIT FROM
THE REAL STARS OF THE SHOW,
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
>> together: YEAH.
>> SHOULD WE BRING OUT THE
BABIES?
>> together: YES.
>> LET'S DO IT.
BABIES?
>> THERE'S SOPHIA.
[applause]
>> SHE'S TOO CUTE.
>> AND BY THE WAY, HOW ABOUT A
ROUND OF APPLAUSE FOR THE PEOPLE
THAT HAVE STOOD BEHIND THESE
WOMEN TOO, ALL RIGHT?
WHO ARE LITERALLY STANDING
BEHIND THEM NOW.
[applause]
I'D LIKE TO THANK OUR MOMS AND
OUR DADS AND OUR GRANDMOMS FOR
JOINING US TODAY.
AS FOR YOU AT HOME,
FOR MORE INFORMATION ABOUT
PREVENTION, HEAD TO:
AND STAY IN CONTROL OF YOUR
LIFE.
LOOK OUT FOR SEASON TWO.
I'M DR. DREW.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat rock music]
*
[cheers and applause]
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com