>> [laughing]
I'M ARIANNA.
I'M A SENIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I LIVE IN SMYRNA, GEORGIA.
MOST PEOPLE THINK OF ME AS A
CREATIVE ARTSY TYPE, WHICH I AM.
>> I SEEN A KID OUTSIDE.
HE HAD THE SAME COLOR HAIR.
>> HE HAD BLUE HAIR?
>> THE WHOLE--YEAH.
>> BUT I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE
TO STUDY PSYCHOLOGY BECAUSE
THERE'S BEEN LOTS TO ANALYZE IN
MY LIFE.
MY MOM HAD ME WHEN SHE WAS 17,
AND MY DAD LEFT WHEN I WAS A
BABY.
IT WAS REALLY HARD GROWING UP
WITHOUT A DAD.
>> JUST OUT OF THE BLUE ONE DAY,
YOU WAS LIKE, "WHY DON'T MY
DADDY LOVE ME?"
THAT JUST MADE ME HATE HIM THAT
MUCH MORE.
>> MY MOM GOT REMARRIED
RECENTLY, AND I REALLY DISLIKE
MY STEPFAMILY, SO NOW I LIVE
WITH MY GRANDMA IN AN APARTMENT
SO SMALL, WE HAVE TO SHARE A
BED.
NIGHT, GRANDMA, I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I DON'T MIND BECAUSE I'M
USUALLY HANGING OUT WITH
MAURICE.
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS SINCE MY
FRESHMAN YEAR, THEN WHEN HE TOLD
ME HE HAD FEELINGS FOR ME, WE
STARTED DATING AND THINGS GOT
SERIOUS...
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
A LITTLE TOO SERIOUS BECAUSE NOW
I'M PREGNANT.
MAURICE AND I WERE ONLY DATING A
MONTH AND A HALF WHEN I GOT
PREGNANT, AND IT CHANGED
EVERYTHING BETWEEN US.
WE STARTED ARGUING ALL THE TIME
BECAUSE IT BECAME CLEAR THAT HE
TALKED A BIG GAME, BUT THEN HE'D
FLAKE ON HELPING AND WOULDN'T
CHIP IN ANY MONEY.
MY MOM AND GRANDMA HAVE ALREADY
SPENT MORE THAN THEY CAN AFFORD,
AND I FEEL REALLY GUILTY ABOUT
THAT.
IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE A BURDEN
BECAUSE I CAN'T HELP YOU GUYS
RIGHT NOW, AND ALL I WANT TO DO
IS PAY YOU GUYS BACK.
AND THEN SIX MONTHS INTO MY
PREGNANCY, HE HAD THE NERVE TO
DEMAND A PATERNITY TEST.
[sighs]
NOW WE'RE BROKEN UP, AND WE'RE
HARDLY SPEAKING TO EACH OTHER,
SO I'M TRYING TO FOCUS ON SCHOOL
AND SPEND TIME WITH MY REAL
FRIENDS.
EW, IT LOOKS GROSS.
NO, THAT'S GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
>> WHAT'S IT TASTE LIKE?
>> I'M GETTING THAT ONE.
>> HOMECOMING'S COMING UP, AND
IT'S SENIOR YEAR.
>> UH-OH.
>> DO YOU WANT TO BE MY DATE?
>> UH.
NO, I DON'T KNOW.
>> ARI, WHY?
>> I DON'T--BECAUSE, LIKE,
I'LL BE, LIKE, PREGNANT FOR
HOMECOMING.
>> AT LEAST CAN YOU THINK ABOUT
IT FOR ME?
>> I MEAN, I'LL THINK ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT DO YOU, LIKE, PLAN ON
DOING AFTER HIGH SCHOOL?
>> WELL, I'LL BE DONE WITH ALL
MY CLASSES IN DECEMBER.
IN THE FALL, I'M GOING TO
KENNESAW STATE UNIVERSITY.
>> HOW DID YOU FEEL WHEN ARI
FIRST TOLD YOU, LIKE, SHE WAS
PREGNANT?
>> I WAS SURPRISED.
>> I CRIED.
>> DID YOU CRY, LIKE, SAD?
>> CRIED? WHY WOULD YOU CRY?
>> BECAUSE MY LIFE WAS ABOUT TO
CHANGE, AND I HAD NO CONTROL
OVER IT ANYMORE.
>> HOW'D YOU TELL MAURICE THAT
YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> I HAD HIM COME OVER 'CAUSE HE
LIVED RIGHT UP THE STREET AT THE
TIME, SO I HAD HIM COME OVER,
AND I JUST, LIKE, SHOWED HIM
THE PREGNANCY TEST.
HE WAS, LIKE, SHOCKED, BUT THEN
HE WAS, LIKE, HAPPY--LIKE A
HOUSE AND CAR AND MONEY AND BABY
STUFF WAS JUST GONNA FALL OUT
THE SKY.
>> YEAH, I DON'T THINK IT REALLY
HIT HIM AT THAT POINT, MAN.
LIKE, IT MIGHT HAVE, LIKE--
>> IT STILL HASN'T HIT HIM.
THE BABY SHOWED ME, WHEN I
GOT PREGNANT, HIS TRUE COLORS--
LIKE, HE'S NOT AMBITIOUS, NOT
MOTIVATED, HE'S RUDE, HE'S
DISRESPECTFUL, AND HE'S LAZY AND
IRRESPONSIBLE.
>> NICE.
DO YOU THINK YOU AND MAURICE
WILL HAVE, LIKE, A FUTURE?
>> IF HE CHANGES, POSSIBLY.
IF HE DOESN'T, DEFINITELY NOT.
I WANT HIM TO CHANGE FOR AIDEN
FIRST BEFORE HE CHANGES FOR ME.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S GONNA HIT
HIM UNTIL HE ACTUALLY GETS HERE,
AND HE'S GONNA BE LIKE, "WOW."
>> I DON'T EVEN THINK IT'LL HIT
HIM THEN HONESTLY.
TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST WITH YOU
GUYS, I DON'T BELIEVE THAT HE'S
GOING TO COME AROUND.
I MEAN...
MIRACLES CAN HAPPEN, BUT NO,
I CAN'T SEE IT.
UH-UH.
NOT HAVING MY OWN DAD AROUND
MEANT THAT MY MOM AND I HAVE
ALWAYS BEEN VERY CLOSE.
STILL, I NEVER THOUGHT I'D MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKE SHE DID.
YOU GAVE ME ALL YOUR BAD GENES--
THE SKIN...
>> SORRY THAT I DID ALL THAT.
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN GOING TO THE
DERMATOLOGIST, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT NOT BEING ABLE TO TAKE ANY
PRODUCTS NOW?
>> I DON'T LIKE IT.
>> IT IS GONNA GET BETTER
SOON AS YOU HAVE LITTLE AIDEN.
>> SO HOW'D YOU FEEL WHEN YOU
FIRST FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT?
>> NOT REALLY DEVASTATED BUT
KIND OF BECAUSE OF EVERYTHING
THAT I HAD TOLD YOU AND TAUGHT
YOU.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT ABOUT THE
STRUGGLES THAT I WENT THROUGH
BEING A YOUNG MOM.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY SAY PEOPLE
WORK PAYCHECK TO PAYCHECK?
THAT'S JUST HOW IT WAS.
WHEN YOU FOUND OUT YOU WERE
PREGNANT WITH AIDEN, DID ANY
OTHER THOUGHTS OR IDEAS COME
INTO YOUR MIND AS FAR AS IF YOU
WOULD KEEP HIM OR GIVE HIM UP
OR...
>> ABORTION, NO, BUT AS TIME
WENT ON AND I SEEN HOW HARD IT
WAS, I SEE HOW SOME OF MY
FRIENDS' PARENTS LIVE, LIKE, HOW
THEY HAVE REALLY BIG HOUSES,
AND I'M LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW IF
I'M GONNA BE ABLE TO DO THAT
FOR HIM."
HE DESERVES A LIFE LIKE THAT, SO
MAYBE I SHOULD I GIVE HIM TO A
FAMILY THAT CAN GIVE THAT TO
HIM, BUT THEN I WAS LIKE,
"I CAN'T DO THAT," SO...
IT MAKES ME ANGRY SOMETIMES
BECAUSE I LOOK AROUND AND I SEE
EVERYTHING THAT YOU GUYS HAVE
BOUGHT, AND IT MAKES ME MAD
BECAUSE ALL OF IT WAS NOT
CONTRIBUTED BY RICE
WHO STILL DON'T HAVE A JOB, AND
IT'S ALMOST THE TIME FOR ME TO
DELIVER.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE I DON'T--
I HATE HIM OR SOMETHING NOW,
I STILL HAVE CERTAIN FEELING FOR
RICE.
>> WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE, I COULD
NOT STAND YOUR FATHER.
>> I GET WHERE THAT COMES FROM.
>> AND SO THAT'S WHY AS FAR AS
WITH THE SITUATION WITH RICE,
IT COULD COME OUT POSITIVE, AND
THEN IT COULD BE THE SITUATION
I HAD WITH YOU.
>> SINCE I DIDN'T HAVE A FATHER
GROWING UP, I'M EXTREMELY
SENSITIVE TO MAURICE NOT BEING
AROUND OR ACTING THE WAY I THINK
A GOOD DAD SHOULD.
>> HEY, GRANDMA.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> WHAT'S GOING ON, GRANDDAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
NOTHING.
>> NOT MUCH? JUST CHILLING.
>> SO YOU GETTING READY FOR THE
BABY?
>> YEAH, I'M READY, AIN'T GOT NO
OTHER CHOICE.
>> IT'S REALLY CRUNCH TIME, AND
YOU DON'T REALLY HAVE A LOT OF
MONEY COMIN' IN.
NOW THAT THE TIME IS ALMOST
NEAR, YOU JUST REALLY GONNA HAVE
TO STEP UP, MAURICE.
SO I STILL GOT THIS MUSIC THING.
>> [sighs]
I KNOW, RICEY, BUT STILL YOU
REALLY NEED TO GET ON THE GRIND
'CAUSE THIS BABY IS ON THE WAY,
AND WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU AND
ARIANNA?
>> NAH, WE NOT TOGETHER.
SHE GOT UPSET AT ME BECAUSE
I MENTIONED PATERNITY TEST.
>> RIGHT, I MEAN, GRANDDADDY WAS
THE MAIN ONE THAT STARTED IT AND
SAID--AND NOT THAT YOU DIDN'T
TRUST HER--
>> RIGHT, Y'ALL KNOW--I KNOW
IT'S MY KID.
>> BUT YOU WANTED TO BE SURE
THAT MAURICE WAS PROTECTED,
YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, YEAH, THAT'S THE MAIN
THING.
>> I REALLY WANT TO MAKE THIS
WORK WITH ARIANNA JUST BECAUSE I
KNOW IT'LL BE THE BEST THING FOR
MY SON JUST TO HAVE BOTH OF HIS
PARENTS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW MY DAD LEFT ME WHEN
I WAS LITTLE.
I DON'T WANT MY SON TO HAVE TO
GO THROUGH THAT OR HAVE TO LEARN
EVERYTHING THAT I LEARNED THE
WAY I DID, YOU KNOW, WITHOUT
HIM.
>> BECAUSE I'M DUE IN DECEMBER,
I'M TAKING ACCELERATED CLASSES
ONLINE SO I CAN FINISH ALL MY
COURSE WORK BEFORE AIDEN IS
BORN.
THIS IS DEFINITELY NOT THE
SENIOR YEAR I HAD ALWAYS
IMAGINED.
I STILL MISS BEING IN A
CLASSROOM.
>> THE STUFF THAT SENIORS DO?
>> OH, YEAH, LIKE SENIOR
KIDNAPPING AND JUST BEING
RECOGNIZED AS A SENIOR AND
PERIOD.
>> MM-HMM, I THINK YOU'RE DOING
GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE IN THIS, BUT IN
A WAY YOU ARE ALONE IN THIS AS
FAR AS THE DAD GOES.
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN THE BABY'S BORN, THE
MAIN THING IS HOW YOU'RE GONNA
HANDLE THE GETTING UP IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT, HOWEVER
MANY TIMES IT TAKES.
IT KIND OF WORRIES ME HOW YOU'RE
GONNA HANDLE IT YOURSELF, BUT I
MEAN, YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST THAT
SINCE YOU'VE NEVER HAD ACTUALLY
A FATHER FIGURE TO SHOW YOU HOW
THE MAN IS SUPPOSED TO BE WITH
THE CHILD, YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES I
JUST WONDER HOW YOU'RE GONNA
REACT TO THE RESPONSIBILITY OF
THE BABY.
I MEAN, OF COURSE, WE'LL ALWAYS
BE THERE, BUT THE RESPONSIBILITY
OF YOU ACTUALLY ON YOUR OWN.
>> THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE MORE I REALIZE, EVEN IF
WE'RE NOT TOGETHER, MAURICE HAS
TO STEP UP AND HELP OUT.
[phone line ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> NOT MUCH.
>> SO ANY UPDATES ON ANYTHING
GOING ON IN YOUR LIFE?
>> HAVE YOU GOTTEN ANYTHING FOR
THE BABY?
>> I SAID, HAVE YOU GOTTEN
ANYTHING FOR THE BABY, SOME
DIAPERS OR SOMETHING?
>> OKAY, SO...
>> WHY ARE YOU HAVING A SHOWER?
YOU'RE NOT THE MOM.
I'M SORRY, BUT THAT MAKES NO
SENSE.
>> YEAH, WELL, WHEN HE IS OVER
THERE--
WHEN.
IT'S NOT GONNA BE ANYTIME SOON.
>> ALL I EVER HEAR FROM Y'ALL IS
TALK.
I DON'T EVER SEE NOTHING.
I NEED TO SEE SOME ACTION.
I'M NOT GONNA BE THE ONLY ONE
TAKING CARE OF HIM FINANCIALLY.
>> AT THE END OF THE DAY, YOU
NEED TO CHANGE UP.
I'M TIRED OF HEARING STUFF.
I WANT TO SEE SOME ACTION.
IF NOT, AIN'T NOTHING GONNA
CHANGE.
I'M NOT GONNA BE THE ONE DOING
THIS--
>> WELL, I NEED TO SEE--
I NEED TO SEE SOMETHING.
I NEED TO SEE IT.
>> I HAVE.
YES, I HAVE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HAVE YOU DONE IT?
>> HAVE YOU DONE IT?
IT DON'T MATTER.
YOU BEING SORRY, THAT'S WHY.
>> YOU BEING SORRY.
DON'T BE LIKE MY DAD OR YOURS.
BYE-BYE.
JESUS [bleep].
>> DOING ALL MY CLASSES ONLINE
HAS MEANT MISSING THE FUN PARTS
OF SCHOOL, SO I AGREED TO GO TO
HOMECOMING WITH NOLYN.
IT'LL HELP TO GET MY MIND OFF
MAURICE FOR A LITTLE WHILE TOO.
>> HEY, BABE.
>> HEY.
>> I MISSED YOU.
>> YOU'LL BE OKAY.
COME GET READY.
[upbeat guitar music]
*
THAT'S CUTE.
>> IS IT REALLY CUTE?
>> YEAH.
YEAH.
>> I JUST REALLY THINK THIS IS
JUST GONNA BE SO--IT'S GONNA BE
JUDGE ARIANNA NIGHT.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE JUDGE
ARIANNA NIGHT.
>> AWW...
>> YOU LOOK SO PRETTY!
>> SHE LOOKS SO PRETTY.
[laughter]
>> BYE.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> BYE. LOVE YOU TOO.
>> * PUSH AND I WILL FALL
* WE'LL GET FARTHER *
* FROM THIS DAY
* AWAY FROM YESTERDAY
* I'LL KEEP THIS GOING AWAY *
>> NO, NONE OF THAT.
>> * I'LL COME BACK *
* WHEN I MUST GO
* I CAN'T GET ENOUGH OF THIS *
>> DANCING AND SEEING FRIENDS
WAS GREAT.
I WAS ABLE TO IGNORE THE LOOKS
AND JUST HAVE FUN FOR A COUPLE
HOURS.
>> DID YOU LADIES HAVE FUN?
>> YEAH, IT WAS COOL.
>> * I CAN'T GET ENOUGH *
* OF THIS
>> ARE YOU GLAD YOU GOT OUT OF
THE HOUSE?
>> YEAH, I DID HAVE FUN.
>> DID IT TAKE SOME OF YOUR MIND
OFF THE PRESSURES?
>> YES, IT DID.
>> THAT WAS THE GOAL.
ACCOMPLISHED!
>> IT WAS, LIKE, I FELT LIKE I
WAS STUCK UNDER A ROCK, AND I,
LIKE, CAME OUT, AND I MISSED
SO MUCH.
IT MADE ME REALIZE HOW MUCH
I STAY IN THE HOUSE AND HOW MUCH
I NEED TO GET OUT.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT ALWAYS HAVING
TO DEPEND ON MY MOM TO DRIVE ME
EVERYWHERE.
A BIG PART OF GETTING READY FOR
AIDEN MEANS FINALLY GETTING MY
DRIVER'S LICENSE.
>> PARALLEL PARKING, LET'S START
WITH THAT.
I WANT TO SEE HOW GOOD OR HOW
BAD YOU ARE.
>> [laughing] OKAY.
>> LET'S GO FOR IT.
>> THAT FELT LIKE IT WAS--
YEAH.
>> UH, I THINK YOU JUST HIT A
FERRARI.
>> [laughs]
I'M DUE IN EIGHT WEEKS, AND
TODAY I HAVE A SONOGRAM
APPOINTMENT.
I'M STILL SO FRUSTRATED WITH
MAURICE THAT I DIDN'T EVEN
BOTHER TELLING HIM ABOUT IT.
>> OKAY!
I'M EXCITED!
>> LITTLE HEART.
>> YOU CAN SEE HIS HEART BEATING
RIGHT HERE.
>> AWW!
>> I'LL ENHANCE HIS HAND.
>> [gasps]
>> SEE HIS HANDS THERE?
>> OH, THEY'RE LIKE THIS.
>> AWW!
>> WAIT, I WANT TO SEE WHAT HIS
LITTLE FEETS LOOK LIKE.
>> I SEE HIS EYES--
BOTH EYES NOW AND HIS MOUTH.
>> OH, I KIND OF SAW, JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
>> OH, I SEE IT!
[sorrowful guitar music]
*
>> * NOBODY'S PERFECT *
>> THEY LOOK LIKE RICE'S LIMBS.
>> * HOW COME YOU ARE?
*IF NOBODY'S PERFECT *
>> AFTER SEEING MY BABY, I JUST
COULDN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT
HIM.
AND THEN LATER THAT NIGHT, I HAD
A DREAM THAT HE ASKED ME WHERE
HIS DADDY WAS, AND I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL HIM.
I TEXTED MAURICE THAT I WANTED
TO TALK FACE-TO-FACE, AND HE
AGREED TO MEET UP.
I KNOW AIDEN DESERVES TO HAVE
BOTH A MOM AND A DAD IN HIS
LIFE, SO I'M WILLING TO GIVE
MAURICE ANOTHER CHANCE
TO MAN UP.
>> I HOPE YOU HAVE A GOOD TALK.
>> I'M KIND OF LIKE, EH...
OKAY, YEAH, I HOPE I DO TOO.
ALL RIGHT.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> SUP, MAN?
>> HEY.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> EH, TIRED.
>> TIRED?
>> YEAH.
I THOUGHT IT'D BE BETTER IF WE
CAME AND TALKED ABOUT HOW WE'RE
GONNA GO ABOUT DOING THINGS.
>> YOU KNOW THAT I'MA ALWAYS
MAKE SURE THAT I'M DOING MY
PART, AND I'M ALWAYS THERE
FOR YOU--
>> WELL, IT'S NOT REALLY ME
KNOWING BECAUSE, FINANCIALLY,
THINGS NEED TO BE BETTER ON YOUR
PART 'CAUSE OF COURSE I WOULD
ALREADY HAVE A JOB IF I WASN'T--
>> BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT--
BUT THAT'S NOT--IT IS AN ISSUE.
>> EXACTLY, AND YOU SHOULD BE
DOING THAT.
>> OKAY, BUT I TOLD YOU
BEFORE THAT--
>> YOU TOLD ME A LOT OF THINGS,
BUT I NEED TO SEE IT.
YOU'RE NOT TRYING AS HARD AS
OTHER PEOPLE WHO REALLY TRY.
LIKE, I WOULD THINK--
>> DON'T TELL ME I'M NOT TRYING
BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT WITH ME.
I MEAN, WE AIN'T BEEN TALKING.
WE AIN'T BEEN TOGETHER, SEEING
EACH OTHER.
>> RICE, I DON'T HAVE TO BE WITH
YOU UNLESS YOU'RE NOT SHOWING
ANYTHING.
>> JUST A LOT GOING ON.
>> WHAT IS GOING ON WITH YOU?
WHAT IS GOING ON IN YOUR LIFE
THAT IS SO HARD THAT YOU CAN'T
GET A 9:00 TO 5:00 JOB?
>> IT'S NOT EVEN ABOUT HAVING
A 9:00--
>> IT IS ABOUT HAVING A JOB.
YES, IT IS.
WE ARE HAVING A CHILD WHO NEEDS
THINGS WHICH COST MONEY.
>> MY FAMILY DONE BOUGHT PLENTY
OF THINGS.
>> REALLY? WHERE'S IT AT?
>> I WILL BRING EVERYTHING TO
YOUR HOUSE WHEN I FEEL LIKE IT'S
NECESSARY.
>> NO, IT'S NECESSARY NOW.
>> HE'S NOT EVEN HERE YET.
>> WHAT DOES IT MATTER?
YOU KNOW WHAT, AND THAT'S ONE
THING--
THAT'S ONE THING THAT I'MA
TELL YOU RIGHT NOW.
A BABY NEEDS BEFORE AND AFTER.
YOU CANNOT HAVE ZERO FOR A BABY
AND HIM COME INTO THE WORLD,
"OH, WE JUST GONNA GO TO THE
STORE."
>> THAT'S THE THING.
YOU SOUND DUMB.
>> NO, I DON'T SOUND DUMB.
>> YOU SOUND DUMB.
>> NO, ANOTHER THING, YOU'RE NOT
GONNA TALK TO ME LIKE,
"YOU'RE CRAZY."
DON'T DISRESPECT ME.
>> YOU'RE CRAZY WHEN YOU'RE
TELLING ME WHAT TO DO--
>> NO, BECAUSE I'M DOING WHAT I
GOT TO DO.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, YOU'RE
NOT GONNA CHANGE.
YOU'RE CHILDISH AND IF THIS
CONTINUES--
>> ALL RIGHT, [bleep]. [bleep].
>> OKAY. WHATEVER.
[sighs]
[phone line ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> MOM, IT WENT--
SO HE JUST WALKED OFF.
>> I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK IT
WOULD THAT BAD.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD END THAT
QUICK.
>> ALL WE WAS TALKING ABOUT WAS
HOW HE JUST NEEDS TO GET JOB.
HE'S TALKING ABOUT, "OH, MY MOM
AND MY GRANDMA DONE BOUGHT A
WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF."
AND I WAS LIKE, "OKAY, SO JUST
BRING IT TO MY HOUSE."
"I'LL BRING IT WHEN I FEEL IT,
WHEN I FEEL LIKE IT, WHEN IT'S
NECESSARY," HAVING A ATTITUDE.
BUT I JUST--I WANTED IT TO WORK
BECAUSE I JUST WANTED AIDEN TO
BE ABLE TO NOT ONLY HAVE BOTH OF
HIS PARENTS IN HIS LIFE, BUT SEE
THAT BOTH OF HIS PARENTS CAN GET
ALONG VERY WELL.
>> YEAH.
I LOVE YOU.
>> BYE.
AIDEN'S DUE DATE IS LESS THAN
SIX WEEKS AWAY, AND TODAY IS MY
BABY SHOWER.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE MY FRIENDS
AND TO GET MORE THINGS FOR AIDEN
IN A WAY THAT ISN'T ALL ON MY
MOM AND GRANDMA.
>> HI!
>> HELLO.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> THERE WE GO.
SO HOW IS REGULAR TEENAGER LIFE?
>> A STRUGGLE.
>> IT'S A STRUGGLE.
>> Y'ALL ARE SENIORS.
I WANT TO BE A SENIOR AT SCHOOL.
>> WE CAN BRING YOU A SHIRT.
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
[laughter]
>> ONE STARTING TALKING RIGHT
HERE, I'M JUST LIKE, "START
OVER."
>> [laughing]
OKAY, NOW THIS IS CUTE.
AH, THIS SMELL'S LIKE--
I'LL LET YOU SMELL MY DIAPERS.
>> I COULDN'T GET ANY WRAPPING
PAPER.
[laughter]
>> THIS IS MY FAVORITE BAG OUT
OF ALL THE BAGS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AWW!
>> THIS IS THE HAPPIEST I'VE
SEEN YOU IN A MINUTE.
>> 'CAUSE Y'ALL ARE HILARIOUS.
>> DID YOU HAVE A GOOD TIME?
>> YES, I DID.
>> GOOD.
>> I JUST WANT TO HAVE A BABY
SHOWER EVERY DAY.
>> SEE, I CAN'T AFFORD THAT.
>> [laughing]
MY DUE DATE IS ONLY THREE WEEKS
AWAY, AND I HAVEN'T HEARD A WORD
FROM MAURICE.
I'M GLAD THAT WE'RE ALL DOING
SOMETHING TOGETHER.
>> YEAH, IT'S FUN.
>> IT'S HARD FOR ME TO GET OVER
MY DISAPPOINTMENT WITH HIM, BUT
I'M TRYING TO TAKE MY MIND OFF
THINGS BY FOCUSING ON GETTING
READY FOR AIDEN TO BE HERE AND
SPENDING TIME WITH FRIENDS.
>> [laughs]
>> WHOO!
>> HELLO!
>> HEY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SO HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
>> I HAVE BEEN TIRED AND SLEEPY
ALL THE TIME.
>> BUT IT'S EXCITING.
LIKE, YOU HAVE, LIKE, A COUPLE
OF WEEKS TO GO.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE DOING WHAT YOU HAVE TO
DO FOR YOUR BABY.
IN COLLEGE, WHAT DO YOU PLAN ON
STUDYING?
>> I WANTED, YOU KNOW, TO GO GET
MY PhD IN PSYCHOLOGY, BUT THAT
TAKES 11 YEARS.
NOW I HAVE TO THINK ABOUT THE
BABY, SO I HAVE TO GO WITH
PLAN B, MAJOR IN REGISTERED
NURSING.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, ANOTHER ONE OF
THE SACRIFICES YOU HAVE TO MAKE
BY GETTING PREGNANT WHEN YOU'RE
YOUNG.
>> SO, LIKE, WHERE DO YOU AND
RICE STAND NOW?
>> WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
AFTER THAT WHOLE PATERNITY TEST
THING, AFTER THAT IT'S, LIKE,
NO.
AND THEN HE KEEPS SAYING THAT
HE'S TRYING TO GET A JOB, AND HE
DOESN'T GET A JOB.
IF IT WASN'T FOR MY MOM AND MY
GRANDMOTHER, MY BABY WOULD HAVE
NOTHING RIGHT NOW, LIKE,
NOTHING.
SO, LIKE, I FINALLY REALIZED
THAT, LIKE, HE'S ALL TALK AND NO
ACTION.
>> HAVE YOU TOLD HIM HOW YOU
FELT ABOUT EVERYTHING?
>> OH, YEAH, PLENTY OF TIMES.
I'VE TOLD HIM HOW I FELT PLENTY
OF TIMES, AND IT JUST DOESN'T
CHANGE.
LIKE, I GET THE SAME RESPONSE
FROM HIM, WHICH IS DIFFERENT
FROM HIS ACTIONS.
>> SO I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY RIGHT
NOW IT HASN'T HIT HIM, BUT WHEN
IT DOES, I MEAN, IT'S GONNA HIT
HIM HARD.
>> I HOPE IT DOES. I REALLY DO.
I HOPE THAT--I REALLY HOPE HE
CAN CHANGE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I WANT HIM TO BE,
LIKE, A BAD PERSON SO I COULD
ALWAYS PUT HIM DOWN LIKE, "YEAH,
YOU AIN'T NEVER BEEN THERE," AND
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH LIKE A LOT OF
GIRLS WANT TO DO.
I WANT TO SEE HIM DO GOOD.
I REALLY TRULY DO FOR THE BABY.
IT'D BE GREAT FOR ME TOO, BUT
IT'S NOT ABOUT ME.
IT'S REALLY ABOUT AIDEN, AND I
JUST WANT HIM TO BE A GOOD DAD,
AND THAT'S REALLY IT.
LIKE, I'M NOT ASKING FOR
ANYTHING MORE, AND I DON'T THINK
THAT'S TOO MUCH TO ASK FOR
ANYWAYS.
>> YEAH.
>> AS MUCH AS I WANTED MAURICE
TO HELP ME PREPARE BEFORE THE
BABY COMES, HE ISN'T GONNA HAVE
A CHANCE NOW BECAUSE WHEN I WENT
FOR MY WEEKLY CHECKUP, THE
DOCTOR WAS CONCERNED ABOUT THE
BABY'S MEASUREMENTS, SO HE
DECIDED TO INDUCE ME RIGHT AWAY.
>> UGH!
>> EVEN THOUGH WE'RE STILL NOT
GETTING ALONG, I WANT TO LET
MAURICE KNOW THE BABY'S COMING.
OKAY, I'M GONNA CALL RICE.
[phone line ringing]
>> YEAH, I'M IN THE HOSPITAL.
THEY'RE GONNA INDUCE ME AND
DELIVER TODAY RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT'S UP TO YOU.
>> I FEEL LIKE I NEED MORE
OXYGEN.
>> OH! I LOVE IT.
>> THAT'S WONDERFUL.
GRANDMA...
IT'S HURTING IN MY BACK LIKE YOU
SAID.
>> I WOULDN'T LIE TO YOU.
>> I KNOW.
OW!
EVEN THOUGH I WAS WORRIED ABOUT
HAVING HIM HERE, BEING IN LABOR
IS REALLY SCARY, AND MAURICE IS
BEING SWEET AND HELPFUL, AND I'M
ACTUALLY HAPPY HE'S HERE.
[sniffles]
[crying]
SO BAD...
WHEN THE PAIN STARTED TO GET
UNBEARABLE, I ASKED FOR AN
EPIDURAL.
>> ARE YOU ALL READY?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> YES. YES. YES.
>> AND BEFORE I KNEW IT...
[baby crying]
>> * I FOUND LOVE
* WHERE YOU ARE
* I DON'T WANT TO GO *
* WITHOUT YOU
>> [babbling]
>> GRANDMA.
>> YOU'RE MY LITTLE PRECIOUS,
PRECIOUS SWEET PEA.
LITTLE SWEET PEA.
[sweeping music]
*
>> * I DON'T WANT TO BE *
* WITHOUT YOU
>> WHAT MADE YOU CALL ME?
>> WHAT I WANT IS...
DIDN'T REALLY HAVE A REASON.
I JUST CALLED.
>> SEEING HIM BEING BORN JUST
MEANT THE WORLD TO ME.
>> I JUST WISH THAT EVERYTHING
WASN'T SO LAST-MINUTE.
>> OH, YEAH?
HE'S HERE NOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"IT'S OVER WITH?"
>> THE SITUATION.
LITTLE AIDEN WAS GONNA BE TAKEN
CARE OF THE RIGHT WAY.
>> YEAH, HE WAS BY MY MOM AND
GRANDMOTHER FOR THE MOST PART.
THAT'S WHAT MADE ME ANGRY.
I'M JUST BEING HONEST WITH YOU.
I'M NOT TRYING TO CAUSE AN
ARGUMENT, BUT THAT'S JUST
HONESTY, AND IT COULD CHANGE.
I'M NOT SAYING IT CAN'T, BUT IT
COULD HAVE BEEN A LONG TIME AGO.
>> COULD HAVE BEEN.
>> DON'T COME BACK TO MY
HOSPITAL.
YOU NEED TO OWN UP TO WHAT YOU
DID WRONG, MAURICE.
YOU JUST NEED TO, AND IF YOU
CAN'T, I DON'T WANT YOU AROUND
ME BECAUSE YOU NEED TO BE MAN
ENOUGH TO KNOW WHAT YOU DID
WRONG.
>> GIVE ME MY BABY.
GIVE ME--
>> I WILL CALL A NURSE IN HERE
IF YOU DO NOT GIVE ME MY CHILD
AND GET OUT OF MY ROOM RIGHT
NOW.
>> YOU'VE BEEN HOLDING HIM.
GIVE ME MY CHILD AND GET OUT OF
MY ROOM.
YOU'RE STRESSING ME OUT.
>> I NEED A NURSE IN MY ROOM
PLEASE.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL I WANTED WAS A SIMPLE
OWNING UP.
JUST OWN UP TO WHAT YOU DID IN
THE PAST.
THAT'S IT.
"NOT GOING TO BECAUSE I DIDN'T
DO NOTHING WRONG."
>> NOW THAT YOU'VE TRIED...
>> BUT I FEEL LIKE IT'S GONNA
GET UGLY NOW, MAYBE I MADE A--
[baby cries]
OH, WHAT'S WRONG?
>> YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY WHAT?
WHEN I ASK YOU TO GIVE ME MY
BABY BACK, YOU GIVE ME MY BABY
BACK.
>> IF HE'S LIKE THAT THE SAME
DAY HE WAS BORN, YOU DO NEED TO
DISTANCE FROM HIM.
>> HOW'S MY BABY?
>> HE'S GREAT.
WITH AIDEN BEING BORN AND
EVERYTHING, THAT WAS LIKE, YOU
KNOW, THE BEST EXPERIENCE.
>> BUT IT JUST WENT DOWNHILL
AND...
>> YEAH.
>> REAL QUICK.
>> LIKE, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> SHE WAS LIKE, STARTED
BRINGING UP, YOU KNOW, OLD STUFF
LIKE, "OH, YOU WASN'T HERE FOR
THE WHOLE NINE MONTHS," OR LIKE,
"YOU WASN'T DOING NOTHING," OR
WHATEVER, BLAH, BLAH, AND SHE
WAS LIKE, "WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE
DID THIS."
I'M LIKE, "ALL RIGHT, BUT IT
WASN'T DONE, SO..."
"WELL, IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN."
"OKAY, BUT IT'S NOT, ANYWAYS,"
AND THEN SHE WAS LIKE, "WELL,
I'MA NEED YOU TO LEAVE THE
ROOM," OR WHATEVER.
"I'MA CALL THE NURSE."
>> SHE'S SO DRAMATIC.
SHE'S SO DRAMATIC.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
AT THIS POINT, I DON'T WANT TO
DEAL WITH HER, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME, I JUST WANT TO SEE HIM.
>> I KNOW.
I WAS THINKING THE SAME THING.
>> THAT'S MY SON, SO...
>> I DON'T KNOW. IT'S HARD.
>> SHE IS MAKING THIS SO
DIFFICULT FOR ME.
I'M TIRED OF IT.
>> MAURICE AND I HAVEN'T TALKED
SINCE I KICKED HIM OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL.
EVEN THOUGH I'M EXCITED TO BE
TAKING AIDEN HOME, I HATE THAT
I HAVE TO DO THIS ALONE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> AIDEN GETS TO GO HOME!
I GOT MY LITTLE AIDEN IN THE
CAR.
>> I'M EXCITED ABOUT BEING A
MOM.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I'M NOT REALLY FOCUSED ON ANY
NEGATIVE STUFF RIGHT NOW.
I'M JUST FOCUSED ON GETTING THE
BABY HOME AND GETTING HIM
SETTLED.
RICE HAS NOT TRIED TO ASK ABOUT
THE BABY, SO UNLESS HE CALLS OR,
YOU KNOW, TRIES TO MAKE ANY TYPE
OF EFFORT, I WOULD RATHER JUST
NOT EVEN TALK TO ABOUT HIM FOR
THE REST OF THE DAY 'CAUSE HE
BRINGS UP NEGATIVE ENERGY, AND
I DON'T WANT TO THINK ABOUT IT
RIGHT NOW.
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO ENJOY
THESE MOMENTS WITH MY BABY.
>> RIGHT.
>> YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
>> YAY, HOME!
>> HE IS SOUND ASLEEP.
>> HE'S ABOUT TO START CRYING
'CAUSE HE'S GRUMPY.
HE DON'T LIKE TO BE NAKED.
WHAT IS HE EATING?
WHAT'S IN MY BREAST MILK?
[laughs]
OH, ARE YOU NOT DONE YET?
>> HOLD ON, MAMA. LIFT HIM.
IT GOT ON HIS ONESIE A LITTLE
BIT.
>> WE'LL HAVE TO GET HIM
SOMETHING ELSE.
>> I KNOW.
[baby crying]
OKAY.
WHERE'S HIS--OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
OKAY, HE'S NOT DONE!
>> OH, WOW!
>> O-M-G!
>> HE'S GOT SOME OVER THERE.
>> I KNOW, MAMA.
GIVE ME A SECOND.
>> ARIANNA.
>> HEY, YOU'RE ACTING LIKE--
GIVE ME A SECOND. STOP--
>> I AM. I'M JUST TRYING--
[baby crying]
>> I KNOW IT.
IF YOU WOULD STOP IT, WE
COULD GET YOU IN SOME CLOTHES.
>> ARE YOU DONE THIS TIME?
>> I NEED ANOTHER DIAPER NOW.
HOW DID IT GET ON HIS FACE?
[baby screeching]
>> OH, HEY, YOU'RE MAD NOW.
>> I COULD USE THAT ABOUT RIGHT
NOW.
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
>> WHERE?
[baby crying]
>> MAURICE HAS STARTED TEXTING
ME ABOUT WHEN HE CAN SEE THE
BABY.
I TOLD HIM AS SOON AS HE GETS A
JOB, BRINGS OVER STUFF FOR
AIDEN, AND APOLOGIZES FOR HIS
BEHAVIOR.
I JUST HOPE THIS IS NOT ONE OF
THOSE NIGHTS WHERE HE'S JUST
FUSSY FOR NO REASON 'CAUSE I
HATE THOSE.
SINCE MY GRANDMA'S RETIRED,
SHE'S AROUND A LOT TO LEND A
HAND, BUT EVEN WITH HER HELP,
TAKING CARE OF AIDEN HAS BEEN
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
[baby crying]
[gentle rock music]
*
[baby crying]
AH!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
[baby crying]
YOU'RE REALLY GETTING ON MY
NERVES.
KEEPING UP IN SCHOOL ON VERY
LITTLE SLEEP HASN'T BEEN EASY,
BUT I'M REALLY CLOSE TO BEING
DONE, SO I CAN'T GIVE UP NOW.
MOMMY'S GOT TO CATCH UP ON HER
SCHOOL WORK, BUT YOU'RE BEING SO
CUTE OVER THERE IS MAKING IT
HARD.
CAN YOU DO MY ASSIGNMENTS FOR
ME?
I GUESS I FINALLY GOT THROUGH TO
MAURICE BECAUSE A WEEK LATER, HE
TEXTED ME THAT HE GOT A JOB AND
EVEN SENT ME A PICTURE OF HIS
NEW WORK I.D.
AND THEN HE CAME BY WITH
EVERYTHING I ASKED FOR.
>> SUP, MAN?
>> HEY.
>> I GOT YOU SOME MORE DIAPERS
AND STUFF, SOME AIR JORDANS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> LITTLE RED AND WHITE ONES.
>> [laughing]
>> LET'S PLAY.
WHAT'S UP?
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> I KNOW.
I'M ABOUT TO TURN HIM AROUND.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
YOU OKAY?
YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> YOU LOOK GOOD.
HE ALWAYS LOOKS GOOD.
>> I KNOW.
I'M GLAD I GOT TO SPEND SOME
TIME WITH YOU, AIDEN.
MISSED MY LITTLE BOY.
>> HE'S HUNGRY.
>> YOU HUNGRY?
YOU GOT A BOTTLE?
>> GO MAKE HIM ONE.
I'LL HOLD HIM.
[baby fussing]
[baby crying]
I WOULD HAVE LIKED AN APOLOGY,
BUT I'M HAPPY THAT MAURICE IS
FINALLY DOING WHAT HE'S SUPPOSED
TO.
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO SEE
FRIENDS AT ALL SINCE AIDEN WAS
BORN, SO I ASKED MY MOM TO WATCH
HIM SO I COULD GO OUT FOR A
LITTLE BIT.
>> LOOKS LIKE YOUR HORMONES HAS
CLEARED UP, YOUR FACE HAS
CLEARED UP SINCE YOU, YOU KNOW--
[popping]
POPPED HIM OUT.
>> DON'T DO THE NOISE OF POPPING
AIDEN OUT.
THANK YOU FOR TELLING ME THAT I
LOOK BETTER.
>> DO YOU MISS, LIKE, BEFORE YOU
WERE PREGNANT?
>> YEAH, MM-HMM.
SURE DO.
>> BUT DO YOU FEEL LIKE THIS
WILL MAKE YOU A MORE WISER
PERSON IN THE FUTURE?
>> IT'LL MAKE ME MORE MATURE,
BUT DO I NECESSARILY WISH IT
WOULD BE RIGHT NOW?
NO.
I DON'T WANT TO BE A MOM
RIGHT NOW.
>> SO THE LAST I HEARD, YOU AND
MAURICE, YOU KNOW, WEREN'T ON
THAT WELL OF TERMS.
HOW SINCE AIDEN IS HERE--
AND HOW'S THAT BEEN TO SEE...
>> THINGS ARE STARTING TO
ACTUALLY LOOK UP WITH HIM FOR
THE SIMPLE FACT THAT HE'S GOT A
JOB NOW.
>> WOW.
>> AND YOU KNOW, IF I ASK HIM
FOR SOMETHING, HE'LL BRING IT
BY.
LIKE, AS LONG AS HE HAS THE
MONEY FOR IT, HE'LL BRING IT BY.
BASICALLY, HE'S JUST, LIKE--
HE'S ON THE RIGHT PATH RIGHT
NOW, AND BEFORE HE WASN'T EVEN
ON THE RIGHT PATH.
LIKE, NOW HE'S ON THE RIGHT
PATH.
HE'S JUST GOT A LONG WAY TO GO.
>> COULD YOU POSSIBLY SEE A
FUTURE WITH HIM AGAIN?
>> HONESTLY, RIGHT NOW, I'M NOT
EVEN TRYING TO REALLY THINK
ABOUT IS OUR RELATIONSHIP
GOING TO BE RECOVERED.
IT'S KIND OF, LIKE, I'M STILL
MAD AT HIM FOR THINGS THAT HE
DID WHEN I WAS PREGNANT, SO
NO MATTER IF ME AND MAURICE WORK
OUT, THE MOST IMPORTANT THING TO
ME IS THAT AIDEN HAVE BOTH
PARENTS IN HIS LIFE.
I'M TRYING TO GET THERE.
>> YEAH, I UNDERSTAND.
>> I CALLED MAURICE AND ASKED
HIM IF HE WANTED TO HANG OUT AT
THIS COFFEE SHOP OR WHATEVER.
I WANT TO SEE HOW THINGS ARE
GONNA GO WITH HIM.
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF YOU
WOULDN'T MIND WATCHING AIDEN
WHILE I GO OVER THERE.
>> OKAY.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
I MEAN THAT FOR REAL.
>> OH, THANKS.
THAT MEANS SO MUCH.
>> SUP, BABY?
>> AW, WHAT IS THIS STUFF?
>> I GOT MY LITTLE MAN A NICE
LITTLE SUIT.
>> AWW.
ROCK ON.
>> HERE'S THAT MANGO SMOOTHIE.
Y'ALL ENJOY.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
>> SO HOW'S YOUR JOB BEEN GOING?
>> IT'S BEEN GOING ALL RIGHT,
'CAUSE, I MEAN, I'VE BEEN
WORKING HARD AND JUST TRYING TO
STAY GOOD FOR LITTLE AIDEN,
SO I CAN'T WAIT TO BE ABLE TO
COME OVER MORE, SO I CAN
CHANGE HIS LITTLE DIAPERS AND
TAKE CARE OF HIM SO YOU CAN GET
SOME REST.
>> I APPRECIATE YOU, LIKE,
GETTING A JOB OR WHATEVER AND,
LIKE, DOING WHAT YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO DO, BUT THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING TO ME
IS THAT AIDEN HAVE BOTH PARENTS
IN HIS LIFE.
>> I GUESS, YOU KNOW, ME NOT
GROWING UP WITH MY DAD AND HIM
LEAVING WHEN I WAS YOUNG,
I MEAN, THAT'S WHY I REALLY FEEL
LIKE I JUST NEED TO, YOU KNOW,
BE THERE FOR Y'ALL.
>> LIKE, WE'VE HAD REALLY BAD
PROBLEMS, LIKE, REALLY BAD
PROBLEMS, REALLY TERRIBLE
ARGUMENTS.
>> YEAH.
>> WE WAS GETTING ALONG BEFORE
AIDEN WAS CONCEIVED BECAUSE YOU
DIDN'T HAVE TO HAVE NO
RESPONSIBILITIES, AND THEN WHEN
YOU HAD TO HAVE
RESPONSIBILITIES, THINGS
CHANGED 'CAUSE I HAD TO PUSH YOU
TO DO WHAT YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO DO.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO PUSH ME TO
NOTHING.
WE JUST DIDN'T GET ALONG BECAUSE
YOU CHANGED--
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
>> QUIT IT.
>> NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S HOW THAT WORKED.
>> IT IS HOW IT WORKED.
>> NO.
LIKE, WE'RE NOT GONNA BRING UP
THE PAST AND TALK ABOUT IT,
ELABORATE ON IT FOR A LONG TIME,
BUT YOU GOT TO OWN UP TO WHAT
YOU DID WRONG.
>> YOU DID--YOU BE WRONG TOO,
BUT I DON'T BRING UP OLD STUFF.
>> YOU CAN IF YOU'D LIKE 'CAUSE
I'LL OWN UP TO MY WRONGS BUT
YOU CAN'T, AND THAT'S THE THING.
NO, YOU JUST CAN'T OWN UP AND BE
A MAN AND SAY WHEN YOU'RE WRONG,
LIKE...
>> TO ME, I'M DEFINITELY ALL OF
A MAN AND JUST BECAUSE YOU FEEL
LIKE SOMEBODY WAS WRONG ABOUT
SOMETHING, DON'T MEAN...
>> OKAY, I'M DONE WITH THIS
CONVERSATION.
I'M SORRY. I'M LEAVING.
I'M NOT DOING THIS.
>> WHY YOU LEAVING NOW?
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE GETTING ON MY
[bleep] NERVES.
>> female announcer: DON'T GO
AWAY, THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND
PREGNANT CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> I'M REALLY, LIKE, NOT EVEN
FEELING IT NO MORE.
LIKE, I'M IRRITATED AS HELL,
LIKE...
>> I MEAN, WE BOTH GET
IRRITATED OBVIOUSLY, BUT...
>> I GET MORE IRRITATED.
LIKE, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
>> I MEAN, I'M REALLY NOT EVEN
TRYING TO, YOU KNOW, DO THE
WHOLE ARGUMENT--
>> NOBODY EVER IS TRYING TO
ARGUE, BUT...
>> RIGHT, THAT WHY I'M TRYING TO
BE COOL.
YOU NEED TO BE COOL TOO.
>> OKAY.
>> EXACTLY, WHICH IS WHY WE NEED
TO CHANGE BECAUSE I KNOW HOW
YOU ARE.
>> YOU NEED TO DO SOME CHANGING
TOO.
>> NO.
>> I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE.
I APOLOGIZE FOR NOT BEING THE
SUPPORT SYSTEM THAT YOU WANTED
ME TO BE.
>> I APPRECIATE YOUR APOLOGY.
>> SO HOW ABOUT YOU GET GOING
AND GET SOME REST AND TRY AGAIN
TOMORROW, COME BY, SPEND TIME
WITH YOU AND AIDEN?
>> YEAH, I GUESS THAT'S COOL.
I MEAN, WE COULD TRY THAT.
>> WELL, I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> OKAY, DON'T, LIKE, NOT
COME BY.
>> * REACHING OUT
* BUT THE PAST CAN'T SAVE YOU *
* WONDER WHAT
* ALL THE EMPTY SOULS DO
>> WHEN I FIRST GOT PREGNANT,
I THOUGHT THAT ME AND MAURICE
WERE GOING TO BE IN A FAIRY
TALE; WE WERE GOING TO STAY
TOGETHER AND ALL THIS CRAP,
AND THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN,
BUT I'M JUST TRYING TO START TO
MOVE ON TO THE FUTURE.
[gentle rock music]
*
>> * DON'T GIVE UP *
* JUST HOLDIN' ON *
>> HELLO.
MAURICE DIDN'T HAVE TO GIVE UP
AS MUCH AS ME BECAUSE HE HAD A
SENIOR YEAR; HE GOT TO GO OUT
AND PARTY WITH HIS FRIENDS,
BETWEEN THAT NINE MONTHS,
I DIDN'T GET TO.
I WOULD HAVE HAVE WAITED YEARS
FROM NOW TO HAVE AIDEN BECAUSE
BEING A TEEN MOM, IT'S NOT WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO.
LIKE, I WOULDN'T RECOMMEND THIS
TO ANYBODY.
IT'S JUST NOT FUN.
[baby fussing]
*
I'M MOST GRATEFUL FOR MY
GRANDMOTHER BECAUSE SHE DOES THE
MOST.
I HAVE A LOT OF HELP, WHICH IS
WHY I CAN'T IMAGINE PEOPLE WHO
DON'T HAVE HELP BECAUSE EVEN
WITH HELP IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
OH, HE NEEDED TO BURP.
I LOVE MY BABY.
OKAY, MAMA?
THE NUMBER ONE THING IN MY LIFE
IS MAKING SURE THAT I CAN GIVE
AIDEN WHAT HE DESERVES.
I PLAN ON STARTING COLLEGE IN
AUGUST.
*
>> SUP, MAN?
>> HEY.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
MAURICE WASN'T THERE FOR ME WHEN
I NEEDED HIM THE MOST, BUT I'VE
GOTTEN TO THE POINT WHERE I'M
GONNA--YOU KNOW, I'VE GOT TO LET
IT GO.
>> GO GET SOME SLEEP, MAN.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE FUTURE
HAS IN STORE FOR ME AND MAURICE,
BUT AS LONG AS AIDEN CAN HAVE
BOTH PARENTS, I'M OKAY WITH
THAT.
>> * WHO KNOWS WHERE THOSE
* STEPPING STONES GO
*
>> announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT...
>> WHEN YOU'RE MESSED UP,
I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE AROUND
YOU.
>> PILLS CAN TAKE YOU DOWN A
ROAD YOU DON'T WANT TO GO.
>> DANG IT, MAMA.
>> KISS ME.
>> STOP, I'M TRYING TO DRIVE.
>> THEY NEED TO DO A SURGICAL
ASSESSMENT OF HIS BELLY.
HE WAS BREATHING TOO FAST.
[siren wailing]
>> [crying]