Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> HOW MANY MASCARAS
ARE YOU USING?
MY NAME'S JAMIE.
I'M 17 YEARS OLD AND
FROM ASHEVILLE, NORTH CAROLINA
IN THE HEART
OF THE BLUE RIDGE MOUNTAINS.
>> YOU WANT A LOT
OF CREAM CHEESE OR WHAT?
>> A LOT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IT'S 7:00.
>> MY DAD LEFT WHEN I WAS
A BABY, SO MY MOM RAISED ME AND
MY BIG SISTER ALL BY HERSELF.
AND SHE'S EXCITED FOR ME
TO GRADUATE.
>> I'M ENTITLED TO HAVE A LIFE.
I'VE RAISED YOU GUYS.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO HAVE A LIFE.
>> I'M HALFWAY THROUGH
MY SENIOR YEAR.
AND NEXT FALL,
I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE
AND STUDY RADIATION THERAPY.
I'M A REALLY GOOD STUDENT.
I GET STRAIGHT "A"s,
AND I'M ON THE STUDENT COUNCIL.
WRITE ME DOWN FOR FUNDRAISING.
SO EVERYONE WAS KIND OF SHOCKED
WHEN I STARTED DATING RYAN.
HE'S A LITTLE
ROUGH AROUND THE EDGES.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER
FOR ABOUT A YEAR.
BUT BECAUSE WE'RE SO DIFFERENT,
IT HASN'T ALL BEEN
SMOOTH SAILING.
RYAN IS KNOWN AS A BIG PARTIER
AND A TERRIBLE DRIVER.
AFTER GETTING A BUNCH OF
SPEEDING TICKETS AND A D.U.I.,
HE LOST HIS LICENSE.
NOW, INSTEAD OF CRUISING AROUND
IN HIS CAR,
WE HAVE TO RIDE THE SCHOOL BUS
AND BUM RIDES FROM MY MOM.
>> RYAN, I'M TAKING YOU HOME AND
I'M GOING TO DONNY'S AFTERWARDS.
MY MOM SPENDS A LOT OF TIME AT
HER BOYFRIEND DONNY'S HOUSE.
SO THINGS CAN GET PRETTY QUIET
AROUND HERE SOMETIMES.
BUT IT'S NOT GONNA STAY THAT WAY
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
GETTING PREGNANT WAS A BIG SHOCK
FOR ME AND RYAN.
BUT I'M GLAD
HE'S STANDING BY ME.
WE FOUND OUT WE'RE HAVING A
GIRL, AND WE'RE NAMING HER MIAH.
THAT MADE THE WHOLE THING
VERY REAL.
BUT IT ALSO MADE US FOCUS ON
WHY WE GOT TOGETHER
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WHAT DID YOU THINK
WHEN YOU FIRST MET ME?
>> YOU WERE KIND OF OUTGOING
AND NOT LIKE THE QUIET, SHY TYPE
I GUESS, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> AND WE JUST CLICKED AFTER THE
FIRST TIME WE HUNG OUT, SO
IF I WASN'T TALKING, YOU WERE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND IF YOU WEREN'T TALKING,
I WAS.
>> AT THE TIME, WE BALANCED
EACH OTHER OUT, AND WE JUST
HAD SO MUCH FUN TOGETHER.
WHEN YOU HAD YOUR CAR, WE WERE
RIDING AROUND ALL THE TIME AND
LIKE, FINALLY, I WAS JUST LIKE,
"YEAH, WE'LL DATE."
AND THAT WAS
A ROCKY RELATIONSHIP.
BUT IT'S GOTTEN SO MUCH BETTER.
LIKE, WE'VE GROWN TO,
LIKE, TWO PARENTS.
>> YEAH.
A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITY.
>> CAN YOU HANDLE IT, RYAN?
>> YOU NEVER CAN BE PREPARED
FOR IT, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
I KNOW.
MY FRIENDS THOUGHT
IT WAS SCANDALOUS ENOUGH
THAT I WAS DATING RYAN,
SO FINDING OUT I WAS PREGNANT
REALLY BLEW THEM AWAY.
>> JAMIE IS PREGNANT?
[laughs]
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO REACT.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WERE ALWAYS, LIKE,
THE BRAINS OF ALL OF US.
LIKE, YOU WOULD ALWAYS BE LIKE,
"WAIT."
>> "Y'ALL CAN'T DO THIS."
>> "WE GOT TO MAKE A PLAN."
[all laugh]
>> I WAS THE PLANNER.
I HAD--WE HAD TO HAVE A PLAN
BEFORE WE DID ANYTHING.
>> HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> MY BODY WAS ACTING FUNNY.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
I WAS JUST KIND OF LIKE, "OKAY,
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER,
THIS COULD BE TEENAGE BULL CRAP
OR IT COULD BE THAT."
AND I TOOK TWO PREGNANCY TESTS.
THEY BOTH CAME OUT POSITIVE.
>> WAS YOU, LIKE,
USING A CONDOM, BIRTH CONTROL?
>> WELL...
[laughter]
WE DIDN'T USE EITHER.
>> LESSON LEARNED.
>> LESSON DEFINITELY LEARNED,
YOU GUYS.
DON'T MAKE THE SAME MISTAKE.
>> SO ARE YOU SCARED
TO ACTUALLY HAVE THE BABY, LIKE,
IN THE HOSPITAL AND...
>> IT'S SO NERVE-RACKING.
IT'S SO SCARY.
AND I'M JUST--
>> I CAN IMAGINE.
SO LIKE, RYAN, YOU THINK HE'S
GONNA STEP UP AND DO EVERYTHING
HE NEEDS TO DO?
ARE YOU WORRIED THAT HE MIGHT
SLIP UP SOMETIMES OR...
AND IT'S GONNA JUST
GET PUT ALL ON YOU?
>> I'M SCARED OF THAT.
>> YEAH?
>> HE DOESN'T
FULLY UNDERSTAND IT.
LIKE, FROM THE DAY
THAT I FOUND OUT, YOU GUYS SAW
THE BIGGEST CHANGE IN ME.
AND THEN YOU SAW HIM STILL...
>> WE'RE GONNA SEE A DRASTIC
CHANGE WHEN SHE'S BORN.
>> WHEN HE SEES--
>> I REALLY HOPE SO, LIKE--
>> A MOTHER BECOMES MOTHER
WHEN SHE GETS PREGNANT.
A FATHER BECOMES A FATHER
WHEN HE SEES HIS BABY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S SCARY TO THINK ABOUT
THE FUTURE.
>> YEAH.
>> I USED TO HAVE EVERY DETAIL
OF MY FUTURE PLANNED OUT,
BUT NOW I'M NOT SO SURE
WHAT'S AHEAD OF ME.
AND THAT'S PRETTY SCARY.
BUT NOTHING COMPARES
TO THE DAY I HAD TO TELL MY MOM
I WAS HAVING A BABY.
SHE'S STILL PRETTY UPSET
ABOUT IT, BUT IS BEING
AS SUPPORTIVE AS SHE CAN.
>> YOU GOT YOUR DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT TOMORROW, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> YOU KNOW HOW
YOU'RE GETTING THERE?
>> POSSIBLY MY LOVELY,
AWESOME MOTHER?
>> HA-HA.
>> YOUR LOVELY, AWESOME MOTHER
HAS TO WORK.
>> SO WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
WHEN, LIKE, WHEN I FIRST TOLD
YOU, LIKE, WHEN I WALKED OUT
AND WAS JUST LIKE,
"I NEED TO TALK TO YOU"?
>> I WASN'T EXPECTING YOU TO
TELL ME YOU WERE PREGNANT.
SO I WAS PISSED.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I CRIED A BUNCH.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> AND I PRETTY MUCH DECIDED
THAT YOU WERE...
>> NOT HAVING IT.
>> YEAH, PRETTY MUCH.
>> BUT I TOLD YOU RIGHT THEN AND
THERE I WAS GONNA HAVE THE BABY.
>> AND YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
I COULD TALK YOU OUT OF THAT.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE IN FOR.
YOU REALLY DON'T.
TRY STAYING UP ALL NIGHT WITH
A BABY AND THEN GOING TO CLASS
AND STAYING UP ALL NIGHT
WITH A SICK CHILD
AND GETTING READY FOR TESTS
AND WORKING IN BETWEEN.
>> I KNOW.
>> NO.
BUT YOU WILL.
>> I THINK I CAN HANDLE
THE STRESS BETTER THAN RYAN.
YOU KNOW HE DOESN'T HANDLE
STRESS VERY WELL.
>> HE'S A 17-YEAR-OLD KID
TRYING TO BE A GROWN-UP.
AND HE DOESN'T QUITE
KNOW HOW TO PULL OFF...
>> THE GROWN-UP PART.
>> RIGHT.
AND YOU'VE GOT TO BE PREPARED
TO DO IT ALONE.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS GROWING UP
WITHOUT A DAD.
>> YEAH.
MY MOM HAS HAD HER SHARE OF
RELATIONSHIP DRAMA IN HER LIFE,
AND SHE'S NEVER BEEN
A BIG FAN OF RYAN.
SO SHE DOESN'T HAVE MUCH FAITH
IN HIM.
I HAVE TO BELIEVE IN HIM.
BUT THE TRUTH IS, HE'S GONNA
HAVE TO CHANGE HIS PARTYING WAYS
AND GROW UP FAST.
>> LIKE, I WANT TO MOVE OUT
AND--IF YOU WASN'T PREGNANT,
I COULD JUST MOVE OUT, YOU KNOW,
NO PROBLEM.
>> YOU COULD LIVE WITH A FRIEND,
YEAH.
YEAH, BUT I DON'T EXACTLY
WANT YOU TO BE LIVING
WITH YOUR FRIENDS 'CAUSE...
IF YOU STOPPED HANGING OUT WITH
PEOPLE WHO DO THINGS LIKE THAT,
THEN YOU PROBABLY WOULD STOP.
>> I'VE STOPPED HANGING OUT WITH
EVERYONE FOR A LONG TIME,
BUT I'VE STILL ALWAYS SOMEHOW
MANAGED TO DO SOMETHING
THAT I SHOULDN'T BE DOING.
>> WE HAVE SO MUCH
TO WORRY ABOUT WITH MIAH.
WE CAN'T--WE HAVE TO THINK
ABOUT HOW WE'RE GONNA
PROVIDE FOR HER.
IT'S NOT US ANYMORE, IT'S HER.
I HAVE FAITH
THAT YOU'LL BE A GOOD DAD.
I REALLY DO.
BUT YOU KNOW, YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO
HAVE THOSE THOUGHTS.
>> REGARDLESS, I CAN PROMISE
THAT I'M GONNA BE THERE FOR HER,
BE IN HER LIFE.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M DEFINITELY
GONNA BE THERE.
>> I REALLY WANT TO
BELIEVE IN RYAN
AND HOPE HE TRADES IN
HIS BAD HABITS
FOR A CHANGE AT FATHERHOOD.
>> I GOT COURT TOMORROW, SO--
>> IS YOUR LAWYER GONNA BE
THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN WE FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, RYAN SAID HE WOULD
TAKE ME TO ALL OF MY DOCTOR
APPOINTMENTS.
BUT SINCE HE LOST HIS LICENSE,
HE CAN'T TAKE ME ANYWHERE.
>> I THOUGHT RYAN
WAS GONNA BE ABLE--
>> TO COME?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, I DID TOO, BUT LAST
NIGHT HE SAID HE HAD TO GO TO
HIS LAWYER TODAY SO--
>> HE SHOULD PROBABLY TRY TO
MAKE ALL OF HIS APPOINTMENTS
NOT ON WEDNESDAY.
>> OKAY.
I HATE DEPENDING ON YOU,
AND RYAN DOES TOO, SO--
>> WELL, IF HE DOESN'T GET A
LICENSE BACK, YOU HAVE A WHOLE
YEAR TO DEPEND ON ME.
>> [sighs]
>> HAVE A SEAT ON THE TABLE.
AND MOM, IF YOU'LL HAVE A SEAT
ON THE CHAIR.
>> HOW Y'ALL DOING TODAY?
>> GOOD.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> SUPER.
>> SEE THAT ONE.
>> YOU'RE MEASURING RIGHT AT 37.
>> SO I'M NOT SMALL ANYMORE?
>> MM-MM.
>> [grunts]
THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE NOW IN THE FULL-TERM
ZONE.
YOU KNOW, MOST PEOPLE HAVE THEIR
BABY SOMEWHERE BETWEEN 39
AND 41 WEEKS, SO I WOULD IMAGINE
SOMETIME OVER THE NEXT
FEW WEEKS.
>> THAT SHE'LL BE HERE.
>> LABOR WILL START.
WHAT ARE YOU THE MOST
WORRIED ABOUT AT THIS POINT?
>> UH,
STRETCH MARKS.
>> STRETCH MARKS.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW TO GET RID OF THOSE?
>> THEY'RE JUST GONNA BE
A PART OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU KNOW, PART OF
YOUR LIFE STORY TO HAVE
A FEW STRETCH MARKS.
>> YAY.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU BACK IN A WEEK
UNLESS YOU GO INTO LABOR.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THIS IS THE THIRD STRAIGHT
DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT
RYAN HAS MISSED.
I KNOW HE NEEDS TO DEAL WITH
HIS LEGAL ISSUES,
BUT I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME
HIS PRIORITIES CHANGE.
>> I MEAN, I ALWAYS WANT TO GO
TO YOUR DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENTS,
AND YOU KNOW I ALWAYS DO UNLESS
I HAVE TO GO TO COURT OR--
>> I KNOW.
LIKE, I TRY TO EXPLAIN THAT
TO MOM, LIKE THOSE TIMES
THAT YOU HAVEN'T BEEN--
>> WAS SHE UPSET ABOUT THAT,
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T CAME
A COUPLE TIMES?
>> IT'S NOT THAT SHE'S UPSET.
SHE'S JUST AFRAID THAT IT'S THE
BEGINNING OF SOMETHING WORSE.
>> I MEAN, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> AND I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
SHE HAS TO THINK ABOUT IT
LIKE THAT 'CAUSE SHE--
BUT LIKE, LATELY, I THINK, LIKE,
THE STRESS HAS BEEN GETTING TO
ME, AND IT'S BEEN A LOT.
>> AND IT'S, LIKE, EVEN HARDER
FOR ME TO DEAL WITH JUST BECAUSE
ALL THIS OTHER STUFF I GOT
GOING ON ON TOP OF EVERYTHING
WE HAVE TOGETHER.
I JUST LOVE YOU, AND I DON'T
WANT TO SEE YOU GET HURT
ANY MORE THAN
YOU'VE ALREADY BEEN HURT.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, FOR EXAMPLE,
THE SUBJECT OF YOUR DAD.
I MEAN,
I KNOW HOW BAD IT HURTS YOU.
>> RYAN IS RIGHT.
MY RELATIONSHIP WITH MY DAD
HAS BEEN REALLY HARD ON ME.
HE HAS A NEW FAMILY NOW,
AND IT SEEMS LIKE
I'M NEVER ON HIS MIND.
HE DIDN'T CALL ME ON MY BIRTHDAY
AND HASN'T WANTED TO SEE ME
SINCE I GOT PREGNANT.
>> WHAT'D YOUR DAD SAY?
>> HE SAW IT ON MYSPACE.
HE SAW THE, LIKE, BABY STUFF
THAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT.
>> HE FOUND OUT BY MYSPACE?
>> BUT LISTEN, OKAY?
HE TEXTED ME, AND HE WAS LIKE,
"SO WHAT IS THIS STUFF
ABOUT A BABY?"
HE SAID, "PLEASE, PLEASE,
NO BABY."
THOSE ARE HIS EXACT WORDS.
HE'S REALLY ANGRY.
>> SO HE'S DISAPPOINTED IN YOU.
>> HE HAS NO REASON TO BE,
THOUGH.
HE WAS NEVER IN MY LIFE.
HE NEVER TOOK CARE OF ME.
>> BUT I MEAN, ONCE HE SEES THAT
YOU CAN BE PREGNANT AND BE 16
AND GO TO SCHOOL AT THE SAME
TIME AND MAKE SOMETHING OUT OF
YOUR LIFE, HE'S GONNA WANT TO
BE PART OF THAT,
PERIOD.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S GONNA
MATTER TO HIM.
IT'S NEVER MATTERED TO HIM.
I WISH I COULD JUST WRITE OFF
MY DAD ENTIRELY,
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE THE MORE
I TRY TO FORGET ABOUT HIM,
THE SADDER I GET.
I DON'T WANT MIAH
SURROUNDED BY FAMILY DRAMA,
SO I DECIDED TO REACH OUT
TO MY DAD ONE MORE TIME.
SO HOW DOES THE PARK
OFF OF AMBOY ROAD SOUND?
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT FOR SOME REASON, MY DAD
ACTUALLY AGREED TO MEET ME.
>> COME HOME WITH ME TODAY.
>> I CAN'T.
>> YOU KNOW YOUR DAD'S
NOT GONNA SHOW UP.
>> HE MIGHT.
I CAN'T BAIL ON MY DAD
IF HE'S ACTUALLY GONNA SHOW UP.
>> HE DOES IT TO YOU.
ALL THE TIME.
>> OKAY.
I AM NERVOUS,
'CAUSE HE HASN'T MET YOU YET.
I THINK I'M ALWAYS NERVOUS
WHEN I SEE MY DAD.
>> LOOK AT YOU.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> NOT MUCH.
OH, MY BIG BABY.
>> HEY, NAOMI,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> HI, I'M JOHN.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, MAN.
>> HEY, DUSTIN.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> THIS YOUR LITTLE BROTHER?
>> YES, THIS IS RYAN, DUSTIN.
>> SO YOU GUYS PRETTY PREPARED
FOR THIS BIG STEP?
>> WELL, AS PREPARED
AS WE CAN BE.
WE'RE PRETTY YOUNG, SO--
>> YEAH.
WELL.
>> RYAN, WOULD YOU AND DUSTIN
LIKE TO GO DOWN
AND WALK TO THE CREEK?
>> YEAH, MAYBE GIVE JAMIE AND
HER DAD HAVE SOME TIME TO TALK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> MY BABY'S HAVING A BABY.
>> THAT'S WHAT MOM SAYS.
>> DON'T EXACTLY KNOW HOW I
FEEL ABOUT IT, BUT I'M NOT--
>> YOU DIDN'T TEXT ME BACK
WHEN I TOLD YOU I WAS PREGNANT.
YOU WERE JUST LIKE, "SERIOUSLY?"
AND THEN DIDN'T TEXT ME BACK.
>> I NEEDED TIME TO SWALLOW
EVERYTHING AND UNDERSTAND AND--
>> I GUESS THAT'S WHY YOU
COULDN'T CALL ME ON MY BIRTHDAY.
>> [sighs]
I DID TALK TO YOU
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY.
YOU TEXTED ME, DIDN'T YOU?
I THOUGHT WE TALKED.
I'M SORRY I MISSED THAT.
>> I KNOW, LIKE,
WE DON'T REALLY SEE EACH OTHER.
DO YOU WANT TO CHANGE THAT
A LITTLE MORE
AND LIKE, SPEND TIME
WITH YOUR GRANDDAUGHTER?
>> SURE.
YEAH, OF COURSE, I DO.
AND I'M THERE.
YOU CAN CALL ME.
I WANT TO GO DO SOMETHING.
MY PHONE'S--
MY PHONE LINE'S OPEN.
>> WELL, I MEAN,
THE PHONE WORKS BOTH WAYS TOO.
>> YEAH.
>> SO--
>> WELL, I'LL HAVE TO MAKE A
POINT OF IT TO BE MORE INVOLVED.
>> THAT WOULD BE NICE.
>> YOU KNOW.
>> DO YOU WANT TO COME
TO THE HOSPITAL?
>> OF COURSE I'LL BE THERE.
OF COURSE I'LL BE THERE.
>> I WONDER
IF SHE'LL HAVE OUR NOSES.
>> OH, NO.
THE CURSE.
[both laugh]
THE CURSE, YEAH.
>> I REALLY WANT MY DAD
BACK IN MY LIFE.
AND IT MAKES ME REALIZE
HOW MUCH I WANT MIAH TO HAVE ONE
IN HER LIFE TOO.
>> HAVE I EVER
DONE YOUR MASCARA?
DO YOU TRUST ME
TO DO YOUR MASCARA?
>> I TRIED TO PUT
A PAIR OF MY PANTS ON.
MY BUTT IS TOO BIG FOR THEM.
I'M AFRAID IF I SIT,
THEY'LL RIP.
>> [laughs]
>> BUT YOU'RE GONNA BE
SMALL AGAIN.
>> I HOPE SO.
MIAH'S DUE IN JUST A FEW WEEKS,
AND I WON'T BE ABLE TO HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS AS MUCH
ONCE SHE'S HERE, SO I'M DYING
TO GET OUT OF THE HOUSE
WHILE I STILL CAN.
Y'ALL SEE ANY CARAMEL APPLES?
>> WHY DO YOU NEED
A CARAMEL APPLE?
>> BECAUSE I HAVE BEEN CRAVING
THEM FOR MONTHS ON END.
>> YOU SHOULD PROBABLY BUY
MORE THAN ONE.
>> YEAH, PROBABLY.
>> WE'RE GONNA GO
RIDE THIS REAL FAST.
>> NOT THAT.
>> IT LOOKS PRETTY FUN.
>> LEIGH-ANN, GO BUY TICKETS.
>> THEY WON'T LET YOU ON THAT
RIDE, WILL THEY?
>> OH, NO, Y'ALL CAN RIDE.
I'LL WAIT.
>> WELL, WE'LL THINK ABOUT YOU
WHILE WE'RE UP THERE HAVING FUN.
[all screaming]
>> I WANT TO GO SO BAD.
THAT'D BE SO MUCH FUN.
YAY!
DO YOU WANT TO
SPLIT A FUNNEL CAKE?
>> OKAY, FUNNEL CAKE
SOUNDS GOOD.
>> LET'S SPLIT A FUNNEL CAKE.
>> THIS FUNNEL CAKE IS SO GOOD.
>> IT REALLY IS.
>> I HAVEN'T HAD ONE IN FOREVER.
HAS RYAN HELPED WITH
THE BABY SHOWER AND STUFF?
>> OH, YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT HE'S DOING
RIGHT NOW.
>> OH, THAT'S GOOD.
>> I'M EXCITED.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, IT'S KIND OF
LIKE A SURPRISE PARTY THAT I
KNOW ABOUT, SO I'M JUST LIKE,
OKAY, I'M READY.
WHEN IS IT?
>> WHEN DO YOU GET TO SEE IT?
>> THE DAY OF THE SHOWER.
>> REALLY?
>> YES.
>> LIKE, WHEN SHE ARRIVES.
>> OH, WOW.
>> I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO MY BABY SHOWER.
RYAN'S STEPMOM VOLUNTEERED TO
HOST IT AT THEIR HOUSE, SO I
HAVE NO IDEA WHAT TO EXPECT.
>> EVERYBODY RELAX, ENJOY.
WE'RE GONNA BE DOING
A BABY SHOWER FOR JAMIE.
HOW BIG IS HER BELLY?
>> I'M GONNA GUESS OR--
>> YOU HAVE TO GUESS, YEAH.
>> ARE WE GONNA HAVE
ENOUGH RIBBON?
>> OH, WOW.
[laughter]
DID SHE MOVE AGAIN?
OH, YEAH.
>> OH!
[indistinct chatter]
>> MY BABY SHOWER IS PERFECT.
RYAN SEEMED REALLY HAPPY
AND SO RELAXED AROUND KIDS.
I'M STARTING TO BELIEVE
HIS PROMISE TO QUIT PARTYING
AND STAY OUT OF TROUBLE
WHICH IS GREAT, BECAUSE
THE ONLY OTHER GUY IN MY LIFE
IS A NO-SHOW.
>> SO YOUR DAD DIDN'T COME.
>> YEAH.
>> WE DIDN'T REALLY
THINK HE WOULD.
>> STEPHANIE SAID SHE SAW HIM
LAST WEEK AT THE FAIR.
THEY COULDN'T HAVE
EVEN INVITED ME?
>> YEAH.
THEY COULD HAVE.
>> COULD HAVE, SHOULD HAVE,
WOULD HAVE.
>> BUT...
>> I'M BUMMED MY DAD
DIDN'T SHOW.
BUT EVERYONE WAS REALLY
GENEROUS, AND I THINK WE'LL HAVE
MOST OF WHAT WE'LL NEED
WHEN MIAH COMES.
AND I THINK WE HAVE DAYCARE
FIGURED OUT TOO.
MY HIGH SCHOOL IS REALLY
SUPPORTIVE OF PREGNANT TEENS.
THEY HAVE A DAYCARE
RIGHT ON CAMPUS.
SO WHEN I'M READY
TO COME BACK TO SCHOOL,
MIAH CAN COME WITH ME.
>> SO AS SOON AS YOU GET BACK
AFTER YOU'VE HAD THE BABY,
WE'LL REQUEST FOR A CAR SEAT
TO BE ON BOTH BUSES
TO TAKE YOU FROM HOME TO HERE
AND FROM HERE
BACK TO THE DAYCARE.
>> OKAY.
I DON'T LOVE THE IDEA OF PUTTING
MIAH ON A SCHOOL BUS, BUT
WE CAN'T PASS UP FREE DAYCARE.
AND WITHOUT A PLACE OF OUR OWN,
WE HAVE TO COME UP WITH A PLAN
FOR RYAN TO STAY AT MY HOUSE.
>> HEY, MAMA.
>> HEY, BABY.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
BUT RYAN AND MY MOM
DON'T REALLY GET ALONG.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GUYS THINKING
AS FAR AS...
>> HIM BEING--
>> HIM BEING HERE
AFTER THE BABY'S BORN?
YOU KNOW, WE--
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT IT.
AND--
>> WHAT ABOUT THE FIRST MONTH
OR A FEW WEEKS THAT HE STAYS
AND HELPS TAKE CARE OF THE BABY?
>> OBVIOUSLY, Y'ALL ARE NOT
GONNA BE SLEEPING IN THE SAME
ROOM UPSTAIRS IN YOUR BEDROOM.
>> MOM.
>> NO, LET ME FINISH.
I THINK HE SHOULD BE HERE
FOR THE RESPONSIBILITY PART
IN THAT BABY ROOM.
>> I DON'T LIKE IT, BUT--
>> YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
BUT THAT IS THE WAY IT IS.
RYAN, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> I'LL TAKE HER WITH ME
SOMETIMES AND JAMIE COULD COME
OVER TO MY HOUSE DURING THE DAY.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE MIAH?
>> I'M DEFINITELY
GONNA TAKE MIAH.
THERE'S NO SAY IN THAT
RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S--
>> MM, YOU THINK?
>> NO, I KNOW.
>> YOU THINK.
>> I KNOW.
>> I GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
SEE HOW IT GOES.
>> WE'LL HAVE TO, I GUESS.
>> YES, WE WILL.
>> RYAN AND MY MOM ARE TWO OF
THE MOST STUBBORN PEOPLE I KNOW.
AND NOW, I'M STUCK
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF THEM.
>> EVER SINCE THE TALK
WITH MY MOM, RYAN HAS BEEN
KIND OF DISTANT.
HE MISSED
ANOTHER DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
AND SOME NIGHTS, I CAN'T
GET A HOLD OF HIM AT ALL.
>> HEY, THIS IS RYAN.
JUST LEAVE A SHORT MESSAGE.
>> HE SWEARS HE'S NOT OUT
PARTYING, AND HE BETTER NOT BE,
BECAUSE IT FEELS LIKE MIAH'S
ON HER WAY...
TONIGHT.
MOM!
I THINK IT'S TIME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GET READY.
>> I'M READY TO GO.
I'M JUST WAITING FOR RYAN
TO ANSWER HIS FREAKING PHONE.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO REACH RYAN
FOR THE LAST HOUR,
BUT HE'S NOT PICKING UP.
HERE, CARLY, WILL YOU CALL HIM?
>> YEAH.
COME ON, RYAN.
>> HEY, CHASTITY, IT'S JAMIE.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO CALL RYAN,
BUT HE'S NOT ANSWERING.
I'M GONNA KEEP CALLING HIM.
BUT WILL YOU PLEASE TRY
AND GET HIM TO CALL ME, PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
BYE.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO PEE
AND [bleep] AT THE SAME TIME.
>> OH, GROSS.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS
MOMENT FOR NINE MONTHS,
AND NOW THAT IT'S HERE,
RYAN IS TOTALLY M.I.A.
MY CONTRACTIONS ARE KILLING ME.
EVERYONE IS TRYING THEIR BEST
TO MAKE ME COMFORTABLE,
BUT THE FACT THAT
RYAN STILL HASN'T CALLED
JUST MAKES ME MORE MISERABLE.
>> SO JAMIE, WHO ALL'S GONNA BE
IN THE ROOM WITH YOU
WHEN YOU DELIVER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> RYAN, IF WE CAN
GET A HOLD OF HIM.
>> LUCKILY, I'M DILATED ENOUGH
TO GET AN EPIDURAL
TO HELP NUMB THE PAIN.
BUT IT'S TAKING A WHILE
TO KICK IN.
FIVE HOURS INTO LABOR,
RYAN FINALLY SHOWS UP
LOOKING LIKE HELL
AND WITH A PATHETIC EXCUSE.
YOU SMELL LIKE YOU HAD FUN.
>> WHY IS THAT?
>> I DON'T THINK I NEED TO SAY
THAT RIGHT NOW.
I'M SO PISSED
THAT RYAN WAS OUT PARTYING.
BUT THERE'S NO TIME TO ARGUE NOW
BECAUSE I'M READY TO START
PUSHING.
>> NEXT TIME YOU HAVE A
CONTRACTION, WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO
IS, WE'RE GONNA HAVE TWO PEOPLE
HELPING HOLD YOUR LEGS.
NOW PUSH DOWN.
>> AND PUSH LIKE
YOU'RE TRYING TO POOP.
GO, GO, GO.
>> PERFECT.
FOUR,
FIVE,
SIX,
SEVEN,
EIGHT,
NINE,
AND TEN.
GOOD.
>> both: ONE LAST TIME, OKAY?
>> KEEP BREATHING.
>> AND GO.
ONE,
>> YOU CAN DO THIS.
>> TWO,
THREE,
FOUR,
FIVE,
SIX,
SEVEN,
EIGHT,
NINE
TEN. GOOD.
DEEP BREATH.
>> [sighs]
>> JUST RELAX.
>> YOU DID GREAT.
>> IS IT NORMAL
TO FEEL NAUSEOUS?
>> both: YES.
[retches]
>> OH, I'M SORRY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
[retches]
>> IF THE HEART RATE DIPS TOO
MUCH, WE'LL HAVE TO MAYBE
INTERVENE AND HELP YOU HAVE
YOUR BABY FASTER USING SOMETHING
CALLED FORCEPS.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD OF FORCEPS?
>> THEY'RE THE, LIKE,
PLIER THINGS, RIGHT?
>> THEY'RE METAL,
AND THEY GO KIND OF BESIDE
THE BABY AND THEY HELP SORT OF
GUIDE THE BABY OUT.
[indistinct chatter]
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT ALL THIS?
>> UM, KIND OF--I DON'T--
I'M NOT SURE.
OKAY.
OH, MAN.
>> MOVE YOUR GOWN UP
SO I CAN GET TO YOUR BELLY.
>> HEY, JAMIE,
THOSE ARE VERY NORMAL.
IT'S OKAY.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT,
SO YOU HAVE A CONTRACTION.
OKAY, TAKE A DEEP BREATH,
PULL YOUR LEGS BACK,
AND PUSH, PUSH, BREATHE.
FOUR,
FIVE,
SIX,
SEVEN,
EIGHT,
NINE,
TEN.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH AND PUSH
ANOTHER TIME FOR A BODY.
>> AND LOOK AT MOMMY.
>> OH, LOOK!
>> PUSH A LITTLE BIT.
>> PUSH, BABY, PUSH.
>> THERE WE GO.
[baby wails]
[all cooing]
>> THERE'S YOUR BABY.
[baby wailing]
[laughter]
LOOK AT YOUR BABY MIAH.
>> [laughs feebly]
SHE'S SO CUTE.
AFTER MIAH WAS BORN,
I TOLD RYAN TO GO HOME.
HE WANTED TO STAY AT
THE HOSPITAL, BUT AFTER
NOT SHOWING UP FOR ME
BECAUSE HE WAS OUT PARTYING,
I CAN'T BELIEVE A WORD HE SAYS.
WAS THAT A POOPIE
OR WAS THAT A FART?
WE'LL HAVE TO FIND OUT.
OH, SHE'S CRYING.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S A POOP.
YEAH.
[baby wailing]
MIAH IS A NICE DISTRACTION
FROM ALL THE DRAMA WITH RYAN.
AND I HAVE SOME VISITORS TOO,
ONE OF WHICH IS A HUGE SURPRISE.
HEY, DAD.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> NOT MUCH.
GOT YOU SOME FLOWERS.
>> OH, THEY'RE PRETTY.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
I'M GOOD.
>> I'M GLAD YOU'RE FEELING GOOD.
SHE'S A CUTIE.
>> YOU WANT TO HOLD HER?
>> SURE.
OH, COME TO GRAMPY.
GRAMPY.
>> GRAMPY.
IF YOU WANT TO BE GRAMPY.
>> OH, YOU WANT TO CRY ON ME?
>> [laughs]
>> OH, WONDERFUL.
>> EVEN THOUGH HE SKIPPED MY
BABY SHOWER, I'M HAPPY MY DAD
CAME TO SEE ME IN THE HOSPITAL.
HOPEFULLY HE'LL BE AROUND MORE
NOW THAT MIAH'S HERE.
IT'S TIME TO TAKE MIAH HOME.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT RYAN WOULD BE
COMING HOME WITH US, BUT I GUESS
I'D BETTER GET USED TO
DOING THINGS ON MY OWN.
>> I'M READY TO BE HOME,
AREN'T YOU?
>> ME TOO.
>> YEAH.
>> LET ME CHECK
THE LAST TIME I FED YOU.
6:00.
OKAY, YEAH, I NEED TO FEED HER.
DOING A GOOD JOB.
IT'S MY SECOND DAY HOME FROM THE
HOSPITAL, AND RYAN HASN'T CALLED
'CAUSE HE KNOWS I'M PISSED.
BUT HE STILL SHOWED UP WITH A
CHANGE OF CLOTHES EXPECTING TO
SLEEP IN THE BABY'S ROOM.
I'M WILLING TO SUCK IT UP FOR
MIAH'S SAKE, BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S BEEN PARTYING NONSTOP,
AND I CAN BARELY
STAND THE SIGHT OF HIM.
I'M GONNA TELL YOU,
MOM'S NOT TOO THRILLED
ABOUT YOU BEING HERE.
>> I MEAN, IF I COULD BREASTFEED
HER, I'D JUST TAKE HER HOME
AND HAVE MY TIME ALONE WITH HER.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA TAKE HER,
RYAN.
>> I'M NOT GONNA
TAKE MY DAUGHTER?
SHE CAN'T STAY WITH ME?
>> NOT RIGHT NOW.
>> WITH MY FAMILY?
>> WOW.
>> I KIND OF HAVE TO FEED HER.
IF YOU'LL HAND ME THAT BOPPY.
>> YOU'RE NOT JUST HURTING ME
BY KEEPING HER FROM COMING
AND STAYING WITH ME.
>> I'M TRYING TO WORK IT OUT,
OKAY, JUST LET ME
DO THE BEST I CAN, OKAY?
>> THAT'S MY DAUGHTER.
YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU CAN NEVER ALLOW ME BACK IN
YOUR HOUSE, BUT I JUST DON'T SEE
WHAT ELSE--
>> I CANNOT GUARANTEE YOU
SOMETHING RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU CAN'T GUARANTEE ME
THAT I GET TO SEE MY DAUGHTER?
>> YOU PUT YOURSELF
IN THIS POSITION.
IF YOU HADN'T HAVE DONE...
>> OKAY, JAMIE--
>> EVERYTHING YOU'VE DONE IN
THE PAST NINE FREAKING MONTHS,
THEN MAYBE MAYBE WE WOULD BE
TOGETHER AND MAYBE YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THAT,
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU DID.
YOU MADE YOUR BED;
NOW YOU HAVE TO LIE IN IT.
>> YO, I'LL TRY TO BE A GOOD
FATHER AND BE HERE FOR MY CHILD.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT
WHEN I CAN'T BE HERE AND
I CAN'T TAKE HER HOME WITH ME?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
IT'S ALL I ASK FOR.
I JUST WANT TO BE ABLE
TO BE WITH MY CHILD.
I DON'T HAVE TO BE HERE
TO DO THAT.
>> I'M NOT TAKING HER
AWAY FROM YOU.
YOU'RE JUST
JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS.
>> CAN I HOLD HER FOR A WHILE?
THEN I'LL LEAVE.
PLEASE.
[both sniffling]
>> SO WHAT DID I JUST WALK INTO?
>> I JUST--
I WAS JUST WONDERING
WHEN AND IF
[sobbing]
I WOULD BE ABLE TO
HAVE MY DAUGHTER AT MY HOUSE
WITH ME.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHEN THAT'S GONNA BE BECAUSE
RIGHT NOW SHE'S A NEWBORN.
AND RIGHT NOW, SHE HAS TO BE FED
BY HER MOTHER, PERIOD.
>> I KNOW,
BUT YOU CAN ALWAYS PUMP
AND GIVE ENOUGH TO ME
TO FEED HER.
>> HEY, RYAN.
RYAN.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S ABOUT MIAH.
AND YOUR DAUGHTER IS RIGHT WHERE
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE RIGHT WITH
HER MOTHER.
>> BUT IT'S HARD, SO YOU JUST
HAVE TO GO WITH IT.
>> IT'S HARD
BECAUSE YOU DAMN HURT HER.
>> THIS--
>> SHUT UP.
YOU SHUT UP A MINUTE.
>> [sighs]
>> WE HAD A PLAN.
EVERYTHING WAS FINE, WASN'T IT?
AND YOU TOTALLY FRIGGIN'
BLEW THAT.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU EVEN MADE IT
TO THE DAMN BIRTH.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
OLD ENOUGH TO DRINK,
AND YOU SHOW UP HUNG OVER.
AND RIGHT NOW, I'M REALLY
PISSED OFF AT YOU BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT RESPONSIBLE.
BUT WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT A DIFFERENT WAY
THAN WHAT WE HAD PLANNED.
>> ALL I EVER WANTED FOR MIAH
IS WHAT I NEVER HAD:
TWO PARENTS IN HER LIFE.
BUT IT'S OBVIOUS THAT RYAN
HASN'T CHANGED A BIT,
AND I JUST CAN'T TRUST HIM
TO BE ALONE WITH MIAH.
>> SINCE RYAN'S BREAKDOWN OVER
MIAH, HE'S CONTINUED TO ASK
ABOUT TAKING HER TO HIS HOUSE,
AND I'VE CONTINUED TO SAY NO.
I'VE GOT TOO MUCH ON MY MIND TO
THINK ABOUT SENDING HER AWAY
WITH HIM.
IS THIS FOUR WEEKS' WORTH?
>> YEAH.
>> IS THAT--
>> OH, MY GOSH.
YEAH.
I'LL BE OUT OF SCHOOL FOR A
WHILE, BUT I CAN'T AFFORD TO
FALL BEHIND, SO MY TEACHERS
SENT ME THE ASSIGNMENTS
FOR THE NEXT MONTH.
I'M GLAD I GOT A BIGGER BINDER.
[baby wailing]
HELLO.
SO FAR, THERE HASN'T BEEN MUCH
TIME FOR SCHOOLWORK.
IT'S OKAY.
[baby wailing]
OOH!
LOOKING AFTER MIAH TAKES UP
EVERY MINUTE OF MY DAY,
AND RYAN NEVER COMES OVER
TO HELP.
HE JUST CALLS FOR ONE THING.
HELLO.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> TAKING CARE OF MIAH.
WITH ME WITH YOU.
RYAN.
SHE'S TOO YOUNG
TO BE AWAY FROM ME, ONE.
TWO, I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH MILK.
HAVE A GOOD DAY, RYAN.
BYE.
I WISH RYAN WOULD JUST
COME OVER AND SPEND TIME
WITH HIS DAUGHTER.
BUT HE SAYS MY MOM
MAKES HIM UNCOMFORTABLE.
AND HE'D RATHER SEE MIAH
AT HIS HOUSE.
>> IS RYAN STILL BUGGING YOU
ABOUT WHEN HE'S GONNA GET TO
KEEP HER OVERNIGHT?
>> YEAH.
BUT RYAN IS THE FATHER.
HE STILL HAS PARENTAL RIGHTS.
YOU NEED TO THINK ABOUT THAT.
>> HIS NAME IS NOT EVEN
ON THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE
AT THIS POINT.
SO RIGHT NOW, HE DOESN'T--
LEGALLY, HE HAS ZILCHO RIGHTS.
IT WOULD TOTALLY BE A LOT
DIFFERENT, JAMIE,
IF HE HADN'T SPUN ME
ALL THAT [bleep] HE WAS--
HE LOVED YOU AND HE LOVED MIAH
AND HE WAS GONNA BE THERE.
AND ALONG BEHIND THE SCENES,
HE'S BEEN DOING
GOD ONLY KNOWS WHAT.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> HE HURT MY DAUGHTER.
>> ME.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I'M TAKING IT A LOT
BETTER THAN YOU.
>> I KNOW, BUT I'M A MOM,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN SOMEONE HURTS YOUR
DAUGHTER, YOU'RE GONNA KNOW
EXACTLY HOW I FEEL.
>> I JUST WANT TO FORGET THOUGH.
>> I KNOW YOU DO.
AND YOU CAN'T.
>> I GET WHERE MY MOM
IS COMING FROM, BUT NO MATTER
HOW I FEEL ABOUT RYAN,
I STILL WANT HIM IN MIAH'S LIFE.
HE LEFT ME A MESSAGE SAYING
HE JUST GOT HIS LICENSE BACK,
AND HE WANTS ME AND MIAH
TO COME TO A HALLOWEEN PARTY
AT HIS PARENTS' HOUSE.
MY MOM DOESN'T THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA,
BUT I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD GO.
HI.
>> WHAT TIME DO YOU WANT ME TO
COME PICK YOU UP?
>> I'LL BE DOWN THERE
IN A SECOND.
YOU CAN TAKE HER OUT.
>> DO NOT GET IN THE CAR WITH
ANYBODY THAT'S BEEN DRINKING.
>> I KNOW.
LOVE YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU TOO.
>> SO WHAT'S UP?
>> NOTHING.
I'M HAVING AN AWESOME DAY.
>> NOW THAT YOU'RE
STUCK IN THE CAR WITH ME,
OBVIOUSLY, YOU DON'T CARE--
>> I LOVE HOW YOU WANT TO FIGHT
WITH ME.
>> NO, YOU'RE STUCK.
>> NO, BUT I CAN GOING TO HOME.
I CAN GET TO YOUR HOUSE
AND LEAVE.
>> I'M NOT TRYING,
BUT MIAH'S COMING WITH ME.
>> SO THEN DON'T FIGHT WITH ME.
NO.
>> I'M NOT FIGHTING
RIGHT NOW THOUGH.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU--
>> YOUR NAME ISN'T EVEN ON THE
BIRTH CERTIFICATE, SO IF YOU
WANT TO TRY AND TAKE HER,
I CAN GET YOU FOR KIDNAPPING.
SO DON'T EVEN TRY THAT.
>> OKAY, YOU'D BE A BITCH
FOR DOING THAT.
I COULD SEE YOUR MOM DOING THAT
IF YOUR MOM WAS YOU.
SO HOPE YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BE LIKE YOUR MOM.
>> YOU KNOW I DON'T WANT TO
BE LIKE THAT, AND YEAH,
IT COULD GET UGLY.
HELLO.
>> HI, GORGEOUS.
AWW.
MIAH.
>> SAY HELLO.
RYAN'S ATTITUDE IN THE CAR MADE
ME REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE,
AND HIM INSISTING HE TAKE MIAH
ON HIS OWN IS REALLY
GETTING ON MY NERVES.
>> ARE YOU GONNA LET ME
HAVE HER TOMORROW?
>> SHE'S TOO YOUNG, RYAN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
WHEN IS SHE GONNA BE OLD ENOUGH?
>> I DON'T KNOW, RYAN.
>> WHETHER MAMA LIKES IT OR NOT,
IT'S GONNA BE SOON.
>> DON'T WANT TO HEAR THIS.
I DO NOT WANT TO
FIGHT WITH YOU TODAY.
>> LET ME SEE MY DAUGHTER,
THERE WOULDN'T BE NO FIGHTING.
WILL YOU HOLD HER?
I'M GONNA GO TALK TO HER
FOR A SECOND AND APOLOGIZE.
BUT YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
WHY I'M GETTING SO AGITATED
ABOUT IT.
I JUST WANT TIME
WITH MY DAUGHTER.
>> AND YOU WILL GET TIME
WITH HER.
YOU HAVE SO MANY YEARS LEFT.
>> YEAH, BUT I JUST
WANT HER NOW.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TRYING TO
KEEP YOU AWAY FROM HER.
>> I JUST WANT TO KNOW WHEN.
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT COMING OVER NOW.
I'M NOT GONNA ALWAYS WANT TO GO
OVER THERE, AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA
ALWAYS WANT TO COME OVER HERE.
SO IT WOULD JUST BE EASIER
ON EVERYONE IF SHE JUST
WENT WITH ME.
>> WELL, MY SISTER'S
ABOUT TO COME GET ME.
IT'S OKAY.
MY MOM IS RIGHT.
BEING AROUND RYAN
IS JUST TOO STRESSFUL.
I DON'T WANT TO KEEP RYAN
AWAY FROM HIS DAUGHTER,
BUT THAT MIGHT BE WHAT'S BEST
FOR RIGHT NOW.
>> YAY.
THE UGLY BACKPACK.
I HAVEN'T SEEN RYAN
SINCE THE HALLOWEEN PARTY.
BUT TOMORROW IS MY FIRST DAY
BACK TO SCHOOL,
AND I'M NOT LOOKING FORWARD
TO RUNNING INTO HIM.
PLUS, MY HOMEWORK ISN'T
ORGANIZED, AND I'M WORRIED ABOUT
HAVING ENOUGH TIME IN
THE MORNING TO GET MIAH READY
FOR DAYCARE.
TWO PACKS OF WIPES.
>> SO WHAT TIME ARE YOU
GETTING UP IN THE MORNING
TO GET READY FOR SCHOOL?
>> 5:00.
[chuckles]
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE TIRED.
[alarm blaring]
>> WE'RE GOING TO SCHOOL.
>> WELL, IT OUGHT TO BE
INTERESTING TO SEE
HOW YOUR FIRST DAY GOES.
>> YEAH.
SO HOW DOES THIS WORK?
>> THAT GOES AROUND HER
SHOULDERS RIGHT HERE, OKAY?
OKAY, PUT HER LITTLE LEGS--
THAT'S IT.
NOW, YOU CAN CINCH IT UP,
'CAUSE THAT NEEDS TO FIT HER
KIND OF TIGHT.
>> YEAH.
I HAVE NEVER CARRIED
THIS MUCH STUFF TO SCHOOL, EVER.
HELLO.
>> HI, BABY.
>> UM, WELL, I GUESS
I GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE,
SO SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> JUST GETTING TO SCHOOL FELT
LIKE A FULL DAY'S WORK.
BUT AFTER BEING OUT FOR A MONTH,
I KNOW THE HARD PART
IS JUST BEGINNING.
>> I'M GONNA GIVE YOU
WHAT THEY WORKED ON ON FRIDAY.
>> OKAY.
YOU'RE PROBABLY GONNA HAVE TO
HELP ME WITH IT.
>> YEAH, WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO
IS, YOU'RE JUST GONNA
PLOT THE POINTS
AND FIND THE SLOPE
AND THE DISTANCE FORMULA.
>> I'M STILL ON TRACK TO
GRADUATE THIS SPRING, BUT I'M
USED TO MAKING STRAIGHT "A"s,
AND KEEPING MY GRADES UP
WHILE TAKING CARE OF MIAH
WILL BE TOUGH.
>> WHICH MAJOR POPULATION SHIFT
IN THE LATE 1800s OCCURRED AS
A RESULT OF INDUSTRIALIZATION?
>> [stammers]
NO.
>> I HAVEN'T READ FAR ENOUGH
TO THIS ONE, SO--
>> OKAY.
[beeping]
>> RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
MY HISTORY EXAM, I GOT A TEXT
THAT MIAH WAS HUNGRY.
HI.
HOW ARE WE DOING?
LET'S GET SOME FOOD
IN YOUR SYSTEM.
WE GOT TO MAKE IT TO 3:00.
MY FIRST DAY BACK HAS BEEN
PRETTY STRESSFUL,
AND I KNOW SEEING RYAN
WILL MAKE IT WORSE.
LUCKILY, I'VE BEEN ABLE
TO AVOID HIM.
>> WHAT'S IT LIKE BEING BACK?
>> CHAOTIC.
IT THREW ME OFF GUARD WHEN
THEY WERE LIKE, "IT'S TIME FOR--
MIAH NEEDS TO EAT."
I WAS LIKE, "WHAT?"
'CAUSE I'M NOT USED TO THAT,
YOU KNOW?
I'M JUST KIND OF LIKE--
BEING BACK IN SCHOOL FEELS
REALLY AWKWARD, AND EVERYBODY'S
GIVING ME THIS WEIRD VIBE
AND LOOKING AT ME
LIKE THEY KNOW SOMETHING.
AND IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG
TO FIND OUT WHY.
AFTER LUNCH, MY FRIEND SYBIL
TOLD ME THAT RYAN
ALREADY HAS A NEW GIRLFRIEND
AND THAT HE'S BEEN SEEING HER
FOR MONTHS.
AND I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT'S WHO HE WAS WITH
THE NIGHT I WENT INTO LABOR.
AND TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE,
EVERYONE IN SCHOOL KNEW
EXCEPT ME.
I FEEL--
WHO CHEATS ON
THEIR PREGNANT GIRLFRIEND?
>> A DOUCHE BAG.
RYAN.
>> I'VE TRIED, YOU KNOW,
TO WORK WITH HIM,
TO YOU KNOW, FOR HER TO SEE HIM.
AND THE FACT THAT HE'S JUST
LIED TO ME THIS WHOLE TIME,
I'M JUST LIKE, I'M DONE.
I'M NOT GONNA DEAL WITH HIM.
I'M NOT GONNA WORK WITH HIM
ANYMORE,
BECAUSE ALL IT'S DONE
IS HURT ME.
>> IT'S JUST MEAN.
>> IT MEANS LAWYER, COURT...
UM,
I GET FULL CUSTODY.
RYAN'S NOT GONNA SEE HER
BECAUSE I JUST--
I NEED TIME.
>> FINDING OUT THAT RYAN
CHEATED ON ME WAS A SHOCK.
HE STILL THINKS HE SHOULD GET TO
SEE MIAH, SO I NEED TO TELL HIM
THAT I KNOW THE TRUTH
AND THAT I'VE DECIDED
TO HAVE CUSTODY
SETTLED IN COURT.
>> SO WHERE'S MIAH?
>> AT HOME.
>> WE REALLY DO NEED TO FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT.
I KNOW YOU'VE GOT RESENTMENT
TOWARDS ME AND--
>> YOU CHEATED ON ME.
>> I CHEATED ON YOU?
>> YES.
I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA
JUST DENY IT.
I KNOW.
I MEAN,
YOU HAVEN'T REALLY GIVEN ME
MUCH TO BELIEVE ANYMORE LATELY.
SO--
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE USING MIAH
TO GET BACK AT ME OR SOMETHING--
YOU'RE USING MIAH
AS A TOOL TO HURT ME AND--
>> IT'S NOT EVEN ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW.
>> AT THE SAME TIME--
>> LISTEN, RYAN.
YOU AND I AREN'T GONNA WORK
ANYTHING OUT.
ALL WE'RE GONNA DO IS FIGHT,
AND I JUST--I DON'T WANT TO
DO THAT ANYMORE.
I FEEL LIKE GOING TO THE COURT,
GETTING SOMETHING THAT WE--
EITHER BOTH OF US CAN AGREE ON
OR THE COURT DECIDES
IS BEST FOR HER.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S EXACTLY
BEST FOR MIAH JUST TO COMPLETELY
KEEP HER FROM ME UNTIL THEN.
LIKE, I DON'T EVEN FEEL LIKE
SHE'S GONNA KNOW ME WHEN I DO
WHEN ALL THIS COURT STUFF GETS
SETTLED 'CAUSE IT'S GONNA BE--
YOU KNOW, IT COULD BE MONTHS.
>> I MEAN, REALLY, THE BOTTOM
LINE IS, LIKE,
WE HAVE TO GO TO COURT,
AND THAT'S THAT.
>> * IT'S RUMORED *
* YOU'RE COMING APART *
>> I THOUGHT EVERYTHING WOULD
TURN OUT WAY DIFFERENT THAN IT
REALLY DID.
I THOUGHT ME AND RYAN
WOULD STAY TOGETHER.
BUT WE DIDN'T, SO--
HE HAD ALWAYS TOLD ME, "OH,
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY.
I'M GONNA TAKE CARE OF YOU.
WE'RE GONNA BE TOGETHER."
AND I BELIEVED IT.
FINDING OUT THAT HE HAD BEEN
CHEATING ON ME
AND HAD BEEN WITH OTHER GIRLS,
THAT REALLY DID SUCK.
>> WHAT CAN WE
HELP YOU OUT WITH?
>> I NEED TO CHANGE
MY PHONE NUMBER TODAY.
I HOPE THAT RYAN AND I
WILL BE CIVIL WITH EACH OTHER
AT SOME POINT,
I THINK IT'LL PROBABLY BE
AFTER COURT AND AFTER EVERYTHING
IS SETTLED BECAUSE RIGHT NOW,
EVERYTHING IS UP IN THE AIR.
>> I'M ASSUMING WE'RE HERE TO
TALK ABOUT MIAH.
>> YES.
>> MIAH.
WHAT IS YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE BIOLOGICAL FATHER
AT THIS POINT?
>> WE AREN'T EVEN SPEAKING
AT THIS POINT.
I HAVE A LOT OF STRONG HATRED
TOWARDS HIM RIGHT NOW,
AND I WANT THE BEST FOR HER,
NOT FOR ME.
>> IT'S PROBABLY GONNA GET
KIND OF A LITTLE UGLY.
>> ME AND HIM PROBABLY--
CANNOT BE AROUND EACH OTHER.
>> MY BIRTHDAY.
>> YOUR BIRTHDAY?
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
I WANT TO GO.
I HAVE A BABY.
A YEAR AGO,
I WOULD BE OUT WITH FRIENDS.
AND NOW,
PARTYING IS KIND OF OUT FOR ME
'CAUSE I DON'T REALLY LIKE TO
LEAVE HER 'CAUSE SHE'S MY
RESPONSIBILITY AND MY DAUGHTER.
I SEE A BIG SMILE.
I WANT TO BE THE BEST MOM I CAN
TO MIAH.
SHE DESERVES THE BEST.
AS FAR AS THE FUTURE GOES,
I KNOW WHERE
I WANT TO BE IN LIFE,
AND I KNOW WHERE I'M GOING TO BE
IN LIFE.
WHETHER RYAN'S IN MY LIFE,
HER LIFE,
I'M NOT--
I'M GONNA DO THE BEST I CAN
FOR ME AND MIAH.
>> female announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT.
>> IT'S KIND OF CRAZY WE'RE
GONNA HAVE A BABY
BEFORE OUR ONE YEAR ANNIVERSARY.
>> EVERY TIME I TALK
TO MY MOM ABOUT IT,
SHE'S, LIKE, GONNA CRY.
>> MY 16-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER
IS PREGNANT.
THIS ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT YOU WANTED.
OH, MY GOD.
>> I WOULD PROBABLY FEEL MOST
COMFORTABLE WITH YOU
JUST HAVING YOUR BABY.
[baby wailing]
>> LOOK AT YOUR SON.
>> HE'S FINE.
HE'S PERFECT.
WHAT DO WE NEED?
HOW LONG IS THE DIAPERS
AND WIPES GONNA LAST US?
>> SHUT UP.
>> YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME.