>> MY NAME IS DANIELLE.
I'M TIRED OF DOING THAT.
MY ARM HURTS.
I'M 16 YEARS OLD, AND I LIVE
WITH MY MOM, STEPDAD,
TWO SISTERS, AND BROTHER
IN THE SUBURBS OF COLUMBUS,
OHIO.
AS A KID, SCHOOL WAS REALLY
IMPORTANT TO ME, BECAUSE I
WANTED TO GROW UP TO BE
A LAWYER.
BUT THAT ALL CHANGED IN MY
FRESHMAN YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL.
I STARTED HANGING OUT WITH
A PARTY CROWD, AND THINGS GOT
PRETTY WILD.
I SKIPPED SCHOOL.
I FAILED CLASSES.
I WAS OUT ALL THE TIME,
AND MY MOM AND I FOUGHT
CONSTANTLY.
MY GRANDMA THOUGHT SHE COULD
STRAIGHTEN ME OUT...
>> I THINK IT'S TIME DANIELLE
CAME AND LIVED WITH ME.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> SO SHE TOOK ME TO LIVE WITH
HER 45 MINUTES AWAY.
THAT'S WHERE I MET MY BOYFRIEND,
JAMIE.
BYE, I LOVE YOU.
>> BYE.
>> WE HAD AN INSTANT CONNECTION
WHEN WE MET.
HE HAS A JOB WORKING AT
A FAST-FOOD PLACE.
LUCKILY, IT'S NEAR HIS HOUSE,
BECAUSE HE LOST HIS LICENSE,
AND WE BOTH HAVE TO RELY
ON OUR PARENTS TO GET AROUND.
NOW MY MOM IS MAKING ME MOVE
BACK IN WITH HER.
AND SHE REGRETS EVER LETTING ME
MOVE TO MY GRANDMA'S,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
EVEN THOUGH MY MOM MADE ME MOVE
BACK IN WITH HER, I STILL SPEND
AS MUCH TIME AS I CAN HANGING
OUT AT JAMIE'S HOUSE.
>> MORNING.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> MAKING YOU BREAKFAST.
>> OH, DO YOU REALIZE THAT
YOU COOK EVERYTHING FOR ME?
THAT I NEVER COOK ANYTHING?
I WISH I COULD COOK.
I NEVER REALLY HAD TO LEARN.
>> I MEAN, YOU GOT TO LEARN
A LOT.
IT'S, LIKE...
>> I KNOW I HAVE A LOT TO LEARN.
BUT I NEVER REALLY THOUGHT
I WOULD HAVE TO LEARN IT
THAT QUICK.
BECAUSE WE DON'T WANT TO LIVE
WITH OUR PARENTS ONCE THE BABY
COMES, WE'RE PLANNING ON GETTING
OUR OWN PLACE SOON.
I'M DUE IN TWO MONTHS.
WE'RE HAVING A BOY, AND WE'VE
ALREADY DECIDED ON A NAME.
CAN YOU BELIEVE YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE A BABY NAMED AFTER YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> JAMIE JUNIOR.
>> CRAZY. JUNIOR.
>> LIKE, YOU'RE GONNA BE CALLED
"DAD."
LIKE, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
A LITTLE KID RUNNING AROUND
CALLING YOU "DAD."
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> I KNOW.
EVERY TIME I TALK TO MY MOM
ABOUT IT, SHE, LIKE, WANNA CRY.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE WE WEREN'T EVEN
TOGETHER FOR A YEAR BEFORE
WE HAD A BABY.
>> THAT'S KIND OF CRAZY.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A BABY
BEFORE OUR ONE-YEAR ANNIVERSARY.
>> I KNOW.
WHEN I MET YOU, I THINK YOUR
ATTITUDE, LIKE, ATTRACTED ME
TO YOU.
>> WHAT KIND OF ATTITUDE
DID I HAVE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU HAD THAT KIND OF,
"I DON'T CARE" ATTITUDE.
>> I'M GOOD ENOUGH FOR MYSELF.
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH. FOR SURE.
YOU HAD THE SAME ATTITUDE,
THOUGH.
YOU UNDERSTOOD, LIKE,
WHAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT,
AND I COULD HAVE AN ACTUAL
CONVERSATION WITH YOU
WITHOUT YOU SAYING SOMETHING
THAT HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH WHAT WE WAS TALKING ABOUT.
>> WE HAD GOOD CONVO.
>> YEAH.
>> SINCE JAMIE LEFT HIGH SCHOOL
AND HAS NO PLANS TO RETURN
RIGHT AWAY, IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT TO BOTH OF US
THAT I GO ON TO GRADUATE.
SO I'M DOING HOMESCHOOL ONLINE,
BUT IT GETS PRETTY LONELY,
AND I REALLY MISS MY FRIENDS.
>> I WAS HAVING BIOLOGY
FLASHBACKS THE OTHER DAY.
LIKE, I MISS MS. SPENCER'S
CLASS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
SHE [bleep] HATED ME.
I FAILED AT THE BEGINNING.
[laughter]
I WAS IN WEEK ONE,
AND I WAS FAILING IT.
>> AFTER YOU HAVE THE BABY,
ARE YOU COMING BACK TO SCHOOL,
OR ARE YOU GONNA BE
HOMESCHOOLED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WANT TO GO BACK FOR MY
12TH-GRADE YEAR, THOUGH.
I DO KNOW THAT.
>> YEAH, YOUR SENIOR YEAR
IS NOT AS CRACKED UP AS IT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE.
>> THAT'S JUST YOU.
>> I BET IT WOULD BE FOR ME.
IF I HAVE A GOOD BODY,
I'M GONNA BE THE PAINTED PEOPLE
AT THE FOOTBALL GAME.
[laughter]
>> WHAT DO YOU, LIKE, MISS
ABOUT SCHOOL?
>> LIKE, EVERYTHING,
JUST BEING ABLE TO BE AROUND
MY FRIENDS ALL DAY, LIKE,
EVERY DAY, AND NOW I DON'T EVER
GET TO BE AROUND THEM.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I WOULD GO BACK IN A HEARTBEAT,
THOUGH.
I KNOW THAT.
>> SO WERE YOU TAKING
YOUR BIRTH CONTROL?
>> NO.
NO.
WE DIDN'T HAVE NO PROTECTION
OR NOTHING.
I WENT TO THE CLINIC TO GET
BIRTH CONTROL, TO ORDER MY
BIRTH CONTROL, AND THEY TELL
YOU--THEY MAKE YOU PEE IN A CUP
TO MAKE SURE YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT
BEFORE THEY GIVE YOU IT,
AND I PEED IN THE CUP
AND EVERYTHING.
THEY TOLD ME, "YOU'RE NOT
PREGNANT."
I ORDERED MY BIRTH CONTROL
AND THEN WENT BACK A WEEK LATER
TO PICK UP MY BIRTH CONTROL,
PEED IN A CUP AGAIN,
AND ENDED UP BEING PREGNANT.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
SO THAT TEST--WAIT, HOLD ON.
SO YOU TOOK A TEST BEFORE,
AND IT SAID YOU WEREN'T PREGNANT
WHILE YOU WERE PREGNANT.
>> YEAH, WELL, IT TAKE YOU--
IT TAKE A LITTLE BIT FOR
IT TO ACTUALLY SHOW THAT
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> YEAH.
WAS THAT WHEN YOU TOLD YOUR MOM?
>> YEAH, SHE CRIED.
YEAH, IT WAS AN EMOTIONAL
MOMENT.
MY MOM HAD ME WHEN SHE WAS 16,
AND IT WAS ROUGH ON HER.
SHE TOLD ME OVER AND OVER AGAIN
HOW TO AVOID GETTING PREGNANT,
BECAUSE THE LAST THING SHE
WANTED WAS FOR ME TO MAKE
THE SAME MISTAKE.
AND SHE'S STILL HAVING A HARD
TIME ACCEPTING THAT I'M HAVING
A BABY.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHY
I WAS SO STRICT?
>> YEAH.
>> NOW?
>> I MEAN, I'VE KNOWN--
I KNEW WHY YOU WERE,
BUT I DIDN'T CARE.
>> YOU KNOW HOW BAD IT BREAKS
MY HEART TO KNOW THAT I LET YOU
GO LIVE WITH GRANDMA
AND ALL THIS HAPPENED?
SERIOUSLY?
AND WHAT WERE MY WORDS
THE DAY THAT GRANDMA CALLED ME
AND SAID, "MAYBE SHE SHOULD
COME HERE AND STAY
AND TRY SCHOOL HERE"?
WHAT WERE MY WORDS?
"WHY?
SO SHE CAN END UP PREGNANT
LIKE I DID?"
BECAUSE I KNEW WHAT MY LIFE
WAS THERE.
THERE WAS NO PARENTAL
SUPERVISION, AND IT'S LIKE
I LET MY BABY GIRL
OUT OF MY HANDS.
AND NOW WHEN PEOPLE LOOK AT ME,
THEY THINK THAT I'M THIS
HORRIBLE PERSON, BECAUSE
I HAVE A 16-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER
WHO'S PREGNANT, WHICH I WORKED
SO HARD TO EMBED IT IN YOUR HEAD
THAT THIS ISN'T SOMETHING
THAT YOU WANTED.
>> BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> STAY AWAY FROM THE CARNIES.
>> IT'S HARD FOR MY MOM
TO ACCEPT MY PREGNANCY,
BUT SHE'S DOING THE BEST
SHE CAN.
HELLO!
AND NOW THAT I'M TAKING CLASSES
ONLINE, IT TAKES A LOT OF EFFORT
TO HANG OUT WITH MY FRIENDS...
>> OH, I MISSED YOU.
>> ESPECIALLY AT EIGHT-MONTHS
PREGNANT.
I WANT TO PLAY A GAME.
>> WELL, PLAY ONE.
>> DO YOU KNOW THAT I'M--
RIGHT WHEN I'M LEGAL TO DRINK,
HE'LL BE ALREADY IN
KINDERGARTEN?
>> THAT'S WEIRD.
>> CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
>> ACTUALLY, HE'LL BE IN
KINDERGARTEN BEFORE I CAN EVEN
DRINK.
>> WELL, WHEN YOU TURN 21,
WE'RE GETTING A BABYSITTER.
[laughter]
WE'RE GOING OUT, BECAUSE IT'S
SERIOUS.
I THINK IT'S WEIRD WE'RE NOT
GOING TO THE SAME SCHOOL
THIS YEAR.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE ALWAYS USED TO SKIP CLASS
TOGETHER.
>> [laughing] I KNOW.
WE DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
>> ALWAYS.
>> REMEMBER, WE WERE,
LIKE, THAT.
>> INSEPARABLE.
>> both: I KNOW.
>> HOPEFULLY, I CAN GET
CAUGHT UP.
LIKE, I'M REALLY BEHIND.
I DIDN'T GET, LIKE, ANY CREDIT,
NOT ONE.
>> YEAH, WHAT GRADE
ARE YOU GONNA BE IN?
>> LIKE, 10 1/2.
I'LL BE, LIKE, A 10 1/2 GRADER.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T DO,
LIKE, ANY SCHOOL.
LIKE, YOU WERE NEVER AT SCHOOL.
>> NO, I GOT IN TROUBLE
ALL THE TIME.
>> ALL THE TIME.
>> LIKE, ALL THE TIME.
CAN YOU BELIEVE I'M GONNA HAVE
A BABY?
>> I CAN'T EVEN, LIKE--
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO SAY.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S JUST WEIRD.
WERE YOU SHOCKED THAT I WAS
HAVING A BABY?
>> YES, BECAUSE--
>> DID YOU THINK THEN THAT
I WOULD BE READY FOR A BABY,
THOUGH?
>> NO.
>> YOU DIDN'T?
ME NEITHER.
>> I DIDN'T THINK THAT YOU WERE
READY THEN BECAUSE OF ALL THE
PARTYING THAT I REMEMBER
YOU DOING AND US DOING.
>> I'M, LIKE, DIFFERENT NOW.
>> THE ONLY REASON WHY IT REALLY
SHOCKED ME WAS BECAUSE IT WAS
JAMIE, YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE, LIKE, YOU GUYS WEREN'T
EVEN TOGETHER THAT LONG.
>> FOR NOT EVEN THAT LONG.
WE GOT TOGETHER IN OCTOBER.
I WAS PREGNANT BY JANUARY.
>> THAT'S CRAZY.
>> YEAH.
>> IT REALLY IS.
>> ME AND JAMIE WOULDN'T BE
TOGETHER, THOUGH, IF I DIDN'T
GET PREGNANT.
WE WOULD NOT HAVE BEEN.
I DIDN'T REALLY CARE ABOUT
OUR FUTURE, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
BUT AFTER I GOT PREGNANT,
IT, LIKE, CHANGED HOW I LOOKED
AT LIFE.
LIKE, NOW I, LIKE, NEED HIM.
WITH JAMIE'S SUPPORT,
IT'LL BE A LOT EASIER
TO KEEP UP IN SCHOOL.
AND AS DIFFICULT AS MY
SITUATION IS FOR MY MOM,
I'M GRATEFUL THAT SHE'S TRYING
TO BE THERE FOR ME TOO.
"PARTY IN MY CRIB.
YOU BRING THE BOTTLE."
[scoffs]
>> NO WAY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
IS THAT A DIAPER GENIE?
ZIP!
>> IT'S GONNA BE EXPENSIVE
TO DRESS THIS BABY.
THIS STUFF ISN'T CHEAP, IS IT?
>> MM-MM.
NOT AT ALL, ACTUALLY.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD JUST TURN
THE FRONT PART OF OUR HOUSE
INTO AN APARTMENT.
>> I DON'T WANT TO--
I DON'T WANT TO LIVE WITH
MY MOM, THOUGH.
I WANT TO BE OUT ON MY OWN,
BE OUT--MAKE IT A FAMILY THING.
HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK I WOULD,
LIKE, NEED FOR, LIKE, EVERYTHING
THAT I NEED TO GET?
>> PROBABLY $300 OR $400 A MONTH
JUST FOR THE BABY.
>> FOR THE BABY?
>> YEAH, FOR THE FIRST YEAR
OR SO, 'CAUSE, I MEAN,
LAUNDRY SOAP, ALL THE BATHING
SUPPLIES, BABY WIPES, DIAPERS,
BOTTLES.
>> AND IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
JAMIE GET PAID $300
FOR ONE PAYCHECK.
>> SO THAT'S, LIKE, $1,200
A MONTH.
IF YOU GUYS WANT TO GET
AN APARTMENT, THAT'S GONNA BE--
>> $1,200 A MONTH?
>> YEAH.
>> HE DON'T EVEN GET THAT.
>> YOU SAID HE GOT--
>> HE GET PAID $300 EVERY TWO.
>> OH, HE MAKES $600 A MONTH?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT?
>> HOW ARE YOU GUYS--
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO FINANCIALLY DO THIS.
>> YOU THOUGHT HE GOT $1,200
A MONTH?
>> WELL, I FIGURED A PAYCHECK
WAS PER WEEK.
>> HE GET PAID, LIKE,
MAYBE $350.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> IF HE, LIKE...
>> I DON'T KNOW, DANIELLE.
A LOT OF STUFF THAT I KEEP
FINDING OUT KIND OF, LIKE,
MAKES ME SICK.
>> MY MOM IS RIGHT.
THE BABY WILL BE HERE
IN TWO MONTHS.
IF WE'RE GOING TO DO THIS
ON OUR OWN, WE NEED TO MAKE
A PLAN.
I PRINTED OUT A SHEET,
AND I HAVE EVERYTHING
WE CAN WRITE DOWN TO, LIKE,
FIGURE OUT IF WE'RE EVEN GONNA
BE ABLE TO AFFORD EVERYTHING
THAT WE'RE GONNA NEED.
HOW MUCH DO YOU MAKE ON ONE
PAYCHECK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE, LIKE, $800 TO $900
A MONTH.
>> I'M PUTTING $800.
SO IF WE HAVE $800 A MONTH,
AND WE HAVE TO BUY...
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF STUFF.
LIKE, WE HAVE ENOUGH WIPES
TO LAST US FOR AT LEAST
TWO MONTHS.
AT LEAST THREE MONTHS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> WHAT ABOUT FOR FOOD?
HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK WOULD
GO TOWARD FOOD IN ONE MONTH?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> OKAY, WELL, HOW MUCH DO YOU
THINK YOU WOULD PUT TOWARD FOOD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU'RE, LIKE, ACTING
[bleep]...
>> YOU KEEP ASKING ME QUESTIONS
I HAVE NO CLUE ABOUT.
>> UM...
>> HOW LONG IS OUR DIAPERS
AND WIPES THAT WE GOT NOW
GONNA LAST US?
SINCE YOU KNOW EVERYTHING,
YOU SHOULD KNOW--
>> I DIDN'T TELL YOU
I KNOW EVERYTHING.
I'M TRYING TO FIND OUT
HOW MUCH WE NEED.
YOU KEEP TELLING ME,
"OH, WELL, WE ALREADY HAVE THAT.
WE DON'T NEED THAT FOR ANOTHER
MONTH AND A HALF."
HOW MUCH [bleep] DO WE NEED
FOR RIGHT NOW?
>> OKAY, WHEN THE BABY IS BORN,
WHAT DO WE NEED?
WE HAVE DIAPERS AND WIPES
FOR WHEN HE'S BORN, RIGHT?
>> UM...
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE
GONNA DO UNTIL WE GET INTO IT.
YOU'RE, LIKE, WAY TOO
HARDHEADED.
>> NO, YOU ARE.
>> YEAH.
I'M HARDHEADED BECAUSE I DON'T
KNOW WHAT WE NEED.
>> OKAY, I DON'T EITHER.
>> WHAT DO WE NEED?
HOW LONG IS THE DIAPERS
AND WIPES GONNA LAST US?
>> SHUT UP.
>> YOU'RE NOT TELLING ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S IN
THE PAPERS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S THERE.
DON'T CRY.
IT'S NOTHING TO CRY ABOUT.
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
I'M TRYING TO UNDERSTAND.
YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO WHAT
I'M SAYING.
HOW LONG IS THAT STUFF
GONNA LAST US?
AND THEN WE CAN TELL HOW MUCH
WE GOT TO SPEND A MONTH.
THAT'S ALL I'M TRYING TO SAY.
I'M NOT TRYING TO MAKE YOU SAD.
I'M NOT TRYING TO MAKE YOU
EMOTIONAL.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW WE'RE GOING
TO DO THIS OR GET OUR OWN PLACE
IF WE CAN'T EVEN GET ALONG.
>> FIGHTING WITH JAMIE ABOUT
WHAT WE NEED FOR THE BABY
MADE IT OBVIOUS THAT WE'RE NOT
QUITE READY TO BE COMPLETELY
ON OUR OWN, WHICH IS WHY
WE WANT TO SPEND THE FIRST
WEEK AT MY MOM'S HOUSE
GETTING USED TO TAKING CARE
OF THE BABY.
THEN WE'LL MOVE BACK TO HIS
DAD'S, SO WE CAN BE CLOSER
TO JAMIE'S JOB.
>> HI, GRAND-DAD.
>> HIS DAD IS COOL WITH IT.
BUT NOW WE HAVE TO SELL MY MOM
ON THE IDEA.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT, LIKE...
LIKE, THE DAY THAT WE COME HOME
WITH THE BABY, HOW DO YOU FEEL
IF, LIKE, WE'RE OVER HERE
FOR, LIKE, A WEEK AND A HALF,
AND THEN I GO HOME WITH HIM?
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD BE HERE
UNTIL YOU'RE 18.
>> I UNDERSTAND FULLY WHERE
YOU'RE COMING FROM.
I'M JUST SAYING, LIKE,
I GOT A JOB OUT THERE,
AND US NOT BEING AROUND
EACH OTHER, IT'S JUST MAKING
A REAL DISTANT FEELING.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND I MEAN, NO ONE WANTS
TO FEEL DISTANT FROM THE PERSON
THEY'RE ABOUT TO HAVE
A KID WITH.
I DON'T HAVE MY LICENSE,
SO IT'S NOT LIKE I COULD JUST
COME OUT HERE AND VISIT FOR
A COUPLE HOURS AND GO BACK HOME,
SO...
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK
THAT I'M NOT GONNA BE AROUND.
LIKE, I DON'T WANT YOU TO THINK
I'M NEVER GONNA BE UP HERE.
>> IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH YOU OVER THERE.
I FEEL LIKE I'M MAKING
BAD CHOICES AS A PARENT
BY LETTING YOU.
A MOTHER LETTING HER DAUGHTER
LIVE WITH HER BOYFRIEND
PRETTY MUCH WOULD MAKE ME
A PIECE OF [bleep] MOM.
>> NO.
>> AND THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
>> I'M SORRY--DAUGHTER.
>> WHY ARE YOU SORRY?
>> IT DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
>> I'M NOT TRYING TO BE
IN THE MIDDLE OR STEP ON
ANYBODY'S TOES OR MAKE ANYBODY
HURT, YOU KNOW?
I WANT EVERYBODY TO BE HAPPY
AND JUST TRY TO MAKE IT
WORK OUT.
THAT'S MY ONLY KID, AND...
[chuckles]
SO, YOU KNOW, I'M GONNA LOVE
THE HELL OUT OF THE BABY, SO...
>> WOULD YOU WANT TO LIVE
AWAY FROM YOUR BABY?
NO MATTER IF YOU WAS IN HIS
POSITION OR YOUR POSITION,
YOU WOULDN'T WANT TO BE
AWAY FROM HIM.
SO RIGHT NOW, IF SHE HAS TO STAY
UP HERE, AND YOU GUYS MAKE HER
STAY UP HERE, THERE'S NOTHING
REALLY I CAN DO.
BUT WHEN HE COMES, I MEAN,
WE'RE ALL GONNA BE FACED
WITH THIS SITUATION,
AND I'M REALLY NOT GONNA WANT
TO BE AWAY FROM MY SON.
WE'RE ALL KIND OF--WE'RE ALL
TUGGING FOR THE SAME THING,
AND ONLY SOME OF US CAN HAVE
WHAT WE WANT.
>> QUIT, MOM.
>> I'M TIRED OF LOSING.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I DON'T WANT TO HURT MY MOM,
BUT I REALLY DO THINK
OUR PLAN TO GO TO JAMIE'S
IS THE RIGHT THING.
I COULD HAVE THE BABY ANY DAY,
SO I'M STAYING AT MY MOM'S
BECAUSE SHE'S CLOSER
TO THE HOSPITAL.
AS MY DUE DATE COMES CLOSER,
I'VE BEEN CRAVING JUST ABOUT
EVERYTHING.
[chime dings]
>> WHAT'S YOUR WEIRDEST CRAVING?
>> CHALK.
>> CHALK?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY DO YOU WANT CHALK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHERE DID THAT EVEN COME
FROM?
>> LIKE, NAIL POLISH REMOVER.
>> EW!
THAT'S SO GROSS.
THAT STUFF WILL BURN YOUR TONGUE
OFF.
EW...
>> I'M GLAD TO GET A CHANCE
TO SEE SOME OF MY FRIENDS
BEFORE THE BABY ARRIVES.
>> YOU'RE GETTING SO BIG.
>> BUT TODAY'S BEEN PRETTY ROUGH
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN GETTING SOME
SHARP PAINS.
>> DO YOU HAVE COOKING SPRAY?
IF NOT, I CAN USE THIS.
>> I'M NOT SURE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO MAKE
ANYTHING.
>> OH, WELL, YOU'LL
HAVE TO LEARN.
YOU'LL BE PACKING LUNCHES.
CAN YOU MAKE PEANUT BUTTER
AND JELLY?
>> UM...
[laughter]
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> WELL, I KEEP HAVING, LIKE,
A WEIRD, LIKE, LIGHTNING BOLT,
LIKE, DOWN THERE.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
>> WELL, DOES IT HURT?
>> YEAH.
>> THEN I THINK YOU SHOULD CALL
THE DOCTOR, IF IT'S HURTING.
>> WHY DON'T YOU ASK YOUR MOM?
>> YEAH, I SHOULD DO THAT,
ACTUALLY.
HEY, MOM?
>> WHAT?
>> YOU KNOW THAT FEELING
THAT I KEPT TELLING YOU ABOUT,
LIKE, THE LIGHTNING BOLT
FEELING?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, I KEEP HAVING THAT.
SHOULD I CALL MY DOCTOR?
>> YES.
IT'S, LIKE, HARD AS A ROCK.
AND THAT'S A CONTRACTION.
YEAH, I THINK WE NEED TO GO
HAVE YOU CHECKED OUT,
LIKE, SERIOUSLY.
>> LIKE, FOR REAL?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU HAVE REACHED
THE AFTER-HOURS MESSAGE FOR
THE OBSTETRICS AND GYNECOLOGY.
FOR OBSTETRIC EMERGENCIES
IF YOU ARE MORE THAN 20-WEEKS
PREGNANT, PLEASE GO DIRECTLY
TO LABOR AND DELIVERY.
YOUR ON-CALL PHYSICIAN WILL BE
NOTIFIED OF YOUR STATUS.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> DID YOU SET THE TIMER
ON THIS?
>> YES...
>> CHECK YOUR--
>> IT LOOKS LIKE BROWNIES.
[laughs]
>> I TEXTED JAMIE, SO HE'S
RUSHING OVER TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> SO JAMIE'S FREAKED OUT?
>> YEAH.
AND I FEEL BAD THAT YOU'RE,
LIKE, HAVING TO TAKE ME.
>> WELL, I'M YOUR MOM, BABE.
THAT'S WHAT MOMS DO.
>> WHEN I GOT TO THE HOSPITAL,
THEY TOLD ME I WAS HAVING
LABOR PAINS.
>> AND IF YOU GO WITH ME,
I'LL TAKE YOU BACK TO A ROOM.
>> OKAY.
>> SURGICAL CLIPPERS.
[clippers buzzing]
>> WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
>> EW, THERE'S HAIR ON IT.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT--
>> THAT'S DISGUSTING.
[laughter]
>> SO EVERYTHING SO FAR
LOOKS GOOD.
I WOULD PROBABLY FEEL MOST
COMFORTABLE WITH YOU JUST
HAVING YOUR BABY.
>> LIKE, TONIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> WELL, WE CAN DO THAT.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW I FEEL YET.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW YET.
>> OH, MAN.
>> SO WHAT WE WOULD DO
IS START AN I.V.,
RUN MEDICINE THROUGH YOUR I.V.
CALLED PITOCIN TO GET YOU
TO START CONTRACTING
AND THEN BREAK YOUR WATER
FOR YOU.
>> UM...
>> YOU GOT TO DO IT.
>> SHOULD I?
YEAH.
I'M GOING TO.
>> TO INDUCE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN AFRAID
THE WHOLE TIME.
NOW I'M GETTING AFRAID.
[monitor pulsing]
>> WHENEVER YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU NEED SOMETHING FOR PAIN,
YOU JUST LET ME KNOW.
YOU CAN HAVE I.V. PAIN MEDICINE,
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, OBVIOUSLY,
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR EPIDURAL.
JUST LET ME KNOW WHENEVER
YOU NEED ANYTHING.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
[exhaling]
[gasping]
OH, MY GOD.
>> I KNOW.
>> [sobbing]
>> PUSH THE BUTTON.
>> MAY I HELP YOU?
>> UH, YEAH, SHE SAYS
SHE WANTS THE--THE MEDICINE.
>> OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> WHEN WE DO THE EPIDURAL,
YOU'LL BE THE ONLY ONE
ALLOWED BACK HERE.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M CARRIE.
I'M FROM ANESTHESIA.
YOU READY FOR YOUR EPIDURAL?
>> OKAY, WE'RE GONNA ROLL UP.
WE'RE GONNA SIT UP.
>> OH, GOD, OH, GOD.
>> YOU'LL GO TOWARDS THE HEAD
OF THE BED AND CROSS YOUR LEGS.
>> YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB,
SWEETIE.
>> [whimpers]
[monitors beeping,
alarms blaring]
AS SOON AS I GOT MY EPIDURAL,
ALARM BELLS WENT OFF,
AND SUDDENLY, MY ROOM FILLED
WITH NURSES AND DOCTORS.
THE DOCTORS SAID THEY NEEDED
TO DELIVER MY BABY IMMEDIATELY
BECAUSE HE HAD STOPPED
BREATHING.
OH, MY GOD!
[sobbing]
>> BECAUSE MY BABY HAD STOPPED
BREATHING, THE DOCTOR HAD
TO SUCTION HIM OUT
IN AN EMERGENCY PROCEDURE.
IT WAS REALLY SCARY,
BUT HE'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> [crying] OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT SCARED ME SO BAD.
LOOK AT YOUR SON.
>> IS HE OKAY, JAMIE?
>> YEAH, HE'S FINE.
HE'S PERFECT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HE'S HERE.
HE'S GOOD.
LOOK AT HIM.
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE ME.
>> HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU,
JAMIE.
>> OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S LIKE, "I'M READY, DUDE.
I'M HERE."
HE'S LIKE, "DUDE, I'M READY."
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HE'S, LIKE, PERFECT.
HE LOOKS IDENTICAL TO ME.
>> LOOK OVER HERE.
>> LOOK AT HIM. LOOK AT HIM.
>> DOES HE REALLY?
>> LOOK AT HIM.
[baby crying]
HE LOOKS EXACTLY LIKE ME.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> WE'RE GONNA TAKE HIM OVER
TO MAMA.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M SHAKING REALLY BAD.
AFTER ALL THE DRAMA OF
JAMIE JR.'S DELIVERY,
MY MOM NEEDED A BREAK,
AND JAMIE AND HIS DAD
WENT OUT TO GET A CAR SEAT.
>> AW...
>> SO I'M HAPPY THAT MY FRIENDS
COULD COME VISIT.
>> WAS IT, LIKE, A LONG PROCESS?
LIKE, YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE WILL
BE LIKE, "I WAS IN LABOR
FOR, LIKE, 20 HOURS."
>> NO, I WAS ONLY IN LABOR
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR AND A HALF.
BUT THEY, LIKE, RUSHED HIM AWAY.
LIKE, HE QUIT BREATHING.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW DID YOU REACT?
>> AFTER THEY TOLD ME THAT
HE QUIT BREATHING, THEY HAD
ALREADY HAD HIM BACK TO NORMAL.
>> OH.
>> THEY, LIKE, HID IT FROM ME.
WHICH I WOULD HAVE FREAKED OUT
IF THEY WOULD HAVE TOLD ME.
YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM?
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY, YOU GOT TO HOLD
THE HEAD.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GOT HIM?
OH!
AW...
I'M ABOUT TO CRY.
>> OH, DON'T CRY.
I KNOW.
AIN'T IT WEIRD?
>> ARE YOU STAYING WITH JAMIE
WHEN YOU GET OUT OF THE
HOSPITAL?
>> WE'RE GONNA GO OVER TO MY
MOM'S FOR, LIKE, PROBABLY MAYBE
A WEEK, MAYBE.
I WANT TO BE ON MY OWN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE OVER THERE
WITH MY MOM.
I THINK I'M MATURE ENOUGH
TO BE ON MY OWN.
>> DIAPER CHANGING.
HAVE YOU DONE MUCH WITH BABIES,
NEWBORNS?
>> NO.
>> NO. OKAY.
AND I'M GONNA HAVE JAMIE COME
OVER AND GET IN ON THIS TOO.
LITTLE BOYS HAVE THE TENDENCY
TO BE A LITTLE EXUBERANT
WITH THEIR PEEING, SO IT'S GOOD
TO PUT SOMETHING OVER THERE.
YOU CAN HOLD HIS LITTLE LEGS UP.
OKAY, NOW, SWADDLING THE BABY
AFTER THE DIAPER CHANGE.
YOU TAKE THE BLANKET.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD HANDLING HIM.
AND YOU PULL IT ALL THE WAY
AROUND.
HE'S JUST LIKE A LITTLE BURRITO.
>> IT'S FINALLY TIME TO LEAVE
THE HOSPITAL AND GO HOME.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
COME ON, LITTLE MAN.
>> WELCOME TO GRANDMA'S
FOR, LIKE, ANOTHER WEEK.
>> WHAT'S YOUR DIAPER
LOOKING LIKE?
YOU STILL FRESH?
HE NEEDS TO BE CHANGED.
YOU GONNA DO IT?
>> NO, MAN.
>> MM, NO.
>> DID HE POOP A LOT?
KEEP IT COVERED.
>> HERE, YOU PULL THAT.
JUST PULL THAT DOWN,
LIKE, REMEMBER HOW I TOLD YOU?
PUSH IT DOWN.
>> I AM.
GOSH.
>> I'LL HOLD HIS BUTT UP.
YOU WIPE.
JUST PUT THAT DOWN OVER HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
>> HERE, WIPE IT.
>> [sighs]
I NEED TO EAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO HOLD HIM
WHILE I DO THAT.
>> YOUR MOM CAN HOLD HIM.
I GOT TO GO TO PATASKALA.
MY DAD'S OUT THERE WAITING.
>> I KNOW JAMIE IS STRESSED
BECAUSE HE MISSED A COUPLE
SHIFTS WHILE I WAS IN
THE HOSPITAL, AND NOW HE HAS TO
GO TALK TO HIS BOSS.
HEY, MAMA.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> AW, DID YOU MAKE THEM?
>> MM-HMM.
IT'S A PICTURE OF JAMIE.
>> AW...
THANK YOU, MAMA.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THEY'RE REALLY CUTE.
>> THANKS.
>> [giggles]
YOU'RE SO ALERT.
YOU'RE THE HANDSOMEST LITTLE MAN
I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> DID HE PUKE?
>> NOPE, HE BURPED, THOUGH.
SEE, HE'S DOING THE,
"I WANT FOOD."
YOU GOT HIM?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?
>> MAN, I GOT SUSPENDED FROM
WORK, AND I DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA EVEN GO BACK THERE.
>> WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'RE TRYING TO, LIKE,
LIMIT ME TO, LIKE,
TEN HOURS A WEEK.
>> WHY?
>> IT'S LIKE THEY HAD A GRUDGE
AGAINST ME.
I MEAN, THEY COULDN'T WRITE ME
UP FOR IT, BUT THEY WERE LIKE--
NOW THEY GOT A GRUDGE, SO I JUST
KIND OF GOT TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> IT SUCKS THAT JAMIE IS OUT
OF WORK, BUT RIGHT NOW, I'M JUST
GLAD THAT HE'S HERE.
I'M NOT GONNA QUIT
TILL YOU BURP.
>> [belches]
>> OH, THERE YOU GO.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> ARE YOU ABOUT TO DO SOME
SCHOOLWORK?
>> YEAH, AFTER I'M DONE
FEEDING HIM.
>> I'LL TAKE HIM
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
>> MY MOM HAS BEEN HELPING ME
A LOT WITH THE BABY, SO I'VE
GOTTEN MORE HOMEWORK DONE
THAN I HAVE IN A WHILE.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN EAT
FOR DINNER?
JAMIE HAS BEEN HELPING A LOT TOO
SINCE HE LOST HIS JOB, BUT HIS
DAD GOT HIM CONSTRUCTION WORK
NEAR HIS HOUSE, SO HE'S READY
TO MOVE BACK THERE.
>> OH, WAKE UP.
>> IT'LL BE HARD WITHOUT
MY MOM'S HELP, BUT I HAVE TO
CONVINCE HER I'M READY TO DO
THIS BY MYSELF.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE
RAISING MY BABY.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO DO IT
ON MY OWN, AND IF I KEEP RELYING
ON YOU, WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WHEN HE GET OLDER AND I AM
ON MY OWN?
I'M PRETTY MATURE FOR MY AGE
ALREADY.
>> YEAH, YOU ARE MATURE FOR
YOUR AGE, BUT YOU'RE ALSO NAIVE.
AND HONESTLY, I'VE BEEN WASHING
HIS BOTTLES.
I GO IN AND CLEAR ALL THE
BOTTLES OUT OF YOUR ROOM.
THEY'RE ON THE COUNTERS.
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN ACKNOWLEDGED
THAT.
>> OKAY, THEN IF I LIVE THERE,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT PICKING UP DIAPERS
OR CLEANING BOTTLES.
>> THIS IS SERIOUS.
>> THERE'S A MILLION MOMS
OUT THERE, AND THEY DO IT.
WHY DON'T YOU THINK I CAN?
>> I'M NOT SAYING THAT I DON'T
THINK YOU CAN, BUT I KNOW THAT
YOU THINK THAT IT'S GONNA
BE GREAT.
YOU DON'T EVEN HEAR ME.
I KNOW YOU DON'T.
YOU'RE LOOKING STRAIGHT
THROUGH ME.
>> NO, I HEAR YOU.
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR
WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
I DON'T WANT TO LET YOU GO.
LIKE, I REALLY DON'T.
IT'S NOT TIME.
>> YOU'RE NEVER GONNA WANT
TO LET ME GO.
I UNDERSTAND WHERE MY MOM
IS COMING FROM, BUT MY MIND
IS MADE UP.
>> BYE.
I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
IT'S TIME FOR US TO TRY TO
MAKE IT WITHOUT MY MOM'S HELP.
>> [groans]
OH, I'M MAKING A MESS.
>> MOVING INTO JAMIE'S DAD'S
HOUSE MAKES ME FEEL LIKE WE'RE
FINALLY STARTING OUR LIFE
AS A FAMILY.
JAMIE SEEMS HAPPIER ALREADY,
AND HIS DAD EVEN LINED UP
A CONSTRUCTION JOB FOR HIM.
YOU LAUGHING AT YOUR MAMA?
>> OOH, YOU'RE A JERK.
>> YOU'RE A JERK.
>> WHY YOU GONNA KICK ME?
>> YOU'RE THE ONE THAT
KICKED ME.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU GONNA--
HOW ARE YOU GONNA DO TOMORROW,
BEING ALL ON YOUR OWN
WHILE I'M AT WORK?
HOW DO YOU THINK IT'S GONNA BE
HAVING HIM ALL TO YOURSELF?
>> I MEAN, I HAVE NO PROBLEM,
LIKE, TAKING CARE OF HIM ALONE,
BUT I THINK I'LL DO GOOD.
I MEAN, I KNOW HOW TO DO
EVERYTHING.
>> IT'S PRETTY SELF-EXPLANATORY.
>> HOW ARE WE GONNA MANAGE
YOUR JOB AND ME DOING MY
HOMEWORK AND EVERYTHING?
ARE WE GONNA HAVE, LIKE,
A PLAN OR...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S REALLY UP TO YOU.
>> I CAN GET, LIKE, AN HOUR
WHEN I'M WITH HIM.
I CAN GET AN HOUR OF HOMEWORK
DONE.
YOU NEED TO TAKE HIM FROM, LIKE,
WHENEVER YOU GET HOME
TO, LIKE, 10:00 OR 10:30,
DEPENDING ON WHENEVER
YOU GET HOME.
>> YEAH.
>> JAMIE HAS TO LEAVE THE HOUSE
AT 5:00 A.M. TO GO TO WORK
WITH HIS DAD.
I'M REALLY GLAD HE GOT A JOB,
BECAUSE WE DEFINITELY NEED
THE MONEY, BUT IT DOES MEAN
I'M GOING TO BE ALONE WITH THE
BABY ALL DAY FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> [crying]
>> OH, WHAT IS YOUR MALFUNCTION?
EVERYTHING IS DIFFERENT HERE.
AT MY MOM'S, THINGS WERE TAKEN
CARE OF FOR ME.
NOW I HAVE TO DO EVERYTHING
ON MY OWN.
BAD DOG.
OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
AS THE WEEK GOES ON, I REALIZE
HOW HARD IT IS FOR ME
TO GET OUT OF THE HOUSE,
AND IT'S GETTING REALLY LONELY.
YOU WANT YOUR BOTTLE?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
TAKING CARE OF THE BABY
MAKES GETTING ANY HOMEWORK DONE
IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT WHEN JAMIE GETS HOME,
HE'S TOO TIRED TO HELP.
AFTER A WEEK ON MY OWN,
WHEN JAMIE DOES TRY TO HELP
WITH THE BABY, IT JUST STRESSES
ME OUT MORE.
PUT THAT JACKET ON HIM.
>> WE'RE GONNA COVER HIM UP.
IT'S ONLY GONNA TAKE
TWO SECONDS.
>> NO, YOU NEED TO PUT HIM
BUCKLED IN.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IF YOU DROP IT,
IF THAT THING BROKE.
THAT THING FLIPPED BEFORE
WHEN I--HOLDING HIM,
THAT THING FLIPPED BACK.
>> YEAH, MAYBE YOU, NOT ME.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU'RE BETTER.
>> AIN'T NEVER HAPPENED TO ME.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M A DAD. I'M A DAD.
>> WELL, YOU DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
YOU WERE DOING A MINUTE AGO.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I WAS GONNA
DROP HIM.
>> I HATE THAT JAMIE AND I
ARE ARGUING, AND TO MAKE MATTERS
WORSE, MY MOM CAME OVER WITH
SOME MORE DISAPPOINTING NEWS.
HEY.
>> HI, BABY.
I BROUGHT YOUR GRADES.
I MISSED YOU.
YES, I DID.
WELL, YOU HAVE TWO "F"s.
SO WHAT'S UP ABOUT THOSE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
JUST NEED TO GET ON IT MORE.
IT'S HARD TO BE ON IT
ALL THE TIME WHEN I HAVE A BABY.
>> LOOK AT HIM.
DO YOU WANT HIM TO HAVE
GOOD SHOES OR NASTY SHOES?
>> I WANT HIM TO HAVE
GOOD SHOES.
>> SO THAT'S WHAT'S GONNA
HELP HIM GET NICE SHOES.
>> I'M TRYING.
IT'S REALLY HARD.
[cell phone ringing]
THAT'S MY ONLINE SCHOOL.
HELLO?
>> OH, HI, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M PRETTY GOOD.
>> UM, IT'S PRETTY HARD,
BUT I'M GETTING THERE.
>> MM-HMM. FRESHMAN?
>> IF I DO GOOD FROM HERE ON
OUT, WHEN DO YOU THINK I'LL BE
ABLE TO, LIKE, GRADUATE?
>> OKAY, WELL, THANK YOU.
I MEAN, REALLY, I DIDN'T KNOW
I WAS THAT BEHIND.
>> THIS IS ALL GOING DOWNHILL.
YOU NEED TO COME HOME, BECAUSE
THERE ARE RULES THERE.
>> I'M DOING FINE HERE.
>> AND I CAN HELP YOU,
AND I CAN MAKE SURE THAT
EVERYTHING'S BEING DONE.
I'M NOT JUST GOING ON WHAT
YOU TELL ME, 'CAUSE A LOT OF
TIMES, YOU DON'T TELL ME
THE TRUTH.
YOU TELL ME WHAT I WANT TO HEAR.
>> I WANT TO STAY HERE
AT JAMIE'S, BUT IF HE CAN'T
HELP ME, I DON'T THINK
THAT'S POSSIBLE.
>> I FOUND OUT I'M IN DANGER
OF FAILING MY ONLINE SCHOOL.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING, BABE?
>> HOW WAS WORK?
>> HORRIBLE.
>> AND FOR ME TO GET BACK
ON TRACK, I'M GOING TO NEED
MORE HELP WITH THE BABY
FROM JAMIE, WHICH SHOULDN'T BE
A PROBLEM, BECAUSE IT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT TO HIM THAT ONE OF US
GRADUATE.
WELL, DID YOU WANT TO, LIKE...
LIKE, MAKE A PLAN?
LIKE, I TAKE HIM ALL DAY,
AND THEN YOU TAKE HIM FOR,
LIKE, FOUR OR FIVE HOURS,
AND THEN WE'LL GET YOU TO BED
AT AROUND 10:00.
I MEAN, IT AIN'T THAT BAD.
IT'S ONLY FOUR HOURS A DAY.
>> YEAH, FOUR HOURS A DAY
IS A LOT, WHEN YOU WORK
A FULL TEN HOURS A DAY.
IT GETS PRETTY CRAZY.
>> IT MIGHT BE HARD, BUT JAMIE
HAS TO FIND A WAY TO HELP OUT
WITH THE BABY, OR I'M NOT GOING
TO MAKE IT THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL,
AND MY MOM WON'T LET ME
LIVE HERE.
BUT SO FAR, IT'S NOT
LOOKING GOOD, BECAUSE JAMIE
IS MORE INTERESTED IN HANGING
OUT WITH HIS FRIENDS THAN
HELPING OUT WITH HIS SON.
>> I'M ABOUT TO GO DOWN
THE STREET FOR A LITTLE BIT.
>> DON'T MATTER.
IT SUCKS BEING LEFT ALONE
WITH THE BABY ALL THE TIME.
THIS ISN'T HOW I PICTURED THINGS
AT ALL, AND I'M REALLY STARTING
TO GET FRUSTRATED.
>> SO TELL ME ABOUT JAMIE
AND YOUR LITTLE DRAMA.
>> WE DON'T EVER REALLY, LIKE,
GET ALONG ANYMORE, REALLY.
WE FIGHT ALL THE TIME.
HE'S BEEN, LIKE, GOING OUT
MORE NOW.
>> WHERE IS HE GOING OUT TO?
>> JUST WITH A FRIEND.
AND I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO,
LIKE, DO MY HOMEWORK.
'CAUSE, I MEAN, I'M ALREADY
BEHIND, AND I'M TRYING
TO CATCH UP.
AND HE AIN'T HELPED OUT
WITH THAT, LIKE, AT ALL.
AND I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I'LL BE ABLE TO PUT UP WITH IT.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
>> I'D PROBABLY MOVE WITH
MY MOM.
I'M HAVING A ROUGH TIME
AT JAMIE'S DAD'S HOUSE,
AND IT TURNS OUT HIS DAD IS
HAVING A ROUGH TIME WITH US TOO.
>> YOU KNOW WHEN I WASN'T
WORKING, I KEPT THIS PLACE
CLEAN.
IT'S JUST REAL FRUSTRATING
SOMETIMES.
>> WELL, I MEAN, I CAN SAY
THAT I CLEAN.
>> I KNOW YOU DO, BUT HOW MANY
TIMES IN THE 22 YEARS I'VE BEEN
POURING WALLS HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
MY MUDDY PANTS LAYING ON
THE LIVING ROOM FLOOR?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, MAYBE.
>> EVER?
I WOULDN'T EVEN MIND WASHING
THE DISHES, IF THEY WERE ALL
RINSED OUT.
HELL, THERE WAS FOUR--
TEN BOWLS IN THERE THAT WERE
COMPLETELY FULL OF SOME KIND
OF SUBSTANCE THAT...
>> THAT BROWN CRAP?
>> YEAH.
I DIDN'T EVEN DO THAT.
I WAS...
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHO DID THAT.
>> IT'S HARD, REAL HARD.
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN ARGUING.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO HEAR IT.
I JUST LEAVE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT THE HELL.
GOT TO COME TOGETHER
FOR THAT BABY RIGHT THERE.
>> EW, DUDE.
HE PUKED EVERYWHERE.
JAMIE'S DAD MAKES A GOOD POINT.
WE HAVE TO TRY TO PULL IT
TOGETHER FOR JAMIE JR.'S SAKE.
SO I FOUND A DAY CARE NEARBY
THAT WILL BE FREE AS LONG AS
I'M A STUDENT.
JAMIE DOESN'T LIKE THE IDEA
OF HAVING THE BABY HERE
BUT AGREED TO COME CHECK IT OUT.
>> IN THIS ROOM, WE HAVE
CHILDREN FROM 6 WEEKS
TO 12 MONTHS.
WE ASK THAT YOU PREPARE
YOUR OWN BOTTLES, SUPPLY
YOUR WIPES AND DIAPERS.
>> OKAY.
>> WELL, FEEL FREE TO CALL
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS.
I'LL LET YOU GUYS THINK
ABOUT IT.
>> OKAY.
>> IT WAS NICE MEETING YOU.
>> YOU TOO.
>> NICE MEETING YOU TOO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT REALLY ALL UP FOR
THE IDEA OF PUTTING HIM
IN DAY CARE, SO YOU'RE GONNA
PROBABLY BE FIGHTING WITH ME
ABOUT THIS FOREVER.
>> I DON'T GET IT, THOUGH.
LIKE, YOU'RE--LIKE--
OH, GOD.
>> IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
HE'S TOO YOUNG.
MAYBE WHEN HE'S OLDER,
I CAN SEE, BUT, LIKE,
NOT RIGHT NOW.
SERIOUSLY.
>> THAT'S [bleep].
>> I'M, LIKE, A MILLION PERCENT
SURE THAT I WOULD RATHER QUIT
MY JOB THAN PUT HIM IN HERE.
>> DON'T--
>> HE CAN WAIT UNTIL HE'S, LIKE,
1 1/2 OR 2, FOR REAL.
SERIOUSLY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU'LL BE GRADUATED
IN HIGH SCHOOL AROUND THEN.
>> OKAY, I'LL GRADUATE
A LOT QUICKER IF I PUT HIM
IN DAY CARE.
I COULD GO TAKE HIM TO DAY CARE
FOR A COUPLE HOURS WHILE I--
>> AND YOU'RE GONNA--
>> LET ME TALK.
>> I'LL QUIT MY JOB.
>> OKAY, CAN YOU LET ME TALK?
>> I COULD COME WATCH HIM
AT NIGHT.
>> I MEAN, RIGHT NOW, THAT
AIN'T--IT'S NOT REALLY WORKING
RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT?
BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN FIGHTING?
>> WELL, YEAH.
>> YOU'RE JUST [bleep] ANNOYING.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE PRETTY ANNOYING
TOO.
LIKE, YOU BLOW EVERYTHING
OUT OF PROPORTION.
>> I BLOW EVERYTHING OUT
OF PROPORTION?
YOU'RE SAYING THAT I DON'T
WATCH HIM.
>> NO, BUT YOU LEAVE
ALL THE TIME, WHICH YOU DO,
AND YOU KNOW YOU DO.
GOD, YOU'RE [bleep] MENTAL.
>> BYE, JAMIE.
>> AFTER OUR FIGHT AT THE DAY
CARE, THINGS BETWEEN ME
AND JAMIE ARE TENSE.
>> SO WHAT'S GOING ON WITH
YOU AND JAMIE?
>> IT'S JUST--LATELY, WE'VE JUST
BEEN FIGHTING REALLY BAD.
LIKE, WE'VE NEVER FOUGHT
THAT BAD BEFORE.
WE'LL BE YELLING AT EACH OTHER,
AND IT'LL CAUSE HIM JUST TO WALK
OUT, 'CAUSE HE DOESN'T EVEN WANT
TO FIGHT WITH ME.
HE'LL JUST LEAVE.
>> YOU JUST GOT TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE BABY DOESN'T
EXPERIENCE, LIKE, THE NEGATIVITY
AROUND HIS PARENTS, BECAUSE
HE'LL THINK THAT'S OKAY.
SO REMEMBER WHAT YOU TOLD ME
ABOUT HOW IMPORTANT FINISHING
YOUR SCHOOLING WAS, BECAUSE YOU
WANTED TO SHOW BABY JAMIE
THAT YOU BECAME SOMETHING?
>> WELL, THAT HASN'T CHANGED.
>> WELL, I MEAN, THE WAY THINGS
ARE GOING RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT
GONNA HAPPEN.
I MEAN, I SAID I WAS GONNA TAKE
A SEMESTER OFF, AND I TOOK
SEVEN YEARS.
SO ARE YOU READY TO COME
BACK HOME?
OR NOT, OR...
>> I MEAN, YEAH.
>> I'VE BEEN TELLING YOU
ALL ALONG.
>> I KNOW, BUT I DIDN'T THINK--
>> BUT YOU WANTED TO TRY IT OUT
ON YOUR OWN.
>> I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D BE,
LIKE, THAT BIG OF A HELP
THAT YOU ARE.
I FEEL LIKE YOU, LIKE,
HELP EVERYTHING.
LIKE, IF WE MOVED THERE,
IT WOULD BE, LIKE, A LOT
OF HELP.
>> YEP.
I'M JUST HAPPY.
>> YOU ARE NOW?
NOW THE BABY WILL BE AROUND
ALL THE TIME.
I'M JUST REALLY HAPPY ABOUT
MY HOMEWORK, 'CAUSE I KNOW,
OVER THERE, I'LL GET IT DONE.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I'LL MAKE YOU.
I'LL PROBABLY BE SITTING
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU,
AND YOU'LL BE LIKE, "OKAY..."
>> I KNOW LIVING AT MY MOM'S
IS THE BEST THING FOR NOW,
BUT I DOUBT JAMIE WILL SEE IT
THAT WAY.
I MEAN, DO YOU...
I MEAN, ARE WE BOTH MOVING
TO MY MOM'S AND GONNA LIVE THERE
AND BE TOGETHER, OR AM I GONNA
GO THERE ALONE?
>> THIS WHOLE SITUATION,
THIS AIN'T ALL MY FAULT.
>> I'M NOT TELLING YOU THAT.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S ALL BEING
COMPLETELY PUT ON MY SHOULDERS,
BUT...
>> I'M NOT TELLING YOU THAT.
>> I FEEL LIKE EVERYTHING
THAT'S GONE ON IS ON MY
SHOULDERS, AND...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I'M NOT QUITTING MY JOB AGAIN
TO COME UP THERE AND STAY UP
THERE LIKE I DID LAST TIME,
'CAUSE I FELT LIKE...
COMPLETELY DEPRESSED UP THERE.
GONNA BE, LIKE, LOCKED UP
UP THERE.
>> LIKE I AM HERE.
>> I'M NOT GONNA HAVE
THE FREEDOM TO DRIVE NOWHERE.
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE THE FREEDOM
TO WALK NOWHERE.
TO GO ANYWHERE, UNLESS I GET
SOMEONE ELSE TO TAKE OUT OF
THEIR BUSY SCHEDULE TO TAKE ME.
>> EXACTLY WHAT I'VE BEEN
DOING HERE.
>> BASICALLY, YOU'RE TELLING ME
I HAVE TO DO THIS, OR WE'RE NOT
GONNA BE TOGETHER.
I JUST DON'T SEE IT WORKING OUT
LIKE IT'S PLANNED.
>> I WISH THAT I WOULD HAVE BEEN
ABLE TO, LIKE, KNOW THE REAL
JAMIE BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT
WITH HIM.
IT WOULD HAVE CHANGED A LOT
FOR ME.
LIKE, I WOULDN'T BE WITH HIM
RIGHT NOW AT ALL.
I THOUGHT THAT MAYBE A BABY
WOULD MAKE OUR RELATIONSHIP
BETTER, AND IT WAS DEFINITELY
NOT WHAT I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
I THOUGHT THAT WE WERE GONNA BE,
LIKE...LIKE A FAMILY.
WE WERE GONNA GO GET MARRIED,
AND I WANT TO BE WITH HIM
MORE THAN ANYTHING, 'CAUSE
I LOVE HIM, BUT IT ISN'T
WORKING.
WHEN I MOVED OUT OF MY MOM'S,
I THOUGHT THAT IT WOULD BE
LIKE FREEDOM.
IT WOULD BE LIKE, "WOW.
I'M ABOUT TO GO BE ON MY OWN."
BUT IT HASN'T REALLY WENT
THAT WAY.
I'M MOVING BACK IN WITH MY MOM.
I NEED THE HELP.
>> HE'S A HAPPY MAN.
>> I FEEL LIKE IF IT KEEPS ON
GOING HOW IT'S GOING NOW,
I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO GRADUATE.
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE A LIFE
ANYMORE.
AFTER I HAD A BABY, ALL MY
FRIENDS JUST COMPLETELY, LIKE,
FORGOT ABOUT ME.
WHEN PEOPLE WANT ME TO COME OVER
AND I TELL THEM I HAVE A BABY,
THEY'RE LIKE, "OH, WELL,
NEVER MIND."
OR THEY DITCH ME OR...
IT'S JUST WAY DIFFERENT NOW.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> female announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT...
>> HOW IN THE WORLD DID YOU
END UP PREGNANT?
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE
LOOKING BACK ON IT
'CAUSE IT STILL DISAPPOINTS ME.
SHE'S PROBABLY GONNA STAY, LIKE,
HERE, LIKE, AT THE BEGINNING
A LOT MORE.
>> I AIN'T GONNA BE OVER HERE.
>> DAMN!
>> SCREAM IT, GIRL.
SCREAM IT.
>> I'D RATHER MY KID LIVE
IN MY HOUSE.
>> I CAN'T JUST LET HER GO
SOMEWHERE.
>> AT HER DAD'S HOUSE?
IF SHE DOESN'T MOVE IN,
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
>> A BABY CHANGES THINGS.
A BABY CHANGES PEOPLE'S LIVES.