>> GOOD?
>> YEAH.
HI, MY NAME'S ASHLEY,
AND I'M FROM MCKINNEY, TEXAS,
A SUBURB OF DALLAS,
BUT I'M ORIGINALLY FROM
WAY SOUTH TEXAS, WHERE MOST OF
MY FAMILY STILL LIVES.
AND IN MY HOUSE,
IT'S JUST US GIRLS:
ME; MY LITTLE SISTER, MIA;
AND MY MOM.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO PLAY?
>> SURE.
>> MY BIOLOGICAL DAD
HAS NEVER BEEN AROUND.
MY MOM AND I ARE VERY CLOSE,
BECAUSE SHE HAD ME WHEN SHE WAS
19 YEARS OLD.
BUT I HAVE BIG PLANS
TO LEAVE THE NEST SOON
AND MAKE IT ON MY OWN
IN NEW YORK.
I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE THERE
AND BECOME A PHOTOJOURNALIST.
MY BOYFRIEND, JUSTIN, AND I
RECENTLY BROKE UP,
SO I'M FOCUSING MORE ON WRITING
AND SCHOOL NOW.
I EVEN STARTED MY OWN BLOG.
I'M ABOUT TO START
MY SENIOR YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I PLAN TO GRADUATE EARLY
TO GET MY REAL LIFE STARTED.
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
GOING TO THE BIG APPLE
MIGHT HAVE TO WAIT,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
I'M ALMOST FIVE MONTHS ALONG,
AND I JUST FOUND OUT
I'M HAVING A GIRL.
SHE'S DUE ON CHRISTMAS DAY.
IT'S FUNNY TO THINK
THAT I'VE BEEN PREGNANT LONGER
THAN JUSTIN, THE BABY'S FATHER,
AND I WERE EVEN TOGETHER.
I DON'T EVEN SEE WHY
I HAVE TO EAT BREAKFAST ANYWAY.
>> YOU HAVE TO.
IT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT MEAL.
>> I NEVER ATE IT LAST YEAR.
>> LAST YEAR, YOU WEREN'T
PREGNANT, AND THIS YEAR,
YOU ARE.
>> MY MOM'S BEEN REALLY
SUPPORTIVE, BUT I STILL
HAVEN'T DECIDED IF I'M READY
TO RAISE A BABY.
WE WENT THROUGH THIS WHOLE THING
FOR, LIKE, A MONTH.
>> YEAH, YOU WERE IN DENIAL
FOR, LIKE, A MONTH,
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL ME.
>> I WASN'T IN DENIAL.
I JUST REALLY THOUGHT, LIKE--
>> LIKE IT WAS GOING TO GO AWAY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU WERE, LIKE,
HAVING NERVOUS BREAKDOWNS AND--
>> I WASN'T HAVING
A NERVOUS BREAKDOWN.
>> YOU WOULD GET ALL
STRESSED OUT AND THEN SAY,
"UGH, I'M JUST SO HUNGRY."
AND I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOSH,
WHAT'S WRONG WITH"--
REMEMBER THAT?
>> NO.
>> I KNEW.
AND WE TALKED ABOUT
THE THREE DIFFERENT OPTIONS.
AND, YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANTED
TO HAVE AN ABORTION, FINE.
HAVE YOUR ABORTION.
IF YOU WANTED TO GIVE IT UP
FOR ADOPTION, FINE.
I'M GOING TO SUPPORT YOU.
BUT WHEN, YOU KNOW,
YOU CONSIDERED KEEPING IT,
I WAS JUST LIKE, "[bleep]."
I STARTED TO PANIC
A LITTLE BIT, 'CAUSE IF YOU WERE
GOING TO KEEP THE BABY,
THINGS ARE GOING TO HAVE
TO CHANGE.
WE WANT YOU TO FINISH SCHOOL.
>> THAT'S TRUE, BUT I JUST
WANT HER TO HAVE, LIKE,
A STAY-AT-HOME MOM.
>> WELL, I CAN'T DO IT.
I'M A SINGLE MOM, AND I WORK,
YOU KNOW, A FULL-TIME JOB.
AND SO MY ROLE'S GOING
TO HAVE TO BE FINANCIAL.
WE'D HAVE TO PAY A NANNY
TO RAISE IT.
I CAN'T STAY HOME.
>> YUP.
>> SO DO YOU CONSIDER
KEEPING IT STILL?
>> OF COURSE I WANT TO.
IT'S JUST REALLY OVERWHELMING
AND STRESSFUL.
>> YOU'RE STILL A KID.
>> EVEN IF MY MOM DOES HELP ME
FINANCIALLY, THE BABY
WOULD STILL HAVE TO GO
TO A DAYCARE, AND I'D STILL
HAVE TO GIVE UP GOING
TO COLLEGE IN NEW YORK.
IF MY MOM'S LIFE
IS ANY INDICATION,
RAISING A BABY ALONE
MEANS SACRIFICING EVERYTHING.
SHE DOES WELL NOW BUT ONLY
BECAUSE SHE WORKS NONSTOP.
NOW THAT I'M THINKING ABOUT
MY OWN BABY AND HER FATHER,
I WONDER WHAT OUR LIVES
WOULD HAVE BEEN LIKE
HAD MY OWN DAD STUCK AROUND.
MAKING THIS DECISION
MIGHT BE DIFFERENT
IF THIS BABY'S FATHER WERE
IN THE PICTURE, BUT HEAND I
DIDN'T DATE FOR VERY LONG,
AND WE'RE NOT REALLY IN TOUCH.
SO YOU TALK TO JUSTIN LATELY,
THE JERK?
>> NO.
>> IS JUSTIN GOING TO BE
A SENIOR AGAIN?
>> HE GRADUATED LAST YEAR,
THANK GOD.
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
>> REMEMBER WHEN WE, LIKE,
FIRST MET HIM?
YOU THOUGHT HE WAS, LIKE,
SO CUTE.
>> HE USED TO, LIKE--
>> SLEEP IN CLASS.
>> YEAH, AND HE WAS REALLY CUTE.
>> HOW LONG WERE Y'ALL DATING
BEFORE Y'ALL HAD SEX?
>> LIKE, TWO MONTHS.
WE ONLY DID IT ONE TIME ANYWAY.
>> JUST THE ONCE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU USE A CONDOM?
OR DID Y'ALL?
>> NO. I MEAN, WE DIDN'T.
IT WAS JUST SPUR OF THE MOMENT.
I GUESS WE DIDN'T REALLY
THINK OF IT AS A BIG DEAL.
BUT I GUESS IT IS.
>> REMEMBER THAT DAY,
THE ACTUAL DAY?
>> IT WAS PHYSICAL FITNESS DAY
AT SCHOOL?
[laughter]
>> YOU HAD YOUR PHYSICAL
THAT DAY.
YOU COULDN'T EVEN RUN.
>> NO, SHELLEY, STOP.
[laughter]
I REALLY REGRET IT.
LIKE, REALLY REGRET IT.
MY FRIENDS ARE REALLY
SUPPORTIVE, AND THEY HELP ME
LAUGH ABOUT THE WHOLE SITUATION.
BUT THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS,
I NEED TO GET SERIOUS
AND MAKE A DECISION.
AND THAT MEANS I HAVE TO TALK
TO JUSTIN AND FIND OUT
WHERE HE STANDS.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
SINCE HIS MOM KICKED HIM OUT
FOR GETTING ME PREGNANT,
SO AFTER MY LAST DAY
OF SUMMER CLASSES
AT THE COMMUNITY COLLEGE,
I CALLED HIM, AND HE AGREED
TO MEET WITH ME.
>> HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> IT'S NICE SEEING YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
>> LIKE, THE LAST DAY OF SCHOOL,
I THINK, WAS THE LAST TIME
I SAW YOU.
>> YEAH, WE DIDN'T GET ALONG
TOO WELL.
>> YOU WERE, LIKE, MEAN
WHEN I TOLD YOU.
>> I DIDN'T BELIEVE YOU.
>> YOU WERE LIKE, "OH, I THINK
YOU JUST WANT TO GET BACK
TOGETHER WITH ME" OR SOMETHING.
>> I GUESS YOU CAN SAY
I WAS KIND OF A [bleep].
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW
IF I WANT TO KEEP IT
OR, LIKE, DO ADOPTION OR NOT.
SO HOW DO YOU FEEL?
LIKE, I KNOW WE DIDN'T WORK OUT,
LIKE, TOGETHER OR ANYTHING,
BUT IT'S STILL, LIKE,
YOUR KID, SORT OF.
>> WELL, IT IS MY KID.
>> DO YOU JUST, LIKE, NOT CARE?
LIKE, OR ARE YOU--
>> NO, DON'T THINK
THAT I DON'T WANT TO HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
I JUST--
>> YOU DON'T?
>> NO, I WOULD.
LIKE, IF I HAD THE MONEY
AND ALL THAT, I WOULD LOVE
TO HELP TAKE CARE OF IT.
BUT I DON'T REALLY WANT
THE BABY GROWING UP
THE WAY I DID.
I WANT IT TO BE ABLE TO HAVE
EVERYTHING IT NEEDS.
>> WHERE ARE YOU NOW?
LIKE, WHERE ARE YOU STAYING?
>> MY MOM WON'T LET ME COME
BACK HOME, SO I JUST SLEEP
IN MY FRIEND'S CAR, SO...
AND I'M ALSO PROBABLY GOING
TO JOIN THE MILITARY.
I NEED MY LIFE BACK ON TRACK
AND EVERYTHING.
>> WITHOUT HAVING A DAD
TO SHARE THE RESPONSIBILITY,
I'M NOT SURE I SHOULD BE RAISING
THIS BABY AT ALL.
I'VE BEEN USING MY BLOG
TO TALK ABOUT MY EXPERIENCE
AS A PREGNANT TEEN,
AND I HOPE THAT SHARING
MY THOUGHTS WILL HELP ME
TO COME TO A DECISION.
IT'S PRETTY OBVIOUS NOW
THAT JUSTIN'S IN NO POSITION
TO BE A DAD, AND I KNOW
HOW HARD IT WOULD BE
TO BE A SINGLE PARENT.
SO I NEED TO TAKE A CLOSER LOOK
AT ADOPTION.
MY MOM AND I FOUND
AN ADOPTION AGENCY.
NOW A SOCIAL WORKER
IS COMING OVER
TO GIVE US MORE INFORMATION.
>> HI, I'M ASHLEY.
>> HI, ASHLEY. I'M DEBBIE.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
COME ON IN.
>> THANKS.
I'M ASHLEY.
>> I'M ASHLEY.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> YOU TOO.
>> THANKS.
SO I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU
A LITTLE BIT ABOUT YOUR OPTIONS.
TELL ME A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
WHEN Y'ALL FIRST STARTED TALKING
ABOUT THE IDEA OF PARENTING
OR ADOPTION.
I MEAN, WHO WAS THE FIRST PERSON
TO KIND OF PUT THE IDEA
OF ADOPTION OUT ON THE TABLE?
>> BOTH MY MOM AND I,
WE CONSIDERED EVERY OPTION.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU HAVE OPTIONS?
I MEAN, DO YOU FEEL LIKE
PARENTING IS AN OPTION?
>> IT'D JUST BE, LIKE,
A STRUGGLE FOR EVERYONE.
>> THIS IS PROBABLY
THE MOST DIFFICULT DECISION
THAT YOU WILL MAKE
IN YOUR ENTIRE LIFE.
IF YOU COULD PUT YOURSELF
IN THE HOSPITAL TODAY, I MEAN,
WHAT WOULD YOU EXPECT
FROM YOURSELF, DO YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW,
JUST THAT I KNOW
IT'S GOING TO BE HARD.
>> IT'S A REALLY HARD--
IT'S EXTREMELY HARD
TO CARRY HER FOR NINE MONTHS
AND TO LOVE HER
AND TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF
AND TAKE CARE OF YOUR BODY
AND GO IN AND DELIVER
AND GO HOME WITHOUT HER.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY HARD.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THAT'S SOMETHING THAT,
I CAN'T MAKE THAT BETTER
FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
I THINK ADOPTION
IS THE BEST CHOICE FOR ME,
BUT AM I STRONG ENOUGH
TO GO THROUGH WITH IT?
>> I'M RUNNING OUT OF OPTIONS.
[alarm ringing]
BUT I CAN'T THINK ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW, BECAUSE THIS IS
THE FIRST DAY
OF MY SENIOR YEAR.
EVERYONE KNEW I WAS PREGNANT
WHEN I LEFT, BUT NOW
THAT I'M ACTUALLY SHOWING,
I'M WORRIED ABOUT FEELING
AWKWARD.
DOES THIS LOOK OKAY?
>> YOU LOOK CUTE.
>> I JUST FEEL REALLY FAT.
>> YOU'RE NOT FAT;
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> I KNOW.
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS?
>> I'M NOT NERVOUS.
IT'S, LIKE, DREAD.
I'M GETTING A LOT MORE NERVOUS
NOW THAT WE'RE ACTUALLY
GETTING THERE OR WHATEVER.
>> REALLY?
I'M GOING NOW, AND I'LL BE
AT SCHOOL IN, LIKE,
MAYBE TEN MINUTES.
>> OKAY, YEAH, JUST TRY
AND BE THERE AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
SINCE I ONLY HAVE THREE CREDITS
LEFT TO GRADUATE, THE SCHOOL
DECIDED I'D GET THOSE
IN CREDIT RECOVERY,
EVEN THOUGH IT'S A PROGRAM
FOR FAILING STUDENTS.
IT'S OKAY, BECAUSE IT MEANS
I CAN BE DONE WITH SCHOOL
BEFORE THE BABY IS BORN.
>> HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> THE ONLY PART I SAW
OF THE SCHOOL WAS
CREDIT RECOVERY, I.S.S.
>> YOU WENT
TO IN-SCHOOL SUSPENSION?
>> THAT'S WHERE THEY TOLD ME
TO GO.
>> YOU'RE IN TROUBLE
FOR BEING PREGNANT.
>> I KNOW; I DON'T HAVE CLASS
WITH ANYBODY
EXCEPT SOME NEW GUY.
I THINK HE'S, LIKE,
ON HOUSE ARREST OR SOMETHING,
'CAUSE HE HAD AN ANKLE BRACELET.
[laughter]
>> THANKS.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> I THOUGHT YOUR PARENTS
WERE GOING TO MAKE YOU
STOP TALKING TO ME,
BUT THEY DIDN'T.
>> LIKE, IF I HANG OUT
WITH A PREGNANT PERSON,
I'M GOING TO GET PREGNANT?
[laughter]
ARE YOU EXCITED TO SEE
WHAT SHE LOOKS LIKE?
>> A LITTLE.
KIND OF SAD.
>> ARE YOU, LIKE, POSITIVE
YOU WANT TO DO ADOPTION?
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE NOT?
>> MM-MM.
>> FOR ME, I DON'T THINK
I WOULD WANT TO GIVE THE BABY
AWAY, BUT, LIKE, IT GIVES YOU
A BETTER OPPORTUNITY,
AND IT GIVES, LIKE, THE BABY
A BETTER OPPORTUNITY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY A GOOD POINT.
LIKE, I DIDN'T WANT TO SOUND,
LIKE, SELFISH, 'CAUSE I'M NOT.
>> YEAH, LIKE, IT'S GOING
TO BE BETTER FOR HER TOO.
>> I DON'T WANT TO, BUT SHE'LL
PROBABLY EXCEL MORE
THAN I PROBABLY COULD LET HER.
>> YEAH.
>> I JUST THINK
THAT'S THE BEST THING.
YEAH.
I KNOW IT'S NOT GOING
TO BE EASY, BUT I'VE FINALLY
COME TO THE CONCLUSION
THAT ADOPTION IS DEFINITELY
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
IT WOULD BE BEST TO GIVE
THIS BABY TO A FAMILY THAT CAN
LOVE AND PROVIDE FOR HER.
SHE WILL HAVE A STAY-AT-HOME MOM
AND A LOVING DADDY.
TWO GREAT PARENTS--THAT'S WHAT
I WANT FOR MY BABY.
IT'S A RELIEF TO HAVE MADE
A DECISION.
>> ASHLEY.
>> HI.
DO YOU HAVE MY BLINK-182 SHIRT
THAT I LEFT HERE?
>> YEAH, I DO, ACTUALLY.
>> 'CAUSE I REALLY DON'T THINK
THIS IS GOING TO FIT.
FINALLY, I CAN TAKE A BREAK
FROM ALL OF THIS ADOPTION TALK
AND HAVE SOME FUN.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS CONCERT FOR MONTHS.
[rock music]
[crowd cheering]
GOING TO A CONCERT PREGNANT,
IT'S NOT AT ALL
LIKE IT USED TO BE.
IT'S TIME FOR ANOTHER CHECKUP.
MY MOM IS MEETING ME
AT THE ULTRASOUND TO SEE
HOW MY BABY IS GROWING.
>> THERE'S THE LITTLE FACE,
AND THERE'S THE BABY'S
LITTLE NOSE AND LIPS.
>> WHOA, WHOA.
HOW CUTE.
>> THAT'S A LOT MORE DETAILED
THAN LAST TIME.
>> SHE'S GROWING
EXACTLY HOW SHE SHOULD
AND LOOKS NORMAL.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THIS IS GOING TO BE HARDER
THAN I THOUGHT.
I MADE THE ADOPTION DECISION,
BUT NOW I HAVE TO DEAL WITH
THE PRACTICALITIES.
LIKE, I STILL HAVE TO CARRY
THIS BABY, WHICH MEANS
GETTING MATERNITY CLOTHES.
>> LOOK ON THAT SIDE
FOR A STORE CALLED PICKLES
AND ICE CREAM.
THERE IT IS.
>> WHY IS IT CALLED PICKLES
AND ICE CREAM?
>> BECAUSE THEY SAY
THAT WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT,
YOU LIKE WEIRD THINGS
LIKE PICKLES AND ICE CREAM.
>> I WANT ICE CREAM.
>> IT'S ON SALE.
NO?
>> NO.
>> DO YOU SEE ANYTHING ELSE,
BABY?
>> NOT OVER HERE.
>> YOU DON'T LIKE THAT
RIGHT NOW.
>> UH-UH.
I WISH WE COULD BUY, LIKE,
A COUPLE OUTFITS OR WHATEVER
FOR THE FIRST TWO DAYS.
>> IT'S JUST HARD.
I MEAN, I'M AFRAID YOU'RE
GOING TO GET ATTACHED AND--
>> WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO BACK OUT.
>> [sighs]
>> OKAY.
MOM, DON'T.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S OKAY.
I'M TRYING TO BE REALLY STRONG
THE WHOLE TIME.
IT'S JUST HARD.
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO SEE ME,
'CAUSE I DON'T WANT YOU TO HAVE
A TOUGH TIME WITH YOUR DECISION.
>> NO, IT'S OKAY.
I'M HAVING A TOUGH TIME
ON MY OWN.
>> I JUST THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE A HARD TIME,
AND I THINK I'M GOING
TO HAVE A HARD TIME.
AND I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO STRUGGLE.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO SUFFER.
>> BECAUSE CREDIT RECOVERY
LETS YOU STUDY AT YOUR OWN PACE,
I WORKED REALLY HARD TO FINISH
ALL OF MY COURSES
AND GRADUATED EARLY.
MY MOM PLANNED A BIG DINNER
WITH THE WHOLE FAMILY
TO CELEBRATE.
THE FAMILY IS ALL
A TEN-HOUR DRIVE AWAY,
BUT GRADUATION
IS AN IMPORTANT EVENT,
SO EVERYONE--
MY UNCLE KENNY; HIS WIFE, LISA,
WHO I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
REALLY CLOSE TO;
AND THEIR TWO KIDS--SHOWED UP.
WE SPEND EVERY HOLIDAY
AND EVERY SUMMER TOGETHER,
SO IT'S JUST NOT A CELEBRATION
WITHOUT THEM.
>> THANK YOU.
I LIKE THAT ONE.
>> EVERYONE LIKES MONEY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
[all gasps]
THANK YOU.
>> AND I WANT TO JUST
CONGRATULATE ASHLEY
FOR HER ACHIEVEMENT
WITH HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I PRAY THAT SHE GOES ON
TO COLLEGE, HOPEFULLY MAKES
WISE DECISIONS
FROM HERE ON OUT.
>> HOPEFULLY.
TO WISE DECISIONS.
>> WISE DECISIONS.
>> MY FAMILY IS DOING
THEIR BEST.
THERE'S A LOT FOR THEM
TO GET USED TO.
BUT IT ALWAYS FEELS LIKE
MY AUNT LISA UNDERSTANDS
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
>> SO YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
MORE EMOTIONAL WHEN YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT CERTAIN THINGS.
HAVE YOU BEEN SURPRISED
AT HOW YOU'RE FEELING?
>> LIKE, SOMETIMES I'M, LIKE,
JUST REALLY, "OKAY, WHATEVER,"
LIKE, HAPPY ABOUT IT.
AND SOMETIMES I JUST GET
NOT IN THE MOOD.
>> YOU JUST DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH.
AND THEN I GUESS MAYBE
IT'S, LIKE, MIXED
WITH FRUSTRATION AND SADNESS
OR SOMETHING.
I'M JUST LIKE--
>> MM.
>> SINCE EVERYBODY'S LEFT
AND THE GRADUATION CELEBRATION
IS OVER, IT'S TIME TO GET BACK
TO REALITY AND MOVE FORWARD
WITH THIS ADOPTION PLAN.
>> WE JUST DISCUSSED
HER OPTIONS, AND SHE HAD SAID
SHE WAS GOING TO GO
WITH ADOPTION.
>> LIKE, I WISH I COULD
HAVE KIDS NOW OR A KID NOW,
BUT I CAN'T.
>> I NEVER MET A BIRTH MOTHER
WHO DOESN'T WISH
THAT THEY COULD PARENT,
THAT THEIR CIRCUMSTANCE
WASN'T DIFFERENT.
THAT'S REALLY, REALLY NORMAL.
YOU KNOW, THE NEXT STEP
IS GOING TO BE LOOKING FOR
ADOPTIVE PARENTS.
DO Y'ALL HAVE ANY SPECIFIC
FEARS, CONCERNS?
>> I GUESS NOT CHOOSING
THE RIGHT ONES.
LIKE, WHAT IF I CHOOSE ONE
AND I'M, LIKE, KIND OF IFFY
ABOUT THEM?
>> I KNOW RIGHT NOW
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
EVEN WHO THESE PEOPLE ARE.
IT'S LIKE A BLACK HOLE.
I MEAN, IN YOUR HEAD,
"WHERE IS MY CHILD GOING?
I HAVE NO IDEA."
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT WE WANT YOU TO WALK AWAY
FEELING PEACEFUL ABOUT THIS,
THAT YOU MADE
THE RIGHT DECISION,
YOU'RE CONFIDENT IN YOUR PLAN
AND WHO'S RAISING YOUR CHILD.
I MEAN, THOSE ARE
THE MOST IMPORTANT THINGS.
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> WE'LL PLAN A TIME
TO COME BACK OUT, BUT KNOW
THAT IF ANYTHING COMES UP,
YOU CAN ALWAYS CALL.
>> THANKS FOR COMING OUT.
>> OKAY, WELL, Y'ALL HAVE
A GOOD WEEK, AND THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
YOU TOO.
>> I SHOULD BE STUDYING
FOR THE S.A.T.s, BUT INSTEAD
I WENT TO THE ADOPTION AGENCY'S
WEBSITE TO CHECK OUT PROFILES.
I TOLD MY CASE WORKER
FROM THE ADOPTION AGENCY
THAT CHOOSING ADOPTIVE PARENTS
FELT OVERWHELMING,
SO SHE SUGGESTED I TALK
TO A GIRL WHO HAD RECENTLY
BEEN THROUGH THE SAME THING.
>> WELL, DO YOU HAVE ANY THINGS
THAT YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT, LIKE,
ADOPTIVE FAMILIES.
>> IT'S SAD.
LIKE, I FELT SO BAD
FOR ALL THOSE PEOPLE.
>> YEAH.
>> I HAVE TO PICK THE ONES
THAT I LIKE THE BEST.
>> I KNOW.
LIKE, I HAVE A HARD TIME
TRUSTING THEM.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE YOU CAN'T EVER
SEE YOUR BABY AGAIN.
LIKE, I HAD A VISITATION
WITH MY BABY, AND HE WAS, LIKE,
FOUR MONTHS.
LIKE, I GOT UPSET, BECAUSE,
LIKE, HE DIDN'T WANT ME.
HE WANTED HER.
>> THAT'S SO SAD.
>> AND I WAS LIKE, "WHY DOES HE
WANT YOU AND NOT ME?"
>> THAT'S LIKE--I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S HOW I'LL BE.
LIKE, I'LL FEEL, LIKE, ANGRY
AT THEM OR WHATEVER.
IT'S, LIKE, A REALLY HARD
DECISION.
I'M SURE YOU KNOW THAT.
WELL, WAS THE FATHER THERE
FOR YOU?
>> NO.
[laughter]
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND,
BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT
GOING THROUGH IT.
>> THEY'RE NOT THE ONE CARRYING.
NOT THAT I'M, LIKE, IN LOVE
WITH HIM OR I LIKE HIM
OR WANT TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP
WITH HIM.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, IT'S HIS KID.
I KNOW HE COULDN'T DO ANYTHING
FOR HER, BUT IT JUST
KIND OF HURTS, YOU KNOW--
>> IT DOES HURT
THAT HE DOESN'T WANT IT.
LIKE, HOW CAN YOU NOT WANT
YOUR OWN KID?
GUYS, THEY JUST DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
>> YEAH, THEY DON'T.
>> ARE YOU, LIKE, WORRIED
ABOUT ANYTHING?
>> WELL, YEAH.
I'M, LIKE, WORRIED
WHEN THE DAY COMES, I'M NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO DO IT.
>> JUST THINK ABOUT YOURSELF.
IT'S THE ONLY ADVICE I HAVE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I WAS ABOUT TO LOOK
AT MORE PROFILES
WHEN MY MOM TOLD ME
SHE WANTED TO TALK TO ME
ABOUT MY AUNT AND UNCLE.
>> LISA AND KENNY CALLED,
AND THEY WANTED ME TO ASK YOU
IF IT WAS OKAY IF THEY COULD
ADOPT YOUR BABY.
>> LIKE 100% ADOPT?
>> LIKE 100% LEGAL ADOPTION.
IT'D BE THEIRS.
>> AND HE'S 100% ABOUT IT?
>> 100%.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE--I MEAN, IT'S A LOT BETTER
THAN HER GOING HOME WITH
STRANGERS, BUT I DON'T KNOW.
>> THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE MORE EXCITED I AM ABOUT
MY AUNT LISA AND UNCLE KENNY
ADOPTING THE BABY.
I TRIED TO CALL THE BABY'S DAD
TO SEE WHAT HE THOUGHT
BUT FOUND THAT HIS PHONE
HAD BEEN DISCONNECTED.
SO IT'S UP TO ME AND MY MOM
TO FIGURE OUT
HOW THIS WILL ALL GO.
>> THEY'RE AT LISA'S.
THEY'RE GOING TO CALL
IN A MINUTE.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO TELL THEM
AS FAR AS, LIKE,
WHAT YOU'RE EXPECTING TO SEE
FROM THEM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST WANTED TO TALK TO THEM
AND JUST SEE, LIKE,
WHAT THEY THOUGHT.
>> JUST PRETEND
THEY WERE STRANGERS
AND YOU'RE GOING TO TELL
THIS STRANGER, "I WANT
TO MAKE SURE I CAN SEE THEM
ANNUALLY.
I WANT PICTURES AND LETTERS
MONTHLY, QUARTERLY, WEEKLY."
>> IT'S MORE COMPLICATED
WHEN YOU HAVE TO, LIKE, DEAL
WITH STRANGERS.
>> IT'S LESS COMPLICATED
WHEN YOU DEAL WITH STRANGERS,
BECAUSE YOU TELL THEM
WHAT YOU WANT--
>> NO, IT ISN'T, BECAUSE
WITH LISA AND KENNY,
MOST LIKELY, THEY'LL BE
PUTTING PICTURES UP ONLINE.
AND, LIKE, ON HOLIDAYS
AND STUFF, I'LL BE SEEING
THE BABY.
>> WELL, BUT YOU DON'T
KNOW THAT.
LOOK, HERE'S LISA.
HI, LISA.
I'M GOING TO PUT YOU
ON SPEAKERPHONE
SO YOU CAN TALK TO ASHLEY.
ONE SECOND.
>> HEY.
>> HI.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN FEELING?
>> GOOD, RELIEVED.
I FEEL, LIKE, REALLY GOOD
ABOUT IT, AND I'M REALLY GLAD
Y'ALL ARE DOING THIS.
>> YOU KNOW I'VE WANTED
TO ADOPT ANYWAY, SO...
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE GETTING EVEN MORE
EXCITED AS THE DAYS
ARE GOING ON.
DO YOU HAVE ANY CONCERNS
OR ANYTHING?
I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT,
YOU KNOW, WE KIND OF
TALK THROUGH EVERYTHING
BEFORE WE DO GO AHEAD
AND GO THROUGH WITH IT.
>> I WAS WONDERING, LIKE,
HOW YOU FELT ABOUT, LIKE,
HOW IT'S GOING TO GO, LIKE,
WHEN I COME DOWN ON BREAK
OR A HOLIDAY OR SOMETHING
TO VISIT.
>> THAT'S GOING TO BE FINE,
BECAUSE YOU'RE PART
OF THE FAMILY.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT,
YOU KNOW, KENNY AND I ARE
RAISING HER AS OUR DAUGHTER,
AND IT SEEMS LIKE
YOU DO KNOW THAT.
>> YEAH.
LIKE, THAT'S HOW I THOUGHT TOO.
>> BUT, SAY, FOUR YEARS DOWN
THE ROAD, YOU'RE ABLE
TO SUPPORT A BABY.
WE JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU REALIZE THAT YOU--
THERE'S REALLY NO GOING BACK
ON IT, RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH, YEAH.
I UNDERSTAND.
I JUST THINK IF I WAS GOING
TO DO ADOPTION ANYWAY,
THIS IS, LIKE,
THE BEST WAY IT COULD GO.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE GREAT,
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO GET
TO SEE HER GROW UP.
YOU ALREADY KNOW US.
I THINK IT'S GOING TO BE GOOD.
>> YEAH, IT WILL BE.
>> ALL RIGHT, THEN.
>> OKAY.
>> BYE-BYE.
>> BYE.
THAT WAS, LIKE, KIND OF FUNNY,
THOUGH, WHEN SHE WAS LIKE,
"WELL, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S NO GOING BACK."
IT KIND OF, LIKE, MADE ME SAD
A LITTLE, BUT, I MEAN, I KNEW--
I KNOW THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
>> THEY'RE RAISING HER.
THEY'RE HER PARENTS, AND--
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'LL GET TO SEE HER.
LIKE, I KNOW
IT'S THE BEST THING.
IT'S GOING TO BE HARD,
BUT I'M STILL MOVING FORWARD
WITH IT.
WE'RE HEADING DOWN TO HARLINGEN
TO START WORKING OUT
AN ADOPTION PLAN.
MY AUNT AND UNCLE DECIDED
THAT SINCE WE'RE A FAMILY,
WE COULD HANDLE THE ADOPTION
PRIVATELY WITH AN ATTORNEY
AND NOT GO THROUGH THE AGENCY.
>> GO AHEAD, ASHLEY.
YOU'RE HUNGRY.
>> THEY ALSO DECIDED
ON A NAME ALREADY,
CALLIE DANIELLE.
"DANIELLE" WILL BE
HER MIDDLE NAME BECAUSE IT'S
MY AND MY AUNT'S MIDDLE NAME.
>> AND SHE'S ALWAYS WANTED
TO ADOPT, AND SO IT JUST SEEMED
LIKE THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY.
>> AND WE'RE HELPING
THE ENTIRE FAMILY.
>> YEAH.
WELL, THANK YOU FOR DOING THIS
AND STUFF.
IT'S RELIEVING.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, AS MUCH AS WE'RE SURE
AND I FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE PRETTY SURE...
>> I AM.
>> AND YOU'RE SET, YES.
WHEN THE BABY IS BORN,
THERE'S GOING TO BE ANOTHER--
THAT'S ANOTHER STEP
INTO IT'S MORE REAL.
>> ANOTHER LEVEL OF REALITY.
>> IT'S ANOTHER LEVEL
OF REALITY.
AND WHEN YOU COME TO THE HOUSE,
HOW DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL
WHEN YOU SEE--
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO, LIKE,
DEAL WITH THAT
WHEN IT HAPPENED.
>> IT'S HARD TO SAY.
>> YEAH, THERE'S GOING TO BE
A SPECIAL BOND THERE
BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU.
SHE'LL ALWAYS KNOW.
>> YEAH.
I DON'T THINK THAT THERE'LL BE,
LIKE, CONFLICT OR ANYTHING.
>> SO Y'ALL WANT TO BE CALLED
AS SOON AS SHE GOES INTO LABOR?
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE DRIVING, YES.
>> DO Y'ALL WANT TO STAY
WITH US?
WOULD YOU RATHER STAY
WITH JENNA?
OR WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
>> ME NEITHER.
I WAS, LIKE, CONFUSED.
>> IS IT GOING TO BE EASIER
FOR YOU?
>> WHATEVER'S EASIER FOR YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GOING
TO FEEL, HONESTLY.
>> A LOT OF THINGS, WE'RE JUST
GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE
AS IT COMES.
>> YEAH.
THE BIGGEST QUESTION
FOR EVERYONE IS,
HOW ARE THINGS GOING TO WORK
AFTER THE BABY IS BORN?
IT'S TEXAS STATE LAW
THAT THE BIRTH MOM
GETS 48 HOURS WITH THE BABY.
WHAT HAPPENS AFTER THAT
IS UP TO US.
WITH MY DUE DATE FAST
APPROACHING, I'M NOW SEEING
THE DOCTOR EVERY WEEK.
>> ASHLEY?
HI.
>> HI.
>> WELL, ARE YOU GETTING
EXCITED?
>> SCARED.
>> THERE YOU GO.
THE BABY'S MOVING A LOT
FOR YOU?
>> MM-HMM.
[heartbeat whooshing]
>> GOT A STRONG HEARTBEAT.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> AS FAR AS
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM,
YOUR MOM'S GOING TO BE
IN THERE, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> ANYBODY ELSE
THAT YOU WANT IN THERE?
>> UM, I DON'T KNOW.
WE HAVEN'T REALLY DISCUSSED IT,
SO I'M NOT SURE.
>> OKAY.
IS THAT SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO TALK ABOUT NOW?
OR IS THAT SOMETHING
YOU'RE GOING TO TALK
WITH YOUR MOM ABOUT,
WHAT YOU'D LIKE TO DO?
'CAUSE I KNOW IT'S GOING
TO BE HARDER
THAN ANYTHING ELSE,
BUT I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT WE KNOW WHAT EXACTLY
YOU WANT, OKAY?
WE'RE JUST GOING TO DO
THIS LITTLE CERVICAL CHECK.
>> OKAY.
>> LET YOUR LEGS FALL
WAY APART THERE.
JUST RELAX.
>> BEING PREGNANT
IS UNCOMFORTABLE ENOUGH
WITHOUT HAVING TO THINK
ABOUT THESE THINGS.
BUT WITHOUT A SOCIAL WORKER
TO HELP US THROUGH,
IT'S UP TO MY MOM TO GET
THE ANSWERS TO THESE QUESTIONS.
>> MY QUESTION TO YOU IS,
DO YOU WANT LISA AND KENNY
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM?
OKAY, SO TELL ME THIS.
WHEN SHE IS BORN AND THE DOCTOR
SAYS, "OH, HERE'S YOUR BABY,"
DO YOU WANT HIM TO HAND HER
TO LISA, OR DO YOU WANT HIM
TO HAND HER TO YOU?
>> WHY WOULD HE HAND HER
TO LISA?
>> 'CAUSE SHE'S GOING TO BE
THE MOM.
>> BUT IF SHE'S THERE,
IT DOESN'T MEAN
HE CAN'T HAND HER TO ME.
>> OKAY, SO HE HANDS HER
TO YOU.
AND THEN WHEN SHE COMES
TO WANT TO HOLD THE BABY,
DO YOU--ARE YOU GOING
TO WANT HER TO HOLD HER?
OR WOULD YOU RATHER HAVE
THAT TIME ALONE AND THEN JUST
BRING HER TO JENNA'S,
WHERE SHE WILL BE WAITING?
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE WAITING
TO KNOW.
HOW IS THIS GOING TO HAPPEN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THAT?
>> WE CAN'T JUST GO
INTO THIS BLIND, BECAUSE
SOMEONE'S GOING TO GET
THEIR FEELINGS HURT.
>> I DON'T LIKE TO MAKE
DECISIONS.
I THOUGHT THE HARDEST PART
WAS GOING TO BE CHOOSING
ADOPTION.
I HAD NO IDEA THERE WERE GOING
TO BE SO MANY MORE DIFFICULT
DECISIONS ALONG THE WAY.
>> MY DOCTOR SAID HE COULD
SAFELY INDUCE ME
A FEW DAYS EARLY SO I DON'T
GO INTO LABOR ON CHRISTMAS.
THIS WAY, THE HOLIDAYS
WON'T FOREVER BE CONNECTED
TO THIS DECISION.
I WENT OVER TO MY AUNT JENNA'S
HOUSE TO TELL HER THE NEWS.
I'M GLAD IT CAN FINALLY BE
A PLANNED DATE, SO THAT'S GOOD.
>> OH, NO, BUT I PUT IT ONLINE,
SO I THINK THEY KNOW.
>> BUT IT'D PROBABLY BE BETTER
COMING FROM YOU.
DO YOU THINK?
>> YEAH.
[line ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> LISA?
>> YES?
>> I WAS JUST GOING TO TELL YOU
THAT WE SET THE DATE TODAY.
>> THE 16TH.
>>YES, THE 16TH.
SO I GUESS YOU KNOW.
>> [laughs] NO.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> BYE.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE HARD,
'CAUSE IT'S, LIKE, "MY KID"
FOR NOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> IN ADDITION TO PLANNING
FOR THE ADOPTION, I NEED
TO START PLANNING FOR COLLEGE.
COLLEGE APPLICATIONS ARE DUE
SOON, AND I DON'T WANT
TO FALL BEHIND, SO WE SCHEDULED
A MEETING WITH
THE COLLEGE ADVISOR.
>> HI, ASHLEY.
RON FRANICK.
>> REALLY NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
COME ON IN.
I WAS HOPING THAT WE COULD TALK
ABOUT WHERE YOU WANT TO GO,
WHAT YOU WANT TO STUDY.
AND I KNOW
THAT YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN NEW YORK CITY SCHOOLS.
WHAT ARE YOU INTERESTED
IN STUDYING?
>> I THINK I'M INTO, LIKE,
PHOTOJOURNALISM OR SOMETHING
A LOT MORE, LIKE, WRITING TOO.
BUT I DON'T--LIKE, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TYPE OF MAJOR.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, A LOT
OF STUFF TO THINK ABOUT
AND DECIDE.
AND THEN BEING PREGNANT
AND HAVING TO DEAL
WITH ALL THE COLLEGE DECISIONS,
THERE'S SO MANY.
>> SHE'S OVERWHELMED
WITH ALL THE CHOICES
OF THE ADOPTION AND--
>> MY AUNT AND UNCLE ARE GOING
TO ADOPT THE BABY.
>> AT THE SAME TIME
WITH COLLEGE AND CLASSES
AND TRYING TO DO HER BEST
ON HER S.A.T. AND--
>> THAT'S A LOT.
IT'S A LOT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I ALSO THINK
THAT VISITING SCHOOLS,
YOU HAVE AN INSTANT REACTION
TO SAYING, "THIS IS A PLACE
THAT I COULD SEE MYSELF AT."
>> YEAH, I WANT TO DO THAT.
>> THERE ARE SO MANY GOOD
SCHOOLS OUT THERE THAT CAN BE
GREAT FITS, CERTAINLY
IN NEW YORK CITY.
YOU HAVE A LOT OF DIFFERENT
CHOICES OUT THERE,
WHICH IS KIND OF WONDERFUL.
IT WAS A REAL PLEASURE
TO TALK TO YOU TODAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> IT REALLY HELPED.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
BYE, ASHLEY.
>> TALKING TO THE COLLEGE
COUNSELOR WAS LIKE GETTING
A SNEAK PEEK AT MY FUTURE.
LIFE WITHOUT PARENTING
LOOKS PRETTY OKAY RIGHT NOW.
BUT I STILL HAVE TO GET THROUGH
THIS PREGNANCY.
MY CURRENT PLAN IS TO HAVE
THE BABY, AND THEN MY MOM AND I
WILL DRIVE HER DOWN
TO MY AUNT LISA
AND UNCLE KENNY'S HOUSE.
SURE, IT'S A LONG DRIVE,
BUT THAT'S OKAY, SINCE IT'LL
GIVE ME MORE TIME WITH THE BABY.
BUT I'M NOT GETTING
MUCH SUPPORT ON THIS PLAN.
>> HARLINGEN'S A TEN-HOUR DRIVE.
>> WELL, I FIGURED
YOU COULD DO IT IN PARTS.
LIKE, TWO PARTS.
STOP AT CRACKER BARREL
OR SOMETHING.
>> MY CONCERN IS,
THE MORE TIME THAT YOU SPEND
WITH THE BABY, YOU'RE GOING
TO BOND.
>> WELL, NO ONE REALLY
UNDERSTANDS HOW I FEEL,
BECAUSE NOBODY'S THE ONE
THAT'S DOING IT.
>> NO, ASHLEY,
BUT WE DO UNDERSTAND,
BECAUSE WE'VE HAD KIDS,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO BOND
WITH YOUR CHILD.
THE MORE TIME YOU HAVE
WITH HER, THE HARDER
IT'S GOING TO BE.
>> [sighs]
FINE, NEW PLAN.
EVERYONE WILL COME UP TO US.
AFTER I HAVE THE BABY,
WE'LL SPEND THE 48 HOURS
IN THE HOSPITAL AND THEN
ALL MEET TO SIGN THE PAPERS
WITH A NOTARY
AT MY AUNT JENNA'S HOUSE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I STILL
HAVE TO RESEARCH COLLEGES
AND KEEP STUDYING
FOR THE S.A.T.s BEFORE I GO
INTO LABOR.
MY INDUCEMENT
IS ONLY DAYS AWAY NOW,
AND I'VE NEVER BEEN
SO UNCOMFORTABLE IN MY LIFE.
>> OKAY, PAGE 93.
>> IT'S FINALLY TIME
TO HEAD TO THE HOSPITAL.
BUT FIRST I WANT TO GIVE
THE BABY'S DAD, JUSTIN,
ONE LAST TRY.
I EMAILED HIM ABOUT
THE ADOPTION, AND ONCE HIS PHONE
GOT RECONNECTED, HE TEXTED ME
THAT HE WANTS TO BE THERE
FOR THE BIRTH.
beep!
UM, HEY, JUSTIN.
I'VE BEEN CALLING,
AND YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ANSWERING,
SO I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF YOU WERE STILL GOING TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL OR NOT.
UM, JUST LET ME KNOW
AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
THANKS, BYE.
I REALLY HOPE HE GETS IN TOUCH,
BECAUSE IT'S SCARY
TO BE GOING THROUGH THIS ALONE.
I'M READY TO BE INDUCED
AND HAVE ALL OF THIS OVER WITH.
>> IS SHE DILATED AT ALL
RIGHT NOW?
HAS HE CHECKED HER?
>> NOT DILATED.
>> NOTHING?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
ARE THE CHANCES I'D GO
INTO LABOR TONIGHT?
>> EVERYBODY'S DIFFERENT.
PROBABLY IN THE MORNING.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
OKAY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
I'M GOING TO BE PUSHING FOR.
THE MINUTE I STARTED
TO FEEL LABOR PAINS,
THEY GAVE ME LOTS
OF MEDICATION AND MY EPIDURAL.
>> HI.
>> MIMI, I LIKE YOUR SOCKS.
THEY'RE ALL FANCY.
THEY GAVE ME SOME MEDICINE,
NUBAIN OR WHATEVER,
AND IT MAKES ME REALLY, JUST,
LIKE--
>> SHE'S LOOPY.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU SAY
YOUR PAIN IS NOW?
>> LIKE A 0.5 OR SOMETHING.
>> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE
AIMING FOR.
>> AM I IN LABOR, LIKE,
RIGHT NOW?
>> YOU'RE IN LABOR.
YOU JUST CAN'T FEEL ANYTHING.
>> I'M GLAD I'M IN THE--FROM--
THE FUTURE.
NOT THE FUTURE BUT--
>> SHE'S GLAD
SHE'S FROM THE FUTURE.
>> MIMI, YOU'RE SO CRAZY.
WHAT IS THIS FOR?
>> THIS IS FOR IDENTIFICATION.
YOU KNOW, IT MEANS THIS BABY
BELONGS TO THIS MOMMY.
IT'LL BE FINE.
>> I'M SCARED.
>> IT'S NOT TYPICAL TO GO
THROUGH SOMETHING THIS HARD
WITHOUT HELP.
SO WHEN THE HOSPITAL REALIZED
WE DIDN'T HAVE
AN ADOPTION AGENT,
THEY SENT UP A SOCIAL WORKER.
>> HI.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HEY, ASHLEY, I'M JUDY.
I'M ONE OF THE SOCIAL WORKERS
HERE.
>> HI.
>> HI, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> I WANTED TO COME BY
AND JUST TALK TO YOU
A LITTLE BIT, OKAY?
JUST TELL ME A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT YOU AND HOW YOU REACHED
THE DECISION FOR ADOPTION.
AND JUST KIND OF START
WITH THAT.
>> WELL, I'M, LIKE, SO YOUNG,
AND I CAN'T--I'M NOT, LIKE,
CAPABLE OF TAKING CARE--
LIKE, I CAN'T EVEN TAKE CARE
OF MYSELF.
AND I JUST WANT THE BABY
TO, LIKE, HAVE TWO PARENTS
AND A STABLE HOUSEHOLD.
>> AND YOUR PLANS ARE TO SPEND
SOME TIME WITH THE BABY.
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> YEAH, I WANT PRETTY MUCH
AS MUCH TIME AS I CAN HAVE.
THAT LOOKS SO PRETTY.
>> YOU LOOK GOOD.
DID JUSTIN COME?
HE DIDN'T?
>> LIKE, HE WANTED TO,
BUT JUST, LIKE, SOMETHING
CAME UP, AND--
>> SO HE JUST COULDN'T MAKE IT?
>> MM-MM.
YEAH.
OH, WELL, THOUGH.
LIKE, AT LEAST I KNOW
THAT HE WANTED TO BE HERE.
>> YEAH.
>> HI.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> OKAY.
>> I'M GOING TO DO
A LITTLE EXAM, JUST KIND OF SEE
HOW WE'RE DOING, OKAY?
OH, YEAH.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
YOU'RE, LIKE, RIGHT HERE.
YOU'RE READY.
>> I WANT YOU TO GRAB UP HERE,
UNDERNEATH YOUR LEGS.
YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE
A DEEP BREATH AND HOLD IT
LIKE YOU'RE UNDERWATER.
AND BEAR DOWN LIKE YOU'RE HAVING
A BOWEL MOVEMENT, OKAY?
WE'RE GOING TO TRY
TO GET THREE PUSHES
WITH EACH CONTRACTION.
>> UNDERSTAND?
>> OKAY, WE'LL TALK YOU
THROUGH IT.
WE'LL TALK YOU THROUGH IT.
OKAY, YOU'RE HAVING ONE NOW.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE
A DEEP BREATH IN.
PUSH DOWN.
HOLD THAT AIR IN AND PUSH DOWN.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE,
TEN.
>> DEEP BREATH.
>> AND PUSH DOWN.
ONE, TWO...
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
GOOD JOB.
>> DID IT WORK?
[laughter]
>> IT TAKES A LITTLE WHILE.
IT TAKES A LITTLE WHILE
TO GET THE HANG OF IT.
>> BUT THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT.
>> OKAY, BIG BREATH IN.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE...
>> JUST LIKE THAT.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
>> NINE, TEN.
>> YOU GOT TO PUSH.
YOU GOT A CONTRACTION.
>> I KNOW. I KNOW.
>> TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
DO IT.
>> GET MAD, ANGRY.
THERE YOU GO. THERE YOU GO.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S PERFECT.
YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB.
>> GOOD JOB, ASHLEY.
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> NINE, TEN.
>> EXCELLENT.
WE'RE GETTING A LOT CLOSER HERE.
>> GET THE BABY NURSES IN HERE.
>> REALLY? THAT CLOSE?
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN SHE'S BORN,
DO YOU WANT HIM TO PUT HER UP
ON YOUR TUMMY, OR DO YOU
WANT HIM TO TAKE HER
RIGHT OVER TO THE WARMER
AND CLEAN HER UP?
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW
I'M GOING TO REACT.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I THINK YOU'LL WANT
TO HOLD HER.
>> OW, CONTRACTION.
>> BIG BREATH.
DEEP BREATH.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
>> SHE'S REALLY COMING, BABE.
PUSH.
KEEP GOING. KEEP GOING.
SHE'S OUT.
ASHLEY, SHE'S OUT.
>> THERE SHE IS!
>> SHE'S OUT.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS,
YOU'RE A GOOD-SIZED ONE.
>> SHE LOOKS LIKE JUSTIN.
>> SHE DOES?
>> IN THE NOSE.
>> LOOK AT ALL HER HAIR.
>> OH, SWEET GIRL.
>> RIGHT BETWEEN THE TUBES.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
SAY HI.
>> * 'CAUSE I CAN'T FIND *
* MY WAY HOME *
>> OH!
>> YES, SWEET GIRL.
>> YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
YOU HAD TO WORK HARD
FOR THAT LITTLE ONE TOO.
>> IS THAT YOUR CHIN?
YOU AND YOUR MOM HAVE
THE SAME NOSE TOO, SO...
YOU THINK SHE HAS YOUR NOSE?
>> OH, MAYBE SHE DOES.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE HER
TO SEE HOW MUCH SHE WEIGHS.
>> YOU'RE DOING A GOOD JOB,
BABY.
>> * 'CAUSE I CAN'T FIND *
* MY WAY *
* BROKE MY HEART *
* YOU BROKE MY HEART *
>> SHE'S PERFECT.
>> IS SHE REALLY?
>> PUT YOUR ARM UNDER
HER LITTLE HEAD.
>> HER SKIN'S SO SOFT.
>> EVEN THOUGH I WANT TO KEEP
EVERY SECOND OF THE 48 HOURS
TO MYSELF, I AGREED TO LET
MY AUNT LISA AND UNCLE KENNY
COME BY TO MEET THE BABY.
I'M TRYING TO BE STRONG,
BUT THE REALITY IS MORE
THAN I EXPECTED.
AND THEY LOVE YOU.
>> I KNOW, MOM, BUT I JUST--
>> I KNOW.
I'M JUST TRYING TO REMIND YOU
THAT THEY'RE NOT THE ENEMY.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU?
>> HI.
>> GOOD JOB.
>> Y'ALL CAN HOLD HER
IF Y'ALL WANT TO.
>> SHE'S CUTE.
CUTE, CUTE.
>> SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'LL SEE YOU.
>> BYE, THANKS.
>> GOOD JOB.
BYE.
[knock at door]
>> HI, MY NAME IS DEBORAH
WITH BIRTH CERTIFICATES.
I JUST WANTED TO COME IN
AND SEE IF YOU HAD
ANY QUESTIONS.
>> WE JUST FILL IT OUT
RIGHT NOW WITH JUST ASHLEY'S
INFORMATION AND THE BABY
AND DON'T WORRY ABOUT MY BROTHER
AND SISTER-IN-LAW AT ALL?
>> SINCE IT'S AN ADOPTION,
THEY WILL APPLY
FOR A NEW BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
AND ON THAT NEW BIRTH
CERTIFICATE, IT WILL HAVE...
>> THEIR NAME.
>> THEIR NAME AS THE MOTHER
AND THE FATHER.
>> IS MY NAME GOING TO BE
ON THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE?
>> YOUR NAME WILL BE
ON THE BABY'S ORIGINAL
BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
YES, IT WILL BE.
>> SHE'S GOING TO HAVE TWO?
>> SHE WILL HAVE TWO
UNTIL SHE'S 18.
THAT'S HOW IT NORMALLY HAPPENS
IN ADOPTIONS.
I MEAN, IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
EXPLAINED ALREADY.
I DON'T KNOW--
>> WELL, SINCE IT'S MY BROTHER
AND WE JUST REALLY HAVEN'T
GONE INTO DETAILS--
AND THAT'S THE THING, ASHLEY.
IT REALLY DOESN'T MATTER,
SWEETHEART, BECAUSE
SHE ALREADY KNOWS WHO YOU ARE.
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU.
YOU SURE?
>> YEAH, NOT RIGHT NOW.
>>* WHEN WE CHANGE *
* OUR MINDS *
* *
>> TOMORROW WHEN THEY
RELEASE YOU, I DON'T THINK
THEY'RE GOING TO KEEP YOU
TILL 7:00.
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE YOU'RE KIND OF
STUCK ON THIS 48-HOUR DEAL
AND THAT'S IT.
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK BY NOON, THEY FEEL
THAT YOU'RE OKAY TO GO.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT DON'T YOU KNOW?
>> I CAN'T MAKE A DECISION
THAT FAST.
>> ARE YOU STILL TRYING
TO MAKE A DECISION?
>> * SLEEP SOUND *
* SLEEP SOUND *
* SLEEP TO WAIT FOR CHANGE *
>> IT'S BEEN 36 HOURS,
AND I HAD NO IDEA THAT I'D DOUBT
MY DECISION LIKE THIS.
NOW IT'S 3:00 P.M., AND MY MOM
WANTS TO KNOW WHAT I WANT TO DO.
>> TIME IS RUNNING OUT.
AND KENNY AND LISA
ARE GOING TO BE OKAY
WITH WHATEVER YOU DECIDE.
THEY'RE CONCERNED WITH YOU.
>> WELL, I HAD DECIDED ALREADY
WHAT I WANTED TO DO.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK
THAT I WOULD, LIKE, RECONSIDER.
>> WELL, HAVE YOU GONE THROUGH
THE LIST OF THE REASONS
WHY YOU DECIDED TO GIVE HER UP
FOR ADOPTION?
>> YES, BUT FOR SOME REASON,
THEY JUST DON'T SEEM TO MATTER
ANYMORE.
>> I DID.
I HAD YOU YOUNG,
AND I HAD TO GROW UP,
AND I WASN'T A STAY-AT-HOME MOM,
AND I DIDN'T GET TO GO
TO YOUR SCHOOL FUNCTIONS, AND--
THOSE ARE ALL THE REASONS
THAT YOU DIDN'T WANT
ON YOUR LIST.
>> I JUST WISH
THAT I COULD DO IT.
>> I'LL SUPPORT
WHATEVER YOU DECIDE.
BUT I HOPE YOU'RE DOING IT
FOR HER.
'CAUSE IF YOU DO IT FOR YOU,
I DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE RIGHT DECISION.
I WANT TO HOLD HER.
I JUST WANT TO SNUGGLE HER
FOR A MINUTE.
I LOVE HER TOO.
IF I LET MY EMOTIONS MAKE
THE DECISION,
I WOULD KEEP HER TOO.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE HARD
TO SIGN THE PAPERS.
>> ARE YOU DECIDING, THEN,
YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING
TO GO THROUGH WITH IT?
>> YEAH.
I CAN'T REALLY THINK ABOUT--
I CAN'T THINK ABOUT MYSELF.
>> *I WAS MADE TO FLY *
* *
*I WAS MADE TO FLY *
>> IT IS COLD.
* *
[crying]
>> * I WAS MADE TO FLY *
* *
* I WAS... *
>> WE ASKED A NOTARY TO MEET US
AT MY AUNT JENNA'S HOUSE,
WHERE KENNY AND LISA
HAVE BEEN WAITING.
>> HI.
>> COME ON IN.
>> I'M TAMIKO. I'M A NOTARY.
>> LISA.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> YOU NEED TO FILL IN
THE PERTINENT INFORMATION,
'CAUSE I'M JUST THE NOTARY HERE.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO READ OVER
THE DOCUMENT.
I'M ONLY WITNESSING YOUR
SIGNATURE AND NOTARIZING, OKAY?
>> * MY LOVE FOR YOU *
* *
* YOUR LOVE FOR ME *
*OH, AND I'LL BE ALL RIGHT *
* YOU FEEL SO STRONG AND TRUE *
* OH, AND I'LL BE ALL RIGHT *
* WITH YOUR HANDS *
* TO HOLD ON TO *
*OH, AND I'LL BE ALL RIGHT *
*LONG AS YOU LOVE *
* TILL MY DAYS ARE THROUGH *
>> I WOKE UP THE NEXT MORNING
FEELING LIKE I HAD MADE
THE WRONG DECISION.
OVER THE NEXT FEW DAYS,
IT DIDN'T GET ANY EASIER.
I'M IGNORING ALL MY FRIENDS,
I HAVEN'T HEARD A WORD
FROM JUSTIN, AND I'VE NEVER FELT
SO MISERABLE.
>> IT'S OKAY TO BE UPSET.
>> I THINK IT'S GOING
TO GET EASIER EVERY DAY.
>> AND WHAT IF IT DOESN'T?
WHAT IF I'M LIKE THIS
EVERY SINGLE DAY?
>> YOU HONESTLY THINK
YOU MADE THE WRONG CHOICE?
>> YES.
I WOULD SERIOUSLY DRIVE
DOWN THERE RIGHT NOW.
I THINK I MADE
THE WRONG DECISION.
I STILL BELIEVE IN ADOPTION.
I JUST FEEL LIKE MAYBE
IN MY SITUATION,
I COULD HAVE KEPT HER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IS RIGHT
OR WRONG RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
I MISS HER.
I COULDN'T TAKE IT.
I BOUGHT A PLANE TICKET
AND CALLED KENNY AND LISA
TO TELL THEM I WAS COMING
TO GET MY DAUGHTER.
BY THE TIME I GOT THERE,
THEY'D HAD SOME TIME
TO GET USED TO THE IDEA,
AND THEY WERE SUPPORTIVE
OF ME TRYING TO PARENT.
LIKE, THIS IS WHAT I WANT TO DO.
LIKE, I WANT TO DO THIS,
AND I FEEL LIKE I CAN DO THIS.
>> WE JUST WANT TO SEE
THAT YOU'RE CONFIDENT.
"I CAN DO THIS.
I'M GOING TO BE THE BEST MOM
THAT I CAN BE."
>> BUT I ALSO WANT WHAT'S BEST
FOR HER, AND I'M JUST WORRIED
ABOUT, LIKE, THE FUTURE,
OF COURSE, 'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE FUTURE HOLDS
AND HOLD I'M GOING TO DEAL.
>> YOU MIGHT HAVE TO GROW UP
A LITTLE BIT,
START THINKING DIFFERENTLY.
AND IT'S ALL, YOU KNOW, FOR HER.
AND WE BELIEVE THAT YOU CAN
HANDLE THE CHALLENGE.
>> IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY,
BUT IT'S POSSIBLE.
IF WE THOUGHT YOU WERE IN
AN IMPOSSIBLE SITUATION,
WE'D--WE'D THINK TWICE
ABOUT TEARING UP ANY PAPERS
THAT HAVE BEEN SIGNED, OKAY?
BUT SHE'S JUST LOVELY.
>> WE LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I CAN--I'LL TAKE HER.
>> KENNY AND LISA WERE OPEN
TO GIVING ME TIME
TO TRY PARENTING.
I JUST NEED TO SPEND
MORE TIME WITH CALLIE
IN ORDER TO BE 100% SURE
WHAT THE RIGHT DECISION IS.
>> AND I'LL GET THE BABY.
>> NEITHER OF US WAS PREPARED
TO HAVE A BABY IN THE HOUSE.
MY SISTER, MIA, WENT TO STAY
WITH FAMILY WHILE WE FIGURE OUT
THIS WHOLE CALLIE SITUATION
HERE.
IT'S VERY CROWDED IN HERE.
>> WELL, IF YOU DECIDE
SHE'S GOING TO BE
WITH US PERMANENTLY,
WE'LL GET ALL THIS FURNITURE OUT
AND WE'LL JUST HAVE A NURSERY.
[Callie crying]
I NEED--I NEED A--
I JUST WANT TO CRY.
>> DON'T CRY.
>> I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I'M DOING
WITH THIS BOTTLE.
IT'S KIND OF COLD.
>> IT SURE IS.
DID YOU HEAT THIS
FOR TWO MINUTES--
I MEAN THREE MINUTES?
>> NO, BUT I HAD
REALLY HOT WATER.
>> IT HAS TO BOIL.
ASHLEY, ASHLEY.
IT'S OKAY, LOVE.
>> I GOT THROUGH MY FIRST NIGHT
AT HOME, BUT THE NEXT DAY,
I WAS ON MY OWN, AND THINGS GOT
A LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED.
OH, MY GOSH.
HOW AM I GOING TO GET THIS
OFF OF YOU?
[line ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> MOM.
>> YES?
>> CALLIE, LIKE, POOPED,
AND IT'S, LIKE, ALL OVER
HER LEGS AND HER CLOTHES
AND EVERYTHING.
[gasps]
IT IS SO MUCH.
IT'S ALL OVER HER BODY.
THIS IS DISGUSTING.
I'M GOING TO THROW UP.
>> WELL, ASH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
CHANGE HER CLOTHES.
>> NO, DO I PUT HER
IN THE SINK OR SOMETHING?
I DON'T WANT TO, LIKE--
>> NO, NO.
JUST GET WIPIES, WIPE HER DOWN,
AND THEN IF YOU STILL FEEL
LIKE SHE'S DIRTY,
GET A LITTLE WASHCLOTH--
>> LET ME CALL YOU BACK.
>> OKAY, BYE-BYE.
>> BYE.
OH, MY GOSH.
OKAY.
WHEN MY MOM GOT HOME,
SHE WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT HOW THIS TRIAL PERIOD
IS GOING TO WORK.
>> DO YOU HAVE A SET OF,
"IF THIS HAPPENS,
I WANT TO KEEP HER,
BUT IF I'M FEELING THIS,
I THINK I SHOULDN'T"?
OR WHAT ARE YOU MEASURING?
HOW ARE GOING TO KNOW?
>> I KEEP SAYING, LIKE,
I WANT WHAT'S BEST FOR HER.
LIKE, I REALLY--
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SCARED TO, LIKE, MAKE
A WRONG DECISION AGAIN.
BUT I DON'T SEE
HOW I COULD BE WITHOUT HER.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I NEED
A LOT OF TIME TO DECIDE.
>> I MEAN, IT'S YOUR DECISION,
RIGHT?
>> HEY.
>> MY FRIENDS CAME OVER
AS SOON AS THEY HEARD
I WAS HOME WITH CALLIE.
>> AW.
>> SHE WANTS HER MOMMY'S FINGER.
>> MY HANDS ARE CLEAN.
OH, THAT FEELS SO FUNNY.
[laughter]
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
NOW WITH SCHOOL,
SINCE YOU HAVE HER?
>> WELL, I'M STILL GOING TO GO
TO SCHOOL.
LIKE, EITHER--LIKE, NO MATTER
WHAT, I WAS STILL ALWAYS GOING
TO GO.
I JUST--I JUST HAVE TO START
APPLYING.
>> ARE YOU STILL THINKING
ABOUT GOING
TO THAT NEW YORK SCHOOL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT REALLY JUST DEPENDS.
LIKE--
>> YEAH.
>> I KNOW, LIKE,
APPLICATION DEADLINES
ARE COMING UP.
>> OH, YEAH, I'VE ALREADY
APPLIED AND EVERYTHING.
>> OH, YOU DID?
>> YEAH, I JUST HAVE TO WAIT.
>> WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
I HAVEN'T EVEN BOTHERED WITH IT.
>> I COULD NOT IMAGINE, LIKE,
APPLYING AND TAKING CARE
OF A BABY.
LIKE, IT WAS ALREADY HARD ENOUGH
TO, LIKE, JUST APPLY.
>> YEAH.
[sighs]
I KEPT PUTTING OFF
WORKING ON MY APPLICATIONS
TO FOCUS ON CALLIE,
AND NOW THEY'RE DUE TOMORROW.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO, BUT I KNOW I NEED
TO KEEP MY OPTIONS OPEN.
[Callie cries]
>> OKAY, YOU'RE ALL SET.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
>> APPLYING TO COLLEGE
IN NEW YORK WAS HARD ENOUGH
WITH A BABY TO CARE FOR.
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE
ACTUALLY ATTENDING.
[Callie crying]
OW.
>> HEY, BABY, WHEREVER
YOU'RE THROWING HER PAMPERS OUT,
YOU NEED TO EMPTY THE TRASH
OFTEN.
YOU CAN'T JUST LET IT SIT
AND FILL UP.
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ANY MORE
ABOUT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT
TO GIVE HER BACK.
>> YOU NEED TO WORK
THIS SEMESTER IF YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BE IN SCHOOL.
>> I KNOW THAT.
I'M JUST SCARED TO LEAVE HER
WITH ANYBODY.
I JUST DON'T FEEL SAFE,
LEAVING HER WITH ANYONE ELSE.
>> CAN I HOLD HER?
HEY, LITTLE STINKER.
WHAT YOU'RE FEELING IS NORMAL,
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO FIND
A WAY TO BE OKAY WITH IT.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE, MAYBE THIS IS
THE WRONG CHOICE
IF SHE'S GOING TO BE
IN DAYCARE ALL THE TIME.
>> AND THEN IF YOU DON'T
WANT THAT FOR HER,
THEN AT SOME POINT,
YOU HAVE TO DECIDE
WHETHER OR NOT SHE'S GOING
TO KENNY AND LISA'S.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO--
LIKE, I CAN'T BE WITHOUT HER.
>> YOU DON'T THINK YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO JUST FUNCTION
AND GO ON WITH LIFE ONCE YOU
GET BUSY IN COLLEGE AND--
>> EITHER WAY, YOU DON'T KNOW.
AND EITHER WAY, IT FEELS LIKE
IT'S STILL SCARY.
>> KENNY AND LISA SHIPPED UP
ENOUGH BABY SUPPLIES
TO GET US THROUGH
THE FIRST FEW WEEKS.
AND EVEN THOUGH IT'S A TRIAL
PERIOD, I STILL WANTED
TO GET CALLIE A REAL CRIB
TO SLEEP IN.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU NEED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> LOOK HOW PRETTY THAT IS.
>> THAT IS.
>> IT'S $580 FOR ALL OF THAT?
>> I THINK THAT'S $1,000.
>> LOOK AT THAT CHAIR.
>> OH, I THOUGHT IT SAID $19.99.
$139.99.
>> IT'S MORE
THAN THE HIGH CHAIR.
>> THAT'S REALLY PRETTY, THOUGH.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD WAIT,
AT LEAST A COUPLE OF WEEKS,
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW
IF YOUR DECISION'S MADE.
I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'VE THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
AVOIDING IT.
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT WE SHOULD WAIT.
AT SOME POINT--I'M NOT
RUSHING YOU AT ALL...
>> I KNOW.
>> I NEED AN ANSWER,
BECAUSE SHE CAN'T SLEEP
IN A PLAYPEN FOREVER.
>> I KNOW.
>> OKAY.
[Callie crying]
PART OF HAVING CALLIE HERE
MEANS THAT I HAVE TO CONTRIBUTE
FINANCIALLY.
I KEPT UP MY END
OF THE BARGAIN AND AGREED
TO LOOK FOR PART-TIME WORK,
BUT THE LONGER I GO
WITHOUT A DECISION,
THE MORE TENSE THINGS GET
IN THE HOUSE.
MY MOM AND I NEVER WORKED OUT
WHO WOULD HAVE
WHAT RESPONSIBILITIES.
>> THIS BOX HAS BEEN SITTING
IN HER ROOM, COLLECTING TRASH.
THAT'S THE BAG OF DIAPERS
THAT SIT ON HER DOOR.
I THINK WRITING DOWN
WHO'S RESPONSIBLE FOR WHAT
SO THAT WHY, THERE'S NOT
ANY MORE CONFUSION.
I INITIALLY TOLD YOU
I WOULD HELP YOU WITH,
YOU KNOW, FINANCIAL,
BUT I ENVISION YOU USING
YOUR MONEY TO SUPPORT CALLIE
AS MUCH AS YOU CAN,
AND THEN WHATEVER YOU CAN'T,
I'LL MAKE UP THE DIFFERENCE.
BUT YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW MANY HOURS
YOU'RE GOING TO WORK.
>> WELL, JUST DO 15,
'CAUSE THAT'S MINIMUM PART-TIME,
PRETTY MUCH.
AND IF I MAKE $7.90,
WHICH ISN'T A LOT,
THAT'S, LIKE, MY WHOLE PAYCHECK.
>> WELL, SHE'S YOUR DAUGHTER,
RIGHT.
MY WHOLE PAYCHECK GOES TO Y'ALL.
>> WELL, WRITE IT DOWN THEN,
I GUESS.
>> I CANNOT MAKE A COMMITMENT
TO BABYSIT IN THE EVENING,
BECAUSE I NEVER KNOW WHEN
MY EVENING EVENTS
ARE GOING TO BE.
BUT IF I'M AVAILABLE
AND I'M HOME, I WILL HELP YOU.
I'M NOT GETTING UP AT NIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, I'M WILLING
TO BABYSIT, I GUESS,
ONE WEEKEND A MONTH
IF YOU WANT TO GO OUT
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
>> A MONTH?
>> YEAH, I MEAN--
WHAT ELSE ARE YOU THINKING
THAT YOU WANT ME TO DO?
>> NOTHING...ANYMORE.
>> 'CAUSE I HAVE A WHOLE LIST
OF THINGS FOR YOU TO DO AT HOME.
>> OKAY.
>> IF SHE'S GOING TO STAY,
I DON'T WANT HER DIAPERS
TO PILE UP LIKE THEY DO
RIGHT NOW.
>> THE TRASH CAN IS ALWAYS FULL.
>> OKAY, THEN TAKE OUT
THE TRASH.
>> OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
>> OKAY, I DON'T WANT
TO DO THIS.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU'RE JUST IMPOSSIBLE
TO TALK TO.
YOU CAN FIGURE IT OUT
ON YOUR OWN.
>> CAN WE PLEASE JUST--
>> NO, ASHLEY,
I WANT YOU TO GROW UP.
I'VE ALREADY RAISED MY KIDS,
AND I DON'T WANT TO GO AROUND
TELLING YOU HOW TO RAISE YOURS.
I WANT YOU TO DO IT.
>> THIS IS NOT HOW I THOUGHT
HAVING CALLIE WOULD BE.
IN MY HEART, I'M FEELING
THAT PARENTING ISN'T RIGHT.
BUT IT STILL FEELS IMPOSSIBLE
TO BE WITHOUT CALLIE.
>> SHE'S SO CUTE.
I'M SURPRISED YOU GOT CALLIE.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO, LIKE,
NOT TRY.
I'VE HAD HER
FOR ABOUT A MONTH NOW.
IT'S A LOT HARDER THAN
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE.
IT'S NOT JUST, LIKE,
CHANGING DIAPERS
AND FEEDING HER.
I ALWAYS HAVE TO, LIKE, WORRY
ABOUT HER FUTURE AND STUFF.
>> I BET.
>> YEAH.
WHEN I SAW CALLIE
IN THE HOSPITAL, ALL OF
MY ORIGINAL REASONS
FOR CHOOSING ADOPTION
WENT OUT THE DOOR.
I WAS TRYING TO CHOOSE
A BETTER FUTURE FOR BOTH OF US:
COLLEGE FOR ME
AND A STABLE HOME FOR HER.
IN MY GUT, I STILL FEEL
LIKE I WAS RIGHT,
BUT I JUST WASN'T PREPARED
FOR THE GRIEVING PROCESS.
THERE IS NO WAY I CAN MAKE
A FINAL DECISION WITHOUT HELP,
SO MY MOM SUGGESTED
WE ASK ASHLEY
FROM THE ADOPTION AGENCY
TO COME BACK.
>> HI, LISA, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> ASHLEY'S HAVING A HARD TIME
MAKING A DECISION.
AND JUST KIND OF FEEL LIKE
SHE REALLY, REALLY WANTS
TO PROCEED WITH THE ADOPTION,
BUT SHE JUST CAN'T, YOU KNOW,
COME TO TERMS WITH IT.
>> I KNOW.
WE HAVE DECIDED TO BRING ASHLEY
FROM GLADNEY BACK
INTO THE PICTURE, BECAUSE
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
THAT SHE'S REALLY EVER
CONNECTED WITH.
AND I THINK THIS IS PROBABLY
GOING TO HELP HER FIND PEACE
IN THE DECISION,
WHICHEVER WAY SHE DECIDES TO GO.
>> YEAH.
>> both: HI.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK
IS GOING TO GET YOU TO A PLACE
TO MAKE A DECISION,
WHATEVER IT IS?
>> I THOUGHT I MADE MY DECISION.
BUT I THINK ONE THING,
AND THEN SOMETHING COMES UP,
AND I THINK ANOTHER THING,
AND IT'S HARD TO STICK
TO ONE DECISION.
>> IT'S NEVER GOING TO FEEL
100% RIGHT, EITHER WAY,
PARENTING OR NOT.
IT'S NOT.
BUT THERE IS STRENGTH
IN BOTH OF THEM, AND I THINK
THAT YOU'RE GETTING CAUGHT UP
IN WEAKNESS.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
>> LIKE, KENNY AND LISA,
THEY CAN GUARANTEE HER A FUTURE
AND COLLEGE, AND I CAN'T
EVEN GUARANTEE HER
HER FUTURE RIGHT NOW.
SOMETIMES I THINK, LIKE,
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE WENT
AND GOT HER--
JUST, LIKE, DEALT WITH IT
IF I WAS GOING TO MAKE
THE DECISION ANYWAY.
>> BUT YOU HAVE THE CONFIDENCE
TO KNOW THAT YOU TRIED
AND YOU DID IT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE TO
THINK, "WHAT IF I NEVER TRIED?"
DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU COULD CALL THEM, OR--
>> I GUESS I HAVE TO.
[line ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> LISA?
>> HEY, ASH.
>> I'M HERE WITH ASHLEY
FROM GLADNEY, THE COUNSELOR.
AND WE WERE JUST TALKING
AND, LIKE, SORTING THROUGH
EVERYTHING.
AND I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT IT.
I JUST THINK THE BEST THING
IS NOT WITH ME, 'CAUSE I JUST
THINK Y'ALL CAN GUARANTEE HER
BETTER THAN WHAT I CAN.
>> IF YOU FEEL LIKE
THE BEST THING FOR CALLIE
IS TO BE WITH US,
THEN WE WANT--YOU KNOW,
WE WANT TO.
BUT I JUST WANT YOU TO REALLY
BE VERY, VERY SURE,
BECAUSE WE JUST--WE'RE AFRAID.
WE DON'T WANT TO DO
THE BACK AND FORTH.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> IT'S HARD ON ALL OF US.
>> I WOULDN'T HAVE--
LIKE, I DON'T WANT HER
BACK AND FORTH.
>> SO WHAT TIME FRAME
ARE YOU THINKING, ASHLEY?
>> I THINK THIS WEEKEND,
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU GUYS.
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT
TO PROLONG IT.
>> RIGHT, RIGHT.
WELL, WE LOVE YOU, ASHLEY.
>> I KNOW.
I LOVE YOU GUYS TOO.
>> OKAY.
>> TALK TO YOU LATER.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> BYE-BYE.
>> SO HOW DO YOU FEEL?
I MEAN, YOU JUST BASICALLY MADE
A DECISION.
>> I MEAN, I FEEL OKAY.
I JUST FEEL REALLY SAD.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
YOU'VE REALLY DONE THE WORK.
YOU HAVEN'T JUST MADE
THESE REALLY DRASTIC, FAST
DECISIONS.
YOU WILL SEE HER AGAIN.
>> TOMORROW
CALLIE IS HEADING BACK
TO LIVE WITH MY AUNT AND UNCLE.
SO WE HAVE TO PACK UP
ALL THE BABY STUFF
THAT THEY SHIPPED UP.
HI.
TAKING CALLIE TO HARLINGEN
BY MYSELF WOULD JUST BE
TOO MUCH, SO MY MOM AGREED
TO DO IT FOR ME.
AND MY FRIEND SHELLEY
IS COMING OVER SO I DON'T
HAVE TO BE ALONE
AFTER THEY LEAVE.
THANKS FOR COMING.
>> WHAT TIME IS SHE LEAVING?
>> SOON.
YEAH.
I STILL MISS CALLIE A LOT.
I THINK I'LL MISS HER
EVERY SINGLE DAY
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
>> OKAY.
>> NO MATTER WHAT,
I JUST SEE HER BEING LOVED
AND TAKEN CARE OF.
NOW I UNDERSTAND SOMEWHAT
WHAT IT WAS LIKE FOR MY MOM
TO HAVE ME SO YOUNG
AND THE HARD DECISIONS
THAT SHE HAD TO FACE.
I KIND OF WANTED TO END
THAT PATTERN.
WHAT I DO TO PUSH ASIDE
THE BAD FEELINGS OF MISSING HER
AND WANTING HER BACK
IS JUST FOCUSING ON THE FUTURE
AND MOVING ON.
I JUST KNOW THAT I'M GOING
TO GO TO COLLEGE,
GET A CAREER, AND MOVE ON
WITH MY LIFE.
>> OKAY, YOU GUYS READY
TO START THE TOUR?
WHAT'S SO GREAT ABOUT
THE NEW SCHOOL SPECIFICALLY IS,
WE'RE IN GREENWICH VILLAGE,
WHICH IS A VERY UNIQUE
NEIGHBORHOOD IN NEW YORK CITY.
* *
>> I CAN SEE YOU HERE.
>> I WISH THIS WOULD HAVE
HAPPENED, LIKE,
YEARS DOWN THE ROAD
SO THAT WAY, I COULD STILL HAVE
THE SAME BABY AND BE ABLE
TO RAISE HER AND GIVE HER
A GOOD LIFE.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com