>> HI, I'M CLEONDRA.
HELLO.
[laughs]
I'M 17 YEARS OLD AND FROM
HORN LAKE, MISSISSIPPI--
RIGHT ACROSS THE RIVER FROM
MEMPHIS, TENNESSEE.
I LOVE TO DANCE.
AND LAST YEAR, MY SCHOOL DANCE
TEAM MADE IT ALL THE WAY TO THE
NATIONAL TOURNAMENT.
NOW I'M A SENIOR, AND I CAN'T
WAIT TO GO OFF TO COLLEGE
AND STUDY PHYSICAL THERAPY.
MY MOM RAISED FOUR KIDS,
SO MY HOUSE HAS ALWAYS BEEN
KIND OF HECTIC.
>> RAH!
ESPECIALLY AFTER MY SISTER
ZERICA HAD HER BABY.
SHE WAS ONLY 17 AND REALLY
STRUGGLED WITH MOTHERHOOD
IN THE BEGINNING.
>> I HAD TO GET USED TO THIS,
CLEONDRA.
I WASN'T USED TO THIS.
>> SO I'VE SPENT THE LAST TWO
YEARS HELPING MY MOM RAISE
MY NIECE.
LUCKILY, I DIDN'T HAVE TO GO FAR
TO MEET MY BOYFRIEND, MARIO.
LOOK OUT YOUR WINDOW.
>> HEY, BABY.
>> HE LIVES RIGHT ACROSS
THE STREET.
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER A COUPLE
OF YEARS, BUT LATELY,
WE HAVEN'T SPENT MUCH QUALITY
TIME TOGETHER BECAUSE HE WORKS
SO MUCH.
AND WHEN HE GETS HOME, HE'S
ALWAYS TOO TIRED TO DO
ANYTHING FUN.
BUT MARIO'S NOT GONNA GET MUCH
SLEEP NOW.
AND ZYRA'S NOT GONNA BE
THE BABY OF THE FAMILY ANYMORE
EITHER, BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
LIVING ACROSS THE STREET
FROM MARIO IS GREAT.
HE MOVED THERE WITH HIS DAD
A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO, AND IT
DIDN'T TAKE US LONG TO NOTICE
EACH OTHER.
I REMEMBER WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU.
YOU WERE WALKING TO JESSE'S VAN.
YOU JUST HAD A JACKET,
AND YOU WERE SHIRTLESS.
I WAS LIKE, "DAMN, HE'S FINE."
>> I WAS PHYSICALLY ATTRACTED
TO YOU.
>> [laughs]
>> THEN I GOT TO KNOW YOU AND
THOUGHT YOU WERE PRETTY COOL.
>> WHEN WE FIRST FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT, I WAS SCARED.
>> YOU GOT A LITTLE BABY
IN YOUR STOMACH.
>> I WAS SHAKING.
RIGHT WHEN I FOUND OUT,
I WAS JUST, LIKE--
"I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO."
>> I'M STILL A LITTLE, UM,
WORRIED, I GUESS, ABOUT IT.
LIFE'S DIFFICULT ENOUGH WITHOUT
TAKING CARE OF A BABY.
>> IT'S LIKE I'M USED TO IT.
'CAUSE I ALREADY, LIKE, I AM
LIKE A MOM TO ZYRA, AND IT'S
LIKE I ALREADY BEEN THROUGH THE
WHOLE NEWBORN STAGE AND...
>> YEAH.
>> GROWING UP TO TWO AND...
>> I HOPE YOUR MOM OR JUST
SOMEBODY DOESN'T THINK THAT
WE'RE GONNA BE RAISING TWO
AT THE SAME TIME.
IT DOESN'T SOUND TOO GOOD
OF A SITUATION TO ME.
>> MARIO IS RIGHT.
THERE'S NO WAY I'LL BE ABLE
TO HANDLE TWO KIDS AT ONCE.
BYE, BABE.
>> BYE.
>> BUT SINCE MY SISTER JUST KIND
OF COMES AND GOES, MY MOM HAS
ALWAYS RELIED ON ME
TO HELP RAISE ZYRA.
GO TO MY ROOM.
BE CAREFUL.
>> BOUNCY, BOUNCY.
QUICKLY, QUICKLY, QUICKLY.
>> ZYRA, STOP.
>> RAH!
>> ZYRA CAN DEFINITELY BE
A HANDFUL SOMETIMES, SO MY MOM
WASN'T THRILLED WHEN I TOLD HER
ANOTHER GRANDBABY
WAS ON THE WAY.
>> HOW IN THE WORLD DID YOU
END UP PREGNANT?
HOW DID YOU FEEL?
>> MY HEART SANK.
AND I COULDN'T STOP CRYING
'CAUSE I WAS DISAPPOINTED
IN MYSELF.
>> AND I WAS SO ANGRY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> BECAUSE OF THE FACT THAT I
MADE IT A POINT TO MAKE SURE
WE'D HAD YOU THE BIG OLD BOX
OF CONDOMS AND WAS READING ALL
THE PAMPHLETS OF SAFE SEX.
SO IT WAS VERY...
YOU SAID YOUR HEART DROPPED.
SO DID MINE.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE LOOKING
BACK ON IT 'CAUSE IT STILL
DISAPPOINTS ME.
>> I THOUGHT THAT YOU WOULDN'T
END UP IN THE SITUATION
YOU'RE IN, AND I THOUGHT YOU
WAS A LITTLE MORE CAREFUL
AND CAUTIOUS THAN WHAT YOU WERE.
AND THAT'S WHAT HURT THE MOST.
AT THE BEGINNING, YOU AGREED
ON HAVING AN ABORTION.
YOU WANTED TO HAVE THE ABORTION.
>> HE GOT THE MONEY
AND EVERYTHING FOR IT.
AND THEN, LIKE, YOU HAD TO HAVE
A PARENT CONSENT ON IT, OR YOU
COULD DO THIS THING, LIKE,
JUDICIAL BYPASS.
BUT, LIKE, YOU HAD TO GO IN
FRONT OF A JUDGE AND EVERYTHING,
AND IT'S TOO CRUCIAL, SO I WAS
JUST, LIKE, I'M GONNA HAVE TO
TALK TO MY MOM.
>> AND I WAS ALL FOR YOU
HAVING THE ABORTION BECAUSE OF
YOUR FUTURE.
AND I DIDN'T WANT NOTHING
HOLDING YOU BACK, BECAUSE YOU'RE
SUCH A BRIGHT GIRL.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THE
RESPONSIBLE CHILD, AND I HATE
FEELING LIKE I LET MY MOM DOWN.
MY FAMILY IS PRETTY TIGHT.
WE HAVE TO BE IN SUCH
A LITTLE HOUSE.
>> CLEONDRA'S A CHEATER.
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO--
[laughing]
>> BUT SINCE I GOT PREGNANT,
THINGS HAVE BEEN A BIT MORE
TENSE.
>> THE MOST THING THAT MADE ME
UPSET WAS, FOR ONE, YOU DIDN'T
TELL ME.
AND THEN ANOTHER THING, I JUST--
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WAS GONNA
BE PREGNANT AT AGE 16.
AND THEN YOU WAS ON DANCE TEAM.
YOU HAD A LOT OF THINGS GOING.
>> JAVON WAS MAD.
GOING AROUND DOING CRAZY STUFF.
>> SLAMMING DOORS.
>> both: PUNCHING WALLS.
AND STUFF.
>> 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
YOU WAS LIKE, "YOU'RE GONNA BE
AN UNCLE."
AND I WAS LIKE, "IS ZERICA
PREGNANT AGAIN?"
AND YOU WAS LIKE, "NO."
>> WHAT?
>> I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE
SMARTER THAN THAT.
BEING PREGNANT GONNA HOLD YOU
BACK FROM A LOT OF THINGS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE YOUR EVENTS
AND THEN THE DANCE TEAM.
YOU WAS ONLY IN IT FOR ONE YEAR
BEFORE YOU QUIT.
SO TWO YEARS COULD HAVE
GOT YOU A SCHOLARSHIP,
GOT YOU ON TO COLLEGE
OR SOMETHING--PAID FOR.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
NOW?
>> I MEAN, I'LL STILL DO
WHAT I DO.
I DON'T WANT THIS PREGNANCY
TO HOLD ME BACK FROM ANYTHING.
BUT I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO BE
A DANCER, AND NOT BEING ABLE TO
DANCE MY SENIOR YEAR
REALLY SUCKS.
I DON'T SEE MY FRIENDS AS MUCH
SINCE I QUIT THE DANCE TEAM.
BUT WHEN THEY HEARD I WAS HAVING
A LITTLE GIRL, THEY WANTED TO
GET TOGETHER AND CATCH UP.
>> I MISS DANCE.
>> I MISS DANCE TOO.
WE WERE REALLY GOOD, MAN.
WE MADE IT ALL THE WAY TO
NATIONALS.
>> WE WERE LIKE THIS.
>> I KNOW.
TEN SISTERS.
NOW WE'RE SO FAR APART.
>> AND YOU WERE BETTER THAN
A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT WAS ON IT.
>> I CAN'T DO NO HIGH "V"s
NO MORE.
>> HOW'S IT FEELING?
LIKE...HAS SHE BEEN KICKING?
>> AT NIGHT, IT'S LIKE SHE
TICKLES ME.
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S WEIRD.
>> SEE, I WANT TO KNOW WHAT
THAT FEELS LIKE.
>> IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE.
WHEN SHE, LIKE, ROLLS AND MOVES,
IT'S LIKE--
>> DOES IT HURT?
>> NO, IT JUST--
>> JUST, LIKE, FEELS FUNNY?
LIKE BUTTERFLIES?
>> I JUST CAN'T DO, LIKE,
NORMAL STUFF.
I CAN BARELY PICK ZYRA UP NOW.
>> DO, LIKE, YOU EVER, LIKE,
WONDER IF PEOPLE THINK YOU'RE...
A HO?
>> NO, I DON'T CARE.
'CAUSE THE PEOPLE I HANG OUT
WITH KNOW I AIN'T.
THEY KNOW I'VE BEEN WITH MARIO
SINCE FOREVER.
>> I USED TO, LIKE, BE LIKE,
"CAN YOU CLOSE YOUR LEGS
PLEASE?"
>> I KNOW.
>> LIKE, FOR REAL.
BUT THEN I WAS, LIKE, WELL,
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES IT'S--
>> IT JUST HAPPENS.
>> YEAH, IT JUST HAPPENS.
LIKE, THINGS HAPPEN.
>> LIKE, HE BLAMES HISSELF
FOR IT.
AND I'M JUST LIKE, "DON'T."
'CAUSE I WASN'T LIKE KICKING
AND SCREAMING AND BEING LIKE,
"GET OFF ME," SO...
[rock music]
I DON'T WANT TO BEAT MYSELF UP
OVER GETTING PREGNANT, BUT
MARIO STILL FEELS REALLY GUILTY
ABOUT IT.
AS SOON AS WE FOUND OUT, HE
DROPPED HIS PLANS TO JOIN THE
ARMY AND GOT A FULL-TIME JOB
AT THE TIRE SHOP.
AND SINCE MARIO HATES ALL THE
CHAOS AT MY HOUSE, HE STARTED
FIXING UP HIS PLACE BECAUSE I
THINK HE WANTS US TO LIVE THERE
WHEN THE BABY COMES.
LOOK AT THESE.
THEY'RE SO CUTE.
SEE? IT SAYS "LITTLE PRINCESS."
>> I'M TIRED.
>> WHAT'S OUR PLAN, LIKE,
GONNA BE FOR, LIKE--
LIKE WHEN SHE GETS HERE?
>> LIKE WHERE SHE'S GONNA LIVE
AND WHERE YOU'RE GONNA LIVE?
>> YEAH.
SHE'S PROBABLY GONNA STAY,
LIKE, HERE, LIKE, AT THE
BEGINNING A LOT MORE.
>> I AIN'T GONNA BE OVER HERE.
I'M GONNA BE IN MY ROOM
IN MY BED ASLEEP AT 6:00.
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE HELPING ME
WITH HER.
>> I AM?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M JUST SAYING I'M NOT GONNA
BE SPENDING THE NIGHT HERE.
>> I MEAN, I WOULD LIKE FOR YOU
TO, LIKE, WHEN, LIKE,
SHE'S FIRST HERE.
>> I MEAN, YEAH, THAT'D BE
GREAT, BUT--
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO BE HERE,
LIKE, WHEN SHE FIRST GETS HERE
UNTIL SHE GETS, LIKE,
ON A SCHEDULE.
'CAUSE MOM SAID SHE'D LET ME
SLEEP AT YOUR HOUSE.
BUT IT'S NOT GONNA BE, LIKE, A--
YOU KNOW, AN EVERYDAY THING IS.
>> SO WHAT YOU WERE SAYING IS
YOUR MOM SAID IT WAS OKAY FOR
MY DAUGHTER TO SPEND THE NIGHT
AT MY HOUSE?
>> 'CAUSE, I MEAN, YOU KNOW YOU
JUST CAN'T PLAN A LOT OF STUFF
UNTIL SHE GETS HERE.
>> WHAT IS THERE REALLY--
I DON'T SEE WHAT YOU REALLY
CAN'T PLAN ABOUT A BABY.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE EXPECTING
A BABY AND WE'RE GONNA GET,
LIKE, A LITTLE--A COYOTE
OR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, WE KNOW WHAT
WE'RE GETTING.
WE'RE GETTING A BABY.
AND WH--EVERYTHING WE WOULD NEED
TO PLAN OUT, I DON'T SEE WHY WE
COULDN'T PLAN IT OUT
JUST 'CAUSE THE KID'S
IN YOUR STOMACH.
>> I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO?
>> YOU--US THREE LIVING THERE
IS JUST...
EASIEST SITUATION IN EVERY WAY.
A FAMILY LIVING UNDER THE SAME
ROOF IS JUST...
NORMAL.
>> I KNOW IT'S NORMAL, BUT
USUALLY, WITH TEEN PREGNANCIES,
THAT'S NOT HOW THEY
ALL PLAY OUT.
>> WE GOT A GREAT PLAN.
NO PLAN.
>> I LOVE THAT MARIO WANTS US
TO LIVE TOGETHER AS A FAMILY,
BUT THE THOUGHT OF LEAVING HOME
IS MAKING ME NERVOUS.
>> TONIGHT IS ME AND MARIO'S
TWO-YEAR ANNIVERSARY.
>> DRINK, JOEY.
DRINK, DRINK, DRINK, DRINK.
OH!
>> AS USUAL, IT'S A LITTLE ROWDY
AT MY HOUSE, SO MARIO DECIDED
HE'D RATHER COOK DINNER FOR US
AT HIS HOUSE.
>> OH, HELL YEAH.
THIS IS GOOD, BUDDY.
SON, YOU'RE 19 YEARS OLD.
I LOVE CLEONDRA TO DEATH,
BUT I WANT MY GRANDBABY TO BE
IN A HOME WITH NOTHING GOING ON,
NOTHING HAPPENING, OR WHATEVER,
YOU KNOW?
>> I'VE ALREADY TALKED TO HER
ABOUT MOVING IN THE HOUSE
ONCE THE BABY'S BORN.
I WANT MY KID TO GROW UP
HAVING WHAT I HAD.
I WANT MY KID TO GROW UP HAVING
HER OWN ROOM, HAVING HER OWN
THINGS, HAVING HER OWN PLACE
TO GO TO, HAVING HER OWN TWO SET
OF PARENTS.
>> YEAH.
[door squeaks]
>> HEY, CLEO.
IT'S ANNIVERSARY TIME.
>> YOU DIDN'T WANT TO GO
ANYWHERE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO TAKE ME
SOMEWHERE.
I MEAN, JUST AS LONG I WAS
SPENDING IT WITH YOU, I MEAN,
THAT'S ALL I REALLY WANTED.
>> SHRIMP IS GOOD.
>> IT'S DELICIOUS.
THANK YOU, BABY.
WANT TO HELP ME DO SOME
HOMEWORK?
COME ON.
[groans]
>> SCHOOL.
>> YEAH, THIS IS FOR SCHOOL.
AFTER I GOT PREGNANT, MY MOM
MADE ME PROMISE I'D STILL
GRADUATE HIGH SCHOOL THIS YEAR.
BUT MY HOUSE CAN BE A DIFFICULT
PLACE TO STUDY SOMETIMES.
>> ALGEBRA II.
>> WHAT COLOR?
>> A PENCIL.
>> TROPHY.
NO.
DON'T WIPE YOUR MOUTH
ON MY BLANKET.
IT'S OBVIOUS I'M NOT GOING TO
GET ANYTHING DONE HERE, SO I
DECIDED TO MEET UP WITH MY
FRIENDS AT THE LIBRARY SO I CAN
GET SOME WORK DONE.
>> YOU LOOK PREGNANT TODAY.
>> THANKS.
>> HOW'RE YOU FEELING?
>> FAT.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> LIKE, I DON'T WANT TO CRY,
BUT, LIKE, IT'S SO DIFFERENT.
LIKE, YOU'RE HAVING, LIKE,
A BABY.
LIKE, OH, MY GOSH.
>> GIRL, PLEASE STOP.
[laughter]
>> I REMEMBER CRYING
WHEN YOU TOLD ME.
I DIDN'T SEE IT AS, LIKE,
HOW YOU'RE SEEING IT NOW.
I KIND OF JUST SEEN IT AS,
LIKE, YOU DON'T HAVE A LIFE
ANYMORE.
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE SUCH A GOOD
MOM, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, YOU'VE ALREADY
HALFWAY DONE IT NOW
WITH ZYRA.
YOU PRETTY MUCH GOT THE BASICS
OF IT.
>> ONLY THING I'M GONNA HAVE TO
DO NEW IS, LIKE--LIKE,
FINANCIAL STUFF; THAT'S IT.
>> SO, LIKE, HOW LONG DO YOU
PLAN TO, LIKE, GO TO SCHOOL?
LIKE--YOU KNOW, LIKE,
HOW MANY DAYS YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE OUT?
>> PROBABLY JUST STAY OUT
THE TWO WEEKS OF CHRISTMAS
VACATION AND THEN COME BACK
IN JANUARY WITH EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> AT LEAST YOU GOT THAT
FIGURED OUT SO THAT YOU CAN
COME BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO STAY
OUT OF SCHOOL LONG 'CAUSE I
DON'T WANT TO BE BEHIND.
I HATE BEING BEHIND.
>> ARE YOUR GRADES GOOD NOW?
>> HEY, GOOD JOB.
DOING BETTER THAN ME.
WHEN THE BABY GETS HERE,
LIKE, WHERE'S SHE GONNA STAY,
LIKE, FOR SURE?
>> I MEAN, LIKE, WE BOTH--
LIKE, I HAVE A CRIB AT MY HOUSE
AND MARIO HAS A CRIB
IN HIS HOUSE.
BUT IT'S, LIKE, IF I STAY
AT MY HOUSE, IT'S, LIKE,
THAT'S WHERE, LIKE,
ALL THE HELP'S AT.
'CAUSE, LIKE, MOM, ROB,
AND THAT'S WHERE, LIKE,
ELIZABETH COMES AND VISITS AT.
>> DOES MARIO WANT TO STAY
AT YOUR HOUSE?
WHY?
>> I SERIOUSLY DON'T KNOW.
IT DOES NOT MAKE SENSE TO ME.
>> HE WON'T GIVE YOU
A REASON OR--
>> HE JUST SAYS HE LIKES
SLEEPING AT HIS HOUSE.
>> DO YOU THINK WHEN THE BABY'S
GET HERE, IT'S GONNA BE, LIKE,
A BIG PROBLEM?
>> I DON'T THINK IT WILL BE,
'CAUSE, I MEAN, HE'S GONNA BE
WANTING TO SEE HER.
AND I'M GONNA BE LIKE,
"YOU'RE GONNA COME OVER HERE."
'CAUSE I HAVE LEVERAGE NOW.
[laughing]
I HAVE LEVERAGE.
[instrumental music]
>> LOOK WHO'S HOME.
>> HEY, ZYRA.
>> BIG FAVOR.
SHE NEEDS TO POTTY, BE CHANGED.
KEEP YOUR EYES ON THE MUNCHKIN
TILL HER MOMMY GETS HOME.
>> WHEN IS SHE COMING HOME?
>> I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> LET'S GO POTTY.
GONNA GO PEE?
GET ON THE POT.
IT'S HARD TAKING CARE OF ZYRA
WHEN I HAVE SO MANY OTHER THINGS
IN MIND, BUT SHE REALLY DEPENDS
ON ME, AND EVEN THOUGH MARIO
WANTS ME TO MOVE IN WITH HIM,
I'M NOT SURE IT'S THE BEST THING
FOR MY FAMILY RIGHT NOW.
[laughing]
* *
I OFFERED TO COOK MARIO DINNER
TONIGHT, BUT IT SEEMS LIKE HE
NEVER WANTS TO HANG OUT
AT MY HOUSE ANYMORE.
>> OH!
>> EVEN THOUGH HE LIVES ACROSS
THE STREET WITH HIS DAD, HIS MOM
LIVES RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER
FROM US, AND HE'D RATHER HAVE
DINNER OVER THERE.
>> SO WE ARE GONNA HAVE TO
TALK ABOUT THIS.
'CAUSE MOM DOESN'T WANT TO BE
CALLED GRANDMA.
BEING THE FIRST GRANDCHILD,
I JUST AM NOT PREPARED TO BE
CALLED GRANDMA OR GRANDMOTHER
OR GRANNY OR ME-MA.
>> I MEAN, YOU'RE A GRANDMA.
I DON'T SEE WHAT'S SO WRONG
ABOUT BEING CALLED A GRANDMA.
>> FOR ME, I WILL FEEL
VERY OLD--90, YOU KNOW.
Y'ALL ARE GONNA HAVE TO CHOOSE
BETWEEN NONA, GIGI,
OR YA-YA.
>> GRANDMA.
I WILL NOT BE CALLED GRANDMA.
>> YEAH, YOU WILL.
IT'S GONNA HAPPEN.
>> SO WE'RE GOING WITH GRANDMA?
>> WE CAN ALWAYS PICK
SOME BABY NAMES.
THE ONES I LIKE.
>> WHAT NAMES HAVE Y'ALL COME UP
WITH?
LET'S GET TO A NEUTRAL SUBJECT.
SO WE'RE KIND OF CONSIDERING
TWILIGHT.
>> NO, THEY'RE NOT.
THEY'RE NOT CONSIDERING IT.
>> I'M LIKING TWILIGHT.
>> WHAT ABOUT BROOKLYN?
I STILL LIKE THAT.
>> NO.
>> WHAT ABOUT AMIRA?
I HAD THAT PAGE TURNED
IN THE BABY BOOK FOR AMIRA.
NO.
>> CAMBRIA'S PRETTY.
>> OH, CAMBRIA IS PRETTY.
CLEONDRA, WHAT NAMES WERE YOU
LOOKING AT IN THERE?
>> JUST GIRL NAMES.
>> WELL...
>> ANY THAT YOU WANT TO SHARE?
>> NO.
I DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
>> WE HAVE A TRUCE.
>> MAYBE WE SHOULD GO EAT NOW.
>> LISTENING TO EVERYONE
SUGGEST BABY NAMES IS AWKWARD,
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE MARIO AND I
SHOULD BE THE ONES TO COME UP
WITH THE NAME.
>> WHAT--SO WHAT ARE SOME IDEAS
HERE, SINCE YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT CAN GIVE IDEAS.
>> WHEN DID I SAY THAT?
>> YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT.
YOU JUST ACT LIKE YOU WERE
PISSED OFF OR JUST HAVE
AN ATTITUDE WHEN--
>> NO, WHEN PEOPLE WON'T
GIVE IT A BREAK, IT GETS
ANNOYING.
>> GIVE WHAT A BREAK?
>> IT'S JUST WHEN YOUR MOM
AND YOUR SISTER KEEP COMING
TO ME, "NAME HER THIS.
NAME HER THAT."
AND WHEN I SAY NO,
"OH, MY GOD. YOU'RE PICKY.
YOU NEED TO DO THIS."
IT GETS ANNOYING.
>> WELL...
>> I'VE ALREADY LOOKED.
I'VE ALREADY SAID MY NAMES.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO NEEDS IT.
>> WELL, THEN GIVE ME A LIST
OF YOUR NAMES.
>> I'VE ALREADY SAID MY TWO.
I SAID KYLEE AND CADENCE.
>> OKAY, WE'LL NAME THE KID
ONE OF THOSE TWO NAMES.
>> NO, 'CAUSE I WANT YOU TO
HAVE A SAY-SO ON IT.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> WELL, YOU DON'T CARE
WHAT YOUR CHILD'S GONNA BE
NAMED.
>> NO.
>> I'M NOT JUST SUPPOSED TO
NAME HER BY MYSELF.
>> YOU COULD.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO.
MARIO AND I WILL HAVE MUCH
BIGGER DECISIONS THAN THIS
TO MAKE IN OUR FUTURE.
OUR DAUGHTER IS DUE IN LESS
THAN A MONTH, AND IF WE CAN'T
EVEN WORK TOGETHER TO COME UP
WITH A NAME, HOW'S IT GONNA BE
ONCE SHE'S HERE?
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT MARIO'S
ATTITUDE TOWARDS NAMING OUR
BABY, BUT I'M GOING TO TRY TO
LET THAT GO, BECAUSE TODAY IS
MY BABY SHOWER.
BYE, ROB.
MY FRIENDS HAVE BEEN PLANNING IT
EVER SINCE THEY FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT.
WE DON'T GET TO HANG OUT AS MUCH
SINCE I QUIT THE DANCE TEAM,
SO I'M REALLY EXCITED TO SEE
EVERYBODY.
THANKS.
>> IT'S THE DIAPER GAME.
IT'S, LIKE, THERE'S CHOCOLATE
IN THE DIAPERS.
AND YOU OPEN IT UP AND Y'ALL
LOOK AT IT.
DON'T EAT IT BECAUSE THAT'S
GROSS.
AND, LIKE, YOU TRY TO GUESS
WHAT IT IS.
[rock music]
* *
[laughter]
>> all: ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS.
>> OH!
>> HEY, Y'ALL.
SHE'S GONNA OPEN UP HER PRESENTS
NOW.
>> OOH!
HAS LITTLE MONKEY FEET.
YOU SEE IT?
OH, THESE ARE SO CUTE.
SO CUTE.
LITTLE FEET.
[laughs]
I CAN'T WAIT TO DRESS HER UP.
YOU KNOW I LOVE ME SOME TIGERS.
THANK YOU ALL.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
THANK YOU.
>> SO, CLEONDRA, WHERE'S MARIO,
THE BABY DADDY?
>> HE WORKS.
LIKE, HE WORKS--
HE WORKS A LOT, GOD.
I FEEL SO SORRY FOR HIM.
>> IS HE GONNA LIVE WITH YOU?
LIKE...HELP YOU OUT?
>> HE'S NOT GONNA LIVE THERE.
HE'S, LIKE, GONNA SPEND THE
NIGHT, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
WE DON'T REALLY TALK ABOUT IT
THAT MUCH.
[high-pitched whizzing]
>> I GOT TWO MINUTES
FOR A BREAK FOR ONCE.
DUDE, IT'S CRAZY THAT I'M 19
AND YOU'RE 20.
>> I JUST TURNED 20.
>> WE'RE THE YOUNGEST KIDS
IN THE SHOP.
YOU GOT ONE ALREADY.
YOU GOT ONE ON THE WAY.
>> YEAH.
>> I GOT ONE ON THE WAY.
>> EXPECT TO CALL EVERY
FRICKIN' FAMILY MEMBER YOU CAN.
THAT'S WHAT LINDSAY HAD TO DO.
>> CLEONDRA'S REALLY--I MEAN,
SHE'S ACTUALLY USED TO IT
ALREADY, SO...
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> ONCE THE KID'S BORN, I WANT
HER TO MOVE INTO MY HOUSE.
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THAT HOUSE OR, YOU KNOW,
I LOVE CLEONDRA'S MOM.
I'D RATHER MY KID, OBVIOUSLY,
LIVE IN MY HOUSE IN HER ROOM.
I MEAN, SHE'S GONNA HAVE A ROOM
AT MY HOUSE.
THERE'S NO ROOM FOR HER
AT CLEONDRA'S HOUSE.
THIS IS WHAT I DON'T WANT MY KID
TO HAVE, WHICH ZYRA HAS,
HER ROOM BASICALLY IS A LITTLE
TENT THAT SHE GOT FOR HER
BIRTHDAY.
IF YOU CALL ANYTHING IN THAT
HOUSE A ROOM FOR HER,
IT WOULD BE THAT LITTLE TENT
OR JUST THE LIVING ROOM.
BUT I CAN'T SAY THAT
BECAUSE SHE'LL CRY FOR TEN DAYS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I MEAN, SHE'S FRICKING
PREGNANT, HORMONAL, AND WHINING
ABOUT SITUATIONS THAT AREN'T--
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO CRY
ABOUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> YEAH, THAT'S--
>> I DON'T LIKE PREGNANT WOMEN.
>> HEY, MAMA.
>> LOOK AT THIS.
IT IS SO CUTE.
>> SO CUTE.
LIKE YOURS.
>> I KNOW, WE'RE GONNA BE
MATCHING.
THEY'RE SO CUTE, AIN'T THEY?
THE SHOWER WAS SO MUCH FUN,
AND I THINK WE HAVE MOST OF
WHAT WE NEED FOR THE BABY,
WHICH IS GREAT, BECAUSE MY
DOCTOR SAID LABOR CAN COME
ANY DAY NOW.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT MARIO
AND I FINALLY DECIDED ON A NAME.
KYLEE SUE.
BUT WE STILL HAVEN'T AGREED
ON WHERE SHE'S GONNA LIVE.
AND NOW WE'RE OUT OF TIME,
BECAUSE THE NEXT DAY,
I WENT INTO LABOR.
I'M ALREADY SIX CENTIMETERS
DILATED, AND MY CONTRACTIONS
ARE EXCRUCIATING.
OH, GOSH.
OH, MY GOD, THIS REALLY DOES
FREAKING HURT.
I'M GETTING AN EPIDURAL
FOR THE PAIN, BUT IT'S TAKING
A WHILE FOR IT TO START
WORKING, AND I'M REALLY FEELING
THE URGE TO PUSH.
[beeping]
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> CAN I GET MY DOCTOR
IN HERE?
>> EXCUSE ME. WHAT NOW?
>> MY DOCTOR.
>> SHE NEEDS TO PUSH.
>> OKAY.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, GIVE ME A KISS.
GOOD LUCK, OKAY.
I'LL BE RIGHT OUTSIDE.
I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
MY MOM IS TOO SQUEAMISH
TO STAY IN THE DELIVERY ROOM,
BUT ELIZABETH AND TYLER
WANT TO BE HERE TO SUPPORT ME.
CAN I PUSH?
>> ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT,
NINE, AND TEN.
ONE MORE TIME.
PUSH.
ONE, TWO--THAT'S IT.
THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE...
AND TEN.
>> STRAIGHTEN OUT THERE.
>> STRETCH THE BELLY.
>> DAMN. AH.
>> SCREAM IT, GIRL.
SCREAM IT.
DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST LET IT OUT.
>> I CANNOT PUSH.
>> AND PUSH.
[baby crying]
>> IT'S YOUR PARTY.
YOU CAN CRY.
>> * NOTHING LESS THAN LOVE *
>> LOOK AT MAMA.
>> * TELL ME, DID YOU KNOW? *
>> COME HERE, MARIO.
BRING IT IN, BIG FELLA.
COME ON, COME ON.
* THIS WAS ALL I'VE KNOWN *
* *
>> YOU KNOW THIS VOICE?
>> OH, ISN'T SHE PRECIOUS?
>> * FEELS LIKE I DIED *
* AND WENT TO HEAVEN *
* FEELS LIKE I DIED *
* FEELS LIKE *
>> [sneezes]
>> BLESS YOU.
IT'S TIME TO TAKE KYLEE HOME.
I HARDLY GOT ANY SLEEP WHILE I
WAS IN THE HOSPITAL, SO I'M
LOOKING FORWARD TO MARIO
HELPING ME OUT TONIGHT
SO I CAN GET SOME REST.
HOME SWEET HOME.
>> HOME SWEET HOME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S MY BABY.
BABY ON MY SHOULDER.
OKAY, SO YOU'RE SPENDING THE
NIGHT HERE TONIGHT, OBVIOUSLY.
YOU AND KYLEE?
I'M SPENDING THE NIGHT
AT MY HOUSE.
SO...
HOW'S THIS GONNA BE
WORKING OUT?
>> I MEAN, YOU CAN EASILY
STAY HERE.
SO, I MEAN...
>> I CAN STAY HERE TONIGHT.
IT'S JUST, I'M NOT GOING TO.
>> I MEAN, SO WHY DON'T YOU?
YOU'RE JUST, LIKE, ACTING LIKE
THERE'S, LIKE...
LIKE, A HUGE REASON WHY, LIKE,
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE TONIGHT OR--
>> DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE THAT I
WANT TO GET SOME SLEEP?
WHY COULDN'T YOU STAY OVER HERE
AT MY HOUSE?
>> 'CAUSE I JUST HAD HER,
AND I WANT TO BE IN MY BED
IN MY OWN HOUSE.
I GET YOU WANT TO DO IT,
BUT IT'S NOT HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW.
I MEAN...
THIS IS WHY I GET MAD.
'CAUSE YOU NEVER, LIKE,
KNOW WHERE I'M COMING FROM
AT ALL.
>> [mumbling]
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHY YOU'RE--
>> WHY I'M CRYING?
'CAUSE I'M AGGRAVATED,
FRUSTRATED, AND I DO IT
WHEN I GET LIKE THIS.
SORRY. OKAY?
>> I'M JUST GONNA GO DO
WHAT I GOTTA DO AND JUST...
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S OUR
FIRST NIGHT HOME WITH THE BABY
AND MARIO IS JUST GOING TO GO
HOME AND SLEEP.
[baby crying]
I'M SO EXHAUSTED AND STILL
IN A LOT OF PAIN FROM LABOR,
SO IT'S DISAPPOINTING THAT MARIO
WOULD BAIL ON ME.
I WAS EXPECTING MORE FROM HIM.
>> YOU FEEL LIKE YOU NEED
A BREAK?
WANT ME TO TAKE HER?
>> AT LEAST MY FAMILY IS
STEPPING UP FOR ME.
OVER THE FIRST WEEK, MY MOM
AND HER BOYFRIEND, ROB,
REALLY HELPED ME OUT.
>> STOP MOVING YOUR HEAD.
AND ZERICA IS STAYING HOME MORE,
SO I DON'T HAVE TO BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR ZYRA
ALL THE TIME.
>> HOW DOES IT FEEL?
HAVING A BABY AND STUFF?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE
A NEW MOMMY.
>> NO, YOU'RE JUST USED TO
HELPING TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, GOOD.
YOU'VE GOT PRACTICE.
>> WHEN YOU HAD ZYRA,
YOU DROPPED HER OFF ON ME
LIKE I WAS HER DAYCARE.
>> I WAS GOING OUT TOO MUCH.
>> I MEAN, SOMETIMES YOU WOULD
JUST BE LIKE, "WATCH HER,"
AND WALK OUT THE DOOR.
>> YEAH, I SHOULDN'T HAVE
DONE THAT, BUT I DID.
I DON'T GO OUT ANYMORE, THOUGH.
I HAD TO GET USED TO THIS,
CLEONDRA.
I WASN'T USED TO THIS.
YOU'RE USED TO IT 'CAUSE YOU'RE
USED TO WATCHING HER.
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS IT JUST TOOK ME
A MINUTE TO WAKE UP, LIKE,
"[gasps] I REALLY HAVE A BABY."
I'M GLAD YOU'RE GRADUATING,
HAVING A BABY AND ALL.
'CAUSE I DIDN'T 'CAUSE I WAS
A LITTLE BAD IN SCHOOL.
GIVE ME A KISS.
GO GET SOME TISSUE.
>> I'M GLAD MY SISTER IS
STEPPING UP AND BEING MORE OF
A MOM TO ZYRA, AND MAYBE SHE CAN
EVEN WATCH KYLEE FOR ME
WHEN I GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
I'M GONNA NEED ALL THE HELP
I CAN GET BECAUSE OTHER THAN
BUGGING ME ABOUT MOVING IN
WITH HIM, I HAVEN'T HEARD MUCH
FROM MARIO THIS WEEK.
>> TELL ME WHAT YOUR BIGGEST
MISGIVING IS ABOUT HER STAYING
THERE AT HER HOUSE.
>> I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH KYLEE BEING AROUND...
ZERICA OR JAVON.
I MEAN, I WOULDN'T WANT EITHER
OF THEM WATCHING HER AT ALL,
BECAUSE I DON'T...
>> WELL, YEAH, I MEAN,
YOU'VE KIND OF MADE IT CLEAR
YOU DON'T EVEN WANT THEM
REALLY AROUND HER.
>> I MEAN, I KNOW ZERICA
AND JAVON ARE--THAT'S HER BLOOD
AND THAT'S HER FAMILY, BUT I
DON'T WANT THEM EVEN--
I TOLD HER I DON'T EVEN WANT
THEM AROUND MY CHILD.
>> YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THAT, BUT--
>> I MEAN, SHE'S GONNA BE LIVING
IN THE HOUSE.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO ABOUT
IT, BUT I JUST DON'T EVEN FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH IT, MUCH LESS
THEM WATCHING HER.
>> YEAH.
HAVE Y'ALL TALKED ANY MORE ABOUT
HER MOVING IN?
>> IF SHE DOESN'T MOVE IN,
THIS ISN'T GONNA WORK.
I MEAN, ME AND HER ISN'T GONNA
WORK.
>> RIGHT.
YOU'LL JUST BE KYLEE'S DAD
AND THEN THAT'S IT.
>> YEAH.
[rock music]
* *
>> TAKING CARE OF KYLEE
CONSUMES EVERY MINUTE OF MY DAY.
WITH MARIO AT WORK ALL DAY,
I DON'T HAVE MUCH HELP, AND IT'S
HARD KEEPING UP WITH MY
HOMEWORK.
I'LL ONLY MISS TWO WEEKS OF
SCHOOL BECAUSE OF CHRISTMAS
BREAK, BUT IF I WANT TO GRADUATE
IN MAY, I CAN'T MISS ANY OF MY
MIDTERM EXAMS.
CAN YOU WATCH HER FOR A LITTLE
BIT WHILE I GO TAKE A TEST?
>> YEAH.
HOW LONG YOU GONNA BE GONE?
>> AN HOUR...30?
>> I'LL WATCH HER.
>> YOUR HAND'S COLD.
BE CAREFUL.
I HAVEN'T LEFT KYLEE WITH ANYONE
SINCE SHE'S BEEN BORN,
BUT MARIO IS AT WORK,
AND I CAN'T AFFORD TO MISS
THIS TEST.
GOLLY, YOU POOP.
ALL DONE.
[loud kisses]
>> MARIO.
>> HERE.
CLEONDRA, HOW'D YOUR TEST GO
TODAY?
>> ENGLISH I MADE A HIGH "C."
>> HOW DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU
ALREADY MADE?
>> 'CAUSE SHE GRADED IT.
>> SO WHO WATCHED KYLEE TODAY
WHEN YOU WENT TO SCHOOL?
>> ZERICA AND JAVON.
>> HOW'D THAT GO?
>> [laughs]
>> THEY SAID IT WENT FINE.
>> HOW LONG WERE YOU GONE?
>> FOUR HOURS.
>> DID HE CHANGE HER DIAPER?
>> I DIDN'T ASK ALL THAT.
>> DID YOU KNOW SHE WAS GONNA
DO THAT?
>> NO.
>> HE DON'T LIKE IT.
>> WHY?
NOT COMFORTABLE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO'S OVER HERE
WHEN IT'S JUST HIM OR WHEN IT'S
ZERICA, I DON'T KNOW WHO'S
ALL OVER HERE.
I WISH SOMEONE COULD'VE ASKED--
SOMETHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> OH, YOU WOULD LIKE FOR HER
TO CONFIRM IT WITH YOU FIRST
WHO NEEDS TO WATCH HER?
>> YEAH.
>> SOMETIMES SHE'S GONNA HAVE TO
MAKE THAT DECISION ON HER OWN.
>> YOU KNOW I DON'T FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH ZERICA
AND JAVON WATCHING HER, RIGHT?
>> I MEAN, I GUESS AT
LAST-MINUTE THINGS THEY'D HAVE
TO WATCH HER.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU KNOW YOU COULD CALL
MY MOM OR MY SISTER AT ANY TIME
FOR HER.
>> OKAY, WELL, THAT WAS
RIGHT THERE, SO...
>> WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
I WOULD RATHER YOU AT LEAST
CALL ME.
I COULD FIND SOMETHING OUT
FROM THEM
INSTEAD OF YOU JUST BEING LIKE,
"OKAY, THEY'RE RIGHT THERE,
SO THEY'RE GONNA DO THIS."
>> SORRY YOU DON'T TRUST
MY FAMILY.
>> UM...
>> I MEAN, DO YOU TRUST THEM
WATCHING HER?
>> NOT COMPLETELY, NO.
>> OKAY, THEN.
>> IT WOULD BE EASIER TO
COMMUNICATE AND TALK WITH EACH
OTHER IF WE WERE LIVING
IN MY HOUSE.
>> WHAT WOULD MAKE THINGS EASIER
IS IF MARIO WOULD STOP TALKING
ABOUT ME MOVING IN WITH HIM
AND START HELPING OUT
WITH KYLEE.
[Kylee crying]
MARIO WAS SO PISSED THAT I
LEFT KYLEE WITH MY BROTHER
AND SISTER WHICH WAS REALLY LAME
SINCE I CAN NEVER GET HIM TO
COME OVER AND HELP.
>> HELLO.
>> HEY.
>> WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
>> JUST SITTING AT THE HOUSE.
>> CAN YOU COME OVER AND HELP ME
WITH KYLEE?
>> I JUST DON'T FEEL LIKE
DOING NOTHING TODAY.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE JUST
HANGING OUT OR ANYTHING.
>> I'M TIRED TOO.
I NEED HELP PUTTING HER DOWN.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
>> BYE.
>> MARIO KEEPS PESTERING ME
ABOUT MOVING IN WITH HIM,
BUT I DON'T THINK HE REALIZES
WHAT IT'S LIKE BEING UP
WITH A BABY ALL NIGHT.
MOM?
COULD I SPEND THE NIGHT AT
MARIO'S TONIGHT?
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE HE'S BEEN, LIKE,
KIND OF PRESSURING ME ABOUT
MOVING IN TO HIS HOUSE AND I
JUST WANT HIM TO SEE, LIKE, HOW
IT IS TO DO A NEWBORN.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW HOW HE'S ALWAYS
TIRED AND STUFF AND HE ALWAYS
WANTS TO SLEEP AND EVERYTHING,
AND HE'S NOT GONNA BE ONE TO PUT
UP WITH A NEWBORN BABY.
>> I DON'T REALLY CARE FOR
THE IDEA BECAUSE I DON'T WANT
YOU GETTING USED TO SPENDING
THE NIGHT OVER THERE BECAUSE
YOU'VE NEVER GOT TO SPEND
THE NIGHT.
AND I DON'T WANT HIM GETTING
COMFORTABLE THINKING YOU CAN
JUST COME SPEND THE NIGHT.
>> HE KNOWS IT'S UP TO YOU.
>> BUT IN ORDER TO PROVE
A POINT, I GUESS I'M OKAY
WITH IT NOW.
YOU NEED TO MAKE HIM BE THE ONE
TO GET UP WITH HER EVERY SINGLE
TIME, ESPECIALLY SEEING HOW
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT'S BEEN DOING
IT ANYWAYS.
* *
>> I'M NOT THRILLED TO BE
LEAVING MY HOUSE AND ALL THE
HELP FROM MY FAMILY, BUT IF
MARIO'S GOING TO INSIST THAT
KYLEE AND I LIVE WITH HIM,
HE NEEDS TO KNOW WHAT HE'S
IN FOR.
SHE POOP?
>> YEAH.
>> HA-HA.
>> SO NASTY.
[Kylee crying]
I'M NOT BEING VERY SUCCESSFUL
AT THIS.
>> YOU GOTTA--'CAUSE SHE'S
SMALL--YOU GOTTA FOLD THIS
DOWN...AND THEN...
>> [crying]
>> SHH, SHH, SHH.
CAN YOU, LIKE, MAKE HER,
LIKE, TWO OUNCES?
I THINK SHE'S STILL HUNGRY.
CAN YOU?
OBVIOUSLY, IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHERE WE SLEEP.
MARIO'S JUST NOT INTO HELPING ME
WITH THIS BABY.
>> THINGS HAVE BEEN PRETTY TENSE
BETWEEN ME AND MARIO SINCE OUR
SLEEPOVER AT HIS HOUSE.
DESPITE THE TENSION, KYLEE AND I
HAVE GOTTEN INTO A NICE ROUTINE.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT ROUTINE IS
ABOUT TO CHANGE BECAUSE I'M
GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
AND SINCE MARIO IS SO UPTIGHT
ABOUT WHO WATCHES KYLEE,
WE HAD TO COME UP WITH A
BABYSITTING PLAN WE COULD BOTH
AGREE ON, AND IT'S A LITTLE
COMPLICATED.
SHE PROBABLY NEEDS TO DO
A LITTLE BURPING.
>> GOOD LUCK, BABY GIRL.
>> THANKS.
>> ROB WILL WATCH HER ON
MONDAYS.
TUESDAY IS MARIO'S DAY OFF,
SO HE CAN KEEP HER.
DON'T WIPE UP.
SHE GOES TO MARIO'S MOM
ON WEDNESDAYS, BACK TO MY MOM
ON THURSDAYS...
SHE ALREADY ATE AND GOT CHANGED.
AND THEN OVER TO MARIO'S SISTER
ON FRIDAYS.
I'M DETERMINED TO GRADUATE
THIS YEAR, BUT I HATE BEING
AWAY FROM KYLEE FOR SO LONG,
AND MARIO AND I RARELY SPEND
TIME TOGETHER ANYMORE.
>> THERE THE MOMMY IS.
SO I AIN'T BEEN SEEING, LIKE,
YOU AND MARIO HANGING OUT
TOO MUCH.
YOU GUYS PLAN ON DOING ANYTHING?
>> A DATE NIGHT?
FAMILY DATE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING TONIGHT.
>> A FAMILY DATE NIGHT?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE SHE'S GOING.
WE'RE BOTH REALLY TIRED,
BUT MARIO HASN'T SPENT ANY TIME
WITH ME AND KYLEE THIS WEEK,
AND I NEED TO LET HIM KNOW THAT
THIS ISN'T WORKING FOR ME
ANYMORE.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHY DON'T YOU PUT HER
IN THE BOOTH?
>> [crying]
>> OH.
HORRIBLE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S SO COMICAL?
>> YOU AND HER.
JUST WATCHING.
>> MAYBE WE SHOULD TRADE PLACES
SO I COULD LAUGH.
>> WHY WOULD YOU LAUGH AT ME
AND I DEAL WITH HER
ALL THE TIME?
>> MAINLY IT'S SOMEBODY ELSE,
ACTUALLY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MAJORITY OF THE TIME,
SHE'S WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
>> I WASN'T EXPECTING THIS
TO BE EASIER THAN IT IS.
>> SO HOW DO YOU THINK
I FEEL?
LIKE, AFTER I, LIKE, COME HOME
FROM, LIKE, SCHOOL
AND NOT GETTING ANY SLEEP.
>> I GUESS YOU FEEL TERRIBLE.
>> AND TIRED AND WORN OUT
AND EXHAUSTED.
DON'T FEEL LIKE DOING NOTHING.
>> ALL OF THE ABOVE.
>> OKAY.
THEN, LIKE, WHY IS IT, LIKE,
WHEN I ASK YOU TO GET HER
OR SOMETHING OR SPEND THE NIGHT
TO HELP ME, WHY IS IT, LIKE,
SO HARD?
OR, LIKE, I HAVE TO BEG YOU.
>> I WOULD RATHER GET HER
AND SPEND THE NIGHT AT MY HOUSE.
SOMETIMES FOR YOU TO CATCH UP
ON SLEEP, SHE HAS TO BE AWAY
FROM YOU.
>> I KNOW, BUT A MOM CAN'T
JUST BE LIKE, "HERE.
TAKE HER."
I CAN'T JUST LET HER GO
SOMEWHERE.
>> YOU CAN'T LET HER GO
RIGHT ACROSS THE [bleep] STREET?
AT HER DAD'S HOUSE?
THAT'S BULL[bleep].
>> YEAH, IT'S SOOOO BULL[bleep].
>> WHAT?
>> I SAID YEAH,
IT'S SO BULL[bleep].
>> IT IS.
BUT WHATEVER.
I WON'T NEVER [bleep] ASK YOU
TO COME SPEND THE NIGHT
AT MY HOUSE.
>> THAT'S SO [bleep] UP.
>> SPEND THE NIGHT WHEN YOU
MOVE IN.
[acoustic music]
* *
>> WHEN I GOT HOME FROM DINNER
WITH MARIO, IT WAS PRETTY
OBVIOUS THAT IT DIDN'T GO WELL.
>> HOW'D IT GO?
>> HORRIBLE.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I JUST REALLY DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW, MOM.
>> WHEN YOU COME HOME UPSET,
YOU NEED TO TALK ABOUT IT.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
WHEN YOU LEFT HERE, EVERYTHING
WAS FINE.
>> JUST SEEMS LIKE HE DOESN'T
CARE ABOUT ME ANYMORE
OR NOTHING.
>> A BABY CHANGES THINGS.
A BABY CHANGES PEOPLE'S LIVES
DRAMATICALLY.
SO TOMORROW, WE NEED TO HAVE
A SERIOUS ADULT TALK
AND LET HIM KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
>> I KNEW HAVING A BABY WOULD
CHANGE EVERYTHING, BUT I ALWAYS
THOUGHT MARIO WOULD BE THERE
TO SUPPORT ME.
NOW THAT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
SUCH A SURE THING.
AFTER LAST NIGHT'S ARGUMENT,
MY MOM INVITED MARIO AND HIS MOM
OVER TO AIR THINGS OUT.
>> CLEE-CLEE.
COME ON, BABY.
SO WHAT I NEED TO KNOW RIGHT NOW
IS, WHAT'S THE TENSION ABOUT
RIGHT NOW?
'CAUSE APPARENTLY Y'ALL GOT SOME
FEELINGS GOING ON RIGHT NOW
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> PRE-KYLEE, I MEAN, WERE THEY
NOT LOVEY DOVEY, HAPPY ALL THE
TIME AND--
>> HE'S NOT CARING.
HE DON'T CARE ABOUT...
IT SEEMS LIKE HE DON'T CARE
ABOUT ANYTHING I DO.
I'LL ASK HIM TO--
"CAN YOU COME OVER AND SPEND
THE NIGHT?"
TO HELP ME WITH KYLEE.
AND HE HAS, LIKE, THE HARDEST
TIME 'CAUSE HE'S SO TIRED
FROM WORK.
YOUR BACK DON'T HURT.
YOUR FEET DON'T SWELL.
YOUR BOOBS DON'T GET BIG.
YOU'RE NOT CRAMPING
ALL THE TIME.
NO ONE'S KICKING YOU IN YOUR
RIBS OR HANGING FROM THEM
OR NOTHING LIKE THAT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE 24/7.
>> I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
WHY DON'T YOU LET HER SPEND
THE NIGHT AT MY HOUSE SO YOU CAN
HAVE A DAY TO SLEEP?
>> LET ME INTERJECT.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO SAY THIS
IN HER DEFENSE, HONEY.
AS A MOTHER AT NIGHT,
IT'S DIFFERENT FOR CLEONDRA
TO LEAVE HER DURING THE DAY.
BUT AT NIGHT, YOU EXPECT YOUR
LITTLE--ALL YOUR CHICKENS TO BE
IN THEIR NEST AT NIGHT.
IF YOU AGREED TO SPEND,
YOU KNOW, A NIGHT HERE
ONE OR TWO NIGHTS A WEEK,
IS THAT SOMETHING THAT YOU
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE, MARIO?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, SEE?
NOW, LOOK.
THIS IS WHAT YOU DO WHEN YOU
LOVE EACH OTHER.
>> IF YOU CAN'T COMPROMISE NOW,
YOU DAMN SURE AIN'T GONNA BE
ABLE TO COMPROMISE TOGETHER
LIVING IN THE SAME HOUSE.
>> RIGHT.
>> I MEAN, BECAUSE BEFORE KYLEE,
WE WERE LIKE ALWAYS BY EACH
OTHER.
>> I MEAN, IF YOU GUYS ARE
REALLY WANTING TO STAY TOGETHER
AND WORK AT IT,
YOU GOT TO DO IT.
>> WE'LL WORK ON THAT.
>> * WHEN I COME HOME *
* PLEASE DON'T TURN ME AWAY *
>> MARIO, HE'S CHANGED A LOT.
HE'S JUST A NEW DAD.
HE'S JUST STILL HAVING TO GROW
ON SOME FEW THINGS.
I MEAN, I LOVE HIM SO MUCH.
HE'S MY FIRST, LIKE,
REAL RELATIONSHIP.
HE ACTS LIKE HE'S GETTING
MARRIED AND LIVING IN A HOUSE
TOGETHER.
WHEN'S IT GONNA BE FINISHED?
>> LIKE A WEEK AND A HALF,
TWO WEEKS.
>> HE'S EVERYTHING I COULD
BASICALLY ASK FOR.
I DON'T ASK FOR MUCH,
AND WHAT HE HAS IS JUST
WHAT I NEED, SO...
WELL, ZYRA IS GOING TO COME OVER
AND VISIT.
MAYBE SPEND THE NIGHT.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL THAT.
>> WHATEVER.
IF I MOVE OVER TO MARIO'S HOUSE,
I THINK ZYRA'S GOING TO MISS ME
A LOT.
YOU WANT CLEE-CLEE TO LEAVE?
>> NOPE.
>> I'M GONNA MOVE IN
WITH MARIO.
[laughs]
MY LIFE AS A TEEN MOM IS
PRETTY HECTIC.
I GO TO SCHOOL AND I RAISE
MY LITTLE GIRL.
MOST OF TEENAGERS, THEY WANT TO
LIVE THEIR TEENAGE YEARS,
HAVE FUN.
AND I MEAN, ONCE YOU HAVE A KID,
ALL THAT GOES OUT THE WINDOW.
IT'S YOUR KID FIRST, THEN YOU.
IT'S YOUR JOB AND SCHOOL FIRST.
BUT I'M WILLING TO DO IT
FOR MY OWN CHILD.
I MEAN, I HAVE NO REGRETS
WHATSOEVER 'CAUSE I'M MAKING
THE BEST OUT OF MY LIFE,
AND MY LIFE IS GOING TO BE
AWESOME.
>> ON THE NEXT 16 AND PREGNANT:
WHEN I WAS 13, I WAS
HOSPITALIZED FOR ANOREXIA.
IT'S SO HARD FOR ME BEING
PREGNANT AND GAINING ALL THIS
WEIGHT.
>> YOU'RE NOT FAT.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> KIND OF FLABBY.
I FEEL REALLY LIGHTHEADED.
>> DO YOU NEED FOOD?
>> NO, I'M SERIOUSLY SCARED.
>> A LOT OF PRESSURE HERE.
YOU WANT ME TO GO ON A DIET
WITH YOU?
>> JUST START WATCHING
WHAT WE'RE EATING.
>> YOU WERE, LIKE, MY BEST
FRIEND BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T
EVEN STAND TO BE AROUND ME.