[lively rock music]
>> I WANT A WORM TOO.
HEY, I THINK I DO HAVE A FISH.
MY NAME IS BROOKE.
I'M 16, AND I'M FROM MANSFIELD,
TEXAS, A SUBURB OF FORT WORTH.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM, DAD,
LITTLE BROTHER, TREY,
AND A HERD OF GOATS.
I'M A JUNIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL,
BUT I'M NOT YOUR AVERAGE
16-YEAR-OLD, BECAUSE I WAS
BORN TO RACE.
MY WHOLE FAMILY LOVES RACING,
AND I'VE BEEN DOING IT SINCE
I WAS SEVEN.
I'M AT THE TRACK ALMOST
EVERY WEEKEND.
LOVE YOU.
AND THAT'S WHERE I MET
MY BOYFRIEND, CODY.
BE CAREFUL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WE'VE BEEN DATING FOR TWO
YEARS, AND THINGS HAVE BEEN
MOVING FAST.
HE ASKED ME TO MARRY HIM,
AND I SAID YES.
MY PARENTS ARE REALLY
UNDERSTANDING BECAUSE THEY GOT
MARRIED WHEN THEY WERE YOUNG
TOO AND SO DID MY MOM'S MOM
AND MY MOM'S MOM'S MOM.
SO THEY LET CODY MOVE IN,
AND THINGS ARE ABOUT TO GET
A LOT MORE CROWDED
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
SINCE WE'RE GETTING MARRIED,
MY PARENTS LET CODY MOVE IN,
SO WE CAN SAVE UP FOR OUR OWN
PLACE WHILE HE WORKS AT
QUIKTRIP, THE LOCAL CONVENIENCE
STORE.
>> HOW MANY GOATS DO Y'ALL HAVE?
>> LIKE, 15.
ONE THING MY PARENTS APPRECIATE
ABOUT CODY LIVING HERE,
HE HELPS OUT.
>> IS THIS ALL THAT Y'ALL
FEED THEM?
>> FOR NOW.
CODY AND I HAVE BEEN ENGAGED
FOR TWO MONTHS, BUT TOMORROW,
WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT OFFICIAL.
MY COUSIN EMALEE CAME DOWN
FOR THE WEDDING, AND SHE'S DYING
TO HEAR HOW IT ALL WENT DOWN.
>> SO, CODY, HOW DID YOU FIND
OUT THAT BROOKE WAS PREGNANT?
>> WELL, I CAME BACK FROM
VACATION.
>> YEAH?
>> AND SHE CALLED ME THE NEXT
MORNING AND TOLD ME.
>> DID YOU BELIEVE ME...
>> NO, I DID NOT.
>> WHEN I CALLED YOU?
>> I DIDN'T REALLY BELIEVE YOU
UNTIL THE NEXT--OR UNTIL YOU
SHOWED ME THE ACTUAL TESTS
AND KIND OF...
>> BUT YOU DIDN'T WANT
TO SEE THEM.
>> NO, I DID NOT.
>> SO IN YOUR HEAD, WHAT WAS
GOING ON?
>> I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, LIKE, HOW I'M GONNA
BE A DAD IN NINE MONTHS
AND THEN HAVE A JOB AND...
>> FINISH SCHOOL.
>> JUST--THEN, YEAH, AND THE
MAIN WORRY WAS HOW I WAS GONNA--
IF I WAS GONNA BE ABLE TO FINISH
SCHOOL OR NOT, SO...
>> SO ARE YOU EXCITED NOW?
>> YEAH, I'M HOPING IT'S A BOY.
[laughter]
>> I WANT IT TO BE A GIRL.
EVEN THOUGH TOMORROW'S
MY WEDDING DAY, EVERYONE
IS GETTING THEIR CARS READY
FOR MY HONEYMOON AT THE
RACETRACK.
MY FAMILY RACES EVERY WEEKEND,
BUT I CAN ALREADY TELL THIS
SEASON IS GONNA BE DIFFERENT,
AT LEAST FOR ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, DAD?
>> FIXING THE RACE CAR.
>> CAN I DO IT?
>> NOPE.
>> WHY NOT?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
THAT'S JUST RUDE.
[laughter]
>> YOU CAN'T DO NOTHING BUT
SIT IN THE STANDS--
>> I CAN HOOK UP WIRES.
MY MOM HAS GIVEN ME AND CODY
HER BLESSING TO GET MARRIED,
BUT SHE'S STILL DISAPPOINTED
THAT I'M FOLLOWING IN HER
FOOTSTEPS: PREGNANT AND MARRIED
IN MY TEENS.
>> HOW THE HELL DID YOU EVER
EVEN GET PREGNANT, AS MODEST
AS YOU ARE?
HOW DID CODY EVER EVEN
SEE YOU NAKED TO START WITH?
>> I DON'T KNOW, MOM.
>> MAMA TRIED TO GIVE YOU EVERY
OPPORTUNITY TO PROTECT YOURSELF.
>> I KNOW.
>> THERE'S CONDOMS UNDER
THE BATHROOM SINK.
FOR FREE!
I SHOWED YOU HOW TO PUT THEM ON
A CUCUMBER.
THERE WAS NO DOUBT THAT YOU
KNEW WHAT WAS GOING ON.
IT WASN'T 'CAUSE YOU WASN'T
EDUCATED.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU WERE DEFINITELY EDUCATED.
>> MY MOM AND DAD ARE PAYING
FOR MY ENTIRE WEDDING.
THEY'VE BEEN REALLY GENEROUS,
BUT THEY COULD ONLY AFFORD
SO MUCH.
THEY'VE MADE IT CLEAR THEY CAN'T
JUST GIVE US MONEY FOR CHILD
CARE ONCE THE BABY COMES.
>> TIME TO GET UP.
YOUR LAST DAY AS A SINGLE GIRL,
SO IT'S TIME TO GET UP
AND GET GOING.
>> TODAY IS MY WEDDING DAY,
AND SINCE CODY AND I JUST GOT
ENGAGED A FEW WEEKS AGO,
I HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE TO SEE
ANY OF MY GIRLFRIENDS YET.
>> SO WHY ARE YOU AND CODY--
LIKE, WHY DO Y'ALL WANT TO GET
MARRIED RIGHT NOW?
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO BE FAT
AT MY WEDDING.
[laughter]
>> IT'S CALLED WORKING OUT.
>> HOW DID YOU FIND OUT
THAT YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> I TOOK A TEST,
AND IT SAID YES.
>> DID YOU TAKE ONE TEST?
>> THREE TESTS.
>> THIRD TIME'S THE CHARM.
[laughter]
>> NO, ALL THREE OF THEM
SAID THE SAME THING.
I CALLED CODY WHEN I FOUND OUT.
HE TOLD ME HE WAS HUNGRY,
SO HE WAS GONNA GO EAT.
[laughter]
THAT'S ALL HE SAID.
>> GONNA CALL YOU BACK.
>> THEN HE HUNG UP THE PHONE.
>> HOW DID YOUR MOM FIND OUT?
>> BROOKE LEFT HER PHONE
ON THE TABLE AT NANA'S.
AND BROOKE KNOWS THAT I'M GONNA
READ HER TEXT MESSAGES.
I PAY THE BILL.
>> NO, I DON'T.
I FIGURED YOU TRUST ME.
IT'S STUPID.
>> BUT I PAY THE BILL.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> SO I CAN, YOU KNOW,
READ WHAT I WANT TO READ.
SO ANYWAY, I WAS LOOKING AT
HER TEXT MESSAGES, AND SHE HAD
BEEN TEXTING ONE OF HER FRIENDS,
AND HER FRIEND WAS LIKE,
"YOU HAVE TO TELL YOUR MOM."
AND BROOKE'S TEXT BACK WAS,
"I KNOW. I WILL.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY."
>> I WAS VERY SCARED.
>> I TOLD DAD, I SAID,
"GET OUT NOW."
>> AND CODY CAME BACK,
'CAUSE MOM CALLED HIM.
AND SHE ASKED US WHAT WE WERE
GONNA DO, AND HE WAS LIKE,
"WE'RE GONNA GET MARRIED."
AND I JUST LOOKED AT HIM.
I WAS LIKE, "WHERE DID THAT
COME FROM?"
I DID NOT SEE THAT ONE COMING.
>> AND THAT BOY, HE DIDN'T
HESITATE ONE SECOND.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
IT MAKES ME HAPPY THAT
HE'S THERE FOR YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW HE'S NOT GONNA
BE A DEADBEAT.
>> YEAH.
IF THERE'S ONE THING I'M SURE
OF, IT'S THAT CODY WOULD NEVER
LEAVE ME OR HIS BABY.
WE'RE IN LOVE, AND ALTHOUGH
WE DIDN'T PLAN ON GETTING
MARRIED SO SOON, WE'VE THOUGHT
ABOUT THIS DAY FOR A LONG TIME.
WHERE ARE THE RINGS?
>> BROOKE.
>> THEY--I--THEY WERE
RIGHT THERE.
THEY'RE IN YOUR PURSE.
>> THEY'RE IN MY PURSE.
>> WHERE IS YOUR PURSE?
>> IN THE TRUCK.
>> I'M REALLY NERVOUS, AND IT
SEEMS LIKE THERE'S SO MUCH
TO DO.
I WONDER HOW CODY'S DEALING
WITH ALL OF THIS.
>> HEY!
>> SEE, THAT ONE LOOKS--
LOOK AT THIS.
OF COURSE, WE WANTED
A RACE CAR THEME, AND THE
GROOM WAS DRESSED APPROPRIATELY.
I WANTED SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE
TRADITIONAL.
SUCK ALL THIS IN,
EVEN THOUGH I STILL HAVE
A BELLY.
I CAN'T SEE MY FEET.
>> GET USED TO IT.
[laughter]
>> I KNEW THAT WAS COMING.
>> ARE YOU READY?
>> YEP.
>> YOU SURE?
>> OKAY, GOOD LUCK, BABY.
>> GETTING MARRIED AT 16
IS NOT WHAT I HAD PLANNED FOR
MY JUNIOR YEAR BUT NEITHER WAS
GETTING PREGNANT.
>> DO YOU, CODY, TAKE THIS WOMAN
TO BE YOUR LAWFUL WEDDED WIFE?
>> I DO.
>> DO YOU, BROOKE, IN LIKE
MANNER, SOLEMNLY AGREE TO
RECEIVE THIS MAN AS YOUR LAWFUL
WEDDED HUSBAND SO LONG AS
YOU BOTH SHALL LIVE?
>> I DO.
>> CODY, ARE YOU READY?
>> YES, SIR.
>> I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
HUSBAND AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
[applause]
>> NOW.
[cheering and yelling]
>> IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE LOVE,
MARRIAGE, AND THEN A BABY
CARRIAGE, BUT IT SEEMS LIKE
WE'RE DOING IT ALL AT ONCE,
AND I HOPE WE'RE READY.
>> CODY AND I CAN'T AFFORD
A REAL HONEYMOON, SO WE'RE GONNA
HONEYMOON AT THE RACETRACK.
>> I THINK THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME I'VE ACTUALLY SEEN THIS CAR
CLEAN.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU MISSED A SPOT.
>> WELL, YOU CAN WASH IT.
>> I GOT MY OWN CAR TO WASH.
I WASHED IT THE OTHER DAY.
>> THAT'S YOUR NEW JOB:
WASH YOUR CAR, WASH THIS CAR,
AND WASH TREY'S CAR.
>> TONIGHT IS THE BOMBER A.M.A.,
THE FEATURE RACE.
AND CODY REALLY THINKS
HE CAN WIN IT, WHICH WOULD BE
NICE, BECAUSE WE COULD SURE USE
THE PRIZE MONEY.
>> WHO'S A BETTER DRIVER,
ME OR YOU?
>> ME.
>> BULL CRAP.
>> I AM.
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU SIT AROUND--
>> YES, I AM.
>> YOU HOLD YOUR LANE,
AND YOU PUTT-PUTT AROUND.
>> I DO NOT PUTT-PUTT ANYMORE.
>> I STILL WENT AROUND YOU.
>> NO, YOU DIDN'T.
>> YES, I DID.
>> I DON'T REMEMBER.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET A VIDEO
TO SHOW ME.
>> I STILL WANT THIS RING.
>> THIS ONE OR THIS ONE?
>> NO, THIS ONE.
I WANT THE ONE THAT'S GOT
ALL THE MONEY BEHIND IT.
[laughter]
>> I LOVE BEING AT THE TRACK
AND COMPETING AGAINST MY FRIENDS
AND FAMILY, BUT GETTING PREGNANT
HAS TAKEN ME OUT FROM BEHIND
THE WHEEL.
I'M FORCED TO SIT OUT OF
THE ENTIRE SEASON.
WISH I COULD DO THAT.
>> I KNOW.
>> NOBODY WILL LET ME TOUCH
ANYTHING.
>> [laughs]
>> I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO'S
SEASON IS COMING TO AN END.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO BUILD
RACE CARS AND SAVE UP
FOR A BABY.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> IF CODY DOESN'T WIN TONIGHT'S
PURSE, IT WILL BE HIS LAST RACE
FOR A LONG TIME.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
WHAT THE HECK!
HE'S GOT A FLAT.
CODY JUST BLEW AN $80 TIRE.
AND HIS CAR IS OUT OF THE RACE.
>> HEY.
>> NO, I'M JUST GONNA GET--
I'M OVER IT.
BUT MINE ISN'T.
MY DAD'S DRIVING OLD NUMBER 74
WHILE I'M OUT OF COMMISSION.
GO, DADDY, GO, DADDY,
GO, DADDY, GO!
>> WHOO!
>> THE VICTORY LANE
TO NUMBER 74!
>> YAY!
>> YEAH!
>> THAT WAS AWESOME.
>> BROOKE, YOU DID WELL BUILDING
THAT CAR FOR YOUR DADDY
TO DRIVE.
THE BROOKE-MOBILE BACK IN
VICTORY LANE!
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, WISH THEM
A HAPPY MARRIAGE FOR HER
AND CODY AS THEY WALK DOWN
THE FRONT STRAIGHTAWAY.
THEY GOT MARRIED LAST NIGHT.
THEY'RE 16 YEARS OLD,
AND THEY'RE GONNA NEED ALL
THE PRAYERS THEY CAN GET, GUYS,
AS THEY WAIT ON THAT YOUNG ONE
THAT'S GOING TO COME ALONG
WITH THEM.
THEY'RE GONNA NEED ALL
THE PRAYERS THEY CAN GET.
>> WELL, YOUR DAD CUTS THE
RACE CAR OFF.
CODY HAS TO FUND YOUR CAR NOW.
>> YEP.
>> WELL, I HOPE HE'S MAKING
SOME GOOD MONEY TO FUND
TWO RACE CARS AND A KID
AND SUPPORT YOU.
>> BUT SHE'S NOT LIVING ON
MAMA'S MONEY NO MORE, BECAUSE
I SIGNED THE MARRIAGE LICENSE.
AND AS I SIGNED THE MARRIAGE
LICENSE, I ZIPPED THE WALLET
CLOSED.
[laughter]
>> LOOKS LIKE ME AND CODY WON'T
BE RACING AGAIN ANY TIME SOON.
I'M CRUISING THROUGH MY JUNIOR
YEAR, BUT I'M ABOUT TO TAKE OFF
FOR TWO MONTHS TO HAVE THIS
BABY, SO I CAN'T AFFORD TO
FALL BEHIND.
MY SCHOOL HAS A TEEN PARENTING
PROGRAM WHERE I CAN LEARN FROM
OTHER TEEN MOMS ABOUT JUGGLING
MOTHERHOOD AND SCHOOLWORK.
>> SHE WAKES UP AT 5:06
EVERY MORNING.
>> OH, GOD.
IS IT HARD FOR Y'ALL'S
SCHOOLWORK?
>> I TAKE HER TO THE DAY CARE
IN THE MORNING, AND THEN IF
I HAVE HOMEWORK, I WON'T PICK
HER UP RIGHT AWAY RIGHT AFTER
SCHOOL.
I'LL GO HOME AND DO MY HOMEWORK.
AND I STARTED OUT REALLY ROCKY,
AND THEN NOW I HAVE ALL "A"s
AND STUFF.
>> I HOPE THAT'S HOW I AM.
LISTENING TO THE OTHER MOMS
MAKES ME REALIZE JUST HOW HARD
GRADUATING IS GONNA BE,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I HAVE TO
DEPEND ON CODY GRADUATING FIRST
SO HE CAN TAKE CARE OF THE BABY.
WHERE IS YOUR HOMEWORK?
I KNOW YOU HAVE SOME.
>> I DON'T HAVE HOMEWORK.
>> YOU'RE LYING.
WHERE'S YOUR ENGLISH STUFF?
>> I DON'T HAVE ANY HOMEWORK
FOR ENGLISH.
>> 'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T TURN IN
THE LAST STUFF YOU WERE
SUPPOSED TO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU FINISH THAT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO READ ABOUT
ANYTHING.
CODY DOES NOT READ.
>> WHETHER CODY READS OR NOT,
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO BUCKLE DOWN.
HE HAS TO GRADUATE EARLY
IN JANUARY SO HE CAN WATCH OUR
BABY WHILE I FINISH MY JUNIOR
YEAR, BUT IT'S NOT LOOKING GOOD.
HE'S MISSING A TON OF
ASSIGNMENTS AND HAS FAILED
ONE OF HIS FINAL EXAMS
THREE TIMES ALREADY,
WHICH HE'S NOT GONNA GET AWAY
WITH, BECAUSE MY MOM WORKS
AT OUR SCHOOL.
>> I AM SIGNING ON TO THE
INTERNET TO LOOK UP CODY'S
GRADES.
>> OH, GOD.
>> WHY ARE YOU "OH, GODDING"?
WHAT AM I FIXING TO FIND?
OKAY, ENGLISH 4, YOU'RE MISSING
YOUR FRANKENSTEIN STUDY GUIDE.
GET A PENCIL AND WRITE THIS
STUFF DOWN.
ECONOMICS.
>> ECO.
>> YOUR TWO ADDITIONAL
BODY PARAGRAPHS.
>> THAT'S WHAT I DON'T GET,
'CAUSE I HAD--
>> WRITE THEM DOWN.
OKAY, YOU NEED TO ASK IF YOU
CAN REDO THE PROFILE OF
THE UNITED STATES.
THESE THAT YOU'RE GETTING
ZEROES IN, YOU CAN'T GET ZEROES.
YOU DON'T HAVE TIME FOR ZEROES.
>> I HOPE MY MOM CAN MOTIVATE
CODY TO GRADUATE EARLY, BECAUSE
IF HE DOESN'T, I'LL HAVE TO DROP
OUT AND STAY HOME WITH THE BABY.
WITH SO MUCH OF OUR FUTURE
UP IN THE AIR, I AT LEAST WANTED
TO KNOW IF WE WERE HAVING
A BOY OR A GIRL.
SO TODAY, WE'RE HEADED TO
THE DOCTOR TO FIND OUT.
>> [giggles]
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT WITH YOU,
I DREAMED THAT I HAD A LITTLE
BABY POODLE.
[laughter]
I DRESSED IT--I DRESSED IT
IN LITTLE DRESSES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DO YOU WANT IT TO BE?
>> AT FIRST, I WANTED A GIRL.
AND I DECIDED, IF IT'S A BOY,
THAT'S GOOD TOO.
>> OKAY, BROOKE, I'M GONNA HAVE
YOU LIE DOWN ON THE STRETCHER
RIGHT ON YOUR BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY FOR THE JELLY?
HERE WE GO.
THIS IS IT.
>> OH, IT'S COLD.
>> HERE WE GO.
HAVE YOU CHOSEN ANY NAMES YET
FOR THE BABY?
>> YES, IF IT'S A BOY,
IT'S BRODY.
>> YEAH?
>> AND IF IT'S A GIRL,
IT'S EMMA.
>> EMMA, I LOVE EMMA.
BUT IT'S A BOY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> HERE'S THE MOUTH.
>> BIG LIPS.
[laughter]
GOT CODY'S BIG LIPS.
>> WE'RE NAMING OUR BOY BRODY
BECAUSE WE HOPE HE'S THE PERFECT
COMBINATION OF THE TWO OF US.
WE WANT TO GET OUR OWN PLACE
TO LIVE BEFORE BRODY GETS HERE,
BUT WITH CODY'S INCOME FROM
QUIKTRIP, IT'S GONNA HAVE TO BE
DIRT CHEAP.
MY PARENTS HAVE BEEN LETTING US
DO THE CLEANING INSTEAD OF
PAYING RENT BUT ONLY ON THE
CONDITION THAT WE BOTH GRADUATE
HIGH SCHOOL, AND THAT DOESN'T
LOOK PROMISING.
DID YOU EVEN GO TO SCHOOL TODAY?
>> YES, I WENT TO SCHOOL TODAY.
>> GEEZ.
>> JUST 'CAUSE I OVERSLEPT
THE OTHER DAY...
>> YEAH, AND DIDN'T GO.
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP THAT.
YOU NEED TO START GOING TO BED
EARLIER.
THAT WAY, YOU CAN GET UP
>> NO.
>> HAVE YOU TALKED TO THE
COUNSELORS ABOUT YOU GRADUATING
EARLY ANYMORE?
>> I'M ALREADY A MIDTERM GRAD.
>> I KNOW, BUT ARE YOUR GRADES
GOOD ENOUGH TO BE A MIDTERM
GRAD?
>> YES.
>> THEY ARE?
>> CODY, LAST TIME I CHECKED,
YOU HAD A 60 SOMETHING IN THAT
ENGLISH CLASS.
>> I HAVE A 72, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>> OKAY, WELL, IT NEEDS TO BE
HIGHER THAN A 72.
>> NO.
>> YEAH.
DO YOU NOT REMEMBER WHAT I SAID
AT THE BEGINNING OF THE YEAR?
>> NO.
>> IF IT'S LOWER THAN AN 80,
YOU'RE GOING TO TUTORING.
>> I HAVEN'T GONE TO TUTORING
SINCE I WAS IN THE FOURTH GRADE.
>> YOU HAVE TO GRADUATE IN
DECEMBER SO THAT YOU'LL BE HERE
FOR THE BABY IN FEBRUARY.
RUNNING AWAY FROM OUR SITUATION
IS NOT A GOOD SIGN,
'CAUSE WE HAVEN'T EVEN GOTTEN
TO THE HARD PART YET.
>> [grunts]
>> MY FAMILY LIKES TO SPEND
A LOT OF TIME OUTDOORS.
WE GET OUT CAMPING WHENEVER
WE CAN.
AS SOON AS BRODY'S OLD ENOUGH
TO CRAWL OR EVEN EARLIER,
HE'S GONNA BE SLEEPING IN
A TENT.
>> LAY ON IT AND SEE IF IT'S
GONNA BE COMFORTABLE ENOUGH.
[laughter]
>> IT WAS SCARY.
YES.
BUT WE'LL EVENTUALLY WANT
A REAL HOUSE TO SLEEP IN.
MY PARENTS HAVE OFFERED US
A LITTLE PATCH OF THEIR LAND
TO PUT A PLACE OF OUR OWN,
AND SINCE WE CAN'T AFFORD MUCH
WHILE I'M STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL,
WE'RE THINKING ABOUT BUYING
A PREFABRICATED BARN.
>> I AM VERY READY FOR YOU GUYS
TO GET YOUR OWN PLACE.
YOU GUYS HAVE FILLED UP
THE HOUSE.
>> WHY ARE Y'ALL LOOKING
AT BARNS, LIKE...
>> YOU KNOW, THAT WAY, THEY CAN
SAY, YOU KNOW, WHEN SOMEBODY
ASKS BRODY, "WERE YOU BORN
IN A BARN?"
HE CAN SAY YEAH.
>> YEAH.
>> IF YOU TAKE ONE OF THESE
WITH THE UPSTAIRS, YOU COULD
MAKE, LIKE, THE UPSTAIRS BE
THE BEDROOM AND THEN THE
DOWNSTAIRS A LITTLE--
LIKE A KITCHENETTE TYPE,
LITTLE-BITTY KITCHEN.
AND IT'S SMALL ENOUGH THAT
WE CAN PUT IT ON OUR LAND,
SO THEY DON'T HAVE TO BUY LAND.
YEAH.
>> IT DEPENDS ON HOW MUCH
CODY MAKES, ON HOW MUCH WE COULD
PAY EVERY MONTH.
>> YOU'LL MAKE IT.
WE DID.
IT'S NOT EASY.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU HAVE IF YOU DON'T
WORK FOR IT.
>> ARE YOU READY TO GO TO BED?
>> LET'S GO.
>> GOOD NIGHT, SWEETHEART.
>> GOOD NIGHT, MOM.
IT IS FREEZING.
AFTER WE BROKE UP CAMP,
I CONVINCED CODY TO GO LOOK
AT BARNS.
HE THINKS IT'S A SILLY IDEA,
BUT I REALLY THINK IT'S
THE WAY TO GO.
>> WHY DO YOU WANT A BARN
TO LIVE IN?
>> I THINK THEY'RE CUTE.
>> WELL...
>> AND THEY'RE NOT EXPENSIVE--
WELL, NOT THAT EXPENSIVE--
AS A REAL HOUSE WOULD BE.
>> I KNOW, BUT...
>> AND WE CAN PUT IT ON MOM
AND DAD'S LAND.
THAT WAY, WE CAN STILL HAVE
A POND IN OUR BACKYARD.
>> YOU KILL ME.
>> I KNOW.
>> Y'ALL ARE PRETTY EXCITED
ABOUT THE BABY COMING?
>> YEAH.
>> YES.
>> TRYING TO SPOIL THAT THING
ROTTEN.
ALL RIGHT, AND AS YOU COME
INSIDE, IT KIND OF OPENS UP.
WE DON'T HAVE THIS ONE
FINISHED OUT.
AND IT COMES STANDARD WITH
THE WINDOWS, THE NINE-LIGHT DOOR
THAT YOU SEE HERE,
AND IT COMES STANDARD WITH
THE STAIRCASE.
AND THIS IS KIND OF THE UPSTAIRS
WHERE THEY TYPICALLY USE
THE BEDROOMS.
WE TYPICALLY WILL DO
A ONE BEDROOM UP HERE.
>> I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
IT'S THE PERFECT SIZE.
>> IT'S PRETTY NICE, I MEAN,
AND IT'S AFFORDABLE,
WHICH IS WHAT MOST PEOPLE...
HEY, IT'S NOT LIKE BUILDING
A $200,000 HOUSE THAT
TIES YOU DOWN.
>> LIKE, HOW MUCH WOULD A BASIC
PAYMENT JUST BE FOR THE SHELL?
>> IF YOU DID THE $25,000,
AND THEN WE GOT THE STANDARD TAX
THAT'S ON THERE AS WELL,
SAY YOU WANTED TO GO 72 MONTHS,
YOU'D BE ABOUT $416 A MONTH.
IF YOU WANTED IT COMPLETELY
FINISHED OUT, NORMALLY,
IT WOULD BE ABOUT $35,000.
72.
THAT'S ABOUT $555 A MONTH.
ALL RIGHTY.
>> THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN AFFORD
THIS BARN ON WHAT CODY MAKES
AT QUIKTRIP.
HE PROPOSED A PLAN TO MAKE IT
WORK.
>> I'M GONNA WORK FULL-TIME.
I'M GONNA WORK IN THE EVENINGS.
>> NO.
I'M TRYING TO TELL YOU THAT
THE FACT IS, IF YOU DO THAT,
AND I HAVE TO STAY UP WITH
THE BABY AT NIGHT, THAT I'M NOT
GONNA GRADUATE.
>> YES, YOU WILL.
>> NO, I WON'T, NOT IF I HAVE
TO STAY UP WITH HIM ALL NIGHT
AND I CAN'T SLEEP,
AND THEN I HAVE TO GO TO SCHOOL.
>> THAT JOB'S NOT GONNA BE THERE
FOREVER.
>> LIKE, ME GRADUATING IS?
>> YEAH, YOU CAN GET YOUR G.E.D.
>> NO, I WANT TO GRADUATE.
>> YOU WILL--
I'M JUST DONE TALKING WITH YOU.
>> WHY ARE YOU ACTING LIKE THIS,
CODY?
>> BECAUSE I'M SITTING HERE
TRYING TO PROVIDE FOR A FAMILY,
AND YOU'RE JUST TELLING ME,
"HEY, TURN IT DOWN."
>> NO, I'M NOT.
I'M SAYING THAT I NEED
TO GRADUATE.
>> WE'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT
ON MY $8.25 AN HOUR.
>> WELL, HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO GET A JOB IF I DON'T HAVE
A DIPLOMA?
>> OKAY, FINE.
IF ANYTHING LIKE THAT COMES
ALONG, I'LL DENY IT.
>> I WANT TO MOVE OUT OF MY
PARENTS' HOUSE JUST AS BAD AS
CODY DOES, BUT I'M NOT GIVING UP
MY SENIOR YEAR OF HIGH SCHOOL
TO DO IT.
[cell phone ringing]
>> HELLO?
>> HEY.
WILL YOU COME OUT HERE AND GET
THIS BELLY FOR ME?
I'M STARTING TO GET REALLY BIG
AND REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
CODY HAS NO SYMPATHY,
SO I THOUGHT I'D BRING HIM
A SURPRISE.
IT'S REALLY HEAVY.
HEAVY, RIGHT?
>> LITTLE BIT.
>> [laughs]
>> SO WHAT IS ALL IN THIS?
>> ALL THE BELLY.
THIS PREGNANCY SUIT GIVES CODY
A CHANCE TO SEE WHAT I'VE BEEN
DEALING WITH FOR THE PAST
FOUR MONTHS.
>> NOW CAN YOU BREATHE?
>> IS IT UNCOMFORTABLE?
>> YEAH.
>> both: GOOD.
[laughter]
>> DON'T.
WHAT DOES IT FEEL LIKE SO FAR?
>> I'M FAT.
>> [scoffs]
>> THIS IS YOUR MATERNITY SHIRT.
>> [snorts]
>> THAT'S CUTE.
>> IT FEELS SO WEIRD.
>> DO SOMETHING.
>> OH, I BET.
[vacuum whirring]
>> [laughs]
AS MUCH AS I'M ENJOYING THIS,
CODY HAS TO SETTLE DOWN AND DO
HIS HOMEWORK.
GO GET YOUR BINDER SO YOU CAN DO
YOUR HOMEWORK.
>> [sighs]
COME ON, YIPPA.
>> YIPPA CANNOT HELP YOU
WRITE A PAPER.
>> YES, HE CAN.
>> WILL YOU JUST DO YOUR
HOMEWORK?
[papers rustle]
SERIOUSLY, CODY.
CODY TOOK THE TEST TODAY THAT
DETERMINES WHETHER OR NOT
HE'LL GRADUATE.
WHEN I GOT BACK FROM SCHOOL,
HE WAS WAITING FOR ME
WITH THE RESULTS.
HELLO.
>> HEY.
>> SO HOW DID YOUR TEST GO
TODAY?
>> I FAILED IT THREE TIMES.
>> OKAY, AND WHAT ARE YOU GONNA
DO ABOUT IT?
>> I ALREADY TALKED TO THEM,
AND I GET TO TAKE IT AGAIN.
>> YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU CAN DO IT, BECAUSE
IF NOT, THEN WE'RE SCREWED,
'CAUSE NOBODY WILL BE ABLE
TO STAY HERE AND WATCH BRODY,
AND WE'LL HAVE TO PAY FOR
DAY CARE.
[phone ringing]
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> DID CODY PASS THE TEST?
>> TALK TO CODY ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T WANT AN EXPLANATION.
I WANT A, "YES, I PASSED."
>> NO, I DIDN'T PASS,
BUT I CAN TAKE IT MONDAY AGAIN
AFTER SCHOOL.
>> YOU BETTER JUST PASS IT.
>> I KNOW.
[laughs]
THAT'S WHAT I'M HOPING ON.
SO FOUR MORE DAYS.
>> I HAVE TO HAVE FAITH IN CODY
BEING ABLE TO PULL OFF
GRADUATING EARLY, BUT MY MOM
IS MORE REALISTIC ABOUT THE
SITUATION.
>> WHO ALL ARE YOU COMFORTABLE
LEAVING BRODY WITH?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WANTS ME TO THINK ABOUT
WHO CAN TAKE CARE OF BRODY
WHILE I'M AT SCHOOL,
BUT I'M COUNTING ON CODY
TO DO THAT.
>> I'M WORRIED ABOUT CODY
PASSING THAT TEST.
HE'S TAKEN IT LOTS OF TIMES
AND HASN'T PASSED IT YET,
AND I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM STUDY
MUCH THIS WEEKEND.
>> I THINK THAT HE CAN PASS IT.
>> WELL, IF HE DOESN'T PASS
THE TEST, THEN Y'ALL HAVE
TO PAY FOR DAY CARE.
ME AND DAD CAN'T HELP YOU.
>> WE KNOW WE HAVE TO PAY
FOR DAY CARE.
I CAN'T BE NEGATIVE.
I HAVE TO HAVE FAITH IN HIM.
>> AT SOME POINT, THOUGH,
YOU HAVE TO HAVE A BACKUP PLAN.
>> WELL, I DON'T RIGHT NOW.
>> CODY GETS TO PUT OFF STUDYING
TODAY FOR A FEW HOURS BECAUSE
IT'S MY BABY SHOWER.
>> SO WHY DO BOYS HAVE TO GO
TO THE BABY SHOWERS NOW?
>> BECAUSE IT'S FUN WHEN YOU CAN
HAVE BOTH GIRLS AND BOYS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I LIKE IT.
>> IT'S A GIRL THING, THOUGH.
>> NOT REALLY.
YOU'RE THE DAD.
DON'T YOU WANT TO BE THERE
TO OPEN ALL THE PRESENTS
AND TELL PEOPLE THANK YOU AND...
>> HA, NO.
>> MY FRIEND NIKKI IS THROWING
THE SHOWER FOR ME.
I KNOW CODY DOESN'T WANT
TO COME, BUT HE'S GONNA HAVE
TO DEAL WITH IT, BECAUSE WE NEED
ALL THE STUFF WE CAN GET.
>> HEY, EVERYBODY, WE'RE GONNA
START OPENING PRESENTS.
WELL, BROOKE IS.
[laughter and cooing]
>> I LIKE THESE.
>> OH, WOW.
>> A BABY FOOD JAR WITH
$20 IN IT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> A BLANKET WITH COWBOY BOOTS.
>> OHH...
>> THAT WAS FUN.
>> I'M GLAD MY MOM AND DAD ARE
COOL WITH US STAYING IN THEIR
HOUSE SINCE WE CAN'T AFFORD
OUR OWN PLACE YET,
BUT I THINK THEY'RE STARTING
TO REGRET IT.
>> WOW.
THAT'S A LOT OF STUFF.
LET'S MOVE STUFF WHEREVER
WE CAN, AND THEN WE'LL FIGURE
OUT HOW WE'RE GONNA ORGANIZE
THE STUFF INTO YOUR ROOM.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO MAKE
THINGS WORK FOR THE THREE OF US
IN MY LITTLE ROOM.
>> CODY, PUT THIS UNDER THE SINK
IN MY BATHROOM.
>> WHY IS ALL THIS BABY CRAP
GOING IN MY ROOM?
Y'ALL ARE HAVING A BABY,
NOT ME.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT ALL FIT
IN HERE.
>> NOW WHEN HE CRIES,
YOU CAN JUST, LIKE,
ROLL TO THE END OF THE BED
AND KICK IT.
>> MM.
JUST MAKE IT SWAY FROM SIDE
TO SIDE.
>> RIGHT.
>> CODY IS TAKING HIS TEST
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY, AND I'M
TRYING TO KEEP MY MIND OFF
OF IT.
IT MAY SEEM LIKE I HAVE A TON
OF STUFF FOR BRODY, BUT THERE
ARE STILL THINGS WE NEED.
I CAN'T DRIVE FOR SIX WEEKS
AFTER I HAVE HIM, SO...
>> GOOD.
MAYBE YOU'LL BE SAFE.
>> CODY HAS TO TAKE ME AND BRODY
TO SCHOOL.
[laughter]
THAT'S WEIRD.
>> AND THEN HE HAS TO GO PICK
THE KIDS UP.
>> 'CAUSE HE'S ALREADY GONNA BE
GRADUATED, AND SO HE'S GONNA
BE LONELY AT HOME.
>> I KNOW.
>> YEAH, RIGHT, HE'S GONNA SIT
THERE AND PLAY XBOX ALL DAY.
>> ONLY IF HE GRADUATES.
>> HE BETTER.
>> HE BETTER GRADUATE.
>> Y'ALL HAVE TO PRAY
EVERY DAY.
>> LET'S PRAY RIGHT NOW.
>> THAT BOY NEEDS MORE THAN
PRAYERS.
>> THAT BOY NEEDS A MIRACLE.
>> "MY KIDS ROCK."
>> CODY SHOULD BE DONE WITH
HIS TEST BY NOW.
I KEPT WATCHING MY PHONE FOR
WHEN THE TEST RESULTS WOULD COME
WHEN I FINALLY GOT CODY'S TEXT.
HE PASSED.
I CAN FINALLY BREATHE A LITTLE.
CODY WILL GRADUATE EARLY,
AND I'LL BE ABLE TO FINISH
MY JUNIOR YEAR RIGHT ON TIME.
>> ARE YOU EXCITED FOR YOUR
GRADUATION PARTY?
>> YEAH, BECAUSE NOW--
>> SUPPOSED TO BE A LOT OF
PEOPLE HERE.
>> YEAH, I'M EXCITED BECAUSE
I DON'T HAVE TO WAKE UP AT 6:15
TO GO TO SCHOOL ANYMORE.
GOOD, THANK YOU.
>> YAY.
>> HELLO, LADYBUG!
>> AH!
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> EVERYTHING'S FOR THE BABY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE SACRIFICES ARE THE BEST.
>> THAT'S WHY HE GRADUATED
EARLY, SO THAT I COULD FINISH
SCHOOL AND HE COULD GET UP.
>> YEAH.
>> HEY.
>> YEAH?
>> I'M PROUD OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> GIVE ME A KISS.
>> MM.
>> THANK YOU.
WE ARE GETTING EVERYTHING
READY FOR BRODY'S ARRIVAL.
DAD HAS TO TRY TO PUT MY
HEATER ON TONIGHT TOO.
I AM NOT BRINGING A BABY HOME
FROM THE HOSPITAL IN A COLD CAR.
MY DUE DATE IS TEN DAYS AWAY,
BUT EVERYONE THINKS I'M GOING
EARLY.
I'VE BEEN DRILLING CODY WITH
OUR BIRTH PLAN, AND I HOPE
IT'S SINKING IN.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO WHEN
I TELL YOU THAT I'M IN LABOR?
>> PROBABLY FREAK OUT.
>> [laughs]
SO YOU'RE GONNA BE NICE
AND, LIKE, MASSAGE MY BACK
AND RUB MY FEET.
>> OCCASIONALLY, I GUESS.
CAN I GO WATCH MY FOOTBALL GAME
NOW?
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> CODY THINKS WE STILL HAVE
TIME TO GET READY FOR THIS BABY,
BUT THE NEXT DAY, MY WATER BROKE
AT SCHOOL, AND HE RUSHED ME
TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE READY FOR A BIRTHDAY
PARTY.
>> CAN I HAVE MY PHONE
SO I CAN CALL SOMEBODY?
I CALLED MY WHOLE FAMILY
TO COME HELP ME CELEBRATE.
THEY JUST MIGHT HAVE TO WAIT
AROUND A LITTLE WHILE.
>> I THINK ALL OF MANSFIELD
IS IN THE WAITING ROOM.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
YOUR I.V. STARTED.
>> AH!
[whines]
I'M SCARED.
I HATE NEEDLES.
>> NOT GONNA BE AS BAD
AS YOU THINK.
>> OW!
[gasps]
PEOPLE MIGHT THINK I'M A TOMBOY,
BUT I DO NOT DEAL WELL
WITH PAIN.
I GOT AN EPIDURAL AT THE
EARLIEST OPPORTUNITY.
COME SIT OVER HERE IN A CHAIR,
PLEASE.
I'VE SPENT SO MUCH TIME GETTING
CODY READY FOR THIS DAY,
BUT NOW I'M NOT SO SURE
I'M EVEN READY.
>> OKAY, LET'S BRING--
CAN YOU BRING THEM UP?
OH, YEAH, WE'RE READY.
YOU'RE A 10.
>> WOW.
>> NOW IT'S ALL UP TO YOU.
>> THIS IS HURTING.
MY LABOR IS PROGRESSING FAST,
AND FOUR HOURS IN, I'M READY
TO START PUSHING.
>> A BIG BREATH, AND START
GRABBING BEHIND OUR KNEES.
PUT YOUR CHIN ON YOUR CHEST.
FOCUS, CLOSE YOUR EYES.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
PUSH DOWN, PUSH DOWN, PUSH DOWN.
THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE PUSH RIGHT THERE.
KEEP GOING, KEEP GOING,
KEEP GOING.
ALL RIGHT.
DO IT AGAIN.
DEEP BREATH, ONE MORE TIME.
PUSH AGAINST ALL THIS PRESSURE.
>> GIVE ME THAT MASK BACK.
>> OKAY.
OKAY, LET'S TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
LET'S BEAR DOWN, AND LET'S PUSH.
COME ON, PUSH!
>> ONE, TWO...
>> COME ON, GO, GO, GO,
GO, GO, GO, GO.
>> FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT,
NINE, TEN.
>> OKAY, QUICK, DO IT AGAIN.
THERE YOU GO.
LOOK HOW MUCH YOU'RE MOVING HIM.
GO.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE...
>> COME ON, SWEETIE, PUSH.
YOU'RE GONNA DO IT.
>> EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
>> CAN ALMOST SEE HIS FOREHEAD.
COME ON, PUSH.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE...
>> REAL SLOW, REAL GENTLE,
REAL GENTLE.
>> THERE HE IS!
>> OH, MY.
HE'S A LONG GUY.
LOOK AT HIM!
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> HOLD ON.
>> [cries]
>> THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU GO.
>> HANDSOME.
>> LOOK AT THOSE CHEEKS.
OH, MY GOSH.
HERE YOU GO.
RIGHT HERE, OKAY?
GO, BIG CUT.
[cheering]
LOOK AT THESE.
>> OH!
>> GONNA TAKE...
>> HEY, KIDDIE.
SEE, HE'S GOT A LOT MORE HAIR
THAN WE THOUGHT HE DID.
>> YEAH!
[Brody cries]
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S LET HIM
GET CLEANED UP.
>> LET ME TAKE HIM OVER THERE.
I'LL BRING HIM BACK.
>> LOOKEE...
>> HE HAS CURLY, CURLY HAIR.
>> OH...
>> HI!
>> EVERYONE WAS SO EXCITED
TO SEE BRODY, BUT I WAS JUST
EXHAUSTED.
>> YOU READY TO BREAST-FEED?
>> YEAH.
ARE YOU HUNGRY?
>> YOU WANT TO BREAST-FEED
15 MINUTES ON EACH SIDE,
AND ONCE HE LATCHES ON,
MAKE SURE HE'S NOT JUST ON
YOUR NIPPLE.
HE NEEDS TO BE ON REAL GOOD,
OKAY?
'CAUSE IT HURTS REAL BAD.
>> IT'S FINALLY TIME TO BRING
BRODY HOME.
OH, HE HAS TO CHANGE CLOTHES.
HE CAN'T GO HOME IN THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE GONNA CHANGE HIM AGAIN.
OKAY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I HAVE TO GET MY SEAT BELT
OFF.
GOODNESS, GRACIOUS.
I'M SORRY THAT I'M NOT IMPORTANT
ANYMORE.
>> [laughs]
COME HERE, CHILD.
>> WANT TO GO GIVE HIM A BATH?
HIS FIRST BATH?
>> HE DON'T NEED A BATH.
HE'S SLEEPIN'.
>> OH, HE SNOOZED THE WHOLE WAY
HERE.
>> YOU'RE GONNA WAKE HIM UP,
AND HE'S GONNA BE COLD.
>> HE WILL BE FINE.
>> AND THEN HE'S GONNA CRY.
>> IT'S OKAY IF HE'S COLD
FOR A FEW MINUTES.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE REALLY MAD,
DUDE.
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT GIVING BRODY
HIS FIRST BATH, BUT I WANT TO
KNOW WE'RE ABLE TO DO IT.
WHAT'S THE RULE ONE
WHEN YOU GIVE A BABY A BATH?
>> YOU ONLY WASH ONE PART
AT A TIME.
>> NO.
>> YOU DAB HIM?
>> WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
WHAT DO YOU START WITH?
>> HIS HEAD.
>> THE CLEANEST PART IS FIRST.
>> WELL, WHERE'S HIS CLEANEST
PART?
>> WILL YOU TWO QUIT ARGUING AND
JUST CLEAN THE FRICKIN' BABY?
>> CODY WAS RIGHT.
BRODY DOESN'T LIKE THIS ONE BIT.
I DECIDED THE BATH COULD WAIT.
OKAY, PUT HIS CLOTHES BACK
ON HIM.
>> I'M STARTING TO FIGURE OUT--
>> YOU HAVE TO HURRY.
HE HATES THIS PART.
HURRY, BEFORE HE WAKES UP MOM.
>> WHAT KIND OF CRY IS THAT?
COME ON.
>> HURRY UP!
>> SHUT YOUR PIEHOLE.
>> WHAT IS TAKING YOU SO LONG?
>> WELL, THEN YOU PUT IT ON.
>> IT AIN'T THAT FRICKIN' HARD
TO PUT ON GLOVES.
>> [crying]
>> HURRY UP!
PUT IT ON!
>> HAVE TO GET FIVE FINGERS
IN THERE.
[Brody crying]
BRODY STILL HATES TAKING BATHS,
BUT WITH MY MOM'S HELP,
I'M STARTING TO GET THE HANG
OF IT.
>> BRODY, OH.
>> MY FAMILY'S BEEN VERY EXCITED
TO HAVE A BABY IN THE HOUSE.
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH
THE LITTLE BUDDY?
>> BUT MY MOM HAS LITTLE
TOLERANCE FOR US GETTING BEHIND
ON OUR CHORES, WHICH IS HOW
WE PAY OUR RENT.
>> IS THAT A NASTY, CRUSTY
BREAST PAD WITH THE BABY'S
PACIFIER SITTING ON IT?
>> NO, IT'S MINE THAT I HAVE IN
RIGHT NOW.
>> CRUSTY BREAST PADS.
>> IF YOU PICK THEM UP ON
THE PURPLE SIDE---
>> I SHOULD NOT HAVE TO PICK UP
A BREAST PAD EVER.
>> SINCE BRODY WAS BORN,
WE'VE HAD A PRETTY STEADY
ROUTINE.
CODY GOES TO WORK IN THE MORNING
WHILE I TAKE CARE OF BRODY
AND TRY TO STAY ON TOP
OF OUR CHORES, BUT ALL OF
THAT'S ABOUT TO CHANGE.
WE'RE GONNA GO OVER EVERYTHING
THAT YOU HAVE TO DO TOMORROW.
TOMORROW IS MY FIRST DAY
BACK AT SCHOOL, AND I'M REALLY
NERVOUS ABOUT LEAVING BRODY.
BREAST MILK'S UP THERE.
FORMULA'S ON THE BOTTOM.
IF YOU'VE ALREADY FED HIM,
THEN BURP HIM.
CHANGE HIS DIAPER.
HAVE YOU SEEN THE NUMBERS
ON THE FRIDGE?
>> DIDN'T KNOW WHAT THEY WERE
AT FIRST.
>> WHO ARE YOU GONNA CALL FIRST?
>> I THINK YOUR MOM IS FIRST.
>> YOU'RE GONNA CALL ME FIRST
AND THEN MY SCHOOL.
[alarm buzzing]
THIS WILL BE THE LONGEST I'VE
BEEN AWAY FROM BRODY SINCE
THE DAY HE WAS BORN.
LET ME SEE HIM.
[crying] HEY, BUDDY.
I'M SAD.
[sniffles]
I'M GONNA MISS HIM.
>> BABY, YOU HAVE TO LEAVE.
>> I KNOW, BUT I DON'T WANT TO.
>> I KNOW YOU DON'T.
THE LONGER YOU STAY HERE,
THE HARDER IT'S GOING TO BE.
>> I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT IT IS
FOR ME TO FINISH MY JUNIOR
YEAR, BUT I NEVER REALIZED
HOW HARD IT WOULD BE TO LEAVE
MY BABY.
[Brody fussing]
>> CODY AND I HAVE BEEN ON
A TIGHT SCHEDULE.
HE MINDS BRODY DURING THE DAY
WHILE I'M AT SCHOOL, AND WHEN
I GET HOME, HE TAKES OFF
AND HEADS TO WORK.
THEN THE NEXT DAY, WE DO IT
ALL OVER AGAIN.
THERE'S NEVER ANY TIME FOR US
TO BE A COUPLE.
WE USED TO SPEND TIME TOGETHER
AT THE TRACK, BUT WE HAD TO GIVE
THAT UP TOO.
BUT TODAY HE'S CALLED IN LATE
TO WORK SO HE CAN BRING ME
TO MY DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
WE'LL TAKE WHATEVER TIME
TOGETHER WE CAN GET.
HI.
>> HEY!
OH, MY GOSH.
WELL, ARE YOU GETTING ANY SLEEP?
>> YEAH, HE'S SLEPT FROM
11:00 TO 6:00 EVERY NIGHT.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S HARD WORK.
>> YEAH.
>> HAVE WE HAD SEX?
>> NOPE.
>> ABSOLUTELY NONE?
>> NOPE, NO NOTHING.
>> OKAY, 'CAUSE WE KNOW WE CAN
GET PREGNANT.
>> YEP, NOT HAPPENING.
>> WHAT DO Y'ALL THINK YOU CAN
REMEMBER FOR BIRTH CONTROL?
>> MIRENA.
>> MIRENA, I.U.D.s.
I THINK IT'S GOOD FOR FIVE
YEARS.
WITH THE I.U.D., THE GOOD THING
ABOUT IT, IT DOESN'T HAVE
A LOT OF HORMONE THAT GOES INTO
YOUR SYSTEM, SO IT SHOULDN'T
AFFECT YOUR BREAST-FEEDING.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S HAVE YOU
LIE BACK.
I'LL PULL THIS UP.
ALL RIGHT.
>> THIS IS AWKWARD.
>> SO YOU MIGHT FEEL
A LITTLE PINCH.
>> OW, THAT HURTS.
>> I'M SORRY.
ALL DONE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, I WANT YOU TO WAIT A
WEEK BEFORE YOU HAVE SEX, OKAY?
ANY QUESTIONS?
>> UH-UH.
>> HOW LONG ARE WE WAITING?
>> both: A WEEK.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> CODY AND I HAVEN'T SAVED
NEARLY ENOUGH TO BUY OUR PREFAB
BARN YET, BUT IT DOESN'T HURT
TO STOP AND TAKE A LOOK
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
>> SAYS CLOSED.
LET'S LOOK AROUND FIRST.
>> OKAY.
THAT ONE CAN BE BRODY'S ROOM.
>> HELL, HE GETS A BIGGER ROOM
THAN WE GOT.
>> WE WANT OUR OWN HOME SO BAD.
BUT WE'RE NEVER GONNA BE ABLE
TO AFFORD IT IF WE DON'T FIGURE
OUT WHERE ALL OF OUR MONEY
IS GOING.
SO AS OF NOW, WE AREN'T PUTTING
ANYTHING ASIDE FOR PAYING BACK
MOM AND DAD OR THE HOUSE
OR ANYTHING.
SO ARE WE GONNA CHANGE THAT NOW
OR...
>> UH, YEAH.
>> ARE WE GONNA KEEP DOING IT
TO SAVE UP FOR THE HOUSE?
>> PRETTY MUCH THE ONLY THING
WE SPEND WEEKLY IS JUST
PROBABLY GAS.
>> CODY.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED TO PULL OUT
THE BANK STATEMENT, BECAUSE WE
HAVE THEM IN THE KITCHEN.
GIVE ME A CALCULATOR.
SMILEY'S, WAS THAT NEEDED?
>> I DIDN'T BUY NEW CLOTHES
FROM SMILEY'S.
>> NOW WE'RE AT $121,
AND THAT'S JUST ONE PAPER.
>> WHAT DID YOU SPEND $35
AT WALMART FOR?
>> I DON'T GO TO WALMART, CODY.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
I DIDN'T SPEND ALL THAT.
>> CODY AND I DON'T HAVE MUCH
TIME TOGETHER, AND EVEN THOUGH,
WE CAN'T AFFORD IT, WE DECIDED
TO MAKE SOME TIME FOR OURSELVES.
>> [sighs]
>> I'M SO TIRED.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
>> IT'S RIDICULOUS.
[Brody fussing]
>> MAMA, PUT HIS PACIFIER IN.
>> [shushing]
TAKE HIS BIB OFF.
HERE, HAND HIM TO ME.
[Brody crying]
HEY, BUDDY.
I WAS EXCITED ABOUT COMING OUT
TONIGHT.
NOW I'M TIRED, AND I FEEL SICK,
AND I WANT TO GO HOME AND GO
TO BED AFTER THIS.
>> I USED TO GO OVER TO NIKKI'S
HOUSE TO HANG OUT, BUT NOW
THERE'S NO TIME FOR HANGING.
I NEED HER TO WATCH BRODY
SO I CAN CATCH UP A LITTLE
ON MY STUDYING.
CODY'S PRETTY EXCITED.
[laughter]
DR. ENGLISH KEPT ASKING ME IF
ME AND CODY HAD DONE ANYTHING
IN SIX WEEKS.
IT'S, LIKE, NO.
HE IS NOT HOME LONG ENOUGH
TO DO ANYTHING.
I PROMISE.
>> CAN MOMMY GET HER HOMEWORK
DONE?
>> I'VE ONLY BEEN OUT OF
THE HOUSE FOR A FEW HOURS,
AND AS SOON AS I GET BACK,
IT FEELS LIKE I'M RUNNING IN
PLACE BETWEEN DOING HOMEWORK
AND CARING FOR BRODY.
I NEVER REALLY GET CAUGHT UP
WITH THE CLEANING AROUND HERE,
WHICH MY MOM EXPECTS US TO DO
SINCE WE DON'T PAY RENT.
>> YOU KNOW THAT THE HOUSE NEEDS
TO BE CLEANED BEFORE FRIDAY
FOR THE WEEKEND, RIGHT?
AND IT'S NOT HAPPENING.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND EVERY TIME WE'VE HAD THIS
CONVERSATION, YOU TELL ME,
"I KNOW," BUT "I KNOW"
ISN'T "I'M GONNA FIX IT."
>> MOM, I TRY.
>> YOU GUYS GOT TO PICK UP
YOUR SLACK, PERIOD.
AND IT'S GONNA GET TO THE POINT
WHERE I'M GONNA START REALLY
GETTING MAD.
WHY DO YOU THINK THERE'S
A PROBLEM WITH GETTING YOUR
PART DONE?
>> I THINK WHEN WE GOT MARRIED,
I MEAN, WE THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA
BE A LITTLE BIT EASIER,
BUT I THINK ONCE REALITY SET IN,
IT'S, LIKE, WHOA.
IT'S, LIKE, NOT AS EASY
AS YOU THINK IT IS.
>> WE'RE ALL COMING TOGETHER
SO THAT YOU CAN LEARN HOW TO BE
A WIFE AND A MOM AND SO THAT YOU
CAN LEARN HOW TO BE A HUSBAND
AND A DAD.
WE'RE TRYING TO GIVE YOU GUYS
THE OPPORTUNITY TO FINISH
SCHOOL, HAVE SOME MONEY SAVED UP
TO FALL BACK ON TO WHERE WHEN
YOU DO MOVE OUT, YOU CAN DO IT
ON YOUR OWN.
IS THIS TOO MUCH?
IS THIS TOO MUCH TO DO?
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> BROOKE, IF IT'S TOO MUCH,
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME.
>> I'M TELLING YOU IT'S NOT
TOO MUCH.
MY MOM WAS ABLE TO MANAGE
WITH ME WHEN SHE WAS A TEENAGER.
I'M NOT GONNA LET HER DOWN
BY MAKING HER RAISE MY BABY.
>> * IF IT'S THE TRUTH *
* THAT SETS YOU FREE *
>> BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
EVERY AFTERNOON I WOULD LEAVE
SCHOOL AND GO TO CODY'S HOUSE
AND LAUGH AND HAVE A GOOD TIME,
BUT NOW AFTER SCHOOL, I PICK UP
BRODY, AND I STAY AT HOME
AND WATCH TV BY MYSELF
BECAUSE CODY'S AT WORK.
SO CODY'S AMAZING.
I MEAN, EVER SINCE DAY ONE
WHEN I FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT,
HE'S STEPPED UP, AND HE'S
BEEN A MAN.
>> THE MAGIC MEDICINE.
WHOO!
>> I COULDN'T ASK FOR ANYTHING
BETTER, BUT NOW HE HAS TO WORK
MORE, AND WE DON'T GET TO SPEND
AS MUCH TIME TOGETHER
AS WE USED TO, AND WE MISS THAT.
JESUS.
IN MY FAMILY, WE'RE ALL ABOUT
RACING AND BEING TOGETHER,
BUT UNTIL WE HAVE ALL OF OUR
STUFF TOGETHER, THERE'S NO WAY
THAT I CAN RACE AND HE CAN RACE
AT THE SAME TIME, 'CAUSE WE JUST
CAN'T AFFORD IT.
I HATE IT WHEN I ARGUE WITH
MY MOM.
IT FEELS LIKE I'M OVERWHELMED
WITH ALL THE CLEANING THAT
I HAVE TO DO, AND IT'S
EXHAUSTING HAVING TO BE A MOM
AND A WIFE AND A DAUGHTER
ALL AT THE SAME TIME.
IT'S OVERWHELMING.
>> I NEVER REALIZED THAT BRODY
COULD TAKE UP SO MUCH SPACE
FOR AS LITTLE AS HE IS.
>> I KNOW.
HE NEEDS A LOT OF STUFF,
AND IT SUCKS.
I JUST--I WANT ME AND CODY
TO HAVE FAMILY TIME ALONE
WITH BRODY.
CODY, I DIDN'T MEAN THAT WAY!
>> WHOO!
>> CODY RYAN!
I DOUBT THAT THAT'S GONNA BE
ABLE TO HAPPEN UNTIL WE MOVE OUT
AND HAVE OUR OWN PLACE.
IT JUST SUCKS THAT WE HAD
TO GROW UP AS FAST AS WE DID.
BUT BRODY'S AMAZING, AND I
WOULDN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com