>> I FEEL LIKE A LITTLE KID.
MY NAME IS WHITNEY,
AND I'M A COUNTRY GIRL FROM THE
SOUTHERN TOWN OF ROME, GEORGIA.
I'M 16,
AND I SPEND MY WEEKENDS
AT THE MALL OR HANGING OUT
WITH MY BEST FRIEND, EERIE.
>> I LIKE THAT ONE.
>> I HAVE LOTS OF FRIENDS
AT SCHOOL, AND WE LOVE
TO GOSSIP AND SHOP.
I'M ONLY A JUNIOR,
BUT I'M ALREADY THINKING ABOUT
GOING TO COLLEGE TO BECOME
AN X-RAY TECHNICIAN.
AND I HAVE A GREAT BOYFRIEND.
HIS NAME IS WESTON.
[chime dings]
HE'S MY FIRST BOYFRIEND,
AND I EVEN LOST MY VIRGINITY
TO HIM.
I HOPE TO LIVE HAPPILY
EVER AFTER WITH WESTON
AND HAVE A BIG HOUSE
AND A BIG FAMILY OF OUR OWN.
[dog barks]
BUT WE'RE NOT READY
FOR ANY OF THAT YET.
WE'RE TRYING TO BE GOOD PARENTS
TO OUR DOG, CHUMPY, BUT SO FAR,
IT'S NOT GOING TOO WELL.
>> HE'S JUST A PAIN
IN THE PANTS.
>> I'M SUPER CLOSE WITH MY
FAMILY, AND ME, MOM, AND GRANDMA
ALL LIVE TOGETHER AT MY
GRANDMA'S HOUSE.
MY MOM'S BOYFRIEND, SCOTT,
LIVES HERE TOO.
I'M AN ONLY CHILD,
SO I'M STILL THE BABY
OF THE FAMILY.
AND THAT'S HOW I LIKE IT.
BUT THAT'S ALL ABOUT TO CHANGE,
BECAUSE MY MOM IS HAVING
ANOTHER BABY.
AND THIS GROWING FAMILY IS ABOUT
TO GET MUCH BIGGER,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT TOO.
>> OH, IT'S SO BIG.
[chime dings]
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
[rock music]
* *
>> WHAT ARE Y'ALL DOING?
>> READY FOR BREAKFAST.
>> WELL, YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT
A FEW MINUTES.
>> MEEMAW LET WESTON MOVE IN
WITH US, SO HE'LL BE HERE
WHEN THE BABY COMES.
HE WORKS SECOND SHIFT
AT THE AUTO PARTS FACTORY,
BUT THEY CUT HIS HOURS BACK,
SO MOST OF THE TIME,
HE'S HOME WITH ME.
ME AND WESTON WERE TOGETHER
LESS THAN A YEAR BEFORE
I GOT PREGNANT.
>> WELL, HOW DID YOU FEEL WHEN
YOU FOUND OUT WHITNEY WAS
PREGNANT, WESTON?
>> I WAS SHOCKED.
>> HE'S STILL IN DENIAL.
>> MAMA, WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN
YOU FOUND OUT ME AND WHITNEY
BOTH WAS PREGNANT
AT THE SAME TIME?
>> SHE WAS SICK.
I CARRIED HER TO THE EMERGENCY
ROOM, AND THEY SAID,
"WELL, GUESS WHAT, WHITNEY?
YOU'RE PREGNANT."
AND I THOUGHT--
>> HONESTLY.
>> "OH, NO."
>> I REMEMBER THE DAY WHEN,
MOM, YOU SAID THAT WHITNEY
WANTED TO TELL ME THAT
SHE WAS PREGNANT.
'CAUSE I KNEW THAT SHE WOULD
BE LIKE ME.
THERE GOES HER SCHOOL,
AND HER TEENAGE YEARS WERE GONE.
>> WHEN I FOUND OUT,
I WAS REAL SCARED.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT
I THOUGHT ABOUT GIVING IT UP,
'CAUSE I THOUGHT I COULDN'T
DO IT.
WE THOUGHT ABOUT ABORTION
AND ADOPTION AT FIRST.
WHEN I DECIDED THAT I WOULD KEEP
IT FOR SURE, THAT'S WHEN I WENT
TO THE DOCTOR THE FIRST TIME.
YOU REMEMBER, AT THE HOSPITAL?
>> YEAH.
>> AND THEN I SAW IT AND...
>> AND YOU LOOKED SO EXCITED,
LIKE AN ANGEL HAD KISSED YOU.
>> WHEN I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, I WAS EMBARRASSED
AND AFRAID OF WHAT PEOPLE
WOULD THINK ABOUT ME,
SO I DROPPED OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL.
I HOPED I COULD GET MY GED
AND STILL GO TO COLLEGE,
BUT NOW I'VE BEEN PREGNANT
FOR OVER SIX MONTHS,
AND I BARELY LEAVE THE HOUSE.
I EVEN STOPPED HANGING OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS BECAUSE I DON'T
WANT PEOPLE TO SEE ME.
>> HEY, WHITNEY.
>> HI.
BUT I CAN'T ISOLATE FOREVER,
SO I'M GONNA FACE MY FEARS
AT THE MALL WITH MY BEST FRIEND,
EERIE.
HOW'S SCHOOL?
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> WHAT DID YOU WANT TO DO
AT THE MALL?
>> I DON'T CARE.
ARE YOU GONNA FEEL NERVOUS
ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE SEEING YOU?
>> YEAH, TO BE HONEST.
>> MAYBE IT'LL BE OKAY.
>> [sighs]
>> HEY, GUYS.
>> HEY.
>> THIS SHOULD BE A LESSON
FOR YOU.
>> WHAT?
TO NOT GET PREGNANT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
[laughter]
>> BEING PREGNANT
IS A BEAUTIFUL THING.
>> NOT ON THE OUTSIDE, IT'S NOT.
[percussive music]
* *
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SCARED
IS GONNA HAPPEN,
'CAUSE I HAVEN'T TOLD THAT MANY
PEOPLE AT ALL.
>> I WOULDN'T EVEN WORRY
ABOUT THEM.
>> [gasps]
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OH, GOD.
I AM GETTING NERVOUS ABOUT THIS.
JUST SEEING YOUNG PEOPLE AROUND
JUST MAKES ME WANT TO CRAWL INTO
A LITTLE HOLE.
>> BE CAREFUL
AND WATCH FOR STRANGERS.
>> I'M JUST NERVOUS.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BE NERVOUS.
>> OKAY.
I'M TRYING TO SEE IF THERE'S
ANYBODY HERE WE KNOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
TOTALLY AWKWARD.
I'M SO SCARED.
>> DID YOU JUST SEE SOMEBODY?
>> NO, I JUST FEEL LIKE
EVERYBODY IS STARING AT ME,
MAYBE BECAUSE I HAVE
A BEACH BALL UNDER MY SHIRT.
I REALLY THINK THAT IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE I'M PREGNANT.
I THINK IT JUST LOOKS LIKE
I'M FAT.
>> YOU LOOK PREGNANT.
>> EVERYTHING CHANGES.
YOUR BOOBS GET BIGGER,
YOUR BELLY, YOUR ARMS.
>> YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE
A BIG TUB OF LARD.
YOU JUST LOOK LIKE YOU HAVE
A BABY.
>> I KNOW.
IT'S SO AWKWARD.
THERE'S KASSI.
>> HEY.
>> HOW ARE Y'ALL?
>> GOOD.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WHO HAS COLD HANDS?
[chime dings]
>> I GUESS OTHER KIDS DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY WHEN THEY SEE I'M
PREGNANT, SO THEY JUST STARE.
[hushed giggling]
>> WOW.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M STARTING TO SEE HOW MUCH
MY LIFE HAS CHANGED SINCE
I GOT PREGNANT.
I'VE BEEN HIDING OUT SO LONG.
I WONDER IF MY OLD FRIENDS
WILL COME TO MY BABY SHOWER.
>> SO WHO DO YOU WANT TO INVITE
TO YOUR BABY SHOWER?
>> I HAVE A LIST OF
THESE PEOPLE.
WHO ELSE?
>> ARE YOU INVITING TIFFANY?
>> NOT PLANNING ON IT.
>> SO, WHITNEY, HOW COME YOU
DON'T WANT TO INVITE TIFFANY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU DON'T SEE HER ANYMORE,
BUT Y'ALL USED TO BE FRIENDS.
>> WE'RE NOT FRIENDS ANYMORE.
>> WOULD YOU INVITE SARAH?
>> I HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER
IN SO LONG.
>> BRYANT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO FEEL STUPID
BY SENDING THEM A BABY SHOWER--
>> INVITATION.
>> WHAT ABOUT TIMOTHY?
>> WE'RE NOT FRIENDS.
JUST AN OPINION.
>> AND ERIN?
>> HER MOM WON'T EVEN LET HER
TALK TO ME ANYMORE,
'CAUSE I GOT PREGNANT.
>> WHY DO PEOPLE THINK
IF THEY HANG OUT WITH YOU,
THEY'RE GONNA GET PREGNANT TOO?
>> IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE HOW MANY
PEOPLE I'VE JUST--
JUST DRIFTED AWAY FROM.
>> YOU SHOULD INVITE HIM.
>> WHEN YOU GET PREGNANT AND
YOU'RE NOT IN SCHOOL ANYMORE,
THE KIDS, THEY GO ON.
SPORTS.
THEY MEET NEW FRIENDS.
>> I FEEL SO ABANDONED.
>> WELL, I KNOW.
YOU HAD SO MANY FRIENDS,
AND YOU WERE SO POPULAR.
IF YOU'D HAVE NOT GOTTEN
PREGNANT AND STILL BEEN IN
SCHOOL, YOU'D PROBABLY STILL
HAD A WHOLE LOT OF FRIENDS.
[dog barks]
WELL, YOU FEEL LOST WITHOUT
YOUR FRIENDS, DON'T YOU?
[dog barks]
CHUMPY.
CHUMPY, WHAT YOU DOING?
>> [gasps]
OH, MY GOD.
[mellow music]
>> CHUMPY!
CHUMPY?
>> * EVERY FATHER *
* AND EVERY SON *
>> COME ON, BOY!
>> * EVERY NATION *
* AND EVERY TOWN *
* WHO WILL GIVE US LOVE? *
>> [crying]
I LOST MY FRIENDS
AND NOW MY DOG.
HOW MUCH HARDER CAN THIS GET?
>> WESTON FINALLY FOUND CHUMPY,
AND THINGS ARE BACK TO NORMAL.
BUT MY DUE DATE
IS IN FIVE WEEKS,
AND WE STILL NEED TONS
OF STUFF FOR THE BABY.
>> IS THAT FOR YOU?
>> YES.
>> ARE WE GONNA CHANGE YOUR
DIAPER IN IT?
>> GET CHUMPY A JOB.
[dog barks]
>> WESTON'S JOB DOESN'T PAY
MUCH, SO MONEY IS TIGHT.
[rock music]
* *
I JUST HOPE WE CAN AFFORD
A CRIB.
>> THIS IS A BEAUTIFUL CRIB.
THIS IS A CHANGING TABLE.
WE HAVE TOYS.
>> WAY TOO EXPENSIVE.
>> YEAH.
WOW, THIS STUFF'S REALLY
EXPENSIVE.
WE'RE DEFINITELY NOT READY YET
FOR THIS BABY, BUT IT'S COMING
WHETHER WE'RE READY OR NOT.
>> WE'RE GONNA LOOK AT YOUR
BABY.
ARE YOU GETTING EXCITED?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU HAVE EVERYTHING READY?
[gasping]
>> OH.
>> HE'S GOT WHITNEY'S NOSE.
>> AND THERE'S THIS,
IF YOU HAVE ANY DOUBT.
[laughter]
>> AND THIS IS THE BABY'S FACE
RIGHT UP AGAINST HER UTERUS.
>> THAT LITTLE CHIN.
>> I THINK HE'LL LOOK LIKE ME.
>> I THINK SO TOO.
>> OH, LOOK.
THERE HE GOES TO YAWN AGAIN.
>> OH.
>> SEE THAT?
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA HELP YOU
SIT UP.
>> MM.
>> WHITNEY CAN'T TIE HER SHOE
HERSELF?
>> SHE'S USED TO BEING WAITED ON
HAND AND FOOT.
>> OH, WHITNEY.
ARE THEY SPOILING YOU?
>> ROTTEN.
>> THAT'S NOT GOOD.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA STAY THAT WAY,
WILL IT?
>> THAT'S NOT REALITY.
>> SHE THOUGHT SHE'D ALWAYS BE
A ONLY CHILD.
[chime dings]
>> YES, I'VE BEEN BABIED
MY WHOLE LIFE, BUT WHO WANTS
TO GROW UP?
I WANT TO HAVE FUN
WHILE I STILL CAN,
SO WESTON'S TAKING ME OUT
TO THE BIG EVENT IN TOWN:
FIGHT NIGHT.
[applause]
[bell dings]
>> I KNOW.
THEY PROBABLY DON'T, DO THEY?
[man yelling]
[bell dings]
THAT WAS SO BLOODY.
>> YOUR DAD'S HERE.
>> WHAT?
[cheering]
>> MY DAD'S HERE?
>> WHITNEY, WHY DON'T YOU
TALK TO HIM FOR A SECOND, OKAY?
>> [whimpers]
>> MY PARENTS SPLIT WHEN I WAS
LITTLE, AND MY DAD NEVER CAME
AROUND MUCH, SO I'M ALWAYS
NERVOUS WHEN I SEE HIM.
>> YOU HIDING?
>> [giggles]
>> ALL THE WAY IN THE BACK.
>> WELL, WE WERE GONNA SAY,
"HEY."
THE SHOWER'S TOMORROW.
I WISH YOU'D COME.
WELL.
>> WE'RE GONNA GET OUT OF HERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHEN.
OKAY, BYE.
>> SEE YOU LATER.
>> IT'S FINALLY THE DAY
OF MY BABY SHOWER,
BUT I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO WEAR.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY IT'S SUCH
A BIG DEAL.
UM, THIS IS PRETTY.
>> SEE HOW THEY MAKE
MATERNITY SHIRTS?
THEY'RE ALWAYS WIDE.
>> WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY SHOWER.
YOU'RE NOT GOING DOWN
THE RUNWAY.
[giggling]
GROSS.
MY BACK IS HURTING.
>> YOU KNOW THAT MY DAD
WILL BE THERE?
IS THAT GONNA BE WEIRD FOR YOU?
>> NO, WHY?
WE GET ALONG GREAT.
>> BUT I REALLY DON'T
LIKE TO BE AROUND HIM.
>> WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE GETS ON MY NERVES, LIKE--
>> THAT'S YOU STIRRING UP CRAP.
>> [snorts]
>> YOU KNOW, SOME PEOPLE DON'T
HAVE IT LIKE YOU'VE GOT IT.
ME AND YOUR DADDY
NEVER CROSSED WORDS.
IT JUST WASN'T THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> MM-HMM.
[smacking sounds]
>> GEEZ, I THINK THE DOG'S
EATING YOUR MAKEUP.
OH!
CHUMPY, YOU NEED A WHIPPIN'.
GET!
>> OKAY, HOW DOES THIS LOOK?
>> I LIKE IT.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> MEEMAW'S HOUSE IS TOO SMALL
FOR MY BABY SHOWER,
SO YOU'LL NEVER GUESS WHERE
WE'RE HAVING IT IN:
THE BOXING GYM.
[bluesy music]
* *
[laughter]
>> OHH.
>> HOW'S HIGH SCHOOL?
>> IT'S KIND OF LAME.
>> OH, SOMEBODY TRIED TO CATCH
THE GIRL'S BATHROOM ON FIRE,
AND MR. HUBBARD WAS LOOKING
AT ME LIKE I DID IT.
[laughter]
>> I WAS WORRIED AT FIRST,
BUT I'M REALLY HAPPY THAT SOME
OF MY FRIENDS FROM SCHOOL CAME.
BUT THERE'S STILL ONE PERSON
MISSING.
I DIDN'T THINK I WANTED
TO SEE MY DAD, BUT I WAS WRONG.
>> IT'S JUST THE BIGGEST BABY.
>> THAT GIRL WAS LIKE--
[all chattering indistinctly]
>> I THOUGHT YOUR DADDY
WAS COMING.
>> I DO WISH MY DAD
WAS IN MY LIFE MORE,
BUT IT MAKES ME REALIZE
HOW LUCKY MY BABY WILL BE
TO HAVE A DADDY LIKE WESTON.
YOU KNOW WHAT WAS REAL STRANGE
TODAY AT THE BABY SHOWER?
>> WHAT?
>> IT WAS JUST WEIRD KIND OF
ABOUT MY DAD.
MY GRANDMA, LIKE, ACTED LIKE
EVERYTHING SHOULD BE FINE
BETWEEN ME AND HIM.
I MEAN, MY MOM AND DAD WEREN'T
EVEN REALLY TOGETHER AT ALL.
I THINK IT WAS MORE OF A--
LIKE A ONE NIGHT STAND THING.
AND THEN HE WAS NEVER AROUND.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR DAD?
>> AS SOON AS THEY GOT
A DIVORCE, I HARDLY EVER
SAW HIM AGAIN.
>> I WANT TO BE A REALLY
GOOD MOM.
I'M STILL NOT GONNA KNOW
HOW TO DO EVERYTHING,
AND MY MOM'S STILL GONNA
HAVE TO HELP ME.
>> I THINK YOU'LL BE
A GREAT MOM.
>> I SURE HOPE HE'S RIGHT.
AND I SURE HOPE WE'LL BE READY
BY THE TIME THE BABY COMES.
>> MEEMAW, IT'S TIME TO GET UP.
>> MM.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
>> IT'S BREAKFAST TIME.
>> THE BIGGER ME AND MOM GET,
THE MORE CROWDED THE HOUSE
SEEMS.
>> WE GOT TO GET ANOTHER
BATHROOM OR BUILD AN OUTHOUSE
OR SOMETHING.
>> MEEMAW LET ME AND WESTON
HAVE HER ROOM, AND MY MOM
AND HER BOYFRIEND, SCOTT,
ARE LIVING IN THE SPARE ROOM.
SO MEEMAW SLEEPS ON THE COUCH.
TWO PREGNANT LADIES
AND ONE BATHROOM IS NOT WORKING.
AND WESTON'S WORK KEEPS
CUTTING BACK HOURS,
SO HE'S HOME MORE TOO.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE ANY ROOM?
YOUR BABY'S GONNA BE SLEEPING
IN A DRESSER DRAWER.
>> THE HOUSE IS A MESS,
BECAUSE THERE'S NO ROOM.
AND WE'RE ALL GETTING ON
EACH OTHER'S NERVES.
>> YOU GONNA HAVE A BABY,
YOU GOT TO HAVE SOMEWHERE
TO LIVE.
YOU KNOW.
>> CHAMBERS?
>> SO ME AND WESTON ARE SAVING
UP FOR OUR OWN PLACE.
>> IS THIS IT?
>> UM, $475 A MONTH.
>> IT'S BIG.
I'VE NEVER BEEN INSIDE
A PLACE LIKE THIS.
>> CAN WE HAVE PETS?
>> OH, I'M SORRY.
IT IS A NO-PET BUILDING.
>> IT'S NICE, BUT WE OBVIOUSLY
DON'T HAVE SOMEWHERE FOR CHUMPY.
>> YEAH.
>> WE DO HAVE A HOUSE,
AND I BELIEVE THEY WOULD TAKE
A PET TOO.
>> OKAY.
>> IN THIS HOUSE, ALL THE ROOMS
ARE JUST REPAINTED.
KITCHEN.
>> BIG CLOSET.
>> WASHING MACHINE AND DRYER.
CLAW-FOOT TUB.
[chuckles]
NURSERY.
>> IT'S COZY.
YEAH, PLENTY OF ROOM.
I LIKE IT.
>> I LIKE IT.
>> THIS HOUSE RENTS FOR $550
A MONTH.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS,
JUST COME GET ME.
>> OKAY, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> W-W-WHAT ARE WE HOPING FOR
EXACTLY?
>> PROBABLY AROUND PAYING $450.
>> $100 OVER.
>> BUT IT'S A HOUSE.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT AN APARTMENT.
THE BABY WOULD HAVE
ITS OWN ROOM.
>> AND CHUMPY, HE'D HAVE
SOMEWHERE TO RUN AND PLAY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND CHUMPY'S GIRLFRIEND.
[giggling]
IT'D BE WORTH IT, I THINK.
>> WE LOVE IT,
AND CHUMPY WILL TOO.
I JUST HOPE WE'RE READY
TO LEAVE THE NEST.
>> WELL, I HOPE Y'ALL
ARE HUNGRY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> BEEN BUSY TODAY, AIN'T YOU?
>> WHAT DID Y'ALL FIGURE OUT
ABOUT THAT HOUSE?
>> IT WAS A NICE PLACE.
>> WE LIKE IT A LOT.
>> IT'S GONNA BE SCARY.
IT'S REAL SCARY, WHITNEY,
LEAVING TO TEND TO A BABY
BY YOURSELF.
>> I CAN DO IT.
>> MEEMAW, I BET YOU'LL BE GLAD
FOR US TO BE GONE.
>> BUT I DON'T WANT YOU TO STAY
GONE ALL THE TIME.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS HOME.
COME BACK HERE.
>> MM-HMM.
WE HAVE AN APPOINTMENT TODAY
WITH THE REALTOR
TO TALK ABOUT THE HOUSE WE WANT.
>> I KNOW Y'ALL LIKED THE HOUSE,
AND IT'S STILL AVAILABLE.
ARE YOU STILL LEANING
TOWARDS THAT?
>> YES, MA'AM.
>> OKAY.
NOW, TELL ME HOW MANY HOURS
A WEEK DO YOU WORK?
>> RIGHT NOW IT'S A MONTH--
A WEEK OFF EVERY MONTH.
>> I SEE.
>> AND WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GO
TO THREE DAYS A WEEK IN MARCH.
>> WOW. OKAY.
>> WE'VE BEEN AT FOUR DAYS.
>> AND THEY'RE CUTTING BACK
EVEN MORE.
LET ME JUST DO THIS MATH
REAL QUICK AND SEE.
OKAY.
UM.
REALISTICALLY,
THIS MAY BE STRETCHING IT.
YOU MAY WANT TO JUST SEE
WHAT YOUR HOURS ARE GONNA BE
AND JUST STAY PUT.
UM, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> DO WE EVEN WANT TO LOOK
AT ANY OTHER HOUSES?
>> TO BE HONEST, I JUST DON'T
THINK WE CAN AFFORD IT.
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
I KNOW.
I WISH I KNEW MORE ABOUT
WHAT WAS GONNA HAPPEN.
>> ME TOO.
>> WELL, HE'S EXCITED.
WHAT Y'ALL DO?
>> MEETING WITH THE REAL ESTATE
AGENT.
>> OH, DID THAT GO PRETTY GOOD?
>> WE JUST TALKED ABOUT WHAT
WE THINK WE CAN AFFORD AND...
>> THEY SAID IT WOULD PROBABLY
BE BEST IF WE WAITED, THOUGH.
>> WELL, I HAVE SOME BAD NEWS,
AND I DON'T WANT TO DROP
ANOTHER BOMB ON YOU,
BUT I TALKED TO THE LANDLORD
TODAY.
HE'S SELLING THIS HOUSE,
AND I ASKED HIM HOW MUCH TIME
WE HAVE BEFORE WE HAD TO MOVE,
AND HE SAID FOR ME
TO START PREPARING NOW.
>> BUT HE KNOWS THAT WE DON'T
HAVE NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
>> I TRIED TO TALK TO HIM.
IT DIDN'T WORK.
>> WELL, WHY WOULD HE PICK
RIGHT NOW?
>> WELL, FOR ONE THING--
>> HE CAN'T WAIT?
HE CAN'T WAIT A MONTH OR TWO?
>> WHITNEY, THE HOUSE MAY NOT
SELL FOR TWO WEEKS, A MONTH.
>> OKAY.
>> WE GOT A WHOLE LOT TO THINK
OF, REALLY, REALLY SHORT TIME.
>> WHERE WILL WE LIVE?
HOW WILL WE PAY FOR EVERYTHING?
AND WILL MY BABY HAVE A PLACE
TO SLEEP IN THIS MESS?
>> THE HOUSE HASN'T SOLD YET,
SO FOR NOW, IT'S STILL OUR HOME.
AND WE'RE ALL BUSY GETTING READY
FOR MOM'S NEW BABY.
WE'RE EXCITED FOR MY MOM
TO FINALLY BRING HOME MY
BABY BROTHER, TACCOA...
>> THEY JUST PULLED UP.
>> EVEN IF IT MEANS I'M NOT
THE BABY OF THE HOUSE ANYMORE.
>> COME LOOK AT THE BABY.
>> LOOK AT HIS CAR SEAT.
I'M JEALOUS.
>> YOU'RE GETTING ONE, WHITNEY.
>> YOU'RE JEALOUS?
>> YOUR SISTER.
YEAH.
UH-OH, MAKE SURE YOU HOLD
HIS LITTLE HEAD.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD, WHITNEY.
>> [giggles]
>> DOES HE FEEL LIKE YOU
THOUGHT A LITTLE, BITTY,
BITTY BABY WOULD FEEL LIKE?
YOU HOLD HIM LIKE YOU'VE DONE IT
ALL YOUR LIFE.
[baby fusses]
>> DOES HE NEED HIS DIAPER
CHANGED?
>> I THINK SO.
>> THIS GONNA BE YOUR FIRST
DIAPER CHANGE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> OH, REALLY, YOUR FIRST ONE.
OKAY.
PUT THE DIAPER UNDER THERE.
EASY, EASY, EASY, EASY WITH HIM.
WELL, THAT A BOY.
[chime dings]
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE CHANGING
A DIAPER IS THIS MUCH WORK.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> MY STOMACH.
>> YOU NEED SOMETHING TO EAT?
WHY DON'T YOU COOK SOMETHING?
>> BECAUSE MY FEET ARE SWOLLEN.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE STANDING UP
AND COOKING.
>> YOU CAN'T EAT IT
IF IT'S NOT COOKED.
>> [sighs]
>> GET A FRYING PAN OUT,
PUT IT ON THE STOVE,
AND START FRYING THE BACON.
>> I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THAT.
>> OKAY, YOUR BABY'S
GONNA STARVE, BOTTOM LINE.
>> [exasperated sigh]
>> OH, SHE'S MAD, WESTON.
>> SHE'S GONNA COOK SOMETHING?
>> OOH.
I CAN SEE FIRE IN THE OVEN--
>> SEE?
YOU CAN'T FRY NOTHING IN HER
KITCHEN, SO THERE'S NO PURPOSE
OF EVEN DOING IT, 'CAUSE YOU
JUST GET FRUSTRATED
AND THINGS FALL OUT.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
YOU GOT TO BE ABLE TO DO
ALL THESE THINGS AT ONE TIME.
BURP HIM, CHANGE A DIAPER,
AND COOK AND MAKE SURE THE HOUSE
IS CLEAN AND THE LAUNDRY'S DONE.
>> JUST 'CAUSE I DIDN'T WANT
TO COOK ANYTHING,
I HAVE TO HEAR THIS LECTURE?
>> [moans mockingly]
POOR LITTLE BABY.
>> BUT IT'S NOT...
NO.
>> OH.
>> SINCE MY LITTLE BROTHER,
TACCOA, WAS BORN, THE HOUSE IS
EVEN MORE CLUTTERED, AND MEEMAW
IS CONSTANTLY NAGGING US
ABOUT IT.
>> LOOK AT ALL THESE DIRTY
CLOTHES.
WE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THE DOG HAIR.
WELL, Y'ALL GOT TO GET THIS
STUFF ORGANIZED AROUND HERE.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO HAVE
JUST ONE LITTLE ROOM.
>> WHY DO YOU HAVE TO START?
>> IF I DIDN'T COMPLAIN,
I WOULDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO TALK ABOUT.
>> SO ME AND WESTON DECIDED
TO CLEAN UP OUR STUFF,
BUT WE CAN'T FIND ANY PLACE
TO PUT IT.
THESE DRAWERS ARE JUST ALL
STUPID STUFF.
LOOK, WHAT IS THIS?
A ROCK.
A BROKEN CALCULATOR.
REO SPEEDWAGON LIVE.
I'M SO SICK AND TIRED OF IT
HERE.
>> IS WHITNEY AND THEM--
WESTON HELPING YOU?
>> IT'S JUST--
IT'S AWFUL.
IT'S BEEN SO HARD, YOU KNOW?
>> IT'S RIDICULOUS
THAT THEY CAN'T HELP YOU SOME.
[breathy laughter]
>> OKAY.
[laughter]
WHAT IS THAT?
THAT IS AWFUL.
[giggles]
>> "I HAVE NO DRINKING PROBLEM.
I DRINK.
I-I GET DRUNK.
I FALL DOWN.
NO PROBLEM."
>> YOU WANT TO GO IN AND SAY,
"HEY, CAN YOU WASH MY COFFEE CUP
FOR ME?"
>> "COULD YOU FIX ME
A CUP OF COFFEE?"
>> [laughs]
I'M GOING TO.
MEEMAW?
>> WHAT?
>> WHEN YOU FIXING A POT
OF COFFEE, WILL YOU TELL ME
AND FIX ME A CUP?
>> IF YOU DON'T STAY OUT
OF MY MOTHER'S DRESSER DRAWERS
AND OUT OF MY PRIVATE STUFF,
I'M GONNA MOVE YOUR ASS
OUT OF HERE.
THIS IS MY HOUSE.
THAT'S MY ROOM.
>> OKAY, SO DON'T COMPLAIN
ABOUT THE CLOTHES, 'CAUSE YOU
KNOW WE DON'T HAVE NOWHERES
TO PUT THEM.
>> YOU CAN FOLD THEM.
>> YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO ARGUE
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
>> I AM SICK OF YOU DICTATING
TO ME EVERY DAMN DAY OF THE
[bleep] WEEK!
>> WHATEVER.
I WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE A JOKE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU THINK
YOU ARE, WHITNEY, BUT YOU'RE
JUST A LITTLE BIT TOO YOUNG
TO BE SCREAMING AND HOLLERING
AT ME.
>> OKAY, WELL, I GET TIRED
OF HEARING YOU CONSTANTLY.
>> I'M TIRED OF Y'ALL
NOT DAMN DOING ANYTHING!
>> WE DON'T DO ANYTHING?
YOU SIT THERE AND COMPLAIN
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE MONEY
ALL THE TIME, BUT YOU--
YET YOU PUT IT IN SLOT MACHINES
AND LOTTERY--
>> WELL, WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU'RE PARIS HILTON
OR SOME-DAMN-BODY?
>> WE CAN'T [bleep] STAND IT
HERE ANYMORE 'CAUSE YOU'RE
THE MOST AWFULEST PERSON
TO BE AROUND.
>> THEN DON'T!
TOMORROW Y'ALL NEED TO MOVE.
>> OKAY.
>> SOME DAMN WAY OR ANOTHER.
>> [sighs]
>> THAT WENT WELL.
>> I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO MEEMAW
SINCE OUR FIGHT, AND SHE STILL
WANTS TO KICK US OUT
OF THE HOUSE.
SO WESTON'S MOM IS TAKING ME
TO MY LAST DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
>> YOU'RE GONNA DO FINE.
YOU OUGHT TO DO FINE.
>> COMING IN.
WHITNEY?
HEY, HOW ARE Y'ALL DOING?
ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
YOU LOOK A LITTLE BIT SCARED
THIS TIME.
IS IT BECAUSE IT'S SO CLOSE?
>> I'M JUST SCARED THAT IT'S
GONNA HURT REAL BAD.
>> DO YOU HAVE A HIGH
PAIN THRESHOLD, YOU THINK?
>> I'M A CRYBABY.
>> CRYBABY?
OKAY, YOU CAN JUST
LAY RIGHT BACK HERE.
I'M JUST GONNA MEASURE YOU HERE.
40 CENTIMETERS.
SO THAT'S VERY GOOD.
AND IS HE MOVING GOOD TOO?
YOU STILL GETTING A LOT
OF GOOD FETAL MOVEMENT?
>> UH, KIND OF.
HE DOESN'T MOVE AROUND AS MUCH.
>> NOT AS MUCH?
[solemn piano music]
UM, WELL, TODAY THEN,
WHAT I'LL DO IS, UM,
WE'LL PUT YOU ON THE MONITOR
FOR ABOUT 20 MINUTES
AND JUST MAKE SURE THAT HE'S
NOT UNDER ANY STRESS,
BECAUSE THEY REALLY SHOULD STAY
WITH THEIR SAME ACTIVE PATTERNS
ALL THE WAY UP UNTIL
YOU DELIVER.
WELL, YOU CAN FOLLOW ME,
AND I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE ROOM
WHERE THE TEST IS DONE, OKAY?
>> [crying]
>> WHAT'S THE MATTER?
>> [sniffles]
I'M JUST SCARED.
>> YOU'RE GONNA GET THROUGH
THIS, I PROMISE.
[heartbeat pulses on monitor]
>> YOU OKAY?
OKAY.
>> WHITNEY?
HEY.
WELL, THIS IS DR. FREEMAN.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> HEY, WE WERE LOOKING AT
THE MONITOR STRIP FOR YOUR BABY,
AND IT'S NOT PERFECT.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS,
WE REALLY WANT TO MOVE TOWARDS
YOU HAVING THE BABY SOONER
RATHER THAN LATER.
SO WE'RE GONNA GO AHEAD AND SEND
YOU ON OVER TO THE HOSPITAL.
THIS BABY'S READY TO BE BORN,
I THINK, SO...
>> WELL, THIS IS--
THIS IS UNEXPECTED.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE I'M HAVING
THIS BABY TONIGHT.
I SPENT THE NIGHT IN THE
HOSPITAL, AND THEY GAVE ME
PITOCIN TO INDUCE MY LABOR.
THE CONTRACTIONS WERE THE WORST
PAIN I'VE EVER FELT.
[sobs]
GET THE NURSE.
THINGS GOT EVEN SCARIER
WHEN THEY TOLD ME MY BABY
WASN'T GETTING ENOUGH OXYGEN.
SO I HAD TO HAVE A C-SECTION.
AND I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH
AFTER THAT.
>> MISS WHITNEY, YOU READY?
>> WHEN IT WAS OVER...
>> HE'S LOOKING REAL NICE.
>> MY BABY WAS PERFECT.
MEEMAW AND I PUT OUR DIFFERENCES
ASIDE TO CELEBRATE,
AND EERIE CAME TOO EVEN THOUGH
IT WAS PROM NIGHT.
WE NAMED HIM AFTER WESTON.
I'M FINALLY HEALED ENOUGH
TO LEAVE THE HOSPITAL.
OW!
I'VE NEVER BEEN IN SO MUCH PAIN
IN MY LIFE.
[moans]
A C-SECTION IS MAJOR SURGERY,
AND I HAD EIGHT STAPLES
IN MY BELLY.
>> [giggling]
>> HELLO.
WELL, WHITNEY, YOU'RE NOT
STILL MAD AT ME?
>> MM-MM.
>> WELL, I LOVE YOU.
AND HOW YOU FEELING?
>> GOOD.
[chime dings]
OKAY, I LIED.
I FEEL AWFUL.
[sobbing]
>> IT'S ALL RIGHT.
>> [sobs]
>> [shushes]
>> CAN YOU HOLD THIS
FOR A SECOND?
>> SURE.
>> THANK GOD FOR WESTON.
>> EAT IT UP.
>> [burps]
>> LITTLE BIT MORE.
[water running]
[sighs]
A LITTLE BIT MORE.
>> [burps]
>> [chuckles]
[kissing sound]
WHITNEY?
HOW YOU DOING?
>> IT JUST HURTS REALLY BAD.
>> IT'LL GET BETTER.
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
I WISH I COULD BELIEVE THAT.
>> LOOK WHO THIS IS.
>> I'M FINALLY RECOVERING
FROM MY C-SECTION.
AND NOW THERE ARE TWO BABIES
IN THE HOUSE AND PLENTY FOR ME
TO LEARN.
EW.
HIS THROW UP SMELLS LIKE
THROW UP.
>> [fusses]
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M TRYING HARD,
BUT I CAN'T DO IT WITHOUT HELP
FROM MY FAMILY.
HAVING A BABY IS EXHAUSTING,
AND I HAVEN'T HAD ANY TIME
FOR MY FRIENDS.
HOW ARE WE GONNA--
>> BYE.
>> THE LAST TIME I SAW EERIE
WAS WHEN SHE VISITED ME
AT THE HOSPITAL ON PROM NIGHT.
SO I'M TAKING LITTLE WESTON
OUT TO THE MALL.
HOW WAS PROM?
>> YOU WENT TO PROM?
>> IT WAS LIKE PROM, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> I WAS GONNA GO THIS YEAR.
I WAS GONNA GO.
>> WELL, NOW THIS IS WHAT
YOU GOT TO DO INSTEAD OF PROM.
>> SO HOW'S SCHOOL?
>> I'D RATHER DROP OUT
THAN STAY IN THERE.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THE WHOLE
GET PREGNANT PART.
>> I DON'T REMEMBER HOW
TO OPEN THIS.
>> YOU PRESS THIS BUTTON THAT'S
NOT--I DON'T KNOW.
>> READY, PUT DOWN.
[baby cries]
HOLD ONTO THIS SIDE.
THIS IS EMBARRASSING.
OW.
GOD DAMN IT!
GOING TO THE MALL WAS NEVER
THIS MUCH WORK.
>> DO YOU LIKE BEING A MOM?
>> IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE
I'M A MOM.
IT JUST FEELS LIKE I'M WHITNEY.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I JUST HAVE A BABY.
>> HOW LONG DO YOU THINK IT
WILL, LIKE, TO TAKE TO REALLY
FEEL THAT--IT'S, LIKE,
"OH, I'M A MOM."
>> IT'LL PROBABLY TAKE ME
A WHILE IF MY FAMILY KEEPS
TREATING ME LIKE A BABY.
>> WHITNEY, YOU NEED TO PICK
YOUR STUFF UP OFF THE FLOOR.
>> WE GOT TO TRY TO GET SOME
OF THIS STUFF STRAIGHTENED UP
AND MOVED AROUND IN HERE.
YOU JUST GOT TO GET MOTIVATED.
AND SOMEBODY COULD GET
A FLYSWATTER EVERY NOW AND THEN
AND KILL A DAMN FLY.
>> OKAY.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
[patting]
>> YOU KNOW WHAT, WHITNEY?
>> I KNOW IT, MEEMAW.
[baby coos]
IT'S A LOT OF NEW
RESPONSIBILITY, BUT ME AND
WESTON ARE LEARNING TO HANDLE
THINGS ON OUR OWN.
>> DID HE BURP AT ALL?
>> MM-MM.
>> YOU GOT TO BURP.
YOU GOT TO BURP.
[baby crying]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
ALL THIS?
>> I'M WORRIED SICK.
THEY NEED TO TAKE ON
SOME RESPONSIBILITY.
>> THEY'RE OLD ENOUGH TO HAVE
SEX, THEY THOUGHT.
THEY'VE GOT TO BE OLD ENOUGH
TO TRY TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO BE
PARENTS, GOOD PARENTS.
>> LEAVE DISHES ALL OVER,
AROUND IN THE BEDROOM.
DIRTY CLOTHES IN THE BATHROOM.
THEY JUST MAKE BIG-ASS MESSES.
AND I'M TIRED OF CLEANING IT UP.
>> I'M TIRED OF IT TOO.
I KNOW THEY'RE BOTH OLD ENOUGH
TO KNOW HOW TO USE
A WASHING MACHINE.
BUT REALITY'S FIXING TO HIT 'EM
RIGHT SMACK IN THE FACE.
BUT IT'S--
NOW'S THE TIME FOR THEM
TO MOVE ALONG.
>> YOU OKAY?
[guitar music]
>> WHY?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
>> WHAT DID SHE MEAN BY THAT?
[laughs]
HE'S SLEEPY.
WELL, Y'ALL,
IT'S JUST NOT WORKING OUT
AT MEEMAW'S.
>> WE JUST REALLY NEED
TO GET OUT OF THERE.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
WHEN I WAS GONNA SAY THIS,
BUT I WAS, WELL, THIS WOULD BE
THE BEST TIME, I GUESS.
YOU KNOW WE'VE GOT THAT UPSTAIRS
IN THE HOUSE THAT WE'VE USED
FOR STORAGE.
THERE'S TWO BEDROOMS
AND A BATHROOM.
AND IT WOULD TAKE SOME WORK,
BUT IF Y'ALL ARE INTERESTED,
WE WOULD LOVE TO HAVE Y'ALL,
YOU KNOW, AT LEAST CONSIDER
COMING TO STAY WITH US.
>> THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
>> IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
>> IT'S PERFECT.
>> GOOD.
Y'ALL WOULD HAVE PLENTY OF ROOM.
PLENTY OF ROOM.
AND CHUMPY TOO.
>> AND WE'RE FINALLY
GONNA DO IT.
>> CAROL ASKED US IF WE WANTED
TO MOVE IN WITH HER,
AND SO WE THINK WE WILL.
>> I WANT TO GIVE THE BABY
A HUG.
I'M GLAD Y'ALL ARE LEAVING
BUT, IN A WAY, I'M NOT.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THE ROOM
EITHER.
I'M JUST CONCERNED ABOUT Y'ALL.
'CAUSE YOU BEING YOUNG,
AND IT IS STRESSFUL.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO TAKE ON
RESPONSIBILITIES OF WASHING
DISHES AND WASHING BOTTLES
AND FEEDING HIM.
>> WE ARE MESSY,
BUT WE ARE TEENAGERS.
>> I DO AGREE.
I THINK WE ARE FILTHY.
>> YOU'RE MORE THAN MESSY.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU STRAIGHT.
I AM SCARED FOR HIM TO LEAVE.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THIS IS, LIKE,
REALITY RIGHT HERE, LIFE.
>> I KNOW.
>> THEY'RE SO CUTE AND ADORABLE,
AIN'T THEY?
BUT THEY'RE A JOB.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN DO IT?
>> YEAH.
EVEN THOUGH HE DIDN'T SHOW UP
AT THE BABY SHOWER,
MY DAD CAME BY TO MEET
HIS GRANDSON.
>> I'M GLAD THAT YOU COME AROUND
MORE NOW.
>> YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU,
DON'T YOU?
LOOK AT HIM.
>> [giggles]
ME AND WESTON ARE FINALLY
MOVING OUT OF MEEMAW'S HOUSE.
AND WE HAVE TONS OF STUFF
TO PACK UP.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO MEEMAW.
SO I'M BAKING A CAKE
TO SURPRISE HER.
>> WHAT COLORS ARE YOU GONNA USE
IN THE CAKE?
>> ALL OF THEM.
>> ALL OF THEM?
>> OH, FOR ME?
NOW, I HOPE YOU DON'T EXPECT ME
TO EAT ALL THAT BY MYSELF.
>> WE DO.
>> RIGHT NOW.
[laughter]
>> IS THIS TO KEEP ME HAPPY
WHEN YOU GO?
>> YES.
>> WELL, IT WON'T WORK.
>> NOW YOU CAN SLEEP
IN YOUR BED.
>> IT'S BEEN REALLY CROWDED
HERE, AND IT'S BEEN HARD.
I'M GONNA MISS YOU.
>> WE'LL MISS YOU TOO.
BUT THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING
AND LETTING US STAY HERE
EVEN THOUGH I WOULD PITCH A FIT
ALL THE TIME.
I'M SCARED REALLY.
DON'T KNOW WHY I DON'T
WANT TO MOVE.
>> WELL, YOU ALL GOT YOUR OWN
LITTLE FAMILY NOW, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS WHAT GROWING UP
IS ALL ABOUT.
IT'S TIME TO LEAVE THE NEST.
>> WELL, LET'S CUT THE CAKE.
>> [laughs]
>> LOOK HOW COOL IT LOOKS.
>> I JUST CAN'T GET OVER IT ALL.
[rock music]
* *
>> COME ON, CHUMPY.
WE'RE GOING TO NANA'S HOUSE.
YOU GONNA MISS MEEMAW'S HOUSE,
WESTY?
>> * THEY CAUGHT YOU *
* LIKE A KITE TO THE SKY *
>> I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
WE'RE LEAVING BEHIND, BUT I HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT'S COMING UP AHEAD.
>> * SO GO IF YOU WANT TO *
>> I'M SO GLAD Y'ALL ARE HERE.
>> GOT SOME STRAWBERRIES
GROWING.
>> UH-HUH.
COME ON, CHUMPY.
LET'S GO AROUND BACK.
GONNA GET RID OF THAT LEASH.
OH, POOR CHUMPY.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> WHOO, IT'S COOL.
YEAH.
THINK Y'ALL ARE GONNA LIKE IT?
>> UH-HUH.
>> OKAY, GOOD.
>> I THINK HE LIKES IT.
I DIDN'T THINK I WAS THE TYPE
TO GET PREGNANT AT A YOUNG AGE.
>> [cries]
>> WHEN I'M FEELING REALLY
OVERWHELMED, I JUST WILL WONDER,
"HOW DID THIS HAPPEN TO ME?"
THE TRUTH IS, HAVING A BABY
IS MORE THAN I CAN HANDLE
AT MY AGE.
SO I HAVE TO RELY ON WESTON
TO DO A LOT.
[baby cries]
>> I'VE GOT IT.
>> * SO GO IF YOU WANT TO *
>> MY TEENAGE YEARS ARE, LIKE,
THEY'RE JUST GONE NOW.
WHAT I THOUGHT I'D BE WORRYING
ABOUT MY JUNIOR YEAR IS WHAT
DRESS I'D BE WEARING TO PROM
THIS YEAR AND WHO AM I GONNA
BE HANGING OUT WITH TONIGHT.
NOW MY WORRIES ARE HOW WILL WE
PAY FOR DIAPERS, WHERE ARE WE
GONNA LIVE, AND HOW AM I GONNA
GET MY GED AND START COLLEGE?
HOW ARE WE GONNA BE
A REAL FAMILY INSTEAD OF
DEPENDING ON OTHERS?
>> WESTON?
DO YOU LIKE IT, MIJO?
>> IT'S GRAND.
I LOVE IT.
[laughter]
TEN MONTHS AGO, I WAS STILL
THE BABY OF THE FAMILY.
SOME DAYS I JUST FEEL
LIKE I'M NEVER GONNA GROW UP
AND I WOULD HATE TO,
BUT I HAVE TO GROW UP FOR HIM.
[guitar music]
* *
>> female announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT...
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
ME AND TY TALKED ABOUT, LIKE,
KEEPING IT, BUT THERE'S NOT
REALLY A LOT OF GOOD THINGS
ABOUT KEEPING IT.
>> I THINK ADOPTION WOULD BE
THE BEST OPTION.
>> ALL THAT BABY NEEDS IS LOVE.
>> NO, THAT'S NOT ALL A BABY
NEEDS IS LOVE, DAD.
>> I JUST WANT HER TO HAVE
BETTER THAN WHAT I HAD.
I KNOW THAT YOU GUYS CAN PROVIDE
FOR HER A LOT MORE THAN I CAN.
>> LOOK, OPEN YOUR EYES.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE.
>> OKAY, NOW DEEP BREATH.
>> IT'S OKAY; YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> LOOK.
[upbeat piano music]
* *
>> * GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS *
* DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA *
* GET THROUGH IT ALL *
* I'M WEAK, BUT I'M *
* STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE *
* WHEN IT'S ALL DONE... *
3 2 F1