- I can't even see what
I'm doing.
This thing's too big.
[gasps]
Hi, I'm Nikkole.
I'm 15, and I'm from Monroe,
Michigan, smack in between
Detroit, Motor City, and
Toledo, Ohio.
My parents are separated, and my
dad is out of the picture.
So I live at home with my mom
and my 12-year-old
brother, Brett.
You have to get up and take
a shower.
Mom just told me to tell
you that.
Even though I'm not the kind of
girl who likes being in the
spotlight, I'm definitely
a princess.
I'd wear this one.
And my mom spoils me
every chance she gets.
- Your total is $72.38.
- This year, I'm going to be
a junior in high school, and I'm
on the cheerleading squad.
My posse of girls and I are
definite pranksters.
As soon as you get your light
back, I'm shooting you.
One of our favorite pastimes
is TP-ing houses.
- Holy crap.
- I got it.
- I guess you could say my life
is pretty charmed, but my luck
is about to change, because...
I'm pregnant.
Everything started when I
met Josh.
I was love-struck.
But our relationship turned
rocky pretty quickly.
One day he would be sweet and
nice, and the next day he would
break it off.
- When did you first start
having sex with Josh?
- When we were dating for,
like, six months.
- Did you guys, like, ever
use condoms?
- We never used them.
- That's crazy.
- He said he was gonna
"pull out."
not surprisingly, with
no protection, I got pregnant.
And when I told Josh I was
keeping the baby,
he broke up with me.
Josh and I haven't really been
talking, and he even started
dating this girl Kyla.
But I'm hoping this break is
just temporary like our
other ones.
- Do you want to be with him?
- Yeah.
- He cheats all the time.
- No, he doesn't.
- Yeah, he does.
- He's never actually cheated
on me.
- Yeah, he has.
- That's when we were broken
up, remember?
- But you guys break up, like,
every other day.
- He breaks up with you
to cheat on you.
What happened when you told him
that you were pregnant?
- He said that, "You have to
get an abortion, or else I won't
be with you."
- Why do you keep calling
him, though?
- Because I love him.
- I know, but you have to be
stronger than that.
- Yeah, but you can't just let
somebody that you're about to
have a kid with just walk out of
your life.
- What did your mom even say
whenever you told her?
- She cried,
and she yelled at me.
And she kicked me out for a day.
My mom is trying to come to
terms with everything.
- The baby's head is down
over here.
- But I know it's hard for her,
especially because she's never
liked Josh.
And now it's even more real,
because I found out I'm having
a boy, and I'm naming him Lyle.
- These are really nice,
Nikkole.
- I know.
- It almost looks real.
- It is real.
- Was there anything you're
scared of?
- The only thing I'm
really scared of is that Josh
won't be there.
- I thought when you and Josh
were dating that I was
doing the right thing
as a parent to protect you from
getting pregnant.
At first, I was angry,
'cause I didn't know what to do.
I felt embarrassed.
People see you.
The first thing they do is look
at your belly, and they probably
think, "That poor girl."
and then they look at the mom,
and they say, "How'd you let
that happen?"
- Sorry.
- 'cause I thought I did all
the right things.
And I felt betrayed by you.
But now that it's here,
I'm gonna hold your hand, and
I'm gonna walk you through this.
And we're gonna deal with it
as a family.
- My mom isn't totally over it,
but I'm glad she's ready
to support me now.
I just wish Josh was too.
[alarm blaring]
Today is the first day
of junior year.
I've kind of been dreading it,
because it's the first time
everyone will see
my pregnant belly.
- What are you wearing
those for?
- Not on the first day of
school, Nikkole.
Usually it's a fairly
dressed-up day.
- You think people are gonna
stare at you?
- Probably.
- Yeah.
- [horn honks]
- Frankie's here.
I love you. Good luck.
- Thank you.
[engine revving]
- I know.
- Yeah.
- Even though there were
definite stares and whispers,
my girls had my back,
and the first day wasn't so bad.
And because Josh is always
getting in trouble, he got
expelled, and I don't see him
at school.
But when I got out, he was
waiting in the parking lot, and
wanted to talk.
- So what's up?
How was your day?
- Great.
- Really?
- So do you think you've
changed now?
- I am sorry for treating you
the way I treated you.
I did do a lot of stupid things
because I really didn't know how
to react.
I felt like it was still my time
to be a teenager and still do
all that stupid [bleep].
- I knew you'd come around
eventually.
- All's I can do is try and
make things right now.
- Are you still talking
to Kyla?
- Well, what do you think's
gonna happen with us?
- I think that there is
definitely still something
between us.
I think that...
I'd love to be with you again.
I really would.
I miss you a lot.
- I miss you too.
- I just want you to know that
I still love you.
- I love you too.
Josh and I are back
together again.
- I'm really excited Josh and I
are back together, but I'm not
sure my mom and friends will
feel the same way.
- Hi.
- Hey, Becca.
How are ya?
- I'm good.
So what happened
yesterday, Nikkole?
- Me and Josh were talking, and
he asked if I would give him
another chance.
And I said yes.
- [groans]
- [laughs]
- And why?
- He apologized to me, and he
teared up.
He teared up.
- How do you feel about
Josh, Becca?
- I don't like Josh, honestly.
Like, he sits there and talks to
other girls, but then he tells
Nikkole, "Oh, I love you,"
and stuff like that.
- Did you hear Josh was dating
that girl, or do you know
for sure?
- He said he was, but now
they're broken up.
- I don't want to see you get
hurt again, Nikkole.
- I know.
- I think after you became
pregnant and he left you, you
cried for...two months straight.
- Yeah.
- I'm disappointed that you're
not giving it more time.
- It's true Josh has a pattern
of hurting me.
But we're having a baby,
so I have to have faith
he can change.
- Are you ready to take the
responsibilities of being
a father?
- I'm not ready for the baby.
I was never ready for the baby.
I'm still not ready
for the baby.
- You better get ready.
- Because you put yourself in
those shoes to where, you know,
you're not supposed to have
a child at 16 or 17.
You need to not only be there
physically but mentally,
not only for him,
but for Nikkole.
♪
- I don't even know how you
think this is gonna work.
- Well, 'cause I think he's
different now.
He seems like he's coming
around finally.
He's trying to get a job.
He's trying to get back
into school.
- Every single time you guys
break up, you say,
"Oh, he's different now,"
and then he goes back.
- I think you just want to
believe in your head that Josh
is gonna change.
But he's really not.
And you see something, like,
totally different than we do.
- Yeah, but you guys don't see
him all the time like I do.
- But I just think you need to
be careful, because we're
looking out for you, and your
mom's looking out for you.
And I don't want to see
you hurt.
- Yeah.
Even though everyone has
reservations about Josh, he's
making a real effort in
stepping up.
- Are you happy we're having
a boy?
- I always wanted to have a boy
first so that whatever I had
after that, you know, he'd have
an older brother.
I'm happy.
- Me too.
[laughter]
- So what are your plans, Josh?
- I'm planning on getting a job
around Toledo.
Like, even if I make minimum
wage or something, that's still,
like, income.
- What are your plans, Nikkole?
- Finish high school and then
I want to go
to the University of Toledo.
- That's good.
Josh, I know in the past that
you've done some very negative
things, and I would like to
know if you are ready to step up
and be a parent.
- It took me a while to come
around, but I think I can do
it now.
- Nikkole needs all the help
she can get.
- My mom is trying to accept
him, but I know she still has
her doubts.
I had to skip class because I
have a doctor's appointment,
and Josh agreed to come along.
- Stop playing with the UV
light and stop pushing it--
- Nikkole, really,
stop playing with that.
- I wasn't doing anything, I was
just moving it--
- Yeah, really? Really, really,
is that how you feel?
- [knocking at door]
Hi.
- Howdy.
- How you doing?
- Good. I don't want to do this.
- You don't want to do this?
- No.
- It's not bad.
Let's see how the baby is doing.
All right, if you don't mind.
- [laughs]
Give me your hand.
- Just relax.
- Hold her hand, buddy.
- 'Cause you're tripping out.
- Okay, well, the baby is low.
The baby is definitely
head down.
- I'm not dilating, am I?
- No.
- Okay, good.
- Let's get you up.
Can I give you a hand?
So we're really looking very,
very well.
Any contractions or anything
like that?
- Not that I know of.
- Good.
All right, I'll see you
in a week.
- All right, thank you.
Appreciate it.
- I'm glad Josh is here,
but I'm worried his immature
attitude is coming back.
- [crying]
- After my doctor's appointment,
I went to hang out with my
friends before they took off for
our school's big game.
[knocking at door]
[laughs]
Hi.
- Hey, Preggo.
- Hi.
- Oh, that was my seat.
Scoot over.
- She don't want to sit by you.
She sat next to me for a reason.
- You missed fourth hour.
- What happened?
- We had a sub.
Are you going to the game?
- No.
- Why?
- Because I don't want to go.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- Where you at?
- Becca's.
- Tell him no.
- Shut up, Sam.
I-I-I don't know. I might, okay?
- Josh.
- He's not coming to my house.
- What?
- [bleep] you, Josh.
- Stop, Becca.
- No, he just called me
a bitch, Nikkole.
- Okay.
- Okay, Josh is a [bleep]
ass -- .
- So does that mean you have to
go to the game?
- I guess. I don't know.
[phone ringing]
- Just tell him, be like, "I'm
with my friends right now.
I'll talk to you later."
- I'll answer it.
- Becca, stop.
Okay, Josh.
- [bleep] stupid.
- Okay, bye.
- Have you ever noticed, every
time you're with Josh, you do
exactly what he says, and you're
like his little puppy dog?
And it's really annoying.
It's because of Josh.
You don't want to go and hang
out with your friends.
You want to go because Josh
is going.
And that's all you care about
now is Josh.
And it's really
[bleep] annoying.
He had no reason to call me
a bitch.
Do I ever say anything rude
to him? No, I don't.
It's been two weeks, and
homecoming is around the corner.
But because Josh got expelled,
he can't come to the dance.
But I'm hoping he'll help me
pick out a dress.
- Well, I'm going outside,
'cause I don't feel like
dress shopping.
- Okay.
- Bye, Josh.
- This one would be a cute
one, huh?
No?
It might look cute on.
You could try it.
- Mom?
- Yes?
- Nikkole, get out, Nikkole.
- It feels like it would fit.
I'm thinking the zipper was
just bad.
- Get out.
- I can't.
- That one's great.
Put that one on.
That's the one you're gonna get.
It's beautiful.
- Want to see, Josh?
- No.
I just want her to get it.
It's beautiful.
Get it. Just get it.
Yes, it's fine.
- I popped the zipper.
- Get another one with a
regular zipper and just go get
it, and then purchase it and
take me home.
- Don't get depressed, Nikkole.
It's all a part about
being pregnant.
Things don't fit the same way
they used to.
It'll be okay, Nikkole.
- I used to be a size 0,
and now I barely fit into
a size 10.
To make matters worse,
Josh is being a jerk.
- Thank you.
- Appreciate it.
- Because.
- Because?
- Why not?
- I guess the big reason that I
don't want you to go to
homecoming is that I can't
even go.
It's supposed to be like
a boyfriend-girlfriend thing.
You want to go with your
friends, it's cool, I guess.
- I'm probably only gonna
stay for, like, an hour.
- 15 minutes?
- Josh.
- I'll be in the parking lot.
- No, you won't.
- Yes, I will.
- I doubt it.
- I will.
- Okay.
- So after an hour, we're gonna
hang out?
- Yeah.
- So it looks like I'm going to
spend at least part of
homecoming night with Josh.
- The homecoming dance is
tonight, and I'm excited,
because I get to spend the first
part with friends and the second
part with Josh.
- So what did Josh have to say?
He's upset that he can't go to
the dance with me.
- Are you gonna meet up with
him afterwards, or--
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, go get your dress on.
- All right.
- I'm surprised that my dress
still fits me.
- You did get a lot bigger I
think in the last week.
It really--
- Just in one week?
- --popped out.
You look beauteous.
Think you're ready.
- Aw, you look cute.
I love your little
pregnant belly.
[camera shutter clicking]
you're like a picture Nazi.
[laughing]
- You guys have a good time at
the dance, and I'll see
you later.
- For sure.
[people chatting]
[bright rock music]
♪
[jumping dance music]
- The dance is really fun, but
I'm more excited to spend
the rest of homecoming night
with Josh.
But when I got out to the
parking lot, he wasn't there.
[phone trilling]
- Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice
message system.
- I'm gonna kill him.
[phone trilling]
- Hello, hello, hello.
- Why have you been ignoring
my calls?
- You did, like, 50 times.
- You told me you were gonna be
there at 9.
- To hang out with me.
- All right, then I just have
to go home then.
- Josh, whatever.
I'm just gonna go home.
- Yeah.
Okay, all right, bye.
I'm getting really sick of Josh
letting me down.
[sighs]
What are you doing?
- Watching TV.
- Okay.
- Where's Josh?
- At his friend's house.
- Why'd you leave early?
- Because I thought Josh was
gonna hang out with me.
But he doesn't want to leave
his friend's house.
- Oh.
That sucks.
- Yeah, he's a jerk.
Whatever.
Do you want to play Rock Band?
- Yeah, I guess.
- All right, go get it.
- Okay.
[thoughtful rock music]
♪
♪ It's my heart
you're stealing ♪
you take ♪
♪ It's my heart
you're dealing with ♪
♪ And it's my heart
you break ♪
♪♪
- I'm really upset with Josh,
and I need to talk to him.
So like, last night when you
ditched me, it made me
feel like--
- Ditched you?
- Yeah, you ditched me.
- Didn't you ditch me first?
- No.
- No?
- 'cause I told you I was gonna
go to the dance and come back.
- Right, we've already talked
about this.
I asked you not to go to the
dance, you went to the dance.
- It just freaks me out when
you do stuff like that, 'cause
it makes me feel like maybe I
won't be able to depend on you
in the future.
- That's retarded.
- Why?
- Uh, because.
How many times have I done
something like that to you?
- A lot in the past.
- Whatever. I'm done
talking about this.
Every little thing is you,
you, you.
You're being selfish.
This is one of the reasons that
we broke up before.
I'm not--I want somebody in
my corner.
That's what a relationship is
to me.
If you want to make it about
you, you, you, instead of "us,"
that's when we're done.
- Right now, it should be more
about me.
I'm about to have a baby.
I hope Josh can stop being so
self-centered when Lyle is born.
Today is my last day of school,
because I'm due in two weeks on
November 4.
- Hey, Nikkole.
- Hi.
- Boring.
- So did you tell
your teachers?
- How many weeks do you plan on
taking off?
- Three, fours weeks?
- Yeah.
I watched a show about babies
being born today.
It was gross.
They're all purple and white
and red.
That's disgusting, Mom.
- No, it's not. It's your baby.
- Yeah, with my blood and
mucus and all that.
Tomorrow is my due date.
I'm really uncomfortable and
can't sleep.
So my doctor said we can induce
labor, but my mom is worried
that inducing might make my
labor more difficult.
- So when the doctor said you
could be in labor up to two
days, how do you feel
about that?
- I'll get over it.
It's not that bad.
- No? How do you know?
- I don't know.
I'll get over it.
- Are you not nervous?
- Yeah, I'm nervous. I'm just
not thinking about it.
- Okay, let's go.
Get your bag packed.
- [groans]
- ♪ Something different
than me ♪
- I can't believe that Lyle is
almost here.
I'm scared, but I'm ready.
I just hope Josh is too.
- I'm inducing today, and I'm
ready to get this baby out.
We're headed to the hospital
to get things started, but my
friends aren't allowed to come
because of a flu scare.
- All right, let's do this.
You ready?
- Good morning.
- Oh, we've got a visitor.
- Are you ready for this? Yes?
Well, remember one thing.
This could be a long process.
I'm just hoping this thing will
get moving quick.
- Here we go. One, two.
- [wincing and sucking air]
- If you had to guesstimate,
like, how many hours?
- I can't. I can't, uh-uh.
- Look.
Aw.
- It says, "I love you with all
my heart, baby.
Thanks for being the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
Love forever, Joshua."
- Aw.
- Thank you.
- How sweet.
- Love you.
- Lyle's angry?
- Yes, he is.
- Why is he angry?
- [laughing]
- He stabbed me.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you tired?
- Yes.
- Why?
- 'Cause I am.
- You slept all day.
- [mumbling]
- You wake up right now.
- Nikkole.
We're gonna start pitocin.
It's gonna make your
contractions stronger.
And then I'll be watching the
contractions the whole time.
- [breathing deeply]
[moaning]
- Yeah, I'm sure it is.
- [breathing deeply]
- It's okay, baby.
- [moaning]
- I'm not trying to do it.
- You.
Right? You do.
You need calm and relaxation.
It's hard to get through it.
- Excuse me, Josh?
- It is my opinion.
- You guys, stop.
- I'm telling you what
she needs.
- All right, you can tell me
what she needs all you want.
- Guys, stop.
- But that--
- Okay, you want to keep it
a calm setting for Nikkole.
- Nikkole, your mom is very
disrespectful.
I really want to yell at her,
very badly.
- He's pissed, I guess 'cause
I'm trying to comfort you.
I don't know.
- Why is she sad?
- Joshua.
If you're gonna be obnoxious,
then leave.
- That's what I just said.
- Then go ahead, but you're
on your own.
- I need a ride home.
- Well, Courtney's coming.
- All right.
- I'm trying to share space
here, Josh.
- Don't talk to me.
- Joshua.
- Do not talk to me.
- I told you earlier about
being disrespectful--
- You're an ass.
- She had her little snap.
I get my little snap, Mom.
- Bottom line, she's the thing
that's important here.
And you know what?
You need to suck it up.
That's still her mom, Joshua.
- I'm trying to tell you to
calm it down.
- I don't want you to tell
me anything.
I don't want you to tell
- I'm gonna tell you, Josh.
- I know.
And that's why I'm telling you
I'm sick and tired of
hearing it.
And you won't give up.
- Joshua.
- So when I say, "Please stop
saying this,"--
- It's my daughter, Josh.
It may be your baby,
but this is my daughter.
I trump you.
- You don't trump anything.
- I trump you.
- You want to tell her--say she
trumps me, Nikkole.
I want to hear it.
- Listen, now I'm putting
a stop to it.
She's in labor, so you shut your
mouth, and you act like
a grown person.
- All right, then!
- Your only concern right now
is her.
So suck it up, Joshua.
Suck it up,
and act like a grown-up.
- Josh's mom finally got
through to him, and things
calmed down.
- All right.
- Don't be nervous.
- This is it.
This is what we've been
waiting for.
- So you got this far.
You got this far, so let's get
this baby out, okay?
- Come on, push, Nikkole.
- I can't.
- Push.
- Come on, do it.
- Nikkole.
- Yes, you can.
- Push that baby out.
- Come on.
- [crying]
- Harder, Nikkole.
- I can't.
- Good, good, push, push, push.
- It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
It hurts!
- Come on, you can do it.
Oh, my god!
[baby crying]
- There's your baby.
[baby squawking]
- Lyle.
- He is bigger than eight
pounds, I think.
- Wow, look at him.
- He looks wonderful.
- Good job.
Good job.
[chime dings]
- The last few days have been
really difficult.
My mom and Josh have been
fighting almost the entire time.
And now my mom won't let Josh
into our house, which means I
have to go home alone and visit
Josh's family later.
- I'm so exhausted and really
angry there was so much drama.
- How you doing, Nikkole?
- Are you tired?
- Those three days with Josh
was a little exhausting.
I'm stressed.
I ain't had much sleep.
- Not only am I worn out by
all the fighting, but I'm in so
much pain I can barely walk.
- [crying]
- Don't cry.
Mom?
- Oh, spit-up.
- Ooh, what do I do?
- Pick him up.
Put this on your shoulder.
- Can he, like, choke?
- He really didn't get that
much to choke.
And then just kind of burp him.
- Mom.
- Burp him.
- Oh, it just went all over.
- You're fine.
It's gonna happen.
- That's disgusting.
- It's a burp.
[doorbell rings]
- Hey, Frankie. Come on in.
- Hi.
- Aw.
- Are you nervous?
- Kind of.
- He's so little.
- I'll go get a blanket.
- No, he's not, dude.
They had to cut my crotch open
so they could get him out.
Isn't that sick?
- Did it hurt?
- Yeah, I have stitches.
- Where's Josh?
- He was gonna come back here,
but he and my mom got in
a big fight.
- Why?
- He said some very mean things
to my mom.
And she said that he's not
allowed over here anymore.
And she wouldn't let me go home
with him either.
[baby squawks]
- He's gonna cry.
- Oh, come here.
- I can't believe you have
a baby.
- I know, right?
Don't ever do it.
[laughter]
- [crying]
Don't cry.
Mom?
- Hold on just a second.
I'm trying to find baby wipes.
- Aw, buddy.
- I should probably go.
- Aw.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'll come visit him again.
- All right.
- All right, bye.
- Bye.
- [crying]
Buddy.
- Do you understand why I got
upset today?
- Yeah.
- And you're okay with him
being disrespectful?
I think you see it.
You understand it.
- I didn't want to deal with it
last night.
I just ignored it last night.
- You shouldn't ignore it.
Also seeing him touch you, put
his whole body on you when you
were trying to focus through
those labor pains, and I asked
him repeatedly to stop,
and he didn't stop.
- It didn't bother me
really, though.
- It doesn't matter.
It bothered me.
- Mm-hmm.
- A lot of things about Josh
doesn't bother you.
It should.
But it doesn't.
That angers me.
- Mm-hmm.
Mom, don't cry.
- It was hard watching
all that.
You need to really have
a serious talk with him.
- I know.
I'm going over to Josh's so he
can see Lyle and we can have
a talk.
What you said to my mom was
really disrespectful.
- She did a bunch of crazy
stuff while she was there, and
she's the one that looked
foolish, not me.
- Josh.
- And then she sat there and
called me immature.
- You just need to put yourself
in her shoes.
She was tripping out.
- I was in her shoes.
- All right, babe--
- I was completely in her shoes
on the other side.
- Mm-hmm.
- She cared about you, and I
cared about you.
- Mm-hmm.
- She thought she was better,
'cause she's your mom.
- This right here is not about
your mother, believe it or not.
- I love my mom.
And I love you too.
And as much as you don't like
her, she's gonna be a part of my
life just as much as you are.
So you guys are gonna have to
get along.
- Yeah.
- I don't know, dude,
like, whatever.
I guess we'll go from when she
finally decides to apologize.
- [sighs]
I really hope I don't have to
choose between my mom and
Josh, because we're all
connected now.
- Since Lyle was born, my mom
and Josh have refused to speak
to each other.
And my mom has made it a rule
that he is not allowed in
our house.
I've been bonding with Lyle, but
this is definitely not the
family picture I had imagine.
So today, I convinced my mom and
Josh to meet
and try and work things out.
- Where to begin?
One of the things that I'm
really upset with you about is
the fact that you're so
disrespectful to people, not
only me: Nikkole, your parents,
everybody that you come in
contact with. It's crazy.
- That's the kind of person
I am.
If you guys feel I was
disrespectful, I guess
I'm sorry.
But I'm not gonna change
who I am.
That's who I am.
I don't even really understand
why you're mad at all.
I did not say one disrespectful
word to you.
- Oh, no, let's see here.
I think you said,
"I'm number one.
You're number two."
that was the first thing that
pissed me off in that
situation, 'cause you're never
gonna be number one.
I'm her blood. I am number one.
- I am.
- Yeah, okay.
You're gonna think that.
- Well, I actually know it.
- [sighs]
- Will you try and resolve
things with my mom, please?
- [bleep] No, dude. Come on.
- Stop.
Seriously, stop.
- You think I'm trying to be
mean right now?
- Stop being a jerk.
What's wrong?
- "What's wrong?"
Are you kidding me?
- No.
- I could jump across that
table and whip the [bleep]--
- I told him he was being
a smart-ass.
- And you're okay with that?
- No, I told him to stop.
You guys need to try and
resolve things.
- I'm not gonna resolve it.
- Why?
Okay, I'll be nice to him
because of the baby.
But I never want to see you guys
together again, period.
- Why?
- I just don't.
- But that's my decision.
- He's not good for you.
- It's my decision, regardless.
- Okay, well, you're still 16.
You're under my care.
- I can move out when I'm 17.
- Good, great.
Until then, you're gonna have
a lockdown, if that's what
it takes.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- You don't need to be
with him.
- All right, well, you have to
let me make those
decisions myself.
It's part of growing up.
- [sighs]
Unfortunately, I know that.
- It's been over a month,
and Josh is still banished from
the house.
But I'm back in school, and even
though my mom has been helping
a lot, it's been really hard.
- [fussing]
[crying]
♪ You tried to warn me
♪ I must confess
[alarm blaring]
♪ Should have killed me
♪ But inside I know
- Josh's mom works nights, so
she's been watching Lyle
during the day.
The only time Josh gets to see
Lyle is when I come over
after school.
He tries to be a good dad.
But because he has limited time
with Lyle, he hasn't quite
gotten the hang
of the parenting thing.
- [crying]
- Are you serious?
You got to be quiet.
- All right, hold him, Josh.
Maybe he'll stop crying if you
hold him.
- You told me to move the baby.
This is what happens.
- [crying]
- You move the sleeping baby,
it starts crying.
- [wailing]
- It sucks that Josh
is acting like this,
but that's the least
of my problems, 'cause I just
found out he's been seeing his
ex behind my back.
Like, last week Becca called me
and told me that Josh is hanging
out with Kyla.
And he denied it, and then she
started texting me and telling
me that they were hanging out,
and that she was, like, falling
in love with him and all
this crap.
And so then he finally
admitted it.
- He just, like, thinks it's
okay to talk to you and Kyla?
- Yeah, pretty much.
- So why do you think that
Josh, like, does all--like, he
acts like he's in love with you,
and he'll just run off and do
things you don't want him to do?
- He just does whatever he
wants without thinking about
what's gonna happen.
He doesn't really care about
other people's feelings
that much.
Like, "Oh, I just popped out
your kid a month ago."
It's like he doesn't
really care.
- Yeah.
- What, like, what would you do
if you found out your boyfriend
was cheating on you?
- I probably wouldn't, like,
go back to him.
But I know it's, like, harder
for you.
You're gonna have to--
- See him all the time.
I can't believe Josh hasn't
changed, and after all this
time, he's still cheating on me.
And now he wants to meet me to
explain what's going on.
- Is he sleeping?
- Yeah.
Don't mess with him.
- He's a cutie.
The reason I wanted you to come
is to talk about the situation.
So, like, I ran into Kyla.
And that one night--you, like,
know I used to date her.
- Mm-hmm.
- So I don't know, like, a lot
of feelings came back,
but I'm trying to sort them out.
Like, I feel like I do love you.
But I'm just
not ready to, like...
totally commit myself to you.
- I just don't, like, want you
to just break up with me so that
you can hook up with other girls
and then still expect me to be
there in the end.
- That's not how it is at all.
- It's just not fair to me,
really.
- [disgusted sigh]
- It's not.
No, 'cause I've already let you
do this, like, twice.
- What's not fair?
All right then. Whatever.
I'm done talking about it,
'cause I already did it.
I'm not making you stay.
- I'm not gonna be
here forever.
- All right then. Don't be.
- I'm just telling you I'm not
going to.
- All right then.
And I'm over it.
Like, you don't have to if you
don't want to.
- All right.
♪ Come here, stay
♪ I've got time
♪ We can play
♪ Valentine
♪ It's just another day
♪ That's all fine
♪ All I wanna say
♪ Is be there
- Josh broke up with me.
- And how do you feel
about that?
- Sad.
I don't want him to leave.
- Does he know how upset
you are?
- Yeah.
Before I had Lyle, I was hoping
that me and Josh could be
really close, and we could be
like a family with our child.
But it really has
had the opposite effect.
- Merry Christmas.
- You can open some gifts
for Lyle.
- At 16, I definitely
don't think I was ready to be a
mom, and I still don't think I'm
ready to be a mom.
But I think I'm doing the best
I can.
- Put your arm around her.
Go on.
- There you go, aw.
- My mom being here and helping
me take care of Lyle has made
things a lot easier for me.
- [crying]
- I like sleep.
I don't think my mom and Josh
will ever make up, because they
disagree with each other
completely.
I don't know what's gonna happen
with me and Josh in the future.
Even though Josh has hurt me
a lot, I still love him.
And I hope that we end up
being together.
I still have a year and a half
left of high school, but I'm
really still determined to
graduate and go on to college.
- It still fits.
- Yeah.
- Awesome.
That looks really cute.
- Even though I love Lyle, I
wish that I would have waited to
have children, because I can't
be as carefree as I used to be.
And if I could have made
a different decision,
then I would have.
- We don't have any reason
to be talking
unless it's about the baby.
It's not fair at all, Matt,
for you to just do
whatever you want to me and you
expect me to just do it.
I just don't want him
in the picture,
because he's not fit
to be a dad at all.
It hurts, Dad.
I'm just trying to be calm.
- Come on, come on.
Just tell him we're on our way
to the hospital.
- [groaning]
- Give me a big push now.
- Look at that.
- ♪
♪
♪ All these nine weeks
♪ Don't know how
I'm gonna get through it all ♪
♪ I'm weak
♪ But I'm strong enough
to see ♪♪