>> [laughs]
HI, MY NAME IS JENNIFER.
KITTY CAT, COME ON.
I'M 16, AND I LIVE RIGHT OUTSIDE
TAMPA, FLORIDA, WITH MY MOM,
DAD, AND LITTLE BROTHER,
ANTONIO.
MOST GIRLS IN MY HIGH SCHOOL
SPEND THEIR WEEKENDS SHOPPING.
LORD, HAVE MERCY.
BUT IN MY FREE TIME, I'D RATHER
BE AT THE BATTING CAGES OR
PLAYING SPORTS WITH MY FAMILY.
>> THERE YOU GO.
LAST ONE.
>> WE'RE SUPER CLOSE, AND
NOTHING EVER GETS BETWEEN US...
>> GET IT, SCOOTER.
CATCH IT.
>> EXCEPT FOR MAYBE
MY BOYFRIEND, JOSH.
I WON.
YOU GOT TO TAKE ME TO GO
GET MY NAILS DONE.
WE MET UP AT SCHOOL
AND HAVE BEEN GOING OUT
FOR OVER A YEAR.
BOY, ARE YOU AN OLD FART.
BUT MY MOM AND DAD DON'T LIKE
JOSH, BECAUSE HE'S TOO OLD
FOR ME.
THEY THINK HE'S DISRESPECTFUL,
AND IN THEIR EYES, NO GUY
IS GOOD ENOUGH FOR THEIR
LITTLE GIRL.
MY PARENTS ARE ABOUT TO HAVE
TWO MORE REASONS NOT TO LIKE
JOSH BECAUSE...
I'M PREGNANT WITH TWINS.
EVEN THOUGH MY BELLY IS HUGE
NOW, THE SHOCK OF BEING PREGNANT
HASN'T COMPLETELY WORN OFF ON ME
OR MY PARENTS.
IT DIDN'T HIT ME FOR A WHILE.
>> WHAT?
THAT YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> YEAH.
>> I'LL NEVER FORGET
THAT FIRST SONOGRAM.
>> WHEN WE FOUND OUT I WAS
HAVING TWINS?
NEITHER WILL I.
SHE ALMOST HAD A HEART ATTACK.
>> I DID.
>> I KEPT TELLING HER,
"CHECK AGAIN."
>> WE DIDN'T WANT THIS FOR YOU
YET, BUT IT HAPPENED.
>> YEAH.
ANTONIO, ARE YOU OKAY WITH
THIS CONVERSATION OR NOT?
>> I'M ALL RIGHT.
BUT, HEY, IF YOU GUYS WANT ME
TO LEAVE...
[laughter]
>> HE LOOKS BORED.
[laughs]
ARE WE GONNA HAVE A BABY SHOWER?
>> I'M NOT TOO SURE.
AND WE GOT BACK-TO-SCHOOL
GOING ON NOW AND...
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HMM...
WITH ONLY THREE WEEKS OF SUMMER
BEFORE MY SOPHOMORE YEAR,
WE DON'T HAVE THAT LONG TO GET
EVERYTHING WE NEED BEFORE
THE BABIES ARE HERE.
>> OKAY, NOW OPEN.
SEE?
BRAND-NEW CAR SEATS.
>> OH, THEY'RE CUTE.
>> AND THIS IS THE CRIB.
DID YOU EVER THINK, A YEAR
LATER, I'D BE SHOWING YOU
A CRIB?
>> NO.
I MEAN, MY LIFE WOULD BE
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT
IF I WASN'T PREGNANT.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK OF ME
WHEN YOU FIRST MET ME?
>> WELL, I SAW YOU IN
THE HALLWAY.
>> THEN YOU ASKED ME OUT.
>> UH-UH.
YOU SAID, "YOU GONNA BE
MY GIRL?"
AND I SAID, "WHAT?"
>> I'M NOT SURE THAT'S
HOW IT WENT DOWN.
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU LIKE THIS CRIB?
>> YEAH, I'D SLEEP IN IT.
>> I THINK YOU COULD SLEEP
IN THIS.
>> [laughs]
EVER SINCE I GOT PREGNANT,
OUR DATES HAVE MOSTLY BEEN
TO DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENTS,
SO I'M HAPPY TO GO OUT WITH JOSH
WHEN I CAN.
>> [laughs]
THIS ONE'S EASY, JOSH.
[laughter]
I'D BRING OUR KIDS HERE.
>> WE COULD HAVE THEIR FIRST
BIRTHDAY PARTY HERE.
>> [laughs]
>> IS IT SCARY KNOWING
TWO ARE COMING?
>> YEAH, IT SCARED ME.
I THOUGHT I WOULD HAVE
ONE LITTLE CREATURE IN ME,
NOT TWO.
I DIDN'T KNOW MUCH
ABOUT BIRTH CONTROL.
I WAS LIKE, "YOU SHOULD USE
A CONDOM."
AND THEN YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T HAVE MONEY.
>> THAT WAS JUST AN EXCUSE,
THOUGH.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO BUY NONE.
>> WHY?
>> IT'S AWKWARD, GOING IN THERE
AND BUYING CONDOMS.
>> UH, IT'S AWKWARD FOR ME
TO WALK AROUND WITH A BIG BELLY.
[chime dings]
WE'RE HAVING FRATERNAL TWINS
AND ARE NAMING THEM NOAH
AND JOSHUA JUNIOR.
MY PARENTS WEREN'T CRAZY ABOUT
US NAMING ONE OF THE BABIES
AFTER JOSH, AND WHEN I TOLD MY
MOM AND DAD WE WANTED THE TWINS
TO HAVE HIS LAST NAME TOO,
THEY WERE REALLY NOT HAPPY.
>> AS FAR AS THE NAME ISSUE,
WE'RE TRYING TO PROTECT YOU.
IF THEY'RE IN HIS NAME,
THAT GIVES HIM, YOU KNOW,
A LITTLE MORE JURISDICTION.
THAT'S A, YOU KNOW, TREASURE
THAT'S EARNED, YOU KNOW,
THAT HE HAS TO EARN.
>> HE JUST WANTS TO HEAR YOU
GUYS SAY IT IS MY CHOICE.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO HEAR YOU GUYS
SAY YOU'RE MAKING IT FOR ME.
>> AND THAT'S PROBABLY
THE NORMAL REACTION,
BUT THEN THE NEXT REACTION
WOULD BE, WE'RE THE ADULTS HERE.
AND IT'S LIKE, "DUDE, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT MY DAUGHTER PREGNANT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU'RE STANDING IN FRONT OF ME
FOR WHAT YOU DID."
I CAN'T JUST ACCEPT HIM.
>> YOU'RE ONLY 16 YEARS OLD.
AND IF HE DOESN'T GET THAT,
WE'RE GONNA CONTINUE
TO BUMP HEADS.
>> I UNDERSTAND BOTH SIDES,
AND IT LEAVES ME IN THE MIDDLE.
>> THIS IS A STAGE IN YOUR LIFE.
FIVE YEARS AGO, YOU WERE
THINKING ABOUT BARBIES.
BELIEVE YOU ME, THREE YEARS FROM
NOW, YOU'RE GONNA BE THINKING
DIFFERENT.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT HIM.
IT'S ABOUT THE TWO KIDS
IN YOUR STOMACH THERE.
>> I REALLY NEED TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO HANDLE THE ISSUES
BETWEEN MY PARENTS AND JOSH.
>> HOW ARE YOU AND JOSH?
>> OKAY.
WELL, LIKE, MY PARENTS DON'T
THINK IT'S RIGHT THAT THE KIDS
SHOULD HAVE HIS LAST NAME.
>> BUT YOU WANT THEM TO HAVE
HIS LAST NAME?
>> IT'S STRESSFUL,
LIKE, BEING IN THE MIDDLE
OF ALL OF THEM.
>> SO HOW IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO WORK WHEN THEY GET HERE?
[laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE NEEDS TO CALL THEM UP
AND JUST TALK.
>> DO YOU THINK HE'LL ACTUALLY
TRY TO?
>> HE WOULDN'T WANT TO,
BUT HOPEFULLY HE WILL.
I THINK YOU GUYS SHOULD TALK.
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> THEY'RE THE ONES MAKING
THE BIG ISSUE OUT OF IT.
I'M SO DISRESPECTFUL
BECAUSE I'M GONNA TELL THEM
MY KIDS ARE GONNA HAVE
MY LAST NAME.
>> NO, 'CAUSE IT WAS, LIKE,
DEMANDING, AND THAT'S HOW THEY
FEEL, JOSH.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> THAT'S WHY THEY THINK
IT'S DISRESPECTFUL.
>> I DON'T CARE IF IT WAS
DEMANDING OR NOT.
OH, WELL.
>> JOSH, I'M 28-WEEKS PREGNANT.
>> AND YOU THINK TALKING IS
GONNA MAKE EVERYTHING BETTER?
>> THE PERSON THAT I LOVE
AND MY OWN BLOOD AND FAMILY
THAT I LOVE ARE FIGHTING.
LIKE, IT'S NOT THAT GREAT, JOSH.
>> LET'S PUT IT THIS WAY.
ME AND THEM AREN'T GONNA GET
ALONG.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO MAKE
A CHOICE.
>> I CAN'T CHOOSE BETWEEN JOSH
AND MY PARENTS, ESPECIALLY NOW
WHEN I NEED THEM ALL MORE THAN
EVER.
>> I HATE THAT JOSH REFUSES
TO SIT DOWN WITH MY PARENTS,
BUT I'M NOT GONNA LET THAT RUIN
THAT LAST TWO WEEKS BEFORE
SCHOOL STARTS.
>> I GOT A RIDDLE FOR YOU.
>> I'M READY.
>> "WHY WAS THE DOG SWEATING?"
>> MM?
>> 'CAUSE HE HAS TOO MUCH FUR.
[laughs]
>> "IT WAS A HOT DOG."
>> OH, GOD, THAT WAS SO EASY.
[laughter]
>> I'M READY FOR FALL.
[sighs]
>> TWO WEEKS, SCHOOL STARTS.
>> DON'T REMIND ME.
>> GETTING UP EARLY IN
THE MORNING.
GETTING DRESSED.
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS, JENNIFER,
ABOUT GOING TO A NEW SCHOOL?
>> SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT THERE.
>> UH, THE FACT THAT I'M
THE FIRST PREGNANT GIRL
AT THIS SCHOOL...
I'LL BE NERVOUS THE NIGHT
BEFORE AND THAT DAY...
THAT WEEK.
[giggles]
EVEN THOUGH IT'S GOING TO BE
HARD TO START A NEW SCHOOL,
THEY'LL LET ME TAKE OFF FOR
A FEW WEEKS TO HAVE THE TWINS
AND BE FLEXIBLE WITH ALL MY
DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENTS I'VE BEEN
HAVING LATELY.
[laughter]
TWINS USUALLY COME EARLY,
SO MY DOCTOR IS PLANNING ON
A C-SECTION, SINCE THEY'RE
ALREADY GETTING CROWDED.
>> ALL RIGHT.
OH, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, SO WE HAVE
THE HEAD RIGHT HERE,
THIS LITTLE CIRCLE,
AND THEN THAT IS THE OTHER
GUY'S STUFF.
[laughter]
HE'S GOT IT RIGHT ON HIS
BROTHER'S HEAD.
[laughter]
HAVE YOU GUYS HAD YOUR
BABY SHOWER YET?
>> NO.
>> NO?
>> WE MAY HAVE ONE.
IT DEPENDS.
>> GOT TO HAVE A BABY SHOWER.
TWINS?
THAT'S A LOT OF WORK.
NEED ALL THE HELP YOU CAN GET.
>> WITH ALL THE TENSION AROUND
MY PREGNANCY, NOBODY HAS PLANNED
A BABY SHOWER YET.
JOSH MUST HAVE TOLD HIS PARENTS
HOW DISAPPOINTED I WAS,
BECAUSE THEY OFFERED TO TAKE ME
OUT TO DINNER TO CHEER ME UP.
>> SO HOW ABOUT US THROWING,
YOU KNOW, THE BABY SHOWER?
WOULD Y'ALL LIKE THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> [laughs]
>> NOW, WHAT IF YOU HAVE THESE
BABIES BEFORE WE'RE ABLE TO HAVE
A BABY SHOWER?
>> I GUESS THEY'LL BE
A SURPRISE GUEST.
[laughter]
>> HOW DO YOU THINK YOUR PARENTS
WOULD FEEL IF THEY WERE INVITED?
>> I THINK MY MOM WOULD
THINK ABOUT GOING.
MY DAD, I THINK HE WOULDN'T.
>> WHAT IS YOUR DAD SO UPSET
WITH JOSH ABOUT?
>> 'CAUSE THEY THINK IT'S--
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY THINK, SAYING THE KIDS
ARE GONNA HAVE MY LAST NAME,
THEY THINK THAT'S THEIR
DECISION, AND IT'S NOT.
>> THEY SEE IT AS IN
PROTECTING ME FOR THE FUTURE.
I MEAN, I DO UNDERSTAND
WHERE THEY COME FROM,
BUT IT'S MY CHOICE.
SO...
>> SO I HAVE AN IDEA
FOR THE INVITATIONS.
IF WE COULD GET A PICTURE
WHILE YOU'RE STILL PREGNANT,
HAVE THAT FOR THE FRONT
OF THE INVITATION.
WHAT DO Y'ALL THINK ABOUT THAT?
NOD ONCE FOR YES
AND TWO FOR NO.
[laughter]
>> IT'S NICE OF JOSH'S MOM
TO PLAN A BABY SHOWER,
BUT I HOPE MY FAMILY
IS OKAY WITH IT.
>> SO WE GOT AN INVITATION
FOR THE BABY SHOWER.
>> THEY SAID THEY FELT BAD
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T HAVE
A BABY SHOWER.
>> I'D LIKE TO DO SOMETHING
ON THIS SIDE OF THE FAMILY.
>> JOSH HAS TO BE THERE.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> IF HE WASN'T ALLOWED HERE,
THEN WE'LL GO TO HIS HOUSE.
AND I'D LIKE IF YOU GO.
>> MIXED EMOTIONS, JENNIFER.
SHOULD I BE THERE?
SHOULD I NOT?
BUT I KNOW, 99%, I'M SAYING NO.
I'M NOT GONNA BE THERE.
>> DADDY, WILL YOU COME?
>> EXCUSE ME?
UNLESS YOU WANT A BRAWL
OR SOMETHING THAT'S GONNA BREAK
OUT IN THERE 'CAUSE OF TENSION.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH LOOKING AT HIM.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, WE'RE GONNA
MEET FOR A BABY SHOWER.
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
A JOYOUS TIME.
I DON'T FEEL THAT WAY.
>> CUTE, BELL?
I WISH YOU COULD SPEAK, BELLA.
TODAY IS MY BABY SHOWER,
AND IT SUCKS THAT MY PARENTS
ARE TOO UPSET WITH JOSH TO COME,
BUT I'M STILL GONNA TRY
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
>> HUG!
>> HEY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> OKAY, EVERYBODY, COME ON.
>> [laughs]
THESE ARE TINY.
>> THAT'S A LOT OF DIAPERS.
>> YES.
>> WHAT A GREAT FRIEND.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, EVERYONE.
>> all: YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THE BABY SHOWER TURNED OUT
TO BE A LOT OF FUN.
>> ARE YOU SURPRISED YOUR MOM
DIDN'T COME?
>> BUT IT HURT MORE THAN
I THOUGHT IT WOULD THAT
MY OWN PARENTS AREN'T HERE.
>> ♪ IS LIFE WHAT YOU'D
♪ IMAGINED?
[acoustic music]
♪ WHEN WE HAD NOTHING ELSE
♪ TO FRAME IT IN
>> TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY
OF MY SOPHOMORE YEAR.
[alarm clock blaring]
THIS IS ANNOYING.
I USED TO GET EXCITED ABOUT
STARTING SCHOOL, BUT BEING
PREGNANT MAKES GETTING UP EARLY
EVEN HARDER.
LOOK.
BUCKLE IT.
>> [laughs]
I DON'T THINK I CAN.
>> IT'S A GOOD THING MY PARENTS
TRANSFERRED ME TO AN ALTERNATIVE
HIGH SCHOOL THAT WILL LET ME DO
MOST OF MY SCHOOLWORK FROM HOME,
BECAUSE I ALREADY FEEL
EXHAUSTED, AND I'M NOT EVEN
THERE YET.
I CAN'T GET UP.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A LONG DAY,
AREN'T YOU?
>> TODAY'S GONNA BE A BAD DAY.
>> HOW YOU FEEL, JEN?
>> I THINK, ONCE THESE BABIES
ARE HERE...
>> YES, LIFE WILL BE EASIER?
[chuckles]
>> I GOT TO GET UP MUCH MORE
EARLY THAN 5:00 IN THE MORNING.
>> IT'S GONNA BE ROUGH.
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
MY BACK HURTS.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
IT'S WEIRD GOING TO SCHOOL
LIKE THIS.
>> WELL, TODAY IS JUST GETTING
TO KNOW...
>> YOUR TEACHER.
>> YOUR TEACHER, WHERE THE
CLASSES ARE AT, AND YOUR
CLASSMATES.
>> LOOK, I HAVE NO INTEREST
IN MEETING CLASSMATES TODAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> DON'T PUKE. DON'T PUKE.
DON'T PUKE. DON'T PUKE.
DON'T PUKE.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH BEING
THE NEW GIRL, WITHOUT BEING
THE NEW PREGNANT GIRL TOO.
EVERYONE KEPT WHISPERING
WHEN I BARELY FIT INTO MY DESK.
AND AS SOON AS WE WENT TO LUNCH,
ALL ANYONE WANTED TO TALK ABOUT
WAS MY BELLY.
>> WHEN'S YOUR DUE DATE?
>> BOY OR A GIRL?
>> WHO'S THE DAD?
>> GETTING MARRIED?
>> THANKFULLY, THE DAY IS
FINALLY OVER.
>> HEY.
>> HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> HEY, ROLY-POLY.
>> IT WAS...INTERESTING.
BUT MY PANTS ARE TOO TIGHT,
AND I CAN'T UNBUCKLE THEM.
>> HERE, LET ME GET IT.
[laughs]
>> I AM SO TIRED.
>> DID ANYBODY ASK YOU ABOUT
YOUR PREGNANCY?
>> OH, YEAH.
THE PEOPLE AT LUNCH,
THEY HAD ASKED ME WHAT THEY ARE
AND IF ME AND JOSH WERE ENGAGED,
AND I WAS LIKE, "UH, NO."
>> THEY ASKED YOU THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> AND DID SHE SAY, "WHY NOT?"?
>> NO.
>> DID SHE SAY, "DO YOU WANT
TO BE?"?
>> NOPE.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> NO!
QUIT.
I'M TRYING TO ENJOY THE LAST FEW
WEEKS BEFORE THE BABIES COME...
THAT'S NOT FAIR, JOSH.
I CAN'T REACH.
WHICH MEANS SPLITTING ALL
MY FREE TIME BETWEEN JOSH
AND MY FAMILY.
>> THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO SEE.
>> TONIGHT IS OUR ONE-YEAR
ANNIVERSARY, SO JOSH IS TAKING
ME OUT TO CELEBRATE.
OH, YOU LOOK NICE.
>> SO DO YOU.
LET'S "CHEERS" TO OUR
ANNIVERSARY.
>> HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, JOSH.
>> HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, JENNIFER.
>> YOU REMEMBER OUR FIRST DATE?
>> YES.
>> WE WERE THE ONLY ONES
WITH THREE OLD PEOPLE
IN A MOVIE THEATER.
[laughs]
THANK YOU FOR THE DINNER.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
VERY BEAUTIFUL.
>> DESSERT FOR YOU.
>> WHAT'S THIS?
>> I THOUGHT I WAS SUPPOSED
TO GET A BOX OF FOOD.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S A BOX
OF FOOD.
>> [laughs]
>> SO, JENNIFER, CAN YOU STAND
UP FOR A MINUTE?
CAN I HAVE YOUR HAND?
WILL YOU MARRY ME, JENNIFER?
>> OF COURSE I WILL.
LOVE YOU.
>> SO YOU GONNA TELL YOUR
PARENTS?
>> YES.
>> YOU WANT ME TO GO IN THERE
WITH YOU?
>> NO.
STAY IN THE CAR.
>> I'LL GO IN THERE WITH YOU.
>> NOPE, STAY IN THE CAR.
HI!
>> HEY.
DID YOU HAVE A NICE EVENING?
>> YES, I DID.
THE FOOD WAS REALLY GOOD.
PERFECT NIGHT.
>> SO DID JOSH LEAVE?
>> NO, HE'S WAITING OUTSIDE.
>> OH.
>> HE...
UH, HE PROPOSED TO ME.
MM-HMM.
>> OKAY.
AND WHAT DID YOU TELL HIM?
>> YES.
>> [scoffs]
I'M JUST...
WHY DON'T YOU TELL HIM
TO COME IN AND TALK TO ME
FOR A MINUTE?
>> MM-KAY.
I'LL TEXT HIM.
[buttons clicking]
>> OH, JENNIFER, THAT'S
A SPECIAL MOMENT FOR ANY WOMAN.
JOSH, HAVE A SEAT.
PLEASE.
JENNIFER HAS JUST TOLD ME
ABOUT THE NEWS.
I'M SPEECHLESS.
SO WALK ME THROUGH THIS, JOSH.
YOU WALK ME THROUGH THIS,
IF YOU CAN, PLEASE.
>> THIS IS JUST THE NEXT STEP
IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I MEAN, WE DON'T PLAN ON RUNNING
OFF AND GETTING MARRIED.
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE PLAN ON DOING
AT ALL.
I DID THIS TONIGHT BECAUSE
I TRULY FELT IN MY HEART
WE WERE READY FOR IT.
REALLY AND TRULY, I DID.
>> [sighs]
JOSH...
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO
MAKE THIS HAPPEN BECAUSE
THE CHILDREN ARE COMING?
>> NO.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE OUTCOME
IS GONNA BE, JOSH.
I HAVE TO TELL MY HUSBAND THAT
YOU PROPOSED TO MY DAUGHTER
TONIGHT.
HE'S NOT GONNA TAKE THIS
VERY WELL.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
A BEAUTIFUL MOMENT FOR YOU,
JENNIFER.
>> AND IT WAS.
>> AND I'M GLAD IT WAS.
BUT IT'S EVEN MUCH MORE
BEAUTIFUL WHEN YOUR FAMILY
ACCEPTS IT, WHEN YOUR FAMILY
CAN SAY CONGRATULATIONS.
BUT I THINK YOU BOTH KNOW
THAT I CANNOT SAY THAT.
>> JENNIFER?
>> YES?
>> COULD YOU COME HERE, PLEASE?
>> I WAS NOT SURPRISED WHEN
I WOKE UP THE NEXT MORNING
AND MY DAD WANTED TO TALK TO ME.
>> I WANT TO HAVE A CONVERSATION
ABOUT SOMETHING THAT JOSH...
PROPOSED TO YOU.
WHY?
WHY DID YOU SAY YES?
>> BECAUSE I'M IN LOVE WITH HIM,
AND I WANT TO BE WITH HIM.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT
YOU'RE ALSO 16 RIGHT NOW TOO.
YOU THINK YOU'RE READY
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
I KNOW YOU'RE PREGNANT,
BUT STILL...
>> WELL, I'M NOT GONNA GO AND
JUST RUN OFF AND GET MARRIED.
>> NO.
WAY, WAY TOO YOUNG.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT HE'S DOING.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> TWO.
THAT'S ENOUGH TO TAKE ON.
SO LET'S SLOW DOWN,
TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU HAVE THE BABIES.
SEE HOW THAT IMPACTS YOUR LIFE
FIRST.
FAIR ENOUGH?
OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I WISH MY DAD COULD BE HAPPY
FOR ME, BUT MAYBE HE'S RIGHT,
THAT WE JUST NEED TO FOCUS
ON THE BABIES.
>> HOW DID Y'ALL'S ANNIVERSARY
DINNER GO?
>> HE PROPOSED TO ME.
>> REALLY?
AWW.
WHAT DID YOUR PARENTS HAVE
TO SAY ABOUT THAT?
>> WELL, MY DAD, HE WAS SAYING
IT'S GOING TOO FAST.
I MEAN, I TOLD HIM, LIKE,
I WASN'T GONNA GO AND GET
MARRIED A YEAR LATER OR NOTHING.
LIKE, WE CAN BE--
>> IT'S JUST THE COMMITMENT.
>> YEAH.
I ALSO DIDN'T, LIKE,
WANT TO LEAVE THE HOSPITAL
WITH, LIKE, TWO KIDS AND SAY,
"HE'S MY BOYFRIEND,"
OR, "HE'S MY BABY DADDY."
[laughter]
I WANTED TO SAY LIKE,
"NO, HE'S MY FIANCE.
WE'RE GONNA BE TOGETHER.
WE HAVE A COMMITMENT."
MY C-SECTION IS PLANNED
FOR NEXT WEEK, AND SINCE
I'M EXHAUSTED AND MORE
UNCOMFORTABLE THAN EVER,
I HAVE TO DO ALL MY SCHOOLWORK
FROM HOME.
TIME IS RUNNING OUT,
AND JOSH AND I HAVE BEEN
AVOIDING MAKING A PLAN
FOR WHEN WE LEAVE THE HOSPITAL.
DOES IT MATTER IF WE COME HERE
OR TO YOUR HOUSE?
>> IF I'M ALLOWED HERE,
JUST THE FIRST WEEK THEY'RE
ALIVE, I'D LIKE TO BE WITH THEM
THE FIRST WEEK THEY'RE ALIVE,
AT LEAST THAT.
>> YOU GUYS GOT TO MAKE THINGS
BETTER, FOR ME AND THE KIDS.
>> DO YOU REALIZE WE'RE NOT
GONNA GET THINGS BETTER?
>> I DON'T KNOW ANYBODY
WHO WANTS TO GET MARRIED TO
SOMEONE AND NOT BE ON GOOD TERMS
WITH THEIR FAMILY.
>> SO I HAVE TO HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP WITH THEM
TO MARRY YOU?
>> [sighing]
>> I JUST WANT TO BE AROUND
MY KIDS.
THEY BELONG TO ME, NOT THEM.
>> IF YOU GUYS DON'T WORK
THINGS OUT, JOSH, NO ONE
IS GOING TO LET YOU BE AROUND.
>> SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> IF JOSH'S ATTITUDE DOESN'T
CHANGE BY THE TIME THE BABIES
ARE BORN, THEN I'M AFRAID MY
PARENTS WILL NEVER ACCEPT HIM.
>> THE DAY OF MY C-SECTION
HAS FINALLY COME, AND ALTHOUGH
MY PARENTS AND JOSH ARE STILL
NOT TALKING, WE'VE ALL AGREED
TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL TOGETHER.
I DIDN'T THINK I'D FEEL THIS WAY
WHEN THIS DAY CAME.
IT'S NERVE-RACKING,
SCARY,
IF YOU'VE NEVER HAD SURGERY
BEFORE.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
>> I'M ABOUT TO BE PREPPED
FOR MY SURGERY.
>> ANY PROBLEMS THIS PREGNANCY
AT ALL?
>> AND EVEN THOUGH I'M NERVOUS,
IT HELPS THAT JOSH IS BY
MY SIDE...
ALONG WITH MY PARENTS.
TEN MINUTES TILL SURGERY.
[monitor pulsing loudly]
AM I GONNA HAVE THE FIRST
C-SECTION OF THE DAY?
>> NO, NOT QUITE.
>> WE'RE ALMOST READY?
>> YEAH, ALMOST.
COME TOWARDS ME.
>> OH, I GOT TO WALK?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE A TROUPER.
YOU'RE A TROUPER.
>> I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
>> YOU READY?
>> YEP.
>> LET'S GO.
>> SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
[baby crying]
>> TWO HOURS LATER,
JOSH AND I BECAME THE PARENTS
OF TWO BABY BOYS.
JOSHUA JUNIOR ARRIVED FIRST.
AND ONE MINUTE AFTER THAT,
NOAH WAS BORN.
>> ♪ WARM REGRETS
♪ AGAINST THE COLDEST WINTERS
♪ YET
♪ THIS SONG SLEEPS IN
♪ OUR MARROW
♪ BECAUSE I LOVED YOU SO
♪ 'CAUSE I LOVED YOU SO
>> HI, JENNIFER.
>> BABY GIRL?
>> HEY.
>> WHERE DID YOUR STOMACH GO?
IT'S GONE.
DID YOU SEE THE CORD
AND ALL THAT?
>> I SAW JOSH CUT IT.
>> HOW BEAUTIFUL.
>> THAT'S NOAH.
>> HOW Y'ALL KNOW THE
DIFFERENCE?
>> THEIR FEET.
>> THEY GOT THEM LITTLE
BRACELETS ON THEIR FEET.
>> IT'S AMAZING.
JUST AMAZING.
>> OUCH.
THE DOCTOR SAID IT WAS GOING
TO BE A COUPLE OF DAYS UNTIL
I'M ABLE TO WALK AGAIN,
SO THANKFULLY, JOSH IS HERE
TO HELP OUT WITH OUR FIRST
DIAPER CHANGE.
>> OH, HE'S PEEING TOO.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
>> I'M RELIEVED THAT EVERYONE
HAS BEEN GETTING ALONG.
BUT NOW IT'S TIME TO MAKE
SOME TOUGH DECISIONS.
>> GOOD MORNING, MOMMY.
BIRTH CERTIFICATES.
>> HELLO.
>> SO WE'RE JUST GONNA ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS TO COMPLETE
THE BABIES' BIRTH CERTIFICATES,
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
FIRST OF ALL, WE'LL GO
WITH TWIN "A."
WHAT'S GONNA BE HIS FIRST NAME?
>> JOSHUA.
>> AND THEN BABY "B,"
WHAT'S HIS FIRST NAME?
>> NOAH.
>> I JUST WANTED JENNIFER
TO SLEEP ON IT ONE MORE DAY.
YOU KNOW, "YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH
A LOT.
LET'S DO THIS TOMORROW."
>> AND, YOU GUYS, THE LAST NAME
FOR THE BABIES, SAME AS
THE DAD'S?
>> YES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> [sobbing]
>> [sighs]
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GONNA
HAPPEN ONCE YOU LEAVE HERE?
>> WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THE DAY COMES TO LEAVE
AND...
I FEEL LIKE I MADE
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
I JUST WISH IT DIDN'T MEAN
GOING AGAINST MY PARENTS.
EVEN THOUGH I'M IN A LOT
OF PAIN, WE LEAVE THE HOSPITAL
TOMORROW.
AND I'M HOPING MY PARENTS
AREN'T TOO DISAPPOINTED
ABOUT THE LAST NAMES
TO LET JOSH COME HOME WITH US.
DO YOU FEEL COMFORTABLE
GOING TO MY HOUSE?
>> AS LONG AS THERE'S NOT GONNA
BE NO ARGUING AND EVERYTHING.
YOU WANT TO CALL YOUR MOM
AND SEE IF IT'S OKAY
FOR US TO GO THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> HEY, JENNIFER, BABY,
HOW YOU DOING?
YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, I'M FINE.
ME AND JOSH WERE TALKING ABOUT
WHAT WE WANTED TO DO.
I WOULD LIKE TO GO HOME.
I'D FEEL MORE COMFORTABLE THERE.
AND JOSH SAID HE'D LIKE
TO GO THERE.
>> I'M NOT SURE WHERE WE'RE
GOING RIGHT NOW, BUT WE'RE BOTH
PRETTY UPSET OVER WHAT HAPPENED.
I JUST WISH THAT JOSH WOULD
THINK BEFORE HE REACTS.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE ABOUT
TO PISS ME OFF.
>> BUT I CANNOT CONTINUE TO GET
DISRESPECTED.
>> NEITHER CAN I.
>> AND THEN JOSH HAS NO
CONSEQUENCES.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE SOME TOO.
>> ALWAYS US MAKING THE PEACE.
>> MAKING IT--YEAH, RIGHT.
>> TRYING TO MAKE THINGS WORK.
>> MAKING THINGS WORSE.
>> IS THAT JOSH?
>> YES, IT IS.
>> YOU NEED TO MEET ME HALFWAY.
>> THEY'RE NOT YOUR KIDS.
I DON'T HAVE TO MEET YOU
HALFWAY.
>> THAT'S THE KIND OF ATTITUDE
THAT I DON'T WANT AROUND.
>> NO, I DON'T WANT TO BE
IN YOUR HOUSE.
>> THIS IS THE CHOICE THAT
YOU'RE MAKING.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA CALL
SECURITY, AND I'M GONNA HAVE
THEM ESCORT YOU OUT OF THAT ROOM
IF YOU CONTINUE TO TALK
LIKE THAT IN THE PRESENCE
OF THE BABIES AND MY DAUGHTER.
>> WE'LL SEE IF JENNIFER
ALLOWS THAT.
>> THIS TEMPERAMENT
THIS BOY HAS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
>> OKAY, GOOD-BYE, MOM.
>> I'M FED UP WITH THAT LADY.
>> JOSH, SEE, THAT'S THE STUFF
I TALK ABOUT.
YOU SIT THERE, AND YOU ARGUE
WITH MY PARENTS.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE GOING HOME.
[sniffles]
>> WHAT'S GONNA HAPPEN TOMORROW,
WHEN YOU'RE READY TO LEAVE?
>> I'D RATHER LIVE IN A HOSPITAL
THAN EVEN GO ANYWHERE RIGHT NOW.
>> TODAY WE'RE LEAVING
THE HOSPITAL, AND I WANT
TO GO TO MY HOUSE, BUT AFTER
THE WAY JOSH ACTED LAST NIGHT,
I'M NOT EVEN SURE IF MY PARENTS
WILL LET HIM.
>> WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT
JENNIFER COMING HOME FROM
THE HOSPITAL.
>> IT'S GONNA BE REALLY HARD
FOR ME.
>> WHY SHOULD I OPEN MY DOORS
TO HIM, WELCOME HIM IN?
>> YOU'D DO IT FOR JENNIFER.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THE BABIES.
>> HEY, JOSH.
>> HMM?
>> MY MOM JUST TEXTED AND SAID
SHE'D BE UP HERE IN ONE MINUTE.
>> OH, BOY.
>> HEY.
>> HELLO.
>> OH, JENNIFER, YOU LOOK
SO PRETTY.
YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT HAPPENED YESTERDAY
IS YESTERDAY'S NEWS.
OKAY?
JENNIFER NEEDS YOU.
THE BABIES NEED YOU.
SO WE'RE GOING HOME
AS A FAMILY TODAY, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> I'M HAPPY MY PARENTS
CAME AROUND, BUT I'VE JUST
HAD MAJOR SURGERY, SO IT'S HARD
TO ENJOY ANYTHING RIGHT NOW.
OW!
OWW!
[wails]
OH, NO, NO.
SLOW DOWN.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M TRYING.
>> IT HURTS.
>> READY FOR HIM, JENNIFER?
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OW...
>> TAKE YOUR TIME.
>> IT'S NICE TO BE HOME,
BECAUSE I'M EXHAUSTED.
BUT THE MOMENT I GOT IN BED,
EVERYBODY WANTED TO MEET
THE TWINS.
>> JENNIFER, YOU HAVE A VISITOR.
>> HI.
CAN WE COME OVER SATURDAY TOO?
[doorbell rings]
>> HELLO.
>> HELLO, MY BABY!
>> HI.
>> MWAH!
>> HI...SO MANY PEOPLE.
>> THEY LOOK ALIKE TO ME.
HERE YOU GO.
[all talking at once]
>> HIS IS DIFFERENT.
>> HEY?
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> YEAH.
>> I'M GLAD ALL MY FAMILY
IS COMING BY, BUT I CAN TELL
HAVING SO MANY PEOPLE OVER
IS UPSETTING JOSH.
>> HOW ABOUT SOME BREAD?
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU BREAD.
YOU WANT SOME?
BREAD AND BUTTER?
>> YEAH.
HOW DO YOU FEEL BEING HERE?
LIKE, YOU OKAY BEING HERE?
>> I FELT A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
WE SHOULD THINK ABOUT LETTING
THEM STAY AT MY PARENTS' HOUSE.
>> WE'LL SEE.
HI.
>> WHATEVER.
>> YOU OKAY?
YOU DON'T LOOK COMFORTABLE.
>> I'M LEAVING.
[door slams]
>> JOSH?
>> WHO WAS ALL THERE?
LIKE, EVERYBODY?
>> COUSINS, FAMILY, FRIENDS.
I MEAN, LIKE, TEN OTHER PEOPLE
THAT SHOULDN'T BE IN THE HOUSE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, IF HER PARENTS HAD
ANY RESPECT FOR ME AND JENNIFER,
THEY WOULD HAVE KEPT EVERYBODY
AWAY FOR A LITTLE BIT.
BUT I DON'T LIKE LIVING WITH
HER PARENTS.
I DON'T LIKE HER PARENTS AT ALL.
SO I JUST LEFT.
[cell phone buzzing]
>> JOSH FINALLY TEXTED ME
AND SAID HE'S NOT COMING BACK
OVER AS LONG AS MY PARENTS
ARE AROUND.
I HAD JUST CAME OUT OF SURGERY,
JUST GOTTEN HOME.
>> WE'VE DONE OUR PART.
YOU KNOW, MOM AND DAD OPENED
THE DOORS FOR HIM.
THAT DAY AT THE HOSPITAL,
I REALLY MEANT IT WHEN I TOLD
HIM, YOU KNOW, "LET'S GO HOME,"
AND I EMBRACED HIM.
I REALLY MEANT THAT.
LET HIM DO WHAT HE HAS TO DO
NOW, WHATEVER THAT MAY BE.
>> I HAVE TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL
SOON, BUT SINCE JOSH ISN'T
AROUND TO PITCH IN WITH
THE TWINS, MY PARENTS HAVE
AGREED TO HELP ME OUT.
CAN YOU LAY HIM DOWN?
>> I WILL.
>> THEN WHEN NOAH WAKES UP,
I'LL FEED HIM.
NOAH'S BOTTLE IS READY.
MWAH.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> TAKING CARE OF TWINS
IS HARDER THAN I EVER THOUGHT.
AS SOON AS ONE BABY STARTS
CRYING, THE OTHER ONE WAKES UP.
I'M STARTING TO REALLY RESENT
JOSH FOR NOT BEING HERE
TO HELP ME.
THIS IS SOMETHING YOUR DAD
SHOULD BE HELPING OUT ON.
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT.
[baby crying]
I'M TRYING TO KEEP YOU WARM
FOR A SECOND.
[baby crying]
[babies crying]
JOSH AVOIDING MY HOUSE
AND THE KIDS IS UNACCEPTABLE,
SO I NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
HEY.
>> ARE YOU GONNA LET ME
SEE MY KIDS?
>> NEVER TOLD YOU YOU COULDN'T.
>> SO WHEN?
>> WELL, YOU CAN COME OVER.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOUR PARENTS?
>> THEY'RE NOT HOME.
>> YOU SURE?
>> YEAH, OR I WOULDN'T HAVE YOU
COME OVER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BYE.
>> HELLO.
SINCE STAYING AT MY HOUSE
OBVIOUSLY ISN'T WORKING,
I AGREED TO TAKE THE KIDS
OVER TO JOSH'S, SO HE COULD
SPEND MORE TIME WITH THEM
AND WE COULD FIGURE THINGS OUT.
[phone ringing]
HELLO?
YES, I AM.
>> HANGING UP THE PHONE, PLEASE.
>> OKAY.
>> HOW DISRESPECTFUL.
LOVE YOU TOO.
>> WHO WAS THAT ON THE PHONE?
>> MY MOM.
>> WHY IS SHE CALLING YOU?
>> SHE SAID MAYBE WE CAN ALL
TALK AND THEN--
>> AND THEN SHE'S GONNA TRY
TO CONTROL US, IS WHAT
SHE'S GONNA TRY AND DO.
>> JOSH.
>> WHAT?
YOU KNOW, DO YOUR PARENTS
WIPE YOUR OWN ASS FOR YOU?
>> WATCH WHAT YOU SAY.
>> BET IT'S TRUE.
YOU DO EXPECT YOUR PARENTS
TO STILL--
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> YEAH, YOU DO.
>> YOU DO.
YOU STILL RELY ON THEM.
>> I DO A LOT MORE THINGS
THAN YOU THINK I DO.
>> REALLY?
LIKE WHAT?
>> YOU TAKE CARE OF TWO KIDS,
JOSH.
>> I DID WHEN THEY WERE BORN.
>> OKAY, AT THE HOSPITAL.
TAKE ME HOME.
>> STUPID ASS BITCH.
>> EXCUSE YOU?
>> YOU HEARD ME.
>> I'M DONE.
>> YOU WANT OUT OF THIS
RELATIONSHIP, JENNIFER?
>> YEAH, I DO.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M THE BAD ONE.
I'M STUCK IN THE MIDDLE
OF ALL THIS STUPID DRAMA,
AND I HAVE TO CHOOSE BETWEEN
THE PEOPLE I LOVE, AND NO MATTER
WHAT, I STILL GET CRAP FROM IT.
>> JENNIFER--
>> NO, NO, IT DOESN'T MATTER,
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT,
NOW, NOW I'M DONE.
>> I'M GONNA TAKE YOU HOME.
YOU'RE GONNA GET OUT OF MY CAR.
THE KIDS ARE STAYING WITH ME.
>> HELL, NO, THEY'RE NOT.
>> YEAH, THEY ARE.
>> NO, THEY'RE NOT.
YOU'RE A [bleep], JOSH.
YOU HAVE KIDS IN THE CAR.
>> SHUT UP!
JUST SHUT YOUR MOUTH, OKAY?
>> SHUT YOUR FACE.
>> SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
>> GET YOUR HAND OUT OF MY FACE.
>> THEN SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
>> CONTROL YOUR [bleep] ANGER,
JOSH.
>> GET THE [bleep] OUT.
>> THEY'RE COMING WITH ME.
[engine revs]
OKAY!
JUST FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
YOU'RE GOING TO JAIL!
THAT'S CALLED KIDNAPPING!
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE JOSH KICKED
ME OUT OF THE CAR AND TOOK OFF
WITH THE BABIES.
>> BITCH.
>> I'VE CALLED MY MOM TO COME
PICK ME UP.
>> GO AHEAD AND CALL THEM.
>> MY KIDS ARE COMING WITH ME.
>> THEY AIN'T [bleep] GOING
WITH YOU, JENNIFER.
YOU CAN BACK UP.
GET YOUR HANDS OFF--
>> THEY'RE NOT YOUR--
>> GET OFF MY STUFF.
>> DON'T [bleep] PICK ME UP LIKE
THAT WHEN I HAVE A [bleep] CUT!
HUH!
HOW ABOUT THAT, JOSH!
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT,
I'M CALLING THE COPS.
I DON'T GIVE A CRAP NO MORE,
JOSH.
MY BOYFRIEND WANTS TO TAKE
MY KIDS.
I WOULD LIKE A DEPUTY OUT HERE.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR DAD.
>> THERE'S YOUR PATHETIC-ASS MOM
RIGHT THERE HERSELF.
GO AHEAD, FLICK ME OFF.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
>> I'M LOOKING AT YOU, OKAY?
YOU IDIOT.
>> STUPID BITCH.
>> YOU'RE AS DUMB AS THEY COME,
JOSH.
>> HOW ABOUT HE THREW ME
OUT OF THE CAR?
>> YOU WHAT!
>> HOW ABOUT--HOW ABOUT--
>> CALLING THE COPS, THAT'S IT.
>> HOW ABOUT--I ALREADY DID.
I ALREADY DID.
HE'S AROUND THE CORNER.
>> RICO?
>> YOU PARKED THE CAR,
OPENED THE DOOR FOR ME--
BECAUSE OF YOU.
>> THAT'S WHY I GOT THIS
RED MARK ON MY FACE, BECAUSE--
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU WOULDN'T LET
ME GET MY KIDS OUT OF THE CAR.
>> DO IT AGAIN.
>> DO IT AGAIN WHAT?
NO!
NO, NO.
>> GO AHEAD.
>> THINK ABOUT YOUR KIDS, JOSH.
YOU WILL NEVER, EVER
SEE THEM AGAIN.
SAY IT AGAIN.
SAY GOOD-BYE.
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT, JOSH,
I HAVE TO CRY BECAUSE MY KIDS
WON'T SEE THEIR DAD ANYMORE.
[police siren wailing]
JOSH ONLY HAD TO SPEND
ONE NIGHT IN JAIL, AND I'M NOT
PRESSING ANY CHARGES.
BUT NOW THAT HE'S OUT,
I DON'T WANT TO SEE HIM.
TELL YOUR DADDY TO QUIT
CALLING MOMMY.
>> WHAT HE DID WAS UNACCEPTABLE,
REALLY.
>> WHAT DOES THIS MEAN WITH
YOUR ENGAGEMENT AND STUFF
LIKE THAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> MEANS IT CAN GO RIGHT UP
HIS BUTT.
[phone buzzing]
>> UNBELIEVABLE.
I'M BESIDE MYSELF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
>> YOU WANT TO TALK TO HIM?
>> NO.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE HIM,
DON'T WANT TO HEAR HIM.
[baby crying]
>> YOU WOULD THINK HE WOULD GET
THE PICTURE; NOBODY WANTS TO
ANSWER HIM.
>> LAST NIGHT, YOUR FATHER AND I
ARE NOT GONNA FORGET.
>> I'M MAD.
I'M HURT, ANGRY.
MORE MAD THAN HURT, MAYBE.
>> IT'S ABOUT TIME
THAT THE YOUNG MAN HAS
CONSEQUENCES FOR HIS ACTIONS.
>> YEAH, SEE, SOMEBODY THAT
LOVES YOU WON'T TREAT YOU
LIKE THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> HE WOULDN'T ACT LIKE THAT.
>> SOME DAYS, YOU'RE GONNA FEEL
SORRY FOR HIM,
SOME DAYS, YOU'RE GONNA
BE ANGRY.
>> YOU'RE GONNA WANT HIM BACK.
>> I MEAN, THERE'S GONNA
BE A LOT HERE.
BUT, JENNIFER, THERE IS
NO GOING BACK ANYMORE.
>> I KNOW.
I CAN CARE LESS.
>> ♪ I LEFT YOU IN THE DARK
>> LOOK WHO'S HERE.
>> HI, MUNCHKIN.
>> ♪ AND YOUR TEARS CAME DOWN
♪ LIKE SPARKS UPON MY HEART
>> THE FIGHT JOSH AND I HAD,
THAT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE.
DON'T FALL ASLEEP.
HERE.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THE ONE
TO STAND UP FOR HIM,
AND HE PROVED ME WRONG.
MY PARENTS HAVE DEFINITELY
HELPED ME OUT THROUGH
EVERYTHING.
>> BABY GIRL, YOU ALWAYS GOT US,
NO MATTER WHAT.
>> RIGHT NOW, I JUST PLAN TO
FINISH HIGH SCHOOL BEFORE
ANYTHING ELSE.
AND I'M THANKFUL MY PARENTS
ARE AROUND TO WATCH THE BABIES,
SO I CAN DO THAT.
>> IT'S A LITTLE TIGHT, RIGHT?
>> OH, NO, THIS ONE IS.
THAT ONE, I FIXED.
WITH TWO KIDS, SOONER OR LATER,
YOU'RE GONNA NEED THE HELP.
AND EVEN WITH THE GREAT SUPPORT
OF MY FAMILY, IT'S DIFFICULT.
>> OKAY, BYE-BYE.
>> BYE.
BOTH JOSH AND MY FAMILY
HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GET ALONG,
AND I WISH WE ALL COULD HAVE
BEEN A HAPPY FAMILY.
IT'LL BE OKAY WITHOUT
YOUR DADDY.
MAMA'S GOT IT UNDER CONTROL.
>> ♪ EVERYONE'S ASLEEP
♪ I WILL WALK ALONG
♪ THE EMPTY STREETS
♪ WITH NO ONE ELSE
>> AND THINGS WITH ME AND HIM
SHOULD HAVE NEVER BEEN THIS WAY.
[sniffles]
Captioning byCaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> SO, LIKE, RYAN, YOU THINK
HE'S GONNA STEP UP?
>> HE DOESN'T FULLY
UNDERSTAND IT.
>> HE'S A 17-YEAR-OLD KID
TRYING TO BE A GROWN-UP.
>> CAN YOU HANDLE IT, RYAN?
>> A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITY.
>> SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
[baby crying]
>> YOU'RE NOT EVEN OLD ENOUGH
TO DRINK, AND YOU SHOW UP
HUNGOVER.
>> I WILL TRY TO BE HERE
FOR MY CHILD.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT
WHEN I CAN'T BE HERE?
>> YOU MADE YOUR BED.
NOW YOU HAVE TO LIE IN IT.3 2 F1