>> HI, I'M AUBREY.
[chime dings]
I'M 17, AND I LIVE IN
PRESCOTT VALLEY, ARIZONA.
MY PARENTS GOT DIVORCED
WHEN I WAS LITTLE, AND I GREW UP
MOSTLY WITH MY MOM, BUT WE
BOUNCED AROUND A LOT.
ALL THAT MOVING AROUND MADE IT
HARD FOR ME TO HAVE A NORMAL
CHILDHOOD.
I STARTED GETTING IN TROUBLE
AND CUTTING CLASS, AND
EVENTUALLY I DROPPED OUT
OF HIGH SCHOOL.
[laughter]
WHEN I WAS 16, I MET BRANDON.
HE WAS A FEW YEARS OLDER,
BUT WE FELL IN LOVE INSTANTLY
AND DECIDED TO MOVE IN TOGETHER
AGAINST MY PARENTS' WISHES.
[chime dings]
NO, DON'T.
LEAVE THAT ONE ALONE.
>> I JUST TOUCHED IT, HON.
>> MY PLAN WAS TO GET MY G.E.D.
AND GO TO CULINARY SCHOOL WHILE
BRANDON SUPPORTED US, BUT OUR
ATTEMPT AT PLAYING HOUSE WENT
SOUTH WHEN BRANDON LOST HIS JOB
AND WE GOT EVICTED.
MY MOM COULDN'T TAKE US IN
BECAUSE SHE WAS LIVING WITH
HER BOYFRIEND.
SO THE ONLY PERSON I HAD TO TURN
TO WAS MY GRANDMA.
>> WHO CARES?
>> NOW BRANDON AND I ARE ENGAGED
AND PLANNING OUR FUTURE
TOGETHER.
IT ISN'T THE PERFECT SITUATION,
BUT WE'LL HAVE TO MAKE IT WORK
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
GROWING UP, MY FAMILY LIFE
WAS UNSTABLE, AND BEFORE I GOT
PREGNANT, ALL I WANTED TO DO
WAS PARTY, BUT NOW THAT I'M
GOING TO BE A PARENT,
I WANT TO DO THINGS RIGHT.
ISN'T IT CRAZY THAT THE NEXT
TIME WE'RE HERE, WE'RE GONNA
HAVE A BABY WITH US?
>> THAT IS PRETTY CRAZY.
>> IT'S WEIRD.
I THINK THE ONE THING THAT'S
MAINLY IMPORTANT TO ME IS THAT
AUSTIN HAS BOTH PARENTS
GROWING UP, 'CAUSE, YOU KNOW,
GROWING UP, I DIDN'T HAVE
BOTH PARENTS THERE.
YOU KNOW, I JUST--I WANT TO TRY
AND BE THERE FOR HIM AS MUCH
AS POSSIBLE AND HAVE US BE HOME
WITH HIM AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE,
YOU KNOW?
>> MY MOM WAS CONSTANTLY DOING
HER OWN THING AND JUST HAD,
YOU KNOW, OTHER PRIORITIES,
YOU KNOW, OTHER THAN HER KIDS.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY THAT AT LEAST,
YOU KNOW, I KNOW HE HAS A MOM
THAT WILL LOVE HIM AND WHO'S
GONNA BE SUPPORTIVE AND...
>> OH, THANK YOU.
[laughter]
EVEN THOUGH MY MOM LIVES NEARBY,
SHE COULDN'T HELP US OUT.
SO MY GRANDMA WAS KIND ENOUGH
TO TAKE US IN.
BUT SHE'S BATTLING EMPHYSEMA,
AND SHE'S HOPING WE'LL MOVE OUT
BEFORE THE BABY ARRIVES.
>> WELL, I COULDN'T PUT YOU OUT
ON THE STREET, COULD I?
>> NO.
AFTER WE FOUND OUT WE WERE
PREGNANT, THEY FIRED BRANDON
FROM HIS JOB.
HE CAN'T CONTINUE TO PAY RENT
WITHOUT A PAYCHECK, SO...
>> THAT WAS FINE.
>> HERE WE ARE, LIVING WITH YOU.
>> I'M NOT VERY ANXIOUS
TO HAVE A BABY IN THE HOUSE.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE I SAID, I'VE BEEN THERE,
DONE THAT, AND I'M NOT CRAZY
ABOUT BABIES, AND THEY MAKE ME
NERVOUS, YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, I KNOW YOU'RE NOT CRAZY
ABOUT BABIES.
>> YOU GET OLDER, AND IT'S...
>> YOU DON'T WANT TO DEAL WITH
THE BABY CRYING ALL THE TIME
AT NIGHT.
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> THE BABY IS DUE IN FEBRUARY.
WE'LL BE OUT OF HERE BEFORE
THE BABY COMES, FOR SURE.
>> AND IN OUR OWN PLACE.
>> WELL, AUBREY, HOW DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING TO GET AN
APARTMENT, PAY UTILITIES,
WHEN NEITHER ONE OF YOU
ARE WORKING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
BRANDON AND I SHOULD BE LOOKING
FOR JOBS, BUT WE'VE DECIDED TO
GET MARRIED RIGHT AWAY.
[chime dings]
AND EVEN THOUGH MY FRIENDS
WANT TO SUPPORT ME, I CAN TELL
THEY THINK I'M RUSHING INTO
MARRIAGE.
>> WOULD YOU HAVE MARRIED
BRANDON IF YOU DIDN'T GET
PREGNANT?
>> YES, I WOULD HAVE EVENTUALLY
MARRIED HIM.
IT WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN RIGHT
AWAY, BUT I WOULD HAVE
EVENTUALLY MARRIED HIM.
I ALREADY HAD MY PROMISE RING
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT.
HE ALREADY MADE THAT PROMISE
TO ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
THE THOUGHT OF YOU HAVING
A BABY, IT'S JUST, LIKE, CRAZY.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, HOW DID YOU GET
PREGNANT?
>> WELL, ME AND BRANDON WENT
TO A PARTY ONE NIGHT, AND THEN
WE CAME HOME, AND...
I DON'T HONESTLY REALLY REMEMBER
MUCH OF THE NIGHT.
SO WE WERE KIND OF TOO STUPID
TO BE HAVING SEX.
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
HAVING SEX, I SHOULD SAY.
WE REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN.
>> WELL, WERE YOU ON, LIKE,
BIRTH CONTROL?
DID YOU GUYS USE PROTECTION?
>> WE USUALLY JUST USED
PULL-OUT, I MEAN,
IF NOT A CONDOM,
AND BRANDON JUST DIDN'T...
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE, I WANT TO ENJOY MY LIFE.
LIKE, I JUST WANT TO BE ABLE
TO DO SO MUCH STUFF THAT, LIKE,
HAVING A BABY AND HAVING
A HUSBAND WOULD, LIKE, RESTRICT
FROM, YOU KNOW?
>> BUT, SEE, I DON'T AGREE
AT ALL.
I DON'T.
LIKE, I THINK THAT YOU CAN
HAVE IT ALL.
AND I STILL PLAN ON GETTING
MY EDUCATION.
LIKE, I'M STILL GETTING
MY G.E.D., AND I'M STILL
GONNA GO TO COLLEGE.
AND I'M STILL, YOU KNOW--
MY LIFE'S NOT GONNA STOP
JUST BECAUSE I'M HAVING A BABY,
AND EVERYONE SEEMS TO THINK
THAT.
I'M SICK OF EVERYONE NOT HAVING
MY BACK.
GETTING MARRIED ISN'T GOING TO
STOP ME FROM GETTING MY G.E.D.
OR GOING TO CULINARY SCHOOL.
BRANDON AND I ARE GOING TO MAKE
THIS WORK.
BUT RIGHT NOW, I NEED TO GET
READY FOR THE WEDDING.
SO I'M GOING TO THE MALL
TO LOOK AT SHOES, EVEN THOUGH
MY CREDIT LINE MAXED OUT.
>> I LIKE THIS, THOUGH.
>> THAT'S ACTUALLY
REALLY PRETTY.
>> SO SOFT.
>> I KNOW.
THESE SHOES ARE PERFECT.
>> WHAT ARE THOSE SHOES FOR,
AUBREY?
>> THE WEDDING.
>> DO YOU HAVE CLOTHES PICKED
OUT, LIKE, WHAT YOU WANT
TO WEAR?
>> YEAH.
SO I THINK--THAT'S WHY I THINK
THESE WILL MATCH.
>> HAVE YOU GUYS PICKED A DATE
YET?
>> NEXT WEEK.
GOOD TO GO.
BRANDON HAS NO JOB, AND I'VE
NEVER WORKED, SO WE'RE IN
SERIOUS DEBT, AND WE NEED
TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET
OUT OF IT IF WE'RE EVER GOING
TO GET OUR OWN PLACE.
I'M GONNA TOTAL UP OUR STUFF
AND SEE HOW MUCH MONEY WE OWE,
SO THAT WE KIND OF HAVE AN IDEA
OF WHAT WE NEED TO PAY OFF.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
>> THIS ONE SAYS, "DEAR BRANDON,
YOUR DELINQUENT ACCOUNT HAS BEEN
TURNED OVER TO THE COLLECTION
AGENCY.
$329."
THIS ONE'S FOR $295.94.
>> AND YOUR AUNT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> DO I OWE HER $500?
>> $700.
SO THAT PUTS OUR TOTAL
AT $2,011.36.
>> WELL, I'M HOPING TO HAVE
A JOB SOON.
>> YEAH.
>> WE HAVE TWO MONTHS TO COME UP
WITH SOME WAY--SOME MEANS
OF STEADY FINANCIAL STABILITY.
>> AND PAY OFF ALL THOSE BILLS.
>> AND PAY OFF ALL THE BILLS
AND GET EVERYTHING READY.
>> I GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO...
I DON'T KNOW.
UNTIL YOU GET A JOB, IT'S GONNA
BE HARD TO PAY OFF BILLS.
>> I'LL LOOK FOR ODD JOBS,
AND THEN I'LL START APPLYING
AT SOME OF THE OTHER PLACES
THAT I DIDN'T ALREADY APPLY TO,
AND THEN I WANT TO APPLY
AT BEST BUY.
THAT'S SOMETHING I COULD DO,
RIGHT?
PROBABLY.
UNLESS THEY ASK ME ANYTHING
ABOUT COMPUTERS.
>> OR CAMERAS.
OR CELL PHONES.
OR ANYTHING ELECTRONIC.
>> [clears throat]
[chime dings]
>> OUR BILLS ARE PILING UP.
WE HAVE NO JOBS AND NEED TO FIND
A NEW PLACE TO LIVE
ALL BEFORE THE BABY IS BORN.
>> I'M REALLY HAPPY BRANDON
AND I ARE GETTING MARRIED
AND ON OUR WAY TO BEING
A REAL FAMILY.
YOU COMING?
AND TODAY WE'RE HEADED TO
THE DOCTOR TO GET A GOOD LOOK AT
OUR BABY BOY FOR THE FIRST TIME.
>> OKAY, LET'S JUST TAKE
A LOOK FIRST AND SEE WHAT
POSITION YOUR BABY IS IN.
>> HOLY CRAP, IT'S HUGE.
>> SO CRAZY.
>> IF I COME IN FROM THE SIDE,
THERE'S THE PROFILE OF THE FACE.
>> SWEET BABY BOY AUSTIN.
>> AUSTIN.
WHAT'S HIS MIDDLE NAME?
>> CARTER.
>> THAT'S A GOOD NAME.
>> YEAH.
OH, HE'S JUST SO PERFECT.
I'M EXCITED.
I WANT TO MEET HIM.
>> OH...
>> TAKE CARE OF LITTLE AUSTIN.
>> I WILL.
THANK YOU.
SEEING AUSTIN MADE ME REALIZE
HOW MUCH OUR LIVES ARE ABOUT
TO CHANGE.
OUR WEDDING IS TOMORROW,
AND WE STILL DON'T HAVE
EVERYTHING WE NEED.
SO WE'RE DOING SOME LAST-MINUTE
SHOPPING.
>> NICE.
>> MOST OF MY GARTERS ARE RIGHT
UP HERE.
WHAT COLOR ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
>> BLUE.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING BLUE YET.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GETTING
MARRIED AT?
>> JUST IN THE COURTYARD.
ALTHOUGH WE CAN'T AFFORD
A BIG WEDDING, GETTING MARRIED
BEFORE THE BABY COMES
IS IMPORTANT TO US,
BUT MY MOM DOESN'T SEE IT
THAT WAY.
>> I KNOW IT'S GONNA BE ROUGH.
>> I THINK IT HELPS A LOT
THAT WE'VE ALREADY LIVED
TOGETHER ON OUR OWN.
>> IT'S A LOT OF WORK,
WHETHER YOU'RE YOUNG OR
A LITTLE BIT MORE MATURE,
AND IT'S GONNA BE DIFFICULT.
>> I KNOW.
I'M...
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT EXPECTING IT
TO BE A WALK IN THE PARK.
IT'S KIND OF HARD TO LISTEN
TO MY MOM'S ADVICE, BECAUSE SHE
HASN'T BEEN AROUND MUCH.
SHE HAS TO WORK TOMORROW,
SO SHE'S NOT EVEN COMING
TO MY WEDDING.
MY AUNT HAS AGREED TO HELP ME
GET READY, BUT EVEN SHE DOESN'T
APPROVE.
>> AUBREY, I WOULD HAVE LIKED
TO HAVE SEEN YOU FINISH SCHOOL
AND GO TO COLLEGE.
>> I KNOW.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT ANYTHING
TO BE TAKEN LIGHTLY.
>> WELL, NO, I'M DEFINITELY NOT
TAKING IT LIGHTLY AT ALL.
>> IT'S A MARRIAGE.
IT'S NOT A SCHOOL DANCE.
>> I THINK WE'LL MAKE IT.
>> I HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING IN TO.
>> YEP.
>> OKAY.
>> GOOD?
>> I THINK SO.
OKAY, WHAT WAS THE THOUGHT
PROCESS ON THESE SHOES?
>> THEY WERE CUTE,
AND THEY MATCHED.
I JUST WANTED TO WEAR
SOMETHING CASUAL.
>> YOU NAILED IT.
I'M REALLY NOT TRYING TO GIVE
YOU A HARD TIME.
IT'S JUST, THIS IS A LITTLE BIT
HARD TO SWALLOW, IS ALL.
>> THE DRESS OR...
>> OH, HONEY, THIS WHOLE THING.
>> BE EXCITED FOR ME.
>> OKAY.
>> MY AUNT WAS GOING TO COME
TO THE WEDDING.
THEN SHE BACKED OUT AT THE LAST
MINUTE BECAUSE SHE HAD TO WORK
AS WELL.
BUT IT'S MY WEDDING DAY,
AND I'M NOT GOING TO LET
ANYTHING BRING ME DOWN.
COME ON, MEEMAW.
AND LUCKILY, I CAN ALWAYS COUNT
ON MY GRANDMA TO BE THERE
FOR ME.
>> OH, THESE SHOES.
OKAY, WHERE ARE WE...
>> WHERE ARE WE GONNA DO IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
ARE YOU GUYS COMING?
>> HI, KIDS.
>> HI.
>> I'M TERRY.
>> I'M AUBREY.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> I'M YOUR MINISTER FOR
THE EVENING.
>> I THINK WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
>> WELL, WE'RE HERE ON THIS
BEAUTIFUL FALL AFTERNOON
TO CELEBRATE BRANDON AND AUBREY
AS THEY ARE UNITED IN THE HOLY
BONDS OF MATRIMONY.
TRUE LOVE KNOWS NO LIMIT.
IN FACT, IT'S THE ONE THING,
WHEN EVERYTHING ELSE COMES
CRASHING DOWN, LOVE WILL
SURVIVE.
ARE YOU PREPARED TO TAKE
YOUR VOWS?
>> YES.
>> BRANDON, DO YOU TAKE AUBREY
TO BE YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED WIFE
AND TO STAND BY HER IN TIMES
OF PROSPERITY OR EVEN POVERTY?
>> I DO.
>> AUBREY, DO YOU TAKE BRANDON
TO BE YOUR LAWFULLY WEDDED
HUSBAND, AND DO YOU PROMISE
TO LOVE HIM AND TO CHERISH HIM?
>> I DO.
>> I NOW PRONOUNCE YOU
MAN AND WIFE.
YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
[applause]
>> THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> YOU ARE OFFICIALLY
MY HUSBAND.
NOW THAT WE'RE MARRIED,
WE'RE READY TO START OUR FAMILY,
BUT WE STILL HAVE A LOT
TO FIGURE OUT.
>> YOU HANG ON TO HER, BRANDON,
WITH THOSE SHOES.
>> AH!
SEE?
>> WELL, YOU PICKED THOSE SHOES,
NOT ME.
>> [laughs]
[marker squeaking]
>> BRANDON AND I HAVE BEEN
MARRIED FOR TWO WEEKS, AND WITH
THE BABY ONLY ONE MONTH AWAY,
IT'S BEEN HARD TO FOCUS
ON MY G.E.D., AND BRANDON
STILL HASN'T FOUND WORK.
WE CAN'T PAY OUR BILLS,
LET ALONE FIND OUR OWN PLACE,
AND MY MOM IS REALLY WORRIED.
>> BRANDON, THIS IS REAL
SERIOUS.
YOU NEED TO HAVE A STEADY JOB.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU KNOW, DO SOMETHING TO
TAKE CARE OF AUSTIN AND AUBREY.
>> YEP.
>> I THOUGHT EVERYTHING WOULD
BE OKAY, BUT NOTHING IS WORKING
OUT LIKE I EXPECTED, AND
EVERYONE IS GETTING ON OUR CASE.
>> SO WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> WELL, WE WERE PLANNING ON--
IF BRANDON COULD GET A STEADY
JOB--RENTING A HOUSE.
>> SO LET'S SEE HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE A PLACE TO LIVE.
YOU DON'T HAVE A JOB.
NOT LOOKING REAL GOOD, IS IT?
>> I'VE BEEN APPLYING, YOU KNOW,
FOR ANYTHING, JANITOR, ANYTHING.
IT'S KIND OF HARD.
I DON'T HAVE ANY COLLEGE OR...
I HAVE SOME VOCATIONAL SCHOOL
AND SOME TRADE SCHOOL STUFF
BUT...
>> WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOUR
G.E.D.?
>> THE TEST ISN'T FOR A MONTH.
>> WELL, YOU CAN STUDY.
YOU CAN SIT AND STUDY.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS ARE GONNA HAVE TO
GET SOMETHING GOING.
THOSE DIAPERS AREN'T CHEAP.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S, LIKE,
CRUNCH TIME.
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO FIND
SOMETHING, FOR SURE.
[chime dings]
>> MAYBE MY UNCLE IS RIGHT.
WE'RE NO CLOSER TO BEING ON
OUR OWN THAN WHEN WE MOVED IN
TO GRANDMA'S.
SO BRANDON IS WORKING
DOUBLE-TIME TO FIND WORK.
AND TODAY, HE'S INTERVIEWING
FOR A MALL SECURITY JOB.
>> HEY, HON, I GOT THE JOB.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, I'M GONNA START
MY TRAINING NEXT WEEK.
>> OH, THAT'S SO EXCITING.
COME GIVE ME A KISS.
YOU BETTER GIVE ME A BETTER KISS
THAN THAT.
YOU JUST GOT A JOB.
[laughter]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
>> IT'S SUCH A LOAD OFF MY BACK.
[alarm clock blaring]
>> NOW THAT BRANDON HAS A JOB,
OUR ROUTINE IS CHANGING.
I PACKED YOUR LUNCH.
HAVE A GOOD DAY AT WORK.
>> I WILL.
THANK YOU.
>> BYE.
HE'S UP AT DAWN TO GO TO WORK,
AND I'M SPENDING A LOT MORE TIME
HOME ALONE.
BEING HERE DAY AFTER DAY
WHILE ALL OF MY FRIENDS
ARE IN SCHOOL SUCKS.
[sighs]
I'M DEPRESSED, AND I NEED
TO GET OUT OF THIS RUT.
MY FRIENDS KNEW I WASN'T FEELING
GREAT, SO THEY TOOK ME BOWLING
TO CHEER ME UP.
AM I GONNA GET MY FINGERS
STUCK?
>> PROBABLY.
>> THANK YOU.
OH, THAT'S SO MUCH LIGHTER.
STRAIGHT DOWN THE MIDDLE.
NO...
[laughter]
I SUCK.
HOW'S SCHOOL GOING?
WHAT AM I MISSING OUT ON THERE?
>> NO, YOU'RE NOT MISSING OUT
ON NOTHING.
IT'S SCHOOL.
WE GOT FIVE MORE MONTHS,
AND IT'S OVER.
>> WELL, AN EDUCATION.
>> OH, BESIDES THE FACT, LIKE,
TRYING TO GET SMART.
ARE YOU GONNA ACTUALLY GO
TO COLLEGE?
>> EVENTUALLY.
>> WELL, DO YOU REALLY, LIKE...
I UNDERSTAND, LIKE, IF YOU WERE
IN MY POSITION, LIKE, THAT WOULD
BE EASIER FOR YOU TO DO,
BUT YOU'RE ABOUT TO HAVE A BABY.
LIKE, HOW ARE YOU GONNA DEAL
WITH, LIKE, LATE NIGHT STUDYING
WHEN YOU HAVE A HUGE FATTY TEST
THAT SAYS, LIKE, YOU PASS
OR YOU DON'T PASS?
>> UM...
>> YOU GOT AUSTIN CARTER CRYING
IN THE BACKGROUND, AND BRANDON'S
AT WORK TILL 2:00 IN THE MORNING
AND STUFF.
LIKE, DO YOU--LIKE, DO YOU HAVE
A PLAN, OR DO YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK IT WILL BE...
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD,
BUT IT'S GONNA...
>> WELL, YEAH, IT'S GONNA BE
HARD, BUT I HAVE TO GO
TO SCHOOL.
BUT ANYWAY...
MY FRIENDS ARE RIGHT.
I'M ALREADY HAVING A HARD TIME
STUDYING FOR THE G.E.D.,
AND IT'S ONLY GOING TO GET
HARDER WHEN THE BABY GETS HERE.
SEEING MY FRIENDS MADE ME
REALIZE I HAVE TO GET MOTIVATED
IF I EVER WANT TO GET MY G.E.D.
BRANDON HAS THE DAY OFF, SO I
ASKED HIM TO TAKE ME TO THE
LIBRARY TO GET BOOKS.
BRANDON, COME ON.
BRANDON?
>> I--FINE, I'M COMING.
>> YOU WANT TO LOOK OVER
MY G.E.D. BOOKS WITH ME?
>> WELL, I'LL TRY AND HELP...
I'LL TRY AND HELP AS BEST I CAN,
HONEY.
>> "BASIC ARITHMETIC."
OKAY.
2,000 DIVIDED BY 4 IS 1,500.
>> 2,000 DIVIDED BY 4 IS 1,500?
>> I MEAN, IT'S NOT 1,500.
IT'S, UM...
2,000 DIVIDED BY 4 IS 500.
>> I WISH MY BANK ACCOUNT
WORKED LIKE THAT.
>> "SO IF ANGLE 'A' AND ANGLE
'C' BOTH EQUAL 70 DEGREES, THEN
WHAT IS THE LENGTH OF SIDE A-B?"
>> I CAN SEE THE SMOKE
ROLLING OUT.
>> WHAT?
I'M NOT A COMPLETE IDIOT,
BRANDON.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FUNNY.
IT'S ANNOYING THAT INSTEAD OF
HELPING ME, BRANDON'S JUST
MAKING JOKES.
I'M SETTING UP A PRACTICE G.E.D.
EXAM TO SEE WHERE I'M AT,
AND BRANDON'S GOING TO PICK ME
UP AFTER HIS SHIFT.
>> ALL DONE?
>> YEAH.
ALL FINISHED.
>> WONDERFUL.
ALL RIGHT, PLEASE,
HAVE A SEAT.
OKAY.
>> I'M REALLY EXCITED TO GET
MY G.E.D. SO THAT I CAN GO
TO COLLEGE, 'CAUSE THAT'S MY--
WHAT I'M EXCITED FOR
IN THE FUTURE, SO...
>> UNFORTUNATELY, YOU FAILED
THE MATH TEST.
YOU GOT 39% CORRECT ON THAT ONE.
YOU NEEDED A MINIMUM OF 65%
TO PASS THAT.
>> [sighs]
I HAVEN'T BEEN IN SCHOOL
FOR SO LONG, AND IT HASN'T BEEN
MY MAIN FOCUS, BUT I'D LIKE
TO WORK ON MY MATHEMATICS.
COST-WISE, HOW DOES THAT
USUALLY GO?
>> THAT ONE-ON-ONE RATE
WOULD BE $48 AN HOUR.
>> 48...
SO AROUND 1,500 BUCKS TO...
>> IF YOU REQUIRE THE FULL
AMOUNT OF TIME.
>> MM-HMM, THE FULL AMOUNT
OF TIME TO STUDY FOR, SO...
>> YES.
IS THAT GOING TO BE MANAGEABLE
AT THIS TIME?
>> UM...
I DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT GETTING MY G.E.D.
WOULD BE SIMPLE, BUT NOW
I REALIZE IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
EASIER IF I HAD JUST STAYED
IN SCHOOL.
>> I'M REALLY UPSET I DIDN'T
PASS THE PRACTICE TEST.
HOW AM I GOING TO GET INTO
COLLEGE IF I CAN'T EVEN GET
MY G.E.D.?
[sighs]
I JUST--I'M REALLY ANNOYED.
I'M SORRY.
>> CAN'T YOU BE IN A BETTER
MOOD?
>> WELL, I'M IN A VERY BAD MOOD.
>> WELL, CHANGE IT.
>> HE SAID THAT HE THOUGHT
I'D NEED, LIKE, 30 HOURS
OF TUTORING.
AND 30 HOURS OF TUTORING
IS 1,500 BUCKS.
EH?
>> THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
>> [sighs]
AND TO MAKE THINGS WORSE,
THE NEXT DAY, MY GRANDMA
SAT US DOWN.
>> WE NEED TO HAVE A TALK,
A REALISTIC TALK, ABOUT HOW LONG
YOU'RE GOING TO BE STAYING HERE.
I THINK IT'S ABOUT TIME YOU KIDS
FIND A PLACE.
>> AT THIS POINT, IT TAKES OUR
WHOLE PAYCHECK JUST TO--
>> JUST TO PAY RENT,
IF WE WERE TO MOVE OUT.
>> THEN MAYBE YOU COULD SAVE
EVERY BIT THAT YOU CAN POSSIBLY
SAVE.
I MEAN, WITHOUT GOING OUT
FOR DINNER AND, YOU KNOW,
THIS AND THAT.
>> WE HAVE TO WAIT TILL--
>> WE DON'T GO OUT, YOU KNOW?
WE DON'T GO OUT TO EAT OFTEN.
WE DON'T GO SHOPPING OFTEN.
>> AUBREY...
YOU UNDERSTAND WHERE
I'M COMING FROM, DO YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> MM-HMM, OF COURSE.
>> DO YOU KIDS HAVE ANY MONEY
SAVED RIGHT NOW?
>> UH...
>> NO.
>> NOT REALLY.
THE BANK ACCOUNT IS PRETTY MUCH
EMPTY.
>> FOR SOME REASON, WE CAN'T
SEEM TO GET IT TOGETHER.
AND THE BILL COLLECTORS
ARE STILL CALLING.
HOW MUCH DID YOU SAY THE AMOUNT
WAS THAT WAS OWED?
$329.92.
I WILL NOT BE PAYING THAT TODAY.
THANK YOU.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
[phone clicks shut]
[sighs]
DUMB [bleep] BILL COLLECTORS.
THE PLAN WAS THAT BRANDON WOULD
WORK WHILE I STAY HOME
WITH THE BABY, BUT NOW IT'S
OBVIOUS THAT WE WON'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY WITH ONLY BRANDON
WORKING.
I DO WANT TO GET A JOB,
FOR SURE.
>> I'D RATHER YOU NOT.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE IT WOULDN'T REALLY
MAKE FINANCIAL SENSE, 'CAUSE,
LIKE, EVEN WITH EXPERIENCE
AT A JOB, I DON'T EVEN MAKE
THAT MUCH MONEY.
WITHOUT EXPERIENCE, WITHOUT
A G.E.D. OR ANYTHING...
>> YES, I'M 17.
I'M SORRY THAT I HAVEN'T BEEN
WORKING MY WHOLE LIFE.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I DON'T
WANT TO.
IT TAKES TWO INCOMES THIS DAY
AND AGE TO HAVE A FAMILY,
FOR SURE.
>> I WOULD MAKE ENOUGH TO TAKE
CARE OF BOTH OF US AND THE BABY.
>> I WANT TO HAVE A LIFE TOO.
>> YOU CAN HAVE ONE.
BEING A HOUSEWIFE ISN'T
THAT BAD.
LOTS OF WOMEN LOVE IT.
>> I'M NOT GOING, YOU KNOW,
TO BE JUST, LIKE, A TYPICAL
HOUSEWIFE THAT JUST SITS AT
HOME.
>> WELL, YOU'RE BETTER
AT COOKING.
YOU'RE MORE EFFICIENT
AT CLEANING.
>> [scoffs]
I JUST THINK IT'S LIKE--
IN THIS DAY AND AGE,
IT'S DEGRADING TOWARDS A WOMAN.
LIKE...
>> OH, BROTHER.
>> [sighs]
>> YOU ARE BETTER AT THAT STUFF
THAN I AM, AND YOU KNOW IT.
WHETHER IT'S YOU'RE A WOMAN
OR NOT, I DON'T KNOW, BUT...
>> THAT'S NOT GONNA BE MY GOAL
IN LIFE, OKAY?
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> I'M GONNA BE WORKING
NO MATTER WHAT, PERIOD, AMEN,
END OF STORY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE BRANDON EXPECTS
ME TO BE A HOUSEWIFE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD HAVE DISCUSSED
THIS A LITTLE MORE BEFORE
WE GOT MARRIED.
HI-LO.
>> HEY.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> OH...
I DON'T KNOW.
IF WE REALLY REALISTICALLY WANT
TO BE OUT OF MEEMAW'S HOUSE
AND WANT TO GET OUR OWN PLACE,
BRANDON DOES NOT MAKE ENOUGH.
>> MM.
>> I'M GONNA HAVE TO GET A JOB.
THERE'S GONNA HAVE TO BE
TWO INCOMES COMING IN.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE NEVER GONNA
MAKE IT.
>> GOSH, THAT'S SO TRUE.
DUDE, HAVE YOU EVEN TOLD HIM
ANY OF THIS STUFF?
>> I THINK HE JUST ASSUMED
THAT I WAS GONNA STAY HOME
WITH THE BABY ALL DAY.
I'M GONNA WANT TO GO TO WORK.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE NOT GONNA WANT
TO SIT AT HOME ALL DAY DOING
NOTHING.
>> I'M NOT GONNA WANT TO SIT
AT HOME AND DO NOTHING ALL DAY.
>> YOU'LL GET IT ALL FIGURED
OUT.
>> THE MORE I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE MORE I REALIZE I NEED
TO TALK TO BRANDON ABOUT
HOW FRUSTRATED I'M FEELING.
I JUST AM SO, LIKE, DEPRESSED
SOMETIMES.
LIKE, I HAVE A HUSBAND
AND SOON-TO-BE SON, AND YOU
GOT A JOB, AND I SHOULD BE,
LIKE, HAPPY, YOU KNOW?
BUT I'M JUST, LIKE, WORRIED
THAT IT'S GONNA GET WORSE
AFTER I HAVE THE BABY.
>> YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME
FEEL GUILTY.
I'M GONNA BE GOING TO WORK,
AND YOU'RE GONNA BE STUCK HERE
ALL DAY.
>> I'M NOT.
[groans]
>> WE'RE ABOUT TO HAVE
A FRICKING KID, AND YOU'RE LIKE,
"OH, IT'S GONNA SUCK SO MUCH.
I'M JUST GONNA BE STUCK
IN THE HOUSE ALL THE TIME."
>> I'M NOT.
>> "WAH, POOR ME."
SERIOUSLY, GET OVER IT.
QUIT WHINING.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE BROUGHT IT UP TO YOU.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE, LIKE--
>> WELL, DON'T BRING IT UP
AGAIN.
>> IF BRANDON WON'T LISTEN TO ME
NOW, HOW ARE WE GOING TO MAKE
THIS WORK ONCE THE BABY IS BORN?
>> MY DUE DATE IS ONLY A WEEK
AWAY...
[groans]
AND THE PREGNANCY
IS EXHAUSTING ME.
I'M READY TO HAVE THIS BABY.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE ANXIOUS
TO HAVE HIM.
>> I'M JUST SO ANNOYED WITH
BEING PREGNANT.
I JUST...
WANT TO BE DONE.
I DON'T WANT TO BE PREGNANT
ANYMORE.
I JUST WANT HIM OUT.
SO NOW I'M TRYING EVERYTHING
TO GET THIS LABOR MOVING,
BUT NOTHING SEEMS TO BE WORKING.
I JUST WISH HE WOULD COME
ALREADY, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> [sighs]
MY DUE DATE HAS COME AND GONE.
LET'S GO.
AND MY DOCTOR HAS FINALLY AGREED
TO INDUCE LABOR.
SO BRANDON AND I ARE ON OUR WAY
TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> THE LAST FEW MINUTES
AS NON-PARENTS.
>> I KNOW.
ISN'T IT--WELL, NOT MINUTES.
WE STILL HAVE HOURS LEFT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE
EXCITED FOR THE MOST?
>> I'M EXCITED FOR THE WHOLE
THING AS A BUNDLE.
>> I WANT TO SEE WHAT
HE LOOKS LIKE.
>> LET'S HAVE THIS BABY.
I WANT TO GET THIS THING GOING.
>> SO THE LAST TIME YOU ACTUALLY
ATE OR DRANK ANYTHING WAS BEFORE
YOU GOT HERE, RIGHT?
>> YES.
[heart monitor pulsing]
I HATE NEEDLES.
>> AND YOU KNOW WHAT, HONEY?
NO PAIN, NO GAIN.
AND IT'S RUNNING BEAUTIFULLY.
[camera beeps]
>> HI, AUBREY.
HOW ARE YA?
>> GOOD, I GUESS, READY.
>> OKAY.
>> MY DOCTOR SHOWED UP TO START
THE PITOCIN AND BREAK MY WATER.
>> A LOT OF PRESSURE RIGHT NOW.
THIS PART IS UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
OKAY, IT'S BROKEN.
NICE CLEAR FLUID COMING OUT.
>> MM-KAY.
THAT WAS EXTREMELY GROSS.
[laughter]
>> SO THIS KIND OF GETS YOU
OVER THAT SPEED BUMP OF,
"AM I HAVING A BABY?
AM I NOT HAVING A BABY?"
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY.
WE'RE GONNA MEET THIS
LITTLE GUY.
>> IT'S, LIKE, NEVER ENDING.
I'M FINALLY STARTING TO FEEL
MY CONTRACTIONS, BUT I CAN'T
BELIEVE THIS IS TAKING SO LONG.
BRANDON IS REALLY STARTING
TO ANNOY ME.
>> IT'S ALL GOOD, HON.
WE CAN DO THIS.
>> THERE'S NO [bleep] "WE"
ABOUT IT.
[sighs]
YOU'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING.
YOU'RE SITTING IN A CHAIR.
[moans]
>> [exhales]
>> HOW COME THEY'RE NOT REALLY
CEASING?
>> I CAN GO AHEAD AND GET YOU
SOME PAIN MEDICINE.
>> I'M HAVING ONE RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW.
I'M GIVING IT TO YOU.
>> I'VE BEEN IN LABOR FOR
NEARLY A FULL DAY, AND I'M ONLY
4 CENTIMETERS DILATED.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR THIS
TO BE OVER.
>> JUST BREATHE, HONEY.
>> MY CONTRACTIONS ARE KILLING
ME, AND I JUST CAN'T TAKE IT
ANYMORE.
SO I'M GOING TO GET AN EPIDURAL.
FINALLY, THINGS STARTED
HAPPENING, AND MY DOCTOR SAID
IT WAS TIME TO PUSH.
>> OKAY, HE'S HERE.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> PUSH, PUSH, THAT'S IT.
>> HARDER.
>> GO, GO, GO.
>> TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
YEAH.
>> [exhales]
>> PUSH HARDER.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
EXCELLENT.
>> HERE WE GO, HONEY.
THE LAST ONE.
>> YEAH, PUSH LIKE THAT, AUBREY.
KEEP GOING.
KEEP GOING. KEEP GOING.
>> THAT'S IT.
>> NINE, TEN.
>> GOOD, RIGHT BACK.
DO THE SAME THING AGAIN.
HE'S COMING OUT.
>> AFTER 30 HOURS OF LABOR...
>> HERE HE COMES.
OOH!
SEE, THERE'S YOUR BABY.
>> NICE.
>> THERE HE IS.
>> NICE!
>> HE'S REACHING FOR YOU.
DO YOU WANT TO SEE HIM?
THERE YOU GO.
>> NICE.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER THAT
HE'S A LITTLE GOOPY, DOES IT?
>> NO.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> HE'S PINKING UP, WHICH MEANS
HE'S BREATHING.
>> 13, 15...
>> A LITTLE MORE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> NICE.
>> WHAT TIME WAS IT OVER?
>> 15:35.
>> OKAY.
>> GIVE HIM RIGHT BACK.
>> I WANT DADDY TO BE ABLE
TO HOLD HIM.
>> OKAY.
>> HE'S SO HANDSOME.
[chime dings]
IT'S SO CRAZY TO SEE HIM, LIKE,
ACTUALLY IN PERSON AND NOT ON
THE ULTRASOUND.
COME IN!
MY MOM AND MEEMAW WEREN'T THERE
FOR THE LABOR, BUT AFTER
AUSTIN CARTER WAS BORN,
THEY CAME TO VISIT ME.
>> HE'S SO HANDSOME, AUBREY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HE'S JUST BEAUTIFUL.
>> GOOD JOB, SWEETIE.
>> THANK YOU.
AND MY FRIENDS SHOWED UP
FOR HIS FIRST BATH.
>> AUSTIN'S FIRST BATH.
>> I AM TIRED, BUT...
>> EVERYONE LEFT, AND I WAS
EXHAUSTED, BUT IT WAS TIME
TO LEARN HOW TO BREAST-FEED.
>> GOOD FIRST TIME.
I'M GONNA WATCH FOR THE LATCH.
THE LATCH IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING.
HIS MOUTH IS OPEN PRETTY WIDE.
DOES IT HURT?
>> NO.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S A GOOD SIGN.
THAT'S PERFECT.
THAT IS JUST PERFECT.
>> READY TO GO HOME,
LITTLE BUDDY?
[baby coos]
>> AND BEFORE WE KNEW IT, IT
WAS TIME TO TAKE OUR BABY HOME.
[sighs]
CAN YOU BELIEVE WE HAVE A BABY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WE HAD REALLY HOPED TO HAVE
OUR OWN PLACE BY NOW, BUT WE
JUST COULDN'T SAVE ENOUGH MONEY.
>> LITTLE BUDDY, YOU'RE HOME.
>> WANT TO SHOW HIM TO MEEMAW?
YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM?
>> ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OH, DEAR.
OH, OH, OH, OH, OH.
>> YOU LIKE MEEMAW.
>> HE DOESN'T LIKE ME.
>> NO, HE'S COLD,
AND HE'S HUNGRY.
>> HOW COME HIS LITTLE CHEEK
IS RED?
HE'S GOT...
>> IT'S JUST NEWBORN RASH.
YOU ALSO HAVE TO REMEMBER,
THOUGH, HE'S NOT CRYING
RIGHT NOW.
>> WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
JUST WAKING ME UP OR ANNOYING ME
OR ANYTHING.
>> HE DOESN'T CRY, THOUGH.
>> HE REALLY DOESN'T.
YEAH, HE WHIMPERS.
>> HONEY, ALL THAT COULD CHANGE.
I DON'T DO BABIES, DARLING.
>> [laughs]
>> I'M SCARED TO DEATH OF THEM.
>> I'M VERY GRATEFUL GRANDMA'S
STILL LETTING US LIVE WITH HER,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA
HAVE TO FIND OUR OWN PLACE FAST.
>> EVEN THOUGH GRANDMA WANTS US
TO GET OUR OWN PLACE,
SHE'S BEING PATIENT FOR
RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, MEEMAW.
SORRY I LEFT THAT IN THERE.
I GOT IT ALL TAKEN CARE OF.
BRANDON'S BEEN HELPING A LOT.
>> YOU'RE REALLY ALL RIGHT.
DON'T SCRATCH YOURSELF.
>> BUT AFTER TAKING FIVE DAYS
OFF, HE HAS TO GO BACK TO WORK.
I'M GLAD YOU DON'T WORK
A LONG SHIFT TODAY.
>> HEY, BABY BOY.
>> IT MAKES ME HAPPY,
AT LEAST, YOU KNOW?
>> ME TOO.
>> THE TIME WE DO HAVE TO SPEND
APART ISN'T VERY LONG.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO, HON.
>> I'LL SEE YOU WHEN YOU
GET HOME.
>> I CAN'T FIND THE CAR KEYS
ANYWHERE.
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO GET
THE EMERGENCY ONES?
>> WELL, DO YOU HAVE THEM?
>> YEAH.
GOD, DON'T LOSE THOSE,
WHATEVER YOU DO.
>> YEAH.
HONEY, WHEN YOU'RE CLEANING UP
THE ROOM, LOOK FOR THEM TODAY.
>> WHEN I'M CLEANING UP
THE ROOM?
I LIKE HOW YOU ASSUME I'M JUST
GONNA CLEAN THE ROOM.
BEING A MOM CAN BE PHYSICALLY
AND MENTALLY EXHAUSTING.
LITTLE BOY, HOW DID YOU JUST
DO THAT?
HE JUST PEED ALL OVER ME
AND HIM.
[baby crying]
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S FINE.
GONNA GIVE YOU A BOTTLE
IN A SECOND.
IT'S BEEN A MONTH SINCE I'VE
HAD AUSTIN, AND WITH BRANDON
BACK AT WORK, I'M GETTING
ALMOST NO SLEEP AND SPEND ALL MY
TIME TAKING CARE OF THE BABY...
>> [fussing]
>> WHICH LEAVES NO TIME TO
STUDY FOR MY G.E.D.
I COULD REALLY USE SOME HELP.
BRANDON, DO YOU WANT TO HEAT
SOME WATER UP REAL QUICK?
HE REALLY SHOULD--HE'S GONNA BE
STARVING HERE IN JUST A MINUTE,
AND HE HASN'T EATEN IN, LIKE,
THREE HOURS.
>> ABSOLUTELY, I'M GONNA EAT
SOME CHIPS TOO.
OH, WAIT, I WANT AN ICE CREAM.
SHOULD I GET CHIPS OR ICE CREAM?
>> I DON'T CARE.
JUST WORRY ABOUT YOUR SON
RIGHT NOW.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
[baby crying]
SERIOUSLY, PLEASE GET OUT.
PLEASE GET OUT.
NO, BRANDON, SERIOUSLY, NO.
>> WELL, LET ME TELL YOU,
YOU'RE DOING JUST FINE.
>> GREAT.
>> BOO-BOO.
>> NO.
IT'S NOT OKAY.
>> I'M NOT SAYING--
I'M SORRY.
>> YOU KNOW I'M EXHAUSTED.
YOU KNOW I'VE BEEN EMOTIONAL
ALL DAY TODAY, AND NOW YOU'RE
JUST MAKING IT WORSE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> BRANDON DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH.
AND TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE,
GRANDMA WANTS US OUT.
>> I WANT MY HOUSE BACK.
IT'S TIME, YOU KNOW?
BEFORE WE REALLY START GETTING
ON EACH OTHER'S NERVES.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I THINK WE'LL BE OUT OF YOUR
HOUSE BY SUMMER.
>> HOW MUCH MONEY HAVE YOU GUYS
PUT ASIDE FOR MOVING?
>> NOT AS MUCH AS WE'D LIKE TO.
>> YEAH, NOT AS MUCH AS WE'D
LIKE TO.
I HAVE 99 CENTS IN MY SAVINGS
ACCOUNT.
>> THIS SUMMER,
WE'LL WAVE ADIOS.
>> YEAH.
>> [laughs]
>> SUMMER IS ONLY TWO MONTHS
AWAY, AND IF WE'RE GOING TO GET
A PLACE OF OUR OWN, I'M GOING TO
HAVE TO CONVINCE BRANDON THAT
I NEED TO GET A JOB TOO.
SO WE HAVE 18 BUCKS TO LAST US
NINE DAYS, AND WE STILL HAVE
BILLS TO PAY.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT EVEN REALLY
REALISTIC TO FRICKING GET OUR
OWN PLACE UNTIL ALL OF OUR BILLS
ARE PAID OFF.
>> I CAN GET ANOTHER PART-TIME
JOB, 'CAUSE ANYTHING WOULD HELP,
YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, I WANTED TO GET
A PART-TIME JOB.
>> YOU COULD GET A PART-TIME JOB
MAKING MINIMUM WAGE.
I COULD GET A PART-TIME JOB
MAKING $10, $11 AN HOUR.
>> WHY DO YOU ONLY GET TO BE
OUT OF THE HOUSE?
>> IT'S ABOUT FREAKING
SURVIVING.
I COULD CARE LESS IF YOU
NEVER LEAVE THE HOUSE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
IT'S ABOUT MAKING ENDS MEET.
>> I'M GLAD YOU COULD CARE LESS
IF I NEVER LEAVE THE HOUSE.
I WANT TO CONTRIBUTE, YOU KNOW?
IT'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
>> I KNOW, HON, IT'S JUST,
TO ME, THE MOST PRACTICAL--
YOU ARE CONTRIBUTING.
THE MOST PRACTICAL WAY YOU'RE
CONTRIBUTING IS BY HELPING--
BEING WITH AUSTIN WHILE
I'M AT WORK.
>> BUT YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M NEVER GONNA BE ABLE TO
HAVE A CAREER IF I DON'T START
GETTING JOB EXPERIENCE.
IF WE'RE GONNA MAKE THIS FAMILY
WORK, THEN WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
DO IT AS A TEAM.
>> YOU WANT TO GO TO BED?
BRANDON AND I STILL DON'T AGREE
ON HOW WE'RE GOING TO COME UP
WITH THE MONEY TO MOVE OUT,
AND NOW HE'S COME UP WITH HIS
OWN IDEA FOR MAKING EXTRA MONEY.
>> THIS IS A COMPLETE KIT
OF EVERYTHING YOU NEED
TO GET STARTED IN PROSPECTING.
IT'S A PROFITABLE VENTURE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> IF YOU GO OUT THERE AND FIND
1/2 OUNCE OF GOLD, THAT'S $600.
THIS WILL MAKE YOU MONEY.
SALE.
WELL, I APPRECIATE IT.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I'M NOT CONVINCED THAT
BRANDON'S IDEA TO GET EXTRA
MONEY IS SOLID, SO I'M COMING UP
WITH MY OWN PLAN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE A FULL-TIME
STAY-AT-HOME MOM, SO I APPLIED
FOR A JOB ONLINE, AND WHILE
BRANDON'S AT WORK, MY MOM'S
AGREED TO WATCH AUSTIN DURING
MY INTERVIEW.
MAKE SURE TO BURP HIM AFTER
EVERY SINGLE FEEDING JUST UNTIL
HE WILL BURP.
>> AUBREY, I THINK YOUR MOM
CAN HANDLE IT, SWEETIE.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S MY VERY FIRST
TIME LEAVING HIM.
>> BUT HE'S GONNA BE FINE.
>> I'M HERE FOR AN INTERVIEW
WITH DANIELLE.
>> HI, I'M DANIELLE.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> AUBREY.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> PLEASE HAVE A SEAT
RIGHT OVER HERE.
SO WHAT QUALITIES DO YOU POSSESS
THAT WOULD MAKE YOU A REALLY
GOOD EMPLOYEE?
>> I KNOW THIS IS GONNA SOUND
CORNY, BUT I'M A GENUINE PERSON.
I REALLY--I REALLY ENJOY
WORKING WITH PEOPLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
HOW WOULD YOU HANDLE, LIKE,
IF A CUSTOMER GOT UPSET?
I'M CALLING YOU RIGHT NOW.
RING-RING.
>> UH-HUH.
>> HI.
I JUST GOT MY PIZZA.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE SAUSAGE,
AND IT'S PEPPERONI.
>> OKAY, UM...
>> OKAY.
>> SORRY.
I'VE NEVER ANSWERED PHONE CALLS
BEFORE.
I'VE NEVER HAD THAT SITUATION
HAPPEN.
>> OKAY.
>> SORRY ABOUT THAT.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
>> I'M REALLY GOOD WITH PEOPLE,
AND I, YOU KNOW, I JUST THINK
THAT I COULD DEFINITELY DO WELL.
I WOULD LOOK FORWARD TO COMING
TO WORK EVERY DAY.
[laughter]
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING IN.
>> YES, THANK YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
I'LL BE IN TOUCH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M NOT SURE IF I'LL GET
THE JOB, BUT IT FELT GOOD
TAKING MATTERS INTO MY OWN
HANDS, AND AFTER PICKING UP
AUSTIN, I WENT TO HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS.
HI.
>> HI.
OOH.
HE IS SO CUTE.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA SET HIM DOWN
ON THE TABLE.
HE'S HEAVY.
>> HE'S GETTING SO BIG.
>> I KNOW.
>> HOW'S SCHOOL GOING FOR YOU?
>> WELL, IT'S DEFINITELY, LIKE,
SINCE HE'S BEEN HOME, IT'S BEEN
HARDER TO STUDY FOR MY G.E.D.
FOR SURE.
BUT I HAD MY JOB INTERVIEW
TODAY.
>> SO ARE YOU GONNA TELL BRANDON
ABOUT IT, SEEING AS HOW HE HAS
NO IDEA YET?
>> I--YES, I AM.
ME AND BRANDON NEVER TALKED
ABOUT, LIKE, DAY CARE AND, LIKE,
WORK AND, LIKE, HOW THAT WOULD
ALL WORK, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, I WANT TO BE ABLE TO
SAY THAT I CONTRIBUTED.
[chime dings]
ON MY WAY HOME TO TALK TO
BRANDON, THE PIZZA PLACE CALLED,
AND I GOT THE JOB.
UM, SO I APPLIED FOR A JOB
ONLINE, AND I WENT TO
MY INTERVIEW.
>> WHAT KIND OF JOB WAS IT?
>> FOR A PIZZERIA POSITION.
>> MM.
>> AND SO I GOT THE JOB.
>> HMM.
>> YEAH.
I THINK IT'S DEFINITELY A STEP
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION FOR US
GETTING OUT OF MEEMAW'S HOUSE
AND MOVING IN TO OUR OWN PLACE,
AND, YOU KNOW, THE MORE MONEY
WE CAN SAVE, THE BETTER.
>> YEAH, INITIALLY, I DON'T
KNOW, I WASN'T REALLY UP FOR
THE IDEA OF BOTH OF US WORKING,
'CAUSE I FIGURED ONE OF US
WOULD HAVE TO BE HOME WITH
THE BABY ALL THE TIME, AND IF
WE CAN WORK IT AROUND, YOU KNOW,
MY WORK SCHEDULE AND YOUR WORK
SCHEDULE, IF WE CAN WORK IT
AROUND RIGHT, WHERE WE DON'T
HAVE TO PUT THE BABY IN DAY CARE
ALL THE TIME, THEN THAT
WOULD BE GOOD.
>> I'M GLAD BRANDON IS BEING
OPEN-MINDED ABOUT ME GETTING
A JOB.
>> AND SINCE WE CAN'T AFFORD
DAY CARE, HE WATCHES THE BABY
WHILE I GO TO WORK.
I'LL GET BETTER AT IT.
MY JOB MAY NOT BE ROCKET
SCIENCE, BUT I'M HAPPY I CAN
CONTRIBUTE TO OUR FAMILY.
THERE'S MY BABIES.
HI, HONEYS.
>> HOW WAS WORK?
>> IT WAS GOOD.
BRANDON AND I BOTH HAVE THE DAY
OFF, BUT WE'RE SPENDING IT
TRYING TO MAKE SOME EXTRA MONEY
GOLD PANNING.
I DON'T THINK YOU GOT ME
ANY DIRT AT ALL.
IT'S ALL ROCKS.
DO YOU THINK THAT AUSTIN BEING
HERE HAS MESSED WITH OUR
RELATIONSHIP A LITTLE BIT?
>> YEAH.
OBVIOUSLY, IT'S CHANGED IT.
THE DYNAMICS HAVE CHANGED
OF OUR RELATIONSHIP, BUT...
>> IT'LL BE NICE WHEN WE DON'T
HAVE TO RELY ON EVERYBODY FOR
EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> I DEFINITELY THOUGHT WE'D BE
OUT OF MEEMAW'S HOUSE BY NOW.
>> YEAH, WE'RE TRYING.
SHE KNOWS THAT, YOU KNOW?
>> EXACTLY.
>> I'M PRETTY PSYCHED THAT
YOU GOT A JOB.
>> YEAH?
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE, AT FIRST,
I WAS WORRIED BECAUSE I DIDN'T
KNOW WHO WAS GONNA WATCH
THE BABY, BUT SINCE YOU GOT
A WORK THAT'S REALLY FLEXIBLE
WITH MY WORK SCHEDULE, IT REALLY
MAKES ME HAPPY, AND IT, LIKE...
>> SO YOU'RE ALL RIGHT WITH IT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> GOOD.
HOW MUCH DO YOU GET FOR
AN OUNCE?
>> RIGHT NOW, IT'S $1,100.
>> OKAY, SO WE JUST NEED TO
FIND SOME BIG PIECES OF GOLD.
WHEN I FIRST GOT PREGNANT,
I DEFINITELY DON'T THINK
WE WERE READY.
SOMETIMES I JUST LOOK AT HIM
AND I JUST THINK, LIKE,
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID THIS.
IT'S SO INSANE.
IT'S SO CRAZY.
HI, HONEY.
OOH.
HEY.
WAY TO PEE IN THE BATH.
THAT WASN'T COOL.
I THINK FROM WHEN ME AND BRANDON
FIRST GOT PREGNANT, OUR
RELATIONSHIP HAS STRENGTHENED
A LOT.
BRANDON HAS REALLY LIGHTENED UP
ON THE IDEA OF ME HAVING A JOB.
HE REALIZES THAT I NEED TIME
AWAY FROM THE HOUSE.
HOW'S SCHOOL GOING?
>> IT'S GOING GOOD.
>> I REALLY WISH THAT I HAD
GOTTEN MY G.E.D. BEFORE I HAD
AUSTIN.
I'VE BEEN WORKING HARD,
AND I'LL GET MY G.E.D.
'CAUSE IT IS IMPORTANT TO ME.
I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE
AND HAVE A CAREER, BECAUSE
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO OFFER
EVERYTHING TO HIM.
HERE, LET'S GET THESE LITTLE
KNEES UP.
I THOUGHT WE WOULD HAVE MONEY
IN SAVINGS BY NOW.
I DO WISH THAT WE WERE
DOING BETTER.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> I RESENT YOU 'CAUSE I'M
PREGNANT, AND I DON'T WANT
TO BE.
>> YOU HAD A SCHOLARSHIP
TO COLLEGE.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO BE HERE.
AND NOT ONLY ARE YOU HERE;
YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING WITH YOU.
>> [crying]
EVERYBODY HAS A PURPOSE IN LIFE.
I DIDN'T THINK MY PURPOSE
WAS TO TAKE CARE OF A BABY.
>> IF I JUST WALK AWAY,
WHAT WAS THE PURPOSE
OF STAYING HERE, THEN?
>> THERE'S NO POSSIBLE WAY
IT COULD BE ANYBODY ELSE'S BABY.
>> I FEEL WE SHOULD HAVE
A DNA TEST.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> GRANNY KNOWS THINGS.
GRANNY KNOWS.