>> [laughs]
HI, I'M HOPE.
I'M 17 YEARS OLD, AND I'M FROM
LEE'S SUMMIT, MISSOURI,
JUST OUTSIDE OF KANSAS CITY.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED, AND I
LIVE WITH MY MOM AND MY LITTLE
BROTHER AND SISTER.
I PICKED UP THE WRONG CARD.
>> YOU SHOULD PICK UP A TWO.
>> I JUST GRADUATED FROM HIGH
SCHOOL, AND I'M EXCITED TO GO TO
COLLEGE.
WHEN I'M NOT WORKING PART-TIME
IN A LOCAL COFFEE SHOP...
OH, MAN.
I'M USUALLY OUT HAVING FUN
WITH MY FRIENDS.
I MET BEN A YEAR AGO,
AND WE'VE STARTED HANGING OUT.
UH-OH.
>> I THINK YOU'RE BUYING
ICE CREAM.
>> I THINK I'M BUYING ICE CREAM
TOO.
I REALLY LIKED HIM A LOT,
BUT BEN WAS A PARTY BOY
AND WASN'T LOOKING FOR
A RELATIONSHIP, SO IT WAS NO
SURPRISE THAT AFTER WE HOOKED UP
A FEW TIMES, HE TOTALLY
BLEW ME OFF.
MY FRIENDS WARNED ME THAT BEN
WASN'T SERIOUS ABOUT ME.
>> I WORRY.
I KNOW YOU NEED, LIKE, A LOT
FROM HIM.
>> I WAS TOTALLY READY TO GIVE
UP ON HIM, BUT THEN I HAD TO
CALL AND TELL HIM
I'M PREGNANT.
WHEN BEN FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, HE SAID HE DIDN'T
WANT ANYTHING TO DO WITH ME
OR THE BABY.
LUCKILY I HAD THE SUPPORT OF
MY MOM, ALTHOUGH SHE'S HAD
A HARD TIME ACCEPTING
THAT I GOT PREGNANT.
>> YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT A SHOCK
THAT WAS FOR YOU TO NEVER HAVE
HAD A BOYFRIEND, AND THEN ALL OF
A SUDDEN, FIRST PERSON YOU'VE
HAD SEX WITH, YOU GET PREGNANT.
HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
>> LIKE, I MET BEN A YEAR AGO,
WHENEVER I WAS WORKING AT THAT
RESTAURANT.
EVERYBODY WOULD GO OUT AND PARTY
TOGETHER, AND WE JUST STARTED
HANGING OUT.
THE IDEA OF SEX CAME UP, AND I
FIGURED I WAS READY.
>> DID HE KNOW THAT THAT WAS
YOUR FIRST TIME?
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE A CONDOM.
HE'S LIKE, "I'LL JUST PULL OUT."
AND I WAS LIKE,
"OKAY, THAT'LL WORK."
THEN WE HAD SEX A COUPLE TIMES,
AND THEN I WAS PREGNANT.
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE LIKE,
"WELL, YOU COULD GIVE IT UP
FOR ADOPTION."
LIKE, I THINK THAT'D BE HARD TO,
LIKE, TO SEE IT, FEEL IT KICK,
AND THEN JUST, LIKE, GIVE IT
AWAY.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> AND TALKING TO ME WAS NOT
IN YOUR MIND-SET.
>> NO, 'CAUSE I KNEW YOU'D BE
DISAPPOINTED, SO I DIDN'T WANT
TO TELL YOU.
ALL MY FRIENDS WERE LIKE,
"COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT TONIGHT."
AND I'D BE LIKE, "OKAY, I'M
GONNA DO IT."
I WANT THE LOVE AND SUPPORT AND,
LIKE, TO KNOW IT'S GONNA BE
OKAY, SO I WAS LIKE, "MAYBE I'LL
JUST GO UP IN YOUR ROOM."
AND I DID.
AND IT MADE THINGS BETTER,
THOUGH.
IT MADE IT SEEM NOT AS HARD,
'CAUSE I FELT LIKE I WAS ALONE.
IT MEANS A LOT TO ME THAT MY MOM
IS BY MY SIDE, BUT WHO I REALLY
WANT IS BEN.
AFTER IGNORING ME FOR TWO
MONTHS, HE FINALLY CALLED ME
BACK AND SAID HE'S HAD A CHANGE
OF HEART.
HE WANTS TO BE A PART OF OUR
BABY'S LIFE AND WANTS US TO
START DATING.
HE'S EVEN FOUND A NEW APARTMENT
AND WANTS ME TO MOVE IN WITH HIM
BEFORE THE BABY IS BORN.
EVEN THOUGH HE LIVES AN HOUR
AWAY AND OUR RELATIONSHIP IS
STILL NEW, I THINK LIVING
TOGETHER IS WHAT'S BEST FOR
OUR BABY.
BUT I'M WORRIED ABOUT BEING
SO FAR AWAY FROM MY MOM
AND MY FRIENDS.
>> I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> I KNOW.
>> SHE KNEW WHEN SHE WAS
PREGNANT.
SHE KNEW AUTOMATICALLY, BECAUSE,
LIKE, THE NEXT, LIKE--MAYBE TWO
DAYS LATER, SHE WAS LIKE,
"I THINK I'M PREGNANT."
I WAS LIKE, "WHAT?"
>> LIKE, I TEXTED BEN.
I WAS LIKE, "IT'S FOR REAL.
LIKE, I'M NOT KIDDING.
I'M NOT TRYING TO GET BACK
WITH YOU."
I WAS LIKE, "JUST, LIKE,
RESPOND TO ME.
LIKE, STOP IGNORING ME."
>> I GOT FED UP WITH IT,
WITH YOU BEING UPSET SO MUCH,
SO I STARTED TEXTING BEN,
AND I, LIKE, TOLD HIM HE WAS
A PIECE OF [bleep] AND STUFF,
BECAUSE--AND HE WAS GONNA BE,
LIKE, THIS DEADBEAT DAD
AND ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT HIM.
>> SO I'D TEXT HIM EVERY
SINGLE DAY.
I WAS JUST LIKE, "I JUST WANT
YOU TO TELL ME, LIKE,
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE OKAY."
>> DO YOU THINK BEN IS GONNA BE
A GOOD DAD?
>> I THINK HE'S GONNA BE
A GOOD DAD.
I JUST--HE'S NOT A GOOD
BOYFRIEND.
>> HAVE YOUR PARENTS, LIKE,
EVER MET BEN YET?
>> NOPE--
>> NOT AT ALL?
>> NO, THEY HAVEN'T MET HIM.
I NEVER BROUGHT HIM AROUND,
JUST BECAUSE, LIKE, I DIDN'T
THINK IT WAS SERIOUS, YOU KNOW?
I GUESS, LIKE, THEY SHOULD MEET
SOMETIME SOON, BUT I'D RATHER
WAIT AS LONG AS POSSIBLE, 'CAUSE
IT'S GONNA BE REALLY AWKWARD.
LIKE, I'M JUST SCARED, LIKE,
HE'S NOT GONNA BE THERE 100%.
>> I'M KIND OF DOUBTING THAT
HE'S GONNA BE THERE, LIKE,
THE WHOLE TIME.
>> I'M GLAD MY FRIENDS HAVE MY
BACK, 'CAUSE I'M REALLY WORRIED
HOW THINGS WILL BE LIVING AT
BEN'S.
AND SINCE WE JUST STARTED TO
WORK THINGS OUT, BEN'S ONLY
COMFORTABLE COMING AROUND WHEN
NOBODY'S HOME.
[doorbell rings]
>> HEY.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> NOT MUCH.
EVERYBODY'S IN ST. LOUIS,
SO NOBODY'S HERE.
SO I'M MOVING IN BEFORE THE
BABY'S BORN OR AFTER?
>> WELL, YOU'RE STAYING THERE
AND EVERYTHING, BUT WE'RE NOT
MOVING ANYTHING BUT THE BABY'S
STUFF INTO MY NEW APARTMENT,
'CAUSE THERE'S NO ROOM.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
YOU CAN STAY THERE EVERY NIGHT
IF YOU WANT TO AND LIVE THERE
OR SAY WHATEVER YOU WANT TO SAY,
BUT WE CAN'T MOVE ALL THE BIG
STUFF, IS WHAT I'M SAYING,
UNTIL AFTER THE BABY IS BORN.
>> LIKE, I UNDERSTAND, LIKE,
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF ROOM,
WHICH I'M FINE WITH.
>> WELL, YOU'RE STILL GONNA BE
STAYING THERE.
>> ARE YOU SCARED TO MEET MY
PARENTS?
>> OF COURSE.
I JUST DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
GONNA HATE ME, 'CAUSE--
I DON'T KNOW--I WAS GONE FOR
THE FIRST MONTH OR SO
AND EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
WE ONLY HAD SEX, LIKE, THREE
OR FOUR TIMES BEFORE YOU GOT
PREGNANT, MAYBE FIVE,
BUT I IGNORED YOU AFTER THAT.
>> WHY?
I DID NOTHING WRONG.
>> I PARTIALLY FREAKED OUT
'CAUSE YOU WERE A VIRGIN,
AND I DIDN'T--I KNEW THAT YOU
WERE GONNA WANT A LONG-TERM
RELATIONSHIP, AND THAT WASN'T
WHAT I WAS LOOKING FOR AT THAT
TIME, YOU KNOW?
>> SO WHAT FINALLY MADE YOU--
>> CHANGE MY MIND?
>> YEAH, WHY'D YOU TEXT ME BACK
THAT ONE TIME?
>> THAT'S MY KID, AND I'M GONNA
HAVE TO OWN UP TO WHAT I DID.
I'VE SPENT A LOT OF TIME
IN MY LIFE RUNNING AWAY FROM
THINGS I SHOULD BE TAKING
RESPONSIBILITY FOR.
I'M TRYING NOT TO DO THAT FOR
ONCE.
>> I'M SIX MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND I HAVE A BUSY SUMMER AHEAD.
I'M WORKING FOUR SHIFTS A WEEK
TO SAVE MONEY FOR THE BABY.
THE REST OF THE TIME, I'M TRYING
TO HANG OUT WITH MY FRIENDS
BEFORE THEY GO TO COLLEGE.
>> WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE BEEN
DOING FOR COLLEGE IF YOU
WOULDN'T BE HAVING THE BABY?
>> HONESTLY, I WANTED TO GO TO
ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY, BUT IT
WASN'T FOR A VERY GOOD REASON.
>> WHAT WAS THE REASON?
>> IT'S THE NUMBER ONE PARTY
COLLEGE IN AMERICA.
>> OH, MY GOD.
SO HOW DO YOU FEEL, THE THOUGHT
OF YOUR PARTY DAYS BEING
OVER NOW?
>> ALL MY FRIENDS, LIKE,
FRIDAY AND SATURDAY NIGHT,
ALWAYS GO OUT AND PARTY.
>> I DON'T.
YOU CAN COME HANG WITH ME.
>> YEAH, NOBODY HANGS OUT WITH
ME ANYMORE 'CAUSE--I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THEY'D RATHER
GO PARTY.
'CAUSE I KNOW, LIKE, IF I WASN'T
PREGNANT, LIKE, I'D BE DOING THE
SAME THING.
>> YEAH.
SO HOW ARE THINGS GOING
WITH BEN?
>> PRETTY GOOD.
MONDAY NIGHT, THOUGH, LIKE,
WE WERE SITTING THERE, LIKE,
YOU KNOW, JUST, LIKE, TALKING,
AND HE WAS LIKE, "YEAH,
AT FIRST, I STARTED TALKING TO
YOU ONLY BECAUSE OF THE BABY."
AND I WAS LIKE, "OKAY, WELL"--
>> WHAT ABOUT NOW?
>> YEAH, SO, LIKE, NOW I FEEL
LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
STILL TALKING TO ME ONLY BECAUSE
OF THE BABY, OR IF IT HAS
ACTUALLY CHANGED."
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE IT'S JUST
THE WAY MY MIND THINKS.
>> MINE WOULD TOO.
HAVE YOU ASKED HIM THAT YET?
>> NO, I DON'T WANT TO, LIKE,
START A FIGHT OVER NOTHING.
>> I MEAN, IT'S NOT REALLY--
ALL YOU'RE DOING IS ASKING
A QUESTION.
IT'S NOT REALLY OVER NOTHING.
LIKE, YOU WANT TO KNOW
HOW HE FEELS ABOUT YOU.
>> HEY, BREAKFAST IS READY.
>> I TOLD MY MOM I'M PLANNING ON
MOVING IN WITH BEN, AND SHE WAS
SURPRISED, BECAUSE SHE HASN'T
EVEN MET HIM YET.
>> WHEN CAN WE MEET BEN?
'CAUSE I'VE GOT A MILLION
QUESTIONS FOR HIM.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> I'M JUST REALLY WORRIED THAT
HE'S GONNA TAKE OFF AGAIN, AND
YOU'RE GONNA GET HURT.
I DON'T KNOW--MOM STUFF.
>> IT'LL BE SO AWKWARD.
>> NOW, YOU KNOW I'M HERE FOR
YOU, BUT THINGS HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
SO TIGHT FOR ME FINANCIALLY
THAT I WON'T BE ABLE TO HELP.
ARE YOU EXPECTING ME TO HELP?
>> I THINK WE'LL BE FINE.
>> IF YOU'RE MOVING IN TOGETHER,
THEN YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE STRONG
FEELINGS FOR HIM.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
ARE YOU AFRAID OF GETTING HURT?
>> I MEAN, THERE'S ALWAYS
A LITTLE FEAR JUST BECAUSE I WAS
ABANDONED AT FIRST, YOU KNOW?
>> I'M KIND OF CONCERNED THAT
HE'LL TAKE OFF AGAIN AFTER THE
BABY'S BORN.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHY MY MOM HAS
DOUBTS ABOUT BEN, BECAUSE I FEEL
THE SAME WAY.
SINCE MY MOM CAN'T HELP PAY
FOR THE BABY, I'M TRYING TO
KEEP MY JOB UNTIL MY DUE DATE.
WE HAVE AN AMERICANO WITH
VANILLA.
BUT WORK HAS BEEN REALLY HARD
RECENTLY BECAUSE MY FEET GET
SWOLLEN FROM STANDING ALL DAY.
I'M GOING FOR A CHECKUP
AFTER WORK AND HOPE MY DOCTOR
CAN HELP ME WITH THE SWELLING.
SINCE BEN HASN'T MET MY MOM YET,
HE DOESN'T COME TO MY
APPOINTMENTS.
MY TOES ARE SWOLLEN.
IT'S SO SAD TO SEE LITTLE FAT
TOES.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> HELLO, THERE.
>> HI, I'M HOPE'S MOM.
>> YEAH, I DO GOT A QUESTION,
THOUGH.
MY FEET AND ANKLES AND, LIKE,
LEGS ARE SWELLING REALLY BAD.
I GOT A NEW JOB.
THEY HAVE ME, LIKE, WORKING
NINE-HOUR SHIFTS, AND, LIKE,
MY ANKLES WILL SERIOUSLY GET,
LIKE, DOUBLE THIS SIZE.
IT, LIKE, IS PAINFUL.
>> I'M GONNA NEED IT PRETTY BAD.
LIKE, MY MOM CAN'T HELP US
FINANCIALLY, SO...
>> YEAH.
>> HOW MUCH HAVE I GAINED
SO FAR?
>> THANK YOU.
>> OKAY, NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T
PHYSICALLY WORK, THEN HOW ARE
YOU GONNA KEEP THIS JOB?
>> I DON'T WANT TO QUIT, THOUGH.
LIKE, I WANT TO--DOES THAT MAKE
SENSE?
'CAUSE THEN--YEAH, WHAT AM I
GONNA DO AFTER?
I'M NOT GONNA HAVE A JOB.
>> I KNOW, BUT HOW DO YOU NOT
QUIT IF YOU CAN'T WORK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
[chime dings]
I WAS HOPING I COULD GET MORE
BREAKS BUT WAS TOLD IT WAS
AGAINST COMPANY POLICY.
SO EVEN THOUGH I NEED THE MONEY,
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO QUIT.
BEN WORKS FULL-TIME AS
A BARTENDER, SO I HOPE I CAN
RELY ON HIM FOR SUPPORT.
TODAY I'M BRINGING SOME
ULTRASOUND PHOTOS OVER TO BEN'S.
WE'RE HAVING A BOY AND DECIDED
TO NAME HIM TRISTAN.
>> DO YOU SEE THOSE LINES RIGHT
NEXT TO HIS FACE?
THAT'S THE UMBILICAL CORD.
>> I CAN TELL HE'S REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT THE BABY.
I JUST NEED TO KNOW HOW HE FEELS
ABOUT ME.
SO I QUIT MY JOB.
>> YEAH, I DON'T THINK YOU
SHOULD BE WORKING THAT LONG
WITHOUT A BREAK.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NOT DEPENDING ON YOU FOR MY
RENT OR THE LIGHT BILL OR THE
FOOD OR ANYTHING.
>> DO YOU THINK WE'RE IN A GOOD
PLACE IN OUR RELATIONSHIP?
>> ARE YOU NOT HAPPY WITH WHERE
IT'S AT, OR...
>> NO, I'M HAPPY.
JUST, LIKE, DO YOU THINK THAT
WE'VE, LIKE, GOTTEN BETTER SINCE
THE BEGINNING?
>> THERE WASN'T REALLY A
RELATIONSHIP IN THE BEGINNING,
AND THEN AFTER YOU GOT PREGNANT,
YEAH.
WE STARTED WORKING ON OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
IT'S GOTTEN 100 TIMES BETTER.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO BE WITH YOU.
YOU ALREADY KNOW THIS.
>> YEAH.
>> ARE YOU HAPPY THAT YOU'RE
ACTUALLY TIED DOWN NOW?
I KNOW BEFORE, YOU NEVER WANTED
TO BE.
>> YEAH, I'M GLAD, 'CAUSE--
I DON'T KNOW.
I ALWAYS WANTED TO FIND SOMEONE
TO BE WITH, BUT--I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS JUST THE WHOLE PARTY,
"LOOKING COOL IN FRONT OF MY
FRIENDS" THING.
>> BUT YOU ACTUALLY WANT TO BE
WITH ME NOW?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SO IT'S NOT JUST 'CAUSE THE
BABY THEN?
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> PROMISE?
>> IF IT WAS JUST 'CAUSE THE
BABY, I WOULDN'T LET YOU
MOVE IN.
I WOULDN'T, LIKE--WE'D BE
WORKING THIS OUT A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT WAY, YOU KNOW?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT A DAY
THAT YOU'RE GONNA BE MOVING IN?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE SHOULD DO AUGUST 1ST.
>> AUGUST 1ST IS ONLY A COUPLE
WEEKS AWAY.
>> I'VE BEEN HAVING LOTS OF
DOUBTS, BUT I'M STARTING TO
BELIEVE THAT BEN REALLY WANTS TO
BE WITH ME.
>> I'M SEVEN MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND SINCE I'M GOING TO BE MOVING
IN WITH BEN SOON, TODAY HE'S
COMING OVER TO MEET MY MOM.
EVERYBODY'S IN THE KITCHEN.
>> I'M BETSY.
>> I'M BEN.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> DON.
>> CHANCE.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, CHANCE.
>> AS A MOM, MY CONCERN IS THAT
YOU'RE EITHER GONNA--THAT YOU'RE
GONNA BREAK HER HEART.
>> I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN IN THE FUTURE ABOUT US
BEING TOGETHER, BUT, I MEAN,
I KNOW I CAN DO MY BEST, SO...
AND I KNOW I'M NOT GONNA LEAVE
MY KID, SO...
>> YOUR PLANS ARE TO MOVE IN
TOGETHER?
WHEN?
AFTER THE BABY OR BEFORE THE
BABY?
>> A MONTH BEFORE THE BABY.
>> IF SHE'S NOT WORKING, THEN
WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO HELP OUT
WITH CAR INSURANCE AND STUFF
LIKE THAT, TO PAY FOR HER?
>> YEAH, SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO PAY
FOR THE FOOD OR RENT AND STUFF
THERE.
I'LL BE TAKING CARE OF IT.
THE MOVING IN--
I THINK IT'S A GOOD DECISION,
BUT SHE CAN STAY HERE--
>> YOU THINK IT'S A GOOD
DECISION?
>> I WANT TO BE THERE TO GET UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND HELP AND STUFF,
SO--I DON'T KNOW.
>> WELL, IT WARMS MY HEART
A LITTLE BIT TO HEAR YOU SAY
THAT--THAT YOU WANT TO BE THERE
AT NIGHT AND HELP HER TOO.
LET'S GO ON IN.
HOW MUCH DID YOU WEIGH WHEN
YOU WERE BORN?
>> I WAS 8 POUNDS, 1 OUNCE.
>> THAT'S WHAT SHE WAS.
>> THAT'S FUNNY.
>> THE WEEKS ARE FLYING BY,
AND IT'S TIME TO START PACKING.
BEN DOESN'T WANT ME TO BRING
TOO MUCH STUFF BECAUSE HIS PLACE
IS SMALL, AND WE STILL HAVE TO
GET READY FOR THE BABY.
SO I'M TRYING TO PACK
ONLY THE ESSENTIALS.
>> NO.
[laughs]
WHILE I'M GETTING READY TO MOVE
IN WITH BEN AND BECOME A MOM,
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE GETTING READY
TO MOVE ON TO COLLEGE.
>> CAN WE GET TWO PEDICURES?
>> OH, WAIT, WHAT ABOUT THAT
ONE?
LET'S DO IT.
>> HAVE A SEAT HERE.
>> IS IT FUN GOING, LIKE,
DORM SHOPPING?
>> IT'S REALLY FUN.
>> LIKE, EVERY STORE YOU GO TO,
IT'S DORM, LIKE, SALES.
>> YEAH, "BACK TO SCHOOL."
>> AND I'M LIKE, "REALLY?
REALLY?"
I FEEL LIKE IT'S GETTING RUBBED
IN MY FACE.
>> OH.
>> IT WOULD'VE BEEN FUN,
US GOING TO COLLEGE TOGETHER.
>> I WISH YOU COULD COME
WITH ME.
>> I'M JEALOUS THAT, LIKE, YOU
ACTUALLY GET TO, LIKE, GO LIVE
AT THE COLLEGE, LIKE, HAVE THE
COLLEGE LIFE, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, IF I GO, I'M JUST GONNA
BE, LIKE, A MOM GOING TO
COLLEGE.
BUT, LIKE, THE THING I'M MOST
WORRIED ABOUT NOW IS, LIKE,
I COULD GO TO SCHOOL,
OR I COULD GET A JOB.
WHAT DO YOU PICK?
>> I WOULD RATHER HAVE THAT
SAFETY BLANKET.
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE JOB--GETTING DECENT
JOBS WITHOUT COLLEGE DEGREES IS
JUST--I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS THESE DAYS,
THEY'RE HARDER TO COME BY.
>> LIKE, I UNDERSTAND THAT,
BUT THEN, LIKE, IT MAKES IT
TEN TIMES HARDER ON US NOW.
THEN BEN HAS TO, LIKE, LITERALLY
PAY FOR EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, IT SUCKS NOW, NOT HAVING
A JOB.
LIKE, I JUST DON'T WANT TO
RELY ON PEOPLE.
I KNOW THAT SCHOOL IS IMPORTANT,
BUT WITH NO MONEY AND A BABY ON
THE WAY, I DON'T HAVE TOO MANY
OPTIONS RIGHT NOW.
WHEN I GOT HOME, MY MOM
WANTED TO TALK ABOUT MY PLAN
TO MOVE AN HOUR AWAY.
>> I'M SAD THAT YOU'RE GONNA BE
MOVING OUT, JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE
MY BABY.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE NEVER
GONNA TALK TO EACH OTHER AGAIN.
>> I KNOW.
THE ONLY CONCERN I HAVE IS,
YOU'RE GONNA BE UP THERE WITH
A BRAND-NEW BABY.
WHEN I MET BEN, HE SAID ALL THE
RIGHT THINGS, BUT IS HE SAYING
ALL THE RIGHT THINGS BECAUSE
HE'S MEETING YOUR MOTHER?
I HOPE HE LOVES YOU.
THAT'S MY ONLY WORRY AND FEAR,
IS THAT YOU'RE GONNA GET
YOUR HEART BROKEN,
AND I WANT YOUR GUARD TO BE UP
AND EXPECT NOTHING.
>> I ALWAYS EXPECT THE WORST.
>> I WANT YOU TO EXPECT NOTHING
FROM THIS MAN, BECAUSE MEN SUCK.
>> I THINK HE LOVES ME.
>> IF SOMETHING BAD HAPPENS
TO YOU--
>> ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
>> I AM GONNA BE HERE, PICKING
UP THE PIECES AND HELPING YOU
DEAL WITH IT, AND I HOPE THAT
THINGS WORK OUT.
I REALLY DO.
I DON'T WANT TO SABOTAGE
YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM
OR ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> GIVE ME A HUG.
DON'T CRY.
>> OH, MY BABY.
>> TRISTAN IS DUE IN A MONTH,
AND I'M MOVING INTO BEN'S TODAY.
THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING WELL
BETWEEN US, AND I'M EXCITED.
>> YEAH, WE DEFINITELY HAVE TO
PUT THE BED THERE TO COVER UP
ALL THOSE SPOTS.
>> BUT MY MOM DOESN'T SEEM
TOO IMPRESSED.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE PLACE?
>> IT'S YUCKY.
THAT WHOLE ENTRYWAY,
I SAW BUGS--DEAD BUGS.
IF I WAS IN YOUR SITUATION AND
I HAD TO LIVE HERE, I THINK
I WOULD GO SWEEP THAT.
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT
SWEEPING THAT.
THAT'S JUST EXTRA TIME AND--
>> IT'S DISGUSTING.
I'M KIND OF NUMB RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> I'LL PROBABLY SIT IN YOUR
ROOM AND CRY TONIGHT.
>> DON'T DO THAT.
>> BEING A SINGLE MOM FOR A LONG
TIME, I RELIED ON YOU A LOT.
>> GIVE ME A HUG.
DON'T CRY.
>> IF YOU HUG ME, I'M GONNA CRY.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> THANK YOU GUYS FOR
HELPING US.
>> BYE, BEN.
TAKE CARE OF HER,
OR I'LL KILL YOU.
[laughs]
>> TAKE CARE, MAN.
>> SEE YOU, MAN.
>> BEN AND I HAVE BEEN BUSY
GETTING EVERYTHING READY FOR
THE BABY.
>> WANT TO HOP IN?
>> YES.
WE COULD DO GREEN.
GREEN'S IN THE ROOM.
>> IT'S UP TO YOU, BABY.
>> THAT'S THE BUMBO.
AND THEN WE COULD SET HIM ON,
LIKE, THE COUNTER OR SOMETHING.
>> THAT IS COOL.
>> MY DUE DATE IS TWO WEEKS
AWAY, AND I'M REALLY
UNCOMFORTABLE.
MY FRIENDS DROVE UP TO TAKE ME
TO THE LAKE, BUT I'M SO BIG
THAT IT'S THE LAST PLACE
I WANT TO BE.
>> LOOK HOW BIG YOUR TUMMY IS.
THAT HAS TO WEIGH A LOT.
>> I CAN'T SEE MY TOES.
>> YOU CAN'T SEE YOUR TOES?
>> YEAH, LIKE, I CAN'T SEE MY
TOES UNLESS I LEAN FORWARD OR
BEND OVER.
>> [laughs]
>> I'VE BEEN GAINING, LIKE,
FIVE POUNDS A WEEK.
>> IT'S HEALTHY.
>> NO, I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
GAINING, LIKE, 1/2 POUND
A WEEK.
>> OH.
LIKE, HOW'S THAT MAKING YOU
FEEL?
ARE YOU OKAY WITH IT?
>> NO, YOU FEEL LIKE YOUR BODY'S
RUINED FOR LIFE NOW, YOU KNOW?
JUST 'CAUSE, LIKE, I HAVE
STRETCH MARKS, LIKE, IN THE
FRONT, LIKE, NOT EVEN ON MY
SIDES.
>> WHEN YOU'RE AROUND BEN AND
STUFF, HE STILL MAKES YOU FEEL
BEAUTIFUL, RIGHT?
LIKE, HE REMINDS YOU AND
EVERYTHING, RIGHT?
>> HE SAYS IT, BUT YOU DON'T
BELIEVE IT, YOU KNOW?
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE LIKE,
"YEAH, RIGHT, I'M FAT."
>> [laughs]
>> SO, LIKE, ONCE TRISTAN GETS
HERE, YOU THINK THAT BEN'S
GONNA, LIKE, KIND OF, LIKE,
STEP UP TO THE PLATE,
OR DO YOU THINK HE'S GONNA
KIND OF FREAK OUT?
>> I THINK HE'LL BE REALLY GOOD
AT FIRST, BUT AS SOON AS
EVERYTHING, LIKE, GETS INTO
A ROUTINE, HE'LL PROBABLY, LIKE,
GO TO THE XBOX A LITTLE BIT.
>> YEAH.
IT'S GONNA BE STRESSFUL,
YOU KNOW, FOR BOTH OF YOU.
>> I THINK HE KNOWS NOT MAKE ME
MAD, 'CAUSE MY HORMONES ARE
CRAZY.
[laughing]
I'VE BEEN SO UNCOMFORTABLE WITH
MY BODY RECENTLY THAT I WANT TO
ASK MY DOCTOR IF I CAN BE
INDUCED EARLY.
>> GO AHEAD AND STEP UP HERE
FOR ME, PLEASE.
AND YOU'RE 38 WEEKS AND ONE DAY.
204.
>> AW, MAN.
>> ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> NO.
>> NO?
>> JUST 'CAUSE I DON'T--
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S BEEN A BAD DAY, SO I'M
GUESSING THEY'RE GONNA TELL ME
I CAN'T BE INDUCED.
>> WHAT ELSE IS WRONG?
>> MY WEIGHT.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S ANYTHING
THAT'S NOT GONNA COME OFF AFTER
THE BABY COMES OUT, BABY.
YOU KNOW?
>> NO, IT'S JUST UPSETTING.
[sniffling]
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY.
YOU STILL LOOK CUTE TO ME.
DON'T ROLL YOUR EYES AT ME.
>> HI, THERE.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
I'M DOCTOR STEINER.
I'M ONE OF DOCTOR CHANG'S
PARTNERS.
HE IS GONE THIS WEEK, SO I'M
FILLING IN FOR HIM, OKAY?
>> SO IS THERE ANY WAY THAT
I COULD BE INDUCED EARLY?
>> WHY WOULD YOU LIKE TO BE
INDUCED?
>> I'M UNCOMFORTABLE.
READY TO GET IT OVER WITH.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
WELL, LET ME GO AHEAD AND CHECK
YOUR CERVIX NEXT, OKAY?
OKAY, SO WHAT I'M GONNA DO IS
INSERT TWO FINGERS, LOTS OF
PRESSURE.
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE.
SO YOU ARE ACTUALLY ABOUT
2 CENTIMETERS DILATED
AND ABOUT 50% THINNED OUT.
YOUR CERVIX IS SOFT, SO I THINK
WE CAN GO AHEAD AND TRY TO
INDUCE YOU ON FRIDAY.
DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
>> SOUNDS GREAT.
>> OKAY, GREAT.
GOOD NEWS, HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
>> ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> YEP, WE'RE HAVING A BABY
IN ONE WEEK.
>> IN ONE WEEK.
>> YAY, YAY, YAY.
IT'S TIME.
>> [yawns]
ARE YOU READY?
>> YEP.
>> NERVOUS?
>> NEXT TIME WE WALK THROUGH
THIS DOOR, IT'LL BE WITH A BABY.
>> YEP.
I SHOULD'VE TOOK ONE OF THOSE
LABOR CLASSES.
>> THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
>> DID YOU SLEEP AT ALL?
>> NOT GOOD.
>> KIND OF.
JUST TOSSING AND TURNING
PRETTY MUCH ALL NIGHT.
>> UM, DID HE KIND OF EXPLAIN
WHAT PITOCIN IS?
OKAY.
OKAY, ARE YOU READY?
IT'S GONNA BE A BIG POKE, OKAY?
>> SO AM I HAVING CONTRACTIONS,
THEN?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> IT JUST FEELS WEIRD.
>> GOOD MORNING.
YOU ALL SET TO GO?
>> YEAH, WE'RE READY.
LET'S GET 'ER DONE.
>> OKAY.
OKAY, YOUR WATER'S BROKEN.
>> IT FEELS I PEED MYSELF.
>> LABOR'S A MESSY THING.
>> AFTER THE DOCTOR BROKE MY
WATER, MY CONTRACTIONS STARTED
TO GET MUCH STRONGER.
>> ALMOST BEEN HERE SIX HOURS.
HOW DOES IT FEEL?
>> OH.
I'M FEELING 'EM.
BACK CONTRACTIONS NOW.
I JUST WANT TO LAY ON MY SIDE.
OW, THAT HURTS.
>> ARE YOU READY FOR AN
EPIDURAL?
>> UH, YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH, I FEEL IT GOING INTO
MY BACK.
IT'S WEIRD.
>> YOU'LL HOPEFULLY START
FEELING THE CONTRACTIONS, BUT
THEY WON'T GO TO PAIN.
>> AFTER TEN HOURS OF LABOR, MY
DOCTOR STARTED TO GET CONCERNED.
>> YOU'VE REALLY GONE SLOWLY.
UM, WE'LL PROBABLY HAVE TO DO
A C-SECTION.
>> IS THE RECOVERY BAD FOR
A C-SECTION?
>> YOU'LL USUALLY GO HOME THE
THIRD DAY AFTER SURGERY.
DON'T FRET.
>> YOU GUYS CAN'T GO BACK WITH
ME.
>> NO, JUST BEN.
>> NO, ONLY BEN.
>> ARE YOU GETTING MORE NERVOUS?
>> YEAH.
>> [sniffling]
>> WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
>> I'M SCARED.
>> WHY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> ARE YOU SCARED I'M GONNA DIE?
>> NO.
>> LET'S GO.
>> WAIT FOR ME.
[gentle piano music]
>> ONE MOMENT.
>> ALMOST.
DOING OKAY?
>> YOU CAN HEAR HIM.
>> IT'S A BOY.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> 7:23 P.M.
>> IT'S A BOY.
>> AW.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> HEY, DUDE.
LOOK AT YOU.
>> HEY, BABY BOY.
[baby crying]
>> WHAT'S THE BABY'S NAME?
>> TRISTAN.
>> YOU WANT TO HOLD THE BABY
FOR A MOMENT?
>> HEY, BABY BOY.
HE WANTS TO SEE HIS MAMA.
DON'T YOU, BUDDY BOY?
>>  LOVE IS HERE
LOVE IS HERE
TO GUIDE YOU HOME
>> OKAY, YEAH...
>> YOU WATCH HIS HEAD...
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE TRISTAN IS
FINALLY HERE.
PASS HIM AROUND.
>> UH, DO I HAVE TO?
>> AFTER THREE DAYS AND A LOT OF
PAIN, IT'S FINALLY TIME TO TAKE
TRISTAN HOME.
OOH.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> WILL YOU GET THE DOOR FOR ME?
I'M SO SORRY.
TRISTAN, ARE YOU READY TO SEE
YOUR NEW HOME?
>> SLOW AND EASY, MAMA.
>> IT'S SO GOOD TO BE HOME.
HE CAN GO FOR A RIDE.
YOU LIKE THAT?
>> ARE YOU HAPPY THAT HE'S HOME
FINALLY?
>> OF COURSE.
>> I WAS READY.
[Tristan crying]
DOES HE NEED TO BE CHANGED?
>> PROBABLY.
[Tristan crying]
DANG IT, TRISTAN.
WHILE IT'S NICE TO HAVE
TRISTAN HOME, BEING UP ALL NIGHT
IS HARD, AND I'M STILL REALLY
SORE.
>> I'M LATE.
>> IT WAS NICE THAT BEN WAS ABLE
TO GET OFF A FEW DAYS, BUT TODAY
HE HAS TO GO BACK TO WORK.
AND SINCE HE'S A BARTENDER,
HE WORKS LATE SHIFTS...
[Tristan crying]
WHICH MEANS NOW I HAVE TO GET UP
WITH TRISTAN IN THE NIGHT
ON MY OWN.
[Tristan crying]
[phone ringing]
HELLO?
>> OKAY.
>> BYE.
I WISH MY MOM COULD HELP,
BUT SHE LIVES AN HOUR AWAY.
I'VE BEEN STUCK IN THE HOUSE
FOR THE PAST MONTH.
I WISH MY FRIENDS COULD COME
OVER, BUT THEY'RE ALL AWAY AT
COLLEGE.
>> HELLO?
>> HEY.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> NOTHIN', WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT ARE THE DORMS LIKE?
>> OH, YEAH?
>> YEAH, THEY ARE.
THERE'S, LIKE, PEOPLE
EVERYWHERE ALL THE TIME.
LIKE, YOU PRETTY MUCH HAVE,
LIKE, 200 NEIGHBORS.
>> I'LL LET YOU GO, THOUGH.
HE'S STARTING TO FUSS, AND YOU
NEED TO STUDY.
>> OKAY, LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> BYE.
[door clicks open]
HEY.
>> HEY, BABY.
>> HOW WAS WORK?
>> IT WAS WORK.
SAME AS ALWAYS.
[sighs]
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
>> KIND OF BORING.
>> ARE YOU GETTING BORED JUST
SITTING AT HOME?
>> YEAH, I GOT A QUESTION.
>> WHAT?
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT ME
TRYING TO GET A JOB?
>> WHAT MAKES YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
NEED TO WORK?
>> JUST 'CAUSE I'M BORED.
I DO THE SAME THING,
AND IT'LL BE NICE TO SEE SOME
GIRLS, YOU KNOW?
I MISS HAVING MY FRIENDS AROUND
ALL THE TIME TOO.
>> ALL YOUR FRIENDS LIVE REALLY
FAR AWAY.
>> SO I CAN ONLY TALK TO THEM ON
THE PHONE.
I CAN'T ACTUALLY SEE THEM.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL FOR YA, THAT YOU HAVE TO
MISS OUT ON IT ALL.
>> SO ARE YOU OKAY WATCHING
TRISTAN?
>> YEAH, I'M FINE.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM WATCHING HIM
WHEN YOU'RE NOT HERE.
>> I'LL MISS HIM BUT--
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK IT'LL BE GOOD FOR ME TO
GET OUT OF THE HOUSE FOR
A COUPLE HOURS A COUPLE DAYS
A WEEK, YOU KNOW?
[chime dings]
>> SINCE BEN AGREED TO WATCH
TRISTAN WHILE I GO BACK TO WORK,
I HAVE AN INTERVIEW TODAY.
>> YOU ARE APPLYING TO BE
A SERVER OR A HOST?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT KIND OF QUALITIES DO YOU
THINK THAT YOU HAVE THAT WOULD
MAKE YOU A GOOD CANDIDATE?
>> I'M RELIABLE, FRIENDLY,
OUTGOING.
>> ON YOUR AVAILABILITY RIGHT
HERE, YOU HAVE MONDAY, TUESDAY,
WEDNESDAY, THURSDAY OPEN.
IS THAT STILL ACCURATE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND IF YOU CAN BALANCE
WHATEVER ELSE YOU HAVE GOING ON
IN YOUR LIFE, THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S ALL I NEED.
OKAY, I'M GONNA CALL YOU IN
A COUPLE DAYS.
HOPE, IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU.
SURE ENOUGH, THE NEXT DAY, THEY
CALLED AND OFFERED ME A JOB.
AND THEY WERE EVEN FLEXIBLE,
SO I CAN MAKE MY HOURS FIT
AROUND BEN'S SCHEDULE.
BYE, BUBS.
CHEESEBURGER, MEDIUM WELL,
WITH FRIES, AND YOUR TOTAL IS
$29.60, AND IT'LL BE READY IN
ABOUT 10 TO 15 MINUTES.
THANK YOU, BYE.
IT'S GOOD TO GET OUT OF THE
HOUSE AND EVEN EARN SOME MONEY,
BUT IT'S NOT THE SAME AS BEING
AT COLLEGE WITH MY FRIENDS.
>> HEY, BABY.
>> HI.
>> HOW'S WORK?
>> HI, BUBS.
IT WAS GOOD.
>> SO ARE YOU LIKING IT AT
54TH STREET?
>> LIKE, I LIKE THE JOB,
BUT I STILL HAVEN'T REALLY
MADE FRIENDS.
I DON'T KNOW HALF THE PEOPLE'S
NAMES.
>> I MEAN, IT TAKES TIME.
YOU STILL GET PEOPLE TO TALK TO
AND GET TO GET OUT OF THE HOUSE.
>> YEAH.
IT'S NICE, JUST BECAUSE WHENEVER
YOU WERE ALWAYS GONE, ALL I HAVE
IS A BABY TO TALK TO, AND HE
DOESN'T TALK BACK.
I'VE REALLY BEEN MISSING MY
FRIENDS, SO TODAY I'M TAKING
TRISTAN TO SEE ELAINE AT
COLLEGE.
HEY.
>> HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
OH, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> I KNOW, I MISSED YOU.
>> I MISS YOU TOO.
OH, HE'S SO CUTE!
HI, BABY.
READY FOR ME TO SHOW YOU
AROUND?
>> I AM.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
THIS IS THE NATURAL HISTORY
MUSEUM.
GO UP THAT WAY.
>> LIKE, IF I DIDN'T HAVE
A BABY, LIKE, THIS WOULD BE
AWESOME.
LIKE, IT'D DEFINITELY BE PRETTY
COOL TO GO HERE.
>> LIKE, YOU CANNOT WALK
ANYWHERE IN THIS PLACE WITHOUT,
"OH, HEY, I KNOW YOU, AND I KNOW
YOU," OR, "I KNOW THIS PERSON,"
OR, "I HUNG OUT WITH THIS
PERSON."
IT JUST NEVER STOPS.
>> SO WHERE DO YOU GUYS GO FOR
ALL THE PARTIES?
>> YOU GO TO, LIKE, ONE HOUSE,
AND THEN THE HOUSE NEXT DOOR AND
THE HOUSE NEXT DOOR AND THE
HOUSE NEXT DOOR ARE ALL HAVING,
LIKE, A PARTY.
THIS IS THE STUDENT UNION.
>> I WISH I WOULD'VE BROUGHT
MY CAMERA.
>> THAT WOULD'VE BEEN CUTE.
HI.
>> HEY.
>> ELAINE!
>> WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
>> NOTHIN'.
>> HI.
>> THIS IS MY FRIEND HOPE.
>> all: HI.
>> SHE'S FROM BACK HOME.
>> YOUR BABY IS SO CUTE.
>> SERIOUSLY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HE'S ADORBS.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOIN'?
>> CHILLAXIN'.
>> PROBABLY GONNA LEAVE SOON.
>> I GOT TO DO HOMEWORK.
>> WHAT ARE WE DOING THIS
WEEKEND, FOR REAL?
>> WE'RE PROBABLY GONNA GO TO
HOUSE PARTIES.
>> HOUSE PARTIES?
>> COSTUME.
>> WELL, WE'RE GONNA GRAB SOME
SMOOTHIES, SO I WILL TEXT YOU
GUYS LATER, THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS NICE MEETING YOU.
>> BYE.
>> BYE, GUYS.
SMOOTHIE TIME.
>> SMOOTHIE TIME.
>> OH, YEAH, THAT LOOKS REALLY
GOOD.
SO HAS IT BEEN NICE TO BE, LIKE,
OUT DOING STUFF AND, LIKE,
SEEING THINGS?
>> OH, YEAH.
IT'S WAY BETTER THAN BEING STUCK
AT THE HOUSE.
AND ACTUALLY, LIKE, INTERACTING
WITH PEOPLE, IT'S NICE.
>> HOW OFTEN DO YOU LEAVE YOUR
HOUSE?
>> JUST TO GO TO WORK OR THE
GROCERY STORE.
>> THAT'S VERY UNLIKE YOU.
>> I KNOW.
I'M, LIKE, TRAPPED IN A HOUSE.
I'M LIKE--I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO.
I'M ABOUT TO GO CRAZY.
I MEAN, I'VE ALWAYS WANTED,
LIKE, THE FAMILY, BUT I WANTED
TO GO TO COLLEGE AND GET MY
PARTYING STAGE DONE WITH FIRST.
>> I GUESS THINGS CHANGE A LOT.
>> IT'S A WEIRD ADJUSTMENT AT
FIRST TOO.
[Tristan crying]
>> I LIKE HIM.
DO YOU THINK IT'S HARDER TO MAKE
NEW FRIENDS NOW?
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S KIND OF WHY, LIKE,
I WANTED TO GET A JOB.
>> JUST TO MEET PEOPLE.
>> MEET SOME FRIENDS UP BY ME.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU'VE GROWN UP
A LOT...
A LOT, A LOT, IN, LIKE, A REALLY
SHORT AMOUNT OF TIME.
>> YEAH.
[chime dings]
SEEING ELAINE AND HER LIFE AT
COLLEGE HAS MADE ME REALIZE
HOW MUCH I'VE HAD TO GIVE UP.
>> female announcer: DON'T
GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> EVEN THOUGH MY LIFE IS NOT
HOW I EXPECTED IT TO BE AT 17,
BEN AND I HAVE STARTED GETTING
INTO A ROUTINE.
HE LOOKS AFTER TRISTAN WHEN I'M
AT WORK...
WOULD YOU LIKE TO UPGRADE YOUR
FRIES TO GRINGO DIP?
AND THEN I RUSH HOME TO TAKE
OVER SO HE CAN GET TO HIS SHIFT
IN TIME.
>> ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU, BABY.
>> IT'S A LOT TO JUGGLE, SO WE
HAVE TO MAKE A REAL EFFORT TO
SPEND TIME TOGETHER.
DO YOU THINK OUR RELATIONSHIP
HAS CHANGED SINCE WE'VE HAD THE
BABY?
>> I THINK WE'RE DOING REALLY
GOOD FOR WHERE WE'RE AT,
YOU KNOW?
>> AND WHERE WE CAME FROM.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I THINK YOU CHANGED
A LOT.
>> I KNOW THAT.
I WAS LIVING FOR THE DAY,
YOU KNOW?
LIFE'S NOT ABOUT INSTANT
GRATIFICATION ANYMORE.
I GOT TO THINK ABOUT 18 YEARS
DOWN THE ROAD.
WHAT'S HE GONNA BE DOING,
YOU KNOW?
I WANT IT TO BE HIS CHOICE,
JUST LIKE WITH YOU.
>> RIGHT NOW, I HAVE NOTHING
GOING FOR ME.
I WORK AT A RESTAURANT AS AN
EXPRESS PERSON.
>> YEAH, BUT I WORK AT
A RESTAURANT TOO.
>> I STILL WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL.
>> WHAT MAKES SCHOOL SO
IMPORTANT?
>> JUST TO HAVE, LIKE, A GOOD,
RELIABLE JOB.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'LL BE ABOUT, LIKE, SCHOOL,
NOT ABOUT THE SOCIAL LIFE.
>> YEAH.
YOU DON'T SEE YOURSELF EVER
FINDING NEW FRIENDS UP HERE,
YOU KNOW?
>> I THOUGHT IT'D BE EASIER TO
MAKE FRIENDS AT MY NEW JOB.
EVERYBODY IN THE RESTAURANT
IS GONNA WANT TO GO PARTY,
AND I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> YOU'RE MAKING IT SOUND LIKE
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA MAKE FRIENDS
AGAIN.
>> THE REASON I DON'T FEEL
LIKE I CAN MAKE ANY FRIENDS
IS BECAUSE I'M DIFFERENT THAN
EVERY OTHER TEENAGER, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> MOST TEENAGERS DON'T HAVE
A TWO-MONTH-OLD.
AND, LIKE, WE DON'T HAVE THE
SAME COMMON INTERESTS.
LIKE, EVERYTHING'S CHANGED.
I DON'T REALLY FEEL LIKE A
TEENAGER ANYMORE JUST BECAUSE I
HAVE A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITIES,
LIKE PAYING THE BILLS AND TAKING
CARE OF ANOTHER PERSON.
IT'S REALLY HARD.
[Tristan crying]
SOMETIMES HE JUST CRIES, AND YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH HIM,
AND YOU JUST GET REALLY
STRESSED.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE HAD TO GIVE UP
MY SOCIAL LIFE.
I DON'T REALLY TALK TO MOST OF
MY FRIENDS ANYMORE.
>> DOES IT MAKE YOU SAD THAT
ALL YOUR FRIENDS ARE AT COLLEGE
AND THAT YOU'RE NOT?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, HERE'S THE SAD PART:
YOU WERE SO CLOSE WITH ALL OF
THESE GIRLS, AND IT'S GONNA BE
REALLY HARD TO KEEP IN TOUCH
WITH ALL OF THEM.
>> I THINK IF I WENT TO COLLEGE
NOW, IT WOULD BE A LOT HARDER,
JUST BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO TAKE
CARE OF A CRYING BABY WHILE
YOU'RE TRYING TO DO YOUR
HOMEWORK, AND I THINK IT'D BE
TEN TIMES HARDER.
BREATHE.
IT WAS HARD LISTENING TO MY
FRIENDS AND FAMILY BE LIKE,
"BEN'S NOT GONNA COME AROUND."
LIKE, "DON'T GET YOUR HOPES UP."
BUT BEN AND I HAVE MADE IT WORK
BECAUSE WE ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT
EACH OTHER.
>> I CAN PUT A PILLOW UNDER YOUR
BUTT IF YOU WANT ME TO.
>> SOMETIMES I THINK A LOT OF
TEENAGE COUPLES JUST ARE
TOGETHER FOR THEIR BABIES, BUT I
THINK IT TAKES MORE THAN JUST
BEING TOGETHER FOR YOUR BABY.
>> HE SAYS, "I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON, BUT I DON'T LIKE IT."
>> I REALLY HOPE ME AND BEN
MAKE IT.
THINGS ARE GOING GREAT RIGHT
NOW, AND I'M NOT SURE HOW
THEY'LL BE IN THE FUTURE,
BUT ALL I CAN DO IS HOPE FOR
THE BEST.
>> DID HE BUY THE TICKETS YET?
>> NO, HE'S WAITING TO BUY THEM.
>> HOW MANY TIMES DID HE PROMISE
TO COME OUT ALREADY?
>> JUST GET OUT, PLEASE!
JUST--
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, SHE'S TURNING PURPLE.
>> WE NEED NICU NOW.
NOW.
>> GOD, LORD, JESUS!