>> [chuckles]
My name's Lori.
I'm from Northern Kentucky,
classic small-town America,
blue skies, green grass,
and riverboats.
Out here in the suburbs,
I live in this house with
my mom and dad.
My parents always want
what's best for me.
>> You've got homework.
What's your anatomy
gonna be on?
>> Chemistry.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I feel lucky that this
is my family, even though
I'm actually adopted.
[chime dings]
I've always wondered about
my birth mother.
Who is she?
And why couldn't she raise me?
[knock at door]
This is my ex-boyfriend Cory.
He's a tough man's man
who loves his sports.
>> I'm gonna laugh when the
Steelers get their butts whupped
today, 'cause their kicker
isn't worth crap.
>> We're still friends,
even though we broke up
last year.
[laughing] You are such a...
I can't help myself.
I still think he's kind of cute.
During the week, I'm a student
at an all-girls Catholic
high school, where I try
to stay out of trouble.
I pray...
and pray...
>> May you be wise in choices
and decisions.
>> And pray for guidance
and strength.
I'm gonna need it big-time,
because... I'm pregnant.
[chime dings]
[assertive acoustic strumming]
* *
When I found out I was pregnant,
Cory and I started fighting
all the time, and we broke up.
Get the fishies.
But now we need to set aside
our differences and make a plan.
I mean, they want to be
grandparents, they do.
They don't want to be parents
again.
>> Yeah.
When we first found out,
I was up for the adoption,
even closed at that point,
but now I can't do it.
>> Yeah. About 90% that
I'm keeping him.
>> I feel the exact same way.
And with, like, us, we just
kind of stopped talking,
'cause every time we did,
we'd argue.
>> I was pissed.
>> Yeah.
We can get along.
[laughs]
We did for a year.
We were actually really close.
>> Yeah.
>> But I think there's still
a lot--a lot that we have got
to figure out.
>> We're in a world of hurt.
I think it's gonna be
a lot of trouble.
>> You ready for it?
>> No.
>> It's scary.
Scary is an understatement.
My mom and dad were pissed
when they found out.
They think Cory and I are
way too young to be parents
and have been talking to me
a lot about choosing adoption.
>> I could have just...
>> Killed me?
>> Thrown up
right there on the spot.
>> And I became physically ill.
>> You know, my gut response
was, "we need to make this
go away."
>> Yeah.
>> I, you know, I'm kind of
against abortion.
I've always said that,
and then when she came and told
me this, I'm thinking, you know,
this is really gonna test
my beliefs in everything.
>> Well, I couldn't, because,
like, my birth mom was in the
same situation 17 years ago.
>> Right.
>> She could have said,
"I want an abortion."
And then...
>> And you wouldn't be here.
>> I wouldn't be here.
>> When we first started
discussing adoption versus
parenting, it's consumed us
since the day we found out
about this.
And that's, I think,
what makes it really painful,
is that this would normally be
a real joyous thing.
We'd be jumping up and down.
But the circumstances--
just it's--
>> They're not right.
>> I obviously don't have
my parents' support in keeping
this baby.
Luckily I have my best friend
Alexa, who's really excited
about the idea of me being
a mom.
>> You're gonna be a mommy.
>> Oh, my God.
I think for me, I mean,
I don't have any, like, actual,
like, biological blood-related
family right now.
And, like, I think that plays
kind of in the role with the
whole, like, putting him up
for adoption thing,
the fact that for the first
time, I have actual family,
then I just give it away.
I think Cory kind of feels
the same way.
I mean, I wonder, like,
had, like, I not been the one
to walk away from the
relationship...
>> I think it would still
be over.
>> I think there was part of me
that wishes we would get
back together.
But there's still that voice
in my head saying,
"You're retarded.
Get over it."
>> That's my voice.
>> Shut up.
That ain't your voice.
Your voice is too squeaky.
>> Why does everyone say that?
>> It's the start of my
senior year.
Sometimes I forget I'm still
a teenager.
I don't want to go to school.
>> Do you ever want to go
to school?
>> Even though I go to
a private Catholic high school,
people seem to be accepting
of my pregnancy.
See you.
Oh, I don't want--
>> Good morning, ladies.
Monday, we want this final
draft, so today's gonna be
kind of important to get
the coeditors together.
>> It's really hard to
concentrate when all I can
think about is what to do
about my baby.
[baby coos]
>> Tired?
[electronic bell dings]
>> My friends are still getting
over the fact that I'm pregnant.
>> I didn't believe you when
you told me...
>> Well, when you're on
antibiotics, it can cancel--
>> I knew that.
>> It can counteract--
>> Yeah, now,
we all learned that.
>> I knew that before...
>> It can counteract it.
>> 'Cause they told me.
>> Thanks for telling me.
I thought you, like,
went off of it.
>> I thought you stopped.
>> I didn't even know you were--
>> I went through the--
>> Like that.
[laughter]
I'm, like, I thought you were
an innocent little girl.
>> All right.
[electronic bell dings]
Jeez, that was the longest
day ever.
>> I know, totally.
>> I think--someone said it's,
like, 200 and something days
until spring break.
>> 200.
>> Even though I'm not totally
sure if I'm gonna keep my baby,
I'm psyched that Alexa wants
to throw me a baby shower.
I wonder how my mom will
take it.
>> I really don't want anyone
to have a baby shower...
>> I didn't know that part.
>> For Lori.
You're 17 years old.
You're not married.
You're still in school,
and you're pregnant,
and I just don't see anything
to celebrate in that.
If you were open to adoption--
>> Not yet, no.
Nope.
>> But it's not completely
out of the question.
>> No, neither is parenting.
>> Let me tell you,
your dad and I have always said
what a loving act this birth
mother did to give you to us,
because she knew that she could
not parent when she was
16 years old.
You know, we just need to keep
all our options open.
>> I know.
>> And we need to really pray
and hope that, you know, you're
guided in the right direction.
>> That's just it.
What if the right direction
for me and the right direction
that you all think is completely
different?
>> It would be such a mistake
for you and for this baby
to bring him into this house.
[chime dings]
>> My mom really wants me
to choose adoption.
I'm just not sure
that's what I want.
>> After my mom made it clear
that a baby shower was out
of the question, my friends
wanted to talk.
>> You are our best friend,
and I want to side with you
more than your mom.
>> Okay, but even if you did
side with my mom, I wouldn't be
pissed or nothing.
>> I don't know, because I kind
of want you to keep the baby.
>> I mean, like, I've thought,
like, if you did give it up
for adoption, I think you would,
like, do worse in school,
and you'd just like--
>> I wouldn't be able to do it.
Like, I would seriously
have a psychological breakdown.
Thank you.
Honestly, I don't know.
Like, it's hard.
It's time for another
ultrasound.
Even though we're not on
the same page about the baby,
my mom and dad are coming along.
>> Now, do you know what
you're having?
>> A boy.
>> It's a boy.
>> This one's gonna be special,
'cause I'll get to see
the little guy in 3-D.
>> Get the little munchkin's
face in here.
Look at those pouty lips.
>> [laughs]
>> He's moving his little arm.
He is active.
>> Hang in there.
You doing okay, hon?
>> Yes.
I wonder how you're doing.
>> She's hanging in there.
>> [laughs]
>> Get you up.
Okay, those are yours.
>> Thank you.
>> And then this CD will have
pictures on it.
>> Look at that.
>> [sniffs]
>> It's the pouty--
pouty lips there.
>> Oh.
>> Yes, it is.
It's gonna be hard.
>> Even though my mom got
pretty emotional after seeing
the sonogram, she still wants
me to consider adoption.
So Cory's coming over to talk
about what we should do.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's like actually seeing him.
You look shocked.
>> I don't know.
It's just so surreal.
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> At least I'm not on my own.
A lot of work
and a lot of us getting along.
>> Uh.
It's getting there.
>> I know.
They're definitely still gonna
push adoption.
They've never--
>> It's not their choice.
But you know exactly what
my dad's gonna ask: how?
Don't know yet.
>> We'll figure it out.
>> I still have to find out
where to go, I mean...
>> You can come live with me.
I don't care.
>> Okay.
We just have to keep looking.
>> I don't even want to look.
>> I know.
[laughter]
I know.
It was really hard.
>> Hmm?
>> We'll do it so they shut up.
>> Okay.
[chime dings]
Cory's master plan is for me
and the baby to move in with him
and his roommate, Ashley.
It's not the best plan,
but it's the only one we've got.
He saw the pictures.
>> So does that make you change
your mind, or what's that do
to you?
>> Yeah, now it's gonna
be harder.
>> I think we're just gonna
continue exploring both sides.
>> Maybe look at some profiles
just to get a feel for what...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> I mean, what we'd be doing.
>> Okay, I have a question.
If you're thinking about
parenting, are you two together?
I mean, are you going to
live together?
Are you going to live
separately?
>> Would there be, like,
custody?
>> Have you even thought
that far?
>> It's still--we have.
We have talked a little bit
about it.
>> No, we've talked about it,
but that's up in the air.
>> We just now got back onto
good terms, so we're still
working into everything
really slowly.
>> Because, you know, there's no
point in staying together--
>> That shouldn't be our--
that's not really our main--
>> Now's the time when you
really have to sit down and get
some details worked out.
I'm telling you.
>> Well, I mean, you're there
freaking out, but--
>> I am freaking out because
this baby is on a schedule,
you know?
>> Well, let's say,
at least two months.
>> Two months?
>> Parenting--I'm just telling
you, you've got a lot to do.
>> Yes, two months.
>> You can't start, like,
jumping on us now.
Like, we're open to, like,
looking at open adoption,
but you also have to be open
to where we're coming from
and what we want to--
>> I am open to it.
>> You both need reality.
>> But what if the reality is
I want to keep this baby?
>> The past week at home
has been tense.
Since Cory made the offer
for me to move in with the baby,
he hasn't been in touch at all
about his plan.
>> Have you talked to Cory
today?
>> I don't know what's going on
with him.
I don't know anything right now.
>> Oh...
>> You guys have to have
dialogue regarding this.
You know, because as delivery
approaches, I don't want him
to have some emotional deal
going, and I mean, he has
to get it together.
>> And so do you.
I just think that you need
to set priorities and check out
everything that's available to
you, so you have no regrets,
saying, "Gee, I wish I would
have done that."
>> My parents thought it would
help me to meet someone who
actually chose open adoption
for their baby.
Liz is here.
>> Hey.
>> Hi.
How are you?
>> Good.
>> So they called our family
friend Liz, a girl who went
through the same thing
that I did.
>> How did you come to that
decision to do an open adoption?
>> I just found out about
open adoption, and it kind of
was really interesting.
That's your first parental
decision.
You know, like, I made the most
important decision.
You're gonna make it,
whatever you decide.
>> You know, to achieve what you
want to achieve and parent
as a teenager, it's just
impossible.
>> I mean, I would not be able
to do it.
There's no way.
It would not be possible.
>> I keep telling her,
it's the best of both worlds.
>> That's what my mom said
to me too.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> It's the best of both worlds.
>> It is, to be able to--
>> That should be your
theme song.
>> I didn't even know
it was a song.
>> Hannah Montana.
>> Is it really a song?
Yeah, Hannah Montana.
>> Just the fact that she knows
a Hannah Montana song should
make her ineligible to parent
at this age.
But now the family that you
chose wasn't through Catholic
Social--that's surprising.
>> No.
>> How did that come about?
>> We just kind of looked
on our own and...
>> Wow.
>> Found Brian and Jen, yeah.
>> That's some divine
intervention.
>> Oh, yeah.
And also they do have
a desire to adopt again.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> And if everything were to
work out that way...
>> Yeah.
>> You know, you could be
birth mom number two.
[chime dings]
>> Talking with Liz really
opened my eyes to the
possibility of open adoption.
But I'm still not sold
and neither is Cory
as my mom found out when she
called him to see where he stood
on things.
[line rings]
Cory told my mom that he was
pretty set on keeping the baby
after all.
>> Oh, my God.
You don't want anyone else
raising your kid.
>> I can tell you,
it's gonna be a disaster.
So she needs--
>> Yes, I do know that.
I do know that, Cory.
Okay, well, I just talked
to Cory.
>> Yeah?
>> And he tells me that you two
are gonna keep this baby
and that you are going to
move into his apartment.
>> It's just something that
we've been considering recently.
>> You know, I'm not even--
as con--so much concerned
about you in raising this child
as I am Cory,
because he's not followed
through on one promise since
I've known him.
>> If you truly think that this
is something that you're
considering, you need to go out
there, and you need to live
with him and see what
a disastrous situation you're
putting yourself in before this
innocent baby is brought into
this world.
We're setting a deadline.
This needs to be done by
the end of this week.
>> That's fine with me.
I'll talk to him tonight.
>> [sighs]
>> My parents seem to think
this is an obvious decision,
but it's much more complicated
than that.
[line ringing]
I'm on my way over now.
My parents and I had our
family discussion tonight.
>> [sighs]
It went--it was pretty scary.
So you and I got some talking
to do.
I will talk about it when
I get there.
How's that?
>> All right.
>> Okay.
I need to talk to Cory
face-to-face.
We have to make these decisions
together.
>> What did your parents say?
>> My mom's still on her whole
thing, "If this is what you're
gonna do, then you need
to do it now."
But the catch is, we have a week
to give them a final answer.
>> I have my final answer
whether they like it or not.
I'm keeping him.
>> This is why if we're sure
about coming here, we have
really got to get moving here.
>> It's not just up to me.
I have a roommate.
>> Well, you said she was
perfectly fine with it.
>> She--I was supposed to talk
to her Friday.
She ain't been home in
a [bleep] week.
>> I don't know.
Why did you throw out
the opportunity for us
to stay here?
>> 'Cause you have nowhere
else to go.
>> I got to know where you
stand with this offer.
>> I got to talk to Ashley.
I'm fine with it, but
I don't know where my
roommate is.
>> Well, you should find out,
like, this week.
>> When she comes home tonight,
I'll talk to her.
>> I got to go.
[sniffs]
[door clicks open]
Living with Cory might not
be an option after all.
How can I raise this baby
if I have nowhere to go?
>> I couldn't believe how Cory
was acting last night.
It made me start to think
about what kind of dad
he would be.
I went out there, and I was
talking to him.
You know how he gets.
And, like, by, like,
halfway through, his temper
started.
I really don't know where
he stands.
>> Well, he also is just now
realizing that you're pregnant,
and I think that's ridiculous.
>> That's why I'm still gonna
pursue open adoption.
>> I just think that you can
give this baby a really
good life.
>> I mean, I have to.
No matter what, I have
to look at it.
Yeah.
Just to be safe, I decided to
meet with Jen and Brian.
I want to see if they might
make cool adoptive parents.
>> Okay, well, you ready
for this?
>> I'm so nervous.
>> Remember, all you're doing...
>> Is meeting them.
>> I know.
>> And Liz is just gonna show
you how it works for her.
>> I think I'm more comfortable
that she's gonna be there.
Since I can't rely on Cory
at the moment, I need
to reconsider all of my options
including open adoption.
>> Hi.
>> I'm Lori.
>> I'm Jennifer.
>> Hey, Liz.
>> Hey.
>> So we're just gonna talk
about open adoption.
Is that okay?
>> Yes, that is fine.
>> Okay.
I had to trust her.
>> Yeah.
>> And she had to trust me,
that we were going to go forward
with the openness of it, and
we've never regretted it since.
>> Yeah.
>> We've always kept that door
open and always thought about
the possibility of doing
another adoption.
>> I want to explore every
option, just so I don't make
a decision and think,
"Oh, I wish I would have done--
looked into this a little more."
>> Oh, definitely.
>> I want to be pretty much
dead set.
>> If I didn't know for sure
that that's what Liz really
wanted, it just would have been
really, really hard.
>> Yeah.
>> So I encourage you to really
make sure that you do what
you're wanting to do.
>> Yeah.
>> Don't do it just because
somebody else wants you
to do it.
>> I've heard that a lot.
And the truth is, I still
don't know what I want to do,
which is what I've told
my parents.
Like, I told them, we just want
to do everything we can to
explore both sides, just so
we have no regrets.
And my friends, who still want
to throw me a baby shower.
>> Lori.
>> Y'all are real funny.
But I don't want to have
the baby shower behind
my mother's back.
Hey, Mom.
So we decided to tell my mom
in hopes that she would change
her mind.
>> Alexa just wanted
to talk to you.
>> Okay, so me and Lauren want
to have a baby shower for Lori.
>> Mom, I wanted you to know
so that if you...
>> Wanted to go or help plan it.
>> Wanted you to be there.
>> You're gonna keep
this baby, aren't you?
I mean, why are we playing
these games, Lori?
>> Mom, I'm really not
decided yet.
>> We need to be honest.
>> I-I'm being honest.
I really haven't completely
decided yet.
That's why we told you
about this.
>> And it is utterly ridiculous
to have a baby shower unless you
know you're planning on keeping
this baby.
>> And if I end up not keeping
him, then I can give it to
the family that adopts him.
>> Oh, God.
I'm sick of it.
I'm just--I'm--
I'm at my wit's end.
I can't take any more.
You need to be honest with me.
>> I am being honest.
>> I don't want to be a part
of any baby shower.
>> My mom was so upset that she
told my dad to call Cory to get
some answers.
>> Cory, has Lori been able
to get ahold of you today?
I mean, I think she really
hasn't made any plans as to how
she's gonna do it.
So I mean, are you thinking
you want to parent?
Do you want to do this open
adoption thing?
Oh, that would be excellent.
Jen and Brian want you to be
a part of this child's life.
Okay.
We'll just go from there.
Okay, I'll see you, buddy.
Bye.
>> Hey, Lori.
>> Come here.
We need to talk to you.
>> Yeah, I'm coming.
>> I got ahold of Cory finally.
>> Yeah?
>> And I asked him what you guys
are planning to do,
and he said that he's convinced
that there's no way that
you guys can parent.
He told me that.
It's what he said.
But you know, my heart
goes out to you.
I know this is tough for you.
I know what you want to do.
[knock at door]
I'm giving him up for adoption.
>> I'm sorry that you're
hurting.
>> Lori, this decision
has to be made.
>> There isn't a decision
to be made.
I have no choice in this.
Call Jen and Brian tomorrow.
I'm not telling them.
>> This isn't the way that
I wanted you to come to this
decision.
>> I mean, you have to admit;
school, life, it's a struggle
for you, Lori.
>> [sniffs]
>> Your mother--
we help you a lot.
Your mom helps you a lot
just to get through every week.
>> Cory's done.
He was my last option.
There's no miracle that's gonna
happen that's gonna change this.
Cory, he doesn't want it
anymore, so you know what?
I'm done.
>> Without my parents' or
Cory's help, it looks like
open adoption is my only option.
>> Facing reality is a--
is tough.
>> Y'all don't know the fact
that I'm--I am being forced
into this, 'cause I have nowhere
else to turn.
Everybody's saying, "Yeah,
your opinion matters.
Your opinion matters."
Okay, so I decide against you.
Where does that leave me?
On the street or something?
>> Well, I think it's the best
thing for this baby, but you
know, I don't want you to be
emotionally scarred.
>> Well, I'm gonna be.
>> [sighs]
>> Here's the thing you guys
don't understand about adoption.
This is the only blood-related
family I have.
This is the only person,
and now you--everyone's making
me give him to somebody else
to let them raise him.
So I want them to just
do it now.
This way, I couldn't think
about it anymore, 'cause I have
to go on with him inside me
knowing as soon as he comes out,
he's not mine anymore.
>> He's always going to be
yours.
>> I'm never gonna be a mom,
ever.
>> You're always going to be
his biological mother.
>> I was blindsided by this
last night.
I've been going on for months
thinking that I had
another option.
>> Well, I certainly didn't
tell him to say that.
>> I didn't say this was
your fault.
I'm pissed off at him.
Hearing the news from my parents
last night was devastating.
I need to find out why Cory
settled on adoption.
Hi.
>> What's up?
>> Congratulations.
You made your first
parental decision.
>> Gee, thanks.
>> You did, deciding what
was best for him.
>> Yeah.
And that decision sucks.
>> It does suck.
I mean, what caused you
to change your mind?
>> I did what your dad said.
I did the math,
just not financially stable.
Our relationship isn't where
it needs to be to raise a kid.
>> Yeah.
How do you think you're gonna
hold up in the delivery room?
>> It's gonna be rough, but
I think I'll make it through it.
>> You might have--like, I'm
gonna want to not let him go,
and I'm not gonna want to do it,
but I--
>> Yeah, watching a family walk
away with our son is gonna suck.
>> It's gonna be extremely hard
to just hand him over.
>> Yeah.
>> Talking to Cory helps me
understand how hard raising
a baby really would be.
Maybe Jen and Brian will be able
to give my baby a better life.
But just as I was starting
to get comfortable with the idea
of adoption, I got an unexpected
phone call from Jen and Brian.
[phone rings]
Hello?
What?
They realized they couldn't
prepare for a newborn in the
two weeks before my due date.
The adoption is off.
And now I have to break the news
to Cory.
Jen called me last night.
>> About what?
>> The adoption.
They said her and Brian are both
concerned with going forward
with this.
>> Like, I put my trust in them,
and they just--they blew that.
>> We may want to look at
other portfolios.
>> It [bleep] sucks.
You know I don't like to meet
new people.
And I'm not going through this
for the next month.
>> But I mean, we're gonna
have to at least try.
You all right?
>> It hurt.
>> Cory seems to be
reconsidering.
But with only a few weeks
to go, I have to look into
another adoptive couple.
So my parents decided it was
time to meet with an adoption
social worker to get this
process moving.
>> So what do y'all think
about an open adoption?
How do you picture the
relationship being in the next
two or three months?
>> I'd like to see him, like,
around the holidays, like,
around, like, birthdays
and everything and...
>> So do you picture going to
their house to visit with them?
>> If, like, they go out,
like, maybe, like, once in
a while, like, I could, like,
be their babysitter or
something, just see him
every once in a while.
>> Okay, I want to tell you
that what you're describing
is very unusual, okay?
>> Okay.
>> I'm not saying it won't
happen, but it'll be a very
unusual family that will agree
to that.
>> Yeah.
>> If they do, that's great,
but the thing you need to find
out now, is there a willingness
for a relationship to build?
What do you want it to be like
at the hospital?
>> I don't want them to be there
the day of, just 'cause I want,
like, my time with him
and everything.
>> That makes sense.
You've got to say hello
before you can say good-bye.
>> Yeah.
>> Mm-hmm.
Cory came over later to look
at some portfolios of new
adoptive couples.
We need to focus and make
our choice together.
Here's this one.
What do you think about them?
>> I don't know.
People are different in person
than on paper.
>> That is the only portfolio
that actually stood out.
Their dog is really cute.
They can still, like,
run around and--
>> Everybody is waiting on me
at the bar.
I don't know.
I'm not gonna meet 'em yet.
'Cause now I have that whole--
>> You're gonna have to meet
them very soon.
>> Well, they're gonna have to
work around my work schedule.
[phone buzzing]
All right, I'm only gonna be
a few more minutes.
Later.
>> Here's this one.
>> Are they up for open
adoption?
>> What do you want in
an open adoption?
>> Be able to see him.
>> I know, but--
>> Be part of his life.
>> Like, how often do
you expect--
>> Two weekends out of the month
would be great.
>> Two weekends?
>> I don't even know anymore.
>> Did something make you
change?
>> Yeah, the whole
Brian-Jen situation.
>> But you're still set on this.
>> No.
I got some thinking to do.
>> You have to be on board.
[phone buzzes]
>> Not today.
I'm not gonna be in any shape
to talk to anybody later.
>> [mumbles]
[sobs]
>> What's the matter?
>> What's up?
>> Cory's not being supportive.
Time is running out.
He's making choosing adoption
even harder than it needs to be.
>> Since Cory is making this
so difficult, my parents and I
are moving forward and meeting
a new adoptive couple.
>> Hey.
>> Hi.
>> How are you?
>> Good, how are you?
I hope this couple turns out
better than Jen and Brian.
>> What kind of adoption
were you looking into?
>> Open adoption.
We feel, as potential parents,
we would be doing an injustice
to our child if we told them,
you know, "We don't know a thing
about you," you know?
Or about your mom,
know nothing about your dad
and trying to close a door on
it, and that's just not
what we want.
>> Yeah.
>> This will be your child.
And whatever you will allow us
to do in terms of contact,
we will--we would greatly
appreciate it.
>> I wouldn't expect, like,
every single week, by any means.
Like, even if it was just,
like, pictures.
>> Yeah.
>> Just to see him grow up
and everything.
>> We understand that.
You need to feel comfortable
for the rest of your life
knowing you made a perfect
decision.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, I mean, we totally,
completely understand that.
>> Like, yeah.
>> And we appreciate that.
>> That's good, yeah.
I really like these guys.
I think they'd make great
parents, and Cory might even
like them too.
We talked about baby names
and agreed on Aidan.
Thank you so much.
They even want to have a special
adoption ceremony to mark
the occasion.
Now that I've found the adoptive
parents, I feel better about
this decision.
I love them.
I couldn't have found, like,
a better family.
They're awesome.
>> That's good.
What does Cory think about it?
>> I don't think he's gonna
take it very well.
It's hit him hard, the fact
that he can't keep him.
>> And I have a feeling that
something's gonna happen with
Cory, and it's not gonna
be good.
>> Cory hasn't fully accepted
my decision to move forward
with the new adoptive parents.
But I don't have any more time
to try and convince him.
>> You know you're officially
term now, which means that you
could go into labor any time.
>> Yeah.
>> So I want us to have a plan.
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Now, do you want the baby
to stay with us in the room
while...
>> Mm-hmm.
>> Okay.
>> Stay in the room.
>> For your whole
hospitalization?
Have you thought about that?
>> Mm-mm.
>> Personally, that sounds
really painful to me.
>> In terms of physically,
after just delivering or just--
>> No, I'm thinking of
emotionally.
>> Emotionally.
>> It's just such an intense
time, and I think if you're
thinking about placing the baby,
that's gonna be pretty hard.
>> Mm-hmm.
[groans]
After nine months of being
pregnant, I can't believe
my due date is here.
But the baby isn't ready yet.
So I wait and wait and wait
for my contractions to start.
>> Yeah.
Since I was four days past
my due date, Dr. Kessler called
and suggested I be induced
at the hospital.
I texted Cory at work and told
him it was time.
>> Come on.
Let's go.
>> I'm really getting nervous.
I know this is gonna be tough.
>> Give me your arm.
>> Okay.
>> Are you feeling anything now,
Lori?
You're contracting.
>> I am?
>> Right now, yeah.
>> Wow.
>> All right.
>> Even though Cory is still
on the fence, he wants to be
here, and I think he should.
Hi.
>> Welcome.
>> My mom was less than
thrilled.
[monitor beeping]
>> That's just--
she's made a big change.
She's, like, 7 to 8.
>> Finally, it was time to push.
I decided to get an epidural
to avoid the real pain.
>> What I'm going to do is,
I'm going to have you pull up
on me.
Okay, there you go.
That's better.
>> I want you to push
through your fear.
Okay, it's time.
You can do it.
Okay, now take a deep breath
and push.
Push like you're trying to poop.
Push as hard as you can.
Go, go, girl.
Now take a deep breath.
Come back and do it again.
Push, push hard, push hard.
Go, go.
Everything you got.
>> Five, six.
>> Go, go.
>> Seven, eight, nine, ten.
And again, one more time.
And push.
>> Push hard, honey.
Push hard.
Come on, that's it.
Nice job.
You are in the right place.
Go, go, girl.
>> Seven, eight.
>> Nice, that's it.
That's it.
You're in the right place.
That's it, Lori, right there.
>> And ah.
>> Push, push, push.
>> One.
>> Think how much you want this
to be over.
>> Eight.
>> Nice one.
>> You got it. You got it.
>> Seven.
>> Come on.
You get him out of there.
You think how much you want
to be done with this.
Make it a good one.
>> Come on, Lori.
Baby's right there.
>> Six.
>> Go-go-go-go-go-go.
That's it. That's it.
You're in the right place.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is it.
>> Hi.
>> It's nice to look at you.
Mommy needs to see you
right now.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Aw.
>> He says hi.
>> Hi.
>> Hi, baby.
[baby cries]
>> So sweet.
>> You got it?
>> You want to take pictures
of him once?
>> Yeah.
>> I'm so proud of you.
You did it.
[baby cries]
>> He looks great.
>> You all right?
>> I'm good.
>> The reality of this adoption
is hitting Cory hard.
>> My mom's hurt.
>> And none--nobody else is?
My family doesn't want me
to give him up.
My grandpa straight up told me
he's disappointed in our choice.
>> I'm sorry he feels that way,
but I don't.
>> I'm sorry that you--
>> Cory, look at us.
>> I'm sorry that you don't have
the support that I have.
>> Look at us.
>> Yeah, look at us because
of your dumb mom.
She's been causing problems
since day one.
>> Dad, get him out.
Dad, get him out.
Oh, my God.
[whimpering]
>> You need to discuss it later.
>> Hold on.
>> I cannot believe you.
>> Cory, easy.
Quit.
>> I'm doing anything--
>> You're pissed off.
>> Give me my son
so I can say good-bye.
>> Not if you're pissed off.
>> Give me my son
so I can say good-bye, please.
>> Okay, I'll stay.
I'll stay in here.
>> I can't get under your arm.
See you later.
Here.
>> Here, he's fine.
>> [sobbing]
>> I'm going.
>> [sobs]
>> Take a deep breath.
Just relax.
You're fine.
You're gonna be fine tonight.
He's okay.
Everybody's good.
Okay?
>> Yeah.
>> What a [bleep] day.
>> If it's this hard
watching Cory say good-bye,
how am I gonna do it?
[baby coos]
I can't believe how fast
these two days have flown by.
It's already time for
the adoption ceremony.
I'm nervous, but I have to stay
true to my decision.
>> * Can you feel it *
* Is it true *
>> This is Aidan.
We're here to celebrate
adoption, celebrate this
wonderful life, and to celebrate
these families that have been
united.
There's never too many people
loving a child.
And this is his as you give him
to his new parents.
>> [sniffs]
>> * Life goes on *
* I have to go *
>> Thank you.
>> [sobbing quietly]
* *
>> * To feel much better soon *
>> You are so lucky.
>> Thank you.
>> We are all so lucky.
>> I have to remind myself
that in an open adoption,
saying good-bye is only
temporary.
[sniffs]
This pregnancy, by far,
has been the hardest thing
I have gone through.
>> You all right?
>> I do wish my parents
would not have tried to push
the adoption so hard.
>> I was really panicking,
but you know, all those fears
are gone.
>> Yeah.
I wish I would have taken it
more seriously from the
beginning, not waiting till
I was four or five months along
to stop and think about what
I was gonna do and how I was
gonna do it.
After the pregnancy, it feels
like a fresh start.
[shrieking]
Been having fun and finishing
off my senior year good.
[screaming]
>> That was awesome.
>> Cory and I have been through
a lot.
We were both on different pages
throughout the whole thing,
and it's a lot harder for him
to come to terms with it
than it was for me.
So how have you been?
I've been a little concerned.
>> I don't know.
I guess in the beginning,
it was really hard.
I mean, I got too attached
at the hospital,
and I know I shouldn't have.
>> I know, but we will always
be a part of his life, always,
till the day one of us--
both of us die.
Like, when I see you in him--
I'll show you a picture.
Like, now he looks like you.
I do know that we both agree
on one thing, and that's that
this was the best thing for
Aidan, and I think that will
always kind of hold us together.
I don't understand why
my birth mother chose adoption.
I have never had her here
to explain to me her reasons.
She must have felt like she
couldn't do it.
I absolutely know what that
feels like firsthand now.
I wanted to parent more than
anything, and I still do,
and one day, I will be a mom.
And that is for sure.
>> What are you scared of?
>> Everything.
>> What size is that?
>> Size 13.
>> Wow.
Going behind her back,
picking her up,
just so that they can have
contact to see each other.
I just don't think that that was
a responsible move as a parent.
>> I really love you.
I really, really don't want
to lose you.
>> [screams]
[crying]
>> Baby's just not gonna fit.
>> It hurts!
>> I know.
>> Could be a C-section.
[whimsical folk music]
* *
[singer singing]
>> * Don't know how I'm gonna *
* Get through it all *
* And I'm weak *
* But I'm strong enough to see *