>> I JUST LOVE THE BACK OF IT.
HI, MY NAME'S SARAH.
I'M 16, AND I LIVE IN
CHICKAMAUGA, GEORGIA,
RIGHT ACROSS THE BORDER FROM
CHATTANOOGA, TENNESSEE.
I LOVE BEING OUTDOORS AND
SPENDING TIME WITH MY FRIENDS.
[chime dings]
AND AFTER HIGH SCHOOL, I REALLY
WANT TO STUDY JOURNALISM IN
COLLEGE.
[laughs]
I LIVE WITH MY MOM AND TWO
BROTHERS.
MY DAD LEFT WHEN I WAS YOUNGER,
BUT I'VE BEEN SUPER CLOSE WITH
MY MOM EVER SINCE.
SHE EVEN DOES MY HAIR AND MAKEUP
EVERY MORNING.
I LIKE HAVING IT DONE.
I JUST DON'T LIKE DOING IT.
THE ONLY PERSON I'M CLOSER TO IS
MY BOYFRIEND, BLAKE.
WE MET IN SIXTH GRADE, AND WE'VE
BEEN DATING OFF AND ON FOR FIVE
YEARS.
BLAKE LOVES WORKING ON BOATS AND
GOING FISHING.
>> WE CAN GO FISHING FOR CRAPPIE
AND BASS.
>> ALL THE FISH LOOK THE SAME TO
ME.
ONE DAY HE HOPES TO BE A SHRIMP
BOAT CAPTAIN.
MY MOM AND BLAKE DON'T ALWAYS
SEE EYE TO EYE, ESPECIALLY SINCE
HE DROPPED OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL
LAST YEAR AFTER FALLING BEHIND
ON HIS GRADE.
NOW HE WORKS A FEW HOURS A WEEK
AT THE LOCAL GROCERY STORE
AND SPENDS THE REST OF HIS TIME
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES AT MY HOUSE.
BUT THEY'LL HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO GET ALONG SOON BECAUSE I'M
PREGNANT.
BLAKE AND I RECENTLY FOUND OUT
WE'RE HAVING A GIRL AND ARE
NAMING HER TINLEIGH.
OH, NO, I GOT IT CAUGHT
ON A TREE.
WE'RE TRYING TO ENJOY EVERY
MINUTE OF SUMMER VACATION
TOGETHER, 'CAUSE WE WON'T HAVE
MUCH TIME TO OURSELVES AFTER
THE BABY COMES.
REMEMBER WHENEVER WE WERE
OUTSIDE THE SCHOOL AND I DREW
ALL OVER YOU WITH THE SHARPIES?
>> YEAH.
WHAT, FIRST TIME WE MET,
WASN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
WHY DID YOU DECIDE TO ASK ME
OUT?
LIKE, WHAT'D YOU--
>> YOU'RE JUST CUTE AND FUN,
AND I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
INTERESTING.
YOU WAS PRETTY FUN GIRL TO TALK
TO AND HANG OUT WITH, SO...
>> I GUESS SOMETIMES, LIKE,
I WISH THAT WE HAD JUST, LIKE,
HAD A LITTLE BIT LONGER, JUST ME
AND YOU, BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, I HAD GOTTEN BIRTH
CONTROL OR SOMETHING THAT WE
SHOULD HAVE THOUGHT ABOUT THEN,
I GUESS.
DO YOU WISH WE HAD?
>> YEAH.
YEAH, SOMETIMES.
BUT SOMETIMES NOT SO MUCH,
JUST BECAUSE WE'VE ALREADY MADE
IT THIS FAR, BEING TEENAGERS
AND, YOU KNOW, BEING KIDS.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, MAYBE WE CAN MAKE
IT BEING GROWN.
PRETTY CONFIDENT WE WILL.
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, I THINK SO.
WHEN BLAKE AND I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, WE WERE REALLY SCARED
TO TELL OUR PARENTS, ESPECIALLY
MY MOM.
SHE NEVER LIKED BLAKE THAT MUCH
BEFORE, AND THE BABY NEWS DIDN'T
MAKE THEIR RELATIONSHIP ANY
BETTER.
NEEDLESS TO SAY, MY MOM TOTALLY
FREAKED.
BUT SINCE BLAKE DOESN'T GET
ALONG WITH HIS FAMILY, SHE
DECIDED TO PUT ASIDE HER
DIFFERENCES AND LET HIM MOVE IN
SO HE CAN BE HERE FOR THE BABY.
BUT BLAKE STILL HASN'T GIVEN UP
HIS DREAM OF GOING DOWN TO
SOUTH GEORGIA TO WORK ON
A SHRIMPING BOAT.
>> [sighs]
WELL, I KNOW WHEN, YOU KNOW,
I FOUND OUT YOU WERE PREGNANT,
I PROBABLY DIDN'T HAVE THE
REACTION YOU EXPECTED.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, THE WHOLE NIGHT,
I KEPT THINKING, YOU KNOW, THAT,
YOU KNOW, YOU WOULD NEVER DO
THIS.
I KNEW, YOU KNOW, YOU HAD DREAMS
TO GO TO SCHOOL FOR JOURNALISM.
AND, YOU KNOW, IT JUST, LIKE,
TOTALLY CHANGES YOUR LIFE PLAN.
>> AND NOW BLAKE LIVES HERE WITH
US, SO IT'S KIND OF A BIG
CHANGE.
>> SOMETIMES I WONDER IF THAT
WAS THE RIGHT DECISION.
>> YOU AND BLAKE, SOMETIMES YOU
LIKE EACH OTHER, AND SOMETIMES
YOU REALLY DON'T LIKE EACH
OTHER.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE WAY
THAT HE TREATS YOU SOMETIMES.
I WANT HAPPINESS FOR YOU AND
TINLEIGH, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> AND HOPEFULLY HE'LL BE
SUPPORTIVE AND, YOU KNOW,
DO WHAT HE NEEDS TO DO.
>> SOMETIMES HE TALKS ABOUT JUST
GETTING HIS G.E.D.
>> DO YOU THINK HE'S GONNA STAY
UNTIL TINLEIGH'S BORN AND THEN
GO BACK?
>> IT'S JUST SOMETHING THAT WE
HAVE TO, LIKE, THINK ABOUT AND
TALK ABOUT.
I'M GONNA TRY TO CONVINCE HIM TO
STAY HERE WITH US BECAUSE I WANT
HIM TO HELP WITH THE BABY.
>> IF HE WANTS TO BE WITH YOU,
THEN HE'LL DO THE THINGS THAT
YOU TELL HIM HE NEEDS TO DO.
>> YEAH.
GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> I'M DUE IN JUST FOUR WEEKS,
AND BLAKE AND I STILL HAVE A TON
OF STUFF TO GET FOR THE BABY'S
ROOM.
>> [bleep].
>> YEAH.
>> ALRIGHTY.
SO DID YOU GET SICK THIS
MORNING?
>> NO, NOT YET.
>> WHAT USUALLY MAKES YOU SICK?
>> STUFF WITH A LOT OF SUGAR...
AND MILK.
HOW'S YOUR CEREAL?
YOU'RE DEFINITELY NOT A MORNING
PERSON.
THE THING IS, BLAKE DOESN'T
REALLY LIKE LIVING UNDER MY
MOM'S RULES.
[chime dings]
SHE EXPECTS HIM TO HELP OUT WITH
CHORES AROUND THE HOUSE AND SAVE
AT LEAST $10 A WEEK FROM HIS
PAYCHECK TO HELP ME PAY FOR
DIAPERS.
BUT BLAKE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
KEEPING UP HIS END OF THE
BARGAIN.
[electronic explosions]
>> HOW ARE THINGS GOING AT HOME?
>> BETWEEN BLAKE AND MOM, THEY
STILL AREN'T TALKING, AND SO
IT'S KIND OF LIKE...
>> CAN'T IMAGINE, THOUGH, LIVING
AT HOME WITH SOME IN-LAWS AND
HAVING A BABY.
>> IT'S STRESSFUL THAT THEY
CAN'T JUST, LIKE, TALK OR
SOMETHING.
>> I THINK YOUR MOM, SHE REALLY
DOES WANT WHAT'S BEST.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, KIND OF
ANNOYING SOMETIMES THAT SHE
JUST, LIKE, KEEPS ON AND ON
AND ON.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT BLAKE WILL
LEAVE BECAUSE OF THE STUFF WITH
HIM AND YOUR MOM?
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO BE,
LIKE, WITHOUT HIM.
I CARE ENOUGH ABOUT HIM THAT,
LIKE, IT MAKES ME LOVE HIM
ENOUGH TO, LIKE, WORK EVERY--ALL
OF OUR PROBLEMS OUT, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, DO YOU EVER THINK THAT
IF BLAKE DECIDED TO GO DOWN
THERE, THAT YOU AND HIM--THAT
YOU AND TINLEIGH AND HIM WOULD
GO?
>> I MEAN, I REALLY WANT TO
FINISH SCHOOL, SO THAT WOULD BE,
LIKE, A HUGE THING TO THINK
ABOUT.
WHAT'S BEST FOR THE FUTURE?
HOW'S IT GOING WITH THE BOAT?
>> IT'S GOING GOOD.
JUST CLEANING.
>> I WAS KIND OF HOPING THAT,
FOR THE FIRST FEW MONTHS AT
LEAST, WE COULD BE HERE TOGETHER
TO, LIKE, TAKE CARE OF THE BABY
AND STUFF.
>> I WANT TO STAY HERE UNTIL
SHE'S BORN AT LEAST, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> THEN GO DOWN THERE AND TRY TO
WORK.
>> WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE IN THE
AMOUNT OF MONEY YOU'D MAKE IF WE
STAY HERE AND IF YOU GO THERE?
>> WELL, $400 A WEEK HERE WILL
PROBABLY BE ABOUT THE MAX I CAN
MAKE RIGHT NOW.
THAT AIN'T THAT GOOD.
BUT IN GOING DOWN THERE, YOU CAN
MAKE FROM $200 TO $1,000 EASY.
>> I MEAN, IT MAKES SENSE FOR
THE MONEY, BUT I DON'T REALLY
WANT TO BE THAT FAR APART.
>> YEAH, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> WELL, WHAT WOULD YOU BE DOING
ON THE BOAT, LIKE,
SHRIMPING-WISE?
>> I'D BE A DECKHAND, OF COURSE.
PULLING THE NETS UP.
AND ALL YOU DO IS SORT 'EM.
>> WHY CAN'T YOU JUST FIND A JOB
HERE?
>> I COULD STAY HERE FOR
A LITTLE BIT I GUESS, BUT WE
JUST NEED THE MONEY.
>> IT'S JUST GONNA BE HARD FOR
ME TO TAKE CARE OF A BABY AND GO
TO SCHOOL AND DO EVERYTHING
I HAVE TO DO WITHOUT ANYBODY,
LIKE, REALLY HELPING ME.
>> IT'S WHATEVER YOU WANT ME TO
DO, REALLY.
>> WELL, RIGHT NOW I THINK WE
SHOULD BOTH STAY HERE.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S HOPE EVERYTHING WORKS
OUT LIKE WE WANT IT TO.
WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> I HOPE BLAKE IS SERIOUS ABOUT
STAYING HERE.
[chime dings]
'CAUSE I REALLY WANT HIM IN
TINLEIGH'S LIFE.
>> SO I TALKED TO BLAKE ABOUT
STAYING UP HERE AND WORKING,
AND I THINK HE'S CONSIDERING IT.
>> I WORRY THAT Y'ALL ARE GONNA,
YOU KNOW, LEAVE AND GO DOWN TO
SOUTH GEORGIA ONCE THE BABY'S
BORN.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S A GOOD
IDEA, BECAUSE I THINK YOU NEED
TO FINISH HIGH SCHOOL AT LEAST
BEFORE YOU DO THAT.
I'M LETTING HIM STAY HERE IN OUR
HOUSE SO HE CAN BE HERE FOR YOU
AND THE BABY.
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE IT'S SO MUCH HARDER
WITH A BABY.
IT'S A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
I WANT YOU TO BE HONEST WITH ME.
I DON'T WANT IT TO BE
A SURPRISE, LIKE, "OH, WE'RE
MOVING NEXT MONTH, MOM."
I WANT TO KNOW AHEAD OF TIME,
YOU KNOW?
>> WELL, DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> WELL, I REALLY HOPE SO.
I JUST DON'T REALLY TRUST HIM.
>> MY DUE DATE IS ONLY A MONTH
AWAY, SO IT'S TIME FOR A
DOCTOR'S CHECKUP TO MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
>> OKAY, I NEED TO MEASURE YOUR
TUMMY AND LISTEN TO YOUR BABY'S
HEART RATE.
ARE YOU LOOKING FORWARD TO BEING
A DADDY?
>> IT'S SCARY.
>> YOU HAVE THE ROUTE TO A
HOSPITAL MAPPED OUT?
>> NO, I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE
IT'S AT.
>> UH-HUH.
OKAY, OH, YOU'RE MEASURING
PERFECTLY.
YOU'RE MEASURING 36 TO 37.
SO I'D LIKE TO TRY AND SEE IF
I CAN REACH YOUR CERVIX TODAY
AND SEE IF IT'S THINNING OUT
AND DILATING.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
I'M SORRY.
>> THAT ONE HURTS.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA REALLY HAVE
TO REACH IF I'M GONNA FIND IT.
>> IT HURTS.
>> OKAY, WE CAN WAIT TILL NEXT
WEEK IF YOU LIKE.
THE BABY'S HEAD'S LOW.
CERVIX IS JUST VERY POSTERIOR.
ALL RIGHT, YOU DOING OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING ABOUT
SCHOOL?
>> ONLINE.
>> SO YOU ARE GONNA GO BACK AND
GET YOUR DEGREE, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND WHAT ABOUT YOU, BLAKE?
>> I'LL PROBABLY JUST HAVE TO
GO DO MY G.E.D. SOMEWHERE.
>> YEAH, Y'ALL NEED TO BE
GETTING YOUR HIGH SCHOOL
DIPLOMA, OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GONNA BE OF EVERY
ADVANTAGE.
OKAY.
>> MY MOM WANTS BLAKE TO FINISH
SCHOOL TOO.
THAT MEANS HE'LL HAVE TO STOP
PLAYING VIDEO GAMES AND START
HELPING GET THE BABY'S ROOM
READY WHILE I WORK ON MY ONLINE
PREP COURSE, SO I CAN GET
A HEAD START ON SENIOR YEAR IN
THE FALL.
>> Y'ALL REALLY NEED TO FIND OUT
ABOUT THE BED TODAY.
>> TODAY BLAKE PROMISED TO PICK
UP A CRIB FROM MY AUNT, BUT WHEN
THE TIME CAME TO GET IT,
HE DITCHED ME AND WENT OFF WITH
HIS FRIEND.
>> WHERE'S HE OFF TO NOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> MAKING A TO-DO LIST.
I HOPE HE TAKES THE HINT AND
DOES THE THINGS ON THE LIST...
[chime dings]
'CAUSE MY MOM ISN'T GONNA PUT UP
WITH HIS ATTITUDE MUCH LONGER.
[line ringing]
>> HEY.
>> I WROTE A LIST OF THINGS I
NEED YOU TO DO WHEN YOU GET
HOME, AND I'M JUST GONNA READ IT
TO YOU SO THAT, UM--
>> TELL HIM--OR IF HE CAN HEAR
ME--THAT HE LIVES HERE FOR FREE
AND THAT HE NEEDS TO DO WHATEVER
HE'S ASKED TO DO.
>> I NEED YOU TO GO PICK UP THE
CRIB FROM MY AUNT, BECAUSE
TINLEIGH WILL BE HERE ANY DAY,
AND SHE NEEDS SOMETHING TO
SLEEP IN.
>> THIS STUFF NEEDS TO GET DONE,
AND, YOU KNOW, SHE'S PREGNANT.
YOU NEED TO HELP HER OUT.
I GUESS WHEN I GET OFF WORK,
I CAN DO IT.
>> YOU DON'T WORK ALL THE TIME.
YOUR JOB IS NOT THAT HARD.
IT MAY TAKE A FEW DAYS.
IT'S JUST THAT...
ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA GET EASIER
WHEN THERE'S A BABY.
>> REALLY GOOD TO BE OUT THE
HOUSE, MAN.
I DON'T LIKE BEING HOME OR AT
THE HOUSE.
YOU KNOW HOW I AM.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD, MAN.
IT'S GONNA BE A LOT DIFFERENT.
IT'S A WHOLE NOTHER BIT OF
RESPONSIBILITY.
BESIDES TAKING CARE OF MYSELF,
I GOT TO TAKE CARE OF TWO OTHER
PEOPLE.
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH, AND, LIKE, I STILL WANT
TO BE A KID, IN A WAY, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, DON'T I WANT TO BE A
KIDDIE-KID, BUT BEFORE
TINLEIGH'S HERE, YOU KNOW,
I WANT TO HAVE FUN.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE OUT HERE RIGHT
NOW.
I WANT TO HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
FUN.
>> I DON'T--I DON'T WANT TO.
I CAN'T TAKE IT.
SOMETIMES I'D RATHER JUST PAY
CHILD SUPPORT AND GET OUT OF
HERE.
>> EVEN AFTER GIVING HIM HIS
TO-DO LIST, BLAKE STILL DOESN'T
SEEM TO BE PUTTING IN MUCH
EFFORT.
HE STAYED OUT WITH HIS FRIEND
ALL NIGHT.
WAKE UP.
WE NEED TO PICK UP THE CRIB
TODAY FROM MY AUNT.
WE REALLY HAVE SO MUCH TO DO
BEFORE THE BABY COMES.
>> YEAH, YOU DO, AND HE'S REALLY
PISSING ME OFF.
DID HE EVER EVEN CALL HER ABOUT
THE CRIB?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S LIKE TALKING TO A BRICK
WALL.
>> WELL, ALL HE HAS TO DO IS GO
GET IT AND PUT IT TOGETHER.
>> I CAN'T KEEP WAITING FOR IT.
>> NO.
WHY ISN'T HE DOING ANYTHING
FOR YOU?
>> HE'S LIKE, "WELL, YOUR MOM
DOES EVERYTHING FOR YOU," AND
I'M LIKE, "WELL"--
>> THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I DO THINGS FOR YOU BECAUSE HE
DON'T.
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I TOLD HIM.
I WAS LIKE, "YOU DON'T OFFER,
OR YOU WON'T DO ANYTHING THAT
I WANT YOU TO DO."
>> YOU DON'T NEED THIS RIGHT
NOW.
YOU'RE 8 1/2 MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND YOU DON'T NEED THE STRESS.
>> YEAH.
>> HE BETTER START TAKING
RESPONSIBILITY, BECAUSE I'M NOT
GONNA TOLERATE THIS BEHAVIOR.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S SO IMMATURE.
WHEN IS HE GONNA START GIVING
YOU MONEY FOR THE BABY INSTEAD
OF SPENDING IT ALL ON HIMSELF?
>> YEAH.
BLAKE HASN'T SAID ANYTHING ABOUT
GETTING THE CRIB, AND IT'S
REALLY ANNOYING ME AND MY MOM.
SHE WOULDN'T EVEN RIDE IN THE
SAME CAR WITH US TO MY DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT TODAY.
>> WHY'D YOUR MOM TAKE A
DIFFERENT CAR, YOU THINK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
PISSES ME OFF, MORE AND MORE
I THINK ABOUT IT.
THAT'S WHY I DON'T LIKE STAYING
HERE.
IT'S 'CAUSE I'M NOT WELCOME.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE SO COOL.
"ASK ME TO DO IT.
ASK ME TO DO IT."
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO BEG YOU TO
DO [bleep] FOR YOUR OWN KID.
>> AND DO WHAT?
LIKE, WHAT IS THERE TO DO?
>> THERE'S PLENTY OF [bleep]
TO DO.
>> OKAY THEN, WELL, I'LL DO
THAT FOR YOU.
>> BLAKE, CAN YOU GET OFF
YOUR ASS?
>> DO YOU DO ANYTHING?
>> I DO WAY MORE THAN YOU DO.
>> THAT'S BULL[bleep], THOUGH.
>> NO.
>> SHUT UP.
I'M TIRED OF LISTENING TO YOU
ALREADY.
RIDE WITH YOUR MOM BACK HOME,
DAMN, PLEASE.
>> WHILE WE WAITED FOR THEM TO
SCHEDULE MY NEXT APPOINTMENT,
THE TENSION BETWEEN BLAKE AND MY
MOM STARTED STRESSING ME OUT.
>> I NEED TO GET TINLEIGH'S BED.
IT'S JUST STRESSING ME OUT,
HER NOT HAVING A PLACE TO SLEEP.
SHE NEEDS HER BED.
>> DID YOU TEXT HER ABOUT
GETTING THE BED?
>> MM-MM.
NOT YET.
>> WELL, LET'S MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
BABY NEEDS A BED.
>> I'M MAKING IT A POINT TO ASK
YOU TO DO SOMETHING, SO IF YOU
COULD DO IT, THAT WOULD BE
GREAT.
>> OKAY, GOD DAMN.
DUMBASS.
>> PLEASE DON'T TALK TO HER
LIKE THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU LIVE IN OUR HOUSE.
>> Y'ALL TALK LIKE THAT TO ME
ALL THE TIME.
>> I DIDN'T CALL YOU ANY NAMES.
>> OKAY.
>> AND IT JUST PISSES ME OFF.
>> HOW?
>> [scoffs]
HOW?
>> BECAUSE YOU DON'T [bleep]
LIKE GOING ANYWAY.
>> HEY, YES, I DO.
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE OF HER, SHE MAKES ME
FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE.
YOU WANT ME TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU?
I'M BEING HONEST WITH YOU
RIGHT NOW.
SHE MAKES ME FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE
AT MY OWN BABY'S DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT.
I JUST DON'T EVEN WANT TO PUT UP
WITH IT.
LIKE, THAT'S WHY I DON'T SAY
NOTHING.
>> OKAY.
>> JUST 'CAUSE I DON'T FEEL LIKE
LISTENING TO LIP FROM BOTH OF
Y'ALL.
I CAN'T DO IT WITH TWO PEOPLE
TAG-TEAMING ME WHEN I'M THERE,
YOU AND YOUR MOM, LIKE, [bleep].
SHE AIN'T IN THIS RELATIONSHIP.
WHY DOES SHE HAVE TO START IN
ON ME?
I DO WANT TO LEAVE.
>> YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT IT.
I TOLD YOU I NEED TO STAY HERE
AND FINISH HIGH SCHOOL, BUT IT
WOULD BE--IF YOU WOULD BE THAT
MUCH HAPPIER SOMEWHERE ELSE--
>> I WOULD.
>> THEN LEAVE.
>> I WILL.
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE DOWN THERE
SPENDING ALL YOUR [bleep] MONEY.
>> NO, I WON'T.
>> BULL[bleep].
THAT'S WHY YOU DON'T EVEN SHARE
MONEY UP HERE.
WHY WOULD IT BE ANY DIFFERENT
WHEN I--ESPECIALLY WHEN I--
>> A PAYCHECK IS 150 BUCKS.
>> YEAH, AND YOU WASTE ALL YOUR
MONEY, BLAKE.
THE ONLY MONEY THAT YOU SPEND
LOGICALLY IS THE MONEY THAT I'M
LIKE, "YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T DO
THAT."
>> AND DOWN THERE I'LL BE
MAKING, LIKE, $1,000, SO I'LL
HAVE MONEY TO SAVE.
>> AND THAT'S A LOT MORE MONEY
TO GO BLOW FOR YOU.
>> OKAY, I WILL.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I WANT TO
WITH IT.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU DO WITH YOUR
MONEY ANYWAYS.
>> OKAY, THEN.
IT'S MY MONEY.
I WORKED FOR IT.
IT'S MINE.
>> THAT'S NOT HOW IT SHOULD BE
IF YOU WANT TO BE WITH SOMEBODY.
>> OKAY.
WELL, I GUESS I DON'T WANT TO BE
WITH YOU.
>> AFTER DRIVING AROUND ARGUING
FOR A WHILE, I TEXTED MY MOM
ABOUT BLAKE THREATENING TO
LEAVE.
I FIGURED SHE'D BE PRETTY PISSED
BY THE TIME WE GOT HOME.
ALL I'M ASKING YOU TO DO IS
SOMETHING FOR YOUR KID.
>> OKAY, WHATEVER.
THAT'S WHAT YOU ALWAYS SAY.
>> WHAT?
I KNOW YOU DIDN'T JUST CALL ME
A BITCH.
>> WHY DID YOU CALL HER THAT?
WHY?
>> 'CAUSE.
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHY.
I DON'T APPRECIATE YOU
DISRESPECTING MY DAUGHTER
LIKE THAT.
>> YOU, LIKE, MUMBLED IT.
IF YOU'RE GONNA SAY IT, SAY IT
SO SOMEBODY CAN HEAR YOU.
>> YEAH, I STILL HEARD YOU.
>> WHAT DID SHE DO, BLAKE?
>> WILL YOU STOP?
>> NO, I WON'T.
>> OH, GOD, YOU'RE [bleep]
CRAZY.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
BECAUSE I LOVE MY DAUGHTER?
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE I DON'T APPRECIATE
YOU DISRESPECTING HER LIKE THAT?
>> OKAY, STOP.
I'M TRYING TO TALK TO HER,
NOT YOU.
I AIN'T GOT NOTHING TO SAY TO
YOU.
I NEVER DO.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE TALKING
TO YOU.
>> I DON'T HAVE NOTHING TO SAY
TO YOU EITHER.
>> THEN WHY ARE YOU TALKING
TO ME?
>> YOU DON'T THINK ABOUT MONEY.
YOU GO BLOW [bleep] WHEN YOU GOT
A BABY COMING--
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> BULL[bleep].
YOU CAN LEAVE.
>> OKAY.
>> BLAKE DIDN'T COME HOME THAT
NIGHT.
HE TEXTED AND SAID HE WAS
STAYING AT HIS FRIEND'S HOUSE.
SINCE HE WASN'T AROUND THE NEXT
DAY, MY MOM HAD TO GO PICK UP
THE CRIB FROM MY AUNT.
IT SUCKS NOT HAVING BLAKE'S
HELP.
HE CAN'T KEEP LETTING ME AND HIS
DAUGHTER DOWN.
LIKE, I DON'T THINK PUTTING HER
FIRST HAS HIT HIM YET.
>> WOULD YOU BE SAD IF HE LEFT?
>> I'D BE REALLY HURT IF HE
LEFT, LIKE, BECAUSE WE HAVE SO
MUCH HISTORY.
BUT I WOULD BE MORE UPSET THAT
HE WASN'T THERE TO, LIKE, SEE
TINLEIGH WHEN SHE TOOK HER FIRST
BREATH, THAN I WOULD BE THAT HE
WASN'T THERE WHEN I WAS IN A TON
OF PAIN, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
MY DAD WAS NEVER THERE FOR ME.
LIKE, ME AND MY DAD NEVER
TALKED; LIKE, WE NEVER HAD
A RELATIONSHIP.
LIKE, I WANT TINLEIGH TO HAVE
A DAD AND TO HAVE--LIKE, TO BE
A DADDY'S GIRL, JUST BECAUSE
I NEVER HAD THAT.
I DON'T LIKE THE WAY BLAKE HAS
BEEN TREATING ME LATELY.
BUT AFTER NOT HEARING FROM HIM
ALL DAY, I WAS WORRIED HE MIGHT
NOT BE COMING BACK AT ALL.
>> YOU'RE SUCH AN ASS.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE
AN ASS[bleep].
YEAH.
>> I DON'T CARE.
THAT'S JUST GONNA MAKE ME
FATTER.
>> I'M SORRY.
>> WELL, DANG, SHOULD WE REALLY
BE TOGETHER IF WE'RE REALLY
GONNA BITCH AND MOAN AND GROAN
ALL THE TIME?
>> I'M SORRY.
>> I'M WILLING TO KEEP TRYING
TO MAKE IT WORK, BUT BLAKE NEEDS
TO START TREATING ME BETTER.
SO I WAS HAPPY THAT BLAKE
SUGGESTED WE GET OUT OF THE
HOUSE FOR A CHANGE AND SPEND
SOME TIME TOGETHER.
>> READY FOR THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, ON THREE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
[whistle toots]
>> OOH, I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
>> ARE YOU, BABY?
>> YEAH, ARE YOU GONNA
HOLD MY HAND?
>> YEAH, I'LL HOLD YOUR HAND.
>> [giggles]
OH, MY GOSH.
THIS IS SO COOL.
YOU CAN SEE, LIKE, THE BASEBALL
FIELD DOWN THERE.
>> SO YOU WANT TO HAVE A LOT
OF FUN BEFORE TINLEIGH'S BORN?
>> YEAH.
>> SCARED?
>> SCARED.
>> I'M SCARED TOO.
SCARED [bleep]LESS.
>> ARE YOU READY?
>> YEAH, BABE.
>> HANGING OUT WITH BLAKE
REMINDS ME JUST HOW MUCH I WANT
HIM AROUND, BUT HE HAS TO FIGURE
OUT A WAY TO GET ALONG WITH MY
MOM.
>> SARAH SAID YOU WANTED TO
TALK TO ME.
>> SHE'S MY DAUGHTER,
AND I LOVE HER.
I MEAN, I WOULD DO ANYTHING
FOR HER.
AND, YOU KNOW, I'VE NOTICED,
LIKE, THERE'S A LOT OF TIMES
THAT YOU'RE, YOU KNOW,
DISRESPECTFUL TO HER AND CALL
HER NAMES AND THINGS AND--
>> THE OTHER NIGHT WAS JUST
'CAUSE, KIND OF, I WAS PISSED.
>> THERE WAS NO REASON TO CALL
HER A BITCH.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE REALLY GONNA
HAVE TO WORK ON THAT, OR YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO, YOU KNOW--
I'M NOT GONNA PUT UP WITH IT.
>> YEAH.
I AM 17 AND STUFF.
YOU KNOW, I GUESS I'M LIKE A--
I'M JUST A BOY MAKING MISTAKES,
BUT I WANT TO BETTER MYSELF.
>> YOU KNOW, WHERE--
KIND OF WHERE WE STAND.
LIKE, IF IT DOESN'T GET BETTER,
THEN, YOU KNOW, YOU'LL HAVE TO
FIND...
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, SOME...
>> SOMETHING ELSE.
>> I MEAN, YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO
STAY HERE.
>> RIGHT.
>> BECAUSE IT'S JUST TOO...
>> CHAOTIC.
>> STRESSFUL.
>> I'M GLAD MY MOM AND BLAKE
AGREED TO TALK, 'CAUSE THE BABY
COULD COME ANY DAY NOW.
THEY EVEN RODE IN THE SAME CAR
TO MY DOCTOR'S CHECKUP.
I HATE THIS PART.
>> [whispers] I'M SORRY.
>> OKAY, OW.
>> IT HURTS, IT HURTS, IT HURTS.
>> WE DON'T LET PEOPLE GO MUCH
PAST THEIR DUE DATE, YOU KNOW?
IF YOU HAVEN'T HAD BABY BY THEN,
I REALLY THINK WE NEED TO TALK
ABOUT INDUCTION.
>> I'M JUST SCARED.
[chuckles]
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE PLANS
TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL AND, LIKE,
BE IN PAIN, BUT...
>> I'M THINKING YOU NEED TO
THINK ABOUT A BABY NEXT WEEK.
>> YEAH.
HAVING THE DOCTOR INDUCE ME IS
GONNA BE REALLY PAINFUL, SO I'M
GONNA TRY TO GET THIS PROCESS
STARTED ON MY OWN.
>> "IDEAS TO INDUCE LABOR
AT HOME."
>> JUMPING JACKS.
[giggles]
LICORICE.
>> IF SHE DON'T, WE'RE GONNA BE
TAKING A TRIP TO THE BATHROOM.
EATING SPICY FOOD.
OH, MY GOD.
THEY SMELL LIKE STRAIGHT
JALAPEÑO.
THESE ARE LIKE FIRE, LIKE--
[exhales]
PINEAPPLE.
>> THESE THINGS ARE GOOD.
>> AND ACUPRESSURE.
"PRESS IN A CIRCULAR MOTION
UNTIL A CONTRACTION."
I'LL EAT A PINEAPPLE WHILE
YOU'RE CIRCULAR MOTIONING AND A
STICK TOO.
MAN.
>> ARE YOU INDUCED?
>> NOT YET.
TINLEIGH?
MOM!
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS THE
JALAPEÑO STICKS, THE PINEAPPLE,
OR THE ACUPRESSURE, BUT LATER
THAT AFTERNOON, I STARTED HAVING
SOME PAINFUL CONTRACTIONS.
I WAS FEELING REALLY NAUSEOUS
TOO, SO MY MOM DROVE ME TO THE
EMERGENCY ROOM.
BLAKE WAS STILL AT WORK, SO I
TEXTED HIM TO MEET US AT THE
HOSPITAL.
AFTER HOURS AND HOURS IN LABOR,
THE DOCTOR GAVE ME SOME
SURPRISING NEWS.
THE BABY'S HEAD WAS POSITIONED
TOO FAR TO THE SIDE, WHICH MEANT
I NEEDED TO HAVE A C-SECTION.
[soft rock music]
* *
>> * WELCOME TO *
* THE WORLD *
>> IT WASN'T THE WAY I PICTURED
IT, BUT IN THE END, TINLEIGH WAS
FINALLY HERE.
>> * I'LL HOLD YOU *
* FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE *
>> AFTER STAYING AN EXTRA DAY
IN THE HOSPITAL BECAUSE OF MY
C-SECTION, MY MOM AND MY BEST
FRIEND, HUNTER, WERE ABLE TO
DRIVE ME AND TINLEIGH HOME.
MY STOMACH WAS STILL SORE FROM
SURGERY, AND EVEN THE SMALLEST
BUMPS IN THE ROAD WERE
EXCRUCIATING.
>> YOU ALL RIGHT?
>> [sobs]
>> SHE CAN TELL WHEN HER MAMA
AIN'T HAPPY.
>> YOU'RE A MOMMY NOW.
MOMMIES CRY SOMETIMES.
I DON'T WANT YOU UPSET.
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH ENOUGH.
IF HE DON'T CHANGE OVER THIS
BABY, HE NEVER WILL.
SHE MATTERS THE MOST.
>> WHO DO YOU THINK SHE LOOKS
LIKE?
>> YOU.
SHE HAS YOUR NOSE, YOUR LIPS.
>> YOUR FAT CHEEKS.
>> YEAH, MY FAT CHEEKS.
THAT'S KIND OF WEIRD, AIN'T IT?
>> IT'S JUST DIFFERENT TO HAVE
SOMEBODY ELSE TO TAKE CARE OF.
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU AND MY MOM
ARE GETTING ALONG BETTER NOW?
>> I THINK WE ARE.
I'M TRYING.
I JUST THINK THAT SHE NEEDS HER
DADDY FOR THE FIRST PART OF
HER LIFE ANYWAY.
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T HAVE MINE,
SO...
>> YEAH.
>> I'D TAKE CARE OF YOU ALL THE
TIME IF I DIDN'T HAVE TO WORK,
I PROMISE YOU, 'CAUSE I DON'T
LIKE WORK.
MWAH.
>> NOW THAT WE HAVE A BABY TO
SUPPORT, BLAKE HAD TO GET A
FULL-TIME NIGHT SHIFT AT THE
GROCERY STORE TO MAKE EXTRA
MONEY.
THAT ALSO MEANS HE'S GONE WHILE
I'M UP TAKING CARE OF TINLEIGH.
WHAT?
[baby crying]
UGH, YOU REALLY DID GET IT
EVERYWHERE.
[baby crying]
YOU STILL HUNGRY?
[alarm buzzing]
WHEN BLAKE FINALLY GETS HOME IN
THE MORNING, HE'S TOO TIRED TO
HELP ME WITH THE BABY.
AND ALL HE DOES DURING THE DAY
IS SLEEP UNTIL IT'S TIME FOR HIS
NEXT SHIFT.
OH.
[baby crying]
I NEED TO GET YOU A NEW BLANKIE,
I KNOW.
IT'S NOT FAIR THAT HE GETS TO
SLEEP AND I DON'T.
AND EVEN WHEN HE IS AWAKE,
HE'S NOT MUCH HELP EITHER.
>> HOW DO THESE WORK?
TRUST ME, THIS IS DISGUSTING.
I WOULD NEVER, EVER WANT TO DO
THIS.
IT'S NOT THE JOB I'D WANT.
>> I KNOW BLAKE HAS TO WORK
LONG HOURS, BUT BEING A PARENT
IS A 24/7 JOB, AND HE DOESN'T
SEEM UP FOR IT.
HEY.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
SHE'S SO CUTE.
HEY, GORGEOUS.
HOW'S IT BEEN AS A FAMILY?
HAS HE--BLAKE BEEN HELPING YOU
A LOT?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
>> HE SHOULD WANT TO DO THAT.
IT SHOULDN'T JUST BE
A RESPONSIBILITY.
>> IT'S REALLY FRUSTRATING.
>> HAS HE JUST NOT BEEN SPENDING
A LOT OF TIME WITH HER?
>> NO, NOT REALLY.
I NEED HELP WITH HER TO DO
THE THINGS IN LIFE THAT I WANT
TO DO, AND OBVIOUSLY HE'S NOT
GONNA HELP ME AS MUCH AS I'LL
PROBABLY NEED IT TO BE IN SCHOOL
AND, LIKE, DO HOMEWORK AND ALL
KINDS OF OTHER STUFF, YOU KNOW?
>> AND KEEPING UP FRIENDSHIPS,
THAT'S HARD TO DO.
>> YEAH.
BUT HE DOESN'T THINK ABOUT
THINGS LIKE THAT.
LIKE, HE ONLY THINKS ABOUT,
LIKE, WHAT HE WANTS TO DO.
LIKE, I DON'T THINK HE
UNDERSTOOD WHAT NEEDED TO BE
GIVEN UP WHEN TINLEIGH WAS BORN
AND STUFF.
>> WELL, IT'S DUMB THAT YOU HAVE
TO GIVE UP MORE THAN HE DOES,
'CAUSE YOU DIDN'T MAKE YOURSELF
PREGNANT.
LIKE, HE KIND OF HELPED.
>> YEAH, LIKE, IT WASN'T JUST
ME.
[crickets chirping]
BLAKE HAS BECOME SO DISTANT.
I WISH HE WOULD START SPENDING
MORE TIME WITH ME AND TINLEIGH.
[sniffs]
>> DO YOU THINK IT'S HARDER
BEING A MOM THAN YOU THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> [chuckles]
>> IF I HAVE IT TO DO OVER,
I WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE KIDS.
>> SARAH.
>> I'M JUST NOT CUT OUT FOR
THE MOM THING.
>> IT'LL BE HARD, YOU KNOW,
WHEN YOU GO BACK TO SCHOOL TOO,
'CAUSE YOU'RE MAINLY THE ONE
THAT TAKES CARE OF HER, SO...
>> YEAH.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE HE COULD DO MORE
TO HELP YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> BLAKE SHOULDN'T BE PLAYING
VIDEO GAMES ALL THE TIME,
AND HE NEEDS TO BE WOKE UP
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT LIKE
YOU'RE WOKE UP.
>> YEAH.
>> HAS BLAKE BEEN SAVING HIS
PAYCHECKS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WE HAVEN'T REALLY TALKED
ABOUT IT.
>> WELL, THAT'S THE THINGS YOU
NEED TO TALK ABOUT.
>> WELL, WE NEVER REALLY HAVE
TIME TO TALK ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW.
>> HE NEEDS TO GIVE YOU MORE
MONEY FOR THE BABY BECAUSE IT'S
JUST GONNA KEEP GETTING MORE
EXPENSIVE.
>> YEAH.
>> AND MONEY CAUSES FIGHTS.
>> ESPECIALLY NOT HAVING IT.
>> I'VE SACRIFICED SO MUCH
ALREADY BEING A MOM.
I BARELY SLEEP ANYMORE.
I'M NOT PREPARED TO GO BACK TO
SCHOOL IN A MONTH.
AND I'VE BURNED THROUGH THE
LITTLE SAVINGS I HAVE
TAKING CARE OF THIS BABY.
MOM.
>> YEAH.
>> THERE'S ONLY ONE DIAPER LEFT.
DO WE HAVE ANY MORE?
>> NO.
WHY HASN'T HE GIVEN YOU ANY
MONEY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS HE'S BLOWING IT ON
HISSELF.
>> YEAH, HE DOES.
>> YEAH.
BLAKE REALLY NEEDS TO BE PUTTING
MORE MONEY INTO BABY SUPPLIES.
[chime dings]
BUT THE NEXT NIGHT, HE SPENT HIS
ENTIRE PAYCHECK ON FOUR NEW
TIRES FOR HIS TRUCK.
WHEN MY MOM FOUND OUT, SHE JUST
COULDN'T LET IT SLIDE.
>> IF YOU'RE GONNA CONTINUE TO
LIVE HERE, THEN YOU NEED TO
START GIVING AT LEAST $10 A WEEK
FOR THE BABY.
>> WOW.
>> THAT'S PART OF BEING
RESPONSIBLE.
>> DON'T HAVE TO GET MAD TOO.
>> 'CAUSE YOU LIVE IN OUR HOUSE,
AND YOU GO, AND YOU BLOW YOUR
DAMN MONEY ON WHATEVER THE HELL
WHILE SHE SPENDS WHAT LITTLE BIT
YOU GIVE HER ON SOMETHING
SHE ABSOLUTELY HAS TO HAVE
FOR THE BABY.
>> I GIVE HER WHAT I DON'T USE
FOR GAS SOMETIMES, BUT SOMETIMES
I DON'T.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD BE GIVING
HER MONEY.
>> YEAH, I MIGHT BE ABLE TO.
>> CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW,
IF SHE WAS WORKING, EVERY BIT
OF HER MONEY SHE HAD WOULD BE,
YOU KNOW, FOR THE BABY.
>> OKAY, DAMN.
>> WELL, IT'S TERRIBLE THAT YOU
DON'T WANT TO TRY TO GIVE
A [bleep] ABOUT HER FAMILY.
YOU [bleep] USE US.
I TRIED WHEN YOU FIRST CAME.
I WAS NICE AS COULD BE TO YOU.
I REALLY TRIED.
AND THEN I SEEN HOW YOU REALLY
ARE, AND, YOU KNOW, I KNOW.
>> OKAY, THAT'S IT.
>> [scoffs]
[soft rock music]
>> * I WON'T LIE *
* LIKE THAT ANYMORE *
* AND I CAN'T HIDE *
>> LATER THAT NIGHT, BLAKE
TEXTED AND SAID HE COULDN'T TAKE
MY MOM'S NAGGING ANYMORE AND WAS
HEADING DOWN SOUTH TO WORK ON
A SHRIMPING BOAT.
[chime dings]
>> female announcer: GET ANSWERS
TO YOUR SEX AND RELATIONSHIP
QUESTIONS AND TIPS ON HOW TO
TAKE CONTROL, AT:
>> BLAKE CAME HOME IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT TO GET HIS STUFF
AND DIDN'T EVEN SAY GOOD-BYE.
MY MOM FELT BAD FOR BLOWING UP
AT HIM AGAIN, BUT THAT'S STILL
NO EXCUSE FOR WALKING OUT
ON HIS FAMILY.
I MEAN, I DIDN'T BELIEVE HE'D
ACTUALLY LEAVE.
I MEAN, HE'S BEEN TALKING ABOUT
IT FOR FOUR MONTHS ALMOST.
>> IT KIND OF PISSES ME OFF
BECAUSE YOU'RE LEFT WITH ALL
THE RESPONSIBILITY.
I MEAN, HE'S GETTING TO GO BE
A TEENAGER.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT MAYBE HE
REALLY DID LOVE YOU,
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST THINK Y'ALL HAVE
DIFFERENT GOALS IN LIFE TOO,
'CAUSE CLEARLY YOU'RE TAKING
CARE OF YOUR CHILD, AND HE'S OFF
DOING WHATEVER.
HOW DO YOU FEEL NOW THAT HE'S
LEFT?
>> IT'D BE A LOT EASIER TO TALK
ABOUT HOW I FEEL IF YOU DIDN'T
HATE HIM.
>> I DIDN'T HATE HIM AT FIRST,
SARAH, AND YOU KNOW THAT.
>> BUT YOU DO NOW.
>> BUT HE LEFT.
THAT'S ALL I WANT YOU TO
REALIZE.
HE LEFT AND HE DIDN'T--
>> I'M NOT AN IDIOT.
I UNDERSTAND THAT.
I REALIZE HE'S NOT HERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO KEEP POINTING
IT OUT.
I UNDERSTAND.
>> NOBODY MADE HIM LEAVE,
THOUGH.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU KNOW, I NEVER EXPECTED
HIM TO LEAVE.
AND I'M SO SORRY.
>> I JUST WANTED HER TO HAVE
WHAT I DIDN'T HAVE.
>> YOU CAN'T LET HIM DRAG YOU
DOWN WHEN YOU GOT TO BE FOCUSED
ON GETTING THROUGH SCHOOL,
TAKING CARE OF THE BABY.
SHE HAS TO BE YOUR PRIORITY.
>> HOW ARE SARAH AND THE BABY
DOING, BLAKE?
>> I GUESS THEY'RE DOING
PRETTY GOOD.
>> YOU PLANNING ON GOING BACK TO
LIVE WITH HER?
>> NO, I'LL NEVER GO BACK AND
LIVE WITH THEM.
HER MOM, THOUGH, SHE'D START
IN ON ME SOMETIMES.
I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT SHE JUST
DIDN'T LIKE ME, I GUESS.
>> PARENTS DON'T LIKE YOU;
IT MAKES IT HARD ON YOU.
>> THIS RIGHT HERE IS JUST ABOUT
THE BEST THING I CAN BE DOING.
>> WHEN YOU'RE YOUNG, YOU DO
CRAZY THINGS.
>> EXACTLY.
>> SCHOOL'S GONNA START IN A FEW
WEEKS, AND I REALLY NEED TO
FINISH MY ONLINE COURSE WORK TO
STAY ON TRACK FOR GRADUATION.
BUT WITHOUT BLAKE AROUND TO HELP
ME, IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
TINLEIGH LOUISE.
[baby crying]
STOP THAT BUSINESS.
[phone ringing]
>> WHERE'S BLAKE?
>> I MEAN, I'VE TRIED CALLING
AND TEXTING HIM AND STUFF, BUT I
HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING FROM HIM,
SO...
>> I GOT TO STAY HOME AND WATCH
TINLEIGH.
I WISH I COULD GO OUT WITH YOU,
THOUGH.
BYE.
[baby crying]
I KNOW!
I FEEL THE SAME WAY!
AH!
[line ringing]
HELLO?
>> HEY.
I MISS Y'ALL.
>> SO YOU JUST LEAVE YOUR
FAMILY.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
>> LOOK, I TOLD YOU, LIKE,
FOREVER THAT I PLANNED ON GOING
SHRIMPING AND EVERYTHING.
>> SO YOU CHOOSE TO GO THREE
WEEKS AFTER I HAVE YOUR KID?
WHY DIDN'T YOU GO BEFORE?
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER.
>> DARN.
>> I'M MAKING MORE MONEY HERE,
AIN'T I?
>> I WANTED TINLEIGH TO HAVE A
GOOD RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU, AND
OBVIOUSLY IF YOU'RE NOT HERE...
BECAUSE I WASN'T CLOSE WITH MY
DAD, AND I WANTED HER TO HAVE
THAT, AND YOU KNEW THAT.
>> SHE WILL BE, THOUGH.
>> HOW, IF YOU'RE NOT HERE?
>> SHE CAN COME ON THE BOAT
WITH ME.
>> NO, SHE'S NOT EVEN GONNA KNOW
WHO YOU ARE BY THE TIME SHE'S
OLD ENOUGH TO GO ON A BOAT.
>> YES, SHE WILL.
>> OH, YOU'RE JUST PISSING ME
OFF.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO TALK TO YOU
ANYMORE.
"YOU KEEP WALKING IN AND OUT OF
MY LIFE."
YEP, THAT'S WHAT SHE'S GONNA
KNOW.
>> OKAY, THEN.
IF THAT'S THE WAY YOU FEEL.
>> THAT IS THE [bleep] WAY I
FEEL.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M GONNA
GET OFF THE PHONE WITH YOU.
>> announcer: DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
[baby crying]
>> [sniffs]
>> I HATE TO SEE YOU SAD.
>> EVERYTHING'S REALLY HARD.
LIKE, NOT BEING ABLE TO SLEEP
AND NOT BEING ABLE TO GO DO
STUFF WHEN I WANT TO.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE A BABY,
THERE ARE SOME THINGS
THAT YOU DON'T GET TO DO
LIKE YOU USED TO.
I JUST DON'T THINK TEENAGERS
REALIZE ALL THE RESPONSIBILITY
THAT COMES WITH A BABY UNTIL
THEY ACTUALLY HAVE 'EM.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU CAN'T JUST BE A TEENAGER
LIKE YOU USED TO.
>> [exhales]
>> YEAH, IT'S HARD.
>> I WISH I WOULD HAVE WAITED TO
HAVE A BABY.
>> EVERYBODY IN LIFE, YOU KNOW,
LOOKS BACK AND SAYS, "I WISH I
HAD DONE THIS DIFFERENTLY."
I'M RIGHT THERE WITH YOU.
I WISH, YOU KNOW--I WISH YOU HAD
WAITED, BUT OBVIOUSLY YOU HAVE
TINLEIGH NOW, AND THINGS ARE
GONNA BE HARDER, AND YOU JUST
HAVE TO MAKE THE MOST OF IT.
>> IT MAKES ME REALLY SAD TO
THINK THAT TINLEIGH'S GONNA GROW
UP WITHOUT HER DAD.
I AM PISSED OFF, LIKE, THAT
BLAKE JUST LEFT.
AND IT DOES HURT.
LIKE, HE HELPED CREATE TINLEIGH,
AND NOW I'M TAKING CARE OF
SOMETHING THAT'S HALF HIS
RESPONSIBILITY.
[baby crying]
HEY.
I DIDN'T WANT A BABY AT 17
BECAUSE THERE WERE THINGS I
WANTED TO DO IN LIFE THAT YOU--
THAT ARE A LOT, A LOT, A LOT
HARDER WITH A BABY.
LIKE, I WANTED TO BE
A JOURNALIST.
THAT'S A CAREER YOU HAVE TO PUT
WORK INTO.
AND WITH A BABY, THERE'S JUST
NOT ENOUGH TIME TO PUT INTO
BOTH.
>> THERE'S MOMMY.
HI, MAMA.
SAY, "I MISSED YOU."
SO HOW WAS SCHOOL?
>> I HAVE SO MUCH HOMEWORK
TONIGHT.
>> AW.
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE A TEENAGER
ANYMORE BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO GIVE
THINGS UP.
AND IT'S NOT FAIR.
MY FRIENDS ARE GONNA GO AWAY TO
COLLEGE AND GO ON SPRING BREAK
WITH ALL THEIR FRIENDS.
LIKE, NOW I CAN'T GO AWAY TO
SCHOOL.
I CAN'T DO THOSE THINGS.
I FEEL LIKE BY MAKING ONE STUPID
DECISION, I KIND OF TOOK THAT
AWAY FROM MYSELF.
[baby crying]
SHH.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GONNA EAT REAL
QUICK, OKAY, 'CAUSE IF MOMMY
DOESN'T EAT, TINLEIGH DOESN'T
EAT.
SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
[baby crying]
BEING A MOM IS A LOT OF WORK,
AND SOMETIMES YOU'RE JUST KIND
OF GOING THROUGH THE MOTIONS
'CAUSE YOU GET NO SLEEP.
THAT'S NOT FUN.
AND I LOVE TINLEIGH TO DEATH,
BUT SOMETIMES SHE DRIVES ME
CRAZY.
YOU ARE GROSS.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
UGH.
[baby crying]
IF I HAD KNOWN HAVING A BABY WAS
GONNA BE SO HARD, THEN I WOULD
HAVE DONE EVERYTHING I COULD TO
PREVENT IT.
I WOULD HAVE NEVER HAD SEX.
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN THE BEST
THING TO PREVENT IT.
I DO FEEL LIKE A SINGLE MOM
BECAUSE BLAKE'S NOT HERE.
BLAKE'S NOT HELPING ME AT ALL.
BLAKE'S NOT GETTING UP IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT OR FIXING
BOTTLES OR CHANGING DIAPERS.
AND THAT WOULD MAKE ME
A SINGLE MOM.
>> DID HE KNOW THAT THAT WAS
YOUR FIRST TIME?
>> HE DIDN'T HAVE A CONDOM.
HE WAS LIKE, "OH, I'LL JUST
PULL OUT."
>> BIG BOY.
>> NOBODY HANGS OUT WITH ME
ANYMORE BECAUSE THEY'D RATHER GO
PARTY.
WHAT ARE WE DOING THIS WEEKEND?
>> PROBABLY GONNA GO TO HOUSE
PARTIES.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S GETTING
RUBBED IN MY FACE.