>> HI, I'M KAYLA.
>> ALL RIGHT, KAYLA!
>> OOH!
>> I LIVE IN MANKATO, MINNESOTA.
I'M A SENIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND SPORTS HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
MY LIFE.
>> KAYLA!
>> I MET MY BEST FRIENDS
ON THE GYMNASTICS TEAM,
AND WE HANG OUT ALL THE TIME.
WHOO!
I'M ALSO ON THE TRACK TEAM,
AND THAT'S HOW I MET MY
BOYFRIEND, MIKE.
HE'S A YEAR OLDER THAN ME
AND ALREADY GRADUATED FROM
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> I'M GONNA GIVE YOU A KISS
ON THE CHEEK TOO.
>> MMM.
AND EVEN THOUGH HE WAS SHY AT
FIRST, I TOTALLY FELL FOR HIM.
I KNEW YOU LIKED ME.
I KNEW IT.
HE LIVES AN HOUR AWAY,
BUT WE'VE BEEN INSEPARABLE
FOR TWO YEARS.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED, AND
I HARDLY EVER TALK TO MY DAD.
MY MOM AND I USED TO BE LIKE
BEST FRIENDS, BUT RECENTLY,
I FEEL LIKE WE'RE GROWING APART.
WE DON'T TALK, AND WE DON'T
HANG OUT ANYMORE.
IT'S LONELY.
>> RIGHT.
>> SHE'S BEEN SPENDING ALL HER
TIME WITH HER NEW BOYFRIEND.
THINGS JUST HAVEN'T BEEN
THE SAME BETWEEN US, AND I THINK
IT'S BECAUSE...
[chime dings]
I'M PREGNANT.
I'M SIX-MONTHS PREGNANT,
AND IT'S THE SUMMER BEFORE
SENIOR YEAR.
I'M TRYING TO MAKE THE MOST OF
IT BECAUSE I KNOW EVERYTHING
WILL CHANGE ONCE I HAVE
THE BABY.
[laughing] I CAN'T!
I CAN RUN,
BUT I'M AFRAID OF FALLING.
>> SENIOR YEAR GYMNASTICS,
ARE YOU GONNA COME TO THE MEETS,
LIKE, WITH THE BABY?
>> NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE
EVERYBODY.
IT'S GONNA BE SAD THAT I'LL BE
MISSING OUT ON ALL THAT.
BECAUSE, LIKE, GYMNASTICS,
YOU MAKE SO MANY MEMORIES,
AND THERE'S, LIKE, PICTURES
ALL THE TIME AND SLEEPOVERS
ALL THE TIME, AND THERE'S ALWAYS
STUFF GOING ON, AND I'M NOT
GONNA BE ABLE TO BE A PART
OF ANY OF IT.
AND ALL OF YOU GUYS ARE ALL
GONNA BE TOGETHER.
>> IT'S GONNA BE DIFFERENT
WITHOUT YOU ON THE TEAM.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE THE ONE THAT KIND OF
BROUGHT US ALL TOGETHER.
>> I KNOW.
THE BABY IS RUINING EVERYTHING.
[laughs]
>> WELL, YOU KNOW THAT
YOU CAN ALWAYS CALL US,
AND WE'LL COME HELP YOU
WITH ANYTHING.
>> I KEEP REALIZING HOW MUCH
I'M GOING TO BE MISSING OUT ON.
BUT AT LEAST MY FRIENDS HAVE
BEEN REALLY SUPPORTIVE.
>> SO HOW DID YOU FIGURE OUT
THAT YOU WERE PREGNANT?
>> I WAS THROWING UP REALLY BAD,
AND I WAS CRABBY, AND I, LIKE,
TOLD MY MOM HOW SICK I WAS,
AND SHE, LIKE--SHE'S LIKE,
"OH, I NEED TO GET YOU
A PREGNANCY TEST."
AND I WAS LIKE, "NO, YOU DON'T,
MOM, STOP BEING DUMB."
AND AS I WAS TAKING IT,
I WAS YELLING AT HER.
I WAS LIKE, "THIS IS SO STUPID."
AND THEN SHE LOOKS AT IT,
AND THEN, LIKE, I WAS PRETTY
SURE, LIKE, THE WORLD STOPPED
FOR, LIKE...
>> IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
>> I WASN'T SAD.
I WASN'T MAD.
I WASN'T SURPRISED.
I WAS JUST, LIKE, DEAD.
LIKE, IT WAS SO WEIRD.
FINDING OUT I WAS PREGNANT WAS
THE SCARIEST MOMENT OF MY LIFE.
WHAT MAKES IT EVEN WORSE
IS THAT I WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
ANOREXIA WHEN I WAS 13 AND HAD
TO BE HOSPITALIZED, SO GAINING
ALL THIS WEIGHT IS REALLY HARD
ON ME.
LUCKILY, MY MOM LET MY
BOYFRIEND, MIKE, MOVE IN,
SO HE COULD BE HERE TO SUPPORT
ME AND THE BABY.
>> REMEMBER WHEN WE FIRST MET?
>> I THOUGHT YOU WERE KIND OF
DOOFY LOOKING.
>> [laughs]
HOW WAS I DOOFY LOOKING?
>> YOU WERE JUST KIND OF A DORK
AND, LIKE, TALL AND SKINNY
AND AWKWARD.
>> I'M NOT AWKWARD.
>> YEAH, YOU WERE.
YOU STILL ARE.
>> I AM NOT.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> WE WEREN'T DATING VERY LONG
BEFORE WE...
>> WE WHAT?
>> DID IT.
>> IT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
>> IT WAS ON YOUR 101 DALMATIAN
BEDSHEETS AND YOUR YELLOW
CHILDREN'S BED.
[laughs]
>> THAT SQUEAKED EVERY TIME
YOU MOVED.
>> [laughs] IT DID SQUEAK!
IT SQUEAKED SO MUCH.
>> SO GLAD I GOT RID OF THAT.
>> NO, I THINK IT'S FUNNY.
>> THEN WE CAN WATCH JUNO.
>> WE DID WATCH JUNO.
[laughs]
I THINK THAT JINXED OUR WHOLE
RELATIONSHIP.
[laughter]
I THINK THAT MOVIE WAS, LIKE,
AN OMEN.
>> THAT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
>> THAT IS WEIRD.
YOU KNEW THAT I WASN'T ON
BIRTH CONTROL WHEN WE DID IT
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY.
I REMEMBER TELLING YOU
STRAIGHT OUT THAT I HADN'T
BEEN TAKING ANYTHING.
>> YEP.
>> THAT WAS SMART.
>> VERY SMART.
>> GETTING PREGNANT CHANGES
EVERYTHING.
I ALWAYS DREAMED OF GOING OFF
TO COLLEGE TO BECOME A NURSE,
AND NOW THAT'S GOING TO BE
A LOT HARDER, BUT AT LEAST
MIKE IS STANDING BY ME.
AND THE WHOLE THING HAS BEEN
REALLY DIFFICULT FOR MY MOM,
BECAUSE SHE WAS A TEEN MOM TOO,
AND I NEVER THOUGHT I'D REPEAT
HER MISTAKE.
>> I WAS LIKE, "OH, MY GOSH.
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?"
KIND OF SHOCKED.
>> THAT DAY WAS THE WORST.
>> AND I REMEMBER YOU GRABBING
YOUR HANDS AND PUTTING THEM
OVER YOUR MOUTH AND--
>> THE FUNNY THING IS THAT
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WILL EVER
BELIEVE ME; I WANTED TO LAUGH.
I THINK THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
WHY I COVERED UP MY MOUTH.
>> I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS FUNNY
AT ALL.
>> WELL, THEN, LIKE, I WAS IN,
LIKE, A WHOLE DAZE, LIKE,
THAT WHOLE NIGHT.
LIKE, I LITERALLY BAWLED
THE WHOLE NIGHT LONG.
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GONNA GROW
UP A LOT ONCE THIS BABY COMES.
YOU'RE GONNA STRUGGLE.
YOU KNOW I HAVE.
>> I DON'T THINK I SHOULD BE
ABLE TO BE A REGULAR TEENAGER.
I'M NOT A REGULAR TEENAGER.
>> WHEN I FIRST FOUND OUT YOU
WERE PREGNANT, WHEN WE FIRST SAW
THE TEST, MY BIGGEST FEAR
IS THAT YOU WOULDN'T KEEP IT.
>> THAT WAS, LIKE, THE FIRST
THOUGHT THAT RAN THROUGH MY
MIND, BUT THEN WHEN YOU ACTUALLY
THINK ABOUT GETTING AN ABORTION,
LIKE, THIS COULD ALL BE GONE
IN A SECOND, IF I WANTED
EVERYTHING TO BE BACK TO NORMAL.
I'LL NEVER EVEN HAVE TO TELL
ANYBODY, AND EVERYTHING WILL BE
JUST FINE.
I CAN JUST FORGET ABOUT IT.
BUT THEN WHEN IT COMES TO
ACTUALLY DOING IT, I COULD
NEVER DO IT.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE
PREGNANT.
YOU WERE, LIKE, SO DETERMINED,
SO I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD EVER
BE YOU.
>> I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S BECAUSE
SHE'S SO DISAPPOINTED WITH ME,
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE MY MOM TAKES
OFF WITH HER BOYFRIEND, MIKE,
EVERY CHANCE SHE GETS, WHICH
REALLY SUCKS BECAUSE BEFORE
I GOT PREGNANT...
[chime dings]
WE DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
>> IS IT FUN TO LIVE WITH ME?
>> [laughs] YES.
IF YOU WEREN'T HERE, NOBODY
WOULD BE TALKING TO ME, AND I'D
BE SITTING HERE ALL LONELY,
MAKING BROWNIES.
>> AND TALKING TO MADDIE.
>> AND TALKING TO THE CAT.
WELL, IT'S DEPRESSING.
>> A LITTLE BIT.
>> DO MY ARMS FLAP, LIKE,
MOVING?
WHEN I DO THIS, DOES MY ARM
JIGGLE FAT?
>> NO.
>> OR IS IT, LIKE,
STILL MUSCULAR?
>> STILL MUSCULAR.
>> IT'S PRETTY RUNNY.
I WHISKED IT REALLY WELL.
I'M SUCH A GOOD WHISKER.
>> A LOT TO SNACK ON.
>> HUH?
>> IT'S--NO.
OF COURSE.
>> MICHAEL, DON'T!
DON'T, DON'T, DON'T, DON'T.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT TO.
EW, YOU HAVE SOMETHING
RIGHT HERE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> I DIDN'T NOTICE.
>> MIKE'S PARENTS WERE
DISAPPOINTED THAT HE MOVED
SO FAR AWAY...
>> I'M GONNA HEAD OFF TO WORK.
YEAH.
>> AND GAVE UP COLLEGE TO GET
A PART-TIME JOB AT THE MALL.
BUT THEY UNDERSTAND THAT
WE HAVE TO START SAVING MONEY
FOR THE BABY.
WITH MIKE AT WORK,
I'M HOME ALONE A LOT.
I DON'T HAVE AN APPETITE,
AND I FEEL LIKE MY MOM HAS JUST
FORGOTTEN ABOUT ME.
SO I'M GLAD THAT ME AND
MY FRIENDS HAVE A LOT OF
SLEEPOVERS.
I FEEL LIKE SHE DOESN'T THINK
SHE HAS ANY RESPONSIBILITIES,
THAT SHE CAN DO WHATEVER
SHE WANTS.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE PREGNANT,
NOW SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO WATCH
YOU.
>> EXACTLY.
LIKE, SHE THINKS THAT
I'M PREGNANT, AND I'M FINE,
AND I CAN BE ALL BY MYSELF
ALL THE TIME.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK
SHE DOES THAT?
>> I SERIOUSLY THINK SHE, LIKE,
MENTALLY BLOCKS ME OUT IN HER
HEAD, AND SHE'S LIKE,
"OH, CRAP."
>> WHY DO YOU ALWAYS COVER YOUR
BELLY UP WITH PILLOWS?
>> I HATE THE WAY, LIKE,
IT FEELS, AND I FEEL FAT
ALL THE TIME.
>> SO, LIKE, EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE
PREGNANT, DO YOU STILL--LIKE,
WHEN YOU LOOK IN THE MIRROR,
DO YOU STILL SEE, LIKE, FAT
AND NOT A BABY?
>> YEAH, IT'S SO HARD FOR ME
BEING PREGNANT AND GAINING ALL
THIS WEIGHT WITHOUT ANY CONTROL.
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS 13,
I WAS HOSPITALIZED FOR ANOREXIA.
>> MM-HMM.
>> BUT THERE'S SO MANY TIMES
WHERE, LIKE, I'LL JUST, LIKE,
SKIP A MEAL, EVEN THOUGH
YOU KNOW, "YOU HAVE A BABY
YOU NEED TO FEED.
DON'T BE STUPID."
BUT, LIKE, STILL SOMEWHERE
IN YOUR MIND IS TELLING YOU,
"DON'T GET FAT.
DON'T GET FAT.
YOU'RE GROSS."
>> WELL, HAVE YOU TALKED
TO YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT, LIKE,
PRENATAL DIETS?
>> YEAH, LIKE, I WAS TELLING
MY MOM HOW I WANT TO SEE, LIKE,
A DIETICIAN, WHO WILL, LIKE,
GIVE ME A MEAL PLAN.
LIKE, YOU AND YOUR MOM SIT DOWN
TO DINNER AT NIGHT, AND...
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST--MY MOM DOESN'T EVEN TRY
ANYMORE.
SHE, LIKE, GAVE UP ON ME
OR SOMETHING.
BEING PREGNANT AND HAVING
AN EATING DISORDER IS SO HARD,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THE ONE PERSON
WHO HAS ALWAYS BEEN THERE FOR ME
IS TOTALLY LETTING ME DOWN.
>> THERE'S JUST A FEW WEEKS LEFT
OF SUMMER BREAK, AND MY MOM IS
AT HER BOYFRIEND'S HOUSE,
AS USUAL.
SO I'M GOING TO THE BEACH
WITH MY FRIENDS, EVEN THOUGH
IT'S PRETTY EMBARRASSING TO HAVE
SUCH A BIG PREGNANT BELLY.
>> I'M SWEATING.
>> ME TOO.
>> I'M SWEATING TOO.
YOU GUYS CAN GET IN YOUR
BATHING SUITS, IF YOU'D LIKE.
>> WELL, YOU HAVE TO TOO.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST WORRIED ABOUT, LIKE,
ALL OF THE WEIGHT I'VE GAINED.
NOT EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT
I'M PREGNANT, SO THEY JUST
THINK I'M FAT.
>> BUT IT'S VERY OBVIOUS,
'CAUSE YOU'RE ROUND.
YOU'RE NOT, LIKE, FLABBY.
>> I'M KIND OF FLABBY.
[laughs]
>> IT'S BABY FLAB.
GET USED TO IT.
>> YOU'RE JUST SCARED OF,
LIKE, THE STARES THAT
YOU'RE GONNA GET?
>> YEAH.
EITHER THEY'LL STARE BECAUSE
THEY'LL KNOW I'M PREGNANT
IF I TAKE OFF MY SHIRT,
OR THEY'LL STARE BECAUSE
I'M NASTY AND FAT.
>> YOU'RE NOT FAT.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T NEED
EVERYBODY LOOKING AT ME.
>> THERE'S ALWAYS GONNA BE
STARES, NO MATTER WHAT.
>> EXACTLY.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT
MY FRIENDS SAY.
I STILL FEEL FAT.
BUT GETTING BIGGER DOES MEAN
THAT I CAN FINALLY FIND OUT
WHETHER WE'RE HAVING A BOY
OR A GIRL.
>> SO DO YOU HAVE A FEELING
OF WHAT YOU'RE HAVING?
>> WE ALL THINK IT'S A BOY,
WHICH KIND OF MAKES ME THINK
IT'LL BE A GIRL, BUT I DON'T...
>> THE BABY'S HEART.
ULTRASOUND IS NEVER 100%,
BUT IT APPEARS TO BE A BOY.
[laughter]
>> I'M EXCITED WE'RE HAVING
A BOY, AND NOW WE JUST HAVE
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO NAME HIM.
COLBY, ASHTON, WARREN, PRESTON,
TRENTON, AND CADEN.
I'M AFRAID IF WE CHOOSE ASHTON,
I'LL ONLY THINK OF ASHTON
KUTCHER.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I REALLY LIKE THAT ONE.
>> WHICH ONE SOUNDS BETTER?
>> PROBABLY PRESTON.
>> THAT'S A NICE NAME.
>> IT'S CUTE.
>> WE HAVE OUR WINNER.
>> I THINK SO.
>> I LIKE IT.
COME HERE.
>> WE NEED TO GET READY FOR
THIS BABY, AND MY MOM HASN'T
GIVEN ME ANY ADVICE, BECAUSE
SHE'S ALWAYS WITH HER BOYFRIEND.
SO IT SEEMS LIKE MIKE AND I
ARE ON OUR OWN.
WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT NURSERY
STUFF, BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO EVEN BEGIN TO SET UP
A ROOM.
>> I KNOW.
>> WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT HOW
WE'RE GONNA PAY FOR THAT.
>> THAT'S JUST MATERIAL STUFF.
>> WELL, IT'S WHAT'S GOT
TO BE DONE.
IT'S, LIKE, THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING.
LIKE, YOU SAY "MATERIAL STUFF,"
BUT, WELL, IT NEEDS MATERIAL
STUFF.
IT'S GOT TO HAVE SOMETHING
TO SLEEP IN.
TO WEAR.
>> WHAT ARE YOU SO WORRIED
ABOUT?
>> THE REST OF MY LIFE.
AND EVERYTHING IS, LIKE,
FALLING APART, AND NOBODY
IS TAKING IT SERIOUSLY BUT ME.
>> I'M HERE.
>> YOU DON'T CARE,
AND THEN MOM DOESN'T CARE.
>> HOW AM I--HOW DO I NOT CARE?
I MOVED DOWN HERE TO BE
WITH YOU.
>> STOP TALKING.
>> WELL, IF YOU WANT ME
TO SHUT UP, I'LL...
>> NO, JUST DON'T BE STUPID,
MICHAEL.
>> KAYLA, THE BABY IS NOT GONNA
BE HERE FOR ANOTHER FOUR MONTHS.
>> [scoffs]
SOONER THAN THAT.
AND THAT'S NOT THAT MUCH TIME.
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT HOW
TO MAKE MONEY AND SAVE MONEY
AND BUY THINGS ALL IN THAT
PERIOD OF TIME.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY MONEY
SAVED UP.
WE HAVE NO MONEY TO SPEND
RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW THINGS ARE GONNA
GET HARD, BUT SOMEONE HAS TO
HAVE A POSITIVE OUTLOOK.
>> I'M NOT GONNA PRETEND LIKE
THINGS ARE FINE, AND IT'LL JUST
WORK OUT, AND WE COULDN'T EVEN
BUY A BAG OF DIAPERS RIGHT NOW
IF WE WANTED TO.
>> SO DO YOU WANT TO GO
AND MAYBE LOOK AT STUFF?
>> WHEN WE CAN'T BUY THEM?
>> JUST TO PRICE STUFF OUT,
HOW MUCH WE'D HAVE TO SAVE,
HOW MUCH WE'D HAVE TO SPEND.
>> SURE.
I'M GLAD MIKE WANTS THINGS
TO WORK OUT, BUT I DON'T THINK
HE REALIZES HOW EXPENSIVE
THIS IS GOING TO BE.
I JUST DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT WE, LIKE--WE ALL NEED.
>> SO THIS IS, LIKE, WHAT?
A BOUNCER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW EITHER.
>> THIS IS WHAT YOU NEED
WHEN THEY'RE REALLY LITTLE,
I THINK.
HOW MUCH ARE THEY?
>> $45.
>> BUT AREN'T THEY GONNA BE
IN IT FOR, LIKE, NOT THAT LONG?
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU KNOW HOW OLD THEY ARE
WHEN THEY SIT IN HIGH CHAIRS?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT THEY HAVE
TO, LIKE, BE ABLE TO HOLD
THEMSELVES UP AND...
>> WELL, YEAH, OTHERWISE,
THEY'D BE FALLING OVER.
IT'S HARD TO MAKE A PLAN
WHEN EVERYTHING IS SO EXPENSIVE,
AND WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
WE NEED.
>> HOW MANY DIAPERS DO YOU THINK
BABIES GO THROUGH?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SO I TEXTED MY MOM THAT I NEED
HER HELP, AND SHE AGREED TO
MEET ME FOR DINNER.
WE WENT TO STORES TODAY,
'CAUSE WE NEED TO START SETTING
UP THE NURSERY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THERE'S SO MANY THINGS
I HAD NO IDEA, LIKE,
WE EVEN NEEDED.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS WEIRD AND KIND OF
OVERWHELMING.
LIKE, EVEN THOUGH MIKE IS THERE,
MIKE'S NOT A MOM
OR EXPECTING MOM.
HE DOESN'T KNOW.
>> HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
GETTING INTO A GROUP TO SUPPORT
YOUNG MOMS?
>> I JUST WISH, LIKE, YOU WOULD
JUST SIT DOWN WITH ME AND, LIKE,
TALK ABOUT STUFF WITH ME.
LIKE, ME AND MIKE, WE HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT WE NEED FOR THE BABY.
>> I THINK IT'S ALL GONNA FALL
INTO PLACE.
>> I FEEL LIKE THINGS NEED
TO BE PLANNED.
>> SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
YOU CAN'T PLAN.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'LL BE--
YOU'LL TRY TO BE AROUND MORE
WHEN THE BABY IS HERE?
AND, LIKE...
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> WELL...
THEN HOW COME, LIKE,
YOU'RE NOT NOW?
SOMETIMES IT WOULD JUST BE NICE
JUST TO SIT DOWN
AND TALK TO YOU.
>> I'LL MAKE A POINT TO BE
THERE FOR YOU MORE.
I WILL.
>> OKAY.
I HOPE MY MOM KEEPS HER WORD
BECAUSE I NEED HER NOW MORE
THAN EVER.
>> EVEN THOUGH THINGS WITH
MY MOM HAVE BEEN TOUGH,
AT LEAST MY FRIENDS HAVEN'T
CHANGED.
SINCE SCHOOL STARTS IN TWO
WEEKS, THERE'S STILL PLENTY
OF TIME TO HANG OUT.
SO TONIGHT, THEY'RE COMING OVER
FOR A SLEEPOVER.
>> MOMMY!
HOW YOU DOING?
>> AH, GOOD.
>> LET'S PLAY.
YOU READY?
>> IF I GET TOO EXCITED,
I GUESS THEM.
[laughter]
>> OKAY, UM, THE TWO PEOPLE--
FIRST PEOPLE ON THE PLANET
THAT ATE THE BAD APPLE.
>> WHAT?
>> GOD'S PEOPLE!
[laughter]
>> OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD.
>> ADAM AND EVE.
>> OH!
>> YOU COOK IN A...
>> PAN.
>> YEAH.
>> AHH!
[all talking at once]
>> IF YOU'RE NOT IN THE COUNTRY,
YOU'RE IN THE...
>> OCEAN?
>> YEAH, OCEAN.
>> NO, CITY!
>> OH!
>> OKAY--
buzz!
>> WHOO!
[laughs]
OKAY, LET'S GO SET UP
WHERE WE'RE SLEEPING TONIGHT.
>> OKAY.
>> ARE YOU THERE?
ARE YOU HOLDING IT?
OH, MY GOD!
>> I GOT IT.
>> I CAN'T DO THAT!
>> WHY ARE YOU FREAKING OUT?
>> WELL, 'CAUSE I WASN'T GONNA
LET YOU, LIKE...
>> WHERE IS THE BABY GONNA GO
WHEN YOU'RE GOING TO SCHOOL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
LIKE, ME AND MIKE HAVE TO WORK
SOMETHING OUT, BECAUSE DON'T
THEY HAVE, LIKE, RULES?
YOU CAN'T PUT A BABY IN DAY CARE
FOR, LIKE, SIX WEEKS.
SO I CAN'T STAY HOME FROM
HIGH SCHOOL FOR SIX WEEKS.
I WOULD, LIKE, NEVER CATCH UP.
>> YEAH.
>> SO THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE TO
FIGURE OUT, IS THAT TIME PERIOD.
'CAUSE, LIKE, I WANT TO GET BACK
INTO HIGH SCHOOL, LIKE, JUST AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE AFTER I HAVE
THE BABY.
I THINK THAT'LL BE HARD.
>> ARE YOU STILL GONNA WALK
WITH US ON GRADUATION DAY?
>> I WANT TO.
I REALLY WANT TO GRADUATE,
AND THE ONLY WAY IT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN IS IF MIKE AND MY MOM
WATCH THE BABY WHEN I GO BACK
TO SCHOOL.
I'M GOING TO HAVE HIM IN THREE
MONTHS, WHICH IS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE SCHOOL YEAR, SO I KNOW
IT'LL BE REALLY HARD TO KEEP UP.
>> ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE
TO HOLD THAT UNTIL I CAN--
>> MOM, IT DOESN'T FIT.
IT'S TOO BIG.
>> THESE SIDES MOVE IN.
>> OH.
[laughter]
IT SEEMS LIKE MY MOM IS GOING
TO KEEP HER WORD AND SPEND MORE
TIME AT HOME WITH ME AND MIKE.
ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE TO TAKE
A VACATION WHEN THE BABY COMES?
>> I'LL BE TAKING SOME TIME OFF,
YES.
>> BECAUSE, LIKE, I ONLY WANT
TO MISS, LIKE, A WEEK OF SCHOOL.
>> I THINK YOU'RE GONNA WANT
MORE TIME, DEFINITELY NEED
MORE TIME THAN A WEEK.
ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT GOING BACK
TO SCHOOL LOOKING HEAVY?
>> IT'S JUST LIKE--IT SEEMS LIKE
IT'S IRREVERSIBLE.
LIKE, EVERY POUND I PUT ON,
I'M, LIKE, UGH, I CAN'T GET RID
OF THAT NOW.
>> JUST REMEMBER THAT
THAT BABY IS ASKING FOR SO MUCH.
>> BUT I FEEL LIKE I'VE ALREADY
GAINED 12 POUNDS, AND I'M JUST,
LIKE...
>> AT SIX MONTHS PREGNANT,
THOUGH, KAYLA?
>> YEAH, BUT I'M ONLY 2/3 OF
THE WAY THERE, AND YOU GAIN ALL
THE WEIGHT IN THAT LAST, LIKE,
COUPLE MONTHS.
>> A LOT OF THAT IS WATER
WEIGHT, YOU KNOW?
>> BUT I WAS, LIKE, READING MY
PREGNANCY BOOK: 1 TO 2 POUNDS
A WEEK.
AND, LIKE, 2 POUNDS A WEEK
FROM HERE ON OUT, DO YOU KNOW
HOW BIG THAT'S GONNA MAKE ME?
>> DO YOU EVER JUST STAND IN
THE MIRROR AND LOOK AT YOURSELF?
>> I CRY.
I CRY BEFORE AND AFTER
MY SHOWERS.
LIKE, THAT'S NOT EVEN A JOKE
AT ALL.
MIKE KNOWS THIS.
I SIT THERE, AND I STARE AT
MYSELF, AND I CRY.
I HATE IT SO MUCH.
>> DO YOU JUST LOOK AT
YOUR STOMACH, OR DO YOU LOOK
AT EVERYTHING?
>> I LOOK AT MY STOMACH
AND MY STRETCH MARKS AND MY--
>> YOU HAVE STRETCH MARKS?
>> IS IT POSSIBLE TO, LIKE,
LOSE WEIGHT DURING PREGNANCY
AND IT BE OKAY?
>> I WOULDN'T THINK LOSING
WEIGHT DURING A PREGNANCY
WOULD BE HEALTHY AT ALL.
>> I'M GLAD MY MOM'S AROUND,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I'M FEELING
SO INSECURE ABOUT MY BODY,
AND SHE'S THE ONLY ONE I CAN
REALLY TALK TO ABOUT IT.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
TONIGHT, MIKE IS VISITING HIS
PARENTS, BECAUSE MY MOM WANTS
TO HAVE A GIRLS' NIGHT OUT.
>> OUR PLANS CHANGED.
ME AND MIKE ARE GONNA GO
TO THE TWINS GAME, 'CAUSE MATT
GOT TWO EXTRA TICKETS, BUT--
>> TWO EXTRA TICKETS,
AND I'M NOT INVITED.
>> GENERAL SEATING.
>> WELL, WHY CAN'T I GO TO
THE TWINS GAME AND YOUR
BOYFRIEND STAY HOME?
>> WELL, THE TICKETS WERE
GIVEN TO US.
IT WASN'T LIKE WE BOUGHT THEM.
>> YEAH, BUT I'M SURE YOU HAD
A CHOICE OF WHO YOU COULD BRING.
>> OKAY.
>> HELLO?
>> HEY.
SO I AM AT HOME BY MYSELF.
>> YOUR MOM LEFT YOU?
>> YEAH, SHE WENT TO
A TWINS GAME.
>> OHH!
WANT TO HANG OUT TONIGHT?
>> SURE, YOU SHOULD COME GET ME.
>> I WILL.
I'LL BE THERE IN A LITTLE BIT.
>> BYE.
THANK GOD FOR MY FRIENDS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'D DO
WITHOUT THEM.
>> KAYLA?
HI, HONEY.
>> I'M ALMOST READY.
I JUST WISH SHE WOULD LOOK AT
HERSELF AND SEE, "OH, GEE,
THERE'S A REASON MY DAUGHTER
IS UNHAPPY."
>> YEAH.
>> BUT SHE DOESN'T SEE IT
THAT WAY.
>> HAS SHE EVEN ADMITTED
TO, LIKE, NOT BEING THERE
FOR YOU?
>> SHE GOES, "I KNOW.
I'LL TRY HARDER."
SHE'S LIKE, "WE ALL NEED
TO FIX THINGS.
NOBODY IS PERFECT."
I'M LIKE, "OKAY, THEN FIX THEM."
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, I AT LEAST EXPECTED HER
TO BE FAKE ENOUGH TO STICK
AROUND, YOU KNOW?
BUT SHE DOESN'T EVEN--
LIKE, SHE DIDN'T EVEN OWE ME
THAT APPARENTLY, 'CAUSE SHE
JUST LEFT.
MY MOM BREAKING OUR PLANS
REALLY HURTS ME, AND THE MORE
I THINK ABOUT IT, THE MORE
I REALIZE I HAVE TO LET HER
KNOW.
>> HELLO?
>> HEY.
>> UM, WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
I GUESS I KIND OF WANT TO SAY
I FEEL LIKE YOUR BOYFRIEND CAME
BEFORE ME.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT AT THE SAME TIME,
I FIGURE, WELL, YOU'VE GOT MIKE.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
TO RELY ON ME TO BE AT HOME
ALL THE TIME ANYMORE.
>> BUT I FEEL LIKE WHETHER
OR NOT I'M PREGNANT, I'M STILL
17 YEARS OLD, AND I'M STILL
YOUR DAUGHTER, AND I STILL WANT
YOU TO BE A MOM TO ME.
>> BUT I ALSO WANT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND THAT I HAVE
A LIFE TOO.
AND AT 17 YEARS OLD, YOU DO NOT
HAVE TO BE OCCUPIED BY YOUR MOM
24-7.
>> BUT I FEEL LIKE WE'RE NOT
EVEN A FAMILY ANYMORE, THAT
WE'RE JUST ROOMMATES WHO LIVE
IN THE SAME HOUSE AND IGNORE
EACH OTHER.
WE DON'T EVEN HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP ANYMORE.
WE DON'T TALK TO EACH OTHER
LIKE WE USED TO.
>> WELL, MAYBE THERE ARE SOME
THINGS ON BOTH OF OUR PARTS
THAT NEED TO CHANGE.
>> SERIOUSLY, I FELT
SO LEFT OUT.
>> MM-KAY, MM-KAY.
[phone beeps]
>> IT'S THE LAST WEEK OF SUMMER
VACATION, AND MY MOM HAS BEEN
EVEN MORE DISTANT SINCE WE
TALKED.
>> I CAN'T REMEMBER.
AND NOW SHE DOESN'T MAKE ANY
OF MY MEALS.
>> DO YOU THINK SHE'LL, LIKE,
HOLD TO HER WORD TO, LIKE,
EVERYTHING SHE SAID SHE
WOULD DO?
>> NO, PROBABLY NOT.
SHE IS REALLY GOOD AT MAKING
PROMISES AND GETTING REALLY
EXCITED ABOUT SOMETHING,
AND IT NEVER LASTS.
>> I REALLY HOPE EVERYTHING
CHANGES SOON.
>> I THINK MY LIFE IS GONNA TURN
INTO--"LET'S JUST SEE WHAT
HAPPENS," IS GONNA BE MY MOTTO.
>> LET'S MAKE IT THROUGH
THE DAY.
>> EXACTLY, LET'S JUST
SURVIVE ONE MORE DAY,
HOWEVER IT WORKS.
WE STILL HAVE SO MUCH
TO WORK OUT, BUT AT LEAST
I HAVE MIKE.
[chime dings]
IF IT WASN'T FOR HIM, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT I'D DO.
TODAY IS MY SEVEN-MONTH CHECKUP,
AND SINCE MIKE'S AT WORK
AND MY MOM IS WITH HER
BOYFRIEND, I'M GOING TO
THE DOCTOR'S BY MYSELF.
>> COME TO YOUR RIGHT, THEN.
EVERYTHING LOOKS GOOD.
>> I WAS KIND OF WONDERING
ABOUT MY WEIGHT GAIN.
>> MM-HMM.
>> IS IT ON THE HIGH SIDE?
>> YOU ARE UP 8 KILOGRAMS,
WHICH IS ABOUT 16 POUNDS,
17 POUNDS.
WE WOULD EXPECT 25 TO 30 POUNDS
OF WEIGHT GAIN.
THE THINGS YOU CAN DO TO MAKE
SURE THAT YOU STAY HEALTHY
DURING PREGNANCY ARE TO STAY
ACTIVE, TO EAT HEALTHY.
>> I DO LIKE MY FRUIT A LOT,
BUT WE TEND TO HAVE MORE COOKIES
THAN WE HAVE FRUIT.
>> SNACKING IS FINE.
SNACKING IS HEALTHY.
BUT YOU WANT TO HAVE
HEALTHY SNACKS, NOT COOKIES...
>> YEAH.
>> ALL THE TIME.
YOU KNOW, A BANANA,
PEANUT BUTTER AND APPLES,
CHEESE AND CRACKERS,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
AND THEN KNOW THAT ONCE BABY
GETS HERE, YOUR BODY WILL
GO BACK TO NORMAL.
>> NO MATTER WHAT THE DOCTOR
SAYS, I CAN'T STAND THE THOUGHT
OF GAINING ANY MORE WEIGHT.
I HAVEN'T EATEN ANYTHING ALL
DAY, BUT I KNOW THE BABY
NEEDS FOOD, SO I'M FORCING
MYSELF TO EAT SOMETHING.
IT'S THE DAY BEFORE SCHOOL
STARTS, AND EVEN THOUGH
I'M SELF-CONSCIOUS, MY FRIENDS
WANT TO MAKE A BELLY CAST.
I FEEL LIKE I'M, LIKE,
FULL TERM; I'M GONNA POP.
>> I THINK WE SHOULD
PAPIER-MACHE YOUR BELLY
BEFORE YOU GET HUGE
AND THEN FOR THE BABY SHOWER.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE YOU HAVE
A BASKETBALL SHOVED UNDERNEATH
YOUR TANK.
LIKE, THAT--SERIOUSLY.
LIKE, YOU DON'T--YOU'RE NOT,
LIKE, PREGNANT ANYWHERE ELSE.
OKAY, FLOUR, THE WATER...
>> TWO PARTS FLOUR,
ONE PART WATER.
>> THAT'S OKAY.
WAS THAT 2 CUPS?
>> KIND OF.
>> OKAY, SO YOU NEED 2 MORE.
KIND OF?
>> YOU NEED TO TAKE THIS OFF.
>> I'M GOING TO.
I JUST DON'T--IT'S COLD IN HERE.
>> DO YOU FEEL WEIRD,
BEING ALL EXPOSED?
>> I'M FAT.
>> YOU'RE VERY SELF-CONSCIOUS
ABOUT YOUR SIDES, BECAUSE YOU
THINK YOU HAVE MUFFIN-TOPS
AND YOU HAVE STRETCH MARKS.
>> YOU DON'T.
>> YOU DON'T--OKAY, YOU DO,
BUT THEY'RE--EVERY PREGNANT GIRL
IS GONNA GET STRETCH MARKS.
>> OH, MY GOD, NO.
ONLY, LIKE, HALF PREGNANT PEOPLE
GET STRETCH MARKS.
THE OTHER HALF--
>> WELL, YOU'RE ONE OF THE
LUCKY HALFS.
>> CAN I SIT NOW?
>> NO.
>> MY FEET HURT, YOU GUYS.
I'M NOT STANDING UP
THIS WHOLE TIME.
>> IF IT'S RUINED,
IT'S YOUR FAULT.
>> ME?
I DON'T REALLY CARE
AT THIS POINT.
I FEEL REALLY LIGHT-HEADED.
WE NEED TO STOP.
>> DO YOU NEED FOOD?
>> UM, I CAN'T SEE.
>> YOU'RE PROBABLY HOT,
'CAUSE I'M HOT.
>> NO, I'M SERIOUSLY SCARED.
>> YOU WANT SOME WATER?
FOR REAL?
>> THERE'S A BOTTLE OF WATER
IN THE FRIDGE.
>> OKAY.
YOU WANT SOMETHING TO EAT?
DO YOU WANT ME TO MAKE YOU
A SANDWICH, KAYLA?
'CAUSE, ARE YOU HUNGRY?
>> [gulping]
>> [whispers]
>> DO YOU WANT SOMETHING TO EAT,
FOR REAL?
>> I DON'T FEEL HUNGRY.
>> I THINK YOU ARE HUNGRY,
THOUGH.
>> I THINK YOU'RE REALLY HOT
TOO.
>> ALL SHE ATE WAS VANILLA
WAFERS THIS MORNING.
>> DO YOU WANT TO CALL
YOUR DOCTOR?
>> I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO.
>> WHERE'S YOUR PHONE?
>> CAN YOU TALK TO HIM?
HERE.
>> HELLO?
THIS IS ONE OF HER FRIENDS.
>> LET'S ME SEE.
NO.
>> DO YOU HAVE PAIN
IN YOUR EYES?
IT'S HER HEAD AND HER EYES.
IT'S JUST ALL PRESSURE.
>> WHAT?
>> OH, MY GOD.
[sobbing]
I'M SO SCARED.
>> I JUST FEEL REALLY WEAK.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
MY FRIENDS GOT ME TO THE
HOSPITAL JUST IN TIME.
>> AND YOU'RE HAVING
CONTRACTIONS, AND A LOT OF
TIMES, WHEN YOU'RE THIS EARLY,
WE START LOOKING AT PRETERM
LABOR.
>> I TEXTED MY MOM, AND SHE'S
COMING, BUT SHE'S AN HOUR AWAY
AT HER BOYFRIEND'S, SO I'M
GRATEFUL MIKE LEFT WORK AND
RUSHED STRAIGHT TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> MICHAEL, I CAN'T SEE
ANYTHING.
>> DIZZY AND LIGHT-HEADED?
>> MM-HMM.
REALLY, REALLY BAD.
>> THE LIGHT-HEADED AND
DIZZINESS OFTENTIMES WILL HAPPEN
IF YOU HAVEN'T ATE OR DRANK
A WHOLE LOT.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT,
YOU'RE MORE LIKELY TO BECOME
DEHYDRATED.
SO DOCTOR SCOTT WANTS FOR US
TO GIVE YOU SOME FLUIDS,
SINCE YOU HAVEN'T ATE AND DRANK
A WHOLE LOT TODAY.
>> I WAS SO WORRIED I WAS GOING
TO LOSE THE BABY, BUT THE
DOCTORS SEEMED TO THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY,
AND I'M STARTING TO FEEL
A LITTLE BETTER.
>> HI.
>> THE BABY IS OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
HE HAS BEEN REALLY MOVING
A LOT.
>> HE'S MOVING A LOT
AND EVERYTHING?
>> YEAH, HE WAS ESPECIALLY
WHEN I WAS LAYING ON MY BACK.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS REALLY SCARY.
>> KAYLA, IT'S MARY.
>> HI.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO I JUST TALKED
TO DR. SCOTT, AND WE'RE GONNA
DISCHARGE YOU, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> BUT YOU REALLY NEED TO BE
EATING AND DRINKING, OKAY?
WHOEVER IS AROUND TO HELP YOU,
TO REMIND YOU.
THAT WAY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
HERE FOR THIS TYPE OF THING.
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE THAT'S NOT ANY FUN,
OKAY?
>> DO YOU NEED HELP WITH
ANYTHING?
>> IT'S TOO LATE FOR MY MOM
TO BE OFFERING TO HELP.
I WISH SHE WAS JUST AROUND MORE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
I REALLY HAVE TO TAKE BETTER
CARE OF MYSELF, SO THE DOCTOR
MADE ME AN APPOINTMENT TO SEE
A NUTRITIONIST NEXT WEEK,
BUT MY FRIENDS ARE STILL REALLY
WORRIED ABOUT ME.
>> MY MOM SAID YOU SHOULD
EAT CARBS.
WE WERE TALKING ABOUT THIS.
SHE SAID YOU NEED REALLY GOOD
CARBS.
>> AREN'T THE CARBS THINGS THAT
MAKE YOU FAT?
PEOPLE GO ON NO-CARB DIETS.
>> YOU'RE NOT GONNA GET FAT.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HAVING
GOOD CARBS AND A LITTLE PROTEIN.
OKAY, WHAT ARE YOU HUNGRY FOR?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
ALL OF THIS IS REALLY FANCY
AND WEIRD STUFF.
>> I JUST FEEL SCARED.
I WANT YOU TO EAT.
>> WELL, I'M NOT DOING IT
ON PURPOSE.
>> WELL, I BELIEVE YOU'RE NOT
DOING IT ON PURPOSE, BUT STILL,
IT JUST FRIGHTENS ME.
>> LIKE, WERE YOU NOT TAKING
YOUR PRENATAL VITAMINS?
>> NO--WELL, I DO WHEN
I REMEMBER, WHICH IS, LIKE,
ONCE A WEEK.
>> PRENATAL VITAMINS MAKE YOUR
HAIR GROW.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL TAKE IT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND YOU SAID YOU WANT
YOUR HAIR TO GROW.
>> WHAT ARE PEOPLE GONNA THINK
WHEN THEY SEE YOU ON THE FIRST
DAY OF SCHOOL AND YOU'RE
PREGNANT?
>> THEY'LL PROBABLY JUST THINK
I'M A BIG OLD SLUT.
>> NO, THEY WON'T.
>> PROBABLY.
IT'S OUR SCHOOL, SO...
>> WELL, WHAT ARE YOU MOST
NERVOUS ABOUT?
>> EVERYBODY STARING AT ME.
ARE YOU GUYS EXCITED FOR
SENIOR YEAR?
>> YEAH.
>> I AM.
>> I'M SUPER EXCITED.
>> I FEEL LIKE YOUR SENIOR YEAR
IS GONNA BE A LOT MORE EVENTFUL
THAN MINE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK THE
TEACHERS ARE GONNA THINK?
>> DO YOU THINK TEACHERS CAN,
LIKE, PURPOSELY FAIL YOU
BECAUSE THEY HATE YOU?
>> NO, NO, THEY CAN'T.
>> I THINK, AS TEACHERS,
THEY SHOULD BE PROFESSIONAL
ENOUGH NOT TO BE JUDGMENTAL.
>> THEY'RE STILL GONNA THINK
THINGS, EVEN IF THEY DON'T,
LIKE, ACT ON IT.
[alarm clock buzzing]
THE FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL
IS FINALLY HERE.
I KNOW IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO HIDE
MY HUGE BELLY, SO THE LEAST
I CAN DO IS TRY TO LOOK MY BEST.
>> HI.
>> HEY.
>> ARE YOU READY FOR SCHOOL?
>> NOT REALLY.
>> FOR SENIOR YEAR, WE ALL HAVE
TO WALK IN AND SAY--
>> SENIORS!
>> SENIOR, SENIOR, SENIOR!
[clapping]
>> WE'RE GONNA GO!
>> I WISH I COULD BE AS EXCITED
ABOUT SENIOR YEAR AS MY FRIENDS
ARE.
>> SENIORS, SENIORS!
[crowd clapping]
>> BUT SCHOOL WAS REALLY
AWKWARD.
EVERYONE STARED AT ME.
IT WAS EXHAUSTING,
AND I COULDN'T FIT IN MY DESK,
LET ALONE FOCUS ON MY WORK.
I HATE SCHOOL,
LIKE, JUST ALTOGETHER,
AND NOW IT'S EVEN HARDER TO GO.
>> WELL, HOW DID THE TEACHERS
TAKE IT?
>> NONE OF THEM, LIKE, ASKED ME
ABOUT IT OR SAID ANYTHING.
>> MM-HMM.
WHAT ABOUT EVERYONE, LIKE,
JUST, LIKE, ALL THE STUDENTS
AND EVERYTHING?
>> LIKE, NOBODY WAS REALLY RUDE
ABOUT IT, BUT THEY JUST ALL
KIND OF STARED AND, LIKE...
>> YEAH.
DO YOU JUST FEEL OUT OF PLACE
AND AWKWARD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST THOUGHT THAT SENIOR YEAR
WOULD BE, LIKE, FULL OF, LIKE,
PARTIES AND FOOTBALL GAMES
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND NOW, LIKE, I CAN'T DO
ANY OF THEM.
IT'S BEEN A WEEK SINCE I WAS
IN THE HOSPITAL, AND I STILL
HAVEN'T SEEN MUCH OF MY MOM.
BUT TODAY, SHE AGREED TO COME
WITH ME TO SEE THE NUTRITIONIST.
>> THE EATING DISORDER VOICE,
IS IT LOUDER NOW THAN--
>> WELL, BEFORE I WAS PREGNANT,
I WAS IN GYMNASTICS, AND I FELT
LIKE I WAS IN REALLY GOOD SHAPE,
AND I ACTUALLY KIND OF LIKED
WHERE I WAS AT IN MY LIFE.
AND THEN NOW IT SEEMS LIKE,
SINCE I GOT PREGNANT,
I JUST, LIKE, LOST CONTROL.
>> SO YOU'RE BACK TO
A PRETTY LOUD...
>> YEAH, EXTREMELY.
LIKE, IT'S--EVERYTHING I EAT,
"CRAP, I SHOULDN'T HAVE EATEN
THAT," OR, "WHY DID YOU EAT
TWO OF THOSE?
YOU ONLY NEEDED ONE."
>> TRULY, YOU SHOULD BE EATING
EVERY FOUR TO SIX HOURS
AND THEN AN IN-BETWEEN SNACK
EVERY TWO TO THREE HOURS.
DOES THAT KIND OF SCARE YOU?
EATING THAT FREQUENTLY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU ALMOST HAVE TO LOOK AT
FOOD RIGHT NOW AS KIND OF
MEDICINE FOR YOU, BECAUSE YOU'RE
PREGNANT, YOU KNOW?
AND THE BABY NEEDS CERTAIN
NUTRIENTS.
SO HOW MANY TIMES A WEEK
DO YOU THINK YOU EAT TOGETHER
AS A FAMILY?
>> THERE'S A LOT OF TIMES WHERE
I'M ON MY OWN.
>> I WOULD RECOMMEND TO EAT
WITH PEOPLE.
>> OKAY.
>> I THINK THAT WOULD BE
VERY IMPORTANT.
>> I THINK SHE WOULD RESTRICT
HERSELF WHEN SHE HAS PEOPLE
WATCHING HER...
>> MM-HMM.
>> RATHER THAN IF SHE'S AT HOME
BY HERSELF, SHE'LL EAT.
>> YEAH, THE ONLY PROBLEM WITH
EATING ALONE IS, IT BECOMES
MORE SECRETIVE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND THEN THAT MAKES THE
EATING DISORDER STRONGER,
FROM WHAT PATIENTS HAVE SAID.
'CAUSE RIGHT NOW, YOU'VE GOT
THOUGHTS 24 HOURS A DAY,
AND IF YOU'RE EATING ALONE,
IT'S JUST, EVERY BITE YOU TAKE,
YOU'RE THINKING.
BUT IF YOU HAVE SOMEONE THERE,
THERE'S MORE DISTRACTION.
>> * YOU KNOW *
* THE WAY TO GO *
[acoustic guitar music]
* YOU KNOW *
* THE WAY TO GO *
>> IT'S BEEN TWO WEEKS SINCE
THE NUTRITIONIST TOLD MY MOM
THAT WE SHOULD BE HAVING MEALS
TOGETHER, BUT NOTHING HAS
CHANGED.
MIKE'S BEEN TRYING REALLY HARD
TO GET ME TO EAT WHEN I GET HOME
FROM SCHOOL, BUT IT HASN'T
BEEN EASY.
>> HOW IS IT?
>> KIND OF GROSS.
>> THIS IS ACTUALLY PRETTY GOOD.
>> IT'S REALLY GROSS.
>> COME ON, JUST HAVE SOME.
>> NO, IT'S NASTY.
LIKE, IT'S ORANGE AND BURNT
AND GROSS.
>> THEN WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> CEREAL?
>> NO.
>> APPLE SAUCE?
DO YOU WANT, LIKE, A REAL MEAL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> SPAGHETTI?
>> NO.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THEN HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FEED YOU?
THE BABY IS GONNA NEED YOU--
>> JUST PUT THE FOOD AWAY.
IT'S MAKING ME SICK.
I KNOW MIKE IS TRYING TO HELP,
BUT I'M JUST NOT HUNGRY.
>> SOUNDS GOOD TODAY.
HE SOUNDS GOOD.
HE SOUNDS HAPPY.
SO LOOKING AT YOUR WEIGHT HERE,
IT LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVEN'T
GAINED WEIGHT.
WE NEED TO WORK ON GETTING
MORE NUTRITION IN YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE I KNOW THE NURSES SAID
YOU HADN'T EATEN MUCH WHEN
YOU GOT TO THE HOSPITAL.
YOU KNOW, WE GET CONCERNED
WHEN WE DON'T SEE WEIGHT GAIN,
THAT THAT COULD BE SOMETHING
THAT THE BABY IS NOT GETTING
ENOUGH NUTRITION OR YOU'RE NOT
GETTING ENOUGH NUTRITION.
ANY MORE LIGHT-HEADED,
ANYTHING LIKE THAT?
>> SOMETIMES I GET TIRED,
AND I'LL JUST SIT DOWN AND DRINK
SOME WATER, AND THEN I'LL FEEL
BETTER RIGHT AWAY.
>> A LOT OF TIMES,
LIGHT-HEADEDNESS CAN BE
A SYMPTOM OF SOMETHING WRONG.
SO YOU NEED TO MAKE SURE
YOU'RE EATING REGULAR MEALS.
BABIES NEED A LOT MORE ENERGY
THAN WHAT YOU'RE USED TO EATING.
AND IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE
A LOT OF HIGH-CALORIE FOOD,
BUT GETTING MORE FOOD IN
WILL HELP.
>> SO HOW HAVE YOUR DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENTS BEEN GOING?
>> THE DOCTOR WAS KIND OF
CONCERNED, 'CAUSE I GUESS
I HAVEN'T GAINED WEIGHT,
WHICH IS UNUSUAL FOR THE END,
BECAUSE THE BABY IS STILL
GAINING.
AND SO, LIKE, I SHOULD OBVIOUSLY
BE PUTTING ON ALL THE WEIGHT
LIKE THE BABY IS.
>> ARE YOU CONCERNED THAT SINCE
YOU HAVEN'T GAINED ANY WEIGHT,
LIKE, THE BABY ISN'T GETTING
ANY NUTRITION?
>> OBVIOUSLY, I WANT HIM
TO BE HEALTHY AND STUFF.
THAT'S MORE IMPORTANT TO ME
THAN THE AMOUNT OF WEIGHT
I PUT ON.
>> MM-HMM.
>> BUT IT'S JUST--IT'S STILL
HARD TO GET OVER.
LIKE, WHEN YOU HAVE, LIKE,
AN EATING DISORDER BRAIN,
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT WORKS.
LIKE, IN THE BACK OF MY MIND,
YEAH, I KNOW HE NEEDS FOOD,
AND I NEED TO BE HEALTHY
FOR HIM, AND HE'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING, BUT THAT
DOESN'T STOP ALL THE OTHER
THOUGHTS.
I KNOW I HAVE TO PUT THE BABY
FIRST, BUT IT'S REALLY HARD
FOR ME.
ON TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE,
MY DUE DATE IS ONLY TWO WEEKS
AWAY.
I'M GOING TO DO HOMESCHOOL
FOR FIVE WEEKS AFTER I HAVE
THE BABY, BUT I'M WORRIED ABOUT
STAYING ON TRACK, BECAUSE
IT'S ALREADY HARD TO KEEP UP.
>> IS THAT ALL FOR ONE CLASS?
>> YEAH.
THIS IS FOR ONE CLASS.
WHAT DID YOU DO FOR YOUR
POLITICAL CARTOON?
>> WHAT?
>> YOUR POL--YOU'RE NOT IN
GOVERNMENT.
DANG IT.
>> NO, FOR SENIOR STRATEGIES,
A COLLEGE CAME THAT'S CALLED,
LIKE, ARGOSY SCHOOL.
AND THEY MAJOR IN, LIKE, VET,
AND THEY HAVE, LIKE, AN ON-SET
SITE, SO I REALLY WANT TO GO
THERE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA
DO FOR COLLEGE?
>> I JUST THINK, IF I NEVER HAD
THE BABY, THAT I DIDN'T WANT
TO STAY AROUND HERE.
LIKE, I HAD, LIKE, BIG DREAMS
AND STUFF FOR MYSELF,
AND I DON'T WANT TO HOLD BACK
BECAUSE OF THAT.
>> YEAH.
>> EVERYBODY IS GONNA PICK UP
AND HAVE--GO ACCOMPLISH ALL
THEIR DREAMS, AND I DON'T WANT
TO BE STUCK HERE BECAUSE OF,
THAT I HAD A BABY, AND I'M JUST
STUCK HERE, LIVING WITH MY MOM
AND BEING, LIKE, A LOSER.
IT SUCKS THAT I HAVE TO PUT
MY COLLEGE PLANS ASIDE.
BUT FOR NOW, I HAVE TO FOCUS
ON GETTING READY FOR THE BABY.
HE'S DUE IN ONE WEEK,
AND TODAY, MY FRIENDS ARE
THROWING ME A BABY SHOWER.
AWW!
IT'S A BALL, MOM.
THIS IS MY FIRST BAG OF DIAPERS
THAT I OWN.
[laughter]
IT'S A LITTLE BATH SET.
NOW THAT WE HAVE A LOT
OF WHAT WE NEED...
THANK YOU!
IT'S TIME TO GET THE NURSERY
READY.
AH, MY ARMS ARE TIRED.
THE BABY WILL BE HERE REALLY
SOON, AND I'M STARTING TO GET
NERVOUS.
I'M GLAD MIKE AGREED TO WATCH
THE BABY WHEN I GO BACK TO
SCHOOL, BUT WE'RE GOING TO NEED
HELP AT FIRST.
WHAT HAPPENS ON THE DAY WE BRING
HIM HOME?
>> YOU'RE GONNA BE TIRED.
>> MM-HMM.
I MEAN, I'M GONNA BE HERE,
SO...
>> TILL I GET USED TO
EVERYTHING, I JUST DON'T
WANT TO BE ON MY OWN.
>> WELL, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE.
>> I HOPE MY MOM IS SERIOUS.
THE BABY COULD BE HERE
ANY MOMENT, AND SHE'S STILL
SPENDING MOST OF HER TIME
WITH HER BOYFRIEND.
MICHAEL!
I JUST FELT--LIKE, I'M, LIKE,
LEAKING.
>> COULD IT BE YOUR WATER
BREAKING?
>> I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S A LOT
OF LEAKY STUFF.
I'M CRAMPING UP.
>> ARE YOU SURE IT'S NOT
A CONTRACTION?
>> I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT CONTRACTIONS FEEL LIKE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS
BY MYSELF.
>> YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU'VE NEVER HAD
YOUR WATER BREAK.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
I CAN'T EVEN--I HAVE NO ONE
TO RELATE TO.
I JUST WANT SOMEBODY TO BE ABLE
TO TELL ME IF THIS IS IT OR NOT.
>> WHY DON'T YOU GO WAKE UP
YOUR MOM?
[knocking at door]
>> COME IN.
>> IT ALL CAME, LIKE,
GUSHING OUT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> I'VE BEEN HAVING THE
CONTRACTIONS ALL NIGHT.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
I GUESS LEAKING FLUIDS
AND HAVING CONTRACTIONS
ISN'T ENOUGH TO CONVINCE MY MOM
THAT THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG.
SO MIKE AND I ARE LEAVING
FOR THE HOSPITAL WITHOUT
TELLING HER.
I DID NOT PREPARE FOR THIS YET.
>> WELL, I'M JUST TRYING
TO CHEER YOU UP.
>> TURN!
TURN, AT MAIN STREET, HOSPITAL,
YOU SEE THAT "H."
>> SETTLE DOWN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
DON'T EVER TELL ME
TO SETTLE DOWN.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU.
OH, MOTHER OF GOD, IT HURTS.
[solemn piano music]
* *
>> EVEN THOUGH MY MOM DOESN'T
BELIEVE ME, SOMETHING IS
DEFINITELY GOING ON, SO MIKE
AND I RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> GOT THE AMNISURE BACK,
AND IT'S POSITIVE.
SO THAT MEANS YOUR WATER BROKE.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> YOU ARE HAVING A BABY.
>> YOU WILL NOT GO HOME
UNTIL YOU HAVE THAT BABY.
>> OH, MY GOSH!
>> [laughs]
OKAY, I'LL BE BACK IN
A LITTLE BIT, OKAY?
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> MY WATER BROKE, BUT I CAN'T
START PUSHING UNTIL MY CERVIX
IS DILATED TO 10 CENTIMETERS.
AND AT THIS POINT, I'M NOT
DILATED AT ALL.
SO ALL WE CAN DO IS WAIT
AND WAIT AND WAIT.
MIKE TEXTED MY MOM,
AND BY THE TIME SHE SHOWED UP,
MY CONTRACTIONS WERE KILLING ME,
AND I HAVE ONLY DILATED
2 CENTIMETERS.
IT'S REALLY NICE TO HAVE MIKE
HERE, BECAUSE I HAVE NEVER BEEN
IN SO MUCH PAIN.
[sighs]
I HATE THIS SO MUCH.
OH, MY GOD.
>> JUST KEEP BREATHING.
BREATHE.
>> YOUR CERVIX WAS STILL
3 TO 4 CENTIMETERS, SO LET'S SEE
WHAT HAPPENS WITH YOUR
CONTRACTIONS OVER THE NEXT HOUR
OR SO.
IF YOU'RE NOT MAKING CERVICAL
CHANGE, WE MAY NEED TO BE
TALKING ABOUT DOING A C-SECTION.
>> BUT I DON'T WANT THE SCAR,
AND I WANT TO BE ABLE TO DO
THE NATURAL BIRTH.
THIS MIGHT BE THE ONLY BABY
I EVER HAVE IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
>> AND I KNOW THIS IS A HUGE
DECISION TO MAKE, AND I'M NOT
GONNA MAKE YOU MAKE IT
RIGHT NOW.
I'M GONNA LET YOU GUYS TALK
ABOUT IT AND THINK ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> YOU DON'T HAVE TO DECIDE
RIGHT NOW.
>> ONLY BECAUSE IF YOU DO
A VAGINAL DELIVERY, HONEY,
YOU'RE GONNA BE SO TUCKERED OUT.
>> [sighs]
[sobbing]
THIS IS THE LONGEST DAY
OF MY LIFE.
>> YEAH, IN THE LAST SIX HOURS,
YOU'VE MADE IT A CENTIMETER.
>> YEAH, THAT'S...WEIRD.
>> THIS MAY BE YOUR BODY'S WAY
OF SAYING, "LET'S BE DONE."
>> [sobbing]
AFTER 23 HOURS IN LABOR,
I STILL HAVEN'T DILATED ENOUGH
TO PUSH, SO EVEN THOUGH I DON'T
WANT TO, I HAVE TO GET
A C-SECTION.
>> IS BABY SOON?
>> UM, NOT YET.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE GONNA FEEL A LOT
OF PRESSURE.
THE HEAD IS OUT.
OH, ARMS.
A LOT OF PRESSURE HERE.
OH, CONGRATULATIONS.
WE CAN TAKE THIS OFF NOW.
CAN YOU HEAR THE CRY?
PERFECT, RIGHT THERE.
PERFECT.
>> HE'S PERFECT.
>> YES, HE IS.
FIRST BABY I'VE EVER HELD.
HE'S A BIG BOY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[sobs]
[chime dings]
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE PRESTON
IS FINALLY HERE.
>> YOU GUYS DID WELL.
BEAUTIFUL.
>> ARE YOU SURE I'M HOLDING HIM
RIGHT?
>> YEAH, YOU ARE.
>> [belches]
>> SEE?
>> SHOULD I STOP BURPING THEN?
>> WHENEVER YOU THINK.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I THINK.
>> NO, HE'S FINE, THOUGH.
HE BURPED.
>> BECAUSE OF MY SURGERY,
I HAVE TO STAY IN THE HOSPITAL
FOR THREE DAYS, BUT WHEN I GET
HOME, MY MOM HAS PROMISED TO
TAKE A WEEK OFF TO HELP US.
BUT FOR NOW, SHE HAS TO GO BACK
TO WORK.
>> OH, HE'S THE CUTEST THING.
>> HOW WEIRD IS IT TO THINK THAT
THAT WAS INSIDE OF YOU?
>> HE'S SO CUTE.
HE HAS PRETTY HAIR.
>> HOW LONG IS THE RECOVERY
DIFFERENT FROM A REGULAR?
>> I CAN'T GO BACK TO SCHOOL
FOR AT LEAST SIX WEEKS.
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS ABOUT
RECOVERING AT HOME AND HAVING
TO TAKE CARE OF HIM?
>> WELL, YEAH, BUT MY MOM
IS STAYING HOME FROM WORK
FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
>> CUTE.
>> THE NURSES ARE TEACHING ME
HOW TO BREAST-FEED
AND TRYING TO TEACH MIKE
HOW TO CHANGE DIAPERS.
[Preston crying]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M TRYING TO CHANGE
HIS DIAPER.
>> IT'S FINALLY TIME TO TAKE
PRESTON HOME.
HOW EXCITED ARE YOU?
>> RIGHT NOW, I'M REALLY
NERVOUS.
>> WITH DRIVING?
>> YES.
>> ISN'T IT WEIRD?
>> IT'S VERY WEIRD.
IT'S LIKE, OH, GOSH, I HAVE
SOMETHING SO SMALL AND FRAGILE
IN THE BACK NOW.
>> IT'S STILL SO WEIRD TO THINK
THAT THIS THING WAS IN MY BELLY.
>> I KNOW.
>> UFFDA.
YEAH, THESE BUMPS FEEL HORRIBLE
ON MY STOMACH.
>> BECAUSE YOU USED TO HAVE
A HARD BODY AND NOW...
>> A HARD, BIG BELLY
THAT DIDN'T--AND NOW I KIND OF
BOUNCE AROUND A LITTLE BIT.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> DOING OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO WITH HIM?
>> LEAVE HIM.
>> JUST STARE AT HIM.
[laughter]
DO WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH HIM.
HE'S YOURS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH HIM.
>> TAKE HIM OUT?
>> I KIND OF JUST WANT TO
LEAVE HIM IN THERE.
>> I KNOW, 'CAUSE I KNOW
HE'S GONNA BE CRANKY.
>> YOU'RE HOME, PRESTON.
>> [crying]
>> SEE?
NOW, WHY WERE YOU CRYING?
[Preston cooing]
PRESTON IS HOME.
>> THAT'S WEIRD THAT
WE'RE BOTH MOMS.
WE'RE ON THE SAME LEVEL,
YOU KNOW?
ISN'T THAT SCARY?
>> IT IS.
>> AND EVERYTHING KIND OF HURTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> ARE YOU HUNGRY?
I HAVE A HUGE DINNER.
I HAVE A POT ROAST IN
THE CROCK-POT AND POTATOES
AND CARROTS AND CORN ON THE COB
AND...
>> JEEZ.
>> IT'S BEEN ABOUT TEN YEARS
SINCE I'VE COOKED.
>> IT'S NICE THAT MY MOM
IS COOKING DINNER.
IT'S GOING TO BE SO MUCH EASIER
WITH HER AROUND THIS WEEK
TO HELP US.
>> IT'S GOOD.
>> THAT'S A LOT.
I WANT TO GET A LOT,
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S REALLY
FILLING OR NOT.
I WANT TO, LIKE, SLEEP
OUT IN THE NURSERY, I THINK,
TONIGHT.
>> I KIND OF DO TOO.
>> REALLY?
>> IT JUST SEEMS WEIRD FOR HIM
TO BE ALL BY HIMSELF.
HE'S NEVER IN HIS WHOLE LIFE
BEEN ALL BY HIMSELF.
>> SO HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
NO DOCTORS, NO NURSES?
HE'S ALL YOURS, NO HELP.
>> ARE YOU GOING BACK TO WORK
TOMORROW?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, YOU SAID BEFORE I HAD
HIM THAT YOU WOULD TAKE
THE WHOLE FIRST WEEK OFF OF WORK
TO STAY HOME AND HELP ME.
>> I THINK YOU GUYS
WILL BE FINE.
AND YOU'LL GET INTO A ROUTINE.
YOU'RE GONNA FIGURE OUT
WHAT WORKS BEST FOR YOU.
>> [crying]
>> I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT
MY MOM WOULD LET ME DOWN.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO FIGURE THIS OUT ON OUR OWN.
[chime dings]
>> MY MOM TOLD ME SHE WOULD HELP
ME WITH THE BABY FOR THE FIRST
WEEK, BUT SHE WENT STRAIGHT BACK
TO WORK.
AND TAKING CARE OF PRESTON
WITHOUT HER HAS BEEN REALLY
HARD.
LUCKILY, MIKE IS GETTING THE
HANG OF IT AND HAS BEEN HELPING
A LOT.
WHY WON'T HE GO TO SLEEP?
[Preston crying]
OH, HE JUST POO-POOED HIS PANTS.
HE NEEDS HIS DIAPER CHANGED.
BUT EVEN WITH MIKE'S HELP,
I'M STILL EXHAUSTED.
PUMPING IS TAKING FOREVER.
I'M BARELY PRODUCING ANY MILK,
AND I THINK IT'S BECAUSE
I'M NOT EATING ENOUGH.
SO NOW EVEN THOUGH WE CAN'T
AFFORD IT, WE HAVE TO START
ADDING FORMULA.
>> INSTANT SHUTTER-UPPER.
[laughs]
>> THE SHUTTER-UPPER?
YOU WAS HUNGRY.
I'M SORRY.
I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY OF MY FRIENDS
SINCE THE HOSPITAL, AND I DON'T
GO BACK TO SCHOOL FOR FIVE MORE
WEEKS, SO TODAY, I'M MEETING
CYNTHIA FOR LUNCH.
[Preston crying]
>> WOW.
>> THAT WAS REALLY, REALLY LOUD.
>> YEAH, WAS THAT EMBARRASSING?
>> ONLY 'CAUSE WE'RE IN PUBLIC.
IT'S FUNNY, 'CAUSE WHEN I WAS
PREGNANT AND ME AND MIKE WENT
OUT TO EAT, I WAS ALWAYS, LIKE--
WHEN WE HEARD CRYING BABIES,
WE WERE LIKE, "THAT'LL NEVER
HAPPEN TO US.
LIKE, HOW HARD IS IT
TO CONTROL YOUR KID?"
>> [giggles]
>> BUT THEN NOW IT'S, LIKE,
UH, IMPOSSIBLE.
>> DO YOU--DO YOU FEEL ANY
DIFFERENT NOW THAT HE'S HERE
THAN, LIKE, WHEN YOU WERE
PREGNANT?
>> I ALMOST KIND OF MISS, LIKE,
BEING CUTE AND PREGNANT
AND ROUND.
I THINK I HATE MY BODY MORE NOW,
'CAUSE THINGS JUST ALL OF
A SUDDEN JUST, LIKE, FELL,
AND, LIKE...
>> DO YOU THINK THAT, LIKE,
YOUR BODY WILL NEVER GO BACK?
LIKE, IT'S, LIKE, PERMANENTLY,
LIKE, A SORT OF DIFFERENT
WAY NOW?
>> I JUST LOOK LIKE A WRINKLY
OLD LADY.
IT'S NOT ATTRACTIVE.
>> SO IT'S NOT, LIKE, FAT.
IT'S JUST SKIN.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IF YOU WORKED OUT
OR WHATEVER AND, LIKE--
I DON'T KNOW.
>> BUT I JUST DON'T HAVE
THE TIME TO, LIKE, HAVE
A GYM MEMBERSHIP AND GO
TO THE GYM AND DEDICATE
FIVE DAYS OF THE WEEK TO IT.
>> I DON'T THINK THAT YOU NEED
TO LOSE ANY WEIGHT.
I JUST THINK THAT IT'S MORE
ABOUT WHAT MAKES YOU HAPPY,
LIKE...
>> I JUST WANT MY BODY BACK,
AND RIGHT NOW, SKIPPING MEALS
IS THE EASIEST WAY.
I'M BEHIND IN ALL MY CLASSES,
SO SINCE MIKE ONLY WORKS
PART-TIME, HE'S TAKING CARE
OF PRESTON WHILE I MEET WITH
A HOMESCHOOL TEACHER
TO CATCH UP.
>> I HAVE WORK FOR YOU
FROM DIFFERENT TEACHERS,
A LITTLE BIT OF EVERYTHING.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE A LOT
OF EVERYTHING.
[laughter]
>> IT'S A LOT OF EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO HERE ARE YOUR ASSIGNMENTS
FOR YOUR ANATOMY CLASS.
UH, I'VE GOT SOME BANKING
HOMEWORK.
>> THIS IS FROM SENIOR YEAR
STRATEGIES, PROBABLY.
>> CORRECT.
>> JEEZ.
>> LOOKS LIKE YOUR GOVERNMENT
HOMEWORK.
LOOKS LIKE YOU HAVE QUITE A BIT
HERE.
>> BUT THIS CLASS IS REALLY--
I REALLY LIKE THIS CLASS,
SO THIS IS GONNA BE EASIER,
BUT IT'S JUST...
>> IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN
ALL AT ONCE, ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
>> I KNOW IT'S HARD TO FIND TIME
WITH THE BABY IN THE HOUSE.
I REALIZE THAT.
BUT YOU REALLY HAVE TO BUCKLE
DOWN AND MAKE A TIME TO DO IT
EVERY DAY.
>> WONDERFUL.
>> YEAH.
>> GETTING ALL THIS WORK DONE
WILL BE TOUGH BECAUSE PRESTON
NEEDS CONSTANT ATTENTION.
>> YOU WANT ME TO MAKE A BOTTLE?
YOU CAN CHANGE HIM.
>> YEAH.
>> [crying]
>> SHOULD BE FINE.
>> YUM, YUM, YUM, YUM, YUM.
THAT WAS EMBARRASSING.
>> WHY?
>> 'CAUSE PEOPLE PROBABLY
THOUGHT I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
I WAS DOING, 'CAUSE HE WAS,
LIKE, SCREAMING AT ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK WE KNOW WHAT
WE'RE DOING.
LIKE, 98% OF THE TIME,
WE KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING.
>> YEAH.
CAN YOU FEED HIM?
YOU OKAY NOW WITH DADDY?
YEAH!
SO WHAT ARE YOUR FRIENDS DOING
TODAY?
>> THEY'RE ALL AT A GYMNASTICS
MEET.
>> DO YOU MISS IT?
>> YEAH.
I MISS BEING IN SHAPE TOO.
LIKE, I WASN'T EVEN THAT GOOD,
BUT I LIKED GOING TO PRACTICES
AND STUFF.
>> I LIKED WATCHING YOU.
>> YOU USED TO LIKE THE
LEOTARDS.
>> A LITTLE BIT.
>> [laughs]
>> WHY DO WE KEEP DOING THIS?
WE, LIKE, EAT OUT ALL THE TIME,
AND WE CAN'T--
>> WE DO EAT OUT ALL THE TIME.
>> AND WE CAN'T AFFORD IT.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW EXPENSIVE
IT WOULD BE TO TAKE CARE OF HIM,
'CAUSE WE DON'T HAVE A LOT
OF MONEY.
>> YEAH.
>> WE REALLY DO NEED TO START
WATCHING OUR SPENDING, BECAUSE
TAKING CARE OF PRESTON
IS EXPENSIVE, AND IT'S ABOUT
TO COST EVEN MORE, BECAUSE
MY MOM WANTS MIKE TO START
PAYING RENT.
>> IS IT POSSIBLE TO START
HELPING OUT?
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> WITH FINANCES AND THINGS
AROUND THE HOUSE.
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> ROUGHLY $300.
>> IS THAT, LIKE, WITH, LIKE,
GROCERIES OR IS THAT--
>> NO.
>> HE'D STILL HAVE TO HELP
PAY FOR GROCERIES AND STUFF
LIKE THAT.
>> YOU KNOW, IF EVERYBODY
CAN CHIP IN, IT'S GONNA BE
LESS STRESSFUL FOR EVERYBODY.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, I'M SURE
IT'S GOT TO MAKE YOU GUYS
FEEL LIKE CRAP IF YOU DON'T PAY
FOR ANYTHING, RIGHT?
>> WELL, WE HAD TALKED ABOUT HIM
BEING ABLE TO STAY HERE
ALL THE TIME.
LIKE, YOU TOLD ME, AS LONG AS
I WAS TAKEN CARE OF AND PRESTON
WAS TAKEN CARE OF AND MIKE COULD
SUPPLY EVERYTHING THAT THE TWO
OF US NEEDED, THAT YOU WOULDN'T
WORRY ABOUT RENT, AND, LIKE,
HE'S BEEN DOING THAT
PRETTY WELL, I THOUGHT.
>> YEAH, HE HAS.
>> LIKE, HE GETS PRESTON
EVERYTHING HE NEEDS.
HE GETS ME EVERYTHING I NEED.
>> I THINK IT'S ONLY FAIR
THAT YOU GUYS PAY, YOU KNOW,
YOUR PORTION, YOUR SHARE.
>> WELL...
>> [passes gas]
>> EXCUSE YOU.
>> YOU FEEL BETTER?
>> IT'S A LOT IF YOU'RE ONLY
WORKING PART-TIME, THOUGH.
>> IT IS?
>> AND YOU ONLY GET 20 HOURS
A WEEK AT MINIMUM WAGE.
THEN IT'S A LOT.
'CAUSE, LIKE, HE DOESN'T HAVE
THE SAME KIND OF JOB AS YOU DO.
>> I MEAN, IT'S GOING
TO BE TOUGH.
>> I DON'T EVEN THINK HE MAKES
THAT MUCH A MONTH.
>> NO, I DON'T.
>> WOULD IT BE POSSIBLE FOR YOU
TO GO FULL-TIME THERE, MIKE?
>> THAT WOULD MEAN THAT YOU
WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO GO BACK
TO SCHOOL.
>> YEAH, IF HE DID THAT,
I WOULDN'T GO BACK TO SCHOOL,
BECAUSE HE WOULD BE WORKING
40-PLUS HOURS A WEEK.
>> IF MIKE'S GONNA STAY HERE,
HE NEEDS TO PAY $300 A MONTH.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE MY MOM
IS DOING THIS.
IF MIKE CAN'T TAKE CARE OF
PRESTON LIKE WE PLANNED,
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GOING
TO GRADUATE.
>> MIKE STARTED WORKING
FULL-TIME, SO HE COULD PAY
MY MOM THE RENT,
AND NOW WE ONLY HAVE $60 LEFT
TO BUY THINGS FOR THE BABY.
WHAT KIND DO WE USUALLY GET?
PAMPERS?
>> PAMPERS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE DIFFERENCE IS.
WHICH ONE IS CHEAPER?
THAT ONE GETS US 112 DIAPERS
FOR $19.79, AND THAT ONE GETS US
92 DIAPERS FOR $19.79.
SO THAT WOULD MAKE MORE SENSE.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S, LIKE, HALF OUR MONEY
IS GONE ALREADY...
>> MM-HMM.
>> ON DIAPERS.
>> SO WE NEED WHAT?
FORMULA AND WIPES?
WHICH ARE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
>> SO THE SIMILAC SENSITIVE
IS $21.09.
WE CAN ONLY GET ONE RIGHT NOW,
'CAUSE IT'S--WE DON'T EVEN
HAVE ENOUGH.
IF WE GET THIS, WE'RE DONE.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY MORE MONEY.
IT'S $20.
HOW MUCH--THIS WAS $30?
>> MM-HMM.
$10, $20.
>> SO WE'RE DONE?
>> YEP.
>> NUH-UH.
[scanner beeps]
NOTHING IS EASY RIGHT NOW.
I'M EXHAUSTED FROM TAKING CARE
OF THE BABY BY MYSELF, AND I
HAVEN'T DONE ANY HOMEWORK
SINCE THE LAST TIME I SAW
MY HOMESCHOOL TEACHER.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> PRETTY GOOD.
>> IT'S HARD WORK, JUGGLING
A BABY AND HOMEWORK, ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
>> AND HAS HE BEEN COOPERATING?
>> HE'S COOPERATING NOW.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE HE IS, YES.
>> HE'S USUALLY--
HE GETS PRETTY FUSSY.
LIKE, HE'LL HAVE A WHOLE DAY
OF JUST--HE JUST WANTS TO CRY
ALL DAY.
>> YEP, THAT'S WHAT BABIES DO.
SO I'VE BEEN TALKING WITH
YOUR TEACHERS, AND THEY'RE
A LITTLE CONCERNED, SINCE YOU'RE
ALL THESE WEEKS BEHIND.
>> MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING NEW
TO TURN IN TO ME TODAY?
>> UH...NO.
>> YEAH, I WOULD SAY,
DO YOUR VERY BEST TO TRY
AND WORK ON IT A LITTLE BIT
EACH DAY, BUT IT'S GONNA BE
A TOUGH HAUL.
YOU'VE GOT A LOT TO DO.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU'RE IN A UNIQUE SITUATION
WHERE YOU NEED TO BE MOM
AND STUDENT.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HARD TO DIVIDE UP
YOUR TIME, I KNOW.
WHAT ABOUT COLLEGE?
>> [sighs] I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T APPLIED ANYWHERE YET.
>> OKAY.
>> LIKE, I NEVER USED TO WANT
TO STAY HERE, BUT I DON'T REALLY
SEE ME GOING OFF ANYWHERE.
>> THAT IS OPPOSITE OF WHAT
YOU SAID EVEN A MONTH AGO.
>> I WAS JUST THINKING, LIKE,
DOESN'T IT JUST SEEM LIKE
A LOT EASIER TO, LIKE,
DROP OUT AND GET YOUR G.E.D.?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU
DO THAT, BECAUSE I KNOW
YOU CAN KEEP UP.
I KNOW YOU HAVE WHAT IT TAKES.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU'RE NOT TAKING
EASY CLASSES HERE, KAYLA.
YOU'VE GOT QUITE A LIST.
AND I'M AFRAID THAT BY GETTING
YOUR G.E.D., IT WON'T SHOW
WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I KNOW YOU CAN GET
YOUR G.E.D.,
BUT I'D LIKE TO SEE YOU
GRADUATE WITH YOUR CLASS.
I KNOW YOU HAVE IT.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO IT.
>> I KNEW KEEPING UP AT SCHOOL
WAS GOING TO BE HARD, BUT NOW
GRADUATING WITH MY FRIENDS
SEEMS IMPOSSIBLE.
>> WHEN DO YOU PLAN ON COMING
BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW
IF I'M GONNA BE ABLE TO.
>> WHY?
>> WELL, I JUST CAN'T AFFORD
A DAY CARE.
AND I KNOW, LIKE, IN THE
LONG RUN, LIKE, IF I GRADUATED,
IT WOULD BE BETTER FOR HIM
AND FOR ME, BUT I FEEL LIKE,
RIGHT NOW, BEING AT HOME
WITH HIM IS BETTER FOR HIM.
>> DON'T YOU PLAN ON GETTING,
LIKE, A JOB OR SOMETHING?
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO BE AWAY
FROM HIM THEN.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WELL, THAT'S KIND OF DUMB.
WE DON'T GET TO, LIKE, GRADUATE
TOGETHER AND STUFF.
>> LIKE, I DON'T WANT TO BE
LAZY, BUT...
>> NOT MOTIVATED TO.
>> YEAH, I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE
HIM, BUT I DON'T WANT TO GET
MY G.E.D., BECAUSE I FEEL
LIKE THAT'S NOT MUCH
OF AN ACCOMPLISHMENT.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA FEEL
STAYING HERE WITH PRESTON
AND MIKE WHILE WE'RE OFF
DOING COLLEGE?
>> WELL, THAT'LL SUCK,
BUT...
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN GO WITH YOU.
[Preston fussing]
>> I'M WORRIED, LIKE,
'CAUSE, LIKE, WE'LL ALL BE AWAY,
AND YOU'LL BE ALONE, AND, LIKE,
WE ALWAYS ALL DO STUFF TOGETHER,
AND NOW IT'S JUST GONNA--
THEN IT'S JUST GONNA BE, LIKE,
STOPPED.
IT'S JUST GONNA BE WEIRD.
LIKE, IT'S SAD.
I HOPE WE'LL STILL, LIKE...
STILL KEEP IN TOUCH AND, LIKE,
UPDATE EACH OTHER ON, LIKE,
WHAT'S GOING ON.
AND, LIKE, HOLIDAYS OR SOME
ODD WEEKEND THAT WE'RE ALL OFF,
WE CAN JUST COME TOGETHER.
>> SOMETHING...
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE THE SAME.
LIKE, WE'RE GONNA PART.
>> I KNOW.
THINKING ABOUT ALL MY FRIENDS
GOING OFF TO COLLEGE WITHOUT ME
IS REALLY SAD, BUT I HAVE MORE
THAN MYSELF TO THINK ABOUT NOW.
LUCKILY, UNTIL MY FRIENDS
LEAVE FOR COLLEGE, WE CAN STILL
HAVE SLEEPOVERS.
[clanking]
OH!
>> WHAT DO WE DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW, CYNTHIA,
AT ALL.
[laughter]
>> THERE'S POLES TO THIS THING.
I KNOW THAT.
WHERE'S MIKE WHEN YOU NEED HIM?
>> YEAH, I ACTUALLY DON'T KNOW
HOW TO DO THIS AT ALL.
>> OH, LET'S PUSH THIS THING IN.
[metal clicks]
>> OH, WE HAVE TO LOCK THESE
FIRST.
>> OH!
STURDY.
>> HEY!
WE DID IT.
>> SO IS YOUR MOM HELPING OUT
NOW THAT THE BABY IS HERE?
>> NOT REALLY.
LIKE, WE'RE TO THE POINT
WHERE, LIKE, I'M, LIKE,
AFRAID TO ASK HER FOR ANYTHING.
LIKE, I DON'T ASK HER FOR MONEY.
SHE'S NEVER BOUGHTEN HIM
ANYTHING.
LIKE, I DON'T ASK HER
TO WATCH HIM, JUST BECAUSE
I DON'T--I DON'T EVEN FEEL LIKE
WE'RE, LIKE, CLOSE ENOUGH
TO EVEN DO THAT.
IT'S JUST WEIRD.
OUR WHOLE RELATIONSHIP
IS AWKWARD.
I DON'T--IT'S UNCOMFORTABLE.
LATELY, I HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN
MY MOM, SINCE SHE'S USUALLY
AT HER BOYFRIEND'S, AND IT'S
ALWAYS WEIRD WHEN SHE DOES
COME HOME.
>> HEY.
>> HI.
>> SO YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE BEEN
THINKING?
LIKE, SIX, EIGHT MONTHS AGO
WHEN I LOST SOME WEIGHT,
REMEMBER THAT?
AND IF YOU'VE NOTICED,
I'VE BEEN PUTTING IT BACK ON.
>> MM-HMM.
>> SO I KNOW IN ABOUT FOUR
TO FIVE WEEKS, I THINK THAT'S
WHERE YOU'RE GONNA BE READY--
YOU'RE GONNA WANT TO...
>> PUT ON WEIGHT?
>> NO.
>> OH.
>> TO START...
>> YOU KNOW?
>> YOU WANT ME TO GO ON
A DIET WITH YOU?
>> NOT REALLY A DIET,
JUST START WATCHING
WHAT WE'RE EATING.
'CAUSE I KNOW, AS DETERMINED
AS YOU ARE, YOU COULD PROBABLY
DISCIPLINE ME.
WOULD YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
YOU CAN HELP ME.
I CAN HELP YOU.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW HOW
I'M SUPPOSED TO HELP YOU.
>> WELL, I MEAN, JUST WATCHING
WHAT WE'RE EATING AROUND HERE,
WHERE THERE'S NOT SO MUCH
JUST JUNK SNACKING AND STUFF
LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW, AND YOU MAY KNOW
BETTER THAN ME, CONSIDERING
WHAT YOU'VE GONE THROUGH
WITH YOUR EATING DISORDER.
>> YOU'RE NOT REALLY HERE
OFTEN ENOUGH, FOR ME TO WATCH
WHAT YOU'RE EATING.
>> WE WOULD PLAN IT WHERE
WE WOULD HAVE DINNER TOGETHER
BEFORE I LEFT.
>> SO YOU WOULD COME HOME
TO EAT WITH ME, AND THEN YOU
WOULD GO BACK TO YOUR
BOYFRIEND'S.
>> YEAH, AFTER WE ATE.
YOU COULD AT LEAST THINK
ABOUT IT.
>> UM, I JUST THINK WE'RE PRETTY
DYSFUNCTIONAL AS A FAMILY...
>> YEAH.
>> THE WAY IT IS, AND I THINK
THAT--I DON'T KNOW.
IF WE'RE GONNA TAKE TIME TO DO
ANYTHING, WE PROBABLY NEED TO
TAKE TIME TO FIGURE [bleep] OUT.
I DIDN'T THINK THINGS COULD GET
ANY WORSE WITH MY MOM,
BUT ASKING ME TO GO ON A DIET
WITH HER IS A NEW LOW.
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN MY MOM SINCE
SHE ASKED ME TO GO ON A DIET
WITH HER, AND EVEN THOUGH
SHE'S CHARGING US RENT,
SHE'S NOT EVEN TAKING CARE
OF THE HOUSE.
>> HI, MOM.
I WAS JUST--I WAS JUST GONNA
TELL YOU THAT I DON'T THINK
THE HEAT IS WORKING.
SO CALL ME BACK WHEN YOU CAN.
BYE.
IT'S FREEZING IN HERE, AND
MY MOM IS AT HER BOYFRIEND'S,
SO WE'RE GOING TO A HOTEL
FOR THE NIGHT.
IT COST $100, AND WE CAN BARELY
AFFORD DIAPERS AND FORMULA.
WELL, SO NOW WE JUST HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT HOW THE HELL YOU'RE
GONNA PAY RENT, WHEN WE JUST
SPENT ALL THAT MONEY ON THAT
STUPID HOTEL.
>> YEAH, WE SHOULDN'T HAVE GONE
TO A HOTEL.
>> NO, SERIOUSLY, THOUGH,
HOW ARE YOU GONNA PAY RENT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR
HOW MY MOM IS TREATING US,
SO I ASKED HER TO MEET ME,
SO WE CAN TALK ABOUT IT.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> DECIDE ABOUT SCHOOL YET?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I WANT TO GRADUATE, BUT...
>> SO WHAT ELSE IS NEW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST--WE DON'T LIKE LIVING
AT YOUR HOUSE.
LIKE, WE FEEL THERE'S NO POINT
FOR US LIVING THERE.
WE'RE JUST KIND OF THROWING AWAY
MONEY THAT COULD BE USED
FOR SOMETHING BETTER,
LIKE TOWARDS, LIKE, A SAVINGS
FOR OUR OWN PLACE OR SOMETHING.
I JUST FEEL LIKE WE'RE WASTING
MONEY, WHEN WE SHOULDN'T EVEN
HAVE TO PAY.
LIKE, SPECIFICALLY, LIKE,
THE HEAT GOES OUT, AND YOU'RE
AT YOUR BOYFRIEND'S HOUSE,
AND WE HAVE TO GET A HOTEL ROOM.
THEN I HAVE TO PAY FOR IT
ENTIRELY BY MYSELF, BUT YOU'RE
ALL NICE AND WARM IN YOUR
BOYFRIEND'S HOUSE, SO IT WASN'T
THAT BIG OF A CONCERN TO YOU.
>> YOU THINK YOU GUYS CAN
MAKE IT ON YOUR OWN?
>> I DON'T KNOW. I JUST--
>> WELL, I MEAN, KAYLA,
IF YOU CAN DO ALL THIS,
IF YOU CAN MOVE OUT OF THE
HOUSE, AND YOU AND MIKE MAKE IT
ON YOUR OWN WITH PRESTON,
THEN DO IT.
>> I JUST FELT LIKE WHEN I FIRST
GOT PREGNANT, YOU'D TELL ME HOW
GOOD THINGS WERE GONNA BE
AND HOW, LIKE, HOW MUCH YOU WERE
GONNA HELP OUT AND STUFF,
AND IT JUST SEEMS LIKE
YOU HAVEN'T.
>> I'VE TRIED.
>> WELL, I JUST FEEL LIKE
YOU JUST DISTANCE YOURSELF,
AND YOU DON'T EVER WANT TO BE
AROUND ME UNLESS--
>> THAT'S NOT TRUE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST FEEL LIKE YOU MADE
A LOT OF PROMISES THAT AREN'T
BEING KEPT.
>> WELL, I TRIED.
THAT'S ALL I CAN SAY.
>> [sighs]
YOU WERE, LIKE, MY BEST FRIEND
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T
EVEN STAND TO BE AROUND ME.
[sniffles]
I JUST WANT THINGS TO GO BACK
TO THE WAY THEY USED TO BE.
[sniffles]
>> YEAH.
>> I THOUGHT SINCE MY MOM WAS
A TEEN MOM THAT SHE WOULD STICK
BY ME THROUGH THIS WHOLE THING
AND SHE WOULD BE, LIKE,
MY BIGGEST SUPPORT SYSTEM,
BUT NOW I JUST FEEL COMPLETELY
ABANDONED BY HER.
YOU'RE SO TINY FOR YOUR FIRST
THANKSGIVING.
>> SO ARE YOU MAD THAT
YOUR MOM IS NOT AROUND?
>> I DON'T REALLY CARE ANYMORE.
IF IT WASN'T FOR MIKE,
I'M NOT SURE WHERE I WOULD BE.
I DEPEND ON HIM AND RELY ON HIM
FOR A LOT OF THINGS, AND I JUST
HOPE THAT WE'RE TOGETHER
FOREVER.
WHOO!
THAT WAS BETTER.
WITH AN EATING DISORDER, BEING
PREGNANT WAS REALLY DIFFICULT,
AND I HAVE MY GOOD DAYS
AND MY BAD DAYS.
SOME DAYS I JUST SEE FLAB
AND DISGUSTING FAT.
OTHER DAYS, I LOOK IN THE
MIRROR, AND I GO,
"THIS IS A GOOD DAY,
AND I FEEL GOOD ABOUT MYSELF."
BASICALLY, BEING PREGNANT
HAS CHANGED MY WHOLE LIFE.
I THOUGHT I WOULD GRADUATE WITH
MY FRIENDS AND GO OFF TO COLLEGE
TO BE A NURSE, AND NOW I'M
SITTING AT HOME ALL DAY
WITH THE BABY, AND IT'S JUST
NOTHING HOW I EVER EXPECTED
MY LIFE WOULD GO AT ALL.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA BE
A PAIN IN MY BUTT.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME HOLD YOU
ALL DAY LONG.
IT SUCKS THAT I JUST KIND OF
WATCHED MYSELF FALL BEHIND,
AND NOW IT'S JUST, LIKE...
SLOWLY, EVERYTHING WAS JUST
KIND OF FALLING APART,
AND I COULDN'T KEEP EVERYTHING
TOGETHER ANYMORE.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE ON TRACK
TO GRADUATE THIS SPRING?
>> NO.
>> NO?
>> I'M, LIKE, A MONTH BEHIND.
YOU CAN'T LOOK AT YOUR CHILD
AND THEN SAY, "I WISH
YOU WEREN'T HERE."
I WISH IT WASN'T LIKE THIS.
I WANT PRESTON TO KNOW THAT
I'LL NEVER ABANDON HIM.
HE FULLY DEPENDS ON ME,
AND I NEED TO BE STRONG FOR HIM
ALL THE TIME.
YOUR CRY IS SO CUTE.
IT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE ME MAD,
'CAUSE IT'S SO ADORABLE.
HOPEFULLY, I CAN TAKE ALL
MY DREAMS ONE STEP AT A TIME
AND JUST SLOWLY GET TO WHERE
I WANT TO BE IN LIFE.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> EVEN IF THEY HAVE BAD THINGS
TO SAY, WE CAN'T LET IT
GET TO US.
>> YOU SHOULD START TELLING
PEOPLE.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO WAIT
TO TELL ME.
>> NINE, TEN.
[baby crying]
>> YOU GUYS NEED TO GROW UP NOW,
'CAUSE NOW YOU HAVE A BABY.
>> I HAVE BEEN LYING TO
YOU GUYS.
>> YOU DECEIVED US.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I WANT YOU
TO BE WITH MY DAUGHTER.
>> WE'VE GIVEN HIM ENOUGH
OPPORTUNITIES.
IF HE DECIDES TO LEAVE,
WE NEED TO KNOW SOONER
RATHER THAN LATER.
[engine revs]