[applause]
>> I'M DR. DREW.
TEEN PREGNANCY REMAINS
AN EPIDEMIC IN THIS COUNTRY.
ONE IN EIGHT GIRLS IN THE U.S.
WILL BECOME A TEEN MOM,
AND MORE THAN 1,500--
GET THIS--
1,500 AMERICAN TEENAGERS
GET PREGNANT EVERY DAY.
THE 12 YOUNG WOMEN
HERE WITH ME TODAY,
HAVE FIRST-HAND KNOWLEDGE
OF THE PHYSICAL,
SOCIAL, AND ECONOMIC CHALLENGES
THAT FACE TEEN PARENTS.
LET'S WELCOME MADDY, AUTUMN,
MILLINA, ARIANNA,
SUMMER,
KARLEY,
ALEAH, JAZMIN,
COURTNEY, SAVON,
JORDAN, AND SAVANNAH.
CHILDREN OF TEEN PARENTS
ARE MORE LIKELY
TO BECOME TEEN PARENTS.
ARIANNA'S MOTHER
HAD HER WHEN SHE WAS JUST 17,
AND NOW ARIANNA IS A TEEN MOM.
LET'S LOOK BACK
ON HER EXPERIENCE
ON 16 AND PREGNANT.
>> YOU BEING SORRY.
DON'T BE LIKE MY DAD.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE THE ONLY ONE
TAKING CARE OF HIM FINANCIALLY.
YOU GOT TO OWN UP
TO WHAT YOU DID WRONG.
>> YOU CAN BE WRONG TOO.
>> YOU'RE GETTING ON BY [bleep]
NERVES.
I'M LEAVING.
I DON'T WANT YOU AROUND ME
BECAUSE YOU NEED TO BE MAN
ENOUGH TO KNOW
WHAT YOU DID WRONG.
>> I WILL CALL A NURSE IN HERE
IF YOU DO NOT GIVE ME MY CHILD
AND GET
OUT OF MY ROOM RIGHT NOW.
I'M DOING WHAT I'VE GOT TO DO.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
AND IF THIS CONTINUES--
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> WELL, WHATEVER.
>> WELL ARIANNA
IS HERE WITH MAURICE.
ARIANNA, WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU SAW MAURICE?
>> ABOUT THREE
AND A HALF MONTHS AGO.
>> THREE AND A HALF MONTHS AGO?
>> YES.
>> HAVE YOU NOT WANTED
TO SPEAK TO HIM OR NO?
>> NO, I'VE GIVEN MORE CHANCES
THAN I CAN COUNT ON MY HANDS
AND TOES.
AND IT'S JUST NEVER ENOUGH,
THE CHANCES THAT I GIVE HIM.
SO AFTER GIVING
HIM SO MANY CHANCES,
YOU CAN'T FORCE SOMEBODY
TO BE A FATHER.
IT HAS TO COME NATURALLY.
>> AND WHEN YOU SAY BE A FATHER,
WHAT WOULD THAT LOOK LIKE?
WHAT DO YOU WANT HIM TO DO?
>> YOU CAN'T BE A FATHER
OR A PARENT
WHENEVER YOU FEEL LIKE IT.
YOU CAN'T BE A REVOLVING DOOR.
IT CAN'T BE, YOU KNOW,
WHENEVER YOU FEEL LIKE IT
AND THAT'S HOW IT WAS.
>> ALL RIGHT, MAURICE.
HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT?
>> WELL, I MEAN,
I WANTED TO BE THERE FOR MY SON,
BUT I CAN'T BE THERE FOR HIM
IF I'M NOT ALLOWED TO.
>> NOT ALLOWED TO?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, THERE'S BEEN
PLENTY OF OPPORTUNITIES
WHERE I WANTED TO COME
BY TO COME SEE HIM,
COME PICK MY SON UP, YOU KNOW,
"YOU CAN'T PICK UP YOUR SON.
YOU CAN'T COME OVER HERE.
DON'T CONTACT MY PHONE NO MORE.
YOU CAN'T TALK TO US."
I CAN'T BE THERE FOR MY SON
IF I'M NOT EVEN ALLOWED TO.
I DON'T HAVE RIGHTS TO MY SON.
I'M NOT ON THE BIRTH
CERTIFICATE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN GO
OVER THERE
AND PICK HIM UP
WHETHER SHE SAY SO OR NOT,
YOU KNOW?
>> ARIANNA?
>> HE'S FULL OF CRAP.
>> SHE CAN'T EVEN
LOOK AT YOU NOW.
>> EXACTLY.
SHE WON'T LOOK AT MY FACE.
>> BECAUSE I'M DISGUSTED
WITH HIM.
>> YOU CAN'T LOOK SOMEBODY
IN THE EYE. WHY?
>> WHY ARE YOU DISGUSTED?
>> BECAUSE HE'S
A DEADBEAT FATHER.
>> I'M A DEADBEAT FATHER, BUT
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO COME SEE MY
SON.
I'M A DEADBEAT FATHER,
BUT I DONE BROUGHT OVER PLENTY.
SO I'M A DEADBEAT FATHER,
BUT I GOT A CREDIT UNION
AND EVERYTHING SET UP.
HE'S GOT $3,200 DOLLARS
TO HIS NAME RIGHT NOW.
>> NO, HE DOESN'T BRING ANYTHING
FOR MY SON.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU--
>> I TOOK $3,200 DOLLARS CASH
OUT OF MY POCKET,
FROM MY LAWYER.
>> I DIDN'T COME ON HERE
TO ARGUE WITH HIM.
>> WHY IS THERE A LAWYER
INVOLVED?
>> A LAWYER IS INVOLVED
BECAUSE I CAN'T EVEN
COME TO THE RESIDENCE
TO SEE MY SON.
>> THAT'S A LIE.
>> TO GET VISITATION OR CUSTODY.
>> TO GET CUSTODY OF MY SON--
>> NO, THAT'LL NEVER HAPPEN.
>> SO I CAN TAKE MY SON
TO MY FAMILY
BECAUSE HE'S MY SON.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO SEE MY SIDE
OF THE FAMILY.
>> DID YOU GET A LETTER
FROM A LAWYER?
>> NO.
>> SHE DIDN'T GET A LETTER.
>> I'M PRETTY SURE
SHE GOT A LETTER
BECAUSE I GOT
MINE YESTERDAY.
>> DEFINITELY DIDN'T GET
A LETTER.
>> I CAN CALL MY LAWYER
RIGHT NOW ON TV, RIGHT NOW.
>> WOULDN'T YOU SAY
IT IS RESPONSIBLE OF HIM
TO WANT TO GET FORMAL CUSTODY
OR VISITATION THAT'S
A STRUCTURED, REASONABLE--
>> MY SON IS SIX MONTHS OLD.
IF HE REALLY LOVED MY SON,
THIS WOULD HAVE BEEN DONE
A LONG TIME AGO.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE,
ASIDE FROM YOUR RAGE, RIGHT?
YOUR RAGE, YOUR DISGUST,
AND THE OTHER THING
IS SORT OF RESENTMENT TOO.
IT SEEMS LIKE, IN YOUR EPISODE,
THE RESENTMENT STARTED WHEN HE
ASKED YOU FOR A PATERNITY TEST.
>> I WAS CONFUSED AS TO WHY.
>> WELL, LET'S GET
TO STRAIGHTEN THAT OUT.
WHY THE PATERNITY TEST?
>> I ASKED HER
FOR THE PATERNITY TEST
FOR THE CLARIFICATION
FOR MY FAMILY.
>> YOUR FAMILY.
THEY DIDN'T BUY IT. OKAY.
>> DID YOU GET A PATERNITY TEST?
>> NO.
>> NO, WE NEVER GOT
A PATERNITY TEST; SHE DIDN'T
WANT TO GET ONE.
AND I'M FILING FOR ONE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE I WANT TO MAKE
SURE HE'S MINE.
'CAUSE SHE TOLD ME THAT HE
WASN'T MINE AT ONE POINT.
>> THAT'S A LIE.
>> YOU DIDN'T SAY THAT?
>> THAT IS A LIE.
>> SHE TOLD ME HE WASN'T MINE,
FIRST OF ALL.
>> YOU SURE YOU DIDN'T
IN A RAGE OR SOMETHING?
>> I'M SURE I DIDN'T.
I'M POSITIVE.
>> I'M 100--I DON'T HAVE
NO REASON TO LIE.
>> IS THERE ANY CHANCE
IT'S NOT YOUR--
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU LYING
FOR EVERYTHING, LIKE,
ALL THIS--
>> THIS IS A CHANCE
TO TALK TO HIM.
>> NO, I DON'T WANT
>> OUTSIDE IN THE WORLD
IT'S GONNA GET OUT OF CONTROL.
>> NO, NO, NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
>> I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THERE
FOR MY SON; I ALWAYS HAVE BREAD.
I'M GOOD. I'M SET.
>> WHERE IS IT?
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> I'VE GOT NONE OF IT. DON'T.
DON'T EVEN.
>> I'D PICK THAT
UP IF I WERE YOU.
IF I WERE YOU.
THAT'S BABY MONEY.
>> [bleep] YOU, BITCH.
>> THAT'S BABY MONEY.
THAT'S BABY MONEY TO ME.
I SAID I BEEN ON MY JOB.
I BEEN GRINDING.
I'M NOT NO JOKE.
I CARE ABOUT MY SON.
>> I'M JUST COUNTING
WHAT'S HERE,
>> OH, THAT'S A GOOD--
>> HANG ON,
AND THIS WOULD COVER FORMULA
FOR ABOUT THREE DAYS.
>> OH, NO.
THAT'S JUST PLAY MONEY.
SHE CAN HAVE THIS BECAUSE SHE
COMPLAINING, BUT LIKE I SAID,
I GOT A CREDIT UNION
WITH $3,200 DOLLARS FOR MY SON.
YOU FEEL ME, THESE PHONES
RIGHT HERE,
THESE $500.
YOU TELLING ME,
THAT'S JUST BABY MONEY.
>> THAT SHOULD HAVE GONE
TO THE BABY.
>> WHAT YOU MEAN?
IT WENT TO
MY LAWYER SO I COULD GET MY SON.
>> ALL THAT MONEY
THAT YOU SPENT ON SHOES
AND A WATCH
SHOULD HAVE GONE TO THE BABY.
>> ONCE I GET THIS CUSTODY,
MY SON GONNA COME HOME SET.
TRUST ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LET'S TAKE A QUICK BREAK,
AND LET'S SEE IF WE CAN RESET
THINGS HERE A LITTLE BIT
AND GET ARIANNA
BACK ON FOR US, OKAY?
>> SO, MAURICE,
HELP ME UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU INTENDED WITH THIS.
I MEAN,
ARIANNA FLEW OUT OF HERE.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN WITH THIS?
>> SHE ASKED ME WHERE IS IT AT.
OKAY, OBVIOUSLY I GOT IT,
SO I JUST SHOWED HER AND JUST
CHANGED THE WAY I SHOWED HER.
>> SO YOU JUST MADE A GESTURE.
>> YEAH, A GESTURE.
TO SHOW I GOT IT.
I'M SET.
>> I'M GONNA SEND THE PRODUCTION
STAFF BACK TO SEE
IF THEY CAN GET ARIANNA TO AGREE
TO COME BACK ONSTAGE HERE,
AND IF THEY CAN BRING HER BACK
OUT, WE'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
>> SHE CAN PICK THE MONEY UP,
TOO, WHEN SHE COME
BACK OUT HERE.
>> LISTEN, SHE'S NOT GOING
TO PICK THE MONEY UP.
ARIANNA, THANK YOU FOR AGREEING
TO COME BACK OUT.
>> MOVE.
>> I'M SORRY I DIDN'T MOVE NOW.
>> OH, SHE DON'T WANT MY MONEY
NOW, WHAT?
>> MAURICE HOLD ON A SECOND.
SO WHAT DID THAT FEEL
LIKE FOR YOU?
>> HE'S DISRESPECTFUL.
HE HAS NO HOME TRAINING.
>> SO THAT WAS DISRESPECTFUL.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
>> WHEN YOU GUYS WERE A COUPLE,
YOU SORT OF GOT ALONG, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT WENT WRONG?
WHERE DID THIS GO SO FAR
OFF TRACK?
>> A CHILD
CAME INTO THE PICTURE,
AND HE'S A LITTLE BOY,
AND HE CAN'T HANDLE IT.
>> SO YOU NEEDED HIM TO STEP UP,
AND HE WASN'T WILLING TO
OR ABLE TO.
>> AGAIN, WE STARTED BY TALKING
ABOUT HOW HURTFUL
THIS IS TO YOU.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THIS MUST HURT EVEN MORE.
>> NO, HE'S DISRESPECTFUL.
THAT'S ALL IT IS.
>> BUT THAT HURTS. THAT HURTS.
>> BECAUSE HE'S DISRESPECTFUL.
I FEEL SORRY FOR HIM
BECAUSE HE HAS NO HOME TRAINING.
HE MADE HIMSELF LOOK
STUPID, NOT ME.
I DON'T LOOK STUPID.
>> I DON'T LOOK STUPID.
>> YEAH, BUT YOUR CHILD
ENDS UP WITH NO DAD.
DON'T YOU WANT TO TRY TO--
>> HE DOESN'T NEED A--SOMEONE
LIKE THAT IN HIS LIFE.
>> WHY WOULD I HAND
OVER NO BREAD
IF I'M FILING WITH A LAWYER
TO GET CUSTODY?
HOW IS HE GONNA HAVE A DAD?
>> WEREN'T YOU TALKING TO ME?
>> I'M TRYING TO TALK
TO BOTH OF YOU.
WE'RE TRYING TO KEEP
THIS A LITTLE BIT BALANCED.
RIGHT, HE'S THE DAD.
>> I AM THE DAD.
THAT'S WHY I'M DOING
MY DADLY THING,
WHICH IS WHY I'M TAKING HER
TO COURT SO I CAN GET MY SON
BECAUSE I DO CARE, SO...
>> AND YOUR CHILD.
YOU WOULD LIKE YOUR CHILD
TO HAVE A DAD, HIS DAD.
>> AND HE WILL.
>> IF HE ACTS LIKE THIS,
DEFINITELY NOT.
NO, NO.
>> AND THIS
BEING CHILDISH, DISRESPECTFUL.
>> YES, IF A JUDGE
SEES THIS, DO YOU THINK
HE'S GONNA LET HIM HAVE MY SON?
THAT'S A JOKE. IT'S A JOKE.
>> WHY?
HE HAS MONEY; WHY WOULDN'T HE
LET HIM HAVE HIS SON?
>> WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SEE FROM MAURICE?
JUST FINANCIAL SUPPORT
AND THAT'S IT?
>> NO, HE HAS TO CHANGE
AS A PERSON.
HE'S CRAZY.
HE'S CHILDISH.
HE'S IRRESPONSIBLE.
HE'S SELFISH.
>> EVERYBODY SEEN THE EPISODE
WHERE I WAS--
>> AND HE'S GHETTO AND RATCHET
AND I'M NOT.
>> WOW.
>> SO ARIANNA,
NOW'S AIDEN DOING?
>> HE'S DOING GREAT.
HE'S MAKING A LOT OF--
LIKE HIS MOTOR SKILLS
ARE GETTING
MORE AND MORE ADVANCED
EVERY DAY.
>> HOW OLD IS HE NOW?
>> SIX MONTHS.
>> SO HE'S STARTING TO CRAWL?
>> NO HE CAN'T CRAWL.
HE CAN FLIP FROM HIS BACK
TO HIS BELLY
AND HE CAN DO--YOU KNOW,
LIKE, SIT UP LIKE THIS,
BUT HE CAN'T CRAWL.
>> NICE, AND HE'S HAPPY?
>> YES. HE'S VERY HAPPY.
>> THAT MAKES YOU HAPPY,
THAT'S GOOD.
AND HE DOES LOVE HIS SON.
WHATEVER ELSE YOU SAY ABOUT
MAURICE, WE GOT THAT AT LEAST.
>> OH, I KNOW THAT HE DOES.
>> SMALL STEPS. BABY STEPS.
KEEP THE GOOD THINGS IN MIND.
OKAY?
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF OTHER STORIES
TO GET TO TODAY.
AND COMING UP,
WE WILL TALK TO SAVANNAH
ABOUT WHAT IT'S LIKE TO CALL
THE COPS ON HER OWN MOM.
STAY TUNED FOR MORE 16
AND PREGNANT: LIFE AFTER LABOR.
>> WELCOME BACK.
I'M JOINED NOW
BY SAVANNAH AND STONE,
AND AN UNFORTUNATE RECURRING
THEME OF THIS SEASON
WAS THE ISSUE OF SUBSTANCE ABUSE
AND ADDICTION.
THREE EPISODES FEATURED TEENS
WHOSE MOTHERS THEMSELVES
STRUGGLED WITH ADDICTION WHICH,
OF COURSE, INCLUDED SAVANNAH.
HERE'S A LOOK BACK
AT HOW SHE DEALT WITH
HER MOTHER'S ALCOHOLISM.
>> I DON'T HAVE TO BE WITH YOU
TO PARENT, I REALLY DON'T.
>> I NEVER SAID YOU DID.
>> WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
YOU DID TELL ME
WE WERE GONNA DO THIS TOGETHER,
AND I FEEL
LIKE I'M DOING THIS WITHOUT YOU
BECAUSE OF YOUR DRINKING.
>> YOU'RE WRONG.
>> DO YOU GUYS FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH THE BABY BEING WITH ME?
>> YOU GOT A MAJOR PROBLEM.
>> OLD HABITS ARE HARD TO BREAK.
STOP SLAMMING DOORS.
I'LL GET THE COPS OVER HERE.
>> DO IT.
>> EVERYTHING'LL WORK OUT
THE WAY IT'S SUPPOSED TO.
I JUST HOPE IT COMES
SOONER RATHER THAN LATER.
>> YOU'RE GETTING A LITTLE TEARY
JUST LOOKING AT THE EPISODE.
WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
>> EMBARRASSMENT.
>> EMBARRASSED?
WHY?
>> BECAUSE IT WAS EASY
TO HIDE WHEN IT WASN'T PUBLIC.
>> WELL, BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE
DEAL WITH THIS, A LOT OF PEOPLE.
IT'S A COMMON THING
YOUR MOM'S GOT.
IT'S DIFFERENT WHEN IT'S
YOUR MOM THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW HARD WAS IT FOR YOU
TO CONFRONT HER THAT WAY?
>> EXTREMELY HARD.
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN FOR SO LONG
IT WAS ME AND MY MOM
AND ALL WE HAD WAS EACH OTHER,
AND I FEEL
LIKE CONFRONTING HER LIKE THAT
ONLY HURT HER FEELINGS.
>> AND SHE'S BEEN TO TREATMENT
MULTIPLE TIMES, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> SO SHE KNOWS
WHAT SHE NEEDS TO DO.
SHE'S NOT DOING IT.
SO IT'S ON HER.
SHE'S RIGHT ON THAT ONE.
BUT IT'S HEARTBREAKING TO SEE
SOMEBODY YOU LOVE DO THAT.
ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HARD.
WELL, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
YOU HAVE STONE NOW IN YOUR LIFE.
HAS HE BEEN HELPFUL?
>> FOR THE MOST PART.
WHAT'S YOUR RELATIONSHIP STATUS
NOW, YOU TWO?
NO RELATIONSHIP.
>> NO.
>> AS WE LEFT THE SEASON,
IT SEEMED LIKE YOU
TWO WERE GETTING TOGETHER.
>> TRYING TO.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> JUST CAN'T DO IT.
>> WHY?
>> A LOT OF ARGUING--I
DON'T KNOW WHAT STARTS IT,
BUT IT'S A LOT.
>> MY UNDERSTANDING IS,
WHEN YOU WATCHED THE EPISODE,
YOU HAD A LOT OF EMOTION.
>> YEAH.
THERE WAS A LOT OF STUFF
THAT I DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT
UNTIL I WATCHED IT AND THEN
I FIGURED IT OUT.
>> LIKE WHAT?
>> HER TALKING TO OTHER GUYS
WHEN WE WERE TRYING
TO GET BACK TOGETHER,
AND IT WAS A LOT, YOU KNOW.
I THOUGHT WE WERE GONNA
MAKE IT WORK AND HAVE A FAMILY,
AND THAT WAS APPARENTLY NOT
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
>> IS THAT WHY--
TELL ME WHAT HE'S TALKING ABOUT.
>> WHEN WE BROKE UP,
I--AND LATER ON,
IN THE BEGINNING OF MY PREGNANCY
WE BROKE UP.
AND THEN LATER ON WE
TRIED TO FIX THINGS.
WHILE DOING SO
I DID KEEP MY OPTIONS OPEN
AND WAS ENTERTAINING THE IDEA
OF A DIFFERENT PERSON.
>> WHILE YOU WERE BROKEN UP
DURING YOUR PREGNANCY?
>> YES.
>> AND THAT'S
WHAT YOU SAW IN THE EPISODE
THAT GOT YOU UPSET.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THAT?
>> NO, AND JUST UNDER A MONTH
BEFORE SHE GIVES BIRTH.
>> DO YOU WANT
TO GET BACK TOGETHER?
OH, WELL THAT'S PRETTY CLEAR.
WHAT DO YOU DO WITH THAT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE
IN A RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE HE MADE ME
MISERABLE MY WHOLE PREGNANCY
AND I CAN'T LET GO OF IT.
>> YOU CAN'T LET GO OF IT.
HOW DID HE MAKE YOU MISERABLE?
>> THE DAY
AFTER I TOOK THE PREGNANCY TEST
AND FOUND OUT I WAS PREGNANT
IS WHEN IT ALL CHANGED.
I WAS CALLED WORTHLESS
FOR TURNING OFF THE TV
AND WANTING YOUR ATTENTION.
>> YOU NEVER WANTED
MY ATTENTION.
>> I WANTED YOUR ATTENTION
SO BAD.
SO BAD, STONE,
I WANTED YOUR ATTENTION.
I WANTED TO BE TREATED
LIKE THE MOTHER OF YOUR CHILD
AND NOT PROPERTY.
I WANTED TO BE TREATED
WITH RESPECT
AND ACTUALLY FELT
LIKE YOU LOVED ME.
EVERY DAY YOU PUT ME DOWN.
>> EVERY DAY I FELT LIKE YOU
WERE EMBARRASSED TO BE WITH ME,
EVEN BEFORE ALL THIS.
>> I WAS SO PROUD TO HAVE YOUR--
I WAS SO PROUD TO BE WITH YOU
AND TO SAY
I WAS CARRYING YOUR BABY.
>> I FEEL THAT THERE WAS NEVER
ANY COMMITMENT
IN THE RELATIONSHIP.
IT WAS ALWAYS A MORE
OF AN OPEN RELATIONSHIP,
ONE-SIDED OPEN RELATIONSHIP,
I MEAN.
>> YOU MEAN SHE WAS ALLOWED
TO SEE OTHER GUYS
AND YOU WEREN'T ALLOWED
TO SEE OTHER GIRLS?
IS THAT WHAT YOU MEAN?
I'M JUST ASKING.
>> IT FELT LIKE IT.
ARE YOU SEEING SOMEBODY ELSE?
HAVE YOU MOVED ON?
>> YEAH.
>> SO SHE'S KIND OF MOVED ON.
HAVE YOU?
HAVE YOU MOVED ON?
PRETTY MUCH.
WITH ALL THIS GOING ON,
HOW DO YOU GUYS PARENT?
DO YOU CO-PARENT?
>> TRYING TO.
>> ARE YOU SEEING THE BABY
ENOUGH?
ARE YOU SEEING THE BABY
ENOUGH FOR YOU?
IS HE PARTICIPATING?
>> YEAH. HE'S AN AWESOME DAD.
>> HAS SHE EVER TOLD YOU THAT?
>> YEAH.
AND I'VE NEVER QUESTIONED
HER MOTHERING SKILLS EITHER.
>> SO FROM THE STANDPOINT
OF YOUR CHILD,
THINGS LOOK PEACEFUL.
SAVANNAH, WHAT IS YOUR HOPE
FROM NOW ON FROM BOTH OF YOU?
FROM HIS PERSPECTIVE,
WHAT'S YOUR WISH?
>> THAT STONE AND I WILL LEARN
TO HAVE A HEALTHY
CO-PARENTING RELATIONSHIP,
AND SHOW ROW THAT EVEN THOUGH
HIS PARENTS AREN'T TOGETHER,
WE CAN STILL GET ALONG.
>> OKAY, I CAN'T IMAGINE THAT
YOU'RE GONNA BE MUCH DIFFERENT.
>> NO.
>> SAME.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS ANYWHERE
NEAR THAT GOAL?
>> NO. FAR FROM IT.
>> LET'S GO BACK
TO HOW WE GOT TO THIS SITUATION,
WHICH WAS LACK OF INFORMATION
ABOUT CONTRACEPTION, RIGHT?
YOU DID NOT UNDERSTAND YOU COULD
GET PREGNANT, IS THAT ACCURATE?
>> WELL, I DIDN'T THINK
IT WOULD HAPPEN TO ME.
>> WHY?
>> I NEVER THOUGHT
IT WOULD HAPPEN BECAUSE,
WELL, I WAS IN A RELATIONSHIP
FOR A YEAR
AND A HALF PRIOR TO STONE,
AND I NEVER USED PROTECTION,
AND I NEVER GOT PREGNANT.
>> SO WISHFUL THINKING.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL THE WAY ALONG.
>> STONE, HOW ABOUT YOU?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> CONDOMS.
>> AND WHAT ABOUT YOU?
>> I HAVE THE I.U.D.
>> I.U.D. GOOD. FANTASTIC.
SO GOOD.
AND IF YOU WERE TALKING
TO ANOTHER 16-YEAR-OLD
WHO WAS THINKING THE WAY
YOU USED TO THINK,
WHAT WOULD YOU TELL THEM?
>> BIRTH CONTROL.
>> "YOU CAN GET PREGNANT;
JUST LISTEN TO ME."
WELL, GUYS,
THANK YOU FOR SHARING THE STORY,
BUT PLEASE FIND A COMMON GROUND
ON BEHALF OF ROWAN.
ALL RIGHT,
WE NEED TO TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
SO WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> PREGNANCY AND PARENTHOOD
PUT A HUGE FINANCIAL STRAIN
ON A COUPLE, ESPECIALLY IF
THE PARENTS ARE TEENAGERS.
THE FACT IS, NEARLY HALF
OF ALL TEEN MOMS
LIVE BELOW THE POVERTY LINE.
JORDAN AND HER BOYFRIEND
DEREK WERE HOMELESS
THROUGH MUCH OF HER PREGNANCY,
MAKING NINE MONTHS
THAT ARE ALREADY REALLY
DIFFICULT, THAT MUCH HARDER.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> WE ARE BASICALLY HOMELESS.
I HATE LIVING OUT OF THIS CAR.
RIGHT NOW WE HAVE NO MEANS
OF SUPPORTING A BABY.
WOULD WE BE ABLE TO STAY HERE?
>> THERE'S NO ROOM.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD ACTUALLY,
LIKE, GO AND GET A JOB.
>> SHE NEEDS HELP.
>> WE'RE LIVING
IN SOMEBODY'S LIVING ROOM.
THAT'S TOTALLY [bleep] UP.
THERE ISN'T NOWHERE TO GO.
FIGURE THAT [bleep] OUT.
>> THE BABY DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THE FUTURE HOLDS FOR MYSELF
AND GENEVIEVE AND DEREK.
>> THERE YOU GO.
WHAT ARE YOU CRYING ABOUT?
>> THAT WAS A REALLY HARD TIME.
>> NO KIDDING.
YOU GUYS WERE HOMELESS.
>> A REALLY HARD TIME.
>> IS IT JUST PAINFUL
TO LOOK BACK ON IT?
HOW DID YOU DIG OUT?
>> WE HAD A LOT OF HELP.
WE DEFINITELY DIDN'T DO
IT BY OURSELVES.
WE GOT HELP FROM FAMILY FRIENDS.
MY GRANDMOM COULD HELP
IN ANY WAY SHE COULD.
>> YOU GUYS WENT DOWN TO TEXAS,
RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DID THAT WORK OUT?
>> WELL, IT WAS FINE.
IT WAS NICE.
I LIKED IT A LOT,
BUT HE NEEDS TO GO TO SCHOOL.
HE HAS A SCHOLARSHIP AND I
DIDN'T WANT HIM TO LOSE THAT,
SO WE HAVE TO GO BACK
TO MARYLAND.
>> GO BACK TO MARYLAND.
AND AGAIN THE TEARS ARE ABOUT
HOW DESPERATE YOU FELT?
>> YEAH.
IT WAS SO UPSETTING TO KNOW
I COULDN'T SUPPORT MY OWN CHILD.
TO KNOW THAT I WAS LIVING
OFF OF SOMEONE ELSE,
IN THEIR HOME,
IN A LIVING ROOM WITH A BABY.
AND I HADN'T BOUGHT HER ANYTHING
BECAUSE I COULDN'T.
IT WAS JUST STUFF
THAT OTHER PEOPLE
BOUGHT THAT'S EMBARRASSING.
YOU BRING A CHILD
INTO THE WORLD,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE ABLE TO SUPPORT THEM,
AND I COULDN'T AND THAT MADE
ME FEEL TERRIBLE.
>> AND YOU WERE LAYING A LOT
OF THAT ON DEREK, RIGHT?
AND THEN HE, AT FIRST,
DIDN'T KICK IN.
THAT MUST HAVE MADE
YOU FEEL MORE DESPERATE.
>> YEAH. THAT STRESSED ME OUT.
HE WAS DEFINITELY WAY
MORE RELAXED THAN I WAS.
>> WHAT WAS THAT LIKE GOING
THROUGH FOR YOU?
>> IT WAS SUPER STRESSFUL.
I JUST HANDLE MY STRESS A LOT
DIFFERENTLY.
>> CAN YOU APPRECIATE
WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT?
DID YOU FEEL ANY OF THAT?
>> OH, YEAH. YEAH.
>> AND WHO WAS IT
THAT YOU WERE LIVING WITH?
>> HER NAME'S TRACY.
>> DO YOU STILL
HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH HER?
>> I TALK TO HER OCCASIONALLY.
SHE WAS ONE
OF HIS DAD'S FRIENDS.
>> SHE'S KEY IN YOU GETTING
THROUGH THIS, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> A HUGE PART.
>> WE SHOULD ALL SAY A BIG
THANK YOU TO TRACY, FOR SURE.
>> VERY APPRECIATIVE.
>> WHAT WAS YOUR FEAR
DURING THAT TIME?
>> THAT WE WOULD STILL BE
IN THE SAME SITUATION
WHEN SHE WAS BORN AND I WOULD BE
TAKING HER FROM PLACE
TO PLACE TO PLACE,
OR I WOULD HAVE NOWHERE FOR HER.
>> I'M JUST CURIOUS
HOW YOU'RE GOING TO SUPPORT
YOURSELF NOW IN MARYLAND
AND GO TO SCHOOL.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF HELP STILL.
HIS FAMILY IS A BIG HELP. YEAH.
>> SO PEOPLE ARE STEPPING UP
STILL.
>> YES.
>> SO WHAT IS IT THAT YOU
WANT TO GO TO SCHOOL FOR?
>> I WANT TO DO KINESIOLOGY
EVENTUALLY,
BUT I'M GOING TO GO
TO A COMMUNITY COLLEGE FIRST
AND AT LEAST GET MY A.A.
>> ULTIMATELY PHYSICAL THERAPY.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
>> AND WHERE DO YOU STAND
WITH YOUR PARENTS NOW?
>> I TALK TO THEM, OCCASIONALLY.
>> AND THAT'S IT?
>> YEAH.
>> JUST CORDIAL?
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I'LL SEND
MY DAD PICTURES OF THE BABY.
>> IF I GET THE STORY RIGHT,
WASN'T IT DEREK
THEY HAD THE PROBLEM WITH,
NOT YOU?
>> THEY ACTUALLY REALLY
LIKED HIM.
>> SO WHO WAS KICKED OUT?
>> HE WAS.
>> HE WAS KICKED OUT,
AND YOU JUST WENT WITH HIM.
>> YES.
>> SO YOU WEREN'T ACTUALLY
KICKED OUT, YOU LEFT.
>> TECHNICALLY, YES.
>> NOW YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THAT FAMILY IS--
>> IT'S GETTING BETTER.
DO THEY COME SEE EVIE?
>> YES. THEY HAVE SEEN HER.
>> AND YOUR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THEM WHEN THEY COME VISIT?
>> IT'S CORDIAL.
>> CORDIAL.
SO IF YOU WERE TALKING
TO YOURSELF BACK THEN NOW
AS YOU KNOW YOURSELF,
WHAT WOULD YOU TELL YOURSELF?
WHAT YOU TELL JORDAN WHEN SHE'S
FIXING TO HAVE SEX WITH DEREK?
>> TO USE A CONDOM?
I MEAN, I WAS ON BIRTH CONTROL
BUT I STOPPED TAKING IT
FOR WHATEVER REASON.
I DIDN'T LIKE THE ONE I WAS ON.
I JUST NEVER GOT A NEW ONE.
HE DID NOT LIKE CONDOMS
AND I DIDN'T ARGUE ABOUT IT.
>> I THINK YOU SAID THAT CONDOMS
WERE LIKE PUNISHMENT.
>> IT FEELS THAT WAY.
>> AGAIN, I TOLD--SOMETHING
I SAY REPEATEDLY TO YOUNG MEN
IS, PRACTICE PUTTING THEM ON,
OR PRACTICE DIFFERENT TYPES,
FIND WHAT WORKS.
YOU SPENT A LOT OF TIME
DOING A LOT OF OTHER STUFF,
HOW MANY HOURS A WEEK
DO YOU SPEND PAYING VIDEO GAMES?
>> NOW? BARELY.
>> OKAY, BARELY.
I'M JUST SAYING.
I'M JUST SAYING THAT YOU
OUGHT TO FIGURE OUT A WAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
>> I AM ON BIRTH CONTROL,
BUT I'M IN THE PROCESS
OF CHANGING IT BECAUSE THEY
HAVE DIFFERENT KINDS
FOR IF YOU'RE BREASTFEEDING
WITH THE LOWER ESTROGEN.
I'M ON THAT ONE,
BUT I WOULD LIKE TO SWITCH.
>> THE PILL.
>> YES.
>> WELL, GOOD LUCK TO YOU GUYS
BACK IN MARYLAND,
AND PARTICULARLY
WITH YOUR TRAINING.
THAT'S GONNA
MAKE A BIG DIFFERENCE
IN WHAT YOUR FINANCIAL
OPPORTUNITIES
ARE GONNA BE IF YOU
FOLLOW THROUGH ON THESE THINGS.
SO THANK YOU FOR SHARING.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
OKAY, WHEN WE GET BACK,
WE WILL TALK TO SUMMER,
AND SHE RECENTLY HAD TO DEAL
WITH HER BABY'S FATHER CHEATING.
AND REMEMBER, IT IS NOT ENOUGH
TO JUST THINK ABOUT PREVENTION,
YOU ACTUALLY HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING.
SO FOR MORE INFORMATION, HEAD
OVER TO 16ANDPREGNANT.MTV.COM.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> SITTING BESIDE ME ARE SUMMER
AND D.J., AND MY UNDERSTANDING
IS THAT SINCE WE LEFT OFF
YOUR RELATIONSHIP
HAS BEEN A LITTLE BIT
TUMULTUOUS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> OH,
WE JUST GOT IN AN ARGUMENT.
WHEN I SEEN HER LEAVING,
I THOUGHT WE WAS DONE
OR WHATEVER.
I DID WHAT I DID.
>> WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> WELL, I CAUGHT A GIRL
OVER TO THE HOUSE OR WHATEVER.
WE WAS HANGING OUT,
JUST CHILLING.
>> TO HER HOUSE?
>> YEAH.
>> TO YOUR HOUSE?
>> TO OUR HOUSE.
I WALKED ME IN THE HOUSE
AND THEY WERE WALKING OUT
AT THE SAME TIME,
AND SHE HAD HIS JACKET ON,
AND I'M JUST LIKE,
"TAKE HIS JACKET OFF."
AND SHE'S LIKE, "I DON'T HAVE
A SHIRT ON UNDERNEATH THIS."
AND ME NOT THINKING,
"WHY DON'T YOU HAVE A SHIRT ON?"
I'M JUST PISSED BECAUSE SHE'S
IN MY HOUSE PERIOD, YOU KNOW.
LATER WE TALKED ABOUT IT
AND HE TOLD ME EVERYTHING AND--
>> DID SHE TAKE THE JACKET OFF?
>> YEAH, SHE TOOK HIS
JACKET OFF.
>> SHE DIDN'T HAVE A SHIRT ON?
>> UH-UH.
SHE WALKED TO HIS MAMA'S HOUSE
IN HER BRA.
I'M JUST LIKE, "GIRL, NO,
LIKE, PUT YOUR SHIRT ON."
SHE'S TRASHY.
SHE'S DISGUSTING.
>> YOU'RE PRETTY FORGIVING,
SUMMER.
>> I'M NOT OVER IT YET.
>> WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
>> IT HURTS MY FEELINGS.
>> YOU SAID IT WITH A SMILE,
THOUGH.
>> BECAUSE I'M GONNA CRY.
IT'S JUST THE FACT THAT YOU
HAD SEX WITH A GIRL IN MY HOUSE
THAT WE RAISE OUR BABY IN AND--
>> THAT'S GOT TO BE HARD.
>> [sniffling]
>> YOU ARE PRETTY FORGIVING,
THOUGH.
IS THAT ANGER I'M SEEING?
>> NO, IT JUST HURTS
MY FEELINGS.
>> WHAT DOES D.J. NEED TO DO
TO MAKE THAT BETTER?
>> WELL, NOT DO IT AGAIN.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> D.J., YOU KNOW IT HURTS
HER FEELINGS?
>> YOU KNEW THAT?
>> YEAH, I DO.
>> OR YOU JUST SEE THE ANGER.
>> I KNOW IT HURTS HER FEELINGS.
I'D BE THE SAME WAY, YOU KNOW.
THE ONLY THING WE CAN DO IS MOVE
FORWARD FROM HERE, YOU KNOW?
>> HAVE YOU APOLOGIZED?
>> A MILLION TIMES.
>> A MILLION TIMES, GOOD.
THAT'S WHAT IT NEEDS.
ARE YOU ACCEPTING
OF THE APOLOGY,
TO THE EXTENT THAT YOU CAN?
>> I TRY.
>> I'M TELLING YOU,
IT TAKES MORE THAN AN APOLOGY.
IT TAKES SHOWING IT,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YEAH.
YOU GOT TO REBUILD THE TRUST.
>> DO YOU TRUST HIM NOW?
>> UH-UH.
>> NO, HOW OLD WERE YOU GUYS
WHEN YOU GOT MARRIED?
>> I WAS 16.
>> OH, IT'S A LOT.
FOR PEOPLE TO CHEAT
ON BOYFRIENDS AND GIRLFRIENDS
IN YOUR AGE GROUP
IS NOT UNUSUAL,
BUT WHEN YOU'RE MARRIED
AND HAVE A KID INVOLVED,
YOU DON'T GET
TO MAKE THOSE MISTAKES.
WELL, SUMMER AND D.J.
ARE MOVING FORWARD.
SHE'S GONNA FORGIVE HIM.
HE'S GONNA REBUILD
THAT TRUST,
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE RELATIONSHIP
WITH SUMMER'S MOM
WHICH WAS STRAINED
BY AN ADDICTION TO PILLS?
HERE'S A QUICK REMINDER OF
WHAT SUMMER HAD
BEEN DEALING WITH.
>> WHEN YOU'RE MESSED UP I JUST
DON'T WANT TO BE AROUND YOU.
>> PILLS CAN TAKE YOU DOWN
A ROAD YOU DON'T WANT TO GO.
>> QUIT IT, MOM.
>> KISS ME.
>> [bleep]
MAMA IS SO MESSED UP,
I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO GO IN THIS RESTAURANT.
>> I'M JUST EMBARRASSED.
>> I LIKE HOW YOU'RE PAYING
FOR A PIT BULL
INSTEAD OF PAYING
FOR SOMETHING FOR PEYTON.
>> I LIKE HOW YOU EVEN
GOT A SAY-SO IN ANY OF THIS.
THIS AIN'T NO FAIRY TALE.
>> NOW, SUMMER, YOU MOM
WAS SUPPOSED TO JOIN US TODAY,
RIGHT; WHAT HAPPENED?
>> SEE, YOU CANNOT DEPEND
ON HER FOR ANYTHING.
I MEAN, I DON'T CARE.
IT HURTS MY FEELINGS, BUT SHE'S
DONE IT SINCE I WAS, LIKE, NINE.
>> IT MEANING PILLS.
>> YES.
>> IN THAT EPISODE WE SAW HER
FACING A COUPLE OF YEARS IN JAIL
FOR THE BAD CHECKS.
>> YES, SHE ENDED UP JUST
GETTING TEN YEARS OF PROBATION.
>> WHAT KINDS OF CONSEQUENCES
HAS HER PILL USE HAD ON YOU?
>> JUST THAT I DIDN'T GET
TO SEE HER.
IT HURT ME THAT I DIDN'T GET
TO GROW UP WITH MY MAMA.
>> AND DID SHE DO SOMETHING
THAT CAUSED HER TO BE
TAKEN AWAY FROM YOU?
>> NOPE, SHE JUST TOOK ME
TO MY DADDY'S AND SAID--
>> OH, SHE WAS UNLOADING YOU.
>> OH, YEAH, SHE SAID,
"HERE, YOU TAKE CARE OF HER.
I DON'T WANT TO BE A MOMMY
ANYMORE."
>> WOW.
>> CAN YOU IMAGINE
DOING THAT WITH PEYTON?
>> NO, I CAN'T.
IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY
BEING AWAY FROM HIM RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU HAVE, AS YOU SAID,
THE YOUNGER HALF-SISTERS.
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU GOT PREGNANT.
HAVE YOU TALKED TO THEM
ABOUT BIRTH CONTROL
OR HOW TO AVOID THIS?
>> YES, TYLER, THE MIDDLE ONE,
I THINK HER AND THE YOUNGEST
GOT ON THE DEPO SHOT,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT MY OTHER SISTER.
>> WEREN'T YOU ON DEPO
AT ONE TIME?
>> NO, I WAS ON THE IMPLANON.
>> IMPLANON.
WHEN YOU GOT PREGNANT?
NO, I HAD GOT IT TAKEN OUT.
I THINK IT WAS TIME UP FOR IT.
AND NOW I JUST
STARTED TAKING THE PILL,
BUT I ALWAYS FORGOT
TO TAKE THE PILL,
SO WE WERE USING CONDOMS, TOO,
BUT IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TAKING NOW?
>> I'M ON THE NEW MIRENA,
BUT I DON'T LIKE IT SO I THINK
I'M GONNA GET THE DEPO SHOT
NEXT TIME.
>> NOW, I KNOW YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT THE CYCLE OF ADDICTION.
THE GENETICS OF ADDICTION,
DO YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU HAVE THAT POTENTIAL?
>> YES, I WOULDN'T EVEN
TAKE PAIN MEDICATION AFTERWARDS.
AFTER MY LABOR, YES.
>> AFTER THE PREGNANCY.
DID YOU HAVE AN EPIDURAL
OR ANYTHING?
>> I DID, BUT I GOT IT
AT EIGHT CENTIMETERS
SO IT DIDN'T KICK
IN UNTIL AFTER I HAD PEYTON.
IT WAS LIKE A NATURAL LABOR.
AND THEN AFTERWARDS, MY LEGS
WERE NUMB THE WHOLE TIME.
>> OH, NO.
>> IT WAS AWFUL.
>> D.J., HOW DO YOU FIND
BEING A DAD?
>> I LOVE IT, MAN.
IT MAKES ME FEEL LIKE I GOT
A MEANING, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
>> A PURPOSE, YEAH.
NO MORE SCREWING AROUND.
YOU SAID HE APOLOGIZED
A MILLION TIMES?
>> PROBABLY MORE THAN THAT.
>> MORE THAN A MILLION.
GOOD. JUST CHECKING.
I DO BELIEVE HIM WHEN HE SAYS--
>> I THINK HE'S SORRY TOO.
I KNOW HE REGRETS IT
BECAUSE WE'VE TALKED
ABOUT IT SO MANY TIMES.
MY ONLY REGRET IS JUST THE FACT
THAT IT HAPPENED, YOU KNOW.
I THOUGHT I MEANT MORE TO YOU.
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT?
>> AND I SURELY HOPE
YOU USED A CONDOM THAT TIME.
>> YEAH, I DID.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M SORRY, BABE.
KISS ME.
>> OH.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE
TO ACCEPT THE APOLOGY.
COME ON NOW.
>> YOU GONNA KISS ME?
>> ACCEPT IT.
>> I ACCEPT YOUR APOLOGY. OKAY.
I HAVE HIGH HOPES FOR YOU GUYS.
DON'T LET ME DOWN. ALL RIGHT.
COMING UP, WERE GONNA FIND OUT
IF AUTUMN'S BOYFRIEND, DUSTIN,
HAS REALLY KICKED THE WEED HABIT
AND WE'LL TALK TO COURTNEY
ABOUT HOW HER PLEDGE
TO GIVE UP SEX HAS CAUSED
A LOT OF PROBLEMS WITH
HER RELATIONSHIP WITH SCOTT.
>> WELCOME BACK.
I'M HERE WITH AUTUMN AND DUSTIN.
WE'RE GONNA START WITH YOU,
AUTUMN, FIRST.
SO, IT SEEMED LIKE WHEN WE MET
YOUR BOYFRIEND, DUSTIN, HE
SEEMED A LITTLE MORE INTERESTED
IN SMOKING WEED
THAN IN BEING A FATHER,
BUT DESPITE COOLING OUT
HIS POT HABIT A LITTLE BIT,
HE DIDN'T QUITE BECOME
THE RESPONSIBLE DAD
AUTUMN HAD HOPED FOR.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> ARE YOU HIGH?
>> NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> YOU'RE LYING.
>> IF SOMEBODY COMES OVER
AND THEY GOT WEED,
SURE, I'M GONNA TAKE A HIT.
>> NOT IN MY HOME.
IT'S ILLEGAL.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT COPS ARE COMING?
DEDE CALLED THE COPS ON DUSTIN.
>> AHHH!
>> CAN YOU BE A PARENT INSTEAD
OF A TEENAGER FOR FIVE SECONDS?
>> I FILED FOR CHILD SUPPORT.
>> YOU'RE ANNOYING.
>> I'M ANNOYING?
SCREW YOU.
LOOK, HONESTLY,
YOU PISSED ME OFF WITH THAT ONE.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO...
HOW ARE THINGS
GOING BETWEEN YOU TWO NOW?
>> PRETTY GOOD.
>> YEAH.
>> A LOT BETTER THAN BEFORE.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> DID YOU BREAK UP?
>> WE'VE BROKEN UP A FEW TIMES,
BUT WE'RE TOGETHER NOW.
>> A FEW TIMES?
WHAT, LIKE EVERY WEEK YOU GUYS
BREAK UP?
>> NO.
>> ABOUT ONCE EVERY THREE
MONTHS.
>> ONCE EVERY THREE MONTHS.
IS IT ALWAYS ABOUT MONEY?
>> NO. NEVER.
>> IT'S DIFFERENT [bleep]
EVERY TIME.
>> IT'S NEVER BEEN ABOUT MONEY,
THOUGH.
>> IT'S NEVER BEEN ABOUT MONEY?
>> NO.
>> IN THE EPISODE IT SEEMED
LIKE MONEY WAS A BIG PROBLEM,
THAT HE'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO GET YOU WHAT YOU NEEDED.
>> WE NEVER REALLY BROKE UP
BECAUSE OF IT,
BUT OF COURSE
WE FOUGHT ABOUT IT.
IT'S A BIG DEAL,
BUT, I MEAN, THE MONEY PROBLEM
ISN'T AS BIG NOW.
HE HAS A FULL-TIME JOB
PLUS ANOTHER JOB.
>> GOOD.
>> HIS SECOND JOB
HE UMPIRES A LITTLE LEAGUE GAME.
>> OH, THAT'S COOL.
>> WHY DID YOU BREAK UP?
>> YOU WANT TO TELL HIM
THAT ONE?
>> I DON'T REMEMBER
THE LAST TIME.
>> HE'S A CHEATER.
>> HE'S A CHEATER?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> HOW MANY TIMES
HAS HE CHEATED?
>> TWICE.
>> TWICE?
>> I WAS PREGNANT WITH BOTH,
AND THEN HAVING DRAKE
AND AFTER DRAKE WAS BORN
UNTIL HE WAS A MONTH OLD.
>> HOW DO YOU SMILE
AND SAY THAT?
>> IT'S A SMART ASS SMILE.
>> IT'S HIDING SOMETHING.
>> NO, IT'S JUST AN ANNOYED,
LIKE, LITTLE BITCH SMILE.
>> IT STILL SEEMS
IT MAKES YOU SAD.
IT HURTS. IT HAS TO.
>> WELL, YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
>> HAS HE EVER
APOLOGIZED FOR THIS?
>> OH, YEAH.
I DON'T THINK HE CARES, THOUGH.
>> WHAT?
>> I APOLOGIZE ALL THE TIME,
AND YOU KNOW I DO.
>> YOU CHEATED
DURING THE PREGNANCY?
>> YEAH.
>> TWICE.
AND AFTER DRAKE WAS BORN.
>> DUDE.
>> SHE MAKES ME MAD SOMETIMES.
>> OH.
>> I KNEW THE GIRL TOO.
WE HAD HUNG OUT.
AND SHE HAD ACTUALLY CAME TO ME
AND TOLD ME ABOUT IT
ONCE WE HAD BROKEN UP.
AND THEN LATER ON WE GOT BACK
TOGETHER AND I WENT THROUGH--
IT WAS AFTER DRAKE WAS BORN,
I WENT THROUGH HIS PHONE AGAIN,
AND FOUND MORE TEXT MESSAGES
OF HIM PLANNING ON SMOKING
AND [bleep] ANOTHER GIRL.
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
YOU HAVE SOMEONE
CARRYING YOUR BABY.
>> HE SAID I WAS CONTROLLING
BECAUSE I KEPT TRYING
TO GET HIM TO STOP SMOKING POT.
AND WE CONSTANTLY FIGHT.
AND IT GOT REALLY BAD.
>> OVER THE POT?
>> YES. REALLY BAD,
LIKE HORRIBLE AND HE CHEATED.
>> AND YOU'VE FORGIVEN HIM
FOR ALL OF THAT?
>> NO.
>> SHE'S NOT FORGIVEN YOU.
>> NOT FORGIVEN, BUT TRYING
TO LOOK PAST IT FOR DRAKE.
>> AND HOW DID YOU GET HIM
FROM A GUY
WHO WAS NOT GIVING YOU MUCH
OF ANYTHING,
WHOM YOU WERE FIGHTING WITH,
WHO WAS CHEATING ON YOU,
TO A GUY THAT'S NOW COMMITTED,
AND WORKING,
AND LIVING WITH YOU.
>> HE HAD NOWHERE TO GO,
SO HE MOVED IN AND MY MOM
SAID HE WAS NOT LIVING THERE
FOR FREE.
SO SHE KIND OF FORCED
HIM TO GET A JOB.
>> HOW YOU DOING WITH THE WEED?
>> PRETTY MUCH I SMOKE WEED
ALL DAY EVERY DAY,
AND I DON'T GIVE A [bleep].
>> YOU SEE YOUR GIRLFRIEND,
IS THAT WHAT YOUR OFFICIAL
STATUS IS NOW?
DO I CALL YOU GIRLFRIEND?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU SEE IT BOTHERS HER.
>> SHE HATES THE STUFF.
CAN'T STAND IT.
BUT I DON'T DO IT AROUND HER.
>> I TOLD HIM THE NEXT TIME
I CATCH HIM DOING IT,
ME AND DRAKE ARE GONE.
HE CAN GET OUT OF MY HOUSE THEN.
SO...
>> IS THIS GONNA WORK OUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
TAKING IT DAY BY DAY.
IT HURTS NOT TO HAVE A PARENT
THERE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE BOTH.
IT'S NEVER THE KID'S FAULT,
REALLY.
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER SEEN A CASE
THAT IT WAS.
SO WHEN A KID
LOSES THEIR PARENT BECAUSE--
>> SO HAVE YOU FORGIVEN
YOURSELF,
WHATEVER THOSE FEELINGS
WERE AS A KID?
HOW DID YOU GET THROUGH THAT?
>> MY MOM WAS A MOM
AND A DAD TO ME.
SHE WAS LIKE MY SUPERHERO.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE DID IT.
FOUR KIDS ON HER OWN.
>> ISN'T THAT CRAZY?
>> SHE'S MY ROLE MODEL.
THAT'S WHO I LOOK UP TO.
I SEE HER AND I THINK TO MYSELF,
"I CAN DO IT TOO."
>> NOW YOUR OLDER SISTER
HAD A BABY, TOO,
JUST BEFORE YOU DID.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HAVING SEEN HER GET PREGNANT,
WOULDN'T THAT HAVE MOTIVATED
YOU TO BE MORE CAREFUL?
>> SHOULD HAVE, BUT IT DIDN'T.
>> DIDN'T HAVE ANY EFFECT?
>> I DIDN'T THINK
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ME,
LIKE A STUPID LITTLE TEENAGER,
LIKE MOST KIDS DO.
>> HOW WOULD YOU SAY YOUR LIFE
HAS CHANGED SINCE GIVING BIRTH?
>> BIG TIME.
I USED TO BE THE PARTY KID
THAT, YOU KNOW, HUNG OUT
WITH EVERYBODY, DID EVERYTHING,
LOVED DOING ANYTHING FUN.
IT WAS JUST SPUR OF THE MOMENT.
DIDN'T REALLY CARE
ABOUT ANYTHING.
NOW I STAY HOME, TAKE CARE
OF A FIVE-MONTH-OLD.
I USED TO DRESS UP ALL THE TIME,
DO MY MAKEUP AND HAIR.
YOU CAN COME OVER, I'M
IN MY PJ'S, PUKE ALL OVER ME,
HAIR UP IN A MESSY BUN,
NO MAKEUP, PALE AS CAN BE
BECAUSE I'M ALWAYS INSIDE.
I DON'T TALK TO NO ONE.
I DON'T HAVE FRIENDS.
I DON'T WANT FRIENDS.
THE FRIENDS I HAD PARTIED
AND DID THINGS TEENAGERS
CAN HAVE FUN DOING,
BUT PARENTS SHOULDN'T
BECAUSE YOU KNOW I'M A PARENT,
AND I DON'T WANT
TO BE LIKE THAT.
SO IN MY EYES, THE BEST CHOICE
IS TO JUST TAKE CARE
OF YOUR KID.
YOU'RE A TEENAGER,
IT'S VERY EASY
TO BACK IN THE WRONG CROWD.
>> WELL SAID. THANK YOU.
WE HAVE TO TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
DON'T GO AWAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> WELCOME BACK.
NOW, CERTAIN METHODS OF BIRTH
CONTROL, SUCH AS I.U.D.s,
ARE OVER 99% EFFECTIVE
IN PREVENTING PREGNANCY.
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO BE SURE
YOU WON'T GET PREGNANT,
YOU CAN ALWAYS NOT HAVE SEX.
COURTNEY PLANNED TO SAVE HERSELF
TILL AFTER MARRIAGE,
BUT ENDED UP BREAKING
THAT PLEDGE WITH SCOTT.
LET'S GO AHEAD AND LOOK BACK
AT THE CONSEQUENCES
OF THAT DECISION.
>> IT TOOK FOUR DOCTORS JUST
TO SAY IT DOES HAVE A CLUB FOOT.
>> BECAUSE THEY CAN'T TELL HOW
SEVERE IT IS UNTIL HE'S BORN.
AHHHH!
I FEEL LIKE A PART OF IT
IS MY FAULT
FOR PASSING ON THE CLUB FOOT.
>> THAT GUILT,
IT CAN TEAR YOU UP, THOUGH,
IF YOU DON'T DEAL WITH IT.
>> WE ARE REMAINING ABSTINENT.
IT IS IMPOSSIBLE
FOR YOU TO LAY IN BED
WITH ME WITHOUT DOING ANYTHING.
>> EVERY MAN HAS A BREAKING
POINT.
IT'S BEEN
HOW LONG NOW WITHOUT SEX?
>> YOU'RE PISSING ME OFF,
SCOTT, STOP.
>> WELL COURTNEY, HOW MUCH
DO YOU REGRET NOT REMAINING
ABSTINENT?
>> I LOVE MY SON SO MUCH,
I DON'T REGRET IT.
OBVIOUSLY I'M NOT A TEENAGER
ANYMORE,
I'M A PARENT,
BUT I LOVE MY SON.
>> WHAT HAVE YOU GIVEN UP?
>> EVERYTHING. I'M A MOM NOW.
I NEVER GOT TO LIVE
MY TEENAGER YEARS.
I'M A MOM NOW,
BUT I DON'T REGRET ANYTHING.
>> IF YOU WERE TALKING
TO ANOTHER 16-YEAR-OLD,
WOULD YOU DISCOURAGE HER?
>> OH, I DEFINITELY WOULD TELL
HER TO USE PROTECTION,
OR IF SHE WANTS TO, IF SHE CAN
OR IF SHE WANTS TO ENOUGH,
TO GO ABSTINENT.
BECAUSE YOU DON'T LIVE
YOUR TEENAGE YEARS.
YOU'RE A PARENT.
I MEAN, I MISSED MY PROM,
I MISSED WALKING WITH MY CLASS
AND HANGING OUT WITH MY FRIENDS.
WE JUST STAY AT HOME.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU USE
PROTECTION?
>> WELL, I WAS TAKING THE PILL,
AND I WAS REALLY IRRESPONSIBLE
WITH THE PILL,
AND I DIDN'T TAKE IT THE NIGHT
THAT WE--
>> WOW. ONE NIGHT.
>> WELL, ACTUALLY IT WAS A FEW
NIGHTS AND WE DID USE CONDOMS,
BUT THAT NIGHT IT WAS SPUR
OF THE MOMENT, SO...
>> YOU HAD BEEN USING CONDOMS.
SO YOU GUYS HAD BEEN HAVING SEX
FOR A WHILE
BEFORE YOU GOT PREGNANT.
>> YEAH.
>> AND SCOTT, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT HER DECISION
TO RETURN TO ABSTINENCE.
>> YOU KNOW,
I TAKE IT LIKE EVERY GUY DOES.
I DON'T LIKE IT,
BUT I LIKE HER, SO...
>> OH.
>> ARE YOU TRYING TO TEST HIM?
>> NO, I'M DOING
IT MORE FOR MYSELF,
BUT IT IS TESTING HIM
SO IT'S GOOD
TO SEE THAT HE'S GONNA STICK
WITH ME THROUGH ANYTHING.
>> AND IT SEEMS
LIKE THERE WAS A LOT OF TENSION
ABOUT WORK AND RESOURCES.
YOU FELT LIKE YOU
WERE BEING EXPLOITED ALMOST,
I HEARD YOU SAY.
>> AH, NO, JUST THE WHOLE,
"I EXPECT YOU TO PAY FOR
EVERYTHING AND DO EVERYTHING,
BUT ALSO RIGHT
WHEN YOU GET OFF WORK,
COME AND DO EVERYTHING HERE."
BUT WE MET IN MUTUAL GROUND.
NOW WE'RE GOOD.
NOW WE JUST STRESS ABOUT MONEY.
MOST OF THOSE FIGHTS
WERE JUST REPETITIVE AND STUPID
BECAUSE MONEY.
ONCE YOU HAVE A BABY YOU THINK
ALL YOU NEED IS A $5 PACK
OF DIAPERS AND $2 WIPES.
WELL, THAT LASTS YOU TWO DAYS.
THERE'S ALSO CLOTHES,
THERE'S BIBS, THERE'S FOOD.
THE OLDER THEY GET,
THE MORE EXPENSIVE THEY GET.
SOON COMES SHOES AND SCHOOL,
AND SO THERE'S A LOT OF STRESS.
>> COURTNEY, TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR PLANS
FOR THE SURGERY FOR YOUR SON.
>> HIS SURGERY IS SCHEDULED
IN AUGUST.
>> AND DEAN HAS A VERY SLIGHT
DEFECT.
>> YES. VERY MINOR.
WE WERE BLESSED.
>> THE SPECIALIST SAID
IT WAS THE MOST MINOR ONE
SHE'S EVER SEEN.
>> HOW ABOUT THE COST OF THAT?
I KNOW THAT STRESSES SCOTT OUT.
>> WE HAVEN'T FOUND OUT YET.
>> THEY'RE GONNA QUOTE US,
YOU KNOW,
AND THEN SEND IT
TO THE INSURANCE.
INSURANCE WILL SAY THIS IS ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA GET PAID.
>> SO YOU'RE WAITING TO SEE WHAT
THE INSURANCE IS GOING TO COVER.
>> AND IT IS CONSIDERED
A COSMETIC SURGERY, SO--
>> IT IS?
>> IT'S RIDICULOUS, I KNOW.
>> YEAH, THEY CHANGED IT,
BECAUSE I THINK HER DAD WAS
SAYING THAT IT WAS NECESSARY,
NOW THEY SAY IT'S COSMETIC.
I THINK IT'S JUST INSURANCE
NOT WANTING TO PAY.
>> YEAH, I THINK THAT'S
WHY WE HAVE TO PAY SOME.
>> I DON'T THINK PEOPLE
UNDERSTAND WHAT A CLEFT LIP IS,
AND YOU SEEM INTERESTED TO SORT
OF EDUCATE PEOPLE ABOUT THAT.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT THE DEFECT YOU HAD?
>> MY PALATE WAS WAY WORSE
THAN MY LIP.
I DID HAVE A BILATERAL.
>> YOU HAD AN OPEN LIP
ON BOTH SIDES.
>> WELL, ONE WENT ALL THE WAY
THROUGHOUT MY NOSE
AND THE OTHER ONE
WAS HALFWAY, SO--
AND THEN IT WENT
THROUGH MY PALATE ON TOP
AND I HAD, LIKE, NO PALATE.
>> I IMAGINE YOU GOT USED
TO PEOPLE LOOKING AT THAT
AND FREAKING OUT ABOUT THAT.
>> YEAH.
IT ONLY MADE ME STRONGER,
THOUGH.
NOBODY REALLY CAME UP TO ME
AND MADE FUN OF ME.
THAT ONLY HAPPENED A FEW TIMES.
>> THEY MADE FUN OF YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE OTHER KIDS?
>> WAS THAT AFTER SURGERIES?
>> A LITTLE,
BUT NOT AFTER ALL MY SURGERIES.
>> HOW MANY SURGERIES
DID YOU HAVE?
>> SEVEN.
>> SEVEN SURGERIES.
AND HOW OLD WERE THEY
WHEN THEY STARTED?
>> THREE MONTHS.
>> INCLUDING JAW SURGERY.
THEY HAD TO BREAK HER JAW
AND PUT IT BACK IN PLACE.
>> THEY HAD TO DO A LOT
OF RECONSTRUCTION ON YOU.
>> AND EDUCATIONALLY
WHAT'S THE PLAN GOING FORWARD?
>> I JUST GRADUATED
LAST WEDNESDAY.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
[applause]
>> OKAY, WELL, THANK YOU, GUYS.
TODAY WE HAVE TALKED
A LOT ABOUT PREVENTION.
TO LEARN THE FACTS,
BE SURE AND CHECK OUT
16ANDPREGNANT.MTV.COM.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> I WASN'T ON BIRTH CONTROL
BECAUSE...
>> I JUST DIDN'T THINK ABOUT IT.
>> BECAUSE I WAS SCARED
TO TALK ABOUT THAT KIND OF THING
WITH MY MOM.
>> I WAS AFRAID OF GAINING
WEIGHT.
>> IT'S HARD TO HAVE A BABY
AS A TEENAGER.
>> GUESS WHAT?
YOU WANT TO GO OUT, TOO BAD.
YOU WANT TO GO WORK
AND MAKE MONEY,
YOU'RE MAKING ALL THAT MONEY
TO WRAP YOUR KID'S ASS.
>> I JUST RECENTLY
GOT BACK ON BIRTH CONTROL.
>> IT'S LIKE A WEIGHT
LIFTED OFF MY SHOULDERS.
>> IT WAS REALLY EASY
TO ASK FOR IT.
>> SO IT'S BETTER TO JUST
PREVENT IT IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> MILLINA HAD TWO PROBLEMATIC
MOTHERS DURING HER PREGNANCY.
ONE WAS HER OWN MOM
WHO WAS INCARCERATED.
SHE CONTINUALLY THEN ALSO
BUTTED HEADS WITH TREVOR'S MOM.
HERE'S A RECAP
OF THAT EXPERIENCE.
>> I WAS TOTALLY AGAINST GETTING
ON BIRTH CONTROL.
NOW I THINK OF ALL OF THE THINGS
I COULD HAVE DONE DIFFERENTLY.
WITH MY MOM BEING IN JAIL,
IT'S REALLY HARD
FOR ME TO FOCUS.
IT'S HARD
TO GO FROM THAT TO THIS.
WITH TREVOR'S MOM,
I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE.
>> THERE'S NOBODY IN THIS WORLD
THAT WOULDN'T TRUST ME
WITH THEIR BABY,
I'LL TELL YOU
THAT RIGHT [bleep] NOW.
>> I TRIED TO TALK TO YOU.
>> I THINK WE JUST
NEED TO TAKE A STEP BACK
AND FOCUS ON THIS LITTLE GUY.
>> DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE GONNA
BE HERE MORE FOR HIM?
>> I'M GONNA
COME AROUND AS MUCH AS I CAN.
>> ALL RIGHT, MILLINA, AFTER ALL
THAT, YOUR MOM LEFT REHAB EARLY?
>> YES, AND HER BOYFRIEND PASSED
ON HER BIRTHDAY LAST WEEK,
AND SHE MET HIM IN REHAB.
>> IN REHAB THIS TIME?
>> YES.
>> WELL THAT'S B.S.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO GET A BOYFRIEND IN TREATMENT.
>> YES.
>> THAT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
>> YES, IT IS.
>> OKAY, SO SHE BROKE
THE CARDINAL RULE NUMBER ONE,
AND THEN USED THAT AS A REASON
TO LEAVE TREATMENT EARLY.
THIS IS NOT YOUR PROBLEM,
IT'S HERS.
I MEAN COME ON, NOW.
HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT IT, MILLINA?
>> I'M CONFLICTED.
I AM.
I'M SO SCARED
THAT SHE IS GONNA RELAPSE.
DEATHLY AFRAID OF IT.
>> HOW IS YOUR MOM DOING NOW?
>> SHE IS WONDERFUL.
>> IS SHE GOING
TO MEETINGS EVERY DAY?
>> YES, NOT EVERY DAY,
BUT SHE DOES GO TO MEETINGS.
>> OKAY, SHE'S LIVING UP
TO HER END OF THE BARGAIN
AT THE MOMENT.
>> YES.
>> HOW ABOUT TREVOR'S MOM?
HOW'S SHE DOING?
>> SHE'S DOING A LOT BETTER.
>> YOU TOLD ME OFF THE AIR
THAT SHE HAD A COMPLICATION
THAT'S CALLED
A CAVERNOUS SINUS THROMBOSIS.
THERE ARE BIG VEINS
IN YOUR SKULL
THAT DRAIN CEREBROSPINAL FLUID
AND THEY CAN GET CLOTS IN THEM.
IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF DANGEROUS,
AND NOW SHE'S ON BLOOD THINNERS?
>> YEAH. SHE'S ON COUMADIN.
>> AND SEIZURE MEDICINE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S TAKING SO MANY MEDICATIONS
THAT THE DOCTORS GIVE HER.
>> FOR HER HEAD INJURY?
>> YEP.
>> I ACTUALLY HELP HER
SORT HER MEDICATIONS.
SHE HAS A GOOD SEVEN PILLS
THAT SHE HAS,
MORE THAN SEVEN PILLS
THAT SHE HAS TO TAKE EVERY DAY.
>> BUT SHE'S NOT ABUSING
MEDICATION.
THESE ARE THINGS THAT--
>> NO, THEY ARE ALL PRESCRIBED.
>> RIGHT.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS
GETTING ALONG NOW?
>> CURRENTLY WE ARE GETTING
ALONG VERY WELL,
BECAUSE I REALLY AM TRYING.
I DON'T ENJOY FIGHTING WITH HER
AND I KNOW IT UPSETS TREVOR
AND IT'S NOT FAIR TO KAYDEN.
>> DO YOU LET KAYDEN
BE TAKEN CARE OF BY HER?
>> IF IT'S HER AND,
LIKE, TREVOR'S LITTLE BROTHER,
OR HER AND SOMEBODY ELSE,
I'M COMPLETELY FINE WITH IT,
BUT JUST HER
AND THE BABY, I DON'T--
>> AND WILL SHE
ADMIT IT HERSELF,
SHE WEARS OUT PRETTY EASILY?
>> I DON'T THINK
SHE WANTS TO ADMIT IT.
>> TREVOR, SHOULD MILLINA
TRUST YOUR MOM WITH THE BABY?
>> IN TIME.
>> AND HOW ARE YOU GUYS
DOING AT YOUR RELATIONSHIP?
WHAT'S GOING ON THERE?
>> IT WAS WEIRD.
WITH THE WHOLE
CO-PARENTING THING
BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN
ON AND OFF FOR WHAT?
TWO YEARS NOW?
>> YEAH.
>> AND TO JUST, LIKE, STOP
AND KIND OF BE FRIENDS--
>> IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
>> YEAH, IT IS. IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT WE DON'T WANT
TO JUST JUMP INTO IT AGAIN
AND JUST, YOU KNOW,
LET IT FALL APART AGAIN
AND THEN JUMP BACK INTO IT.
WE WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT IF WE
GET BACK TOGETHER AGAIN,
WE'RE SETTLING DOWN.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GUYS WERE BROKEN UP.
>> YES.
>> DID YOU GET
INVOLVED WITH ANYBODY ELSE
WHEN YOU WERE BROKEN UP?
>> WE BOTH DID.
>> ARE YOU WITH ANY
OF THOSE PEOPLE NOW?
>> NO, IT WAS A ONE NIGHT
STAND TYPE THING.
>> FOR YOU TOO?
>> YES.
>> YOU HAD A ONE NIGHT STAND
AND YOU HAD A ONE NIGHT STAND?
>> MINE WAS A LONGER
THAN ONE NIGHT STAND.
>> HOW LONG?
>> ABOUT A MONTH AND A HALF.
>> OH,
THAT'S QUITE A LONG NIGHT.
>> IT IS. IT IS.
>> SIX WEEKS.
AND TREVOR,
THAT DOESN'T MAKE YOU HAPPY.
>> NO, BUT I CAN UNDERSTAND
HOW SHE FEELS.
>> ARE YOU IN A RELATIONSHIP
NOW?
>> PRETTY MUCH.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
>> ARE YOU HOOKING UP STILL?
WHAT ARE YOU USING
FOR BIRTH CONTROL?
>> OH, I'M ON IMPLANON.
I HAVE IT IN MY ARM RIGHT HERE.
>> GREAT.
>> IT LASTS FOR THREE YEARS.
>> FANTASTIC. GOOD.
YOU GLAD YOU DID THAT?
>> YES.
BECAUSE AS MUCH AS I
LOVE MY SON,
I AM NOT CAPABLE
OF RAISING ANOTHER CHILD.
I'M HARDLY CAPABLE
OF RAISING OUR ONE.
AND THE NEXT BABY I HAVE,
I WANT TO BE MARRIED
AND I WANT TO BE WITH THE GUY
THAT I'M GONNA BE WITH FOREVER,
AND I WANT TO HAVE MY OWN HOUSE
AND I WANT TO BE ABLE
TO SUPPORT THEM,
NOT LIVING
UNDER MY GRANDMA'S ROOF,
NOT HAVING SOMEBODY ELSE PAY
BY BILLS.
>> DO YOU HOPE
THAT WOULD BE TREVOR?
>> I DO.
I DO.
>> OKAY, WELL, TREVOR,
WE'LL BE CHECKING BACK IN TO SEE
WHEN YOU FOLLOW THROUGH ON THAT.
I'LL CHECK IN ON YOU.
AND WHEN WE RETURN,
WE HAVE A SHOCKING REVELATION
ABOUT MADDY'S BOYFRIEND
THAT YOU DO NOT WANT TO MISS.
STAY WITH US.
>> AND WELCOME BACK.
NOW, NINE MONTHS
AFTER GIVING BIRTH,
LESS THAN HALF OF TEEN MOMS
ARE LIVING
WITH THE BIOLOGICAL FATHER.
THAT NUMBER INCLUDES MADDY,
WHO HAS NOT EVEN SPOKEN TO CODY
SINCE THEY STOPPED
FILMING THEIR EPISODE,
SO AS WE BRING THEM TOGETHER HER
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN OUR STUDIO, LET'S FIRST
TAKE A LOOK AT THEIR STORY.
>> I SLEEP WITH CODY
ONE TIME AND THIS HAPPENED.
I BARELY KNOW HIM AND I'M GONNA
RAISE A BABY WITH HIM?
>> I DID NOT EXPECT
TO BE PREGNANT
BEFORE WENT ON A SINGLE DATE.
>> I JUST THINK
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG FOR THIS.
I THINK YOUR WHOLE LIFE IS DONE.
>> I DIDN'T CHOOSE TO GET
PREGNANT AT THIS AGE, MOM.
I DIDN'T PLAN IT.
>> I TOLD YOU FROM DAY ONE
THAT I WOULD ALWAYS KICK YOU OUT
IF YOU EVER GOT PREGNANT AT 16.
>> WELL, LET'S SEE HOW IT GOES.
MADDY TEXTED ME, AND SAID
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO LIVE HERE.
>> I FEEL LIKE SINCE WE
HAVE A KID, EVERYONE
THINKS WE HAVE TO BE TOGETHER.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I GUESS YOU GUYS
HAVE NOT REMAINED TOGETHER,
RIGHT?
>> NO.
>> AND HOW ARE THINGS NOW.
>> I HAVE NOT EVEN SEEN HIM
OR TALKED TO HIM SINCE DECEMBER.
>> HOW COME?
>> HE DOESN'T WANT
TO BE A FATHER, I GUESS.
>> CODY?
>> NO, BECAUSE YOU GOT INSULTED
BECAUSE I ASKED FOR A DNA TEST.
YOU GOT ALL DEFENSIVE OVER IT.
>> OKAY, IF YOU WANT A DNA TEST
SO BAD, WHY WOULD YOU
SIGN THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I FIGURED IT WOULDN'T BE
A PROBLEM GETTING IT--
>> AND WHY ARE YOU COMPLAINING
THAT SHE DOESN'T HAVE
YOUR LAST NAME IF YOU DON'T EVEN
THINK YOU'RE HER FATHER?
THAT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE SENSE.
>> I DON'T SEE WHAT THE PROBLEM
IS IN MAKING SURE SHE IS MINE,
THOUGH, BEFORE I TRY--
>> OKAY, THEN YOU PAY FOR IT.
IF YOU'RE NOT PAYING
CHILD SUPPORT,
WHY SHOULD I PAY TO BE TOLD
WHAT I ALREADY KNOW?
>> YEAH. I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU HAVE A JOB.
PAY FOR IT. I'M NOT DOING IT.
>> I GOT ANOTHER KID
TO WORRY ABOUT TOO.
>> CODY, YOU HAVE ANOTHER CHILD?
>> YEAH.
>> DID YOU GET THAT WOMAN
PREGNANT AROUND THE SAME TIME?
LIKE, RIGHT AROUND
THE SAME TIME?
>> TWO MONTHS PRIOR.
>> TWO MONTHS.
SO MADDY, IT SEEMS YOUR ANGER
FOR HIM IS MULTI-LAYERED,
RIGHT?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> SO YOU'RE ANGRY THAT
HE'S NOT SUPPORTING THE CHILD,
YOU'RE NOT WILLING TO GET
A PATERNITY TEST.
>> NO, I'M WILLING TO,
I'M JUST NOT PAYING FOR IT.
>> OKAY.
>> AND ARE YOU GONNA
HIRE AN ATTORNEY TO GET CUSTODY?
>> IF THAT'S, LIKE, NECESSARY,
AND IT SEEMS LIKE IT IS.
EVEN WHEN WE WERE TALKING, YOU
WOULDN'T LET ME BRING HER HOME.
YOU WOULDN'T LET ME DO NOTHING.
>> SHE'S BREAST FED,
WHAT, ARE YOU GONNA
FEED HER WITH YOUR BOOB?
>> PUMP IT, YOU PUMP IT.
THEY MAKE THEM FOR A REASON.
>> SHE WON'T TAKE A BOTTLE.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO BOTTLE
SINCE SHE WAS A NEWBORN AND SHE
WILL NOT TAKE THE BOTTLE.
>> WHY NOT PAY
FOR THE PATERNITY TEST?
>> IT'S $600.
>> IT'S $130 DOLLARS.
>> NO, PLUS LAB FEES.
>> AND HE STARTED--
>> IF IT'S JUST $130 DOLLARS
WHY DON'T YOU--
>> BECAUSE I PAY FOR STUFF
FOR HER.
WHAT DO YOU PAY FOR, NOTHING.
>> YOU DON'T GOT A JOB.
>> YEAH.
>> YOUR DADDY
PAYS FOR EVERYTHING.
>> NO, HE DOES NOT.
I HAD MONEY SAVED
BEFORE I HAD HER.
MY FAMILY'S NOT EVEN RICH.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU ARE LIVING WITH YOUR DAD
THOUGH.
>> YES.
>> AND HE DOES SUPPORT YOU.
>> HE HELPS.
>> I MEAN, SOMEBODY'S SUPPORTING
YOU; IT'S A LOT TO BE A MOM.
DO YOU WORK ALSO?
>> NO. I CAN'T.
I'M BREASTFEEDING, SO...
>> OKAY, IS THERE A PLAN
TO WORK?
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHY I'M SUPPOSED
TO BACK TO SCHOOL IN AUGUST,
BUT I PLAN ON GETTING MY G.E.D.
BEFORE SUMMER'S
OVER SO I CAN WORK NEXT YEAR
INSTEAD OF BE IN SCHOOL.
>> OKAY.
>> BECAUSE I HATE RELYING
ON OTHER PEOPLE
TO PAY FOR MY CHILD.
I CAN'T STAND THAT.
>> EVEN CODY?
>> NO, THAT'S HIS CHILD TOO.
HE SHOULD BE CONTRIBUTING.
>> OKAY.
AND WILL THERE BE DAYCARE THEN?
OR WILL SOMEBODY ELSE
BE TAKING CARE OF--
>> I'M GONNA WAIT
UNTIL SHE'S ONE
SO SHE'S OLD ENOUGH TO LIKE
GO TO MY MOM'S WHILE I WORK.
>> YOUR MOM HAD ONE RULE.
WHAT WAS THAT RULE?
>> DON'T GET PREGNANT.
>> THAT'S THE ONLY RULE.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU COULDN'T KEEP
THAT ONE RULE IN MIND?
>> WELL, I MEAN,
I DIDN'T PLAN TO GET PREGNANT.
>> DID YOU USE BIRTH CONTROL?
>> NO.
>> OKAY,
ISN'T THAT THE SAME THING
AS PLANNING TO GET PREGNANT?
>> WELL, NO.
>> HOW'S IT DIFFERENT?
>> BECAUSE I WASN'T PLANNING
ON HAVING SEX WITH ANYONE.
IF I WAS GONNA GET
IN A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP,
THEN I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
ON BIRTH CONTROL.
>> CODY, DO YOU WANT TO HAVE
A RELATIONSHIP WITH MADDY?
>> NO, I GOT A GIRLFRIEND
WITH THE OTHER GIRL
I HAD A KID WITH.
>> SO YOU HAD SOMEBODY
PREGNANT--
>> I DIDN'T KNOW IT.
>> DO YOU STILL HAVE FEELINGS
FOR HIM?
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> NOT AT ALL,
>> NEVER. NO.
>> BUT YOU MUST HAVE SOMETHING
BECAUSE HE'S THE DAD--
>> ANGER. THAT'S IT.
>> ANGER THAT?
>> THAT HE'S NOT IN HER LIFE.
>> I WANT TO BE. I REALLY DO.
>> I FEEL BAD FOR MY DAUGHTER.
I DON'T WANT HER TO GROW UP
WITHOUT A DAD.
>> DID YOU FEEL LIKE YOUR DAD
WAS TOO FAR AWAY FOR YOU?
>> NO.
>> MY DAD HAS ALWAYS BEEN
THERE FOR ME.
LIKE, I'M A DADDY'S GIRL,
I KNOW THAT.
AND SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT A DAD IS.
SHE HASN'T SEEN HIM
SINCE SHE WAS TWO MONTHS OLD.
>> I HAVE NO PROBLEM, LIKE,
STEPPING UP AND TAKING THE ROLE.
I JUST WANT HELP
WITH THE DNA TEST,
THAT'S ALL I'VE BEEN ASKING.
>> BUT YOU SAID
IT'S NOT WORTH SEEING HER
IF YOU CAN'T TAKE HER OVERNIGHT.
YOU CAN'T. I'M SORRY.
I DON'T TRUST YOU.
>> LIKE I CAN NEVER TAKE
MY OWN DAUGHTER; I HAVE A KID.
I KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH BABIES.
>> LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAD A MARIJUANA PLANT
GROWING IN YOUR BACKYARD,
PLEASE DON'T DENY IT.
>> BEFORE I HAD A KID, YEAH.
>> YEAH.
WHAT IF YOU DO IT AGAIN AND
THE NEIGHBOR'S CALL THE COPS.
MY DAUGHTER'S GONNA
GET TAKEN AWAY.
>> I'VE OBVIOUSLY STRAIGHTENED
MY LIFE UP; I'M A LOT DIFFERENT.
I DON'T PARTY OR NOTHING.
>> PATERNITY CAN BE ESTABLISHED
ANYWHERE ALONG THE WAY HERE.
I'M JUST PLAYING THE ODDS.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO STEP UP, HM?
>> YEAH, WELL.
I DON'T KNOW.
WE NEED TO GET THIS DNA TEST.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
>> I CAN'T AFFORD TO PAY
FOR THAT; I HAVE TO BUY DIAPERS
FOR YOUR CHILD
THAT YOU DON'T HELP WITH.
YOU HAVEN'T BOUGHT
A SINGLE THING.
>> I SAID THAT'S
WHY I WANT A PATERNITY TEST.
>> OKAY, WELL, I
WANT STUFF FOR AUBREY.
>> WHAT IF YOU SPLIT THE COST
OF THE PATERNITY TEST?
YOU BOTH ARE DEEPLY INVESTED--
>> BECAUSE, HE STILL HASN'T PAID
FOR ANYTHING FOR HER.
>> HOW ABOUT THIS:
YOU SPLIT THE COST OF IT.
IF IT'S YOUR CHILD,
YOU PAY HER BACK AND--
>> BECAUSE HE'S UNRELIABLE
AND HE WON'T.
>> I'LL PAY YOU RIGHT BACK
AS SOON AS I GET IT.
>> OKAY, THAT'S A COMMITMENT
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY HERE.
>> IT STILL DOESN'T MEAN
ANYTHING TO ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE ANYTHING
HE HAS TO SAY.
HE'S SITTING UP HERE LYING
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE, STILL.
>> OKAY.
LET'S TALK ABOUT SCHOOL.
WHAT'S THE PLAN?
>> I PLAN ON GETTING MY G.E.D.
THIS SUMMER.
I HAVE MY WITHDRAWAL LETTER
FROM SCHOOL.
I'M ALREADY SIGNED
UP I HAVEN'T PUT THE DATE YET
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO DO WITH HER
FOR TWO HOURS
WHILE I'M TAKING THE TEST.
>> OKAY. G.E.D.
AND THEN FURTHER EDUCATION?
>> YEAH.
I PLAN ON GOING TO COLLEGE,
I JUST DON'T KNOW FOR SURE
WHAT YET.
BECAUSE I WANTED TO BE A LAWYER,
BUT I'M NOT GOING
TO DO THAT NOW.
>> OKAY, SO THAT DREAM, GONE.
>> YEAH.
>> SO BIRTH CONTROL
FOR YOU GOING FORWARD?
>> I MEAN,
I PLAN ON GOING ON IT.
>> WHOA, WHAT BIRTH CONTROL
DO YOU HAVE PLANNED?
>> I.U.D.
>> EVENTUALLY, YEAH.
>> I.U.D. MIRENA OR SOMETHING?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY EVENTUALLY.
WHY NOT NOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST HAVEN'T GOTTEN
TO DO IT YET.
>> DO YOU HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
>> NO.
I'M NOT EVEN TALKING TO ANYONE.
>> ARE YOU SEXUALLY ACTIVE?
>> NO, HONESTLY I DON'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT SEX ANYMORE.
I FEEL LIKE MOMS DON'T HAVE SEX.
I FEEL DISGUSTING EVEN, LIKE,
THINKING ABOUT IT.
>> CODY, WHAT DO YOU DO
FOR BIRTH CONTROL NOW?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T TAKE BIRTH CONTROL.
>> I KNOW YOU DON'T.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
TO DEAL WITH--
>> I USE A CONDOM NOW.
>> YOU USE CONDOMS.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW IS AUBREY?
>> GREAT.
SHE'S THE MOST HAPPY BABY
THERE IS.
SHE'S LEARNING
TO CRAWL RIGHT NOW.
SHE SITS UP. SHE SAYS MAMA.
SHE'S GREAT.
>> BEFORE WE WRAP THIS UP,
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU GUYS
WANT TO SAY TO EACH OTHER?
>> I HOPE THINGS WORK OUT BETTER
THAN THEY HAVE BEEN.
>> OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, GUYS.
THANK YOU, CODY.
COMING UP, WE'LL FIND OUT
WHETHER OR NOT SAVON HAS LET
MAHWI BECOME A FATHER FIGURE
TO HER SON
EDEN, AND WE WILL BRING
ALL 13 BABIES ON STAGE
TO SEE
HOW MUCH THEY'VE GROWN UP.
BE RIGHT BACK.
>> female announcer:
DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THERE ARE PRESENTLY
AROUND 733,000 TEEN PREGNANCIES
IN THE U.S. EVERY YEAR.
WE DOCUMENTED 12 IN THIS SEASON
OF 16 AND PREGNANT.
AND SO FAR TODAY WE HAVE
CAUGHT UP WITH EIGHT OF THEM,
BUT NOW HERE ARE SAVON,
KARLEY, ALEAH, AND JASMINE.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
IN YOUR EPISODE,
WE SAW YOU TELLING MAHWI, RIGHT?
THAT YOU WERE NOT READY
FOR A ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIP.
>> RIGHT.
>> SO THAT ENDED.
>> MM-HMM.
WHERE ARE WE AT NOW?
>> ME AND MAHWI ARE FRIENDS.
WE'RE GOOD CLOSE FRIENDS.
WE TALK TO EACH OTHER ABOUT,
HE'S KIND OF LIKE A BEST FRIEND.
STILL NOT LOOKING
FOR A RELATIONSHIP
OR TO BE INTIMATE ANYTIME SOON.
>> SO YOU'RE NOT DATING ANYBODY?
>> NO.
>> YOU KNOW,
YOUR AUNT'S HERE, LADONNA,
AND I THINK
SHE HAD SOME CONCERNS.
LADONNA, IS THAT RIGHT?
SHE'S NOT INTIMATE WITH ANYBODY
RIGHT NOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW
IF SHE'S INTIMATE OR NOT,
BUT I KNOW THAT HER SON'S FATHER
HAS BEEN COMING BACK AROUND.
>> OH. WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
>> HE ACTUALLY DID COME
AROUND TO SEE HIS SON
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN THREE MONTHS.
OF COURSE ALLOWED HIM TO
BECAUSE THAT'S HIS DAD.
I WANT TO SEE
HIM INTERACT WITH HIS SON.
THAT'S ABOUT IT. NOTHING MORE.
>> DID YOU GUYS HOOK UP?
>> NO. NO.
>> LADONNA, NO?
>> I THINK THEY DID.
>> I WAS ON VACATION
FOR ABOUT THREE WEEKS,
AND HE DIDN'T COME AROUND
UNTIL I LEFT.
>> OH, INTERESTING.
>> SO THAT WAS SUSPECT
TO ME RIGHT THERE.
>> DOES HE HAVE, LIKE,
OTHER KIDS?
>> YES.
>> HOW MANY?
>> HE HAS THREE OTHER CHILDREN
THAT I KNOW OF.
>> SO HE HAS FOUR?
>> SIX.
HE PROBABLY HAS SIX OR SEVEN.
BUT THERE'S--
>> SIX KIDS? HOW OLD IS HE?
HE'S 19,
AND IT WAS FIVE BEFORE HERS.
>> HE'S A MENACE.
>> YEAH.
>> RIGHT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> MAHWI SEEMED
LIKE SUCH A GOOD GUY.
>> HE IS.
>> AND HE'S WAITING
AROUND FOR YOU.
DON'T KID YOURSELF.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO JUST
BE FRIENDS.
HE WANTS A LITTLE MORE.
HE'S WILLING TO SETTLE
FOR FRIEND.
>> RIGHT.
>> NO?
>> NO.
>> KARLEY, YOU HAVE TWINS.
>> YES.
>> BEING A TEENAGER,
BEING A TEEN MOM,
HAVING A BABY AT ANY AGE,
BUT TWINS, OH, MY GOD.
HOW DO YOU DEAL?
>> IT'S NOT AS TERRIBLE
AS EVERYONE MADE IT OUT TO BE,
BUT IT'S DEFINITELY HARD.
>> WHERE ARE YOU LIVING
THESE DAYS?
>> TONY AND I ARE LIVING
IN A TOWNHOME OF OUR OWN.
WE MOVED OUT OF MY MOM'S HOUSE.
>> OH, FANTASTIC.
HOW ARE YOU AFFORDING
THE LIVING SITUATION NOW?
>> WELL, TONY WORKS FULL TIME.
>> SO HE'S STEPPING UP?
>> OH, YEAH.
HE'S STEPPED UP A LOT.
>> ISN'T THAT WHAT YOUR MOM
WAS CONCERNED ABOUT?
>> WELL, SHE WAS JUST CONCERNED
FOR ME IN GENERAL.
SHE WAS SCARED FOR ME.
HER 17-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER
WAS HAVING TWINS
SO SHE WAS JUST SCARED
IN GENERAL.
>> NOW, ALEAH, SHAWN
WAS PREVIOUSLY A DAD, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> NOW YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT'S ALL ABOUT.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ABOUT BIRTH CONTROL?
>> I GUESS JUST
BE SMART ABOUT IT.
I THINK IT'S SOMETHING
THAT NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
KNOW TOO MUCH ABOUT, YOU KNOW.
I KNEW THERE WAS BIRTH CONTROL.
BUT IF YOU ASK A LOT OF TEENS
WHAT TYPE OF BIRTH CONTROL
THERE IS, WHAT WOULD BE
THE BEST OPTION FOR THEM,
THEY HAVE NO CLUE.
YOU KNOW, SO--
>> WHAT ARE THE RESTRICTIONS
YOU HAVE IN TERMS
OF WHAT BIRTH CONTROL CHOICES
YOU HAVE AS A DIABETIC?
>> REALLY, AS FAR
AS I WAS CONCERNED, EVERYTHING
OTHER THAN THE PILL WAS OKAY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TAKING?
>> I HAVE THE IMPLANON
IN MY ARM.
>> SO IT'S GOOD FOR THREE YEARS?
FIVE YEARS? THREE YEARS.
>> MM-HMM. THREE YEARS.
>> AND YOUR BABY ENDED UP
IN THE NEONATAL I.C.U.,
AND A LOT OF THAT WAS
COMPLICATIONS OF THE DIABETES,
RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> HOW ARE THINGS NOW
WITH THE BABY?
>> SHE'S PERFECTLY HEALTHY.
>> AND YOUR HEALTH.
>> I'M GONNA CRY.
THE N.I.C.U. WAS THE HARDEST
PART OF MY ENTIRE LIFE.
BECAUSE, I MEAN, AS SOON
AS YOU HAVE YOUR BABY
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO PROTECT HER.
PROTECT YOUR BABY
FROM ALL OF THAT STUFF
AND THEN YOU
GO INTO THE N.I.C.U.
AND YOUR BABY HAS AN I.V.
IN HER HEAD
AND SHE'S GETTING HER FEET
POKED LITERALLY EVERY TWO HOURS.
THAT WAS PAINFUL TO SEE,
AND THEN I'M IN PAIN.
I JUST HAD LABOR,
AND I'M WALKING BETWEEN MY FLOOR
AND THE N.I.C.U.
LITERALLY EVERY TWO HOURS.
IT WAS A LOT.
>> I DON'T MEAN TO IMPLY THIS
BY ASKING THIS QUESTION,
BUT SOME PEOPLE
WOULD FEEL THIS WAY.
DID YOU FEEL RESPONSIBLE
SINCE IT WAS YOUR DIABETES--
YEAH, THE DIABETES
CREATED THE SITUATION
SO YOU BLAMED YOURSELF.
>> YEAH, I MEAN,
OF COURSE THERE WAS THINGS
THAT I COULD HAVE DONE BETTER,
BUT I REALLY DID TRY MY BEST.
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT
WAS THE BEST EFFORT
I HAD EVER
PUT IN WITH MY DIABETES,
BECAUSE I'VE ALWAYS BEEN
A PERSON
WHO CARES WAY MORE ABOUT
OTHER PEOPLE THAN MYSELF.
>> HOW'S YOUR SUGAR RIGHT NOW?
>> IT WASN'T GOOD EARLIER.
>> HOW COME?
>> I FEEL LIKE I HAVE A LOT
GOING ON, YOU KNOW,
BECAUSE WHEN I'M NOT DEALING
WITH PEYTON,
I'M DEALING WITH NOAH.
WHEN I'M NOT DEALING WITH NOAH,
I'M DEALING WITH PEYTON.
SO IT'S LIKE I NEVER REALLY
HAVE THE TIME
TO TRACK MY BLOOD LIKE I SHOULD.
I DON'T EAT LIKE I SHOULD.
>> IT'S HARD.
>> YEAH.
>> SHAWN WANTED A VASECTOMY?
TALK TO ME ABOUT THAT?
DID HE HAVE IT?
>> NO, WE HAD A LONG TALK
ABOUT IT.
AND HE WANTS TO GET A VASECTOMY
AFTER THE IMPLANON,
BECAUSE WE BOTH AGREE,
WE DON'T WANT ANYMORE KIDS.
WE WANT TO FOCUS ALL OF OUR LOVE
ON THE TWO THAT WE HAVE.
IT'S ALREADY HARD TO SPLIT
OUR ATTENTION BETWEEN THE TWO,
I COULDN'T IMAGINE SPLITTING
IT BETWEEN THREE.
AND WITH MY HEALTH,
I WOULD NEVER ENDANGER
ANOTHER BABY LIKE THAT.
AND TO BE HONEST, I DON'T THINK
MY BODY COULD HANDLE IT.
I THINK THAT EITHER MY KIDNEYS
OR SOME OTHER VITAL ORGAN
WOULD GO OUT.
>> THAT'S REALISTIC.
>> YEAH.
>> TAKE CARE
OF YOUR DIABETES, HM?
>> I'LL TRY.
>> JAZMINE, WHAT'S UP WITH DEL?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW?
>> I DON'T TALK TO HIM.
>> WELL, THAT'S THE CURRENT
STATUS; YOU DON'T SPEAK?
>> NO, WE DON'T.
>> WAS THAT REALLY ABOUT
THE HOUSE RULES OR WAS THERE
SOMETHING ELSE GOING ON?
>> NO. NOT AT ALL.
HE ONLY HAD A PART TIME JOB,
AND SO...
HE WOULD SLEEP ALL MORNING,
GO TO WORK
FOR THREE OR FOUR HOURS,
AND THEN HE WOULD GO
TO HIS FRIEND'S HOUSE,
AND HE WOULD COME OVER
TO OUR HOUSE
TO SEE LAILA AT 10:00
OR 11:00 AT NIGHT.
SO IT'S KIND OF LIKE.
"NO, WE'RE GOING TO SLEEP.
YOU CAN'T COME HERE THAT LATE,
GOOD-BYE."
AND SO HE FELT LIKE BECAUSE HE
HAD A DAUGHTER THERE, HE COULD
COME ANY TIME HE WANTED,
AND THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
IT'S LIKE, "NO, YOU
CAN COME EARLIER IN THE DAY,"
OR, YOU KNOW...
>> DOES HE OFFER
ANY FINANCIAL SUPPORT?
>> NO, ONE DAY HE CAME,
HE RUNG THE DOORBELL AND,
LIKE, THREW A BOX OF DIAPERS
AT THE DOOR.
THEY WERE, LIKE, A SIZE FOUR,
AND SHE'S ONLY A SIZE TWO.
LIKE, NO.
>> ARE YOU SEEING ANYBODY?
>> YEAH, KIND OF, YEAH.
>> OH. TELL ME ABOUT THAT?
>> IT'S GOOD.
I JUST--I DON'T WANT
TO MOVE TOO FAST WITH ANYTHING.
I'M JUST KIND OF--
I FEEL LIKE WITH DEL,
I FEEL LIKE I MET SOMEONE,
BUT THAT WASN'T WHO IT
TURNED OUT TO BE, SO RIGHT NOW
I'M JUST TRYING TO--
>> YOU'D LIKE TO SEE WHO HE IS?
>> YEAH. FEEL THINGS OUT.
>> IS HE FREAKED OUT
BY THE HOUSE RULES TOO?
>> HE DOESN'T COME OVER.
LIKE, I SAID I'M MOVING SLOW.
>> DOES YOUR FAMILY
HAVE ANY FEELINGS ABOUT HIM?
>> THEY DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY LIKE SLOW,
LIKE "LET ME SEE WHO YOU ARE,"
TYPE THING BEFORE ANYTHING ELSE
GOES ANY FURTHER AT ALL.
>> OKAY, WELL, I WANT TO THANK
ALL 12 OF OUR MOMS
FOR SPEAKING WITH ME TODAY
AND OF COURSE,
SHARING THEIR STORIES WITH YOU.
LET'S END THE SHOW
BY BRINGING ALL THE MOMS
AND ALL THE BABIES
ONSTAGE RIGHT NOW.
OOPS, SPIT UP.
ALL RIGHT, A REMINDER THAT TEEN
PREGNANCY CAN BE AVOIDED.
SO HEAD TO 16ANDPREGNANG.MTV.COM
FOR MORE FACTS
AND INFORMATION ON PREVENTION.
I'M DR. DREW,
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.