>> I'M AUTUMN.
I'M A 16-YEAR-OLD SOPHOMORE FROM
RICHMOND, VIRGINIA, AND I LOVE
PARTYING WITH MY FRIENDS.
>> all: OH!
[all laugh]
>> I MET MY BOYFRIEND, DUSTIN,
OVER A YEAR AGO, AND IT WAS LOVE
AT FIRST SIGHT.
>> I'M TIRED.
>> YOU HAVE PJs ON?
>> YEAH.
>> WE SPEND ALL OUR TIME
TOGETHER.
LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> MY MOM WARNED ME TO TAKE
THINGS SLOW WITH HIM, ESPECIALLY
BECAUSE MY OLDER SISTER MISTY
JUST HAD A BABY.
BUT I DIDN'T LISTEN, AND NOW I'M
PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
AFTER I FOUND OUT I WAS
PREGNANT,
I STOPPED PARTYING AND GOT
SERIOUS ABOUT MY FUTURE.
I STARTED HOME SCHOOL SO I CAN
KEEP UP MY GRADES WHILE I TAKE
CARE OF MY BABY.
DUSTIN, ON THE OTHER HAND, STILL
LIVES A CAREFREE LIFE.
[all laugh]
>> WE'RE ALREADY STUCK.
>> HE DOESN'T HAVE A JOB AND IS
ALWAYS HANGING OUT WITH HIS
FRIENDS.
I'M WORRIED HE HAS NO PLANS TO
GIVE UP PARTYING FOR PARENTHOOD.
>> NOT EVEN CLOSE.
>> YOU'RE LYING.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> EVERYONE DOUBTS DUSTIN WILL
MAN UP FOR OUR SON,
EVEN HIS OWN MOM.
>> I DON'T FEEL AS THOUGH YOU
ARE MENTALLY READY TO BE A DAD.
>> I KNOW I'M NOT.
I JUST WANT TO PARTY WHILE I
CAN.
>> I KNOW DUSTIN HAS A LOT OF
GROWING UP TO DO, BUT I LOVE
HIM, AND I BELIEVE HE WILL BE A
GOOD FATHER.
I'M WRITING, "I LOVE YOU."
>> FIGURES.
HEY, DON'T DO THAT.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S ONLY A
YEAR SINCE WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER.
>> I'M YOUR LONGEST
RELATIONSHIP.
>> I'M YOUR LONGEST.
>> I KNOW.
>> MM-HMM.
>> [laughs]
REMEMBER WHEN I TOLD YOU I WAS
PREGNANT?
>> NO.
>> I PUT THE PREGNANCY TEST UP
TO FACETIME.
>> OH, YEAH.
I HONESTLY DON'T BELIEVE THE
LITTLE PREGNANCY TEST THINGS.
>> HOW THE HELL DO YOU NOT
BELIEVE PREGNANCY TESTS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THEY WERE--
THEY WERE BULL[bleep].
WHAT?
>> I HOPE YOU BELIEVE IT.
>> I BELIEVE IT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO ABOUT
SCHOOL?
>> I'M GONNA STAY ON HOMEBOUND,
HOPEFULLY.
>> YOU'RE GONNA STAY ON
HOMEBOUND FROM 10TH GRADE ALL
THE WAY TO 12TH.
>> I SURE AS HELL HOPE SO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GONNA
HAPPEN.
YOU THINK I'VE CHANGED SINCE
WE FIRST GOT TOGETHER?
>> NO [bleep].
>> I GREW UP, AND YOU DIDN'T.
>> EXACTLY.
THAT'S OBVIOUS.
I'M SCARED.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT ME?
YOU AIN'T THE ONE PUSHING IT OUT
YOUR HOO-HA.
>> [laughs]
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT WHEN
THE BABY COMES, WHAT WE'RE GONNA
DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO.
>> I MEAN, ARE YOU GONNA STOP
PARTYING OR NOT?
>> THAT'S THE SAME THING.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> I'M SCARED OF HOW THINGS ARE
GONNA END UP.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GONNA
END UP AS?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IF YOU DON'T STOP PARTYING,
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA GET MAD AT
YOU WHEN THE BABY'S HERE,
AND I'M NOT GONNA BITE MY TONGUE
LIKE I DO NOW.
>> I'M GONNA STOP PARTYING AS
MUCH.
>> ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE TO DO
THAT, OR ARE YOU JUST SAYING
THAT?
>> I'M GONNA BE ABLE TO DO IT.
>> I'M DUE IN TWO MONTHS,
AND WHILE DUSTIN IS BUSY HANGING
OUT WITH HIS FRIENDS...
>> HAVE YOU GOT STUFF FOR THE
BABY?
>> HEY, I DON'T HAVE NOTHING.
>> I'M BUSY SETTING UP FOR THE
BABY.
[grunts]
OOH.
[chuckles]
WE'RE HAVING A BOY AND NAMING
HIM DRAKE.
OH.
[laughs]
OUR PLAN IS TO HAVE BOTH OF US
STAY LIVING WITH OUR MOMS
BUT FOR DUSTIN TO HAVE A SETUP
FOR THE BABY AT THEIR PLACE SO
WE CAN STAY THERE TOO.
NOTHING'S THE SAME ANYMORE.
>> IT SEEMS WEIRD BECAUSE YOU
WERE OUT EVERY WEEKEND, AND NOW
IT SEEMS LIKE WE'RE ALWAYS HERE
DOING MOMMY THINGS.
IT'S KIND OF BIZARRE BUT COOL
BUT WEIRD AT THE SAME TIME.
>> I GOT TO BE A MOMMY.
I CAN'T BE A TEENAGER.
>> IT'S A BIG CHANGE.
>> TRUST ME, I KNOW.
I GAVE UP, LIKE, EVERYTHING
ALREADY.
>> WHEN YOU FIRST TOLD ME YOU
WERE PREGNANT, I WAS JUST LIKE,
"NUH-UH," BECAUSE MISTY HAD JUST
TOLD ME SHE WAS PREGNANT.
>> AND I WAS SO SICK FOR THAT
WHOLE TIME.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS WRONG.
I THOUGHT I JUST HAD THE FLU,
AND THEN MISTY ASKED IF I WAS
PREGNANT, AND I SAID, "NO."
AND SHE SAID, "LET'S GO TO THE
STORE AND BUY A TEST AND MAKE
SURE."
SO WE WENT THERE, BOUGHT THE
TEST, WENT TO THE BATHROOM
STALL.
I COULD TELL YOU WHICH ONE IT
WAS.
TOOK BOTH TESTS, AND MISTY'S
SITTING THERE, "WHAT'S IT SAY?"
AND I'M LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW YET.
IT'S NOT SHOWING."
AND THEN IT CAME UP, AND I SAID,
"UH-OH."
AND SHE SAID, "LET ME SEE."
AND I SLID IT UNDER THE DOOR.
>> I WAS REALLY ANGRY BECAUSE
I TOOK YOU AND HAD THE BIRTH
CONTROL, FROM PILLS TO RINGS TO
EVERYTHING.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO GET FAT.
>> BUT, YEAH, BUT LOOK WHAT
HAPPENED FROM YOU WORRYING ABOUT
GAINING FIVE POUNDS.
YOU DONE GAINED HOW MANY POUNDS?
>> 40.
>> SEE, YOU GOT TO PROTECT
YOURSELF.
IF YOU WOULD HAVE ACTUALLY TOOK
IT CORRECTLY, YOU MIGHT NOT BE
STANDING HERE WITH THAT BIG OLD
BELLY RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT HOW
IT'S GOING TO CHANGE YOUR LIFE
WITH YOU AND DUSTIN?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S GONNA BE REALLY HARD
WHEN THE BABY DOES COME AND
DUSTIN'S WANTING TO STILL HANG
OUT AND DO HIS OWN THING.
ARE YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT
WITH THAT?
>> NO.
>> I REALLY HOPE HE GETS A JOB
BECAUSE THE BABY'S GONNA NEED
FOOD.
IT'S GONNA NEED SHELTER.
IT'S GONNA NEED DIAPERS.
WHY DO I MAKE YOU--
>> YOU ACT LIKE DUSTIN'S NOT
GONNA GET A JOB AT ANY POINT.
>> WELL, I MEAN, ARE YOU FOR
SURE HE'S GONNA PAY CHILD
SUPPORT AND FINANCIALLY--
>> I MEAN, IF HE'S HELPING,
HE DOESN'T NEED TO PAY CHILD
SUPPORT.
HE'LL BE PAYING FOR STUFF WITH
ME.
>> DO YOU SEE YOURSELF STILL
BEING WITH HIM LATER?
>> HOPEFULLY.
HE'S THE ONLY PERSON I'VE LOVED.
MY MOM DOESN'T THINK THAT DUSTIN
IS READY TO BE A RESPONSIBLE
DAD, SO SHE WANTS TO TALK THINGS
THROUGH WITH HIM AND HIS MOM.
>> FIGURE WE'D GET A LITTLE
GATHERING HERE AND TALK ABOUT
THE BABY.
IT'S BEEN EIGHT MONTHS, AND WE
REALLY HAVEN'T DISCUSSED WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO WITH HIM AND COME
TO SOME CONCLUSIONS.
DO Y'ALL HAVE A LITTLE SETUP FOR
THE BABY YET?
>> NO, UM, DUSTIN AND I WILL SAY
WE WENT TO A YARD SALE, BOUGHT A
CRIB FOR A DOLLAR.
>> ONLY FOR A DOLLAR.
>> BUT I'M NOT TOO FOND OF THE
CRIB.
>> MM-HMM, RIGHT.
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT AFTER
YOU'VE HAD THE BABY WHEN YOU'RE
COMING HOME, WHERE YOU WANTED TO
BE, HOW YOU WANTED IT TO BE?
>> WHEN THE BABY'S FIRST BORN,
I WANT TO GO TO MY HOUSE
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
I'M COMFORTABLE THERE.
>> RIGHT, ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND I WANT DUSTIN TO COME
WITH ME.
>> I JUST HOPE SHE DON'T GET TOO
OVERWHELMED.
>> HE'LL BE WITH ME MOST OF THE
TIME, HOPEFULLY.
>> PROBABLY WHENEVER I CAN.
>> YEAH.
DO Y'ALL THINK THAT ME AND
DUSTIN ARE GONNA MAKE GOOD
PARENTS AND HAVE PREPARED
OURSELF ENOUGH?
>> I THINK YOU'RE PREPARING
YOURSELF THE BEST THAT YOU KNOW
HOW.
I THINK THAT YOU COULD DO A
LITTLE MORE PREPARING.
Y'ALL HAVE A LOT THAT Y'ALL ARE
GONNA BE GIVING UP, YOU KNOW,
AS FAR AS--
>> PARTYING.
>> UH-HUH, YOU THINK?
>> I ALREADY GAVE THAT UP.
>> SON, YOU LIVE A LIFE THAT
DOESN'T ACCOMMODATE A CHILD
RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> OKAY, SO HOW DO YOU PLAN ON
ACCOMMODATING YOUR SON?
>> I NEED TO STOP SMOKING IN THE
HOUSE.
I DEFINITELY WON'T DO THAT OTHER
CRAP AROUND HIM.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M NOT GONNA BE AROUND HIM,
SMOKE AROUND HIM, OR ANYTHING
WHILE I'M HIGH.
>> SO YOU PLAN ON GETTING HIGH?
>> MOST LIKELY, I MEAN--
>> REALLY?
I'M NOT LAUGHING.
I'M NOT--
>> I'VE BEEN DOING IT FOR FIVE
YEARS.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
>> I DON'T CARE HOW LONG YOU'VE
BEEN DOING IT, AND IF YOU THINK
FOR ONE--YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME
GET LOUD IN THIS RESTAURANT.
>> I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT,
MAMA?
>> WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GET THE
MONEY TO BUY WEED, SON?
>> PLEASE BE QUIET.
>> THIS IS HOW I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
READY TO BE A FATHER.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN READY TO BE AN
ADULT.
>> BECAUSE IF YOU'RE GONNA PLAN
ON SMOKING WEED, YOU'RE AN
IDIOT.
>> YOU ACT LIKE I'M GONNA BE THE
ONE BUYING WEED.
IF SOMEBODY COMES OVER, THE
BABY'S NOT THERE, SOMEONE HAS
WEED, SURE, I'M GONNA TAKE A
HIT.
>> NOT IN MY HOME.
YOUR GOAL RIGHT NOW SHOULD BE TO
LIVE LIFE THE BEST WAY THAT YOU
CAN FOR YOUR CHILD AND FOR YOUR
GIRLFRIEND.
OKAY, SO YOUR PLAN SHOULD BE TO
GET A JOB TO FIGURE OUT HOW
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THAT CHILD
TO EAT AND FOR THAT CHILD TO
HAVE WIPES, FOR THAT CHILD TO BE
CLOTHED.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT IS--
>> EVERYBODY SAID I--
I'M TALKING ABOUT WHEN I GO OVER
TO A FRIEND'S HOUSE AND THEY
HAVE IT, I MIGHT TAKE A HIT.
THAT'S IT.
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL
ABOUT THAT?
>> IT'S ILLEGAL.
THAT'S THE BIG DEAL.
AND YOU HAVE A CHILD COMING.
>> [cries]
>> COME HERE.
NOW I JUST FEEL LIKE THE BIGGEST
ASS[bleep].
>> [cries]
>> DUSTIN FELT REALLY BAD ABOUT
UPSETTING ME AT LUNCH.
ARE Y'ALL EXCITED TO SEE THE
BABY ON THE SONOGRAM?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> ARE YOU?
>> YEAH.
SO HE PROMISED TO TAKE
FATHERHOOD MORE SERIOUSLY AND TO
QUIT SMOKING FOR GOOD.
>> OH, LOOK,
THAT'S HIS NUT SACK.
>> OH, MY GOSH, THAT'S HIS NUTS?
[all laugh]
HE'S EVEN STARTING TO GET HIS
HOUSE READY FOR THE BABY.
YOU THINK WE CAN DO THIS SO WHEN
HE LAYS HERE THAT HE DOESN'T GO
THROUGH?
>> WE'LL FIGURE THAT OUT WHEN
WE'RE DONE.
>> WE'RE GONNA PUT THE CAT IN IT
TO TEST IT, RIGHT?
>> NO, JUST PUT THE DOG IN IT.
>> [laughs]
>> OH, IT'S BROKE RIGHT THERE.
>> HOW MUCH DID YOU PAY FOR THIS
AGAIN?
>> A DOLLAR.
>> THAT'S WHY IT'S BROKE.
>> THIS IS A PIECE OF CRAP CRIB.
>> THAT'S WHY IT WAS A DOLLAR.
WE'RE NOT PUTTING OUR BABY IN
THIS.
LOOK AT THAT ONE.
THERE'S ONE.
FOR A CRIB, I MEAN, IT'S NOT
BAD.
$69.
>> $69, I SEE THAT.
IT'S BETTER THAN THE ONE I GOT.
IT'S STILL TOO MUCH MONEY FOR
ME.
>> YOU DON'T REALIZE HOW MUCH HE
IS GOING TO COST.
>> OBVIOUSLY I CAN SEE.
>> WELL, YOU'RE NOT CARING.
>> WHAT, DO YOU WANT ME TO POOP
OUT MONEY?
>> LIKE, INSTEAD OF RIGHT NOW
JUST GOOFING OFF WITH YOUR
FRIENDS AFTER SCHOOL, START
LOOKING FOR A JOB.
YOU NEED TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO
PAY FOR HIM.
I'VE BEEN SO BUSY GETTING
EVERYTHING FOR DRAKE, SO TONIGHT
I WANT TO DO SOMETHING FUN.
HEY.
>> HEY, I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN
FOREVER.
>> HOW IS SCHOOL?
>> IT'S SCHOOL.
>> I MISS BEING IN 9TH GRADE
AGAIN, THOUGH.
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW; I FEEL
LIKE IT WOULD BE BORING JUST
SITTING AT HOME INSTEAD OF BEING
AT SCHOOL, BUT THE WORK IS, UGH.
>> I REMEMBER ME AND YOU SITTING
IN CLASS GOOFING OFF THE WHOLE
TIME SITTING THERE SUPPOSED TO
BE DOING WORK, AND WE'RE
LITERALLY JUST GOSSIPING ABOUT
DUSTIN.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
IS HE EXCITED ABOUT THE BABY?
>> HE SAYS HE'S NERVOUS,
AND THAT'S REALLY ALL HE SAYS IS
HE'S NERVOUS.
>> YEAH.
I KNOW HE'S STILL AT SCHOOL,
BUT IS HE PLANNING ON, LIKE,
GETTING A JOB AND EVERYTHING?
>> HE HASN'T BEEN LOOKING.
I'M WORRIED ABOUT HIM BECAUSE
HE'S NOT REALLY BIG ON
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> YEAH, WELL, THAT'S ALL
TEENAGE BOYS THESE DAYS.
HOPEFULLY HE CAN FIND SOMETHING.
>> I HOPE HE CAN.
MY MOM WANTS TO HELP DUSTIN FIND
A JOB, SO SHE PUT TOGETHER A
LIST OF LOCAL SHOPS FOR HIM TO
CALL.
>> ONE IS GRAFFITI'S TATTOOS.
>> I CAN'T DO NO TATTOOS.
>> WELL, YOU HELP AROUND THE
SHOP.
>> WHAT DO I DO?
>> YOU CALL, SAY, "HEY, CAN I
SPEAK TO THE MANAGER?"
THEN HE GETS ON THE PHONE,
AND YOU BE LIKE, "HI, MY NAME IS
DUSTIN.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WERE
HIRING?"
>> DO I HAVE TO SAY MY NAME IS
DUSTIN?
>> LEARN TO BE A MAN.
CALL.
THIS IS SOMETHING I CAN'T DO
FOR YOU FOR ONCE.
>> YES, IT IS.
>> I CAN'T GET YOU A JOB.
[line trilling]
>> CAN I SPEAK TO A MANAGER?
>> ARE Y'ALL HIRING?
>> OH, ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
THAT BITCH SOUNDED STONED.
[line trilling]
>> CAN I SPEAK TO ANTONIO?
ARE Y'ALL HIRING?
>> OKAY.
>> CAN I HELP YOU?
>> CAN I SPEAK TO A MANAGER?
>> ARE Y'ALL HIRING?
>> ALL RIGHT, HOW OLD DO YOU GOT
TO BE TO WORK THERE?
>> OKAY, SO HOW DO I GET AN
APPLICATION?
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> GOOD JOB, BIG BOY.
GOOD JOB.
I'M GLAD YOU CALLED PEOPLE,
BUT YOU NEED TO HAVE A BIT MORE
ENTHUSIASM IN YOUR VOICE.
>> I'M NOT ENTHUSIASTIC.
>> OUR BABY IS DUE IN SEVEN
WEEKS, AND I'M GLAD DUSTIN IS
STEPPING UP.
>> HEARD YOU WERE HIRING.
>> I AM.
>> HE KEPT CALLING AROUND,
AND HE GOT HIRED AT A LOCAL BIKE
SHOP.
>> THANKS FOR THE OPPORTUNITY.
>> YEAH, YEAH, I APPRECIATE YOU
COMING IN, BUDDY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> HE'S ALSO STAYING CLEAN,
BUT NOT EVERYONE IS CONVINCED
THAT HE'S ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ABOUT
DUSTIN LATELY?
>> I DON'T REALLY HAVE FAITH
THAT DUSTIN'S GONNA BE A GOOD
DAD OR STICK AROUND.
>> WHY DO YOU SAY THAT, THOUGH?
>> HE DOESN'T ACT LIKE HE FEELS
LIKE HE NEEDS TO GROW UP.
LIKE, HE JUST ACTS LIKE,
"I'M NOT THE ONE THAT'S PREGNANT
AND I'M NOT THE MOM, SO I'M JUST
GONNA, LIKE, DO WHATEVER I WANT
TO DO AND NOT CHANGE A THING
ABOUT ANYTHING."
>> BUT, I MEAN, YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
AROUND HIM LATELY.
HE DOESN'T SMOKE ANYMORE.
>> DO YOU THINK HE, LIKE, REALLY
QUIT SMOKING?
BECAUSE, LIKE, WHAT HE DOES
WHEN YOU'RE NOT AROUND, LIKE,
YOU DON'T KNOW EVERYTHING.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE FAITH THAT HE'S TELLING
THE TRUTH.
>> REALLY, THOUGH?
BECAUSE I THINK YOU NEED TO,
LIKE, WEIGH IT OUT MORE, AND
MAKE HIM PROVE TO YOU THAT HE'S
WORTHY OF ACTUALLY BEING A TEEN
DAD AND ACTUALLY STICKING AROUND
AND--I MEAN, BECAUSE THIS IS
A LOT OF WORK.
IT MIGHT LOOK LIKE IT'S NOT THAT
BAD, BUT IT'S REALLY HARD,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE TRYING TO
DO SCHOOL.
AND WHEN YOU'RE, LIKE, GETTING
UP EVERY NIGHT,
AND YOU JUST WANT TO LAY THERE.
LIKE, YOU CAN'T DO THAT ANYMORE
BECAUSE HE COMES FIRST.
IT'S OKAY, BUDDY.
>> WHAT'S VIBRATING?
IS THAT YOU?
>> YEAH, IT'S DUSTIN.
HELLO?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
COPS ARE COMING?
OH, MY GOD.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> DEE CALLED THE COPS ON
DUSTIN.
>> WHY?
>> HOLD ON.
I'M PUTTING YOU ON SPEAKER.
>> THE COPS ARE ON THE WAY TO
DUSTIN'S NOW FOR IT.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO SAY.
[phone beeps]
>> STILL THINK HE'S READY TO BE
A DAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> AFTER DUSTIN TOLD ME HIS MOM
CALLED THE COPS ON HIM,
I RUSHED OVER.
BUT BY THE TIME I GOT THERE, HIS
MOM HAD CALMED DOWN AND HAD TOLD
THE COPS EVERYTHING WAS OKAY.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
>> SHE CALLED THE COPS BECAUSE
THERE WAS STUFF THAT MY FRIENDS
LEFT HERE LAST NIGHT.
SO I JUST PICKED IT UP AND THREW
IT AWAY.
>> WHEN YOU CALLED RIGHT THERE,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SMOKING WEED
FROM HOW YOU SAID IT, AND I WAS
PISSED OFF AT YOU.
>> I HAVEN'T DONE IT IN SO LONG.
>> I MEAN, I HOPE NOT.
>> HEY, SWEETIE,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> DO YOU WANT TO SIT DOWN?
>> SURE.
SO WHAT HAPPENED WITH DUSTIN
WITH THE COPS AND EVERYTHING?
I THOUGHT HE STOPPED AND
STRAIGHTENED UP.
>> HE SAYS HE HAS.
I BELIEVE HIM.
I MEAN, I'M WITH HIM, LIKE,
ALMOST EVERY SINGLE DAY.
AND I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM SMOKE.
I HAVEN'T SMELT SMOKE ON HIM.
>> WELL, I GOT A QUESTION
FOR YOU.
LIKE YOU DO A HOME PREGNANCY
TEST, DON'T THEY GOT THE HOME
DRUG TESTS SO YOU GOT KIND OF AN
IDEA?
>> THAT'S FINE.
>> BUT YOU DO KNOW IF IT'S
POSITIVE, THAT'S GONNA BE UGLY.
>> YEAH.
BETWEEN THE STRESS OF KEEPING UP
WITH MY SCHOOLWORK
AND MAKING SURE THAT EVERYTHING
IS READY FOR THE BABY, I'M ALSO
WORRIED THAT DUSTIN HAS BEEN
LYING TO ME.
>> CAN I SEE IT?
>> YEAH.
>> WHICH ONE DID YOU GET?
>> IT COVERS FOUR DIFFERENT
DRUGS: MARIJUANA, METHADONE,
COCAINE, AND...
OPIATES.
>> SO HAVE YOU STOPPED TOTALLY
SMOKING POT?
100%?
>> YUP.
>> ARE YOU DOING IT FOR THE
BABY OR FOR YOU OR FOR BOTH?
>> PROBABLY FOR BOTH.
>> THAT'S THE BEST ANSWER
I CAN HEAR.
YOU SHOULD WANT IT FOR YOURSELF
ALSO.
BECAUSE THE BETTER YOU ARE, THE
BETTER YOU ARE FOR YOUR CHILD.
>> WELL, IF YOU TOOK A DRUG TEST
RIGHT NOW, DO YOU THINK YOU'D
PASS?
>> PROBABLY.
>> WHY DON'T YOU GO TAKE THAT?
>> HELL NO.
I'M NOT TAKING THAT.
>> TAKE IT.
>> "TEST FOR MARIJUANA, COCAINE,
METHAMPHETAMINE, AND OPIATES."
>> WILL YOU GO TAKE THE DRUG
TEST NOW IN THE BATHROOM?
>> I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> GO TAKE THE TEST.
>> MM-MM.
>> WANT MY ICE?
>> NO, GO TAKE THE TEST.
>> I'M NOT TAKING THE TEST HERE.
>> GO TAKE THE TEST, DUSTIN.
>> RIGHT NOW?
>> RIGHT NOW.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I BET YOU DO.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> GOOD LUCK?
>> THE BABY SAYS GOOD LUCK.
>> THAT IS SO MEAN.
>> I REALLY HOPE HE PASSES.
>> I REALLY, REALLY HOPE HE
PASSES.
DO YOU THINK HE'S GOING TO?
>> SO I SEEN YOU TURN AROUND
LOOKING.
YOU HEARD A DOOR, AND YOU TURN
AROUND QUICK.
I JUST TELL YOU'RE VERY NERVOUS.
I WONDER HOW NERVOUS HE IS RIGHT
AT THIS SECOND.
>> HE'S PROBABLY MISSING.
HE'S COMING.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
READ THIS.
WHAT DOES TWO LINES MEAN
AND WHAT DOES ONE LINE MEAN?
>> WHERE'S YOUR TEST?
>> IN HERE.
>> GIVE ME THE TEST.
>> THERE'S TWO LINES ON ALL OF
THEM.
>> WHERE'S THE BOX?
>> THAT'S THE INSTRUCTIONS.
THERE ISN'T A BOX.
>> OH, HE HAS IT RIGHT THERE.
>> NEGATIVE.
>> ON WHAT?
>> YOU PASSED.
>> DID HE REALLY?
>> HE PASSED, NEGATIVE.
>> EVEN IF IT'S STAYING?
>> T.H.C., HE PASSED.
O.P.I., HE PASSED.
>> OPIATE.
>> METHADONE, HE PASSED.
COCAINE, HE PASSED.
HE PASSED EVERYTHING.
HE BARELY IS PASSING HIS T.H.C.
ONE, THOUGH, BUT SINCE THERE'S
TWO LINES STILL--
>> IT'S STILL CLASSIFIED AS
PASSING.
>> HE PASSED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[all laugh]
>> TAKE A PICTURE.
SHOW YOUR MOMMY.
AND SAY, "WHAT?"
[laughs]
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, DUSTIN.
>> ME TOO.
>> PLEASE KEEP IT UP.
>> NO MORE WEED.
>> THAT'S THE FIRST DRUG TEST
I'VE EVER PASSED.
>> REALLY?
>> HIGH FIVE, DUDE.
>> TWO.
>> HEY.
>> YOUR HAND WAS WET.
I'M HAPPY THAT DUSTIN IS DOING
THE RIGHT THINGS FOR OUR BABY.
>> OKAY, LET'S DO SOME BRACKETS.
>> HE'S NOT PERFECT, BUT HE'S AS
READY FOR FATHERHOOD AS HE'LL
EVER BE.
WHAT THE HELL IS IT?
>> IT'S A BELLY MOLD.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU MAKE YOUR BELLY.
>> AND IT STAYS LIKE THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S [bleep] SWEET.
>> OW, I'M HAVING A CONTRACTION.
>> AGAIN?
WHAT THE HELL IS A CONTRACTION?
>> WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> I FORGOT.
>> IT'S WHEN THE BABY IS GETTING
READY TO COME.
>> YOUR STOMACH IS ROCK HARD.
>> THAT'S CALLED A CONTRACTION,
YOU DUMMY.
OH, COLD, COLD, COLD.
AND I'M HAVING A CONTRACTION.
MY DUE DATE IS STILL A MONTH
AWAY, BUT SINCE I'VE BEEN HAVING
CONTRACTIONS MORE FREQUENTLY,
WE'RE GOING TO THE DOCTOR TO
MAKE SURE EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
>> THE HEAD'S DOWN ON THE
PELVIS.
IT'S JUST SORT OF SITTING RIGHT
THERE.
>> OH, YOU CAN FEEL IT?
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S CRAZY, DOG.
>> I WOULDN'T BE SHOCKED IF YOU
DIDN'T DELIVER IN THE NEXT WEEK
OR 10 DAYS.
>> MM-KAY.
>> BUT IT COULD BE LONGER.
YOU COULD GO ALL THE WAY TO
TERM, SO WE'LL SEE.
>> LET'S HOPE NOT.
TURNS OUT, I DIDN'T HAVE
TO WAIT LONG.
A FEW DAYS LATER, MY
CONTRACTIONS STARTED UP AGAIN...
[sighs]
MOM!
AND DIDN'T STOP.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I THINK THE BABY'S COMING.
WILL YOU GO CALL DUSTIN?
>> YEAH, HONEY.
>> WHEN I ARRIVED AT THE
HOSPITAL, I WAS FOUR CENTIMETERS
DILATED, AND THE CONTRACTIONS
WERE BECOMING REALLY PAINFUL.
THEN THE DOCTOR BROKE MY WATER
AND GAVE ME PITOCIN.
I'M SO SCARED.
I'M PETRIFIED.
WE GONNA GET MY TUBES TIED.
NO MORE BABIES.
WE GONNA GET BIRTH CONTROL,
AND YOU GONNA LEARN HOW TO PUT
ON A CONDOM.
>> YOU SCARED?
>> IT'S JUST THE THOUGHT OF THE
VAGINA RIPPING OPEN IS WHAT'S
SCARING ME.
AFTER A FEW HOURS, THE PAIN
BECAME UNBEARABLE, SO I ASKED
FOR AN EPIDURAL.
I WAS GLAD I HAD MY WHOLE FAMILY
AND DUSTIN THERE WITH ME.
>> ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO
SLEEP?
>> [bleep], YEAH.
SHE DON'T CARE.
>> BEFORE I KNEW IT, IT WAS TIME
TO START PUSHING.
>> ALL RIGHT, GO BACK ON YOUR
LEGS.
>> MOMMY.
>> I'M COMING, I'M COMING.
>> DEEP BREATH.
PUSH HARD RIGHT HERE.
PUSH HARD.
TWO, THREE, FOUR.
I WANT YOU TO PUSH...
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> NO MATTER WHAT.
>>> THIS IS COMING.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
KEEP GOING.
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
>> YOU CAN SEE SOME.
>> LIFT YOUR HEAD UP TO ME.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
COME ON, PUSH HARDER.
NINE, TEN.
>> [groans]
>> GOOD JOB.
>> YOU SAY NO?
>> PUSH.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
[all yelling]
>> IT'S COMING!
IT'S COMING!
>> BREATHE, BREATHE.
IT'S COMING OUT.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> [groans]
I FEEL HIM!
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
COME ON, MORE AND MORE.
>> I FEEL HIM!
>> PUSH, COME ON.
>> HE'S COMING OUT NOW.
>> GET YOUR BREATH.
GET YOUR BREATH.
>> PUT DOWN YOUR HEAD.
ALMOST.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK OVER.
LOOK HERE.
>> OPEN YOUR EYES AND LOOK.
>> DON'T LOOK.
>> LOOK, AUTUMN, PUSH.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, COME ON.
>> LOOK, OPEN YOUR EYES.
[all yelling]
>> OH, HE'S ALREADY
WANTING TO CRY.
[all speaking at once]
>> OH, YOU DID IT.
COME HERE NOW, DUSTIN.
[baby crying]
>> * GIRL YOUR LOVE WILL
* SET ME RIGHT
>> IS IT WORTH ALL THAT PAIN?
[laughs]
>> HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
>> [laughs]
>> YOU CAN TOUCH HIM.
>> HI, BABY.
LOOK AT YOUR DADDY.
COME HERE.
[baby crying]
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
>> WHERE'S THE--
>> I KNOW, LET ME GET THIS.
>> [grunts]
OH, MOTHER[bleep].
>> IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF COOL.
>> SHUT UP, YOU NASTY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE
A BIG-ASS BRAIN.
>> OH, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
GET THAT AWAY FROM ME.
PEOPLE PAY TO EAT THAT.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> A PLACENTA.
>> THIS IS WHERE THE BABY WAS,
INSIDE THIS SACK RIGHT HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> BABY BOY, 7 POUNDS,
5 OUNCES.
>> all: YAY.
>> * GIRL YOUR LOVE WILL
* SET ME RIGHT
[chime dings]
>> I'M GONNA GO PUT YOU IN YOUR
CRIB SO DADDY CAN PACK UP SOME
STUFF.
THERE YOU GO.
>> I LIKE THAT YOU'RE HELPING
AND BEING HERE.
>> I HELP DURING THE DAY.
IT'S JUST DURING THE NIGHT, I--
>> IT'S HONESTLY A LOT EASIER
WITH YOUR HELP.
>> HERE'S YOUR HOME.
YOU AIN'T SEEN IT YET.
>> I THINK YOU GOT A [bleep]
DIAPER.
>> I THINK YOU SHOULD CHANGE IT.
>> WHY DO I GOT TO CHANGE IT?
>> IT'S YOUR TURN.
>> I CHANGE HIM AT NIGHT.
YOU CHANGE HIM DURING THE DAY.
>> OH, I KNOW.
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU CRY EVEN MORE
RIGHT NOW.
>> GET IT UNDER HIS BALLS.
MOVE HIS BALLS AROUND.
[baby crying]
>> I KNOW, BUDDY.
IT'S OKAY.
[baby crying]
>> [mumbles]
[sighs]
ARE YOU GONNA HELP ME?
>> HOW?
>> MY LEGS.
PULL.
>> I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU.
[baby crying]
>> TAKING CARE OF A BABY IS WAY
HARDER THAN I IMAGINED.
>> YOU NEED AN ASPIRIN?
YOUR HEAD HURTING?
>> I'M JUST TIRED.
>> YOU LOOK IT.
>> AND TRYING TO KEEP UP WITH MY
SCHOOLWORK IS NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE.
I REALLY WISH I HAD DUSTIN'S
HELP, BUT DAYS GO BY WHERE I
DON'T SEE HIM AT ALL.
AND WHEN HE DOES COME OVER,
HE'S USUALLY SLACKING OFF.
>> DUDE, DID HE JUST FART?
>> HE [bleep].
>> YOU'RE CHANGING.
>> YOU GONNA CHANGE IT?
>> NO, YOU'RE CHANGING IT.
>> YOU'RE CHANGING IT.
>> YOUR STUPID GAME IS NOT
IMPORTANT.
>> IT IS IMPORTANT.
>> CAN YOU BE A PARENT INSTEAD
OF A TEENAGER FOR FIVE SECONDS?
>> I'M ON THE FINAL LAP.
>> GET UP.
AND TO TOP IT OFF, HE HASN'T
SPENT ANY OF HIS PAYCHECKS ON
DIAPERS OR WIPES.
ONLY SEVEN DIAPERS.
THAT'S [bleep].
STUPID.
[knock on door]
>> COME IN.
HEY.
>> HOLA.
>> WELL, AUTUMN'S IN THE ROOM.
YOU WANT TO GO CHECK HER OUT?
THE BABY'S IN THERE.
>> YEAH, SCREW AUTUMN.
I WANT THE BABY.
>> YOU WANT THE BABY.
>> GIVE ME MY SON.
HEY, DOES THIS HURT?
>> STOP TOUCHING ME.
YOU'RE BEING IMMATURE.
>> I'M NOT TOUCHING YOU.
YOU'RE TOUCHING ME, SEE?
>> YOU'RE--BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO
KEEP YOU AWAY FROM ME.
>> BRING ANY DIAPERS?
>> NO.
IF YOU WOULD'VE TOLD ME,
I MIGHT HAVE.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY DON'T YOU DO THE NICE
THING AND JUST, "HERE, AUTUMN,
LET ME--LET ME HELP YOU OUT SO
YOU CAN GO GET YOUR EYEBROWS
DONE LIKE YOU'VE BEEN WANTING TO
DO FOR MONTHS."
>> HOW MANY DIAPERS YOU GOT?
>> A BOX.
>> THAT'LL LAST A WEEK AT LEAST.
>> WHAT HAPPENS AFTER THAT WEEK?
>> WE BUY MORE.
>> WE?
>> WE.
>> OR ME?
>> I'LL GIVE YOU $2.50 RIGHT
NOW.
>> THAT GETS THIS.
THAT'S LITERALLY HOW MUCH THIS
IS, $2.50 JUST FOR THIS.
>> THAT'S BETTER THAN NOTHING.
>> YOU KNOW HOW FAST YOU GO
THROUGH THIS?
TWO DAYS.
>> THAT'S BETTER THAN NOTHING.
>> TWO DAYS.
>> HERE, YOU CAN COUNT THAT OUT.
>> THIS ALL YOU GOT?
>> FOR NOW, YEAH.
>> LOOK AT THIS DOLLAR, DRAKE.
IT'S THE FIRST DOLLAR YOUR DADDY
GAVE YOU.
PUT IT IN YOUR PIGGY BANK.
I REALLY THOUGHT DUSTIN WAS
GONNA STAY ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
BUT NOW I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT HE'S
SPENDING HIS PAYCHECK ON.
>> OH, SOMETHING FOR DRAKE.
OH.
>> WHAT?
>> HE HAD HIS CIRCUMCISION BILL,
AND THE INSURANCE DIDN'T COVER
IT, AND IT'S FOR $287.
>> LET ME READ IT.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T AFFORD THAT.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
YOU MIGHT NEED TO GIVE DUSTIN A
CALL ABOUT THIS.
>> I'LL SAY SOMETHING TO HIM,
BUT HE AIN'T GONNA PAY IT.
HE'S GONNA LAUGH.
>> SO BASICALLY WE GOT TO PAY
FOR ALL THE DIAPERS AND THE
WIPES, AND HE JUST COMES TO PLAY
WITH HIM, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, PRETTY MUCH.
>> I KNOW YOU SAID BEFORE YOU
DIDN'T WANT TO DO THE CHILD
SUPPORT, BUT AT THIS POINT,
HE'S WORKING.
HE STILL HASN'T CAME AND BOUGHT
ANYTHING FOR HIM.
>> I FEEL STUCK.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO BECAUSE
HE WAS DOING GOOD, YOU KNOW,
QUIT WEED AND ALL THAT AND HE
GOT A JOB.
BUT NOW THERE'S NOTHING--
HE'S NOT DOING ANYTHING.
>> LIKE I SAID, THE CHILD
SUPPORT'S THE ONLY WAY I CAN
EVEN THINK OF TO EVEN SCARE HIM
TO MAKE HIM DO WHAT HE'S
SUPPOSED TO DO.
AND I THINK AFTER A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME, YOU'RE GONNA GET
REALLY FRUSTRATED.
MY PERSONAL OPINION, YOU NEED TO
TAKE THE NEXT STEP AND TO MAKE
HIM DO IT.
>> THINGS BETWEEN DUSTIN AND I
HAVE NOT BEEN SAME SINCE DRAKE
ARRIVED.
BUT BEFORE I FILE FOR CHILD
SUPPORT, I WANT TO GIVE HIM ONE
MORE CHANCE TO STEP UP.
I HAVE PHYSICALLY AND
FINANCIALLY PAID FOR EVERY
SINGLE THING THAT THAT BOY HAS.
>> SAYS YOU.
>> YEAH.
YOU DON'T TAKE CARE OF HIM.
I DO.
YOU HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
>> BULLCRAP.
>> NAME ONE THING YOU'VE BOUGHT
HIM.
>> I HAVEN'T DONE--I HAVEN'T--
I HAVEN'T TAKEN CARE OF HIM LIKE
THAT, BUT...
>> YOU THINK YOU DON'T HAVE TO?
>> NO, I KNOW I GOT TO.
I WILL.
>> YOU JUST GO BUY A PACK OF
DIAPERS EVERY WEEK ON FRIDAY
WHEN YOU GET A PAYCHECK AND A
BOX OF WIPIES, AND I'LL BE FINE.
>> ALL RIGHT, BOX OF--WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA.
NOW YOU PUT THE BOX OF WIPIES IN
THERE, SO I DON'T--
>> WELL WHAT DO YOU EXPECT,
ME AND HER TO DO EVERYTHING?
>> I BARELY GET $40 FOR WORKING
ONE DAY.
>> ONE DAY, ALMOST $40.
THAT'S A LOT FOR A WEEK.
GIVE ME $40 A WEEK.
THAT'D BE FINE.
>> WELL, THAT'S TWO GRAMS.
I WAS JUST MESSING WITH YOU.
>> I'M NOT JOKING THOUGH.
I'M BEING SERIOUS, AND YOU CAN'T
BE SERIOUS.
YOU GOT ONE MONTH, AND YOU GOT
TO START GIVING ME MONEY FOR HIM
OR BUYING HIM STUFF, BETTER YET,
OR YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO CHILD
SUPPORT.
>> UH-UH.
>> YOU AIN'T JUST GONNA BE A
LITTLE DADDY THAT DON'T DO
NOTHING FOR HIM BESIDES COME
AROUND EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
>> I'M TRYING NOT TO DO THAT.
>> HOW ARE YOU TRYING?
>> OH, GOD, LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> YOU HAVEN'T BOUGHT ANYTHING.
>> [belches]
[laughs]
>> IT'S NOT FUNNY WHEN IT
ACTUALLY COMES DOWN TO ME AND
HER PAY FOR EVERYTHING AND
YOU'RE JUST COMING AROUND BEING
FRIEND TO THE BABY.
YOU GOT TO STEP UP.
>> I WISH I COULD SAY I GOT
THROUGH TO DUSTIN, BUT IT'S BEEN
A MONTH, AND HE STILL HASN'T
PAID FOR ANYTHING.
[line trills]
WE SEE HOW MUCH HE WANTS TO TALK
TO US.
[smooches]
[phone beeps]
OBVIOUSLY NOT THAT BAD.
LAST YEAR ON VALENTINE'S DAY,
WE WERE INSEPARABLE.
HE WROTE, "YOU'RE THE BEST THING
THAT HAS EVER HAPPENED TO ME,
AND I NEVER, EVER WANT TO LOSE
YOU.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
LOVE, DUSTIN."
>> THAT WAS PRETTY DEEP
FOR DUSTIN.
>> HE GOT ME THIS.
BUT THIS YEAR, I'M ON MY WAY TO
SEE A LAWYER TO FILE FOR CHILD
SUPPORT.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
OH, HONEY.
I'M SORRY.
>> I DON'T WANT TO SPEND
MY VALENTINE'S DAY TALKING
TO A LAWYER.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS.
>> THE THINGS WE DO
TO BE A GOOD MOM.
BECAUSE MOST MOMS WOULDN'T BE
THERE WITH THEIR KID.
THEY WOULD BE DITCHING THEM
WITH THEIR GRANDMA.
>> NO, MOST MOMS WOULDN'T KICK
DUSTIN TO THE CURB BECAUSE HE'S
NOT HELPING.
>> I AGREE.
>> I CAN'T MAKE SOMEBODY DO
SOMETHING.
>> OH, THE GOVERNMENT CAN MAKE
HIM.
THE GOVERNMENT CAN MAKE HIM.
THEY WILL MAKE HIM.
>> HI.
>> HI, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD, GOOD.
WHY DON'T Y'ALL HAVE A SEAT.
>> I'M ON THE LEFT.
THANK YOU FOR MEETING US.
>> I'M PLEASED TO.
I KNOW THAT YOU WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT YOUR RIGHTS AS A NEW
MOTHER.
>> YEAH.
>> WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME HOW YOU
SEE THE FATHER.
>> FINANCIALLY, HE HASN'T GAVE
A DOLLAR.
>> THAT WILL CHANGE.
YOU DO HAVE A RIGHT TO SEEK
SUPPORT FROM HIM, AND YOU NEED A
COURT ORDER TO DO THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> IF HE DOESN'T MEET THAT
OBLIGATION, THE COURT PUTS HIM
IN DETENTION IF HE'S STILL A
JUVENILE AND IN JAIL
IF HE'S AN ADULT.
>> YEAH.
>> THEY WILL NOT TOLERATE A
PARENT THAT IS NOT WILLING TO
SUPPORT THEIR CHILDREN.
>> MM-KAY.
>> PERIOD.
>> WE EVEN ASKED A REASONABLE
THING, WHICH IS A PACK OF
DIAPERS AND A PACK OF WIPES A
WEEK.
THAT'S ALL WE ASKED FOR.
>> DID YOU GET IT?
>> NEVER.
NOT THE FIRST DIAPER.
NOT ANYTHING.
>> YOU'VE ALREADY DONE THE CIVIL
THING.
YOU'VE ASKED HIM OUTSIDE OF
COURT, "HELP ME FINANCIALLY.
BRING ME SOME DIAPERS."
HE HASN'T LISTENED TO YOU.
EVERY FATHER IN THE UNITED
STATES HAS THE OBLIGATION TO
SUPPORT THEIR CHILDREN
FINANCIALLY, AND YOU SHOULD FEEL
NO GUILT WHATSOEVER IN BRINGING
THIS TO HIS ATTENTION.
YOU CANNOT AFFORD TO RAISE THAT
CHILD ON YOUR OWN.
YOU'RE GOING TO NEED THE
ASSISTANCE OF HIS FATHER,
AND WE'RE GOING TO MAKE SURE
THAT HE GETS THAT ASSISTANCE.
>> female announcer: DON'T
GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU WANT TO GET CHANGED?
[baby whimpers]
NO?
YOU ANGRY.
I SEE THAT FACE.
[baby crying]
>> WHERE'S DADDY?
HUH?
DADDY NOT HERE?
SAY, "SHAME ON DADDY.
SHAME ON DADDY."
>> HEY, DO YOU WANT HELP?
HI, SQUIRT.
HI.
WHERE'S YOUR DADA?
>> AT HOME.
HE'S NOT AROUND AS MUCH
AS HE SHOULD BE.
>> SO HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT
GOING DOWN TO THE COURTS AND
TAKING CHILD SUPPORT OUT ON HIM
SINCE HE'S NOT WILLINGLY GIVING
YOU ANYTHING?
DO YOU NOT LIKE THAT IDEA?
>> MOM AND I ACTUALLY TALKED TO
A LAWYER.
>> SO ARE YOU GONNA DO IT NOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU THINK HE'S GONNA, LIKE,
LASH OUT?
>> IT'S NOT LIKE I DIDN'T GIVE
HIM A CHANCE OR WARN HIM OR ASK
HIM A BILLION TIMES.
>> I TOLD YOU THAT THIS WAS
GONNA HAPPEN WHEN YOU WERE
PREGNANT.
SO HOW ARE YOU GONNA FINISH
SCHOOL WITHOUT HELP FROM DUSTIN?
>> I MEAN, I GOT ALL A's AND B's
RIGHT NOW.
AND ALL MY WORK GETS DONE.
EVEN IF IT'S LATE, IT ALL GETS
DONE.
MOM HELPS ME WITH HIM A LOT,
AND, LIKE, IF I'M TIRED.
BUT I KNOW I NEED TO GET
SCHOOLWORK DONE, AND I CAN'T
JUGGLE BOTH AT THE SAME TIME.
>> DON'T YOU FEEL LIKE THAT
SHOULD BE DUSTIN'S PLACE THOUGH,
NOT MOM'S, CONSIDERING IT'S
DUSTIN'S KID?
>> I'M FED UP WITH DUSTIN.
>> SO YOU SHOULD GET CHILD
SUPPORT.
IT SHOULDN'T BE A QUESTION.
>> MM.
[sniffles]
>> I'M GLAD THAT YOU'RE DOING
WHAT'S RIGHT FOR DRAKE AS A MOM
AND NOT CARING ABOUT HOW DUSTIN
FEELS.
>> [sighs]
>> ARE YOU NERVOUS?
>> A LITTLE.
I KNOW THAT FILING FOR CHILD
SUPPORT IS THE RIGHT THING TO
DO, BUT I DON'T KNOW HOW DUSTIN
WILL REACT.
NO, I DON'T NEED HELP.
THANK YOU.
>> I KNOW YOU DON'T.
OH, LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S AWAKE.
>> WHAT YOU DONE TODAY?
>> NOTHING. SCHOOL.
>> I GOT SOMETHING TO TELL YOU.
IT'S KIND OF DIFFICULT TO SAY.
>> IS IT BAD?
>> NOT ON MY BEHALF.
IT MIGHT BE ON YOURS.
>> THEN I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
>> WELL, YOU HAVE TO KNOW.
>> I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
>> WELL, I FILED FOR CHILD
SUPPORT.
>> YOU'RE NOT HELPING AT ALL.
YOU HAVEN'T BOUGHT THE FIRST
THING FOR HIM.
AND, I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT AROUND
THAT MUCH.
AND I NEED HELP.
>> DUSTIN, STOP.
>> I WANT TO SEE HIM SMILE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM IN A WHILE.
>> YOU GONNA TALK TO ME?
>> I DON'T WANT TO.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD.
>> WHY?
I FEEL LIKE IT'S STUPID.
>> YOU'RE MAD.
I CAN TELL ON YOUR FACE BECAUSE
YOU WON'T LOOK AT ME WHILE
YOU'RE TALKING.
>> I HAVEN'T LOOKED AT YOU THE
WHOLE TIME.
>> AND YOU GOT THAT LITTLE,
LIKE, SMARTASS LOOK ON YOUR
FACE.
>> COME ON, DON'T USE HIM AS A
DISTRACTION.
EVERY TIME I TRY TO TELL YOU
SOMETHING, YOU JUST GIVE ME ONE
WORD ANSWERS.
I'M PAYING ATTENTION TO HIM.
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT ME TO DO,
ISN'T IT?
>> I'D LIKE FOR YOU TO ACTUALLY
HAVE A TALK WITH ME FOR ONCE.
IT'S WHAT RELATIONSHIPS DO WHEN
THEY'RE FAMILIES.
THEY DON'T JUST ACT LIKE YOU'RE
ACTING.
>> LIKE WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
I AIN'T GOT NOTHING TO SAY.
>> I JUST WANT TO, LIKE...
>> I WANT TO PLAY WITH HIM.
>> BLOW IT UP.
THAT'S ALL YOU WANT TO DO
WHEN I'M TRYING TO TALK TO YOU.
ANY OTHER TIME, YOU DON'T WANT
TO PLAY WITH HIM.
SO ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME HOW YOU
ACTUALLY FEEL?
>> YOU'RE ANNOYING.
>> I'M ANNOYING?
>> MM-HMM.
>> SCREW YOU.
>> [laughs]
>> SEE, THAT'S HOW YOUR AN
ASS[bleep] RIGHT THERE.
>> [chuckles]
>> YOU KNOW, LIKE, HONESTLY, YOU
JUST PISSED ME OFF WITH THAT.
>> * HOME
* HOME ALL ALONE
* LYING IN MY BED
* HIDING IN MY HEAD
>> WHEN I FIRST MET DUSTIN,
I LIKED HIM BECAUSE HE WAS
FUNNY, RECKLESS, CAREFREE, AND
WE HAD FUN AND PARTIED TOGETHER.
AND THEN WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
EVERYTHING CHANGED.
DUSTIN'S STILL THE CAREFREE
PERSON, BUT I LEARNED THAT
I HAVE TO BE A FULL-TIME MOMMY.
A YEAR AGO I NEVER THOUGHT I'D
HAVE A BABY AT 16 AND BE IN A
COURTROOM AT 17 FILING FOR CHILD
SUPPORT ON MY BOYFRIEND BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T HELP.
MAMA.
I NEVER THOUGHT THAT I'D BE
STRONG ENOUGH TO GO AND DO CHILD
SUPPORT, BUT I GOT WORRY ABOUT
MY SON AND WHAT HE NEEDS
AND WHAT'S BEST FOR HIM.
>> WELCOME TO KASEY'S.
>> HI.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE YOU A JOB
APPLICATION.
>> OKAY.
>> SO YOU COULD WORK DAYS OR
NIGHTS.
>> UH-HUH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, THAT SOUNDS
AWESOME.
>> IN THE BEGINNING, I WAS THE
ONLY ONE THAT HAD HOPE FOR
DUSTIN, AND EVERY DAY THE FAITH
GOES AWAY MORE.
I DON'T REALLY SEE ME AND DUSTIN
TOGETHER FOREVER.
WE'RE HONESTLY TWO DIFFERENT
PEOPLE NOW.
[sighs]
MY OPINION, YOU SHOULD WAIT TO
HAVE A BABY BECAUSE YOUR LIFE IS
NOT WHAT YOU'RE GONNA THINK.
YOU'RE GONNA THINK YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE A FAMILY AND THE MONEY IN
THE HOUSE, AND YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE STUCK AT HOME
WITH YOUR MOM OR YOUR DAD FOR
YEARS, AND MOST LIKELY, HATE TO
BREAK IT TO EVERYBODY, YOU'RE
NOT GONNA BE WITH THE PERSON
YOU HAVE A BABY WITH.
>> announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT...
>> WITH MY MOM BEING IN JAIL,
IT'S REALLY HARD FOR ME TO
FOCUS.
>> I THINK HE'S BETTER OFF HERE.
>> WITH TREVOR'S MOM, I DON'T
FEEL COMFORTABLE SAYING,
"HERE'S MY KID.
YOU CAN BE ALONE WITH HIM."
I'M NOT SAYING THAT YOU'RE A BAD
MOM, TINA.
>> THERE'S NOBODY IN THIS WORLD
THAT WOULDN'T TRUST ME WITH
THEIR [bleep] BABY!
>> I TRIED TO TALK TO YOU.