>> I'M NOT A SQUARE.
>> [laughs]
I'M JAZMIN.
I'M 17, AND I'M FROM RAYTOWN,
MISSOURI.
I'M IN MY SENIOR YEAR OF HIGH
SCHOOL, AND I'M LOOKING FORWARD
TO GRADUATING AND STARTING
COLLEGE.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM, STEP DAD,
AND YOUNGER BROTHER, XAVIER.
>> WE GOT TWO DIFFERENT PEPPERS.
>> THEY'RE THE SAME SHAPE.
I'M REALLY CLOSE WITH MY MOM,
BUT MY PARENTS ARE SUPER STRICT,
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO
DATING.
>> DON'T PLAY HOUSE.
LIVE REALITY.
>> I MET MY BOYFRIEND, DELL,
ALMOST A YEAR AGO,
AND HE ONLY LIVES A BLOCK AWAY.
BUT WE COULDN'T GO ON DATES
UNTIL MY PARENTS APPROVED.
>> MAKE YOUR MOVE.
THAT ONE WORKS.
>> [laughs]
AND EVEN THEN, THEY SET VERY
INTENSE HOUSE RULES...
WHICH WE FAILED TO FOLLOW.
AND NOW I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
DELL AND I MET ONLINE, AND WE
ONLY KNEW EACH OTHER FOR THREE
MONTHS WHEN I GOT PREGNANT WITH
OUR DAUGHTER, LAILA...
>> LOVE YOU.
>> YEAH, I LOVE YOU TOO.
BUT WE IMMEDIATELY HIT IT OFF,
AND WE LOVE SPENDING ALL OUR
FREE TIME TOGETHER.
WE WANT TO GET OUR OWN PLACE
ONCE THE BABY COMES, BUT DELL
NEEDS TO FIND A JOB FIRST.
HELP.
>> NEED HELP GETTING UP THERE?
>> YES.
WHAT'D YOU THINK WHEN WE FIRST
MET?
LIKE, THE VERY FIRST TIME.
FOR A WHILE.
>> WILL YOU HELP...
[laughs]
I CAN'T FIGURE OUT IF YOU TRYING
TO BE AN INSULT OR WHAT.
DON'T START WITH ME.
>> YOU WASN'T EVEN SHY OR
NERVOUS OR NONE OF THAT.
>> YOU WERE SHY.
YOU WAS NERVOUS.
YOU WERE SHAKING.
YEAH, YOU ARE GONNA TALK TO ME.
YOU'RE GONNA TALK TO ME.
YOU HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO
TALK TO ME.
>> I DO.
>> [laughs]
OKAY.
SO WITH THE WHOLE PREGNANCY
THING, HOW'D YOU FEEL?
>> I WAS NERVOUS.
I WAS SCARED.
>> I UNDERSTAND THEY
GRANDPARENTS AND WE YOUNG,
BUT THEY DON'T NEED TO METER
OUR EVERY MOVE.
LIKE, WHEN WE DO GET OUR OWN
PLACE, I MEAN, YOU DON'T HAVE
THE ADDED WORRY.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO MOVE IN
TOGETHER.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> [laughs]
STOP MAKING THAT FACE.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T TAKE YOU
SERIOUSLY.
AS LONG AS SHE'S TAKEN CARE OF.
I DON'T WANT TO SIT HERE.
I WANT TO SIT THERE.
>> THAT'S WHAT'S NOT GONNA
HAPPEN.
>> THAT'S THE QUEEN'S CHAIR.
[laughs]
>> YOU CAN SIT RIGHT THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WHO'S BLESSING THE
FOOD?
>> TEESHA MILLER.
>> FATHER GOD IN HEAVEN,
WE THANK YOU FOR THIS DAY, LORD.
BLESS US AS WE TAKE THE FOOD.
AMEN.
>> PASS 'EM.
>> THANK YOU.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU JUST HANDED
THOSE KNIVES TO ME.
I THINK I'M MODERATELY WORRIED
THAT YOU'RE NOT GONNA FULFILL
YOUR POTENTIAL BY HAVING A BABY.
A PART OF ME WONDERS IF YOU'LL
BE ABLE TO MAKE THE JUMP IN
MATURITY TO SAY, "THIS IS WHAT
MY HEART SAYS OR MY BODY FEELS,
BUT HOW WILL THIS IMPACT MY LIFE
IN THE LONG RUN?"
>> I'M JUST GONNA DEAL WITH IT.
>> YOU'RE JUST GONNA DEAL WITH
IT?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
DID YOUR COUNSELOR AND THE
PRINCIPAL AGREE THAT YOU WILL
ACTUALLY STILL GRADUATE IN
DECEMBER?
>> YEAH.
I'M GONNA DO ONLINE.
>> IT DOESN'T COME WITHOUT
SACRIFICE.
ARE YOU AT ALL WORRIED ABOUT HOW
THIS IS GONNA CHANGE YOUR LIFE?
>> NO.
I FIGURE I'LL MAKE IT HAPPEN.
>> I DO PRAY IT WORKS OUT,
NOT FOR YOUR SAKE SO MUCH,
BUT FOR LAILA'S SAKE.
BUT I WAS HUGELY DISAPPOINTED.
>> MAJOR, MAJOR DISAPPOINTMENT.
IT JUST HURT.
EVERYTHING CHANGED, AND THEN
WORRYING ABOUT YOU AND DELL
BEING SO YOUNG.
>> I CAN LOOK YOU IN YOUR EYES
AND TELL YOU THAT YOU HAVE NO
IDEA--NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE IN FOR.
>> IT SUCKS HOW UPSET MY PARENTS
ARE, AND I REALLY WANT TO PROVE
THEM WRONG BY STAYING ON TOP OF
MY ONLINE SCHOOLWORK.
BUT I MISS SEEING MY FRIENDS
EVERY DAY.
>> DO YOU GUYS HAVE STRAWBERRY
SMOOTHIES?
>> YEAH. FOR YOU?
>> STRAWBERRY BANANA.
>> HERE'S YOUR STRAWBERRY
SMOOTHIE FOR YA.
>> THANK YOU.
GOD, OF COURSE YOU DO.
>> I REMEMBER HOW I TOLD YOU
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT.
DO YOU REMEMBER?
AND YOU WERE LIKE, "OH, MY GOSH,
NO!"
>> LIKE, 'CAUSE I THOUGHT IT WAS
A JOKE.
LIKE, WHO SAYS THAT?
>> RIGHT.
>> LIKE, I JUST HUNG OUT WITH
YOU LAST WEEKEND.
YOU DIDN'T LOOK PREGNANT THEN.
LIKE...
DID YOU KNOW THAT PREGNANCY WAS
A POSSIBILITY?
>> YEAH, BUT LIKE I SAID, IT WAS
KIND OF LIKE A RATIO TYPE
OF THING.
LIKE, YOU THINK, LIKE, "NO,
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN TO ME."
AND I THOUGHT BIRTH CONTROL JUST
MADE YOU FAT.
WHICH I ENDED UP FAT ANYWAY.
>> OKAY, BUT...
>> THEN I HEARD ONE MAKES YOU
LOSE YOUR HAIR, AND I WAS JUST
LIKE, "OKAY, IT'S JUST"--
>> LOSE YOUR HAIR?
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I MEAN, WE'RE GIFTED
WITH HAIR STORES.
I MEAN, IF YOU LOSE YOUR HAIR...
>> SHUT UP.
>> GO BUY SOME MORE.
[laughs]
WITH YOU LEAVING SCHOOL EARLY
AND EVERYTHING, IT'S LIKE WE'RE
STILL IN HIGH SCHOOL LIVING HIGH
SCHOOL LIFE, AND YOU'RE, LIKE,
GROWN.
>> I THINK IT'LL BE REAL WHEN
YOU GUYS ACTUALLY DO GO TO
COLLEGE, 'CAUSE THEN I'LL BE
SITTING HERE.
>> YEAH, WE'LL BE POSTING
PICTURES ON INSTAGRAM, PARTYING.
>> AND I THOUGHT I WAS HAVING,
LIKE, THE SAME PATH AND THE SAME
KIND OF, LIKE, LIFESTYLE.
WE'RE KIND OF STAGGERED NOW.
YEAH, I WAS GONNA GO TO SCHOOL.
>> FOR WHAT, THOUGH?
>> PLAY WITH BLOOD?
>> YEAH.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO NOW?
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU AND DELL
WILL BE TOGETHER FOR, LIKE,
EVER?
>> OH, YEAH.
WE JUST HAVE TO FIND THAT MIDDLE
GROUND WHERE WE CAN BOTH GO TO
SCHOOL, HAVE A JOB,
YOU KNOW, BE COMFORTABLE,
AND HOPEFULLY MOVE IN TOGETHER.
WHEN I GOT HOME, I FOUND OUT
DELL GOT A JOB.
I'M REALLY EXCITED, BECAUSE THIS
IS A STEP CLOSER TO US GETTING
OUR OWN PLACE.
MY PARENTS WANTED TO TALK TO US
TODAY ABOUT OUR PLANS,
AND I HOPE THEY AGREE WITH WHAT
WE'RE THINKING.
>> HI, EVERYBODY.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP, DELL?
>> IT'S B-RAD.
>> HAVE A SEAT.
LET'S TALK FOR A SECOND.
>> WHAT KIND OF PLANS DO Y'ALL
GOT, AS FAR AS, LIKE, STICKING
MONEY TO THE SIDE
FOR EMERGENCIES, OR...
>> AND INCOME IS JUST A QUARTER
OF THE BATTLE, 'CAUSE THE REST
OF THE BATTLE IS HAVING BENEFITS
AND HAVING A CAREER PATH,
A LADDER.
>> ME NOT HAVING A JOB AS LONG
AS I DID, I COULDN'T CONTROL
THAT.
>> DISAGREE WITH THAT ONE,
BROTHER.
SO WHAT'S THE PLAN FOR WHEN THE
BABY'S BORN?
WHERE'S--
YOU KNOW, HOW IS THIS ALL GONNA
WORK OUT?
>> SOMETHING THAT I WAS THINKING
ABOUT IS SOMETHING THAT MY DAD
HAS PREACHED TO ME.
HE SAID WHEN I HAD KIDS,
I WAS OUT OF MY PARENT'S HOUSE.
AND SO FOR ME, I FEEL LIKE
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT I NEED
TO DO.
>> I THINK THAT'S COMMENDABLE.
BUT IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
LIVING TOGETHER, YOU KNOW,
I SHOULD BE REAL CLEAR WITH YOU
THAT THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
I SUPPORT.
>> FOR A MYRIAD OF REASONS.
YOU MOVE IN TOGETHER, AND YOU
DON'T EVEN HAVE A BASIC
UNDERSTANDING, AND YOU REALLY
DON'T KNOW ONE ANOTHER.
THAT'S JUST A RECIPE FOR
DISASTER.
>> SO I THINK WE SHOULD JUST BE
CLEAR, YOU KNOW, FOR YOU ALL'S
SAKE, WHEN BABY LAILA COMES,
OUR HOUSE HAS NOT CHANGED.
>> THERE ARE CONSEQUENCES FOR
EVERYTHING THAT WE DO.
>> YOU KNOW, THERE ARE RULES ON
HOW YOU CAN DATE HER.
>> MM-HMM.
>> SO A PART OF MY REACTION TO
THE PREGNANCY IS THAT THERE
OBVIOUSLY HAVE BEEN SOME
DECEPTION AND DISOBEDIENCE
TO THE RULES.
JAZMIN, YOU HAD REALLY
ESTABLISHED YOURSELF AS A
TRUSTWORTHY CHILD, YOU KNOW,
SOMEONE WHO HAD GREAT POTENTIAL,
SO YOU HAD EARNED JUST A LEVEL
OF TRUST IN OUR HEARTS THAT THIS
WAS DEFINITELY A GREAT BLOW TO.
>> I'M BUMMED MY PARENTS WON'T
LET US GET OUR OWN PLACE,
AND I HATE THAT I LET THEM DOWN,
BUT I REALLY HOPE THEY'LL RELAX
THE HOUSE RULES ONCE LAILA
COMES.
HI, DELL.
>> HELLO, JAZMIN.
>> I'M HUNGRY.
I JUST WANT TO SHOW MY PARENTS
THAT DELL AND I ARE TAKING THEM
SERIOUSLY.
>> MISS ME?
>> YOU GONNA EAT THAT MANY EGGS?
>> THERE'S THREE OVER HERE.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THREE PEOPLE.
>> SHE DON'T WANT NO EGGS.
ARE YOU COMING TO THE DOCTOR'S
APPOINTMENT TOMORROW?
IT'S EARLY.
>> YEAH.
I GOT TO WORK LATE TONIGHT,
BUT I'M GONNA BE THERE.
>> YOU GOT TO BE UP AND HERE
OR WE'LL LEAVE YOU.
>> ARE THEY CHECKING YOUR CERVIX
OR SOMETHING THIS TIME?
>> YES.
I HEARD THAT HURT WHEN THEY
CHECK YOUR CERVIX.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT A CERVIX
IS.
I DON'T EVEN--I DON'T KNOW WHERE
IT IS.
I MEAN, I KNOW IT'S IN THERE,
BUT...
>> HOW MANY OF THEM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SIX.
IS SHE KICKING YOU?
>> NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> 'CAUSE SHE DON'T WANT TO.
>> WAKE UP.
>> SHE DON'T WANT TO WAKE UP.
>> I JUST WISH YOU HAD, LIKE,
A CODE WORD OR SOMETHING.
LIKE, IT JUST TAKES YOU...
>> WHY WOULD THEY FIRE YOU
'CAUSE YOU HAVING A BABY?
'CAUSE YOU LEAVING EARLY?
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK THEY MAKE EXCEPTIONS
FOR STUFF LIKE THAT.
>> YOU TIRED?
>> JAZMIN, FOR REAL, THIS IS THE
LAST 7:00 DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT.
>> THE NEXT ONE'S AT 8:30.
>> AND THEN ANY AFTER THAT IS
GONNA HAVE TO BE AFTERNOON.
>> JAZMIN, YOU READY TO COME ON
BACK?
>> YEP.
[knocks on door]
>> HEY.
HOW ARE YOU, PUMPKIN?
>> FINE. HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WHAT ARE YOU
FEELING?
>> SHE'S INCREASINGLY MORE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> THIRD TRIMESTER SUCKS,
DOESN'T IT?
>> I CAN'T GET COMFORTABLE.
>> I KNOW IT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA CHECK YOU.
>> WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WHAT DO I
DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
YOU AIN'T GOT NO MACHINE?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> FINGERS.
IT'S GONNA BE UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> OH.
>> I KNOW.
THIS IS THE PART NOBODY LIKES.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ONE FINGER.
TAKE ANOTHER DEEP BREATH.
>> THAT'S WEIRD.
>> YEAH.
YEAH, YOU'RE PRETTY THINNED OUT.
>> LAILA DON'T LIKE THIS.
>> YOU DID MUCH BETTER THAN I
THOUGHT YOU WOULD.
GOOD JOB.
>> GOOD FOR YOU.
>> YOU DID GOOD.
>> [laughs]
>> HI, JAZMIN.
>> HI, DELL.
TODAY'S MY BABY SHOWER, AND
DESPITE HOW MUCH DELL'S BEEN
WORKING, HE'S COMING OVER TO
HELP ME GET READY,
AND I HOPE MY MOM SEE'S HOW MUCH
HE'S STEPPING UP.
HELLO.
HEY!
THAT'S PRETTY.
>> LIKE A PEACOCK TAIL.
>> AW...
OHH...
>> YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
>> YOU LOOK SO PRETTY, TEE TEE.
>> THANKS.
CAN I OPEN STUFF?
I'M GOING TO.
BABY CLOTHES STUFF.
I LIKE CLOTHES.
AW...
>> THAT IS SUPER CUTE!
>> MAMA, LOOK.
THIS IS SO CUTE.
>> NO.
>> AH!
>> OH, NAIL POLISH.
FOR BABY LAILA AND HER TOESIES.
LOOK, HER BLANKET MATCHES MY
ROBE.
>> THAT'S GOING HOME WITH ME.
[laughter]
>> BUT IT MATCHES MY ROBE.
>> IT MATCHES MY BED.
[laughter]
>> THANKS, GUYS.
AND EAT CUPCAKES.
DON'T EAT ALL OF THEM, THOUGH.
HOLD ON.
[laughter]
WITH DELL WORKING AND ALL THESE
GREAT GIFTS FROM THE SHOWER,
I FEEL EVEN MORE PREPARED FOR
WHEN LAILA GETS HERE.
>> JAZ AIN'T SMILING.
>> SO YOU SAID "CHEESE,"
BUT OKAY.
>> SMILE.
[chime dings]
MY DUE DATE IS IN JUST SIX
WEEKS, AND I REALLY WANT TO MAKE
TIME TO SEE MY FRIENDS BEFORE
THE BABY ARRIVES.
>> SO HOW ARE THINGS GOING WITH
YOU AND DELL?
>> EVERYTHING'S GOOD.
HE'S GOT HIS NEW JOB.
BUT IT'S WEIRD 'CAUSE HIS
SCHEDULE IS JUST--
ONE DAY HE WORKS DAYTIME, NEXT
TIME HE WORKS LATE AT NIGHT,
THEN THE NEXT DAY HE WORKS VERY
EARLY IN THE MORNING.
>> SO IS YOUR MOM, LIKE,
WATCHING YOU TWO WHEN YOU'RE IN
THE ROOM TOGETHER NOW?
>> [laughs]
NO, SHE JUST--I DON'T KNOW.
SHE JUST KIND OF HAS, LIKE,
THIS LITTLE AIR TO HER,
LITTLE ATTITUDE.
BUT OTHER THAN THAT--
>> ATTITUDE, LIKE, "MM-HMM,
WHAT Y'ALL DOING?"
THAT KIND OF STUFF?
>> YEAH. [laughs]
>> DO YOU WISH THAT, LIKE, YOU
DIDN'T GET PREGNANT SO YOU WOULD
STILL HAVE THEIR TRUST?
>> I MEAN, IT'S JUST HARD,
'CAUSE, YOU KNOW, LIKE, ME AND
MY MOM WERE BEST FRIENDS, AND
HAVING HER TRUST IS JUST--
>> IMPORTANT?
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK YOU GUYS WILL BE
FINE.
SO ARE YOU, LIKE, HOPING THAT
LIKE, WHEN LAILA GETS HERE THE
RULES WON'T BE SO STRICT ABOUT
HIM BEING OVER THE HOUSE AND,
LIKE, THEY'LL LET HIM STAY OVER
LATE IF HE'S, LIKE, WATCHING HIS
DAUGHTER?
>> YEAH.
>> I THINK HE'LL WORK IT OUT.
I MEAN, HE'S STEPPING UP NOW,
SO HOPEFULLY THINGS JUST GET
BETTER.
>> YEAH.
I THINK THEY'RE GONNA BE OKAY
WITH IT.
I JUST HOPE MY PARENTS SEE THAT
HE'S TRYING TO MOVE FORWARD INTO
FATHERHOOD AND CHANGE THE RULES.
>> I HOPE YOUR PARENTS DO SEE
THAT, YOU KNOW, HE'S TRYING.
>> I JUST HOPE THAT HE HAS
ENOUGH TIME WITH HER,
THE TIME THAT HE WANTS, THE TIME
THAT HE NEEDS TO GET LEARN HIS
DAUGHTER.
>> THIS MORNING, I HAD ANOTHER
DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT, AND DELL
WAS SUPPOSED TO MEET US THERE,
BUT HE NEVER SHOWED UP.
[beeping]
[line ringing]
>> HI.
WHERE WAS YOU THIS MORNING?
>> DELL, YOU DIDN'T KNOW THERE
WAS A DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT THIS
MORNING?
IT IS JAZMIN, BUT I'M IN THE CAR
AS WELL.
I'M KIND OF CURIOUS AS TO WHY
YOU DIDN'T CALL HER.
>> OKAY.
NICE TALKING TO YOU.
BU-BYE.
>> SO HOW DID YOU FEEL ABOUT THE
DOCTOR'S APPOINTMENT?
>> THEY ALL GO THE SAME.
>> I FEEL A CERTAIN WAY ABOUT
DELL NOT BEING THERE.
>> WHY?
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY REACTION
TO HIM NOT BEING THERE?
>> NO, BECAUSE
HE'S REALLY WORKING HARD.
>> I'M SICK OF BEING PREGNANT.
I'VE BEEN PREGNANT FOR, LIKE,
TWO YEARS.
>> IT'S NOT ALL IT'S CRACKED UP
TO BE?
>> JUST FAT.
CAN'T BREATHE.
CAN'T TOUCH MY TOES.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK LAILA'S
GONNA BE LIKE?
I THINK SHE'S GONNA BE JUST LIKE
YOU.
YOU WERE A CRYBABY.
>> I HOPE SHE'S NOT A CRYBABY.
I DON'T HAVE TIME.
I HAVE TO GET ALL MY SCHOOLWORK
FINISHED.
>> I'M KIND OF CONCERNED ON
WHETHER OR NOT YOU CAN REALLY
REALIZE HOW LARGE THIS WILL BE
TO DO HOMEWORK, CATCH UP ON
HOMEWORK, AND TAKE CARE OF A
NEWBORN BABY.
>> I DON'T NEED A SET SCHEDULE.
THAT'S WHAT MESSES ME UP IN
LIFE.
LIKE, MY OWN...
DOO, DOO, DOO, DOO.
>> I DON'T THINK SHE'S GONNA
FOLLOW YOUR DOO, DOO, DOO, DOO.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
SO HER SCHEDULE IS GONNA
ADD THE BIG DOOPS.
>> IN OTHER WORDS, YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE YOUR CUES FROM HER.
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN SHE ASLEEP, YOU'RE GONNA
STUDY.
>> YEAH, AND DO STUFF.
>> HOWEVER, CONVENTIONAL WISDOM
SAYS, "WHEN YOUR BABY SLEEP,
YOU SLEEP."
SO WHEN YOUR BABY ASLEEP,
YOU'LL BE STUDYING.
>> OR SHE'LL BE UP.
I'M GONNA SIT THERE WITH HER
AND DO MY WORK.
>> YOU'RE KIND
OF MINIMIZING THIS.
I DON'T THINK IT'S GONNA BE AS
EASY AS YOU THINK.
>> OKAY, WELL, I GOT TO GET IT
DONE, EASY OR NOT.
>> RIGHT.
THAT'S MY POINT.
SO I'M GLAD WE BOTH GOT THERE.
>> GO ON.
[both giggle]
DELL IS OFF TODAY, SO HE TOOK
ME OUT TO LUNCH, AND NOW WE'RE
DOING SOME SHOPPING FOR LAILA.
OH, BABY COSTUMES.
LOOK.
WHAT IS THIS, AN ELEPHANT?
>> IT'S A HIPPO.
>> WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
THIS IS AN ELEPHANT.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> I THINK A HIPPO IS JUST A
WATER ELEPHANT.
[laughs]
>> ELEPHANTS DON'T LIVE IN
WATER.
>> YEAH, THEY DO.
>> IT'S A MAMMAL.
IT LIVES ON LAND.
SHE REALLY CAN'T WEAR TUTUS?
THIS IS CUTE.
>> NOPE.
>> EVEN FOR, LIKE, BABY
PICTURES?
>> NO.
>> WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
DELL, THIS IS REALLY CUTE.
YOU CAN'T EVEN LIE.
>> NO.
>> IT'S OKAY, LAILA.
I GOT YOU AND YOUR CLOTHES TOO.
>> "DADDY'S SWEETHEART."
SEE THAT?
>> OH, THAT'S CUTE.
>> IS THIS GONNA BE ALL FOR YOU
TODAY?
>> YES, MA'AM.
HERE YOU GO.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> both: THANK YOU.
>> HOW Y'ALL FEELING?
>> I'M READY.
>> HAVE Y'ALL THOUGHT ABOUT ALL
THE LITTLE HOOPS AND STUFF
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO JUMP
THROUGH?
>> WHAT HOOPS?
>> HOW WE RUN THE HOUSEHOLD.
JUST SO WE CLEAR...
>> YES.
>> NO VISITATION WHEN THERE'S NO
ADULTS HERE.
>> WELL, WHO COUNTS AS ADULT
SUPERVISION?
>> TEESHA'S MOTHER, MY FATHER,
MYSELF, TEESHA.
IT'S A TRUST THING.
THAT'S ONE OF THE DOWNSIDES
TO NOT DOING IT
THE TRADITIONAL WAY,
THAT WE GET A CALL FIRST BEFORE
DELL COMES OVER.
>> YEAH.
>> NO SEX.
IT'S JUST THE RULES OF THE
HOUSE.
>> I UNDERSTAND THE RULES.
WE GET 'EM.
IT SUCKS MY PARENTS AREN'T
EASING UP ON THE HOUSE RULES,
BUT SINCE I REALLY WANT TO EARN
THEIR TRUST BACK, I CAN'T AFFORD
TO BREAK THEM AGAIN.
HOW'S IT GONNA WORK, LIKE, WITH
OUR SCHEDULES AND STUFF,
WHEN WE FIRST GET HOME FROM THE
HOSPITAL?
I MEAN, 'CAUSE OBVIOUSLY, YOU'RE
STILL GONNA HAVE TO WORK AND
STUFF.
SO ARE YOU GONNA COME OVER EVERY
DAY?
>> OF COURSE I'M GONNA COME OVER
EVERY DAY.
>> LIKE, WHAT DO YOU EXPECT TO
DO?
LIKE, DO YOU EXPECT TO JUST SIT
THERE AND PLAY WITH HER?
DO YOU--
>> I EXPECT TO DO EVERYTHING.
>> SO IF SHE'S HUNGRY,
YOU'RE GONNA FEED HER.
>> MM-HMM.
>> IF SHE POOPS,
YOU'RE GONNA CHANGE HER.
>> YEAH.
>> HOUSE RULES:
NOBODY UNDERAGE HOME ALONE.
>> THAT'S PISSING ME OFF,
IRRITATING ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> RIGHT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M KIND OF FED UP
WITH IT.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE NOT SPENDING ENOUGH TIME
WITH HER.
I WANT YOU TO SEE HER AS MUCH AS
YOU WANT TO.
BUT RULES ARE RULES.
WE SHOULD RESPECT HER RULES,
HER HOUSEHOLD, JUST LIKE
I WOULD WANT, I GUESS,
LAILA TO RESPECT OURS.
>> OKAY.
>> WHATEVER ME AND HER
COMPROMISE ON, I'LL BE OKAY
WITH.
AS LONG AS I GET THE EXTRA TIME.
>> WHAT IF THERE'S NO
COMPROMISE?
>> ONCE THE BABY COMES, I DON'T
WANT TO DEAL WITH MY HAIR.
MY DUE DATE IS IN A WEEK, AND
DELL'S COMING BY TO TALK TO MY
MOM ABOUT LOOSENING THE HOUSE
RULES.
>> HI, DELL.
>> HEY.
>> COME ON IN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> OKAY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I WANTED TO KNOW, LIKE, IF
THAT COULD BE A POSSIBILITY OR
CHANGE IN SOME KIND OF WAY.
>> I CAN APPRECIATE YOU WANTING
TO BE THERE FOR YOUR DAUGHTER'S
FIRSTS AND SEEING THINGS,
YOU KNOW, THAT AS SHE DEVELOPS,
THINGS LIKE THAT, BUT THE TRUTH
OF THE MATTER IS, WE EXTENDED
TRUST TO YOU AND JAZMIN, AND
THAT TRUST WAS ABUSED,
AND THAT'S NOT TAKEN LIGHTLY.
>> I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD BE ABLE
TO COME OVER AND BE TRUSTED
AND TO KNOW THAT WE GONNA BE
OKAY.
>> LET ME TALK TO MR. BRAD.
WE'LL SIT DOWN AND TALK WITH YOU
AND JAZMIN AND FIND A WAY THAT
TAKES EVERYTHING INTO ACCOUNT.
THIS IS OUR HOME, SO WE TAKE
EVERYTHING THAT HAS TO DO WITH
OUR HOME VERY SERIOUSLY.
>> BUT BEFORE MY MOM COULD TALK
OVER DELL'S REQUEST,
I STARTED HAVING CONTRACTIONS.
AND SINCE DELL CAN'T COME OVER
WHEN NO ONE'S HERE, MY MOM'S
RUSHING HOME.
>> OKAY, KID, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> EVERYTHING HURTS.
>> OKAY, TELL ME ABOUT--
WHY IS YOUR LEG SHAKING?
>> BECAUSE IT HURTS.
>> OKAY.
>> [groans]
>> I KNOW.
SO ARE YOU HAVING A CONTRACTION
NOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> DOES IT HURT BETWEEN YOUR
LEGS?
>> MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU GOT TO
POOP?
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY, WE NEED TO GO TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>> I TEXTED DELL, AND HE'S GOING
TO MEET US AT THE HOSPITAL.
[breathing heavily]
THIS ISN'T COLD ENOUGH.
AND MOVE FAST, PLEASE.
>> JAZMIN, DO YOU FEEL PRESSURE
WITH THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> GOOD.
GOOD.
>> ONCE I GOT THE EPIDURAL,
IT REALLY HELPED.
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT,
IT WAS TIME TO START PUSHING.
[indistinct speech]
>> ALL RIGHT, YOU READY?
SHE'S COMING.
STOP.
TAKE ANOTHER DEEP BREATH, PUSH.
ONE, TWO, THREE, STOP.
GOOD, JUST LIKE THAT.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
STOP.
LOOK DOWN.
LOOK DOWN, JAZMIN.
>> LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
LAILA!
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY, LAILA.
>> THANK YOU, JESUS.
[Laila crying]
>> OKAY, GO.
>> * YES, I GOT YOU
* GOT YOU IN MY LIFE
*
* IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT *
[chime dings]
[Laila crying]
>> GOOD MORNING, JAZ.
GOOD MORNING, DELL.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> GOOD MORNING, LAILA.
DID YOU BOO-BOO?
>> EW, WHAT WAS THAT?
>> DON'T STAB HER WITH THEM
NAILS.
>> I'M TRYING NOT TO.
I'M EXCITED LAILA'S HERE, BUT
THERE'S A LOT FOR ME TO LEARN,
SO I'M GLAD DELL'S BEEN ABLE TO
TAKE TIME OFF OF WORK TO BE WITH
ME AT THE HOSPITAL.
>> WHY IS SHE RED?
>> I KNOW.
WHY IS SHE SO RED?
>> SHE GETTING HER COLOR.
OH, JAZ, SHE'S HERE.
I CANNOT BELIEVE IT.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
DELL'S PRETTY TIRED FROM STAYING
UP WITH ME AT THE HOSPITAL,
SO HE'S GOING HOME TO TAKE
A NAP.
>> YOU'RE HOME, LAILA.
>> OH!
>> HOW DO YOU WANT TO DO IT?
YOU WANT TO SPONGE BATH HER--
SPONGE BATHE HER THIS FIRST
TIME?
>> YEAH.
SHE MUST BE TRAUMATIZED.
SHE JUST WOKE UP.
>> SO I'M GONNA WIPE HER REALLY
QUICKLY.
AND SHE'S NOT GONNA LIKE THIS.
IT'S A FOREIGN SENSATION.
I KNOW.
AND YOU SAY, "I KNOW"
JUST TO LET HER KNOW--
>> SHE DON'T KNOW THAT YOU KNOW.
SHE THINK YOU TORTURING HER.
>> OH!
THIS IS YOUR PART.
>> EW.
>> AND THIS IS THE PERFECT
REASON TO TAKE THOSE FINGERNAILS
OFF 'CAUSE YOU HAVE TO PUT IN
EVERY CREASE AND FOLD REALLY,
REALLY WELL.
YOU'RE ALL FRESH AND CLEAN.
[doorbell chimes]
WHO HAS HER?
>> I HAVE MY BABY, LAILA.
>> GIVE ME. GIVE ME.
SHE LOOK JUST LIKE ME,
GIRL VERSION.
>> WHAT'D YOU THINK OF THE
LABOR?
>> YEAH, I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
PASS OUT.
>> REALLY?
YOU EXCITED?
>> OH, YEAH.
THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
>> OH, LORD.
>> ALL RIGHT, TIME TO GO.
>> I REALLY WISH DELL DIDN'T
HAVE TO LEAVE EARLY BECAUSE OF
THE HOUSE RULES...
[Laila crying]
WHAT ARE YOU SAD--
WHAT ARE YOU SAD ABOUT?
BUT THE NEXT DAY, MY PARENTS
ASKED US TO SIT DOWN BECAUSE
THEY HAD COME TO A DECISION.
I'M REALLY HOPING THEY'LL BE
MORE FLEXIBLE NOW THAT LAILA'S
HERE.
>> HOW ARE YOU GUYS FEELING
SINCE LAILA'S BEEN HERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST BE--JUST...
LIKE, "WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HER?
WHAT'S SHE DOING?"
YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT THE SENSE OF SHE'S NOT
BEING TAKEN CARE OF.
IT'S JUST, I'M HER DADDY, AND I
WANT TO KNOW WHAT SHE DOING.
>> IT'S GOOD THAT THE INSTINCT
IS KICKING IN.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I KNOW WE TALKED ABOUT MAYBE
CHANGING THIS, BUT, YOU KNOW,
I HAD A CONVERSATION WITH MY
HUSBAND.
YOU ALL MADE A LIFE-CHANGING
DECISION FOR YOU TWO.
WE, AS PARENTS, ARE NOT WILLING
TO ALTER THE LANDSCAPE OF OUR
HOUSE 'CAUSE YOU ALL COULDN'T
EXHIBIT SELF-CONTROL.
WE HAVE TO ANSWER TO GOD ABOUT
WHAT GOES ON IN HERE.
>> JUST 95% OF THE TIME, I WORK
A LOT, AND OUR SCHEDULES ARE
DIFFERENT, SO IT'S A LETDOWN.
>> HE NEEDS TO SEE HIS DAUGHTER
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE
OR I WANT HIM TO.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE DISAPPOINTED.
SO AM I.
>> STOP PEEING EVERYWHERE.
STOP PEEING EVERYWHERE.
IT SUCKS MY PARENTS WON'T CHANGE
ANYTHING BECAUSE LAILA'S FUSSY
AT NIGHT, AND I COULD REALLY USE
DELL'S HELP.
[Laila crying]
YOU ARE A CRYBABY.
NO, LAILA,
YOU CAN'T GO TO SLEEP?
COME ON.
BETWEEN BEING UP ALL NIGHT AND
NO ONE TO HELP ME TAKE CARE OF
LAILA DURING THE DAY, IT'S BEEN
IMPOSSIBLE TO GET MY HOMEWORK
DONE.
DELL'S BEEN WORKING MORE LATE
SHIFTS AND HASN'T BEEN ABLE TO
SPEND ANY TIME WITH ME OR LAILA.
SLEEPY BUTT.
BUT SINCE HE AND MY MOM ARE OFF
TODAY, HE CAN FINALLY COME OVER.
IT'D BE NICE IF YOU COULD COME
OVER EVERY DAY AND SPEND MORE
TIME WITH HER.
AND ALSO, I NEED TIME TO DO MY
SCHOOLWORK, AND I DON'T HAVE
TIME TO DO THAT 'CAUSE I HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> I CAN SEE WHY THAT'S HARD FOR
YOU.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
GETTING ENOUGH TIME WITH LAILA
AND, LIKE, GETTING TO SEE HER
AND STUFF?
>> NOPE.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU ARE EITHER.
>> WORK HAS GOT IN THE WAY
A LOT.
WE NEED MORE DADDY/DAUGHTER
TIME.
>> I WANT YOU TO BE ABLE TO SEE
HER AS MUCH AS YOU CAN, BUT WE
GOT TO WORK AROUND WHAT THEY
WANT AND THEIR WISHES
'CAUSE IT'S THEIR HOUSE.
>> MM-HMM.
I'M FRUSTRATED WITH IT ALL.
WORKING, NOT BEING ABLE TO COME
HOME TO Y'ALL.
IT'S IRRITATING ME.
I JUST GOT KIND OF MAD
'CAUSE NOW I FEEL LIKE I AIN'T
NEVER GONNA SEE YOU.
NOT SEEING YOU IS GONNA BE
A PROBLEM.
SHE DON'T LIKE YOU.
>> I DON'T THINK WE SPEND ENOUGH
TIME AS A COUPLE EITHER.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE DON'T SPEND
ENOUGH TIME EITHER.
>> I BE MISSING YOU WHEN YOU BE
AT WORK 'CAUSE I DON'T BE HAVING
NOBODY TO PLAY WITH.
>> YEAH.
GIVE ME A DIAPER AND SOME WIPES.
>> PUT THAT UNDER THERE FIRST.
TAKE IT OFF.
>> I THOUGHT YOU WAS SUPPOSED
TO POKE IT.
>> [laughs]
DELL, HER BUTT IS OUT ON THE
SIDE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
>> YOU CAN SEE HER BOOTY CHEEKS.
[Laila crying]
>> YOU WANT YOUR MAMA? FOR REAL.
>> YES.
COME HERE, SKINNY MINNIE.
>> HOW'S OUR RELATIONSHIP GONNA
WORK IN THE FUTURE?
HOW DO YOU SEE IT?
IF WE CAN'T SPEND TIME WITH EACH
OTHER, HOW IS THIS US SUPPOSED
TO WORK?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> DELL WORKED THREE NIGHT
SHIFTS IN A ROW AND HASN'T BEEN
ABLE TO SEE LAILA THIS WEEK,
BUT HE'S FINALLY OFF TONIGHT.
>> HER WHOLE FACE IS GETTING
DARKER.
[phone tone playing]
>> HELLO?
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I'M SITTING HERE WITH MY MAMA
AND LAILA.
UH, HOLD ON.
LET ME ASK MY MAMA.
MOM, CAN DELL COME OVER?
>> NO, IT'S 10:00 P.M.
I'M GOING TO SLEEP.
>> NO.
DELL'S GETTING EVEN MORE
FRUSTRATED WITH THE HOUSE RULES,
AND TODAY HE'S COMING BY TO TALK
TO MY MOM ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> DOES THAT EVERYBODY INCLUDE
ME?
>> YES, EVERYBODY.
>> 'CAUSE THAT--SO ADDRESS ME,
'CAUSE WE CAN GO AHEAD AND GET
THAT ALL THE WAY OUT RIGHT NOW.
>> EVERYBODY.
>> AND WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS REMEMBER YOUR IRRITATION
IS SITTING IN MY HOUSE.
>> WHICH IS IRRITATING ME
'CAUSE IT'S NOT ABOUT WHAT WE
GOT GOING ON.
IT'S ABOUT WHAT'S BEST FOR HER.
I'M JUST TRYING TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN FROM
HERE SINCE SHE'S HERE NOW.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT FOR EVERYBODY
TO GET ALONG BECAUSE EVERYBODY
HAS A RELATIONSHIP WITH LAILA.
>> I AM GOING ABOVE AND BEYOND
WHAT I FEEL IS APPROPRIATE AND
ACCEPTABLE, BUT MY PATIENCE ARE
GROWING VERY THIN.
I UNDERSTAND YOU WANTING TO BE
WITH LAILA AND BE A FATHER
ACTIVE IN HER LIFE, BUT WE ARE
GONNA HAVE OUR HOUSE RESPECTED.
>> HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO BE A
GOOD FATHER IF I DON'T EVER SEE
HER?
>> WHEN YOU DO THINGS OUT OF
GOD'S ORDER AND YOU'RE DEALING
WITH THE SITUATION THAT YOU WANT
TO BE ALL "HE-HE-HE-HE-HE"
CELEBRATORY, BUT THE TRUTH OF
THE MATTER IS, YOU'RE STILL
A KID, AND YOU'RE STILL A KID,
AND THIS HOUSE IS NOT GONNA BE
TURNED UPSIDE DOWN.
>> I'M A LITTLE FRUSTRATED
RIGHT NOW.
I AIN'T GOT NOTHING TO SAY.
[sighs]
>> WHAT'S CRACKING?
I REALLY WANTS TO KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> AIN'T NOTHING CHANGED.
RULES ARE STILL THE SAME.
LIKE, WE AIN'T KIDS.
>> EXACTLY.
YOU CAN'T STILL TREAT HER LIKE A
CHILD, BECAUSE SHE HAS ADULT
RESPONSIBILITIES NOW.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO SEE THE
BABY?
>> MOST DAYS I DON'T EVEN GET
TO SEE HER.
>> THAT'S HORRIBLE.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO JAZMIN JUST DON'T BE
SAYING NOTHING?
LIKE, WHAT DOES SHE HAVE TO SAY?
>> SHE TELLS ME SHE WANTS THE
SAME THING, BUT SHE'S NOT SAYING
NOTHING TO HER MAMA ABOUT HOW
SHE FEELS ABOUT THE RULES.
>> 'CAUSE SHE'S SCARED.
>> MM-HMM.
>> ARE YOU UPSET ABOUT IT?
>> YEAH, I'M UPSET.
LIKE, SHE WANTS ME TO BE THERE,
BUT SHE'S NOT HELPING THE
SITUATION.
SHE'S NOT SAYING NOTHING TO HER
MAMA.
>> SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE IN THE
CONFRONTATION, SO SHE'S, LIKE,
SAYING YES TO YOU, BUT AT THE
SAME TIME SAYING YES TO HER MOM
SO THERE ISN'T AN ARGUMENT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK
FOREVER.
LIKE, ARE YOU STRESSED OUT WITH
THE SITUATION?
BECAUSE I'M STRESSED WITH THE
CONVERSATION.
>> YES.
I GUESS I JUST FEEL LIKE I CAN'T
SEE MY DAUGHTER.
>> I FEEL LIKE, JUST GIVE HER
THE TIME.
LIKE, EVENTUALLY, IT'LL ALL PLAY
OUT RIGHT.
>> I HOPE SO.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HI!
HOW'S LAILA?
>> ASLEEP.
>> WHAT YOU BEEN UP TO?
>> NOTHING MUCH.
I'M WITH HER 24/7.
EVERYTHING'S JUST EVERYWHERE.
IT'S A MESS.
>> SO HOW ARE YOU AND DELL?
>> MIXING THE HOUSEHOLD RULES
AND OUR DIFFERENT SCHEDULES AND
GETTING HIM TIME TO SPEND WITH
LAILA, IT'S BEEN HARD.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT YOU REALLY
NEED THOSE RULES?
>> WE ALREADY TALKED ABOUT THE
WHOLE RULE-CHANGING THING.
MY MOM SAID SHE'S GONNA THINK
ABOUT IT, BUT THEN SHE THOUGHT
ABOUT IT AND SAID NO.
>> HOW DOES THAT MAKE YOU FEEL
THAT HE CAN'T COME OVER?
LIKE, DOES IT SUCK?
>> I MEAN, IT SUCKS.
I WANT HIM TO SPEND TIME WITH
HER, YOU KNOW, LIKE, HAVING
LITTLE--
>> DADDY/DAUGHTER TIME.
BUT HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT,
LIKE, HIM COMING OVER ANYWAY?
>> NO.
>> NO?
IT'S KIND OF LIKE THE THOUGHT
THING.
LIKE, IN THE BACK OF MY MIND,
IT'S KIND OF LIKE, "DANG, I'M
SITTING HERE, JUST MESSING UP
THE TRUST THAT WE TRYING TO
BUILD BACK," YOU KNOW?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> RESPECTING THE RULES OF THE
HOUSE AND HAVING A DAUGHTER,
YOU DO REALIZE THAT THOSE THINGS
JUST AREN'T COMPATIBLE, RIGHT?
>> DELL GOT OFF WORK BEFORE
10:00 TONIGHT, SO HE'S COMING BY
FOR A QUICK VISIT BEFORE MY MOM
GOES TO BED.
SHE LOOKING AT ME LIKE,
"WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHY IS HE HOLDING ME?"
>> COME HERE.
SO NOW THAT THE RULES OF THE
HOUSE AIN'T GONNA CHANGE,
I SHOULD BE ABLE TO HAVE LAILA
OVER AND SPEND THE NIGHT WITH
ME SOME POINT SOON.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, I'M GONNA WANT
TO SPEND MORE TIME WITH LAILA.
>> I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING ABOUT WANTING TO SPEND
TIME WITH HER,
BUT I NEED TO FEEL COMFORTABLE
WITH YOU AS A CARETAKER,
YOU AS A PARENT.
I DON'T WANT TO JUST, "OKAY,
YEAH, HERE, YOU CAN HAVE MY
BABY.
I'VE HAD HER HER WHOLE LIFE,
BUT HERE, YOU CAN JUST HAVE
HER."
LIKE, NO.
>> BUT STILL, I'M HER DADDY.
I'M THE PROTECTOR TOO.
>> ALL RIGHT, TIME TO GO.
TIME TO GO BYE-BYE.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
>> I DON'T LIKE SAYING NO TO
DELL, BUT I'M JUST NOT READY TO
LET LAILA BE AWAY FROM ME
OVERNIGHT.
[Laila fussing]
YEAH, LITTLE GIRL.
I'M TRYING TO PREPARE FOR
COLLEGE AND CAREER STUFF.
[Laila crying]
I'M GLAD YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO A
RESUME 'CAUSE ALL YOU DO IS POOP
AND CRY AND SLEEP.
WANT TO CALL YOUR DADDY?
LET'S CALL HIM, OKAY?
[line rings]
>> HELLO?
>> HI, DELL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GONNA BE A WHILE.
>> 'CAUSE IT'S COLD--
IT'S COLD OUTSIDE.
I DON'T FEEL THAT COMFORTABLE
WITH HER GOING ANYWHERE, WHICH
IS WHY SHE'S NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO COME WITH YOU UNTIL I'M
COMFORTABLE.
OKAY.
YOU CAN, OVER HERE.
>> GET MAD.
IT'S NOT GONNA CHANGE NOTHING.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
I FEEL BAD ABOUT HOW MY LAST
CONVERSATION WENT WITH DELL,
BUT WORKING AROUND THE HOUSE
RULES HAS BEEN REALLY TOUGH,
SO I'M HOPING HE'S WILLING TO
MEET UP WITH ME TODAY.
[line rings]
>> HELLO?
>> DO YOU WANT TO GET TOGETHER
SOMEWHERE AND TALK?
>> YOU WERE SWEATING IN THERE.
>> ANGRY BEAVER.
>> I CAME HERE 'CAUSE I WANTED
TO TALK ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP
AND WHERE WE AT.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE CAN TALK ABOUT
IT.
>> I FEEL LIKE, IF WE DIDN'T
HAVE LAILA, OUR RELATIONSHIP
WOULD BE REALLY GOOD.
>> I CATCH MYSELF THINKING ABOUT
THAT A LOT.
MY BIGGEST THING IS NOT BEING
ABLE TO COME HOME TO Y'ALL AND
WAKING UP TO Y'ALL IN THE
MORNING.
SEEING THAT PRETTY FACE AND
SEEING THIS PRETTY FACE.
LIKE, I THOUGHT I HAD IT DOWN.
I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA BE ABLE TO
DO THIS AND DO THAT,
LIKE, BEING ABLE TO TAKE CARE
FOR Y'ALL, BEING ABLE TO HAVE
OUR OWN PLACE.
>> COME HERE, LITTLE MAMA.
>> I WANT US TO BE HAPPY.
I WANT OUR FAMILY TO BE
TOGETHER, BUT I'M NOT GETTING TO
WHERE I NEED TO BE, BUT THAT'S
BECAUSE OF THE HOUSE RULES
YET AGAIN.
>> I THINK THE SAME THING.
IT WENT FROM ROMANTIC TO
BUSINESS, LIKE, REALLY FAST.
I DON'T THINK WE'D EVEN BE HERE
IN THIS POSITION THAT WE IN NOW
IF LAILA WASN'T AROUND.
...BIG RESPONSIBILITY.
NOT THAT I REGRET HAVING HER.
IT'S JUST, I WOULD'VE--
I THINK WE SHOULD'VE WAITED.
>> WE SHOULD'VE THOUGHT DEEPER
INTO OUR ACTIONS FOR HER,
NOT JUST FOR US.
SO NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS
DOWN THE LINE, THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING TO ME IS LAILA.
ME AND DELL THOUGHT THAT WE
COULD CO-PARENT TOGETHER AND WE
COULD FIGURE IT OUT ON OUR OWN
AND BE HAPPY, BUT IT DIDN'T
HAPPEN THAT WAY.
[Laila fussing]
THE HOUSE RULES ARE DIFFICULT
BECAUSE I WANTED TO GAIN MY
TRUST BACK, BUT ON THE OTHER
HAND, I WANTED DELL TO HAVE TIME
WITH HIS DAUGHTER AS MUCH AS
POSSIBLE.
>> DOES DELL HAVE TO WORK TODAY?
>> NO.
>> DID HE SAY HE WAS COMING OVER
LATER OR HE WANTED TO COME OVER?
>> HE WANTS TO, YEAH.
IT WAS JUST HARD TRYING TO
BALANCE THE APPROPRIATE AMOUNT
OF TIME THAT HE NEEDED WHILE
ALSO RESPECTING THE HOUSE RULES
AND GETTING THE TRUST BACK FROM
MY MOM.
[Laila crying]
LAILA, SERIOUSLY?
STOP SCRATCHING YOURSELF.
I'M DETERMINED TO GET DONE WITH
SCHOOL, BUT IT'S KIND OF HARD
BECAUSE I SET ASIDE TIME TO DO
MY SCHOOLWORK, BUT THEN IT GETS
SEEN AS BABY TIME.
I CAN'T DO IT WITH YOU SQUIRMING
AND CRYING 'CAUSE YOU'RE
DISTRACTING.
BEFORE I HAD A BABY, I TREATED
SEX A LOT MORE LIGHTLY THAN I
SHOULD'VE.
IT'S HARD WITH ONE HAND.
SHE WANT TO BE HELD ALL THE
TIME.
AND I MADE A MESS.
I MADE A BIG OLD MESS.
IF I COULD CHANGE ANYTHING, I
WOULD JUST HAVE LAILA LATER IN
LIFE ONCE I GOT MY DEGREE AND
FINISHED SCHOOL AND GOT SETTLED
INTO A CAREER AND A HOUSE AND
EVERYTHING AND JUST HAVE A
STABLE HOME FOR HER TO COME HOME
TO.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THINGS WITH ME
AND DELL ARE GONNA WORK OUT.
I'M HOPING FOR THE BEST BUT
PREPARING FOR THE WORST.
AND SO I GUESS WE'LL JUST SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
[chime dings]
>> WE ARE BASICALLY HOMELESS.
I HATE LIVING OUT OF THIS CAR.
>> IT'S TOUGH [bleep]!
THERE ISN'T NO WHERE TO GO!
>> WOULD WE BE ABLE TO STAY
HERE?
>> THERE'S NO ROOM.
[baby crying]
>> HER ONLY OPTION RIGHT NOW
IS A HOMELESS SHELTER.
>> YOUR BABY DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING.