>> [laughs]
[chime dings]
HI, I'M KRISTINA.
I'M 16 AND FROM DE BERRY, TEXAS,
WHICH IS A SMALL TOWN RIGHT ON
THE BORDER OF LOUISIANA.
I LIVE WITH MY MOM, SISTER,
BROTHER, AND GRANDMOTHER.
>> KRISTINA.
>> YEAH.
>> HI.
>> OH!
>> [laughs]
>> AND THAT'S MY AUNT DOTTY.
I NEED DOTTY BEFORE
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
>> [laughs]
ALWAYS.
>> SINCE MY MOM AND I
DON'T GET ALONG THAT WELL,
I SPEND A LOT OF TIME
AT DOTTY'S HOUSE
WITH HER HUSBAND, DANIEL,
AND THEIR THREE KIDS.
THIS IS WHERE I MET
MY BOYFRIEND TODD.
HE'S DANIEL'S LITTLE BROTHER.
>> THEN SHE GETS HIM.
>> A YEAR AGO, TODD AND I
STARTED DATING, AND THEN...
[chime dings]
THINGS MOVED PRETTY FAST.
WHEN I WAS PICKING OUT
A PROM DRESS,
TODD PICKED OUT A RING.
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE REALLY YOUNG,
I SAID YES BECAUSE I KNOW
HE'S MY SOUL MATE.
BUT THEN EVERYTHING CHANGED.
THIS SUMMER, TODD AND I
WERE SWIMMING AT GALVESTON BEACH
WHEN A RIPTIDE PULLED US UNDER,
AND WE STARTED TO DROWN.
I BLACKED OUT
BUT WAS SAVED BY A LIFEGUARD.
AS SOON AS I WOKE UP
ON THE SAND,
I REALIZED I WAS OKAY,
BUT TODD WAS MISSING.
>> WE'RE WITH PETER DAVIS,
GALVESTON ISLAND BEACH
PATROL CHIEF, AND, PETER,
YOU WERE CALLED TO EAST BEACH
ABOUT NOON, IS THAT RIGHT?
>> YEAH, IT WAS RIGHT ABOUT
12:00.
ONE OF OUR BEACH CLEANING GUYS
WITH THE PARK BOARD
SAW A BODY ALONG THE SHORELINE.
AND, YOU KNOW, LOOKING AT IT,
LOOKS LIKE IT MATCHES
THE DESCRIPTION OF THE PERSON
THAT WE'RE MISSING.
>> I'VE NEVER FELT SO WEAK
AND ALONE IN MY LIFE,
BUT SOMEHOW, I'LL HAVE TO FIND
THE STRENGTH TO GO ON...
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
[solemn acoustic music]
♪
THE DROWNING HAPPENED WHEN TODD
WAS WITH ME AND MY FAMILY
ON VACATION A FEW MONTHS AGO.
I'M SIX MONTHS PREGNANT NOW
AND CHOSE TO MOVE IN WITH DOTTY
AND TODD'S BROTHER DANIEL
AFTER THE FUNERAL.
I FEEL THEY UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M GOING THROUGH
MORE THAN MY MOM DOES SINCE THEY
WERE REALLY CLOSE TO TODD.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHY IT HAD TO BE
THE WAY IT HAD TO BE,
BUT WE'LL--
WE'LL GET THROUGH IT.
>> HOPEFULLY.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I GOT USED
TO TODD BEING THERE,
LIKE, EVERY HOUR, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> ALWAYS.
AND I KNOW THAT'S TOUGH,
BUT WHAT YOU REALLY NEED
TO FOCUS ON RIGHT NOW,
I GUESS, IS THE PREGNANT LIFE
HAS REALLY STARTED NOW.
>> YEAH, I CAN'T WAIT.
>> I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT LIVING
FOR YOURSELF ANYMORE.
YOU'RE LIVING FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED.
>> TODD DEFINITELY WANTED A BOY.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
AND HE'D BE SO PROUD. HE WOULD.
>> ARE YOU GONNA HOLD HIM,
DANIEL?
>> AW, YEAH, YOU BET
I'M GONNA HOLD HIM.
>> I CAN'T DEPEND ON ANYBODY
BUT Y'ALL.
I DON'T PLAN ON GOING BACK
TO MY MOM'S.
>> YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE WELCOME TO BE HERE,
BUT YOU DO NEED TO INCLUDE HER.
>> SHE FEELS LEFT OUT.
>> YOU KNOW, SHE'S YOUR MOTHER.
SHE--YOU ONLY GET ONE OF THEM.
>> MY MOM WAS ON THE BEACH
THE DAY IT ALL HAPPENED
AND ISN'T HANDLING IT VERY WELL,
SO IT'S BEEN HARD SPENDING TIME
WITH HER WHEN I'M TRYING
TO KEEP IT TOGETHER MYSELF.
I WISH WE'D STAYED HOME
THAT WEEKEND.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU READY?
WITH THE BABY COMING,
THINGS'LL CHANGE.
>> I STILL HAVEN'T, LIKE,
REALLY ACCEPTED IT.
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW,
EVEN THOUGH I THREW A FIT
AT FIRST, I'M GONNA BE THERE.
>> YEAH.
WE DON'T TALK ABOUT IT A LOT.
LIKE, THE DEATH AND STUFF,
BUT IT HELPS.
>> BUT I DO MISS YOU,
AND I WAS HOPING THAT,
MAYBE SOONER OR LATER,
YOU WOULD CHANGE YOUR MIND
AND WANT TO COME HOME.
>> I DON'T PLAN
ON MOVING BACK IN.
I KNOW MY MOM WANTS TO BE THERE
FOR ME, BUT WE'RE DEALING
WITH THINGS DIFFERENTLY,
SO I FEEL STAYING AT DOTTY
AND DANIEL'S IS WHAT'S BEST
FOR ME AND THE BABY RIGHT NOW.
MY BEST FRIEND, TRESSIE,
IS ONE OF THE ONLY PEOPLE
WHO REALLY GETS
HOW I WANT TO REMEMBER TODD.
IT'S, LIKE, HARD TO FIGURE OUT
HOW TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> I THINK OF ALL THE HAPPY
TIMES, LIKE, WHEN WE FIRST
STARTED DATING,
HOW WE WERE ALWAYS LAUGHING,
AND WE'D WRESTLE AROUND
AND JUST LAUGH ALL THE TIME.
I REMEMBER ONE TIME,
ONE OF MY BRAS
WERE LAYING ON THE BED.
I LEFT OUT OF THE ROOM
TO GO TO THE BATHROOM,
AND I CAME BACK, AND THEN
ALL OF A SUDDEN HE POPS
OUT OF THE BED, AND HE HAS
MY BRA OVER HIS SHIRT!
AND I JUST DIED LAUGHING,
'CAUSE IT WAS, LIKE, SOMETHING
I NEVER IMAGINED HIM DOING.
[laughter]
WE LAUGHED OVER
THE DUMBEST THINGS, I SWEAR,
BUT IT WAS, I DON'T KNOW--
IT MADE SENSE
'CAUSE IT WAS WITH HIM.
I MISS THAT.
I MISS HEARING HIS LAUGH
AND, LIKE, LAUGHING WITH HIM,
YOU KNOW?
MY SENIOR YEAR
IS SUPPOSED TO START NEXT MONTH,
BUT WITH EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED, I'M NOT SURE
ABOUT GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> ARE YOU GONNA GO BACK
TO CHEERLEADING?
>> LIKE, I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE--
LIKE, TRYOUT FOR CHEERLEADER
FOR MY SENIOR YEAR, YOU KNOW.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I'M NOT REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT CHEERING.
>> DO YOU LIKE LIVING HERE
BETTER?
>> YEAH, IT WAS, LIKE,
VERY TENSE AT MY MOM'S.
MY MOM IS JUST, LIKE,
UP UNDER ME.
LIKE, "I WANT TO HELP YOU!"
BUT THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN SAY
TO, LIKE, MAKE IT BETTER.
SO I WOULD, LIKE,
LOCK MYSELF IN THE BATHROOM,
AND, LIKE, SHE WOULD
BEAT ON THE DOOR OR SOMETHING.
>> I THINK IT'S GOOD
THAT YOU'RE HERE.
HOW'S TODD'S MOM
DEALING WITH EVERYTHING?
>> DOES IT MAKE YOU SAD
WHEN SHE COMES OVER
AND TALKS ABOUT IT WITH YOU?
>> IT MAKES ME MISS HIM MORE.
>> WELL, IF YOU HOLD IT IN
A LONG TIME, WHEN YOU BREAK,
IT'S GONNA BE EVEN WORSE.
>> YEAH.
TODD'S MOM HAS BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT HOW I'M DOING WITH
THE PREGNANCY AFTER LOSING TODD,
AND SINCE I'M DUE
IN JUST THREE MONTHS, SHE WANTED
TO COME OVER AND TALK TODAY.
>> COME ON IN, MOM.
>> HEY, SON.
KRISTINA...
I LOVE YOU.
YOU OKAY, BABY?
>> YEAH, I'M FINE.
>> I KNOW THAT EVERYBODY HANDLES
EVERYTHING IN THEIR OWN WAY.
THOUGH HE WAS MY SON, I FEEL
LIKE A PART OF YOU HAS TO HURT
ALMOST AS SEVERELY AS I DO.
I'M SCARED, IF YOU DON'T
RELEASE SOME OF THAT STRESS,
THAT IT'S GONNA CAUSE YOU
TO HAVE PROBLEMS
DURING THIS PREGNANCY.
GRANTED, I DON'T WANT YOU
FALLING APART LIKE I AM, OKAY?
>> BUT I CAN'T TALK ABOUT
THE DAY 'CAUSE, I MEAN--
>> IT'S PAINFUL.
>> IT TAKES--I MEAN,
I KNOW IT'S PAINFUL FOR Y'ALL,
BUT BEING IN THE WATER TOO,
TALKING ABOUT IT JUST
TAKES IT BACK.
AT FIRST, YOU HAVE
THE NIGHTMARES, AND THEN
YOU HAVE THE "WHY DIDN'T--
WHY DIDN'T I DIE, TOO,
WITH HIM?"
I MEAN, WHAT'S THE POINT
FOR GOD LETTING YOU
FIND SOMEBODY TO BE WITH
AND GET ATTACHED TO
AND THEN JUST TAKE HIM
BUT SAVE YOU?
[sniffles]
I JUST DON'T LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> I NEED TO GET SOME AIR.
I'M SORRY.
>> ALL RIGHT, MOM, THAT'S FINE.
>> EVEN THOUGH TODD'S MOM
AND MY MOM THINK TALKING
ABOUT HIS DEATH WILL HELP ME,
REMEMBERING THAT DAY
IS TOO PAINFUL,
AND WHAT I REALLY HAVE
TO BE FOCUSED ON IS THE BABY.
WHEN I FIRST FOUND OUT
I WAS PREGNANT, TODD SAID
HE LIKED THE NAME LUKAS,
SO THAT'S WHAT I'VE DECIDED ON.
I THINK LUKAS IS GONNA LIKE IT.
>> I'M READY TO SEE HOW MUCH
HE LOOKS LIKE LITTLE TODD.
>> SO WHAT ALL DO WE HAVE LEFT
TO DO FOR OUR BABY SHOWER?
ORDER THE FOOD.
DECORATIONS NEXT FRIDAY.
>> I GOT TO GET--
YEAH, I GOT TO GET
THE DECORATIONS.
YOU GOT TO GET THE CRIB
AND STUFF SO WE CAN GO AHEAD
AND SET THAT UP.
>> THE ONLY THING
I'M NERVOUS ABOUT
IS PEOPLE NOT COMING.
SUMMER'S OVER NEXT WEEK,
BUT I'VE DECIDED THAT INSTEAD OF
GOING BACK TO HIGH SCHOOL,
IT WOULD BE BEST
TO LOOK INTO GETTING MY G.E.D.
AT THE COMMUNITY COLLEGE.
I HAVE TO BE AT THE COLLEGE
AT 11:00.
>> THAT'S REALLY GREAT THAT
YOU AND YOUR MOM ARE ACTUALLY
GOING AND DOING THINGS TOGETHER.
[horn honks]
>> ALL RIGHT, LOVE YOU.
>> LOVE YOU TOO.
>> HAVE YOU GRADUATED
HIGH SCHOOL YET?
>> NO, UM...
>> OKAY, 'CAUSE WE DO
OFFER A PROGRAM
FOR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS
WHERE THEY CAN FINISH
HIGH SCHOOL HERE.
SO WHAT KIND OF EXTRACURRICULAR
ACTIVITIES ARE YOU
WANTING TO BE INVOLVED IN?
>> I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT ANY.
I JUST THOUGHT ABOUT JUST GOING
TO SCHOOL AND GET IT OVER WITH.
>> IN SCHOOL, SHE USED TO
PLAY VOLLEYBALL,
STUFF LIKE THAT,
AND SHE WAS GOOD.
>> OKAY. YEAH.
>> IN HIGH SCHOOL,
SHE DID EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW, STRAIGHT "A" STUDENT,
SO THE PREGNANCY
WAS REALLY A SHOCKER.
>> YEAH.
SO WHAT IS YOUR SON'S NAME?
>> LUKAS.
HERE, I CAN SHOW YOU
A PICTURE OF HIM.
THAT'S MY FAVORITE SONOGRAM,
FOR SURE.
>> THAT IS THE BEST.
>> HE'S BLOWING BUBBLES.
[laughter]
>> I SEE THAT. YES.
IS YOUR BOYFRIEND OR ANYTHING
COMING, OR...
>> MM-MM.
HE--HE'S MY FIANCE, ACTUALLY.
>> OKAY.
>> AND HE PASSED AWAY.
>> [sighs]
>> THEY WERE SWIMMING
AT GALVESTON BEACH, AND I JUST--
I REMEMBER SCREAMING HER NAME
AND JUST TAKING OFF
FOR THE WATER.
>> YEAH.
>> LUCKILY, THE LIFEGUARD
WAS ABLE TO GET TO HER,
'CAUSE I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING.
AND I REMEMBER FEELING RELIEF
AND JUST HAPPY,
AND THEN I REALIZED
TODD WASN'T WITH THEM.
>> I'M VERY SORRY
YOU HAD TO GO THROUGH THAT.
>> BABY, I WANT TO
TAKE IT ALL AWAY.
I WANT TO FIX IT, AND I CAN'T.
BUT IF YOU'RE GONNA BLOW
ONE OF THESE DAYS AND--
LIKE I DO, YOU KNOW,
TILL I GET MAD--
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE NOBODY
UNDERSTANDS IT.
>> I WORRY ABOUT YOU.
ALL RIGHT, BABY.
CAN I GET A HUG BEFORE YOU GO?
COME HERE.
LOVE YOU. BE GOOD.
>> BYE.
>> I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
>> I KNOW YOU WILL.
>> GOT YOUR PHONE?
YOU GOT YOUR--
OKAY.
>> ME AND MY MOM HAD PLANS TODAY
TO DECIDE ON A CAKE
FOR MY BABY SHOWER, BUT I TOLD
HER I WAS STAYING HOME INSTEAD.
SHE'S BEEN CALLING ME ALL DAY,
BUT I JUST NEED
SOME TIME AWAY FROM HER.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> FILLING OUT
BABY SHOWER INVITES.
>> SO HOW MANY PEOPLE
YOU GOT SO FAR?
>> LIKE, 137.
>> I'M NOT FEEDING THAT MANY
PEOPLE, SO WE NEED, LIKE, 37.
>> [laughs]
WELL, ONLY 37
WILL PROBABLY COME.
>> YEAH, THAT'S PROBABLY TRUE.
>> I MEAN, TODD TALKED ABOUT IT.
IT WAS JUST, LIKE, HE WAS LIKE--
>> OH, YEAH, HE HAD
HIS SELECT FEW PEOPLE.
>> "I'M NOT GONNA GO.
IT'S A GIRL THING."
>> YEAH.
>> NOW IT'S TURNED INTO, LIKE,
A BIG FAMILY THING.
AND I THINK IT WOULD HAVE
TURNED OUT THAT WAY ANYWAY.
>> YEAH, I BELIEVE
IT WOULD HAVE.
>> BECAUSE HE NEVER LEFT ME,
AND I NEVER LEFT HIS SIDE.
>> YEP.
[phone vibrates]
>> MOM'S CALLING ME.
SHE'S, LIKE, FREAKING OUT.
[phone beeps]
SHE MAKES ME CRAZY.
>> STILL...
[phone rings]
>> HELLO?
>> HEY.
>> I DON'T SEE WHY
YOU FEEL THAT WAY
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN INVOLVED.
YOU'RE MAKING THE CAKE
AND EVERYTHING.
>> WHY DO YOU BRING THAT UP
EVERY TIME?
KRISTINA--
>> IT KILLS YOU?
IT KILLS YOU.
HOW DO YOU THINK I FEEL?
>> NO, YOU DON'T!
DON'T SAY YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO WATCH
WHAT I WATCHED
AND ALMOST DIE TOO.
>> OKAY, I JUST SAID I DIDN'T
WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
>> IT'S NOT ANYBODY'S FAULT!
OBVIOUSLY, THERE WAS NOTHING
NOBODY COULD HAVE DONE.
PERIOD.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED.
>> THE WAY MY MOM HAS BEEN
ACTING IS REALLY STRESSING
ME OUT, AND LAST NIGHT,
I COULDN'T GET ANY SLEEP.
I KEPT HAVING PAINS
IN MY STOMACH, AND WITH MY
DUE DATE JUST TWO MONTHS AWAY,
IT'S KIND OF SCARING ME.
DOTTY?
>> YEAH.
>> MY STOMACH'S CRAMPING.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
IT'S CRAMPING?
>> IT'S TIGHTENING UP IN
THE MIDDLE, AND I HAVE PRESSURE.
>> HOW LONG HAS IT
BEEN HAPPENING?
>> SINCE LAST NIGHT.
>> I THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD
TAKE YOU TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> THIS IS TOO EARLY
TO BE HAPPENING.
WHEN WE GOT TO THE HOSPITAL,
THEY CONFIRMED
I'M HAVING CONTRACTIONS,
AND I'M GOING INTO EARLY LABOR,
BUT SINCE I'M ONLY
SEVEN MONTHS PREGNANT,
THE DOCTOR'S DOING A SONOGRAM
TO SEE WHAT'S WRONG.
>> HOW WE DOING?
>> WHEN THE BABY MOVES,
IT HURTS ALL OVER.
>> OKAY, LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT.
THAT'S THE BABY,
AND THAT'S THE CORD.
THERE'S NOT ANY FLUID
IN THERE TO MEASURE.
SO YOU HAVE A GROWTH-RESTRICTED
BABY WITH LOW FLUID.
>> BUT YOU THINK HE'LL BE OKAY?
>> DON'T KNOW, BUT THAT
ENVIRONMENT IN THERE SAYS,
"I'M NOT CONDUCIVE FOR GROWTH,
AND I'M NOT CONDUCIVE
FOR GOOD THINGS HAPPENING."
>> I'M BEING ADMITTED
INTO THE HOSPITAL RIGHT AWAY
BECAUSE HAVING THE BABY
THIS SOON IS REALLY DANGEROUS,
SO EVERYONE MADE THE HOUR-LONG
DRIVE TO BE BY MY SIDE.
I'M TRYING TO STAY CALM,
BUT THE BABY WEIGHS
LESS THAN 3 POUNDS.
I JUST FEEL LIKE I'M, LIKE...
>> IF YOU WANT, GO AHEAD
AND GO GET A ROOM.
THAT WAY YOU GET THE KIDS
TO SLEEP.
I MEAN, IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
I'LL CALL.
JUST KEEP THE PHONE BESIDE YOU.
>> I'LL BE HERE IN THE MORNING.
>> LOVE YOU, KRISTINA.
>> I LOVE ALL Y'ALL.
>> IT'S BEEN OVER 14 HOURS,
AND MY CONTRACTIONS
ARE GETTING WORSE.
THE HOSPITAL'S DOING EVERYTHING
THEY CAN TO STOP MY LABOR,
BUT I'M REALLY SCARED
THAT MIGHT NOT BE ENOUGH.
>> I'M RIGHT HERE, BABY.
>> OKAY, HOLD ON.
HEY, WHERE Y'ALL AT?
SHE WAS ASKING FOR DOTTY.
ALL RIGHT, BYE.
SHE'LL BE HERE IN A MINUTE,
BABY.
>> EVERYONE WENT HOME TO REST,
BUT I ASKED DOTTY
TO STAY WITH ME.
THEY FINALLY GOT MY CONTRACTIONS
UNDER CONTROL WITH MEDICATION,
BUT TO MAKE SURE
I DON'T GIVE BIRTH TOO EARLY,
I HAVE TO STAY IN THE HOSPITAL
UNTIL MY DUE DATE,
WHICH IS OVER TWO MONTHS AWAY.
I NEED TO CALL TINA.
>> HELLO.
>> HEY.
>> HOW'S MY GIRL DOING?
>> UM, SHE'S DOING ALL RIGHT.
>> YES.
THEY JUST WANT HIM TO GET
A LITTLE BIT BIGGER 'CAUSE
HE ONLY WEIGHS 2 POUNDS,
11 OUNCES, SO...
>> MM.
>> YEAH.
>> I LOVE Y'ALL.
>> WE LOVE YOU TOO.
OKAY.
IT'S THE LAST THING
Y'ALL GOT LEFT OF HIM.
>> SINCE MY HOSPITAL IS
SO FAR AWAY, MY FAMILY HAS BEEN
TAKING TURNS STAYING WITH ME.
[knocking on door]
>> WE'RE HERE.
>> HEY, SWEETIE.
DO YOU NEED ANYTHING?
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> WELL, WHAT DID THEY TELL YOU?
>> HE COULD BE IN THERE
FOR A MONTH AND A HALF.
IT JUST MATTERS HOW LONG
IT TAKES HIM TO GAIN WEIGHT.
I'M READY FOR HIM TO BE HERE.
>> WHAT WE'LL DO TOMORROW--
I'LL HAVE TO GO HOME AND GET
SOME CLOTHES, BUT I'LL COME BACK
AND STAY THE NIGHT, OKAY?
AND I'LL COME BACK
AND STAY WITH YOU.
>> THAT'S TOO DIFFICULT.
>> NO, IT'S NOT TOO DIFFICULT,
BABY.
>> YES, IT IS.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
I HAVEN'T GOT TO STAY WITH YOU--
>> YES, IT IS!
>> AT ALL. IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> WELL, TALK TO ME, BABY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS!
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT YOU ALONE,
SO I'M GONNA COME BACK.
>> NO.
>> YES, I DO.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY,
KIM.
SHE JUST DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> KRISTINA,
YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN.
>> [sobbing]
>> WELL, TALK TO US, BABY.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE HERE FOR.
WE'RE HERE TO LISTEN.
JUST TELL US.
TALK, SCREAM, YELL--
>> WELL, TALK TO US ABOUT IT.
>> I KNOW.
AND I'M SO SORRY
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, BABY,
IF I COULD FIX IT, I COULD.
>> I KNOW.
EVERYBODY WOULD.
IT'S NOT FAIR.
>> TODAY WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
MY BABY SHOWER,
BUT WE HAD TO CANCEL IT
BECAUSE I'M IN THE HOSPITAL,
SO MY FRIENDS TEXTED ME
AND SAID THEY WERE ON THEIR WAY
TO CHEER ME UP.
>> HEY, KRISTINA.
>> SO WHAT ARE Y'ALL DOING HERE?
>> WHY?
YOU'RE NOT A GOOD LIAR,
SO JUST TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
THEY WOULDN'T LET YOU
OUT OF HERE TO GO
TO YOUR OWN BABY SHOWER?
>> NO, I'M, LIKE, ON LOCKDOWN.
I'VE BEEN IN HERE
FOR ALMOST A MONTH.
>> IF I WAS IN THE HOSPITAL
FOR A MONTH, I'D BE BOUNCING
OFF THESE WALLS.
I COULD NOT STAY IN HERE
FOR A MONTH.
>> YOU'RE GONNA NEED ME
TO PUT THAT ON?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SO WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON?
>> YOU LOOK REALLY CUTE.
>> DO THE NURSES KNOW
YOU'RE TAKING ME?
WHERE ARE YOU TAKING ME?
>> YOU'LL SEE.
>> all: SURPRISE!
[laughter]
>> THIS IS MY PIECE.
>> SO YOU GET THE WHOLE CAKE NOW
INSTEAD OF JUST A PIECE LIKE--
>> OH!
>> I COULDN'T HELP IT.
>> DANIEL.
>> HA.
[all talking at once]
>> WHAT'S THIS?
"MY MOM IS EXHAUSTED."
>> [laughs]
>> ARE YOU MAD?
>> MM-MM.
I'M GLAD.
I WAS BUMMED.
[laughter]
IT WAS NICE TO SEE EVERYONE,
AND IT'S STILL HARD
LIVING AT THE HOSPITAL.
I'VE BEEN HERE FOR ALMOST
A MONTH NOW, AND EVEN THOUGH
I'M NOT DUE FOR ANOTHER
SIX WEEKS, MY DOCTOR CHECKED
ON LUKAS' GROWTH AND DECIDED
HE'S DEVELOPED ENOUGH
TO TAKE ME OFF THE MEDICINE
THAT HAS BEEN STOPPING MY LABOR.
>> WE'VE TRIED EVERYTHING.
WE'VE GIVEN HER FLUIDS
THROUGH HER I.V.
WE'VE DONE EVERYTHING WE CAN.
JUST LAYING HERE
WON'T MAKE THINGS PROGRESS.
>> YEAH.
>> SO I THINK WE'RE GONNA GO
DO A C-SECTION, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> IS ANYBODY GOING BACK THERE
WITH YOU?
>> NOPE.
>> OKAY.
WE'LL GET THINGS READY,
AND WE'LL GO HAVE A BABY, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> DID YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS,
MAMA?
>> NO.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU JUST NERVOUS FOR HER?
>> IT'S KIND OF SCARY,
BUT I'M KIND OF RELIEVED.
>> WHERE'S MY PHONE
SO I CAN CALL DANIEL?
>> THEY'RE ABOUT TO START
PREPPING ME FOR C-SECTION.
>> I KNOW THEY. THEY TOLD ME.
I TALKED TO THE DOCTOR OUTSIDE.
>> I WAS HOPING THEY WOULDN'T
HAVE TO DO THIS.
>> THEY SAID HE'LL BE HERE
BY 10:00, 10:15.
>> [sniffles]
SHE WON'T LET ME GO IN THERE.
>> I WOULD IMAGINE.
>> I'M NOT HAVING ANYBODY
BACK THERE.
[winces]
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, I'M CONTRACTING.
>> KIM, SHE SAID
THAT SHE WANTS YOU
TO GO IN THERE WITH HER,
BUT JUST DON'T HOVER OVER HER.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME CRY.
AND I DON'T WANT TO.
>> AND DON'T FREAK OUT.
OR ANYTHING.
>> YEAH, JUST TRY TO STAY CALM,
OKAY?
>> ARE YOU GUYS GONNA
BE IN HERE?
THAT'S REALLY WHAT--
>> SHE'S GONNA BE
IN THERE WITH ME.
MY MOM IS.
>> YOU'RE GONNA GO BACK THERE
WITH HER?
WE'LL GET YOU SOME SCRUBS.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL SEE YOU
IN JUST A BIT.
>> LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
SEE YOU SOON.
>> I LOVE YOU. GOOD LUCK.
>> I'LL SEE Y'ALL
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
HOPEFULLY.
>> ♪ STARS SHOT
♪ THROUGH THE SKY
♪ RIGHT THROUGH YOUR BLOOD
[gentle instrumental music]
♪
>> SHE'S COMING. SHE'S COMING.
[baby cooing]
[laughter]
[all talking at once]
>> HE'S SO LITTLE.
>> HAS HE GOT ANY HAIR?
>> NO.
>> OH, WE GOT TO TAKE HIM
TO THE--OKAY.
>> ♪ EVERY NOW AND THEN
♪ IT HITS ME ONCE AGAIN
♪ SEEMS AS THOUGH
♪ ITS NEVER GONNA END
>> HE IS PROUD.
>> HE LOOKS LIKE BOTH OF Y'ALL.
[chime dings]
>> SINCE LUKAS CAME
SIX WEEKS EARLY,
HE HAD TO BE TAKEN
STRAIGHT TO INTENSIVE CARE
AFTER MY C-SECTION.
>> DO YOU HEAR YOUR MOMMY?
>> HE'S SO CUTE.
LUKAS.
>> LOOK AT ME AND SMILE, BABY,
SO WE CAN PUT THIS ON FACEBOOK.
[camera clicks]
>> HE LOOKS LIKE TODD.
WISH HE COULD BE HERE.
AND HE'S BREATHING OKAY
AND EVERYTHING?
>> HE'S DOING GOOD.
>> I LOVE YOU, LITTLE MAN.
>> READY TO TAKE
YOUR STAPLES OUT.
>> AFTER OVER A MONTH
IN THE HOSPITAL,
I FINALLY GET TO GO HOME.
>> YOU DID VERY GOOD.
>> BUT BECAUSE LUKAS WAS BORN
SO EARLY, HE HAS TO STAY
IN INTENSIVE CARE
UNTIL HE DEVELOPS A BIT MORE.
>> YOU OKAY?
OH, MAN, HE IS JUST SO TINY.
>> I WONDER HOW MUCH
HE WEIGHS NOW.
>> JUST A HAIR OVER 3 POUNDS.
>> ABOUT HOW LONG
AFTER HE GETS OUT OF THAT
WILL HE GET TO GO HOME?
>> IT'S STILL
A COUPLE WEEKS AWAY.
>> [squeaks]
>> GIVE HIM KISSES,
AND WE'LL PUT HIM BACK.
[solemn orchestral music]
♪
>> HE'S IN GOOD HANDS.
>> [sniffles]
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE HOME.
ARE YOU EXCITED?
>> HEY.
WATCH OUT. WATCH--
>> HER BELLY'S CUT OPEN, BABY.
>> WHAT? CAN WE SEE?
>> LET HER GET IN.
>> WANT TO GO SEE YOUR ROOM?
>> YEAH, I WANT TO LAY IN IT.
>> DO YOU LIKE YOUR ROOM?
>> IT LOOKS GOOD.
>> ARE YOU HAPPY SHE'S HOME?
>> all: YES!
>> I AM MOSTLY.
>> CAN WE SEE YOUR BELLY NOW?
>> YEAH, WE WANT TO SEE
YOUR BELLY!
>> OKAY, LET ME LIE DOWN.
>> DON'T TOUCH HER BELLY,
THOUGH, OKAY?
>> IT AIN'T CUT OPEN.
OH, IT IS!
>> THEY HAD TO DIG AROUND
AND FIND HIM.
>> EW!
THEY HAD TO PUT THEIR HAND
IN YOUR BELLY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT'S DISGUSTING!
>> ALL RIGHT, KIDS,
Y'ALL WANT TO PULL ME UP?
[knocking on door]
>> COME IN.
>> HEY, SWEETIE.
>> HEY.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> WELL, HOW'S THE BABY?
I MEAN--
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO LEAVE HIM.
IT'S SCARY.
>> HE WILL BE HOME
BEFORE TOO LONG.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE
IT'S ANY DIFFERENT THAN
WHEN I HAD TO LEAVE GALVESTON
AND LEAVE TODD, AND I THOUGHT
HE WAS GOING TO COME HOME,
AND THEN HE DIDN'T.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO SIT HERE
AND WORK YOURSELF UP.
>> WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
I JUST--YOU DON'T--
YOU DON'T GET IT AT ALL.
>> BABY, I DO GET IT.
>> LEAVE ME ALONE.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> WELL, I LOVE YOU, BABY.
I REALLY DO.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> HONIES, I'M HOME.
>> HEY.
>> NO, I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE
LIKE THIS EITHER.
>> IT'S BEEN HARD BEING HOME
WITHOUT LUKAS,
BUT HE HAS TO STAY
IN THE HOSPITAL
FOR A COUPLE MORE WEEKS,
SO I'VE BEEN MAKING THE LONG
DRIVE TO VISIT HIM EVERY DAY.
DID YOU MISS ME
AS MUCH AS I MISSED YOU?
YOU READY TO COME HOME?
[laughs]
AFTER THREE WEEKS
IN INTENSIVE CARE,
TODAY, I FINALLY GET TO
BRING LUKAS HOME,
AND I COULDN'T BE MORE EXCITED.
[laughter]
YAY, YAY, YAY.
WE'RE HERE.
I'M SO HAPPY
WE GET TO PICK HIM UP.
>> HE'S GETTIN' CHUNKY NOW.
>> LET'S SEE WHAT THE BABY
LOOKS LIKE.
WHERE'S HE AT?
>> WHO'S THAT?
IS THAT LUKAS?
>> NO, THEY STOLE ANOTHER KID.
>> HE'S SO CUTE.
>> LOOK AT HIS LITTLE ARMS!
>> HE LOOKS, LIKE, KIND OF
LIKE UNCLE TODD IN THE FACE.
>> YEP, I'M SURE.
>> HE DOES.
>> I LOVE HIM!
[Lukas cries]
>> YOU'VE GOT KRISTINA'S
ATTITUDE ALREADY,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> YOU'RE SO FUNNY, DANIEL.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY GREAT
TO HAVE HIM HOME.
HOW SCARY EVERYTHING WAS,
AND THEN HE'S PERFECT.
>> I KNOW HE'S OKAY NOW.
NOW I FEEL RELIEVED.
>> YEAH, HE'S GREAT.
>> HEY, ARE YOU READY
TO BATHE THE BABY?
>> YEAH.
[Lukas cries]
>> I KNOW, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT DO I DO,
JUST SIT HIM IN IT?
>> MM-MM. NO.
WHEN YOU WASH HIS HEAD,
YOU WANT TO WASH HIS HEAD
AND DRY IT REALLY FAST
AND THEN WASH THE REST OF HIM.
SO--
>> [gasps]
OH, MY GOSH.
>> IT'S OKAY.
JUST GO AHEAD AND BATHE HIM.
UH-UH, DON'T STICK HIM
IN THE WATER.
HOLD HIM LIKE A FOOTBALL.
>> OH!
>> IT WON'T BURN.
IT'S BABY SOAP.
[Lukas cries]
>> LUKAS.
>> JUST GONNA MAKE SURE
HE'S TOTALLY DRY,
ESPECIALLY HIS HEAD, 'CAUSE
YOU DON'T WANT HIM TO GET SICK.
>> YEAH.
[Lukas cries]
>> YOU EAT SO SLOW.
HEY.
[Lukas cries]
LET'S GO INTO THE BEDROOM.
[phone chiming]
[Lukas cries]
HEY.
I'M EXHAUSTED,
AND EVEN THOUGH MY MOM
AND FRIENDS HAVE ALL OFFERED
TO COME OVER AND HELP,
I'D RATHER JUST BE
BY MYSELF RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE THE PERSON I WANT MOST
ISN'T HERE.
[Lukas cooing]
CAN YOU HOLD LUKAS?
>> YEAH.
YES.
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
>> LIKE, HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> female announcer: DON'T
GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> LUKAS HAS BEEN HOME NOW
FOR OVER A MONTH,
BUT ALL I CAN FOCUS ON IS TODD.
I'M NOT SURE WHAT ELSE TO DO,
SO I'M GOING TO A THERAPIST
TO SEE IF IT HELPS.
>> SCARED OF YOUR EMOTIONS?
>> I THINK THAT I'VE JUST
PUSHED EVERYTHING DOWN,
AND NOW IT'S GONNA ALL COME OUT.
>> IT NEEDS TO, THOUGH.
YOU HAVE YOU AND HIM NOW
TO THINK ABOUT,
NOT JUST YOURSELF.
>> HEY, KRISTINA.
>> HEY.
>> I'M JANA.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> IT'S NICE MEETING YOU.
>> WHAT BRINGS YOU IN TODAY?
>> UM...
MY FIANCE PASSED AWAY.
>> GOD, I'M REALLY SORRY.
HAVE YOU HAD A GOOD SUPPORT
SYSTEM TO TALK ABOUT THIS WITH?
>> YEAH, BUT I DON'T TALK
ABOUT IT.
>> HOW COME?
>> THEY'RE GRIEVING TOO,
SO I DIDN'T WANT TO PUT
HOW I FEEL ON THEM.
>> OKAY, SO IT'S A GOOD TIME
TO PUT IT ON ME.
>> [laughs softly]
YEAH.
>> HOW WERE YOU FEELING
AFTER IT HAPPENED?
>> I JUST WISH
I WOULD HAVE DIED TOO.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
HOW WE SURVIVED AND HE DIDN'T.
>> I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A QUESTION
THAT ANYBODY'S EVER GONNA
BE ABLE TO ANSWER FOR YOU.
WHAT I TRY TO GET PEOPLE
LOOKING AT IS,
WHAT DO YOU WANT NOW?
>> I THINK I JUST WANT TO, LIKE,
NOT FEEL SO NUMB.
>> DO YOU HAVE DIFFICULTY
SOMETIMES CONNECTING
WITH THE BABY?
>> I LOVE HIM
MORE THAN ANYTHING,
BUT I JUST CAN'T HANDLE IT
SOMETIMES.
I CAN'T HANDLE KNOWING
IT COULD BE DIFFERENT
IF HE WAS HERE,
THAT I COULD BE HAPPY.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GONNA TELL HIM
ABOUT HIS DAD?
>> HE CARED A LOT.
LIKE, IF I WAS UPSET,
HE WOULD JUST BE THERE,
EVEN IF I DIDN'T WANT HIM THERE
'CAUSE I WAS UPSET AT HIM.
HE WOULD STILL HOLD ME
AND JUST...
HE WOULD BE THERE.
>> I SAW A SMILE, SO AT LEAST
YOU WERE FEELING SOMETHING.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT WASN'T JUST NUMB.
>> IT MAKES ME REMEMBER.
>> REMEMBERING'S NOT ALL BAD.
GRIEF IS NOT A PROCESS
THAT HAS A TIME LIMIT ON IT.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE
LOOKING WEAK.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE WEAK?
AFTER EVERYTHING
YOU'VE GONE THROUGH?
YOU GONNA TEACH LUKAS THAT
CRYING AND EMOTIONS ARE WEAK?
>> MM-MM.
>> NO, NO, NO.
WE NEED TO GET YOU UP TO A LEVEL
WHERE WE CAN START DEALING
WITH THE GRIEF AND THE FEELINGS,
WHERE YOU DO MAKE GOOD DECISIONS
FOR BOTH YOU AND LUKAS.
SO YOU WANT TO COME BACK
AND SEE ME?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, EXCELLENT.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME IN.
>> TOOK A LITTLE WHILE
TO GET ME IN HERE.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S STILL HARD
FOR ME TO ACCEPT
THAT TODD IS GONE,
I THINK ALLOWING MYSELF
TO REMEMBER HIM
IS THE FIRST STEP,
SO I THOUGHT GETTING
OUT OF THE HOUSE
TO MEET UP WITH TODD'S MOM
WOULD BE A GOOD PLACE TO START.
>> HEY, MOM.
LOOK AT THIS GUY.
>> CAN I HOLD HIM?
>> YEAH, YOU CAN FEED HIM
IF YOU WANT.
>> THANKS.
SO HOW HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?
>> TIRED ALL THE TIME.
>> [laughs]
>> I AM TIRED ALL THE TIME.
>> TODD USED TO TELL ME
THAT KRISTINA ALWAYS HAD
TO HIDE HER FACE.
HE SAYS, "I ALWAYS GOT
TO MOVE HER HAIR."
>> I DIDN'T KNOW
HE NOTICED THAT.
>> HE DID.
HE'D SAY, "I LIKE HER."
I SAID, "YOU JUST LIKE HER?"
AND HE'D GO,
"[sighs]
I LOVE HER, MAMA."
[laughter]
TELLING YOU ABOUT YOUR DADDY
IS PUTTING YOU TO SLEEP.
SO TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR SCHOOL PLANS.
YOU AND TODD
HAD TALKED ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
>> YEAH, HE WANTED ME
TO GO TO SCHOOL,
SO I'M GONNA DO IT.
I'M ACTUALLY STARTING IN FALL,
AND I'M EXCITED.
I'M SO READY.
I'M REALLY GLAD
THAT YOU GOT TO SEE HIM.
>> IF HE'S ANYTHING
LIKE HIS DADDY AND HIS MOM,
HE'S GONNA BE ONE HECK
OF AN AWESOME MAN.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'M IN
A BETTER PLACE THAN I WAS.
I DON'T WANT TO FEEL NUMB
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE,
SO I HAVE TO MOVE ON.
I THINK THAT IT'S IMPORTANT
FOR LUKAS TO SEE ME HAPPY.
I DON'T THINK THAT I WOULD
BE WHERE I'M AT IF IT WASN'T
FOR DOTTY AND DANIEL.
THEY WANT ME TO HAVE
A GOOD LIFE, AND THEY WANT
LUKAS TO HAVE A GOOD LIFE,
AND IT'S THE SAME THING
MY MOM WANTS,
AND IT TOOK ME A LONG TIME
TO REALIZE THAT.
>> I'M SORRY.
I KNOW YOU WERE MAD AT ME
'CAUSE I CRIED AND WANTED TO
TALK ABOUT TODD.
I JUST DIDN'T STOP AND THINK
ABOUT HOW YOU WOULD FEEL.
>> IT'S OKAY.
EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING GOOD
TO COME OUT OF MY LIFE,
AND I'M BEYOND READY
TO START SCHOOL AGAIN.
THIS SPOT IS THE THOUSANDS SPOT.
I'M SO READY TO BE AROUND PEOPLE
MY AGE AND MAKE NEW FRIENDS.
I PROBABLY WASN'T READY
FOR KIDS.
IT'S DEFINITELY CHALLENGING.
[Lukas cries]
ONE DAY, HE'S GONNA ASK ME,
YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENED THAT DAY
THAT TODD PASSED AWAY.
I HOPE THAT I CAN BE THE ONE
TO TELL HIM,
BUT UNTIL HE'S OLD ENOUGH
TO UNDERSTAND IT,
I JUST WANT HIM TO KNOW
HAPPY THINGS ABOUT TODD.
MAYBE THINGS WILL START
LOOKING UP FROM HERE.
>> IF TODD WAS STILL HERE,
HE WOULD ALWAYS PROBABLY HAVE
BEEN HOLDING HIM, AND HE WOULD
HAVE HELPED ME FEED HIM
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
HE WOULD HAVE BEEN A GREAT DAD.
[chime dings]
[upbeat piano music]
♪
>> ♪ GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
♪ DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
♪ GET THROUGH IT ALL
♪ I'M WEAK, BUT I'M
♪ STRONG ENOUGH TO SEE