>> THIS IS GROSS.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO PUT MY HAND
IN THIS.
HI, I'M SUMMER.
I LIVE IN COLLINS, GEORGIA,
A SMALL TOWN AN HOUR
OUTSIDE OF SAVANNAH.
I MET MY BOYFRIEND, DJ, ONLINE,
AND WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER FOR
THREE YEARS.
HE'S A REAL COUNTRY BOY...
BE CAREFUL.
AND WE'RE TOTALLY IN LOVE.
>> [strumming guitar]
* GIRL, I LOVE YOU
* IT'S WHY I'M WRITING *
* THIS SONG
>> DJ GOT HIS G.E.D. AND IS
TAKING CLASSES TO BE A WELDER,
AND I WANT TO GRADUATE NEXT YEAR
AND GET MY DIPLOMA.
WHEN I'M NOT WITH DJ, I LOVE
HANGING OUT WITH MY THREE
HALF SISTERS.
bang!
UGH, I JUST RAN OVER A SNAKE.
OH, MY GOD.
>> I DON'T LIKE THAT.
>> AS THE OLDEST, I ALWAYS TRY
TO LOOK OUT FOR THEM, ESPECIALLY
BECAUSE OUR MOM STRUGGLES WITH
ADDICTION AND HAS BEEN IN AND
OUT OF OUR LIVES SINCE HAVING US
AS A TEENAGER.
BUT I'M HOPING I LEARN FROM HER
MISTAKES, BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH I
WANT TO DO THINGS DIFFERENTLY,
I'M PREGNANT.
WE'RE TWO MONTHS AWAY FROM
HAVING OUR SON, PEYTON.
SINCE MY MOM IS STRUGGLING WITH
ADDICTION, I DECIDED TO MOVE IN
WITH DJ'S PARENTS SO OUR SON
WOULD HAVE A STABLE HOME.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD
AT THIS.
YOU GOT TO PRESS DOWN HARD
OR SOMETHING.
>> I AM PRESSING DOWN HARD.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
SEE, YOU'RE LEAVING STUFF ON
THAT.
YOU GOT TO ROLL THAT STUFF IN.
>> THAT'S 'CAUSE I AIN'T USING
A LOT OF PAINT.
>> OH, YOU GOT IT ALL OVER THAT,
DIDN'T YOU?
I WISH Y'ALL WOULD HAVE WAITED
FOR ME.
>> SEE, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO
GET PAINT ON THIS.
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE WHITE.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT.
>> YOU DON'T PAINT
EVERYTHING BLUE.
>> DJ'S DAD WORKS OUT OF TOWN IN
VIRGINIA AND ONLY COMES HOME
WHEN HE HAS TIME OFF.
I'M REALLY GRATEFUL DJ'S PARENTS
ARE SO SUPPORTIVE AND THAT WE
WILL HAVE A PLACE TO LIVE ONCE
THE BABY COMES.
>> I MEAN, I'M, LIKE, A
CHEERLEADER IN Y'ALL'S CORNER,
ROOTING FOR Y'ALL TO MAKE IT.
I MEAN, A FAT CHEERLEADER, YES,
BUT A CHEERLEADER NEVERTHELESS.
[laughs]
>> I AM GRATEFUL THAT YOU ARE
LETTING ME START STAYING HERE
'CAUSE I MEAN, YOU KNOW,
AT MAMA'S, IT'S CHAOTIC.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I'M JUST REALLY GRATEFUL
THAT Y'ALL HELPED ME AND LET ME
JUST STAY HERE, AND Y'ALL HELPED
ME OUT WITH EVERYTHING
THAT I NEEDED.
>> WELL, WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT
Y'ALL WAS GONNA HAVE A CHILD,
I WAS WORRIED.
OF COURSE, IT STRESSES ME OUT
AND ALL, BUT BASICALLY, IT'S
JUST BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT'S
JUST A BAD TIME IN Y'ALL'S LIFE
RIGHT NOW 'CAUSE HE'S GOT TO
FINISH HIS COLLEGE, AND YOU'VE
GOT TO FINISH YOUR SCHOOLING.
BUT AFTER THE BABY'S BORN,
I EXPECT YOU TOO--PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'RE GONNA FINISH SCHOOL.
>> I AM.
>> WELL, IT'S A GOOD THING
YOU'RE A SWEET GIRL,
'CAUSE IF YOU WASN'T,
YOU WOULDN'T BE HERE.
[laughs]
YOU GOT ANYTHING TO ADD TO THAT?
>> YOU DON'T THINK I'M SWEET?
>> YEAH.
[laughter]
>> HEY.
>> I HATE MATH.
I HATE IT.
>> IT'S SO HARD.
>> I KIND OF MISS GOING
TO SCHOOL.
>> DO YOU MISS TALKING TO
EVERYBODY?
>> YEAH.
BEING IN THE COMMONS AREA
WITH EVERYBODY AT BREAK
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
>> SO YOU CAN'T GO BACK UNTIL
PEYTON'S BORN?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'LL BE LIKE, JANUARY,
'CAUSE WE HAD A SCARE.
THE DOCTOR RECOMMENDED THAT I GO
AHEAD AND START MY HOSPITAL
HOMEBOUND.
THAT WAY, I WOULDN'T PUT
SO MUCH STRESS ON THE BABY.
I GUESS I JUST DIDN'T THINK THAT
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ME, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
>> DJ AND ME, WE WERE STILL
USING CONDOMS AND STUFF, BUT I
JUST--I THINK WE RAN OUT
OR SOMETHING.
WE RAN OUT,
AND WE NEVER GOT ANY MORE.
AND THEN WE JUST STARTED BEING
REALLY CARELESS.
>> SO WHEN YOU FOUND OUT YOU
WERE PREGNANT, DID YOU EVER,
LIKE, CONSIDER PUTTING PEYTON UP
FOR ADOPTION OR HAVING
AN ABORTION?
>> NO, NO ABORTION.
I NEVER EVEN THOUGHT ABOUT
ABORTION.
I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT ADOPTION
EITHER, BUT DEFINITELY NOT
ABORTION.
WE DON'T BELIEVE IN THAT.
AND I JUST--I DON'T KNOW.
>> I THINK YOU UNDERSTAND THAT
IT'S GONNA BE HARD WHEN YOU HAVE
PEYTON, BUT I DON'T THINK YOU
REALLY UNDERSTAND HOW HARD IT'S
GONNA BE.
DO YOU THINK YOU WOULD LET YOUR
MAMA WATCH PEYTON?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
BECAUSE OF MY MOM'S ADDICTION
PROBLEMS, OUR RELATIONSHIP IS
REALLY HARD.
BUT SHE SAYS SHE'S SOBER NOW,
AND I'M HOPING IT'S FOR GOOD.
>> SO HOW YOU BEEN?
>> GOOD.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
>> BETTER.
>> GOOD.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
I WANT US TO START CLEAN.
YOU KNOW, HAVE THIS CONVERSATION
AND GET EVERYTHING OUT OF
THE WAY BEFORE THE BABY'S HERE
AND WE CAN HAVE ALL THAT
TAKEN CARE OF.
>> I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO TELL YOU.
I'VE GOT IT DEAD SET IN MY MIND
THAT I WANTED TO TELL YOU THIS.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, YOU DO IT.
YOU STOP.
I DO IT. I STOP.
AND, YOU KNOW, I KNEW YOU WAS
AGGRAVATED WITH ME, BUT--
>> SPIT IT OUT, MAMA.
>> BUT I DO WANT TO APOLOGIZE TO
YOU, SUMMER.
[sniffles]
PILLS CAN TAKE YOU DOWN A ROAD
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO.
IT'S BEEN ME TELLING YOU THIS
AND PROMISING YOU THIS AND
GOING BACK AND DOING IT ALL.
IT'S JUST ONE BIG CIRCLE.
>> YOU JUST HAD A LOT FOR
THE PAST MONTHS, ALWAYS HELPED
ME, AND BEEN BASICALLY CLEAN.
>> FOR THE PAST--ACTUALLY, I
WROTE IT ON MY CALENDAR.
I THINK IT'S BEEN NOT QUITE
THREE WEEKS.
AND WHAT MADE MAMA KNOW THAT
I HAD TO GET BETTER IS BECAUSE,
SUMMER, I JUST DON'T HAVE
THE OPTION.
I MEAN, I HAVE PEYTON COMING,
YOU KNOW?
AND YOU CAN'T BE A GRANDMAMA
NOR A MAMA IN THAT STATE OF
MIND, PERIOD, WHATSOEVER.
I WOULD NOT WANT TO DO ANYTHING
TO JEOPARDIZE YOU NOT LETTING
ME, YOU KNOW--I MEAN, I KNOW YOU
WOULD COME AND LET ME VISIT WITH
HIM WITH YOU WITH HIM.
BUT I KNOW YOU WOULDN'T BE,
LIKE, FEELING SAFE WITH MAMA
ATTENDING TO HIM.
>> I ALSO WANT TO SAY, WHEN
YOU'RE MESSED UP, I JUST DON'T
WANT TO BE AROUND YOU.
AND IT'S NOT LIKE I, LIKE, TRY
TO COMPLETELY AVOID YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT IT MAKES YOU SO
MAD TO SEE YOU LIKE THAT,
YOU KNOW?
AND IT JUST HURT MY FEELINGS.
DON'T CRY, MOM.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME CRY.
[chuckles]
DON'T CRY.
BE HAPPY.
I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE PROUD OF
YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW, THAT TAKES A LOT TO
JUST STOP DOING THAT STUFF,
YOU KNOW?
>> UH-HUH.
BUT I'M GONNA STAND FIRM THIS
TIME AND STICK TO MY PROMISES.
AND WHEN YOU NEED MAMA,
I'M GONNA BE MAMA.
I'M GONNA BE THERE FOR YOU.
I DON'T CARE OF IT'S
DAYLIGHT OR DARK,
WEE HOURS OF THE MORNING,
I DON'T CARE.
>> IT WAS REALLY HARD GROWING UP
WHILE MY MOM WAS BATTLING
ADDICTION.
AND EVEN THOUGH I MOVED OUT,
I STILL MAKE TIME TO HANG OUT
WITH MY SISTERS.
[trash can clatters]
I JUST RAN OVER THE TRASH CAN.
[laughter]
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YES! OH, MY GOD.
>> SUMMER.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I DENTED HIS TRUCK.
>> WAS THAT ALREADY DENTED?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> WELL, HELP ME PICK IT UP.
>> I'M PREGNANT.
I AIN'T SUPPOSED TO LIFT STUFF.
>> QUIT SMACKING THAT GUM.
>> GOSH.
>> YOU WILL SPIT IT OUT.
>> I'M GONNA BE AN AUNT.
THAT'S WEIRD.
>> IT'S NOT EASY, Y'ALL.
LIKE, FOR REAL.
Y'ALL BETTER GO GET
ON BIRTH CONTROL...
>> YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I WAS
THINKING.
>> OR Y'ALL GONNA END UP
PREGNANT AND FAT LIKE ME.
>> NOT IF WE SAY NO.
>> AND I'M GONNA--YEAH, THAT'S
WHAT ME AND DJ SAID.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GET THAT
THING IN MY ARM.
>> I'M SCARED OF A NEEDLE.
>> WELL, YOU SCARED OF A NEEDLE,
BUT YOU CAN HAVE SEX?
>> NO.
>> UH-HUH.
I'M JUST SAYING.
>> OH, WATCH THE ROAD.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SAY IT.
>> TAYLOR, NOBODY'S GONNA BE
LOOKING AT YOUR FEET.
>> IT'S THE SMELL.
>> OH, MY GOD.
[laughter]
>> WHAT DO THEY SMELL LIKE?
>> FRITOS.
[laughter]
>> OH, THAT'S DISGUSTING.
>> WANT TO SEE THAT?
[laughs]
LOOK AT MY BEAUTIFUL FEET.
AIN'T THEY PRETTY?
>> HEY, LOOK.
SHE'S PEELING A POTATO.
[laughter]
>> LOOK AT THAT BELLY.
>> I'M SO FAT.
I'M READY FOR MY LITTLE TUMMY TO
COME BACK.
I JUST WANT TO BE A GOOD MAMA
TO PEYTON.
I JUST WANT HIM TO KNOW THAT
I'M ALWAYS THERE FOR HIM AND
THAT HE CAN DEPEND ON ME.
DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE
LITTLE AND MOM WAS, LIKE,
THE BEST MAMA, LIKE, THAT YOU
COULD ASK FOR?
THAT'S THE KIND OF MAMA
I WANT TO BE.
BUT WHEN SHE STARTED ACTING
WILD--I DON'T WANT TO BE LIKE
THAT.
THAT'S TAUGHT ME TO NOT GO CRAZY
WILD, YOU KNOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I HAVEN'T KNOWN MAMA TO STAY
SOBER LIKE THAT FOR A FEW WEEKS,
HAVE YOU?
>> NOPE.
>> SHE, LIKE, AT LEAST ONCE
A WEEK IS MESSED UP.
LIKE, I'M SAYING I HAVEN'T SEEN
HER EVER TRY TO DO BETTER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> MM-HMM.
>> SHE JUST LEFT US
WITH OUR DADDIES.
AND THEN, SHE--SHE JUST...
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE DIDN'T REALLY WANT TO
BE A MAMA, SO...
>> SHE NEVER EVEN CALLED US.
>> MM-MM.
SHE BARELY EVER CALLED.
AND WHEN SHE DID CALL, I WOULD
IGNORE IT 'CAUSE I WAS MAD
AT HER.
>> [laughs]
>> I DIDN'T TALK TO HER FOR,
LIKE, A YEAR.
>> IT WAS HARD.
LIKE, WHEN WE STARTED OUR
PERIOD, MAMA WASN'T THERE.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, LIKE, DADDY
GOING TO THE STORE, HAVING TO
BUY US A BRA AND STUFF.
>> A GIRL NEEDS HER MAMA.
YOU CAN'T--YOU HAVE GIRL STUFF
THAT YOU HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF.
AND GROWING UP, YOU KNOW, YOU
START YOUR LADY THINGS AND YOUR
FIRST DAY OF SCHOOL,
AND YOU WANT YOUR MAMA TO BE
THERE AND HELP YOU PICK OUT WHAT
TO WEAR AND DO YOU HAIR AND
ALL THAT STUFF, AND TEACH YOU
HOW TO PUT MAKEUP ON WHEN YOU
START USING IT.
>> [sniffles]
>> EVERYBODY GOES THROUGH A HARD
TIME IN THEIR LIFE, AND I'M SURE
SHE REGRETS IT.
BUT I THINK IT'S US THAT--
THAT WE HAVE TO SUFFER FOR IT,
NOT HER.
I REALLY HOPE MAMA, LIKE,
KEEPS DOING WHAT SHE'S DOING
AND JUST STAYS BETTER AND DOES
BETTER FOR HERSELF.
>> TIME WILL TELL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
TIME WILL TELL.
>> I DON'T KNOW, 'CAUSE YOU KNOW
HOW, LIKE, SHE HAS THAT CAR,
BUT SHE DON'T NEVER HAVE ANY GAS
IN IT.
[chuckles]
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
I MEAN, HE HELPS US OUT A LOT,
LIKE, A LOT.
HE LETS US LIVE HERE, AND HE
FEEDS US AND BUYS US, YOU KNOW,
THINGS THAT WE NEED.
AND I'M GRATEFUL HE HELPS US,
BUT IT JUST--I WISH, YOU KNOW,
MY FAMILY WOULD HELP A LITTLE
MORE, AND IT KIND OF HURTS MY
FEELINGS.
>> THIS AIN'T NO FAIRYTALE.
>> AND I DON'T WANT TO STOP
GOING TO SCHOOL.
AND I WANT THAT PROM EXPERIENCE
AND THAT HIGH SCHOOL EXPERIENCE,
'CAUSE I ONLY HAVE A YEAR LEFT.
>> I MEAN, I AIN'T SAYING IT'S
GONNA BE EASY.
I'M JUST SAYING, YOU KNOW,
LIKE,
GOD'S GONNA LOOK OUT FOR US,
I MEAN, WE'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S JUST GONNA BE HARD.
>> I KNOW, BUT YOU GOT ME.
I GOT YOU.
>> [chuckles]
[horn honks]
I REALLY WANT MY MOM TO STAY
SOBER AND BE A PART OF MY LIFE.
>> YOU FINALLY MADE IT?
>> SO I INVITED HER OUT TO
DINNER TONIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO EAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I NEVER ATE HERE BEFORE.
>> THEY HAVE AN AWESOME CHINESE.
I ENJOY MY TIME WITH YOU,
SUMMER.
I'M GLAD ME AND YOU ARE
TOGETHER.
[coughs]
EXCUSE ME.
YOU GONNA LET ME BABYSIT
SOMETIME?
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> LOOK AT ME.
REALLY.
DO YOU THINK HONESTLY THAT I
WOULDN'T TAKE CARE OF PEYTON?
>> [chuckles]
>> I LOVE YOU.
KISS ME.
>> MM-MM.
QUIT IT, MAMA.
>> KISS ME!
>> STOP!
I'M TRYING TO DRIVE!
>> [clicks tongue]
>> NO, BABY.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
>> EW, EW, EW.
I WANT TO SMOKE A CIGARETTE.
YEAH.
>> JUST HOLD ON.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
[door dinging]
MAMA, WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
JUST WAIT.
MAMA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAMA, GET IN.
OH, MY GOD.
>> GOL.
>> NO, MAMA, YOU'RE MESSED UP.
LIKE, I THOUGHT--YOU'RE
SLURRING YOUR WORDS.
YEAH, YOU ARE.
>> OH, MY GOD, HAVE MERCY.
>> NO, I AIN'T!
>> YES, YOU ARE.
LIKE, WHAT DID YOU TAKE ON THE
WAY HERE?
LIKE, I SEEN YOU TAKE SOMETHING.
WHAT DID YOU TAKE?
>> TWO, MAMA?
OH, MY GOD, I'M GOING HOME.
MAMA, I KNOW.
>> WHAT?
[line ringing]
>> HEY.
DJ, MY MAMA IS SO MESSED UP.
LIKE, I DON'T EVEN WANT TO GO IN
THIS RESTAURANT.
I DON'T KNOW, DJ.
SHE'S JUST SLURRING HER WORDS.
AND I CAN JUST TELL
SHE'S MESSED UP.
AND SHE TOOK SOMETHING BEFORE WE
CAME UP HERE.
AND I'M JUST EMBARRASSED.
[crying]
>> I THINK I'M JUST GONNA TAKE
HER HOME.
ALL RIGHT, I LOVE YOU.
BYE.
[sniffles]
[soft chiming]
>> I WOKE UP TO A TEXT FROM MY
MOM SAYING SHE'S SORRY AND IT
WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
BUT I DON'T BELIEVE HER.
WHEN I CALLED YOU, SHE WAS
REALLY MESSED UP.
AND THEN ON MY WAY HOME,
I THINK IT GOT WORSE.
IT JUST HURTS MY FEELINGS THAT
SHE WOULD COME LIKE THAT,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE, I WAS SO EXCITED THAT--
'CAUSE WE NEVER GO OUT AND
DO ANYTHING.
>> I KNOW, RIGHT?
>> WE WENT OUT LAST NIGHT, AND
SHE CAME MESSED UP.
AND IT JUST HURT MY FEELINGS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS SHE JUST NEEDS HELP.
>> I WANT HER TO, LIKE, HAVE A
RELATIONSHIP WITH PEYTON, AND I
WANT PEYTON TO GO OVER THERE,
YOU KNOW, BUT I DON'T WANT HIM
TO BE OVER THERE AND HER BE SO
MESSED UP THAT...
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> HER NOT EVEN KNOWING WHAT
SHE'S DOING WITH HIM.
>> I INVITED MAMA TO THE BABY
SHOWER, BUT I DON'T THINK
I WANT HER TO GO.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH.
SINCE WE'RE REALLY TIGHT ON
MONEY, WE'RE GOING TO PICK UP
A USED CRIB WE FOUND ONLINE.
YOU DRIVE LIKE A GRANDPA.
>> WELL, I DO HAVE A BABY ON
BOARD.
[both laugh]
>> HEY.
THIS IS THE CRIB?
>> YEAH.
JUST DO IT RIGHT IN THERE.
>> AND THIS IS THE SCREWS?
>> YEAH, THERE'S A COUPLE
MISSING, BUT I MADE DO WITH IT,
SO....
>> OH, OKAY.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
>> BUT BESIDES THAT, YOU'RE
GOOD.
>> I LIKE IT.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S YOUR $30.
>> OKAY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
[door dinging]
I LIKE THAT CRIB, DON'T YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU PROMISE?
>> DANG, THAT THING IS HEAVY.
>> ARE THEY GONNA FIT
THROUGH THAT?
>> IT AIN'T GONNA FIT.
>> DANG.
WELL, I HOPE.
>> MAN.
[laughs]
>> DON'T TELL ME THAT.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO TAKE IT
APART.
ALL THIS STUFF NEEDS TO COME
OUT, WHAT THEY DONATED.
>> I'M GUESSING THAT SHE HAD
BUGS IN HER HOUSE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT WILL CAUSE YOUR HOUSE TO
HAVE ROACHES.
>> YOU DON'T WANT IT IN YOUR
HOUSE.
IT'S SO HARD TO GET RID OF.
>> YOU DON'T THINK THEY'RE IN
THE MATTRESS, DO YOU?
>> NO.
THEY'RE TOO BIG TO GO IN THE
MATTRESS.
BUT WE NEED TO GET IT OUT OF THE
HOUSE AND LET IT SIT OUTSIDE FOR
A FEW DAYS.
>> THERE'S ONE RIGHT THERE.
>> THEY ACCUMULATE TO TRILLIONS,
LIKE, IN NOT EVEN A WEEK,
AND YOU NEVER CAN GET RID OF
'EM.
THEY GET INSIDE YOUR WALLS.
>> WELL, LET'S SET IT OUTSIDE.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> THEY ABOUT SUFFOCATE
IN THERE.
>> I'M SO MAD.
THIS CRIB'S DISGUSTING.
>> NO, IT'S GONNA BE FINE,
THOUGH.
I MEAN, ALL WE GOT TO DO IS
SPRAY IT DOWN REAL GOOD AND THEN
CLEAN IT AFTERWARDS AND THEN
WE'LL BRING IT ON IN THE HOUSE.
>> OH.
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE GONNA MAKE
THE CRIB WORK, WE STILL NEED
A LOT OF STUFF FOR PEYTON,
SO I'M REALLY GLAD DJ'S FAMILY
IS THROWING US A BABY SHOWER.
BECAUSE OF ALL THE DRAMA WITH MY
MOM, I ASKED HER NOT TO COME.
>> YOU MADE IT?
OH, MY GOSH.
I LOVE IT.
THEY'RE SO PRETTY.
>> "I GET MY AWESOMENESS FROM MY
AUNT SAM."
[laughter]
"I'M FINALLY OUT.
I WAS RUNNING OUT OF WOMB."
[laughs]
I TOLD YOU.
LOOK, OUT HOW CUTE.
I TOLD YOU IT WAS CUTE.
>> HEY.
HEY, MOM.
>> NO WAY.
WAIT TILL Y'ALL GET
Y'ALL'S OWN PLACE.
>> OH, WE GETTING HIM TODAY.
>> NO, WAIT TILL Y'ALL GET
Y'ALL'S OWN PLACE.
>> BECAUSE I WANT A PIT BULL.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GETTING THE PIT
BULL FROM?
>> [coughs]
>> HOW MUCH IS SHE SELLING IT TO
YOU FOR?
>> $85.
>> HUH?
>> I LIKE HOW YOU'RE PAYING FOR
A PIT BULL INSTEAD FOR PAYING
FOR SOMETHING FOR PEYTON.
>> I LIKE HOW YOU EVEN GOT A SAY
SO IN ANY OF THIS.
>> FOOLISH.
WHY WOULD--WHY DO YOU EVEN WANT
A PIT BULL?
YOU'RE ABOUT TO HAVE A SON.
YOU'RE GONNA BE TRAINING
A PIT BULL ALONG WITH
RAISING A BABY.
REALLY?
>> WELL, YEAH, I GUESS WE'RE NOT
GETTING A PIT BULL.
>> WE CAN GET IT IF YOU WANT TO
GET IT.
I'M GOING BACK INSIDE.
HUG ME.
BE CAREFUL.
I'M ANNOYED THAT DJ IS
CONSIDERING SPENDING MONEY ON
A DOG WHEN WE HAVE MUCH MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
>> WELL, IT SAYS THAT IT CAN
PLUG IN SOMEHOW.
>> [chuckles]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
>> LET THE GENIUS WORK ON THAT.
>> WHO, DJ?
>> YEAH, OF COURSE.
YOU KNOW, HE'S THE GENIUS.
[laughs]
>> HE'S SO PRETTY, AIN'T HE?
>> [laughs]
LOOK AT HIM.
GET HIM SO HE DON'T MESS UP
OUR STUFF.
>> LOOK,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
HE'S ANOTHER MUTT TO FEED.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
>> SO YOU DON'T LIKE THE DOG?
>> I DON'T DISLIKE THE DOG.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE READY
FOR A PUPPY.
>> OH, YEAH.
[laughs]
I'M NOT READY FOR A PUPPY,
BUT I'M READY FOR A SON.
>> THAT'S WHY YOU'RE NOT READY
FOR A PUPPY.
>> YEAH, BECAUSE YOU'RE ABOUT TO
HAVE A SON, AND YOU'RE GONNA BE
COMPLETELY PREOCCUPIED WITH
PEYTON WHEN HE'S BORN,
AND YOU'RE NOT GONNA HAVE AS
MUCH TIME ON YOUR HANDS
TO TRAIN A DOG.
>> DJ, ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT HOW
THAT DOG WILL ACT WHEN PEYTON
GETS HERE?
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> YOU THINK HE'LL BE FINE?
>> YEAH.
>> I DEFINITELY SEE WHERE YOUR
MOM IS COMING FROM 'CAUSE THIS
IS HER AND YOUR DADDY'S HOUSE.
toot!
>> WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
>> SO WHAT Y'ALL THINK
ABOUT THAT?
>> THAT'S THE DOG.
>> PEW.
GET RID OF THAT THING.
HE'S OVER HERE BETWEEN US.
>> WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
EVERY TIME I WANT SOMETHING,
LIKE, YOU'VE ALWAYS GOT
SOMETHING NEGATIVE TO SAY
ABOUT IT.
>> YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A REALLY
HUGE PRIORITY IN YOUR LIFE IN
THE NEXT COUPLE OF WEEKS.
>> I'M JUST SAYING YOU ALL AIN'T
GOT TO WORRY ABOUT ME.
YOU CAN TRUST ME.
AND I'VE GOT THIS.
I GOT EVERYTHING UNDER CONTROL.
DON'T ASK ME NO MORE QUESTIONS,
I SWEAR TO GOD.
OR WHATEVER Y'ALL SAY, I MEAN,
Y'ALL SEE.
I REALLY DON'T CARE.
>> NAH, SINCE YOU DON'T CARE TOO
MUCH ABOUT PEYTON.
>> I DIDN'T EVEN SAY THAT.
WHAT THE [bleep]?
>> 'CAUSE YOU DON'T REALLY CARE.
>> DJ, HOLD ON. GOD!
>> WATCH OUT, WATCH OUT.
>> YOU COULD'VE SAID,
"EXCUSE ME."
I GET THAT DJ WANTED A PUPPY,
BUT I REALLY DON'T WANT TO UPSET
HIS FAMILY WHILE WE'RE
LIVING HERE.
DJ.
>> HUH?
>> COME HERE.
I THINK THAT MY WATER'S LEAKING.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> 'CAUSE I WAS PEEING, AND THEN
I WASN'T PEEING ANYMORE.
AND THEN, LIKE, IT WAS, LIKE,
LEAKING.
>> WELL, DO YOU WANT TO GO?
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S GO.
>> COME ON.
MY BELLY IS REALLY HURTING.
I'M EXCITED.
>> I AM SORRY, BUDDY.
>> ARE WE JUST GONNA
LEAVE HIM HERE?
>> I RECKON.
>> POOR THING.
[chuckles]
>> WHEN WE GOT TO THE HOSPITAL,
I WAS FOUR CENTIMETERS DILATED,
SO THEY ADMITTED ME FOR LABOR.
>> HEY.
>> I KNOW MY MOM I STRUGGLING,
BUT I REALLY WANT HER TO BE
HERE TOO, SO I'M GONNA GIVE HER
ANOTHER CHANCE TO SHOW UP
FOR ME AND PEYTON.
MAMA.
>> WHAT?
>> I'M IN THE HOSPITAL,
AND I'M AT FOUR CENTIMETERS.
>> I SAID I'M IN THE HOSPITAL IN
STATESBORO, AND I'M AT FOUR
CENTIMETERS.
OHH, HOLD ON.
MY BELLY'S HURTING.
OH, MY GOD.
LIKE, IT'S HURTING, BUT I'M SO
EXCITED AT THE SAME TIME.
[chuckles]
>> HAVE YOU HAD AN I.V. BEFORE?
>> THESE THINGS ARE THE WORST.
I HATE A NEEDLE.
>> YES, THEY ARE.
>> [sucks teeth]
>> HOLD STILL.
>> EW, EW, EW.
[gasps]
>> HOLD STILL.
IT'S GONNA STING, OKAY?
>> IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I COULD PUNCH SOMEBODY IN THE
FACE RIGHT NOW.
THIS HURTS SO BAD.
>> YOU WANT ME TO BE HONEST?
IT'S GONNA GET WORSE.
THAT WAS WORST I HAD EVER BEEN
THROUGH IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
I STARTED CRYING AND EVERYTHING.
>> MY FOOT FELL OFF THE TABLE,
AND I COULDN'T PICK IT UP.
I SAID, "PUT ME TO SLEEP."
IT SCARED ME.
>> NOW I'M FREAKING OUT.
>> IT HURTS LIKE A BITCH.
[laughs]
>> IT'S UNDESCRIBABLE.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, IT HURTS.
>> I TRIED TO DESCRIBE IT TO
HER BEFORE, AND IT'S THAT SICK
FEELING, BELLY HURTING, YOU'VE
GOT TO GO TIMES 50.
>> NO, IT WAS WORSE THAN THAT.
OH, LORD.
IT WAS WORSE THAN THAT.
>> WELL, I DON'T WANT TO TALK
RIGHT NOW, LIKE, FOR REAL.
JUST LET ME CALM DOWN.
LIKE, I JUST--LEAVE ME ALONE.
>> I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP HER.
THEY CAN GIVE HER SOMETHING TO
HELP HER CALM DOWN.
>> [sniffles]
OH, THIS HURTS.
[whimpering]
I'M SCARED.
OH, THIS HURTS.
[sobbing]
OW, OW, OW, OW, OW.
>> YOU'RE TEN CENTIMETERS NOW,
OKAY?
>> [sobbing]
I'M SCARED.
I DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
NO, DJ.
IT'S NOT OKAY. I'M SCARED.
[sobbing]
OW! OW!
>> USE ALL OF ENERGY.
USE YOUR--ALL OF YOUR ENERGY TO
PUSH.
PUSH, HONEY.
PULL YOURSELF UP AND CURL INTO
IT AND PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH...
>> I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T. I CAN'T. I CAN'T.
I CAN'T!
>> PUSH ACROSS THE BURN.
HARDER.
AGAIN.
COME ON. COME ON. COME ON.
>> PUSH! PUSH! PUSH!
>> PUSH, BABY.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> GET HIM OUT!
[laughter]
>> COME ON, SUMMER, PUSH.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST DONE!
>> YOU'RE GETTING IT, BABY.
>> THERE YOU GO!
>> OH!
[baby cries]
>> * ANY MORNING
* COULD BE OUR FINAL FIGHT
*
* WHEN IT'S OVER *
* THE SUN MAY NEVER RISE
*
* TIME WILL TAKE US
* WHEN WE RUN THE RIVER DRY
*
>> * YOU'RE RIGHT HERE WITH ME *
[chime dings]
>> * RIGHT HERE WITH ME
[troubled piano music]
*
>> I WAS SO HAPPY PEYTON WAS
FINALLY HERE,
BUT AFTER EVERYONE WENT HOME,
THE DOCTOR NOTICED HE WAS
BREATHING TOO FAST.
SO THEY ARE RUSHING HIM TO
A BIGGER HOSPITAL IN SAVANNAH.
[sirens wailing]
[dramatic music]
*
>> SINCE THE DOCTOR SENT PEYTON
TO SAVANNAH FOR URGENT CARE,
THEY ARE CLEARING ME EARLY SO WE
CAN BE WITH HIM.
>> HIS HEART RATE WAS BEATING
TOO FAST AT FIRST TONE.
HIS HIGHEST--200 TIMES A MINUTE,
AND THAT'S NOT NORMAL FOR
BABIES.
HE WAS ALSO BREATHING TOO FAST,
WHICH IS WHY HE WENT TO THE
LEVEL 3 NURSERY 'CAUSE THEY
HAVE PEDIATRIC SURGEONS.
IF THEY NEED TO DO A SURGICAL
ASSESSMENT OF HIS BELLY, THEN
ALL THAT CAN BE TAKEN CARE OF
THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> OH, MAN.
[gentle percussive rock music]
*
[chime dings]
IN INTENSIVE CARE, THEY FOUND
OUT PEYTON HAD A BACTERIAL
INFECTION.
THEY HAD TO KEEP HIM ON
ANTIBIOTICS IN THE HOSPITAL FOR
A WEEK, WHICH MEANT BORROWING
MONEY FROM DJ'S DAD
TO STAY IN SAVANNAH.
BUT IT WAS ALL WORTH IT WHEN
THE DOCTORS FINALLY CLEARED HIM
TO COME HOME WITH US.
>> WELL, IS THERE ANYTHING THAT
Y'ALL GOT TO DO?
DID THEY GIVE Y'ALL ANY KIND
OF INSTRUCTIONS ABOUT ANY KIND
OF MEDICINES OR ANYTHING?
>> THEY SAID THAT HE WAS GOOD
TO GO.
>> HE AIN'T GOT NO MEDICINE.
>> COOL.
>> I'M JUST READY TO FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT AND QUIT HAVING
TO, LIKE, GUESS ON WHAT'S
GONNA HAPPEN.
>> WHERE'S OREGON?
>> EXACTLY.
>> WHERE IS IT AT?
>> THAT'S MY POINT.
THAT'S EXACTLY MY POINT.
>> SO WHAT IS OREGON?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT THAT IS.
YOUR DADDY HAS LOST IT.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
MM-HMM.
[Peyton crying]
>> [moans]
>> [mumbles indistinctly]
[water running]
>> IT'S BEEN A WEEK SINCE WE GOT
HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL,
AND PEYTON IS DOING WELL.
DJ'S BEEN IN PUTTING EXTRA
TRAINING HOURS WELDING, AND I'VE
BEEN STRUGGLING TO KEEP UP WITH
MY SCHOOLWORK.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> LOOK AT THIS WORK I HAVE.
AND I STILL HAVE SOME FROM LAST
WEEK AND THE WEEK BEFORE THAT.
>> YOU'D BETTER GET ON THE BALL.
>> AFTER PEYTON WAS BORN, I GOT
SO BEHIND, ESPECIALLY WHEN IT
WAS THAT WEEK IN SAVANNAH.
AND I DIDN'T HAVE ANY TIME DO
ANYTHING, SO THAT MADE ME TWO
WEEKS BEHIND, AND THEN
HE'S CRYING HALF THE TIME.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN I DO
MY SCHOOLWORK.
YOU HEAR HIM?
>> WELL, WHAT'S YOU GONNA DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
AND HALF OF IT, THEY DON'T EVEN
SEND ME NOTES TO DO, LIKE--
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO DO THIS.
>> THIS IS EASY.
>> WELL, YOU WANT TO DO IT?
>> "IF ALEXA BUYS THREE SHIRTS
FOR $42, HOW MUCH WILL EIGHT
SHIRTS COST AT THE SAME PRICE?"
42 TIMES 8.
WELL, WHAT YOU GONNA DO?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M GONNA DO.
AND I SAID I'M GONNA GRADUATE,
BUT, I MEAN, I DON'T HAVE TIME
TO CATCH UP ON ANYTHING.
I JUST THINK I MIGHT JUST GET
MY G.E.D. AND JUST DO THAT.
>> I KNOW I MIGHT DISAPPOINT
PEOPLE THAT I'M NOT GONNA
GRADUATE, BUT, I MEAN,
I GOT TO DO WHAT'S BEST FOR ME.
I MEAN, I CAN'T BE ALL STRESSED
OUT AND DEPRESSED.
>> THESE STEAKS ARE GONNA BE
GOOD 'CAUSE I JUST WENT
AND BOUGHT 'EM.
>> DJ'S DAD IS HOME FOR THE
WEEKEND TO VISIT PEYTON.
>> BLESS THIS FOOD TO
THE NOURISHMENT OF OUR BODIES
WITH HEAVEN.
AND FOR ALL THINGS, WE GIVE YOU
THANKS AND PRAISE, GOD.
>> all: AMEN.
>> SO, SUMMER, WHAT'S BEEN GOING
ON WITH SCHOOL WHILE
I'VE BEEN GONE?
>> YEAH, WHEN WE WERE IN
SAVANNAH THAT WEEK WITH PEYTON,
I GOT FAR BEHIND ON MY CLASSES,
SO ME AND DJ WAS TALKING, AND I
JUST THINK IT'LL BE EASIER IF I
GET MY G.E.D. AND THEN START
COLLEGE THIS COMING SUMMER.
>> WELL, ORIGINALLY, WHEN YOU
FIRST CAME HERE, I SAID ONE OF
THE THINGS I ASKED YOU TO DO IS
FINISH SCHOOL,
AND YOU TOLD ME YOU WOULD.
>> I WAS PLANNING ON IT.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE
SO HARD AFTER PEYTON GOT HERE.
>> I AM DISAPPOINTED THAT YOU
DIDN'T DO WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
>> I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
>> IT'S JUST NOT EASY
WITH A BABY.
I DON'T--I MEAN, I KNOW Y'ALL
HAVE HAD KIDS, BUT Y'ALL HAVEN'T
HAD KIDS IN HIGH SCHOOL, SO YOU
KNOW, IT'S, LIKE, A LOT HARDER
NOW THAT PEYTON IS HERE.
I DID THINK I WOULD BE ABLE TO
DO IT.
BUT, I MEAN, IT'S JUST HARD ONCE
YOU GET BEHIND ON ALL YOUR
STUFF.
>> I THINK A G.E.D. IS TAKING
THE EASY WAY OUT.
>> I DON'T THINK HAVING A G.E.D.
WILL GIVE YOU ANY OPPORTUNITIES.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT I WAS ALWAYS
TOLD WHAT THE G.E.D. STANDS FOR:
GOOD ENOUGH DIPLOMA.
>> SO IF THAT'S THE WAY IT IS,
THEN WE'LL DEAL WITH IT
AS IT COMES.
DO YOU AGREE?
>> DON'T HAVE NO CHOICE.
>> I HATE LETTING DJ'S PARENTS
DOWN, BUT I KNOW THIS IS THE
BEST THING FOR ME AND PEYTON.
[phone buzzing]
HELLO?
>> HI.
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> LIKE, WHAT'S HER PLAN?
I MEAN, SHE HAS TO HAVE
SOMETHING FIGURED OUT.
[melancholy rock music]
*
>> LORD, HELP ME.
>> DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> MY MOM IS FACING SOME SERIOUS
PRISON TIME, AND I'M STRUGGLING
TO COME TO TERMS WITH IT.
>> ANY OBJECTIONS?
IT'S A 13 CASE.
>> I LOVE YOU.
BE CAREFUL.
[solemn piano rock music]
*
>> * I ANTICIPATE
* THE SOUND
*
* THAT BREATH OF SILENCE
* AND THE WORDS COME OUT
* AND I FEEL IT
* OH, OH
* OH-OH-OH
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
SHE DID THAT.
BUT THEN AGAIN, DRUGS MAKE YOU
DO CRAZY STUFF.
MY MAMA'S A MESS.
>> SHE IS.
TO BE HONEST, I DON'T WORRY
WITH HER NO MORE.
>> IF Y'ALL EVER NEED ANYTHING,
ALL YOU GOT TO DO IS CALL ME.
SHE CAN COME LIVE WITH ME.
DJ JUST DON'T KNOW IT YET, BUT
SHE CAN COME LIVE WITH ME
WHENEVER I GET MY OWN HOUSE.
>> I'M COMING, DEFINITELY.
>> DEFINITELY.
>> MY MOM HAS BEEN RELEASED
UNTIL HER TRIAL.
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M REALLY
HURT, WE'RE GOING OVER TO SPEND
SOME TIME WITH HER.
IF MAMA GOES TO JAIL, I DON'T
THINK THAT WOULD REALLY AFFECT
PEYTON MUCH 'CAUSE HE'LL STILL
BE YOUNG.
AND PEYTON WON'T ASK QUESTIONS,
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
"WHY IS SHE IN JAIL?"
AND "WHEN IS SHE COMING HOME?"
AND "WHAT IS JAIL?"
AND ALL THAT STUFF.
HEY THERE.
>> COME IN.
IF I DO GET SENT OFF,
YOU GONNA WRITE ME?
>> I WILL DECIDE TO COME SEE
YOU, BUT I WON'T BE ABLE TO
MAKE MANY TRIPS.
>> MM-MM.
>> THAT'S SUCH A LONG DRIVE.
DON'T CRY.
EVERYBODY MAKES MISTAKES, MAMA.
>> I KNOW IT.
>> I'M NOT SAYING THIS IS GONNA
HAPPEN, BUT I'M SAYING, YOU
KNOW, IF IT WAS TO HAPPEN, AS
LONG AS YOU DO GOOD, LIKE,
YOU'LL GET OUT IN HALF THE TIME.
>> [sighs]
I DON'T WANT TO DO
NONE OF IT, DJ.
I'M SCARED.
>> I KNOW.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T THINK
ABOUT WELL, EVENTUALLY, THIS IS
GONNA CATCH UP WITH ME OR I'M
GONNA HAVE TO--IT DIDN'T EVEN
CROSS MY MIND.
I WISH I COULD TAKE IT ALL BACK,
ERASE IT.
I MIGHT BE GONE AWAY FROM HIM.
MY GOD, IT JUST ABOUT DRIVES ME
CRAZY.
[Peyton crying]
>> [sniffling]
>> MAMA, DON'T MAKE ME CRY.
DON'T CRY.
I'VE GOT FAITH.
I'VE GOT FAITH THAT EVERYTHING'S
GONNA WORK OUT.
I'M JUST GONNA MISS YOU.
>> I'LL MISS YOU, BABY.
>> [sniffling]
>> I LOVE YOU.
WHEN I WAS IN FOURTH GRADE IS
WHEN MY MAMA STARTED MESSING UP
REAL BAD WITH HER PILLS,
AND IT AFFECTED MY WHOLE
CHILDHOOD.
I WAS JUST EMBARRASSED TO EVEN
GO PLACES WITH HER.
IT REALLY HURT MY FEELINGS AND
HOW SHE LEFT 'CAUSE I'M JUST
LIKE--'CAUSE I LOVE PEYTON SO
MUCH, I'M JUST--
HOW DO YOU GET--HOW CAN YOU LOVE
YOUR CHILD SO MUCH AND JUST
LEAVE 'EM LIKE SHE DID ME?
[Peyton crying]
IT'S JUST SO HARD TO BE IN
HIGH SCHOOL AND HAVE A BABY
AND TRY TO FINISH SCHOOL AND,
YOU KNOW, STILL HAVE YOUR
TEENAGE LIFE, 'CAUSE ONCE YOU
HAVE A BABY, YOU'RE NOT--
YOU'RE AN ADULT.
YOU'RE NOT A TEENAGER ANYMORE.
YOU CAN'T DO THE THINGS YOU
WANTED TO DO.
YOUR WHOLE LIFE REVOLVES AROUND
YOUR BABY.
EVEN THOUGH I DIDN'T FINISH
SCHOOL AND I'M NOT GONNA
GRADUATE, I DO HOPE THAT I DO
GET SOME KIND OF EDUCATION,
WHICH I PLAN TO DO.
I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE, AND I
WANT TO BE INDEPENDENT AND MAKE
SOMETHING OF MYSELF.
LOOK AT HIS LITTLE SOCK.
>> IT FELL OFF.
>> [speaking indistinctly]
HOPEFULLY SOON, DJ AND I WILL
GET OUR OWN HOUSE, AND WE CAN BE
A FAMILY AND RAISE PEYTON IN OUR
OWN HOME.
I JUST FEEL LIKE PEYTON WILL
GROW UP BEING VERY LOVED AND
WITH BOTH OF HIS PARENTS.
AND I JUST WANT PEYTON TO HAVE
A BETTER CHILDHOOD THAN THE ONE
I DID.
>> YOU DISRESPECTED THE PERSON
WHO TAKES OF YOUR CHILDREN.
IT'S NOT FAIR TO ME, TONY.
>> I'M [bleep] LEAVING.
I GO TO WORK EVERY [bleep] DAY!
>> I DO TOO!
>> [bleep]!
>> GET OUT!
YOU ARE NOT GONNA TALK TO HER
LIKE THAT!
>> [bleep] YOU!
>> I HATE THIS, KARLEY!
I HATE THIS!
[screams]