>> [laughs]
DO WE NEED THOSE LITTLE
BUMPER THINGS?
'CAUSE Y'ALL KNOW I CAN'T BOWL.
MY NAME IS MARKAI.
I'M 16 YEARS OLD, AND I LIVE
IN FLORIDA.
YOU WANT CREDIT OR DEBIT?
I'M A SENIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL,
AND I'M WORKING PART-TIME
AT A GROCERY STORE, BUT I HAVE
BIGGER PLANS.
EVER SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL,
I WANTED TO BE A VETERINARIAN,
AND I'M LUCKY, BECAUSE MY SCHOOL
HAS COURSES THAT FAST-TRACK ME
TO VET SCHOOL.
MY MOM, SARINA, RAISED ME
ON HER OWN.
>> I NEVER HAD ANY REGULAR
CONTACT WITH MY DAD, WHICH IS
OKAY WITH ME NOW BECAUSE I HAVE
A STRONG MAN IN MY LIFE.
I MET JAMES AT A FOOTBALL GAME,
AND WHEN I FELL FOR HIM,
NOBODY WAS MORE SURPRISED THAN
ME, BECAUSE HE'S NOT MY TYPE.
BUT HE ENDED UP WINNING ME OVER.
YOU'RE WHITE WITH DREADS.
THAT'S THE WEIRDEST THING
I'VE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
>> HOW IS THAT WEIRD?
[laughter]
>> HAVING A SINGLE MOM LEFT ME
WITH A LOT OF RESPONSIBILITIES
FOR RAISING MY LITTLE SISTER,
SAMARRA.
IT'S A GOOD THING THAT I GOT
A LOT OF PRACTICE RAISING A KID
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
>> THIS THAT TURKEY BACON?
>> YES.
>> WHAT'S UP WITH Y'ALL?
WHY Y'ALL DO THAT?
>> WE ALMOST ATE WITHOUT
YOU GUYS.
>> THAT'S MESSED UP.
>> ONE THING ABOUT MY MOM,
SHE'S NOT SHY ABOUT SAYING
WHAT'S ON HER MIND.
>> I JUST--MY QUESTION TO YOU
GUYS IS, WERE YOU PRACTICING
SAFE SEX?
>> NO.
>> NAH.
>> WE WEREN'T.
>> WHY?
>> WELL...[mumbles]
CONDOMS BE ALL IN THE WAY,
PRETTY MUCH.
>> CONDOMS IN THE WAY...
OKAY.
WELL, I KNOW I WENT AND BOUGHT
BANANAS FOR MY KIDS AND TAUGHT
THEM HOW TO PUT CONDOMS ON
THEMSELVES AND NOT TO LET
THE BOYS PUT IT ON.
AND IF THEY COULDN'T WEAR
A CONDOM, THAT MEANT WHAT?
>> THEY COULDN'T HAVE SEX.
CROSS YOUR LEGS.
>> I ASKED YOU GUYS WHAT YOU
WERE GONNA DO, AND, YOU KNOW,
I'M PRO-CHOICE, SO...
>> JAMES ANSWERED BEFORE
I COULD.
>> YEAH.
>> both: "I'M GONNA TAKE CARE
OF MINE."
>> YEAH, THAT.
THE FAMOUS LAST WORDS.
>> MY MOM CAN'T HIDE HER
FEELINGS.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE HIGH HOPES
FOR JAMES AND I AS A COUPLE.
SHE'S SCARED I'LL FOLLOW
IN HER FOOTSTEPS.
MY MOM SUPPORTED MY DAD,
AND THEN HE TOOK OFF WHEN
THE TIME CAME TO RAISE US.
SHE'S BEEN REALLY STRICT
ABOUT NOT LETTING JAMES
STAY AT THE HOUSE.
HE DOESN'T HAVE A JOB,
SO HE CAN'T GET US A PLACE
TO LIVE WHEN THE BABY COMES.
>> WE GONNA DO OUR VERY BEST
TO TAKE CARE OF HER, WHETHER
SHE HAS ALL THE GOLD AND JEWELS
IN THE WORLD OR WHETHER SHE HAS
A ROOF OVER HER HEAD
AND FOOD IN HER MOUTH.
SHE GOT US.
>> IT'S NOT FUNNY.
YOU REMEMBER THE FIRST DAY
WE SEEN EACH OTHER?
>> I WILL NEVER FORGET IT.
YOU SEE ME, AND YOU SEE
THAT I WAS ALREADY CUTE.
>> YOU WAS ALL RIGHT.
>> WHATEVER.
I WAS NASTY.
>> HMM?
>> I MEAN, JUST PARTYING
AND NOT CARING AND...
>> NOW IT'S JUST ME AND YOU.
>> I KNOW.
WE MATURED A LOT.
'CAUSE...
>> NOW WE GOT A BABY.
>> I JUST WANT HER TO HAVE
A GOOD LIFE.
YOU KNOW, SHE CAN KNOW
THAT HER PARENTS ARE ALWAYS
GONNA BE THERE, BOTH PARENTS.
>> WELL, LIKE I SAID,
LIKE, IF YOU GO INTO SOMETHING
WITH FEAR IN YOUR HEART OR
WHATEVER, YOU AIN'T GONNA DO
NOTHING BUT PANIC.
IT'S JUST GONNA MAKE THINGS
WORSE.
BUT IF YOU GO INTO IT THINKING
ON THE POSITIVE SIDE, YOU RIGHT.
>> LIKE, US BREAKING UP
IS NEVER AN OPTION.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OH, BABY, IT'S A SPIDER.
THAT'S A SPIDER.
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
>> IN YOUR HAIR.
YOU SEE IT?
>> WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
Y'ALL TRYING TO GET ME KILLED
OUT HERE.
>> MY SENIOR YEAR IS JUST
BEGINNING.
MY BABY IS DUE IN NINE WEEKS,
SO I HAD TO TAKE A LEAVE FROM
MY JOB, AND I DON'T HAVE A PLAN
YET FOR WHEN THE BABY COMES.
ALL I KNOW IS, THERE IS NO WAY
I'M GONNA BE A HIGH SCHOOL
DROPOUT, AS AN EXAMPLE
FOR MY BABY.
[doorbell rings]
>> HEY.
>> HI.
>> HOW YOU BEEN?
I BROUGHT YOU SOME CUPCAKES.
>> OH.
WE'RE HAVING A GIRL,
AND WE'RE NAMING HER ZA'KARIA.
AND MY BEST FRIEND CASSIDY
AGREED TO BE THE GODMOTHER.
"TO MY BEST FRIEND
AND GODDAUGHTER, FROM CASSIDY.
SOMEDAY SHE'LL BE A FAMOUS
PIANIST OR A HIGH SCHOOL SCIENCE
TEACHER.
SOMEDAY SHE'LL BE A STRONG,
CONFIDENT WOMAN.
SOMEDAY SHE'LL HAVE HER OWN
HOPES AND DREAMS, NOT KNOWING
THAT ONCE UPON A QUIET TIME
YOU CLOSED YOUR EYES AND DREAMED
TO HAVE HER IN YOUR LIFE."
I'M GONNA CRY.
IT REALLY WARMS MY HEART
THAT MY FRIENDS ARE BY MY SIDE.
BUT IT WAS HAVING A TOTALLY
DIFFERENT EFFECT ON MY MOM.
>> MY HEART IS BROKEN.
YOU HAVE BROKE MY HEART.
HOW MANY--I MEAN, I MIGHT NOT
SAY IT EVERY DAY, "OH, MY HEART
IS BROKEN."
YOU'VE KNOWN FROM DAY ONE, WHEN
I ASKED YOU IN THAT HOSPITAL,
WHAT YOU WERE GONNA DO.
ALL I REMEMBER FROM JAMES IS,
"I'M GONNA TAKE CARE OF MINE.
IF IT'S MINE, I'M GONNA
TAKE CARE OF MINE."
AND ALL I HEARD FROM YOU WAS,
"WE DECIDED TO KEEP THIS BABY.
WE'RE GONNA RAISE THIS BABY."
>> WHY ONE MINUTE DO YOU BELIEVE
IN US AND THE NEXT MINUTE
YOU DON'T?
>> I WANT YOU TO SUCCEED.
I WANT YOU TO BE SUCCESSFUL.
BUT JUST LIKE YOU READ THAT CARD
CASSIDY BROUGHT YOU ABOUT
THE DREAMS FOR YOUR CHILD
AND THE STUFF SHE GONNA DO,
ALL I COULD THINK WAS,
"I HAD THOSE SAME DREAMS."
AND I JUST HOPE YOUR BABY
IS NOT PREGNANT AT 16.
WHAT YOU THINK, WHEN I LOOKED
AT YOU OR FELT YOU MOVE IN MY
STOMACH, IT WAS, "HMM,
I WANT HER TO BE PREGNANT
AT 16, HER SENIOR YEAR
OF HIGH SCHOOL, NO JOB,
NO PLACE TO LIVE"?
THAT WAS NOT MY DREAM
FOR MY CHILD.
HOW MUCH HAVE Y'ALL SAVED UP?
>> NOTHING, MOM.
>> JAMES BOUGHT HIS FIRST PAIR
OF DIAPERS TWO WEEKS AGO.
AND THE ONLY REASON I THINK
YOU DID THAT IS BECAUSE I SAID,
"DON'T HAVE THAT BOY COME IN
THIS HOUSE WITH--EMPTY-HANDED.
NOT ANOTHER DAY, BECAUSE THE
SIGHT OF HIM IS DISGUSTING ME."
DID I NOT TELL YOU THAT?
I MIGHT NOT HAVE TOLD YOU THAT.
>> NO, YOU AIN'T NEED TO TELL ME
THAT.
>> BUT I TOLD HER THAT.
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU THERE.
BUT WHAT I'VE ALWAYS TAUGHT
MY DAUGHTER, AND I KNOW I'VE
SHOWED THEM BY EXAMPLE, LIKE,
YOU CAN'T DEPEND ON BABY DADDY.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU CAN'T RELY ON ANYBODY
BUT YOU.
AND I'M NOT TRYING TO HURT
YOUR FEELINGS.
I WANT YOU TO SUCCEED.
YOU USED TO IT.
>> I'M USED TO IT.
>> WELL, I'M USED TO YOU
BREAKING MY HEART, AND I'M
TIRED OF THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> LAST NIGHT, MY MOM REALLY
LET LOOSE WITH HER FEELINGS,
BUT I KNOW SHE'S JUST LOOKING
OUT FOR ME.
SHE WAS A YOUNG MOTHER,
AND IF ANYBODY KNOWS WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO BE IN MY POSITION,
IT'S HER.
>> MARKAI?
I DON'T WANT YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO LEARN THE HARD WAY.
I WANT SOME THINGS YOU TO LEARN,
YOU KNOW, THROUGH ME, FROM ME.
BECAUSE I WENT THROUGH SCHOOL
WITH TWO KIDS, AND IT WASN'T
EASY, AND I FEEL IT MADE
MY OLDEST GROW UP FASTER
THAN SHE REALLY SHOULD HAVE.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT I DON'T WANT YOU TO EVER
THINK I DOUBT YOU.
I KNOW YOU'RE GONNA MAKE IT.
SO THE STUFF THAT I'VE ALWAYS
TOLD YOU IS STILL THERE.
IT'S JUST HARDER FOR YOU,
AND I DIDN'T WANT IT TO BE
HARDER FOR YOU.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WANT.
THANKS.
>> JAMES AND I AREN'T ALWAYS
SEEING EYE TO EYE ON HOW WE'RE
GOING TO RAISE ZA'KARIA.
BUT WE DO KNOW HOW WE PLAN
TO FEED HER.
I WANT TO BREAST-FEED.
I THINK IT'S THE BEST THING.
I KNOW YOU THINK IT'S
THE BEST THING.
BREAST MILK TASTES SWEET TO ME.
>> [groans]
>> BREAST MILK IS NOT THAT BAD.
>> IT'S NASTY.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
>> JUST TASTE IT.
THAT'S ALL I WANT Y'ALL TO DO.
>> I HAVE TASTED IT.
IT'S NASTY.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
EXPLAIN IT.
[spits]
I NEVER KNEW BEING PREGNANT
HAD SO MANY WEIRD SIDE EFFECTS.
[spitting]
I'VE BECOME WHAT DOCTORS CALL
A SPITTER.
[spitting]
I PRODUCE SO MUCH SALIVA,
I CAN'T SWALLOW IT WITHOUT
WANTING TO PUKE.
>> YOU EAT SOAP.
IT'S NASTY.
>> YEAH, I DO EAT SOAP.
I'VE ALSO DEVELOPED A CRAVING
TO EAT SOAP.
BUT IT'S LIKE I HAVE TO BITE IT.
AFTER I SMELL IT, I HAVE TO
BITE IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> NO, YOU...
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW TO
EXPLAIN IT.
HOPEFULLY MY DOCTOR CAN TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> HELLO.
>> HOW ARE YOU, DR. ERICSSON?
>> NOW, I WAS READING
YOUR CHART.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH THE SOAP?
YOU NIBBLING ON SOAP?
>> NO, NOT NO MORE.
I WAS.
>> DID YOU FEEL BETTER
WHEN YOU ATE THE SOAP?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH?
WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT,
YOUR BLOOD COUNT CAN LOOK
ANEMIC, AND YOU CAN HAVE
THESE URGES TO EAT SOAP, CLAY.
DID YOU HAVE AN URGE
TO EAT CLAY OR ANY DIRT,
ANYTHING LIKE THAT?
>> IT'S SOAP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN, I GUESS WE PROBABLY
SHOULD JUST ADVISE YOU TO DO
THE IRON SUPPLEMENT NOW, THEN.
I'LL WRITE A PRESCRIPTION.
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> [spits]
>> SEE, IT'S WOBBLING.
[chime dings]
JAMES HAS TO HURRY UP AND GET
A CRIB FOR THIS BABY.
AND WHEN HE'S DONE DOING
ALL THAT, HE BETTER FIND A CRIB
FOR ALL THREE OF US.
UNTIL I CAN GET MY JOB BACK
AND HELP OUT, JAMES IS JUST
GONNA HAVE TO CARRY THE
FINANCIAL LOAD ON HIS OWN.
>> I WAS WONDERING IF Y'ALL
WERE HIRING.
>> I DON'T THINK WE HAVE
APPLICATIONS RIGHT NOW.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
I'M JAMES.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU, JAMES.
>> I TURNED IN AN APPLICATION
ABOUT A MONTH AGO, MAYBE.
I JUST WANTED TO COME IN,
CHECK ON IT AGAIN.
>> OKAY, WELL, THE STORE MANAGER
COMES IN AT 1:00.
IF YOU JUST LEAVE ME YOUR NAME
AND PHONE NUMBER, WE WILL MAKE
SURE THAT WE LOOK IN TO IT.
>> OKAY, DO YOU HAVE A PEN
OR PAPER OR SOMETHING?
>> SURE, YEAH, LET ME GET YOU...
[motor rattling]
>> WHAT IS UP...
>> PUSH THE GAS.
>> I AM.
[engine whining]
THEY CAN'T SAY WE'RE NOT TRYING.
JAMES STILL DOESN'T HAVE
A JOB, AND NOW WE DON'T HAVE
A CAR EITHER.
THE BIGGEST THING IS, HE HASN'T
FOUND A PLACE FOR US TO STAY
ONCE THE BABY COMES.
WE STARTED MOVING HIS STUFF
INTO HERE, BUT MY MOM MIGHT NOT
BE CLEAR ON OUR PLAN.
>> WHEN IS JAMES MOVING IN?
>> MA, OH, MY GOODNESS.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.
>> I COULD HAVE SWORN I TALKED
TO YOU ABOUT IT.
>> NO, DON'T SWEAR.
>> WHETHER I THINK IT'S FAIR
OR NOT, IT'S HER HOUSE,
HER RULES.
ZA'KARIA'S HERE IN ONE MONTH.
AND IF JAMES DOESN'T GET THIS
SORTED OUT, HE'LL BE LOOKING IN
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
>> ALL RIGHT, LOCKING THE FORT
DOWN.
>> WITH THE BABY DUE IN FOUR
WEEKS, GOING TO SCHOOL GETS
HARDER EVERY DAY.
I WANT TO BE A VETERINARIAN,
AND I WAS TAKING VET COURSES
AT MY SCHOOL, BUT BECAUSE
PREGNANT WOMEN CAN GET DANGEROUS
GERMS AND PARASITES THAT ANIMALS
CARRY, MY DOCTOR SAID I COULDN'T
BE AROUND THEM.
GETTING PREGNANT MEANS I'M GOING
TO BE STUCK AT THE CHECKOUT
LONGER THAN I PLANNED.
>> HI, MARKAI.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
LONG TIME NO SEE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> I'M OKAY.
SINCE I GOT PREGNANT,
A CASE WORKER HAS BEEN HELPING
ME MANAGE FINISHING SCHOOL,
BUT WITH THE PRESSURE OF HAVING
TO FIND ME AND JAMES A PLACE
TO LIVE, SCHOOL IS THE LEAST
OF MY PROBLEMS.
>> HOW IS IT GONNA--
AFTER THE BABY IS BORN,
ARE YOU GONNA BE ABLE TO PICK UP
YOUR WORK, OR IS SOMEONE GONNA
BRING IT TO YOU?
>> EITHER SOMEONE'S GONNA GO
GET IT FOR ME, OR I'LL JUST
PICK IT UP.
>> OKAY.
>> MISS SUE?
>> YEAH?
>> IS THERE ANY POSSIBLE WAY,
LIKE, WE CAN, LIKE, HELP JAMES
FIND A PLACE TO STAY OR
SOMETHING?
>> I CAN BRING YOU A LIST
OF LOW-INCOME APARTMENTS UP
FOR OUR NEXT VISIT.
>> OKAY.
>> IS HE WORKING?
>> NO.
BUT HE'S LOOKING.
LIKE, HE'S REALLY...
>> SO HOW IS HE GONNA AFFORD
HIS OWN APARTMENT?
>> BELIEVE ME, I'VE BEEN ASKING
THAT SAME QUESTION.
BUT FOR RIGHT NOW, I'M PUTTING
THAT OUT OF MY MIND...
HEY.
>> HI.
>> BECAUSE TODAY IS
MY BABY SHOWER.
>> HELLO.
>> YAY.
I MISSED YOU.
HI, BLUE.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> HI, MAN!
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> WHAT'S UP!
>> HAND ME THAT BOO.
HEY, MAN.
I WANT TO SEE HOW YOU HOLD
A BABY.
>> YOU GONNA SEE,
JUST NOT RIGHT NOW.
>> [fusses]
>> I KNOW.
HE DON'T WANT TO HOLD YOU.
>> MAN, IT AIN'T NOTHING
AGAINST YOU, BRO.
>> IT'S GREAT TO SEE ALL
MY FRIENDS AGAIN, BUT I COULD
FEEL THE TENSION BETWEEN MY MOM
AND JAMES, AND SO CAN HE.
>> NO MATTER WHAT JAMES SAYS
TO HIS FRIENDS, HIS JOB HUNT
HAS FALLEN OFF TRACK.
I USED TO SEE HIM ALL OVER
THE HELP-WANTEDS.
NOW HE'S SPENDING MORE TIME
ON MYSPACE.
I FOUND OUT THAT ONE OF HIS EXES
IS TRYING TO HOOK UP WITH HIM
ONLINE, AND WITH OUR BABY DUE
IN LESS THAN ONE MONTH,
THAT'S TOTALLY UNACCEPTABLE.
>> SO IT MEANS YOU STILL
WANT TO CHILL WITH HER.
>> WELL, I DON'T TRUST HER.
>> I HAVE HAD NO INTIMACY WITH
THE BOYS THAT COME OVER TO
MY HOUSE, NONE WHATSOEVER,
HUGGING, KISSING, ALL THAT OTHER
TYPE OF STUFF.
>> ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I AIN'T NEED TO HEAR THAT.
>> I HAVE NOT DONE ANY OF THAT
WITH THEM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
SOUNDS GOOD.
>> [sighs]
I'M DONE.
WHATEVER.
>> SINCE LAST NIGHT, I HAVEN'T
BEEN TALKING TO JAMES.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S BEEN
TALKING TO HIS EX ONLINE.
THERE'S ONLY ENOUGH ROOM
IN THE PICTURE FOR ME, JAMES,
AND ZA'KARIA.
I'M SCARED TO THINK THAT JAMES
ISN'T IN THIS FOR THE LONG RUN.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR ME THAT
ZA'KARIA HAS HER DADDY, BECAUSE
I'VE WASTED A LOT OF DAYS
WAITING FOR MY DAD TO SHOW UP.
MY DAD LIVES AN HOUR AWAY.
HE SAID HE WAS GOING TO HELP ME
AND JAMES FIND A PLACE TO STAY,
AND IT'S GOING TO BE THE LAST
TIME I SEE HIM BEFORE
THE BABY COMES.
>> AT THE TONE, PLEASE RECORD
YOUR MESSAGE.
[phone beeps]
>> HEY, DAD.
I'M CALLING YOU BECAUSE EARLIER
TODAY, YOU SAID THAT YOU WERE
GONNA COME OUT HERE OR GONNA
AT LEAST TRY TO COME OUT HERE.
UM...
YEAH, SO JUST CALL ME
WHEN YOU CAN.
>> DON'T GET MAD.
>> WELL, 'CAUSE HE ALWAYS
DOES THIS.
LIKE, COME ON, GET REAL.
LIKE, IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA COME,
DON'T SAY YOU GONNA COME.
I STILL HAD A LITTLE HOPE
THAT HE WOULD COME, BUT, I MEAN,
I KNEW AS SOON AS HE SAID,
"I'LL TRY," HE WEREN'T GONNA
COME.
[chime dings]
>> MY DAD LETTING ME DOWN
REALLY MAKES ME GRATEFUL
FOR JAMES.
HE MIGHT NOT HAVE FOUND A JOB
YET, BUT AT LEAST JAMES IS HERE
AND TRYING.
>> HEY, I THINK I GOT IT.
BABE.
I THINK I GOT IT.
>> HE EVEN FIXED THE CRIB
JUST IN TIME, 'CAUSE IT LOOKS
LIKE BABY ZA'KARIA IS ON
HER WAY.
I'M CRAMPING.
I GOT THAT SHARP PAINS
IN MY VAGINA, AND I FEEL LIKE
I HAVE TO--A BOWEL MOVEMENT.
LIKE, I NEED TO BOO-BOO.
>> LET'S GO.
GOOD MORNING, GOOD MORNING.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> * STAGE THE PHOTOGRAPHS *
>> BLESS THIS YOUNG FAMILY,
LORD, AS THEY START THEIR
NEW JOURNEY.
IN YOUR NAME WE PRAY, AMEN.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA HURT, IS IT?
>> I WASN'T SURE HOW I WAS GONNA
HANDLE THE LABOR PAINS.
JUST GETTING STUCK WITH A NEEDLE
FREAKED ME OUT.
>> SAMARRA DID HER BEST
TO DISTRACT ME.
[laughter]
OH...
[yells]
THE LABOR PAINS STARTED
GETTING REALLY INTENSE.
[gags]
>> YOU OKAY, BABY?
AND SO FAR, YOU'RE DOING
A WONDERFUL JOB.
>> [groans]
I DECIDED TO GET AN EPIDURAL
TO HELP WITH THE PAIN.
>> WHAT DOES THE EPIDURAL
FEEL LIKE?
>> JUST NUMB EVERYTHING.
LIKE, I STILL FEEL PRESSURE,
BUT I DON'T FEEL MY
CONTRACTIONS.
LIKE, I DON'T FEEL
THE SHARP PAIN.
WITH THE EPIDURAL, IT'S HARD
TO KNOW WHEN TO PUSH, BUT
SOMETHING LET ME KNOW THE TIME
HAD COME.
AND I DON'T NEED MY SPIT CUP.
>> NO MORE SPIT CUP.
WE HAVE DISPOSED OF
THE SPIT CUP.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH,
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> COME ON, ONE MORE, BOO!
COME ON!
[baby crying]
>> THERE SHE GOES.
>> * PLEASE LET ME *
* TAKE YOU HOME *
* LET ME *
* LET YOU KNOW *
>> JAMES, HOW DO YOU FEEL?
>> LIKE A DADDY.
>> * THAT I CAN CHANGE *
* AND I WILL CHANGE *
* TO BETTER FIT *
* YOUR FOLD *
>> I THINK SHE'S HUNGRY NOW.
>> OH, LET'S SEE.
SHE WILL.
[chime dings]
>> I'M EXCITED TO SHOW ZA'KARIA
HER NEW HOME.
THIS IS YOUR--COME ON.
I'M STARTING TO REALIZE
MY NEW LIFE IS ALL ABOUT
BREAST-FEEDING.
YOU THINK SHE HUNGRY?
>> I THINK SO.
>> SHOOT.
MAMA JUST FED YOU.
MY BREASTS ARE KILLING ME.
LET'S REDO THIS ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> YOU STILL WORKING ON THAT?
>> YEAH.
SHE DIDN'T WANT TO GIVE ME
HER FOOTSIES THE FIRST TIME.
NOW THAT ZA'KARIA IS HERE,
MAYBE MY MOM WILL SEE HOW MUCH
I NEED JAMES AROUND.
I HOPE SHE'LL EASE UP
AND LET HIM SPEND THE NIGHT.
>> JAMES?
>> BUT I GUESS NOT.
>> IF ANYBODY KNOWS HOW HARD
IT IS TO RAISE A KID ON YOUR
OWN, IT'S MY MOTHER.
I THOUGHT SHE WANTED AN EASIER
LIFE FOR ME.
[baby crying]
>> [shushing]
OKAY, IT'S RIGHT THERE.
I'LL GET IT LIKE THIS.
>> [fusses]
>> [laughs]
STOP GRUNTING AT ME.
IT SUCKS THAT MY MOM WON'T LET
JAMES STAY OVER, 'CAUSE I NEED
HIS HELP NOW MORE THAN EVER.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GET
A PLACE OF OUR OWN.
HEY, DADDY.
>> HEY, BABY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> NOTHING.
I NEED YOUR HELP.
I'VE LEARNED THE HARD WAY
NOT TO COUNT ON MY DAD,
BUT NOW THAT I GOT A KID
OF MY OWN, I'M GONNA HAVE TO DO
WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
JAMES, HE HAS NOWHERE ELSE
TO GO, AND, YOU KNOW, MOM SAID
THAT, LIKE, YOU KNOW, SHE DON'T
WANT TO TAKE CARE OF ANOTHER
PERSON, AND I UNDERSTAND,
BUT SHE'S NOT GONNA LET HIM
GET KICKED OFF ON THE STREET.
YOU KNOW, LIKE...
>> NO.
>> PROBABLY LIKE $100 SOMETHING.
BUT THEY GONNA STOP IT IN
A MINUTE, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN ONLY DO IT FOR SO LONG.
>> YEAH.
>> THANK YOU, DADDY.
I LOVE YOU.
[baby fussing]
>> I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
A COINCIDENCE OR IF MY DAD
TALKED TO MY MOM, BUT THAT NIGHT
SHE CALLED US IN FOR A TALK.
>> HEY, YOU TWO.
I'VE BEEN GIVING IT SOME
THOUGHT, AND I WANTED TO TALK
TO BOTH OF YOU.
WATCHING MARKAI LATE AT NIGHT
WITH THE BABY OR UP WITH THE
BABY, IT WAS EXHAUSTING TO HER
AND TO ME.
I SAW IT IN HER FACE AND JUST
THOUGHT IT WAS OVERWHELMING
FOR HER.
AND I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR THAT
THE MOTHER HAVE TO BE STUCK,
SO I HAVE DECIDED TO GO AHEAD
AND LET YOU MOVE IN.
I WANT YOU TO USE THIS TIME
WISELY.
OUT THERE HUSTLING,
LOOKING FOR A JOB.
YOU WILL HAVE TO SLEEP
OUT IN THE LIVING ROOM.
>> AS LONG AS I GOT SOMEWHERE
TO STAY.
>> YEAH, YOU WON'T GET WET
WHEN IT RAINS.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
I HELP YOU.
YOU HELP HER.
BUT THERE HAS TO BE AN END DATE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT WE TRYING.
>> I'M RELIEVED THAT JAMES'
LIVING SITUATION IS HANDLED
FOR THE MOMENT, BUT ALL HIS WORK
OPPORTUNITIES SEEM TO FALL
THROUGH.
I'M SUPPOSED TO START BACK
AT THE GROCERY STORE NEXT WEEK,
SO AT LEAST WE'LL HAVE
A LITTLE MONEY COMING IN.
BUT TO MAKE THINGS WORK,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BLOW
MY ENTIRE SAVINGS AND THEN SOME
ON GETTING A CAR.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> YOU SAYING YOU DON'T
TRUST ME?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
>> EVER SINCE I FOUND JAMES
CHATTING WITH HIS EX ON MYSPACE,
LITTLE THINGS THAT NEVER USED
TO BOTHER ME ARE STARTING
TO BOTHER ME.
THE THOUGHT OF HIM AND ANOTHER
GIRL IS ALWAYS SOMEWHERE IN
THE BACK OF MY HEAD.
[baby crying]
[shushes]
WHAT TIME IS IT?
>> 6:48.
6:49.
>> ALONG WITH GOING BACK
TO WORK, I ALSO HAVE TO GO BACK
TO SCHOOL SO I CAN GRADUATE
ON TIME, BUT I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW HARD IT WOULD BE TO LEAVE
ZA'KARIA.
BYE.
>> BYE.
>> JAMES DROPPED ME OFF AT
SCHOOL AND TOOK CARE OF ZA'KARIA
FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
I DEFINITELY HOPE HER DAY
WAS LESS MESSED UP THAN MINE.
FIRST OFF, I'M WAY BEHIND
IN MY SCHOOLWORK.
THEN JAMES' EX CAME RIGHT UP
TO ME WITH SOME MESSED UP NEWS.
JAMES CHEATED ON ME WITH HER AT
THE START OF OUR RELATIONSHIP,
AND THE THING THAT HURTS EVEN
MORE, THEY DIDN'T EVEN USE
PROTECTION.
AND TO TOP IT OFF, I CALLED
JAMES, AND HE TOLD ME EVERYTHING
WAS TRUE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS [bleep].
BECAUSE I NEVER CHEATED ON
JAMES.
I NEVER DID ANYTHING TO JAMES.
I WAS DEFINITELY JAMES'
SINCE DAY ONE.
OH.
USUALLY WE HOOK UP WITH JAMES
IN THE PARKING LOT,
THEN WE GO PICK UP ZA'KARIA
FROM DAY CARE, BUT TODAY,
HE DECIDED TO WALK.
>> YOU CAN'T PARK RIGHT THERE!
OH, MY GOD!
I WILL DIE!
>> SO YOU GONNA BE LIKE THIS?
ARE YOU FREAKING SERIOUS?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DID THIS!
IT'S YOU.
>> TWO WEEKS INTO OUR
RELATIONSHIP!
>> IT DOESN'T [bleep] MATTER!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO DID THIS
[bleep]!
I DIDN'T EVER CHEAT ON YOU.
>> HEY, DO YOU WANT ME
TO MOVE THE CAR?
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SAID?
>> DO YOU WANT TO GET MAD
AT ME?
>> I AIN'T MAD.
>> THE [bleep] THAT YOU DID!
>> I'M HURT 'CAUSE OF
THE [bleep] YOU SAID.
>> OH, SOME [bleep] THAT I SAID?
WHAT ABOUT THE [bleep]
THAT YOU [bleep] DID?
WHAT ABOUT THAT HO GETTING--
>> OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS CRAZY.
>> EVERYTHING YOU DID
IN THE PAST?
>> THIS IS CRAZY.
>> WHAT [bleep] THAT I DO?
>> DON'T TOUCH ME, MAN.
YOU SAY THE [bleep] YOU SAID,
AND I'M SUPPOSED TO BE COOL?
>> FINE, THEN.
IT'S OVER.
>> WHATEVER.
>> YOU GONNA HAVE TO FIGHT ME
FOR CUSTODY.
YOU DON'T EVER COME SEE
MY CHILD.
>> [fussing]
>> STOP, ZA'KARIA.
YOU GOT A BOOGER THAT'S, LIKE,
KILLING...
AFTER OUR ROADSIDE BLOWOUT,
JAMES DIDN'T COME HOME.
WHEN MY BEST FRIEND KAIA
FOUND OUT ABOUT OUR FIGHT...
>> YOUR BEST FRIEND IS CRYING.
>> ARE YOU CRYING, MARKAI?
>> SHE CAME OVER TO PULL ME
OUT OF MY MOOD.
[sobs]
>> WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
BUT, LIKE, IT JUST
PISSED ME OFF.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WHO CAME UP TO THE SCHOOL?
>> HIS--THE GIRL.
>> THE GIRL CAME AFTER SCHOOL...
YOU DIDN'T USE A CONDOM WITH ME,
AND THEN YOU DIDN'T
USE A CONDOM WITH HER.
>> THAT'S NASTY.
>> AND THEN YOU DIDN'T USE
A CONDOM WITH ME AGAIN.
THAT'S HUMILIATING.
THAT'S EMBARRASSING.
AND IF HE WOULD HAVE JUST,
YOU KNOW, BEEN WITH ME,
LIKE HE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE,
THIS [bleep] WOULDN'T HAVE
HAPPENED.
>> OKAY, IT'S TOO LATE
FOR SHOULDA, COULDA, WOULDAS,
BECAUSE IT ALREADY HAPPENED.
>> MM-HMM, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> HAS HE DONE IT RECENTLY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S JUST IT.
WHO KNOWS?
>> WELL, MARKAI, YOU KNOW...
I'M WITH HIM, AND THAT'S
IN THE PAST.
I MEAN, IF HE NOT DOING IT NOW,
THEN IT SHOULDN'T MATTER.
YOU SHOULDN'T THROW IT UP
IN HIS FACE.
>> EXACTLY WHAT I'M SAYING.
I'M NOT OVER IT.
>> WELL, THAT'S SOMETHING Y'ALL
HAVE TO TALK ABOUT.
YOU DIDN'T GET TO TALK HIM.
Y'ALL WAS JUST GOING BACK
AND FORTH YELLING.
THAT'S NOT TALKING.
[solemn fiddle music]
>> * JUST A FEW HONEST WORDS *
* IT SHOULDN'T BE THAT HARD *
>> I WAS JUST LIKE, MAN...
>> IT AIN'T NO WRAP.
IT'S NEVER A WRAP.
HEY, I'M TALKING ABOUT, MAN...
[baby crying]
>> I KNOW.
MAMA'S HERE.
BUT YOU GOT TO GET DRESSED,
BECAUSE WE PROBABLY GOT TO GO.
TODAY IS MY FIRST DAY BACK
AT WORK, AND WITHOUT JAMES
AROUND TO HELP, I'M GONNA HAVE
TO LEAVE ZA'KARIA WITH MY MOM.
HOW ARE YOU, SIR?
>> GOOD.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
DID YOU FIND EVERYTHING OKAY?
>> YEAH, EVERYTHING'S FINE.
>> I THOUGHT WORK WOULD HELP ME
TAKE MY MIND OFF THE SITUATION,
BUT I MANAGED TO STAY MAD AS
HELL THROUGHOUT MY WHOLE SHIFT,
AND WHEN I GOT OFF WORK,
JAMES WAS OUTSIDE, AND HE WANTED
TO TALK.
>> I'M SORRY FOR ALL THAT
[bleep].
I REALLY, TRULY AM.
IF I COULD GO BACK IN TIME...
IF YOU LOVE ME, YOU'D UNDERSTAND
HOW MUCH I LOVE YOU.
YOU HAVE MY HEART,
YOU AND ZA'KARIA.
>> IF HER HOUR OF HAVING SEX
MEANS MORE TO YOU THAN OUR TWO
WEEKS OF BEING TOGETHER,
JUST MAKES ME...
>> BABY, IT WAS TWO WEEKS.
WE DIDN'T KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT EACH OTHER IN TWO WEEKS.
>> BABY, YOU WAS TELLING ME
YOU LOVED ME AT TWO WEEKS.
I WAS PREGNANT IN, LIKE,
TWO WEEKS.
>> THE BIGGEST GIFT I COULD GIVE
ZA'KARIA IS TO HAVE HER DADDY
IN HER LIFE.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO WORK THIS
OUT WITH JAMES, BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF I'LL EVER BE ABLE TO LET THIS
GO.
SO IF I CHEATED ON YOU,
WOULD YOU BE ABLE TO TRUST ME?
>> YES.
YOU CANNOT SEE HOW MUCH I LOVE
YOU, HOW MUCH...
>> THAT DOES NOT MATTER TO ME.
>> MY LOVE DOESN'T MATTER?
THAT'S WHAT YOU JUST SAID?
>> NO, I'M SAYING IT DOESN'T
MATTER TO ME WHEN IT COMES
TO THAT.
NO, IT DOESN'T.
>> TWO WEEKS IN A [bleep]
RELATIONSHIP.
>> WELL, TWO WEEKS IS...
>> DAMN, SEE, YOU LIKE--GOSH.
>> I'M THE ONE--DURING YOUR
WHOLE PREGNANCY, I WAS THERE.
ALL YOUR FRIENDS,
WHO THERE NOW?
I WAS THERE.
EVERY TIME YOU WAS THROWING UP,
I'M IN THE BATHROOM HOLDING YOUR
HAIR BACK!
>> WHOA, YOU NEED TO CALM DOWN
'CAUSE THIS--ALL THIS YELLING
AND THIS [bleep]--
>> DON'T [bleep] CRITICIZE
MY [bleep] RIGHT NOW.
>> YOU REALLY NEED TO CALM DOWN.
>> FOR WHAT?
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
YELLING AT ME LIKE THAT.
>> I YELL AT WHO THE [bleep]
I WANT TO YELL AT.
THAT'S THE WHOLE POINT OF BEING
WITH SOMEBODY, BECAUSE YOU TRUST
THEM, NOT BECAUSE YOU THINK THEY
GONNA SIT HERE AND [bleep]
SOMEBODY.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD THAT SAYING
BEFORE?
"YOU CAN TURN A [bleep]
INTO A HOUSEWIFE"?
>> [laughs]
HELL [bleep] NO.
HELL NO.
YOU JUST--
>> WHERE THE [bleep]--
>> LET ME GO.
LET GO!
[bleep].
>> I HATE YOU! OH!
>> I KNOW YOU HATE ME.
I KNOW YOU--
>> [bleep] YOU!
I HATE YOU, YOU [bleep] IDIOT!
I HATE YOU!
OOH, I HATE YOU!
>> STOP PUNCHING ME!
>> I HATE YOU!
>> STOP PUNCHING ME.
YOU'RE ACTING CRAZY!
[bleep] WRONG WITH YOU?
>> [sobbing]
>> AH, SHE SPIT UP.
>> [crying]
>> SINCE OUR BIG FIGHT,
JAMES HASN'T SLEPT HERE
FOR TWO NIGHTS.
I CAN SEE THAT ZA'KARIA
MISSES HER DADDY
BECAUSE SO DO I.
[shushes]
I HATE DOING THIS.
[phone ringing]
HELLO?
>> HEY, MARKAI.
>> HEY, DADDY.
>> YOU ARE?
>> YOU COMING OVER NOW?
>> YEAH.
>> WHY IS THIS A SURPRISE?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
YESTERDAY?
>> [laughs]
>> HEY, DADDY.
>> HOW YOU DOING?
LOVE YOU, BABY.
LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
YOU DOING OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
>> IT MADE ME PROUD TO SEE MY
DAD SO HAPPY TO BE A GRANDDADDY.
>> LOOK AT YOUR PRETTY SELF.
YES, YOU ARE ADORABLE.
YOU KNOW WHO THIS IS, DON'T YOU?
IT PA DADDY.
>> THIS IS A SHOCK THAT YOU'RE
HERE.
>> YEAH.
IT'S GOOD TO BE HERE, THOUGH.
>> HE ASKED WHERE JAMES WAS,
AND I HAD TO LET HIM KNOW
WE WERE HAVING SOME TROUBLES.
>> I TELL YOU, MARKAI.
WHEN I MARRIED YOUR MOTHER
AND WHEN WE HAD CHILDREN,
I DID NOT ASK FOR THIS
FOR MY KIDS.
I WANTED YOU GUYS TO LIVE
IN A WHOLESOME ENVIRONMENT
WHERE IT'S FULL OF LOVE.
AND WHEN YOU GUYS LEFT ME,
THAT HAPPY LITTLE GIRL,
I SAW YOUR FACE JUST CHANGE,
AND THAT HURT ME SO MUCH,
BECAUSE I KNEW THAT THERE WAS
A WALL NOW THAT WAS GONNA BE
BUILT UP AROUND YOU,
A BRICK WALL, THAT YOU COULDN'T
TRUST ANYMORE.
YOU WEREN'T GONNA TRUST NOBODY.
YOU WEREN'T GONNA LISTEN
TO ANYBODY.
YOU JUST CLOSED UP.
IF I HAVE NOT BEEN THERE FOR YOU
AS MUCH AS I SHOULD HAVE BEEN,
I APOLOGIZE, OKAY?
WITH YOU AND JAMES, IT WAS
A ROCKY ROAD, OKAY?
NOW YOU HAVE A BABY,
A BEAUTIFUL BABY--
DON'T CARE HOW YOU GUYS
CONCEIVED OR IF IT WAS
A MISTAKE OR NOT.
I DON'T CARE.
SHE'S NOT A MISTAKE.
SHE IS BEAUTIFUL AND GORGEOUS.
>> EVEN BEFORE I EVEN MET JAMES,
YOU KNOW, I DIDN'T EVEN PLAN
ON HAVING BABIES THIS EARLY.
I WAS THINKING WAY AFTER,
YOU KNOW, SCHOOL AND ALL THAT
STUFF, BUT I TOLD MYSELF
IF I WAS GONNA HAVE A BABY,
THAT BABY IS GONNA HAVE A DADDY,
NO MATTER WHAT.
I DON'T CARE IF WE'RE TOGETHER.
I DON'T CARE IF WE HATE
EACH OTHER.
I DON'T CARE.
THAT BABY IS GONNA BE
THAT MAN'S MAIN PRIORITY.
AND THAT'S WHO ZA'KARIA
IS TO JAMES.
JAMES CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT
ZA'KARIA.
>> RIGHT.
>> ME, HE CAN BE OKAY WITH.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
HE'LL BE ALL RIGHT WITHOUT ME.
WITHOUT HIS BABY...
>> * THIS AIN'T THE LIFE *
* I THOUGHT I'D LIVE *
* THIS AIN'T THE HOME *
* I'D HOPED WE'D MAKE *
* THIS AIN'T THE PATH *
* I THOUGHT I CHOSE *
* THIS AIN'T THE SKY *
* I'D HOPED WE'D SEE *
* THIS AIN'T THE TREE *
* I THOUGHT WOULD GROW *
* THIS AIN'T THE GOD *
* TO WHICH I PRAY *
>> IT IS HARD.
I'M NOT GONNA SIT UP HERE
AND LIE.
IT IS VERY HARD.
>> HEY, BIRTHDAY GIRL.
>> MY RELATIONSHIP WITH MY MOM
HAS CHANGED, AS I'M NOT AS OPEN
WITH HER AS I USED TO BE.
>> THERE THAT BE MY BABY GIRL.
>> GETTING PREGNANT PUSHED ME
AWAY.
SHE FELT LIKE I WAS GONNA BE
LIKE THESE OTHER TEENAGE MOMS
THAT SHE'S SEEN, AND THAT'S JUST
NOT THE WAY I AM.
ME AND MY MOM USED TO BE, LIKE,
THE BEST OF FRIENDS.
I USED TO TELL HER EVERYTHING.
I USED TO FEEL LIKE I COULD BE
OPEN WITH HER.
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE THERE'S
SOME STUFF THAT SHE NEEDS
TO KNOW AND SOME STUFF THAT
SHE DOESN'T.
[camera clicking]
>> THERE WE GO.
THERE WE GO.
GOOD. GOOD.
>> HI, THERE.
>> OH, I LIKE THAT.
LOOKING AT YOU, THAT'S CUTE.
>> YOU'RE SO CUTE.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> HI, MAMI!
AH, YEAH.
HI, MAMA.
>> THAT'S PERFECT.
>> A GIRL NEEDS HER FATHER,
BECAUSE WHATEVER HER FATHER
DOES, THAT'S WHAT SHE'S GONNA
LOOK INSIDE--FROM ANY MAN
OR ANY BOY THAT SHE'S WITH.
>> * THIS AIN'T THE END *
* I THOUGHT IT'D BE *
* ARE YOU SOMEONE *
* I'VE LOVED BEFORE? *
>> JAMES MIGHT NOT BE
THE PERFECT GUY.
LIKE I SAID, OBVIOUSLY,
I DID NOT KNOW THE WHOLE TRUTH,
BECAUSE I WOULD HAVE NEVER
THOUGHT YOU WOULD DO THAT TO ME.
>> YOU...
YOU SIT UP HERE AND ACT LIKE
I HAVEN'T EVEN CHANGED,
LIKE, FROM THE [bleep]
THAT YOU KNEW I DID BACK THEN.
LIKE, YOU ACT LIKE I HAVEN'T
EVEN, LIKE--I HAVEN'T EVEN
TRIED TO CHANGE OR I HAVEN'T
EVEN CHANGED A LITTLE BIT,
LIKE, AT ALL.
>> AND I'M SURELY NOT
THE PERFECT WOMAN.
>> YOU HIT ME.
WHAT YOU MEAN?
YOU HIT ME.
THAT'S HOW YOU SHOULD KNOW
I LOVE YOU.
>> I AIN'T HIT YOU HARD.
>> YOU HIT ME DEAD IN MY--
I COULD FEEL IT RIGHT HERE.
YOU HIT ME DEAD IN MY [bleep].
>> I'M JUST READY.
I'M READY TO STOP FIGHTING.
I'M READY TO STOP FUSSING,
ARGUING.
I WANT TO GIVE THIS THING
A CHANCE.
NOBODY HAS AN EASY ROAD AHEAD.
ME AND JAMES WILL HAVE BUMPS
IN OUR ROAD.
WE'RE ALWAYS GONNA HAVE
BUMPS IN OUR ROAD.
BUT AS LONG AS WE GET THROUGH
IT, WE'LL BE OKAY.
WITHOUT GETTING A FLAT TIRE,
WE'LL BE FINE.
>> * I CAN'T BE YOUR MAN *
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
>> THE ONE THING THAT'S
IMPORTANT TO ME IS THAT
AUSTIN HAS BOTH PARENTS.
>> HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE GETTING INTO.
>> YEP.
>> YOU MAY KISS THE BRIDE.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> HERE HE COMES.
>> WHOO!
>> DO YOU HAVE A PLAN?
>> YEAH, IT'S GONNA BE HARD,
BUT I HAVE TO GO TO SCHOOL.
I WANT TO HAVE A LIFE TOO.
>> WELL, YOU'RE BETTER
AT COOKING.
YOU'RE MORE EFFICIENT
AT CLEANING.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, YOU FAILED
THE MATH TEST.
>> I'M SO DEPRESSED SOMETIMES,
LIKE--
>> QUIT WHINING.