- *
- CHRISTINNA: I am Christinna.
I'm 17, and I grew up
in upstate New York.
My mom and I moved down
to Huntsville, Alabama,
when I was a junior,
and getting adjusted to the
South has been a challenge.
I don't know why they have
their mustaches down to here.
All they talk about
is football down here,
and I couldn't care less--
until I started dating Isiah,
the star of our high
school football team.
- [ding]
- CHRISTINNA: We were psyched
when Isiah got a scholarship
to play college football.
I graduated early
so I could go off
to college with him.
We have our futures
all mapped out.
I'm going to teach English
to inner-city kids,
and Isiah's going to the NFL.
The only problem
is that his grandma
is not a big fan
of our relationship.
- Christinna, you
will get to know me.
I do speak my mind.
- CHRISTINNA: All my plans
got turned upside down
when Isiah and I didn't
take off for college.
I moved into his mom's
house instead of the dorms,
and we snuck off and got
married on our own, because...
I'm pregnant.
- *
- ISIAH: [indistinct chatter]
- Look at these eggs.
- Is it expired?
- No, I looked at it.
- It's not?
They're just brown.
Sometimes it feels like Isiah
and I are just playing house.
But with our baby
just two months away,
we're forced to get serious.
We were only
dating for eight months
when I found out I was pregnant.
And even though it seemed quick,
we both thought getting married
was the best thing for our baby.
Isiah and I threw out any
idea of a traditional wedding,
including letting
any of Isiah's family
know about our decision,
and there's still
some bad feelings around that.
Isiah's high school
football days might be over,
but the team still drops by.
Luckily you couldn't see
Isiah's whole tux
in this picture.
- [laughter]
- You was pregnant
in that picture.
- I didn't know it, though.
I should've known.
I was being stupid.
- You went to the
bathroom, like, 10 times.
- CHRISTINNA: Probably.
- So did you know that she
was pregnant during the prom?
- I didn't know, man.
We found out she was
pregnant on my 18th birthday.
- That is horrible. Dang!
- That was, like, right after
I signed my scholarship,
about to graduate,
just turned 18.
Y'all, I found out
like that, man.
- What was your reaction
like when you saw it?
- I was crying, 'cause
I was thinking, like,
I can't do this,
that, that, that.
It's just done--
like, everything.
- Y'all feel like y'all
ready to be parents?
- We got no choice.
- I don't know, man.
Take it one day at a time now.
- CHRISTINNA: Even though we
all tried convincing him to go,
Isiah gave up his
football scholarship
to stay home with me,
and I can see he's
still heartbroken about it.
- [crowd cheering]
- CHRISTINNA: Now he's working
at a sandwich shop
until we can figure out
our next move.
Isiah's not the only one
who has to make sacrifices.
I gave up my senior year of
high school to graduate early.
And now I have to take a break
from community college
to have the baby.
My friends
still have a hard time
believing the whole situation.
- Did y'all just
not use protection?
Didn't feel like it?
Didn't want to?
- We did at first.
We used a condom maybe three
times, and it broke one day.
- Oh... were you
on birth control?
- CHRISTINNA: No.
I mean, I didn't
really know too much,
'cause I had never
had sex before.
So I was just, like, going
with the flow pretty much.
I wasn't paying no attention
like I should've been.
And... he just started
getting careless, I guess.
I don't know.
It's his fault, not mine.
- [laughter]
- No, I'm joking.
- What did your mom say
when you told her?
- I don't know.
It was weird.
I thought she was gonnna
spaz at me, but she didn't.
She was, like, real nice
about it and everything.
And then, like, I don't
know when Mother's Day was,
but she went out
and bought me, like,
some flowers and this
little fruit basket thing.
And she was like, "Happy
first Mother's Day!"
- [laughter]
- [ding]
- CHRISTINNA:
Unfortunately for me,
that was the last Mother's Day
we'd live in the same town.
My mom came down to Alabama
to help out a sick relative.
When they got better,
my mom packed up
and moved back
to upstate New York.
I miss her,
but it freaks me out
because now I'm totally
dependent on Isiah's family.
Since Isiah dropped his
scholarship and got married,
they're a little disappointed
in him and a lot mad at me.
His grandma Kathy is only
talking to me through Isiah.
- Last week, I told you to
tell Christinna that basically,
I'm not really sorry
for how I feel.
I'm sorry for treating her the
way I did when I found out,
you know what I mean?
Did you tell her?
- Yes, I did.
- I wasn't really mad at you.
What I was upset about
was the marriage.
Not that I'm against you
guys getting married,
'cause that would be
the right thing to do.
However, nowadays, come on.
You don't just-- people
don't-- 'cause you're pregnant,
they don't run on
and get married.
- I don't talk much,
'cause it just hurts.
I'm not happy.
I'm disappointed.
I mean, I still don't believe
you guys really know
what you've really
gotten yourself into.
What are you plans?
Why did you want to get married?
That's the real reason
you should've got married.
I haven't heard neither
one of y'all say that ever.
You had a scholarship
to college.
- That didn't feel like it
was the right decision.
- You just didn't want to go.
- No, it was not the feelings.
It was, like...
being there for
my child, though.
- KATHY: How are you gonna feel
if she ain't yours?
Isiah,
I'm just gonna look at you
and tell you just like this.
Where are you now?
You didn't have to be here.
And not only are you here,
you brought something with you.
- [claps]
- [sobs]
- CHRISTINNA: After the way
I was treated by his family
last night, Isiah's
acting extra nice.
I understand they're upset about
what's happened to his plans,
but this isn't how I planned
my senior year either.
I definitely don't feel
welcome in this house anymore,
and it's putting a
strain on the two of us.
I don't know if I resent
you 'cause I'm pregnant,
and not want to be,
because it's just kind of...
you've ruined everything
that I wanted for me or you.
- You don't think like
that, like it's ruined, man.
It's just delayed.
18 years from now, I'll be 36.
She'll be graduating
high school.
Say that's the only kid.
36 is still young.
You can still go get your
degree, still travel the world.
- But you can't get
your teenage years back.
- We both can't say anything
until she's actually born.
We'll look into her
eyes and be like, wow.
It's, like, really
important to me
to actually try
to make it work, though.
- *
- [indistinct chatter]
- I think I'm good
on this other stuff.
- CHRISTINNA: My friends are
throwing me a shower today.
They're hoping it's going to
cheer me up after the drama
last night with Isiah's family.
- Smile!
- [laughter]
- [gasps] There's a fly
on it and it won't move!
- That's gross.
- You've buried it.
- [laughter]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Is it hard being
away from your family?
- Yeah, 'cause my mom always
took care of me and everything.
And now I gotta
depend on Isiah.
- Is his family acting
any better about it?
- A little bit, but not really.
- CHASITY: Does it really matter
since the things
they said to you?
I mean, it wouldn't matter to
me if my baby's dad's parents
were acting any better after
the things they said.
- I don't know.
- I wouldn't forgive them.
- I really don't.
But you know,
I can't do that forever.
But I can now.
- [laughs]
- Ow.
- Is she moving?
- She's, like, poking me.
- [laughter]
- [gasps]
Oh my goodness!
Feel it!
You have to push in
a little bit.
Do you feel her?
- CHRISTINNA: We're
having a girl,
and we're naming her Destiny.
Isiah and I are
on my way to the doctor's
for my 32-week checkup.
With the way I was
treated last night,
it's clear to me we're going to
have to get a place of our own.
Every extra penny needs
to go to our apartment,
but Isiah's sitting there
thinking about
a new exhaust system.
But you can't
get pipes on your car.
- Why can't I?
- It's, like, a waste of money.
- To you it is.
- What do you need pipes for?
- Personal enjoyment.
- That's ridiculous.
- Pleasure.
- That is selfish.
- You think everything's stupid
if it has nothing
to do with you.
It's honestly stupid.
- The bigger picture
is you have a baby,
and the baby needs
to be taken care of.
- Cold jelly here.
Alright, let's see.
- CHRISTINNA: Oh, wow.
I'm just wondering who
she's gonna look like.
I think she's gonna
look like Isiah
because they say whoever
you think about the most,
that's who your baby
will come out looking like.
Isiah's paycheck from the
sandwich shop doesn't go far,
and he's only left with
$50 to cover our groceries.
I think we can buy about six
things in this store for $50.
- Okay, we got some croutons.
Aw, what the heck!
That is the biggest
bottle of hot sauce
I think I've ever seen.
- Are you keeping track of
how much all this costs?
- [snickers]
- [scanner beeping]
- $2.78.
- ISIAH: 15...
- CHRISTINNA: This
is embarrassing.
We don't even have enough
money to feed two people,
let alone three.
- KATRINA: Look in the back.
It should be in
the back of Sports.
- CHRISTINNA: I've been bugging
Isiah to get us out from under
his mom's roof, but he's got
to his finances in order first.
- KATRINA: If your rent is 585,
you're gonna need about $1,500.
Hey, get an ink pen
and start marking.
- So you make how much a month?
- ISIAH: Let's go with 900.
- 900? Are you sure?
- ISIAH: Yeah.
- CHRISTINNA: Okay, 900 a month.
The one apartment was 515.
So Mr. Math Man,
what's 900 minus 515?
- ISIAH: We're gonna go to 485.
I am that good at math.
Oh, no.
It's gonna be 385.
- CHRISTINNA: Well, dang.
- ISIAH: 385, that's right.
- CHRISTINNA: And the utilities,
that would be, I'd say,
around $100.
That'll leave you
with 285 to spend a month.
- Okay, you can subtract 80 from
that, 'cause my insurance %80.
Subtract another 80 from that,
'cause that'll probably be
my gas for the month.
- Leaves you with 125 a month.
For us to get a
decent apartment,
it's going to be a stretch.
But this place seems cool.
And over the phone, the realtor
said she'd work with us.
- And you said y'all
were looking
to get into an apartment
pretty quick?
- CHRISTINNA: Yes,
as soon as possible.
- TINA: Alright.
- That's not bad.
This really ain't bad.
And this is 515?
- TINA: Yes, Sir.
- This really-- wow,
this is a huge closet.
- Yeah, that's
our third bedroom.
- Oh my goodness.
- Picnic table.
- TINA: Yeah, we've got
picnic areas
located all over the property.
We've got a playground,
which it's gonna be a while
before you need the playground.
I mean, it's peaceful
here, it's quiet.
It'd be a nice place
to raise a family.
- I like that it's quiet.
It's really nice.
- We have a $30 application fee.
We will run the credit,
and that also will determine
your security deposit.
Hmm.
Okay, unfortunately it
did come back denied.
Um, is there anyone else
that would be willing
to help you out, or...
- I don't have any
family in Alabama.
- I mean, all I can tell
you is just, you know,
keep your head high and
try again, you know?
Just see if you can get some
help, and then come back,
and we will do anything
we can to help you out.
Y'all have a great day.
- You, too.
- Well, we back on--
back looking again.
- * Looking for
the great escape *
- CHRISTINNA: Just because
we're going to be parents,
everyone expects
us to be adults.
But the reality is
we're still kids.
How are we supposed
to become a family
if we can't even
get our own place?
- *
- CHRISTINNA: I'm finishing
up all my classes,
and it's just in time,
because with my baby due
in less than a month,
my head is no
longer here in school.
- "100 Questions
About Your Pregnancy."
- Look at that.
- Um, "Nipples...
"Tenderness is a very common
early sign of pregnancy,
"and may occur
in 80% to 90% of women
as early as five to six weeks."
- That was very true.
- What if you have
to have a C-section?
- Yeah, you'd have a nasty scar.
- When babies are born
that need a C-section,
you can't hold them
until after they
stitch you back
up and everything.
You just get to look at them.
I'd want to hold my baby.
"Circumcision."
- Are you gonna get
your baby circumcised?
- It's a girl.
- Yeah-- but it's a girl.
- [laughter]
- *
- CHRISTINNA: I want
to breastfeed Destiny.
It's healthier for her, not
to mention that it's free.
- * Lactation!
- CHRISTINNA: My doctor
recommended I take a class.
- Hey, what's lactation?
Do you really know?
- It has to do with milk, so
I'm assuming breastfeeding.
- *
- GLENNI: So let's look at
the positions for nursing.
This is the football hold.
Tuck her little arm
around your waist,
and you bring baby up
and on to the breast.
But we're gonna just try
the three basic positions.
So the first one, the
cradle hold like this.
And this arm supporting
your breast, thumb on top,
fingers below.
See how much control you've got?
It feels real
secure, doesn't it?
- Yeah.
- GLENNI: How much time
are you gonna have off?
Are you wanting to get back
right when school starts?
- Whatever they'll let me do.
- GLENNI: Alright, you
are going back to school,
so you are gonna be pumping
at school, probably.
If you're wanting to breastfeed
and go back to school,
one of the best things that
you can invest in probably
is a decent breast pump.
Looks like a backpack.
And what we can do is talk
to your school counselor,
and I'd be happy
to intervene here
and do anything I can to help.
Very good.
I've got a bra box up front.
I'll measure you, and then
you get to go through the box
and you can pick out two bras.
We've got several over here.
- Looks way too big.
- [crickets chirping]
- Did y'all miss me?
- No, we did not miss you.
- CHRISTINNA: Isiah's twin
sister's visiting from college.
We had big plans to go off
and room together
before I got pregnant.
It depresses me to know
I should be at school with her
instead of being here,
studying lactation.
- We had planned this.
You were gonna go to A&M.
We were gonna stay in the
same dorm and everything.
When you got pregnant, you
couldn't do that no more.
I mean, I like my roommate now,
but I wish you were my roommate.
- [laughs]
- [door shuts]
- Where he going?
- It's a good question.
- How much for the speakers?
- Uh, what did we say?
Like, 380?
Alright.
- Cool.
- Alright, man.
Take it easy.
- You, too.
- [door opens]
- Who was that?
Who was that?
- ISIAH: Boy.
- Huh?
- Boy.
- Who was that?
- Jason. You just gave
Jason the money.
- I don't have any money.
I got all the money I got.
- What did you do?
- I'm doing something.
- Mm-hmm.
- Doing what?
- He's doing something
to my system.
- CHRISTINNA: What?
- ISIAH: Something
to my system.
- What is he doing
to your system?
- ISIAH: He's
hooking something up.
- Why don't you just tell me
so I'll stop asking
all these questions?
See, Isiah has $300
left from his check,
and he wants to spend when we
gotta buy all this baby stuff.
It's, like, a month left 'till
the baby's about to be born.
Isiah don't give a damn
about nobody but himself.
I'm going to be a single mother.
- There's a lot
of hostility here.
- *
- Where are my keys at?
You put it in, Jason?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, gosh.
I'm about to wake some
people up at night.
- CHRISTINNA: Finding out
Isiah took the money
we were supposed to be saving
and blew it on
speakers for his car
really makes me want to
rethink this marriage.
After last night, I needed to
get out of Isiah's mom's house
and clear my head.
- I mean, you used to be happy.
It isn't a child
that'll make you happy.
You're eight months
pregnant right now.
And I love Isiah to death.
But he really needs to, like,
get his priorities in order
because you have no
family down here.
- Exactly!
- CHASITY: Like,
he is your husband.
He's the only person.
- CHRISTINNA: And now I'm, like,
completely dependent on him,
and he's not taking
care of me in any way.
I mean, I'm not saying
he has to, like,
pay for me all the time, get
my hair did, my nails done,
and all that stuff.
But he's supposed
to take care of me.
Like, if I wasn't pregnant,
I would just been like,
adios, bye, I'll see you later!
- Are you gonna try to
make it work for Destiny?
- I really don't even know.
'Cause, like, I don't believe
in getting divorced at all.
- I mean, you don't
want to get a divorce,
but it's the rest of your life.
- Exactly.
I can't just throw
my whole life away.
And I don't want me being
miserable to affect my daughter.
And then she's
gonna be miserable.
I don't know what to do.
Whatever I'm going to do,
Isiah's going to have
to be a part of it somehow.
He's Destiny's father,
and now he's my husband.
No matter how mad I am,
we have to sit down and
discuss this like grownups.
You know what I'm saying?
I just want to understand how
you think you can afford
to spend money on speakers
when there's...
so much stuff we gotta buy.
If you'd rather spend
your money however you want,
on whatever you want, you
just need to tell me that.
- ISIAH: I just feel like
you're sitting back and relaxing
and pointing the
finger and criticizing.
Look, I would understand,
like, if you were working
and doing the
same thing I'm doing,
then it'd be a better argument.
- What do you mean?
- My girl, she out there trying,
so I need to start
trying harder.
- But the way it is right now
is you're the one
with a job and I don't.
You have a problem
with taking care of me.
And basically right now, I
need you to take care of me.
If you don't want to do that,
then I don't need to be here.
- I don't have a problem
taking care of you.
- CHRISTINNA: You do, because
you don't want to do nothing.
- You're always just
talking about leaving,
so what do you going to do?
- I'm saying I'm not
about to stay here and...
have to live like this--
- Hold on, this is
so bad, isn't it?
What's up?
The fact that she, your
daughter, your baby,
should be your number one
priority, and she's not,
and that's what worries me.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: If Isiah
doesn't come around
and see things my way,
I'm going to have to
start looking at my options.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: As our
due date gets closer,
Isiah seems like he's getting
serious about taking care of me
and the baby.
Do you feel like
you're going to
take your responsibility
more serious?
- I know really wasn't, like,
doing all I could, of course.
I was, like-- I was being 50%.
I wasn't being 100.
I'm 100 now.
No, I take that back.
I'm twice.
I'm twice as ready.
I'm about 151, 200 now.
- CHRISTINNA: Isiah meant it.
He went out
and found us an apartment
where they are more
understanding of our finances.
- We don't do a
credit check here.
We just need a proof of
income, and it'll be fine.
- CHRISTINNA: It might not be
everything I was looking for,
but it sets me free from
Isiah's family's house,
and that's all I care about.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: Well, dang!
Who squished my lamp?
- *
- You ready to go?
- [grunts]
- CHRISTINNA: It feels good
to know Isiah and I
are making a fresh start.
And he got us into our
new place just in time,
because my due date
is a week away.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: We're going in
for what's supposed to be
my last doctor's visit
before I deliver Destiny.
- Hello!
- CHRISTINNA: After my checkup,
Dr. Carlota decided
we are potentially three days
away from delivery.
- He'll be home
before Christmas.
- WOMAN: Y'all have
a good Christmas.
- You, too.
- *
- KATRINA: Christinna,
we have an appointment!
Isiah, you're gonna be late
for your own child's birth.
Let's go.
- CHRISTINNA:
Isiah's mom and I
put aside the tension
between us.
She wants to be there
for Destiny's birth.
- I need a-- I need a--
I misplaced my car keys.
- CHRISTINNA; Isiah
is as nervous as hell.
- Do you have the baby bag?
- ISIAH: I knew
she had found you.
Where are my car keys at?
- Hurry up.
We'll be late.
- Hold on.
- CHRISTINNA: I thought I'd
be freaking out a lot more,
but I'm actually just
excited to meet my baby.
- Alright, you ready?
When you get your Pitocin
started, it has to, like,
drip into this, you know?
- CHRISTINNA: It took a few
hours for the contractions
to start, and it was the most
pain I've ever experience.
[groans]
My contractions came on strong.
[breathes deeply]
[moans]
The pain was so bad,
I had to get an epidural.
And now I'm in kind of a haze.
- You feeling better
with that epidural?
Okay, good.
We are 5 centimeters dilated
and about 80% thinned out.
That's pretty good.
The baby's coming down.
- CHRISTINNA: After a
whole day of waiting,
I was finally dilated
enough to start pushing.
- NURSE: You feel it? Okay.
- Push, one, two,
three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
All into your bottom.
Push, seven, eight, nine.
Quick breath, and push again.
- DR. CARLOTA: It's not moving.
- Did you say it wasn't moving?
- Well, it comes down a little,
then comes right back up.
It's not-- it hasn't
moved much yet.
- And grab.
Keep it going.
Keep it going, you got it.
Keep going, keep going.
Keep it going.
- NURSES: Seven,
eight, nine, ten.
- Are you able to
feel anything yet?
- DR. CARLOTA: If it's
not coming this way,
you know which way we
might have to get the baby.
It's okay.
It's not failure or anything.
You're doing fine.
The baby's doing fine.
These things, we just never
know until we're here.
- CHRISTINNA: After
pushing for over an hour,
the doctor knew I was exhausted,
and was trying to prepare me
for a C-section.
But I'm going to fight
as hard as I can
before I even consider that.
- Push hard.
Two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
- CHRISTINNA: But it
just wasn't working.
- NURSE: I know.
- *
- NURSE: Come on, go, push!
Don't hurt your back.
Curl up over that baby.
Curl up just like that.
Push, push, push...
- CHRISTINNA: Even though
I'm totally exhausted,
I wanted to give it one last
shot before they cut me open.
- NURSE: Do it again
just like that.
Push, push, push.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Come on, push it, push it,
push it, push it, push it.
- [pants]
- Show him how good
you've been pushing for me.
Come on, push!
- DR. CARLOTA: Go ahead.
- Give it all you got.
- Where are we at?
- Right there.
Is that where it
was or is it lower?
- DR. CARLOTA: I'd
just leave it--
- [moans]
- NURSE: Can we give
her something for pain?
'Cause she can't push.
She's having a hard time.
- CHRISTINNA: I was totally
against having a C-section.
But after 26 hours of labor, I
feel like it's my only option.
- Come on, Isiah.
- *
- There she is.
- CHRISTINNA: Aww!
- Keep smiling.
- NURSE: Congratulations!
- NURSE: You're a pretty
little Christmas baby.
She has not cried.
Say, "I'm not a crier!"
Alright!
Little Miss Destiny's
going to see Mama!
- ISIAH: Say hi, Mom.
Man, who does it?
Who does it all the time?
That's me.
- Feel good?
- [laughter]
- DESTINY: [cries]
- *
- CHRISTINNA: I'm doing the
first diaper change on my own.
This is all going to
be a learning process.
It's good Destiny looks
like a patient baby.
Now that I'm on my feet,
I'm reminded that
I just had major surgery.
- *
- Okay, there it
is, there it is.
Tired of being locked
up, aren't you?
Don't cry. Oh!
- CHRISTINNA: Along with
nervousness and exhaustion,
I'm in a daze from
the pain meds I need
for the stitches in my belly.
Isiah is being super attentive
and trying to help
with all he can.
After a bathroom break and a
feeding, I can finally rest.
- Are you tired still?
- Yeah.
- Going to bed?
- ISIAH: If she starts
crying, just yell.
- DESTINY: [cries]
- CHRISTINNA: I wish I had
some guidance for this.
I don't feel comfortable calling
on Isiah's family for help,
and my mom could only be so
much help from 800 miles away.
- [cries]
[cries]
- *
- [alarm clock beeps]
- CHRISTINNA: Isiah's
pitching in as much as he can,
but money's tight for us,
and he has to up his hours.
On the fourth day, he
had to go back to work.
Now that I'm seeing
what our lives are like
with Destiny here,
I'm wondering how we're
ever going to do all this
and get back to school
like we had planned.
- CHASITY: Hi
there, pretty girl!
How are things between
you and Isiah going?
- They're going good.
- Does he still
work a whole bunch?
- Mm-hmm.
- Does he help change diapers?
- Yeah.
I don't really like him
changing diapers, though,
'cause I'd be like,
"You missed something."
- [laughs]
- I don't know, I'm weird.
- Are you going to go
to school this semester?
- Yeah, do the summer semester.
- What are y'all
goinna do with her?
- I don't know.
- I couldn't even imagine having
a baby and going to school.
That'd be, like, way
too much to handle.
- CHRISTINNA: If I'm at
school and Isiah's at work,
there's no one to watch Destiny.
It's starting
to make me resentful
that Isiah gets to leave the
house while I'm stuck here.
- You like being a mom now?
- [mumbles]
I don't like it or dislike it.
It's not fun doing
all that crap.
It's not that bad, but it's
just not really interesting,
unless you stay here
and take care of the baby.
I can go to school, and
[unintelligible] all day long.
- [ding]
- CHRISTINNA: I can sit and
dream about getting my degree
and teaching inner-city kids,
but the reality is
I'm a full-time mom and now.
And without help, I'm going to
have to give up school for now.
- WOMAN: You may be asked
if there's a daycare.
- Hi, I'm calling because I want
to take the semester off
because I just had a baby.
- WOMAN: Okay, Miss, can I get
your Social Security number?
- CHRISTINNA: I had no idea
I was going to have to give up
so much to be a mom.
- WOMAN: How old is she?
- CHRISTINNA: Two months old.
- She's sweet! Aww!
We do have a special today.
It's a $5 pork plate.
- CHRISTINNA: I'm not happy
that being a mom
is forcing me to delay college.
Chasity is bummed, too.
She was my best
friend in high school,
and knows how important my goal
of being an English teacher
is to me.
I just think the reason I wanted
to be an English teacher
is 'cause I went to
this school in Rochester.
It was, like,
a city-city school.
And there were so many
illiterate people,
it was ridiculous.
I was like, if only my
English teacher was better,
'cause she would just
sit around and did nothing.
- That's good.
I mean, you want to
help other people.
- Everybody has a
purpose in life.
I didn't think my purpose
was to take care of a baby
before I had her.
Like, that wasn't my life plan.
Like, I was born on this
earth to take care of kids.
No.
I'm not going to
give up on my dreams.
But with Destiny, it's going
to take me longer to get
where I want to go.
Isiah's had to give up a
lot for our baby as well.
This is the first year he hasn't
been on a football field
since he was five years old.
And I know that working at
a sandwich shop full time
is not exactly fulfilling
Isiah's dreams.
- [crowd cheering]
- * I have my chest doubled
*
* I have my chest
falling down *
- What's up, man?
I mean, how everything
going with the fam?
- Finances ain't good.
- TONY: Finances is never good.
So what's up, man?
What you thinking, man?
- I don't know, man.
It's just a lot of decisions
I gotta make here next year.
So, the clock is running
out on a lot of stuff, man.
I watched our
football highlight film.
Haven't watched it in a year.
Man, every time I
watched it, like, man,
I can still be that
guy on that tape.
- Don't rely on this
football thing, dude.
- ISIAH:
I'm not gonna rely on it.
That's the only thing
I've ever been good at.
- The football thing, that
should be in the thinking,
but that should be last.
You need to think about
what you gonna do about you,
the baby, and the money for it.
- So how did everything change
just 'cause
she got pregnant, though?
Really?
I mean, what would've been worse
if I still took the scholarship?
We probably still would've
been right where we at now.
I never saw this
for myself, man.
- You gonna talk to Christinna
bout what you've been saying?
I mean, what you've
been talking about?
- I don't know, really.
I might and I might not.
- *
- Whoa!
- Oh, is it a lot?
- Yeah.
- CHRISTINNA: Oh, gosh.
Lift up her foot.
- It went right up the diaper.
- Really?
- Are you using all the wipes?
Gosh, these things aren't free.
I sense something's
bugging Isiah.
And even when we do get
a rare moment alone,
we aren't really talking.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: Most of
the day, Isiah works,
and Destiny and
I are on our own.
When he does get free time,
he's been spending more
of it at his mom's house.
They all love Destiny, but I
don't exactly feel welcome.
But tonight, after
he gets off of work,
I'm meeting him over
there for dinner.
It's the first time
we're all getting together
since Destiny was born,
and I'm trying
not to be nervous about it.
- When you off this week?
- Thursday.
- What's wrong with you?
- [mutters]
- He's frustrated.
- I'm not frustrated.
- I can tell!
- Get on top of the situation?
- I know.
If I just say forget it
and walk away, I mean,
what was the hell my purpose
of staying here, you know?
Giving up my scholarship if I'm
just gonna walk away that easy.
I at least
wanted to give it a shot
with me, her, and the baby.
- I feel like you could
be there for the baby.
You don't have to
be there for her.
- KATRINA: I feel
she'll make that difficult.
- I feel we still
should have a DNA test.
She knows that she's
the baby momma for sure.
But there's always a doubt
there, and we all know that.
- Come to find out
it ain't yours,
then you've been going
through this for no reason.
Then I would be mad.
- Get that over with,
'cause if that ain't yours,
it's gonna be some
rumble in the jungle.
When Christinna and I was
arguing a long time ago,
she told me, "Soon
as the baby's born,
"I'm gonna get a DNA test and
I'm gonna bring it over there
and slap you in the face."
I'm still waiting for that slap.
I've been waiting on that
slap since December 22,
'cause I wanna know, you
know what I'm saying?
And you wanna know.
Stop playing.
- 39.99 at the drugstore.
One swab on your cheek,
one swap on her cheek.
Then we all know.
That's it.
Yes, I want to do this.
No, I don't.
- KATHY: You ain't scared?
- ISIAH: Of what?
- I got your back.
- I mean, really, it's
not gonna hurt anything.
- Alright, I'll just go get it.
- *
- [crickets chirping]
- CHRISTINNA: When we
sat down for dinner,
I was starting to wish
I hadn't come at all.
Last time Isiah's grandma
and I had dinner together,
it didn't go so well.
I had a bad feeling
about coming this time,
and now I'm wishing I hadn't.
- The only thing that's
bothering me
is Christinna told me,
when we were arguing,
she said she was
gonna get a DNA test,
and she's gonna come over and
slap me in the face with it.
And I haven't got that.
How come y'all haven't
posted that on my door?
Or does that not matter anymore?
- It don't matter to me.
- KATHY: No, it
don't matter to you.
You already know it's your baby.
- CHRISTINNA: I
know it's his baby.
- You were going
to do that for me.
You said that.
- I know.
- Can we do it?
- CHRISTINNA: I don't
see the point.
- KATHY: Why?
- CHRISTINNA: Because
I don't want to.
I know whose baby it is,
and that's all
that's important to me.
There's no possible way it
could be anybody else's baby.
- You know that beyond
a shadow of a doubt.
Just saying, we would
like to know that, too.
- I mean, that's up to him.
It's not anybody else's
baby but mine and his.
If he has a doubt in his
mind, then I'll gladly do it.
But if he doesn't have a
problem with it, then...
- I don't want to air
out your dirty laundry--
- There is no dirty laundry.
I've had sex with one person,
and there's no possible way
it could be anybody else's baby.
- It depends on
what you call sex.
- No other man's [bleep]
has entered my [bleep]
except for his.
If you think that
that's not his baby,
then have nothing
to do with her.
I don't really care.
- That's fine.
I don't have to have
anything to do with her.
But I do have to have
something to do with him.
- Okay, I'm just saying.
- It shouldn't be a big deal.
- But it is to me.
- Do you want to go on
and on, years to come,
with this doubt
in your mind that maybe
that baby could not be mine?
Or do you want to know?
- ISIAH: I guess every man
could say whenever their child
is born, they want to
know, period, though.
There's not one man that
can probably say they don't.
- So what are you saying?
- We can just do it.
I mean, there really ain't no
doubt in my mind, you know?
- DEVON: Are you sure?
- I mean, 'cause I'm 110%.
- Well, then the test
don't matter, do it?
Is the answer no?
- Let's see what
I got in my purse.
- WOMAN: What?
- I can't read, but
y'all gotta read it.
- *
- Well.
Well.
- KATHY: And I've got my answer.
I don't need a DNA test now.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: I've got
nothing to hide from anybody.
I know who Destiny's father is.
But I'm not going to sit there
and let me and my daughter
be insulted by Isiah's
crazy grandma.
After leaving
Isiah's mom's house,
I felt like leaving the whole
family behind me forever.
But to leave Isiah's family
is to leave Isiah as well,
which I don't want to do.
- [crickets chirping]
- [birds chirping]
- CHRISTINNA:
Isiah felt really bad
about the way
things went that night.
He's made it clear to his family
that some issues
have to be handled
just between the two of us.
- How do you feel?
- I asked you first.
- I think that if we both
try and we both want to work,
it'll last as long as
we both want it to.
If we both don't try, then
we're not gonna get very far.
It's back to you.
Effort on both parts.
She's eating my shoulder.
- I think as long as
both of us try, we will.
But you know if we both try,
it's still gonna be hard,
though.
I can just say that.
- It's always gonna be hard...
until we're, like, 60 and old.
- Hell, we ain't even got too
much stuff we can do but try.
And we're still here.
- Yeah.
- *
- CHRISTINNA: Getting pregnant
at such a young age
was difficult.
It brought a lot
of extra stress.
You have to worry about
a lot more things
that you usually
wouldn't have to worry about
if you were just a normal,
typical teenage girl.
I think Isiah's
family blames me
for him not taking
his scholarship.
If I was a mother and my
son got a girl pregnant,
and he had a scholarship to
go play college football,
I'd probably feel
resentful, too.
- That's the one.
You was, like, two months.
- ISIAH: This is her
when she was two months.
Same eyes, same nose.
- CHRISTINNA: If Isiah wants a
paternity test, he can have one.
I just feel that's something
for me and him
to deal with and decide on.
And if he wanted one,
he should've been a man
and asked me for one by himself.
I'm going to college
no matter what.
And I'm going to
graduate no matter what,
so I always know that I'll be
able to provide in my way
for our family.
And Isiah can be a
stay-at-home dad.
- Hi, mom, me.
- CHRISTINNA: Me and Isiah's
relationship, it's okay.
It could be a lot better, but
it could be a lot worse, too.
If it works, that's great.
If it doesn't work, life will
be okay, and it will go on.
- *
- FEMALE ANNOUNCER: On the
next "16 and Pregnant."
- It makes me sad, having
to grow up sometimes.
- [gunshot]
- I was never
disappointed in you.
It's really gonna be hard on me.
- What are your plans?
Because I feel real strong
about not moving in together
until you're married.
- Kayla, will you marry me?
- KAYLA: I don't want
to feel on my wedding day
that I'm getting married
because we had a baby.
- I want to support my family.
- I'm not moving.
- *
* Go these nine awful weeks
* Don't know how I'm gonna
get through it all *
* I'm weak, but I'm
strong enough to see *
- [car horn honking]
- *