>> THEY STARTED OFF AS CAREFREE
TEENAGERS, AND THEN, IN THE
BLINK OF AN EYE, THEY BECAME
YOUNG ADULTS WITH THE WEIGHT OF
THE WORLD ON THEIR SHOULDERS.
BEING PREGNANT IS HARD ENOUGH,
BUT BEING 16 AND PREGNANT
MAKES YESTERDAY'S PROBLEMS SEEM,
WELL, SEEM TRIVIAL.
HOW DID THESE TEN GIRLS DO IT?
WHAT DID THEY LEARN ALONG THE
WAY?
AND WHAT DOES THE FUTURE HOLD
FOR THEM, THEIR HOME LIVES,
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY, THEIR
BABIES?
THIS IS THE 16 AND PREGNANT
FINALE SPECIAL: LIFE AFTER
LABOR.
[applause]
[upbeat piano music]
♪
>> ♪ GO THESE NINE AWFUL WEEKS
♪ DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
♪ GET THROUGH IT ALL
♪
[applause]
>> HI, I'M DR. DREW, AND BEFORE
WE DIVE INTO THESE TEN STORIES,
I'D LIKE TO WELCOME OUR TEN
TEENAGE MOMS HERE.
THEY'VE JOINED US TOGETHER IN
ONE PLACE FOR THE VERY FIRST
TIME.
HERE THEY ARE:
KIANNA, KAYLA,
ALLIE, JORDAN,
IZABELLA, TAYLOR,
JAMIE, JENNIFER,
CLEONDRA, AND DANIELLE.
WELCOME TO THE SHOW, ALL OF YOU
GUYS.
ONCE AGAIN, THIS SEASON WE
WITNESSED THE MIRACLE OF
CHILDBIRTH AND ALL THE PROBLEMS
THAT ARISE WHEN KIDS AREN'T
READY TO BE GROWN-UPS,
LET ALONE PARENTS.
THERE WERE MARRIAGE PROPOSALS,
HEALTH ISSUES, SIBLING
RIVALRIES, MISCOMMUNICATIONS,
BETRAYAL.
HERE NOW IS A QUICK RECAP OF
THIS SEASON'S 16 AND PREGNANT.
>> MOM.
I THINK IT'S TIME.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> ONE, TWO, THREE.
>> WASN'T USING A CONDOM, BIRTH
CONTROL?
>> WE DIDN'T USE EITHER.
>> SO DO YOU GUYS ALREADY KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE HAVING?
>> TWO BOYS.
>> TWO BOYS? OH.
>> WHEN I WAS 13, I WAS
HOSPITALIZED FOR ANOREXIA.
I'M FAT.
>> YOU'RE NOT FAT.
YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> SHE ALWAYS STILL WANTS TO BE
MY NUMBER ONE PERSON, BUT I'M
NOT ALLOWED TO BE HERS ANYMORE.
>> YOU WILL ALWAYS BE HER
SISTER.
>> I FEEL LIKE I SACRIFICE MORE
THAN YOU DO.
I'M STUCK AT HOME WITH HER
ALMOST 24-7.
>> YOUR BACK DON'T HURT; YOUR
FEET DON'T SWELL; YOUR BOOBS
DON'T GET BIG;
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PEE 24-7.
>> I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
>> A MOTHER LETTING HER DAUGHTER
LIVE WITH HER BOYFRIEND WOULD
MAKE ME A PIECE OF [bleep] MOM.
>> YOU STILL THINKING ABOUT
ADOPTING?
WHAT DOES ZAK WANT YOU TO DO?
>> NOT ADOPTION.
>> YOU NEED TO START...
>> BEING MORE RESPONSIBLE?
>> YEAH.
>> I JUST FEEL REALLY WEAK.
NOW I'M SERIOUSLY SCARED.
>> AND...PUSH.
>> WHY SHOULD I TAKE CARE OF
YOU?
YOU AIN'T MY DAUGHTER.
>> I DON'T CARE.
>> GET THE [bleep] OUT!
>> YOU'RE LUCKY YOU EVEN MADE IT
TO THE DAMN BIRTH.
>> THIS WHOLE SITUATION IS WHY I
SAID THAT CHILD NEEDED TO BE PUT
UP FOR ADOPTION.
>> YOU HIT WITH IT, JOSH!
>> NO, I DID NOT.
>> YEAH, YOU DID.
[siren wailing]
>> SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR KIDS,
JOSH.
YOU WILL NEVER SEE THEM AGAIN.
[applause]
>> WELL, WELL, WELL, HUH?
OKAY, GUYS.
NOW, TOWARDS THE END OF THE
SEASON, MANY OF YOU, YOUR
RELATIONSHIPS WERE SORT OF KIND
OF WORKING OUT.
HOW MANY AT THE END OF YOUR
SHOW, YOUR RELATIONSHIPS WERE
INTACT?
HOW MANY OF YOU NOW FIND THESE
RELATIONSHIPS TO BE ON THE
ROCKS?
INTERESTING.
NOW, KAYLA, YOU USED TO HEAR
OTHER BABIES CRYING AND WONDER
"WHY CAN'T THE MOTHER POSSIBLY
GET THAT KID UNDER CONTROL?"
HOW HARD IS IT NOW FOR YOU?
>> WHEN THEY'RE OUT IN PUBLIC
AND THEY'RE SCREAMING, LIKE, I
DON'T THINK ABOUT IT AS MUCH AS,
LIKE, WHEN I SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
LIKE, IF HE'S CRYING IN PUBLIC,
LIKE, I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT HIM
CRYING.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE HIM FEEL
BETTER, AND I DON'T REALLY CARE,
LIKE, WHO SEES ANYMORE.
>> HOW HARD IS IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT'S PRETTY HARD, ISN'T IT?
I HAD BABIES. IT'S HARD.
>> YEAH.
>> IZABELLA, IT TOOK 14 HOURS
UNTIL YOU WERE EVEN READY TO
PUSH.
HOW MUCH HARDER WAS LABOR THAN
YOU EXPECTED?
>> IT WAS--YEAH, IT WAS REALLY
PAINFUL, AND...
BUT THE ONLY THING THAT, I
GUESS, I WASN'T READY FOR
WAS, LIKE, GETTING AN EPIDURAL
AND, LIKE, EVERYTHING, 'CAUSE NO
ONE REALLY PREPARES YOU FOR HOW
BAD IT REALLY DOES HURT AND HOW
HARD IT IS TO PUSH.
>> OKAY.
ALLIE, YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T WORRY
ABOUT GETTING PREGNANT BECAUSE
YOU WERE ON THE PILL.
BUT THE PILL HAS TO BE TAKEN
PROPERLY FOR IT TO WORK.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT BIRTH
CONTROL NOW?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I AM ALWAYS UP-TO-DATE WITH MY
STUFF, THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> YOU FEEL THERE'S NO ROOM FOR
ERROR ANYMORE.
>> YES.
I DIDN'T PAY ATTENTION SO MUCH
AT FIRST.
>> AND NOW YOU DO.
>> YES.
>> FAIR ENOUGH.
NOW, AS WE SAW WITH ALLIE, YOU
NEED TO TAKE THE PILL THE RIGHT
WAY, OTHERWISE IT WILL NOT BE
EFFECTIVE.
GOT IT?
SO I HOPE ALL VIEWERS OUT THERE
FIND OUT HOW BIRTH CONTROL
REALLY WORKS BEFORE THEY DECIDE
TO HAVE SEX.
AND, OF COURSE, PREVENTION WILL
BE A BIG TOPIC THROUGHOUT
TODAY'S SHOW.
TO LEARN MORE, LOG ON TO:
COMING UP AFTER THE BREAK IS
JORDAN.
NOW, THERE WAS A BIT OF A POWER
STRUGGLE BETWEEN SHE AND HER
TWIN SISTER AND HER BABY'S
FATHER.
WHO IS NUMBER ONE IN HER LIFE
NOW?
ALL THREE OF THEM ARE HERE,
AND WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUT
AFTER THE BREAK.
[applause]
NOW, MY UNDERSTANDING THAT THERE
WERE RESTRAINING ORDERS.
WHY DID THEY HAPPEN?
>> HE SAID HE WILL HAVE ME IN
JAIL AND RAPED.
>> MY PHONE WAS DEAD.
>> HOW DID YOU GET A HICKEY ON
YOUR NECK?
>> HUH?
>> HOW DID YOU GET A HICKEY ON
YOUR NECK?
>> I TOLD YOU. A GIRL.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU HAD SEX WITH
ANOTHER GIRL.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> BROKE.
>> JOEY, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
US BRINGING THE BABY OUT?
>> YEAH, I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM
IN MONTHS.
>> DO YOU WANT TO TAKE A RISK
AND BRING THE BABY OUT AND SEE
HOW THAT FEELS?
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO LIFE AFTER
LABOR,THE 16 AND PREGNANT
FINALE SPECIAL.
I'M DR. DREW, AND I WANT TO GIVE
YOU A SCARY STATISTIC.
LISTEN TO THIS.
NEARLY 1/3 OF TEENAGE GIRLS
IN AMERICA WILL GET PREGNANT.
WE HAVE TEN OF THEM HERE TODAY,
AND ONE OF THEM IS A TEEN MOM
WHO SACRIFICED MODELING, SOCIAL
LIFE, AND A SPECIAL RELATIONSHIP
WITH HER TWIN SISTER.
AND HERE WITH US NOW IS BABY
NOAH'S DAD, BRIAN.
NOW, BRIAN, SINCE WE'VE SEEN THE
END OF YOUR EPISODE, YOUR
RELATIONSHIP HAS CHANGED, HAS IT
NOT?
>> YES.
RECENTLY, JORDAN AND I HAVE
GOTTEN MARRIED.
>> WOW. IT'S BIG NEWS.
WE DIDN'T KNOW THAT, SO THANKS
FOR SHARING THAT WITH US.
HALF OF TEEN MOMS DON'T HAVE
THEIR PARTNERS.
EIGHT OUT OF TEN DON'T GET
MARRIED.
SO YOU GUYS, SO FAR, ARE THE
EXCEPTION.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WELL, IT'S BEEN QUITE A YEAR
FOR YOU GUYS.
HERE, LET'S TAKE A LOOK BACK AT
JORDAN'S JOURNEY ON 16 AND
PREGNANT.
>> THE DECISION THAT YOU TWO
MADE AFFECTS EVERYONE,
ALL YOUR FAMILY.
>> I KNOW.
>> IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BOND WITH
YOU WHEN YOUR TWIN SISTER IS
ALWAYS THERE.
>> YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
CLOSE WE WERE.
>> YOUR LIFE PRETTY MUCH
REVOLVES AROUND HIM.
>> NO, IT DOESN'T.
>> YEAH, IT DOES.
>> NO, IT REVOLVES AROUND MY
BABY.
WHEN WILL I, LIKE, BE ABLE
TO TAKE MY GED?
>> GOT A LITTLE BIT OF WORK TO
DO, BUT HANG IN THERE.
>> OH!
>> THERE'S MY GIRL.
>> WHAT IF IT WAS ME THAT HAD
THE BABY, AND I HAD MY BOYFRIEND
LIVING HERE, AND YOU DIDN'T
NEED ME?
>> I DO NEED YOU, JESSICA, BUT I
HAVE TO BE A MOM FIRST.
>> OKAY, BE A FRICKIN' MOM!
[baby crying]
>> HE WON'T STOP CRYING BECAUSE
HIS MOUTH IS SO DRY.
>> I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO.
>> I DON'T EITHER.
>> BABIES WITH REFLUX ARE
PROBABLY GOING TO BE A LITTLE
BIT MORE HIGH-MAINTENANCE,
BUT WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO MAKE IT
BETTER.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> GOING TO SCHOOL.
>> I GAVE UP JUST, LIKE,
FREEDOM.
I GAVE UP NOT PLANNING FOR
MY FUTURE.
I THINK YOU SHOULD JUST, LIKE,
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF, LIKE,
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE.
LIKE, I DON'T HAVE ALL THOSE
OPTIONS.
>> WELL, DON'T WORRY.
I WILL TAKE ADVANTAGE OF ALL MY
OPTIONS FOR YOU.
>> BRIAN, WE SAW YOU CRYING
IN THE DELIVERY ROOM.
YOU DESCRIBED THE EXPERIENCE AS
INTENSE.
>> YEAH, I MEAN, SEEING
SOMETHING THAT YOU CREATED,
IT'S REALLY NICE.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST CRYING NOW JUST
THINKING ABOUT IT.
JORDAN, WE SAW IN YOUR EPISODE
YOUR GRANDMOTHER LECTURING YOU
ON THE DANGERS OF PREMARITAL
SEX.
SHE WOULDN'T EVEN LET YOU GUYS
SHARE A BLANKET, AS I RECALL.
>> YEAH.
>> AS YOU THINK BACK ON IT,
WHAT MIGHT YOU HAVE DONE
DIFFERENTLY?
>> I WOULD HAVE TAKEN BIRTH
CONTROL A LOT BETTER.
WAITED A LOT LONGER, UNTIL I WAS
ON IT FOR AT LEAST A COUPLE
MONTHS.
>> WERE YOU TRYING TO BRING HIM
CLOSER TO YOU, OR WAS THERE...
>> YEAH, I MEAN, I HAVE THIS,
LIKE, SECURITY THING ABOUT
PEOPLE LEAVING ME.
>> THIS IS BECAUSE OF YOUR MOM?
>> AND MY DAD AND MY BROTHERS.
>> SO THE TWINS WERE LEFT WITH
YOUR GRANDMA?
>> YEAH.
I WAS NINE WHEN I GOT ADOPTED.
>> THAT'S PRETTY HEAVY.
>> MY MOM'S IN FLORIDA,
AND MY DAD'S IN TENNESSEE,
AND MY BROTHERS ARE, LIKE, THREE
HOURS AWAY, AND, LIKE, WE ALL
WERE TOGETHER AT ONCE,
AND THEY JUST KIND OF, LIKE, ALL
GOT UP AND LEFT.
>> HOW OLD WERE YOU WHEN THAT
HAPPENED?
>> I WAS NINE, EIGHT.
NINE WHEN I GOT ADOPTED.
I WENT TO LIVE WITH MY AUNTS
FOR A WHILE AND...
>> DID YOU BLAME YOURSELF
AS A CHILD?
>> I MEAN, SORT OF.
I MEAN...
>> THAT'S WHAT CHILDREN DO.
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD CHILDREN FEEL
LIKE THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS TO THEM.
SO IF A FAMILY BREAKS UP OR THEY
GET ABUSE OR ABANDONED, THEY
BLAME THEMSELVES, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, AND JUST MY MOM GOT
PREGNANT AS A TEENAGER RIGHT OUT
OF HIGH SCHOOL, AND...
THEN SHE GOT PREGNANT AGAIN
AND AGAIN.
>> AND SO WHAT WAS YOUR PLAN?
>> UH, NOT TO GET PREGNANT.
>> OOPS.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S FUNNY HOW WE RE-CREATE
THE PAST, ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH, NOT EVEN KNOWING IT.
>> WHAT IS THE PLAN?
YOU'RE NOT WORKING ANYMORE,
RIGHT?
YOU WERE MODELING?
YOU WERE GOING TO SCHOOL?
>> YEAH, I GOT MY GED.
>> AND WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS?
>> UM, AS OF RIGHT NOW, I'M
ACTUALLY ENLISTING IN THE AIR
FORCE.
>> WHERE DO YOU LIVE NOW?
>> IN MISSOURI. ST. LOUIS.
>> WITH...
>> WITH HER GRANDMA.
>> WITH YOUR GRANDMA.
SO IN THE HOUSE WITH YOUR
SISTER.
DOES THAT CAUSE TENSION?
>> UH, SOMETIMES.
NOT ANYMORE.
>> WE SAW A LITTLE BIT OF IT ON
YOUR EPISODE.
YOUR SISTER WAS FEELING JEALOUS
AND LEFT OUT.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I'D PROBABLY BE THE SAME
WAY IF I WAS HER.
>> WELL, JESSICA, OF COURSE, IS
HERE, SO SHOULD WE TALK TO HER?
>> YEAH.
>> LET'S BRING HER OUT.
[applause]
>> HELLO.
>> JESSICA, THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
SO YOU HEARD WHAT WE'VE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT.
HOW HAS THIS BEEN FOR YOU?
>> UM, REALLY EMOTIONAL, BUT...
>> YOU SEEM EVEN EMOTIONAL NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> WHY?
>> SEEING HER CRY MADE ME CRY,
SO...
>> ABOUT YOUR CHILDHOOD STUFF.
DO YOU FEEL RESPONSIBLE FOR
BEING ABANDONED?
>> KIND OF.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY
LEFT, SO...
IT WAS JUST...
DIFFICULT.
>> YEAH.
NOW THAT JORDAN HAS HAD A BABY,
DOES IT THREATEN THAT SPECIAL
BOND YOU GUYS HAD?
>> WELL, AT FIRST 'CAUSE SHE GOT
PREGNANT AT FIVE MONTHS--
THEY WERE ONLY TOGETHER FOR,
LIKE, FIVE OR SIX MONTHS.
>> DID YOU NOT TRUST HIM?
>> KIND OF, YEAH.
I WAS SCARED FOR HER.
BUT NOW I'M, LIKE, REALLY HAPPY
FOR HER BECAUSE SHE'S MARRIED,
AND BRIAN'S, LIKE, A WONDERFUL
DAD.
>> YOU GUYS ARE SO ENMESHED AND
SO TIGHT, AND YOU HAD TO RELY
ON EACH OTHER SO MUCH,
IT'S VERY THREATENING TO HAVE
SUDDENLY THIS DUDE SHOW UP.
DID YOU FEEL ANY OF THAT, BRIAN?
>> EVEN BESIDES THEM BEING
TWINS, HER GRANDPARENTS WITH
THEM ARE VERY CLOSE, AND I WAS
JUST KIND OF THROWN INTO IT.
I'M THE GUY WHO KNOCKED UP THEIR
LITTLE GIRL.
SO...
>> HOW DOES YOUR FAMILY TAKE ALL
THIS?
>> MY PARENTS WERE ALSO TEEN
PARENTS.
MY MOM GOT PREGNANT AT 19
AND GOT MARRIED RIGHT AWAY,
BUT THEY ENDED UP SEPARATING.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO WE HAVE--
YOU'RE A PRODUCT OF TEEN
PARENTING.
YOU'VE GOT ABANDONMENT.
HOW DID YOU NOT FALL INTO THE
SAME PATTERN?
>> I'M THE FIRST ONE OUT OF MY
WHOLE FAMILY TO GO TO COLLEGE,
SO--
>> WHY DOES THAT MAKE YOU SAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WANTED TO GO TO SCHOOL,
BUT NOW SHE'S A MOM.
>> SO YOU'VE GOT TO DO IT FOR
HER.
>> WELL, YEAH, I'M DOING IT FOR
I WANT TO, LIKE, SHOW HER THAT
WE COULD HAVE DONE IT,
AND SHE COULD HAVE DONE IT,
BUT...
>> ARE YOU JEALOUS?
>> THAT SHE'S MOVING ON WITH HER
LIFE?
UH, A LITTLE, YEAH.
I MEAN, I'M...
A STAY-AT-HOME MOM.
>> WHY ARE YOU CRYING?
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO RELY
ON BRIAN.
I MEAN, SURE HE'S MY HUSBAND,
BUT I WANT TO MAKE SOMETHING OF
MYSELF.
AND I FEEL LIKE I CAN'T BECAUSE
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE NOAH WITH
SOMEONE I DON'T KNOW.
>> AGAIN, FOR THE PURPOSES OF
PEOPLE AT HOME, THOUGH, WOULDN'T
YOU SAY THAT BEING A TEEN MOM...
>> IS VERY HARD.
>> YOU KNOW, THE ONE THING THAT
I KEEP SEEING OVER AND OVER
AGAIN IN THIS PROGRAM
PARTICULARLY, IS KIDS SAYING,
"OH, YES.
I'M GOING TO GO TO GRADUATE
SCHOOL; I'M GOING TO GET
A PROFESSIONAL DEGREE;
I'M GOING TO RAISE MY BABY."
HOW REALISTIC IS ALL THAT?
>> IT'S LIKE--
OUR PLANS HAVE CHANGED
DRASTICALLY BECAUSE, I MEAN,
FOR HIM TO GO TO COLLEGE, THAT
COSTS MONEY, AND WE CAN'T JUST
DO STUDENT LOANS.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PAY THAT
BACK.
SO AIR FORCE WAS, LIKE, THE BEST
THING FOR US.
>> RIGHT.
SO THE REALITIES OF HAVING A
BABY ROB YOU OF A LOT OF
OPTIONS, 'CAUSE MAKING THINGS
HAPPEN TAKE A LOT OF WORK,
A LOT OF PLANNING, A LOT OF
STRUCTURE, A LOT OF EDUCATION.
>> TAKES TIME.
>> WELL, JORDAN, BRIAN, JESSICA,
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
JORDAN IS, OF COURSE, GOING TO
BE BACK LATER TO CHAT WITH ALL
THE OTHER YOUNG MOMS.
IN A MOMENT, WE'RE GOING TO
RETURN WITH JENNIFER AND HER
DAD.
AS IF HAVING TWINS WASN'T ENOUGH
WORK, JENNIFER HAS ALSO HAD TO
DEAL WITH THE ARREST OF THEIR
FATHER, JOSH.
SO WHERE DOES THIS ALL STAND
RIGHT NOW?
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND OUT
WHEN WE COME BACK.
[applause]
>> I'M DR. DREW, AND THIS IS
LIFE AFTER LABOR: THE 16 AND
PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL.
NOW, BEFORE WE GO ON, I WANT TO
REMIND OUR VIEWERS TO GO TO
ITSYOURSEXLIFE.COM,
WHERE YOU'LL FIND ANSWERS TO SEX
QUESTIONS AND TIPS ON HOW TO
TAKE CONTROL OF YOUR SEX LIFE.
NOW, ALL TEN OF THIS SEASON'S
YOUNG MOMS HAD THEIR HANDS FULL,
NEED I SAY, TAKING CARE OF A NEW
BABY, BUT ONLY JENNIFER HAD TO
DEAL WITH TWINS.
WELL, THERE'S A LOT TO TALK
ABOUT, OBVIOUSLY.
FIRST, THOUGH, I WANT TO TAKE A
LOOK BACK AT HER STORY.
>> SO DO YOU GUYS ALREADY KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE HAVING?
>> TWO BOYS.
>> TWO BOYS? OH.
>> DID YOU EVER THINK, A YEAR
LATER, I'D BE SHOWING A CRIB?
>> NO.
>> IT'S LIKE, "DUDE, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT MY DAUGHTER PREGNANT.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU'RE STANDING IN
FRONT OF ME."
>> YOU'RE ONLY 16 YEARS OLD,
AND IF HE DOESN'T GET THAT,
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO BUMP
HEADS.
>> THE PERSON THAT I LOVE AND MY
OWN FAMILY ARE FIGHTING.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
MAKE A CHOICE.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
>> OF COURSE I WILL.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE TO
MAKE THIS HAPPEN BECAUSE THE
CHILDREN ARE COMING?
>> NO.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
OUTCOME'S GOING TO BE.
>> [cooing]
>> THE LAST NAME FOR THE BABY,
SAME AS THE DAD'S?
>> YES.
>> YOU NEED TO MEET ME HALFWAY.
>> THEY'RE NOT YOUR KIDS.
I DON'T HAVE TO MEET YOU
HALFWAY.
>> YOU SIT THERE AND YOU ARGUE
WITH MY PARENTS.
I'M TRYING TO KEEP YOU WARM
FOR A SECOND.
SOMETHING YOUR DAD SHOULD BE
HELPING OUT ON.
I'M DONE.
>> YOU WANT OUT OF THIS
RELATIONSHIP, JENNIFER?
>> YEAH. I DO.
OKAY, JUST FOR YOUR INFORMATION,
YOU'RE GOING TO JAIL!
SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR KIDS, JOSH.
YOU WILL NEVER, EVER SEE THEM
AGAIN!
[siren wailing]
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL WHEN YOU
WATCH THAT FOOTAGE?
>> IT HURTS.
>> HURTS.
MM.
>> HE WAS, FOR A WHOLE YEAR--
WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
WE DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
>> BUT THAT'S THE GUY CAPABLE
OF DOING THAT.
>> MM-HMM.
I NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD GO THAT
FAR.
I NEVER THOUGHT HE WOULD DRIVE
OFF WITH THEM.
>> SO YOU'RE TELLING US YOU KNEW
A DIFFERENT PERSON.
>> YEAH.
HE WAS A COMPLETE DIFFERENT
PERSON.
>> YOUR PARENTS KNEW YOU WERE
SEXUALLY ACTIVE.
>> MM-HMM.
MY MOM DID.
>> AND SHE TOOK YOU TO GET BIRTH
CONTROL.
>> SHE TOOK ME TO THE DOCTOR AND
HAS DEFINITELY GIVEN ME OPTIONS.
>> HOW'S YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH
YOUR FAMILY NOW?
>> I WOULD SAY IT'S PROBABLY
STRONGER.
>> STRONGER AS A RESULT.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WHY DON'T WE BRING YOUR DAD
OUT AND HAVE FURTHER
CONVERSATION ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, LET'S BRING OUT HER
FATHER.
HE'S HERE WITH US.
RICO, COME ON OUT.
[applause]
>> HEY, DR. DREW.
>> RICO.
SO WHAT'S YOUR PERSPECTIVE ON
ALL OF THIS?
I MEAN, THIS IS A PRETTY--
A LOT TO TAKE, A LOT TO SWALLOW.
>> YES.
I DIDN'T KNOW SHE WAS SEXUALLY
ACTIVE.
KIND OF A SHOCK.
>> IT'S HARD TO TALK ABOUT THIS
STUFF, EVEN WHEN PARENTS ARE
OPEN AND TALKING ABOUT IT.
IT IS UNCOMFORTABLE FOR
EVERYBODY.
IT'S A HARD TOPIC.
>> YOU JUST DON'T IMAGINE YOUR
LITTLE GIRL, AT 16,
PARTICIPATING IN THAT.
>> SO YOU WEREN'T AWARE THAT SHE
WAS SEXUALLY ACTIVE, BUT SHE
SAID HER MOM WAS.
>> I WOULD SAY THAT'S PROBABLY
TRUE.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT I, YOU
KNOW, TALKED ABOUT THAT OPENLY.
MAYBE IF I WAS MORE INVOLVED,
IF I WOULD HAVE TALKED MORE...
>> YOU COULD HAVE MADE A
DIFFERENCE.
>> COULD HAVE MADE A DIFFERENCE.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> SO YOU REGRET.
>> YES.
>> WHAT ACTUALLY WERE YOU
TALKING WITH YOUR MOM ABOUT?
"MOM, I'M SEXUALLY ACTIVE;
I NEED TO HAVE BIRTH CONTROL"?
OR...
>> UM, NO.
>> NO? OKAY.
SO WHAT WAS THE CONVERSATION?
>> I GUESS SOMEBODY MENTIONED
SOMETHING TO HER, AND SHE
FOUND OUT.
>> SO SHE WAS AWARE.
YOU WEREN'T ACTUALLY TALKING
ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
>> MM-HMM.
>> IF YOU'D HAD THAT
CONVERSATION WITH YOUR MOM,
WHAT DO YOU WISH SHE'D SAID?
>> TELL HER TO TAKE ME TO GO GET
BIRTH CONTROL OR GO OVER OPTIONS
FOR ME.
>> WERE YOU AFRAID OF HOW YOUR
PARENTS WERE GOING TO REACT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> HAVE THERE BEEN FURTHER
CONVERSATIONS ABOUT BIRTH
CONTROL?
>> NO, NOT--I MEAN, MY MOM TELLS
ME, WHEN I'M READY, SHE WILL
TAKE ME IF I WANT TO...
>> WHAT OPTION WOULD YOU BE
LOOKING FOR?
>> THE SHOT.
>> YOU WANT DEPO SHOT?
>> PROBABLY.
>> MIGHT BE SOMETHING TO TALK
ABOUT.
NO? DAD, YOU DON'T LIKE THAT?
>> AGAIN, THIS IS MY LITTLE
GIRL.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE SITTING HERE
DISCUSSING, YOU KNOW, PREGNANCY
PREVENTION.
THAT MEANS, OBVIOUSLY, SHE'S
CONTEMPLATING SEX,
SO, YOU KNOW...
BUT AT THIS POINT, YOU KNOW, YOU
GOT TO BE REALISTIC;
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN, NO MATTER
WHAT I SAY.
>> HOW'S THE RELATIONSHIP WITH
JOSH NOW?
>> THINGS ARE CIVIL.
>> DO YOU HARBOR THAT SAME
FANTASY THAT SO MANY OF OUR TEEN
MOMS DO THAT SOMEHOW THIS IS
GOING TO BE A MAGICAL
RELATIONSHIP, THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE YOUR FAMILY TOGETHER
AGAIN?
>> I DID, AND I STILL DO
SOMETIMES, BUT THERE'S STILL
TIMES WHERE, LIKE, LOOKING BACK
AT THAT AND LOOKING BACK AT
PICTURES, I SAY, IF HE CAN
CHANGE, MAYBE.
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT TAKES A STRONG
PERSON, AND IT TAKES A PERSON TO
WANT TO CHANGE.
>> WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT WITH
JOSH?
WHAT DO YOU THINK THAT WAS?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO BASH JOSH
OR SAY ANYTHING, YOU KNOW, BAD
ABOUT HIM, EVEN THOUGH I DON'T
REALLY CARE FOR HIM.
SOME OF WHAT I'VE LEARNED TO TRY
TO UNDERSTAND ABOUT JOSH IS THE
WAY HE WAS, I GUESS, BROUGHT UP,
PARENTING.
I MEAN, IT ALL COMES BACK ON THE
PARENTS.
>> NOW, MY UNDERSTANDING THAT
THERE WERE RESTRAINING ORDERS
AND ALL KINDS OF STUFF BETWEEN
YOU AND JOSH.
IS THAT CORRECT?
WHY DID THEY HAPPEN?
>> UM, THE FIRST ONE HAPPENED--
I FILED IT THE DAY HE WAS IN
JAIL.
>> OKAY, THAT'S ONE.
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
WHAT WAS THE SECOND ONE?
>> HE SAID HE WILL HAVE ME IN
JAIL AND RAPED.
>> SO HE'S GOING TO SEE TO IT
THAT YOU WERE RAPED IN JAIL?
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT'S NICE.
>> [chuckles]
>> REALLY DESERVE THAT?
>> NO.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU'RE WORTHY
OF THAT KIND OF ABUSE.
DO YOU?
>> MM-MM.
>> OKAY.
JENNIFER, RICO, THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK,
AND WE WILL RETURN WITH
DANIELLE.
NOW, SHE, TOO, HAS HAD TONS OF
DRAMA SURROUNDING HER
RELATIONSHIP WITH HER BABY'S
FATHER.
SO WHERE DO SHE AND JAMIE STAND
TODAY?
WE'RE GOING TO ASK THEM BOTH.
DON'T GO AWAY.
[applause]
>> WE ARE BACK WITH MORE OF THE
16 AND PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL,
TALKING WITH TEN YOUNG WOMEN
WITH COMPLICATED LIVES WHO ALL
BECAME PREGNANT IN HIGH SCHOOL.
UP NEXT IS DANIELLE, HERE WITH
HER MOM, CASEY, AND HER BABY'S
FATHER, JAMIE.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK BACK AT
DANIELLE'S EXPERIENCE BEING
16 AND PREGNANT.
>> IT'S KIND OF CRAZY WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE A BABY BEFORE OUR
ONE-YEAR ANNIVERSARY.
>> I KNOW.
>> I WORKED SO HARD TO EMBED IT
IN YOUR HEAD THAT THIS ISN'T
SOMETHING THAT YOU WANTED.
>> HOW MUCH [bleep] DO WE NEED
FOR RIGHT NOW?
>> OKAY, WHEN THE BABY'S BORN,
WHAT DO WE NEED?
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT WE'RE GOING
TO DO UNTIL WE GET INTO IT.
>> THAT'S A CONTRACTION.
YEAH, I THINK WE NEED TO GO HAVE
YOU CHECKED OUT.
>> LOOK AT ME.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
OH, MY GOD.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE RAISING
MY BABY.
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO DO IT
ON MY OWN.
>> I DON'T WANT TO LET YOU GO.
LIKE, I REALLY DON'T.
>> PUT IT SOMEWHERE.
>> [crying]
>> I BROUGHT YOUR GRADES.
YOU HAVE TWO "F"s.
>> PUSH IT DOWN.
>> I AM.
>> YOU'RE JUST [bleep] ANNOYING.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE PRETTY ANNOYING,
TOO.
LIKE, YOU BLOW EVERYTHING OUT OF
PROPORTION.
WE NEVER REALLY, LIKE, GET ALONG
ANYMORE, REALLY.
WE FIGHT ALL THE TIME.
>> THE WHOLE SITUATION,
THIS AIN'T ALL MY FAULT.
I JUST DON'T SEE IT WORKING OUT,
LIKE, AS PLANNED.
>> WELL, YOU ARE ALREADY HAVING
A REACTION.
WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
HARD TO WATCH?
WHY?
>> JUST CRAZY HOW MUCH HAS
HAPPENED IN ONLY A YEAR.
>> ALL THAT HAS HAPPENED TO YOU
IN THE LAST YEAR, YEAH.
CASEY, YOU'RE HAVING A REACTION
TOO.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
>> JUST SAD.
>> WHAT'S SAD?
>> JUST WATCHING HER GO THROUGH
WHAT I DID.
>> SAME THING YOU WENT THROUGH
AS A TEEN MOM.
>> YES.
>> IT'S A CYCLE, ISN'T IT?
>> IT IS, AND I TRIED VERY HARD
TO BREAK THAT CYCLE.
AND I JUST FEEL LIKE I FAILED.
>> HOW DID YOU TRY TO PREVENT
THAT WITH YOUR DAUGHTER?
>> WELL, WE TRIED BIRTH CONTROL.
>> WHAT HAPPENED WITH THE BIRTH
CONTROL?
>> I QUIT TAKING IT.
>> WHY?
>> UM, I NEVER REMEMBERED TO.
>> AND THIS IS WHERE YOU BLAME
YOURSELF?
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHAT IS THE STATUS OF YOUR
RELATIONSHIP NOW, BETWEEN YOU
TWO?
>> IT'S ROCKY, BUT WE'RE
TOGETHER.
>> TOGETHER, AS OF THE LAST FIVE
MINUTES OR...
>> YEAH, BASICALLY.
>> THE LAST FIVE MINUTES.
HOW ABOUT TEN MINUTES BEFORE
THAT, WHERE WERE YOU?
>> UM, WELL, WE JUST HAD A
REALLY BIG BREAKUP.
>> WHEN?
>> 2 1/2 WEEKS AGO.
>> IT WAS FINISHED?
>> IT WASN'T FINISHED.
WE WAS FED UP WITH EACH OTHER AT
THE TIME, BUT I REALIZED, BEING
GONE OUT OF THE HOUSE, AWAY FROM
JAMIE AND AWAY FROM HER,
THAT IT'S WAY EASIER TO JUST
STAY AND FACE THE PROBLEMS THAT
HAVE--OR CAME TO US.
>> I THINK IT'S EASIER TO RUN
AWAY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> NO, IT'S NOT EASIER TO RUN
AWAY 'CAUSE IT DON'T SOLVE
NOTHING.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
CASEY, WHAT DO YOU SEE GOING ON
HERE?
IS IT JUST THE STRESS OF BEING A
PARENT AND BEING A TEEN MOM?
>> IT HONESTLY IS.
IT REALLY IS.
>> WE DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
WE WERE, LIKE, TEENAGERS.
>> THIS SORT OF BROUGHT REALITY
DOWN FOR YOU, HUH?
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND THAT'S WHAT UPSETS YOU.
>> MY LIFE WAS WAY DIFFERENT.
LIKE, I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO
WORRY ABOUT.
>> CASEY, DID YOU HAVE A PERIOD
OF TIME WHEN YOU WERE PARENTING
WHEN YOU NEEDED TO BE HER BEST
FRIEND?
>> PROBABLY.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT
NOW?
>> I REGRET IT.
I HONESTLY FEEL LIKE I'VE RAISED
HER AS MY LITTLE SISTER.
I ALWAYS...
I'M SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
THAT YOU ALWAYS WHAT?
>> I JUST ALWAYS WANTED THE BEST
FOR HER.
>> OF COURSE.
DO YOU OWE HER A LITTLE BIT
OF AN APOLOGY FOR DOING THAT?
>> I DO.
>> DO YOU WANT TO SAY THAT TO
HER?
>> I REALLY AM SORRY, BABY.
I DIDN'T RAISE YOU THE WAY THAT
I SHOULD HAVE, BUT I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT ALL OF
THIS?
>> SHE IS PHENOMENAL FOR SURE.
>> YOU WANT TO TELL HER THAT?
>> YES, YOU ARE PHENOMENAL.
YOU TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
EVERYTHING THAT NEEDS TO BE
TOOK CARE OF, YOU GOT IT.
THERE'S NO...
>> DO YOU FEEL THE SAME WAY,
DANIELLE?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> YEAH. SO MOM'S STEPPING UP.
>> FEELING GUILTY AND REGRETFUL,
UNDERSTOOD.
>> SHE HELPS ME A LOT.
>> LET'S MOVE FORWARD.
YOU WERE TRYING TO SURVIVE.
>> YEAH.
>> SO MOVING FORWARD, WHAT ABOUT
SCHOOL?
>> I'VE BEEN BEGGING HER TO--
I WANT TO GET MY GED.
>> YOU'RE BEGGING YOUR MOM TO
GET THE GED.
>> I'VE TRIED TO TAKE YOU.
>> NO, TO TAKE ME.
LIKE, I WANTED TO GO TO COLLEGE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TRYING TO,
LIKE, BLOW COLLEGE OFF.
>> HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> 17.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU TAKE YOURSELF?
>> I CAN'T DRIVE.
>> FIRST ORDER OF BUSINESS,
GET YOUR DRIVER'S LICENSE,
AND THEN TAKE YOURSELF, MOM.
>> MM-HMM.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THE BABY FOR
A MINUTE.
HOW ARE THINGS WITH THE BABY?
>> I LOVE HIM.
>> YOU LOVE THE BABY.
>> YEAH.
>> EVERYTHING GOING OKAY?
HE'S HEALTHY?
>> YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
>> HE'S FAT.
HE'S A GIANT CHUNK OF BUTT.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, EVERYONE
WATCHING RIGHT NOW NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND, OF COURSE, THE
IMPORTANCE OF PREVENTION.
TO LEARN THE FACTS, MAKE SURE TO
HEAD ON OVER TO:
I WANT TO THANK DANIELLE,
JAMIE, CASEY.
VERY COURAGEOUS AND FOR ALL OF
YOU FOR BEING HERE.
LET'S MOVE RIGHT ON TO OUR NEXT
TEEN MOM, TAYLOR.
HERE IS HER STORY.
>> THESE PANTS, LOOK AT 'EM.
I COULD PUT ANOTHER PERSON IN
THERE.
WHAT DID WE DO WHEN WE FIRST
STARTED DATING?
>> WENT OUT DANCING OR
SOMETHING?
AND LOOK WHAT ALL THAT GOT US
INTO.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU GIVE
THE CHILD UP FOR ADOPTION.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE THE IDEA
OF ADOPTION.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO HAVE TO
STRUGGLE.
I KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE HARD FOR
YOU.
>> IF I CAN'T STAY IN SCHOOL
I GUESS I'M GONNA HAVE TO
DO VIRTUAL SCHOOL, BUT
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT NATHAN TO
HAVE AS A DAD?
>> A JOB.
>> I'M GETTING A JOB SOON.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A BABY
IN LESS THAN 24 HOURS.
>> YOU GOT IT, HONEY.
YOU GOT IT.
GREAT.
>> I TOLD YOU, ONCE YOU HAVE A
BABY, YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO HAVE
ANY SLEEP AGAIN.
>> I AT LEAST NEED AN HOUR OF
SLEEP TO FUNCTION RIGHT.
>> SOMEBODY NEEDS TO GET A JOB.
>> I'M TRYING.
I'VE BEEN FILLING OUT
APPLICATIONS.
>> LET'S TRY HARDER.
>> GO GET THE FRICKIN' BOTTLE.
>> I'M NOT DOING IT, 'CAUSE
IT'S NOT MY TURN.
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE LAZY.
>> OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE SO FRIGGIN'...
>> IT'S NOT HARD FOR YOU TO GET
SOMETHING.
>> IRRITATING.
>> THIS SITUATION IS OUT OF
CONTROL.
KIDS SHOULD NOT HAVE KIDS
'CAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO
HANDLE SITUATIONS YET.
>> I THINK THE ONLY REASON WE
STAY TOGETHER IS A LITTLE BIT OF
LOVE AND BECAUSE OF HER.
>> I'M HERE NOW WITH TAYLOR AND
AUBRI'S FATHER, NATHAN.
NOW, GUYS, THINGS WERE SHAKY AT
BEST BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU WHEN
WE LEFT OFF.
WHAT'S THE STATUS NOW?
>> WE'RE STILL TOGETHER AND
DOING A LITTLE BETTER.
>> TAYLOR, HOW DID YOU FEEL
WATCHING THAT EPISODE JUST NOW?
>> IT'S KIND OF UPSETTING.
>> IN WHAT WAY?
>> LIKE, I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW
MUCH WE DID FIGHT, AND IT WAS
JUST OVER LITTLE THINGS.
>> WHY DO YOU PICK ON HIM SO
MUCH?
>> HE JUST WANTS TO PLAY WITH
HER WHEN IT'S CONVENIENT FOR HIM
SOMETIMES, AND THAT'S JUST WHAT
MAKES ME MAD.
>> THIS IS THE THING OF TEEN
PREGNANCY.
YOU CAN'T BE WHAT YOUR
CHRONOLOGICAL AGE TELLS YOU
TO BE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GROW UP REALLY
FAST.
TAYLOR, THIS HAS MADE YOU GROW
UP, HAS IT NOT?
>> YEAH, DEFINITELY.
>> NATHAN, YOU HAD A LOOK OF
SHOCK DURING THE DELIVERY.
WHAT WAS GOING THROUGH YOUR
MIND?
>> FIRST OFF, THE SMELL,
AND THEN JUST...
>> WELL, LET ME SAY, PLACENTA
HAS A UNIQUE SMELL.
>> AND THEN JUST, LIKE, THAT WAS
LIKE WHEN THE HEAD FIRST STARTED
COMING OUT AND JUST LIKE:
LIKE, "WHOA."
LIKE, "SHE'S COMING."
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING FOR BIRTH
CONTROL NOW?
>> I'M ON THE PILL.
>> OKAY. TAKING IT PROPERLY?
>> YES.
>> WHAT WENT WRONG BEFORE?
>> CONDOM BROKE.
>> CONDOM BROKE?
MORNING AFTER PILL,
YOU GUYS EVER HEARD OF THAT?
EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION.
>> I DIDN'T WANT TO TELL MY MOM.
I WAS LIKE, "EW. HOW AWKWARD."
>> YOUR MOM SEEMS LIKE SOMEBODY
THAT TALKS VERY OPENLY WITH YOU
ABOUT THIS STUFF.
NO?
WELL, LET'S TALK ABOUT, FOR
OTHER PEOPLE OUT THERE, WHAT
EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION IS.
IF THERE IS A FAILURE OF
A BARRIER METHOD LIKE A CONDOM,
YOU CAN GO TO A PHARMACY AND GET
SOME PILLS YOU TAKE WITHIN THREE
DAYS OF THAT ENCOUNTER AND
REDUCE THE RISKS OF PREGNANCY
MARKEDLY.
JUST BEFORE WE WENT ON THE AIR,
YOU MENTIONED TO ME DURING THE
BREAK THAT AUBRI HAD HAD A LUNG
SURGERY, HAD A TUMOR REMOVED
FROM HER LUNG.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW'S THAT GOING NOW?
HOW'S SHE DOING?
>> SHE'S WONDERFUL NOW.
IT WAS JUST SO SAD TO SEE HER GO
THROUGH THAT.
IT WAS SO HARD.
>> IT'S EXTRA INTENSE, HUH?
YEAH.
WHAT THEY TOOK OUT WAS THE
CCAM, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, AND 20% OF HER LUNG.
>> RIGHT.
SO THEN THAT'S ALL NOW A
COMPLETE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH, IT'S JUST HARD.
YOU DON'T--SHE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING.
SHE'S SO LITTLE.
>> IT'S HARD.
NOW, MY UNDERSTANDING IS, YOUR
MOM HAD PUT A CHILD UP
FOR ADOPTION AND THAT SHE WAS
ENCOURAGING YOU TO DO THE SAME.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
TAYLOR'S MOM, DEBI, IS HERE
WITH US.
DEBI, COME ON OUT.
[applause]
HAVE A SEAT. WELCOME.
SO YOU WERE IN FAVOR OF
ADOPTION, MOM?
>> YES.
>> AND DID TAYLOR MAKE A GOOD
DECISION NOT TO DO THAT?
>> NOW, YES.
I CAN'T SEE LIFE WITHOUT AUBRI.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE'S A GOOD BABY.
>> AND, DEBI, YOU'RE PICKING UP
A LOT OF THE PARENTING.
LET'S BE FAIR.
LIKE, WHAT WOULD THEY DO WITHOUT
YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> THIS IS A COMMON THEME IN OUR
COUNTRY--THE GRANDPARENTS DOING
A LOT OF THE PARENTING.
>> AND IT'S VERY HARD ON ME.
IT REALLY IS.
>> YOU WORK?
>> I WORK THIRD SHIFT, SO I COME
HOME AND THEN I WATCH HER,
YOU KNOW, AND THEN I HAVE TO
STAY UP ALL DAY.
I MIGHT TWO OR THREE HOURS'
SLEEP A DAY, AND THAT'S PRETTY
MUCH IT.
>> YOU SORT OF SHIFTED WHEN SHE
SAID THAT.
DO YOU FEEL GUILTY?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE, LIKE, I TRIED
HOMESCHOOLING, BUT I COULDN'T
DO IT.
I NEED SOMEONE TO TELL ME, LIKE,
"YOU NEED TO DO THIS, THIS,
AND THIS."
>> WHOSE IDEA WAS IT TO GO BACK
TO SCHOOL?
>> IT WAS MINE.
I WAS LIKE, "I CANNOT SIT IN
THIS HOUSE ANY LONGER.
I CAN'T DO HOMESCHOOLING."
>> DEBI, YOU SUPPORTED THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SHE NEEDED TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> SO LET'S BE CLEAR.
I MEAN, YES, DEBI'S STRESSED
AND DEBI'S WORKING HARD,
BUT SHE WANTS YOU TO GO BACK TO
SCHOOL.
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE BEING
SELFISH BY GOING BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> NO.
>> OKAY.
DEBI, YOU'VE BEEN VERY, UM,
VOCAL ABOUT YOUR CONCERNS ABOUT
TEEN PREGNANCY.
ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE TO SAY TO
PEOPLE WATCHING OUT THERE?
>> USE CONDOMS. USE PROTECTION.
THEY JUST REALLY NEED TO KNOW
THAT IT IS VERY HARD.
IT IS VERY HARD, AND YOU ARE
DEALING WITH A HUMAN LIFE
THAT YOU HAVE TO SACRIFICE AND
TAKE CARE.
YOU KNOW, AND IF YOU KNOW THAT
YOUR FREEDOM'S GONE, YOUR TIME
IS GONE, YOUR SLEEP IS GONE.
>> YOUR CHILDHOOD'S GONE.
YOU KNOW, IT...
>> TRUE?
>> IF YOU VALUE GOING OUT,
STAYING OUT LATE, VALUE YOUR
SLEEP, AND BEING CAREFREE
AND NOT HAVING TO DO ANYTHING,
WEAR PROTECTION, BIRTH CONTROL,
SOMETHING.
>> NO MATTER WHAT.
IF YOU HAVE TO ASK SOME BUM OFF
THE STREET FOR A CONDOM,
ASK THE BUM OFF THE STREET
FOR A CONDOM.
LIKE...
>> WELL, THANK ALL OF YOU FOR
BEING HERE, AND MORE WITH TAYLOR
AT THE END OF THE SHOW, OF
COURSE.
BUT FOR NOW IT'S TIME FOR A
LITTLE BREAK, AND WE WILL COME
BACK WITH JAMIE, WHOSE STORY GOT
MORE INTENSE AND COMPLICATED
ONCE THE CAMERAS STOPPED
ROLLING.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO LIFE AFTER
LABOR.
I'M DR. DREW.
ONE IN SIX AMERICAN TEENS WILL
HAVE A BABY BEFORE TURNING 20.
THAT'S ONE IN SIX.
JAMIE'S HERE WITH US.
JAMIE, DID YOU EVER THINK YOU'D
BE ONE OF THOSE GIRLS?
>> NO.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD HAPPEN
TO ME.
>> OKAY, WELL, WE'LL TALK MORE
WITH JAMIE AND BRING OUT HER MOM
AND THE BABY'S FATHER AFTER THE
RECAP OF HER STORY.
TAKE A LOOK.
>> JAMIE IS PREGNANT?
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO REACT.
>> DON'T MAKE THE SAME MISTAKE.
>> SO, LIKE, RYAN, YOU THINK
HE'S GOING TO STEP UP?
>> HE DOESN'T FULLY
UNDERSTAND IT.
CAN YOU HANDLE IT, RYAN?
>> YOU NEVER CAN BE PREPARED FOR
IT, YOU KNOW?
>> HE'S A 17-YEAR-OLD KID TRYING
TO BE A GROWN-UP.
YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE
MIAH?
>> I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO TAKE
MIAH.
>> I GUESS WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
SEE HOW IT GOES.
>> SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
DEEP BREATH, AND PUSH ANOTHER
TIME FOR HER BODY.
AND LOOK AT MAMA.
>> OH, LOOK.
YOU'RE NOT EVEN OLD ENOUGH TO
DRINK, AND YOU SHOW UP
HUNG OVER.
>> WHICH MAJOR POPULATION SHIFT
OCCURRED AS A RESULT OF
INDUSTRIALIZATION?
>> I HAVEN'T READ FAR ENOUGH TO
THIS ONE.
>> WHO CHEATS ON THEIR PREGNANT
GIRLFRIEND?
>> A DOUCHE BAG.
RYAN.
>> IT WOULD TOTALLY BE A LOT
DIFFERENT, JAMIE, IF HE HADN'T
SPUN ME ALL THAT [bleep] THAT HE
LOVED YOU AND LOVED MIAH.
HE WAS GOING TO BE THERE.
AND ALL ALONG BEHIND THE SCENES,
HE'S BEEN DOING GOD ONLY KNOWS
WHAT.
>> YOU CHEATED ON ME.
>> I CHEATED ON YOU?
>> I KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO JUST
DENY IT.
I KNOW.
YOU AND I AREN'T GOING TO WORK
ANYTHING OUT.
WE HAVE TO GO TO COURT,
AND THAT'S THAT.
>> WELL, YOU'RE HAVING SOME
FEELINGS.
>> WELL, YEAH.
>> DID SOMETHING SPECIFIC
TRIGGER YOU?
JUST HOW INTENSE THIS LAST
YEAR'S BEEN.
NOW, WHEN WE LEFT OFF, YOU AND
RYAN WERE GOING TO COURT TO
FIGURE OUT HOW OFTEN HE COULD
SEE MIAH.
WHERE DO WE STAND NOW?
>> HE SEES HER EVERY WEDNESDAY
AT THE VISITATION CENTER.
IT'S SUPERVISED, AND HE SEES HER
FOR AN HOUR.
>> DOES HE COME EVERY TIME?
>> HE'S ONLY MISSED ONE DAY.
>> SO HE'S BEEN SHOWING UP.
>> YES.
>> THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE ARE YOU AND HE AT?
>> WE DO NOT SPEAK AT ALL.
I CHANGED MY NUMBER SO HE COULD
NOT CONTACT ME AT ALL.
>> IS THAT HARD?
>> YEAH.
I'VE BEEN WITH HIM FOR TWO
YEARS.
>> WELL, YOUR FRIENDS SAW HIM
THE WAY YOU SEE HIM NOW.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW COME YOU DIDN'T SEE IT?
>> LOVE IS BLIND.
>> TALK TO ME ABOUT RYAN'S
CHEATING.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> I CANNOT BELIEVE I DID NOT
SEE IT, BECAUSE I WAS LIKE,
WHEN I WAS PREGNANT, I WAS LIKE,
"NO. I HAVE A GOOD MAN.
HE'S NOT GOING TO DO THAT TO ME.
HE LOVES ME."
>> YOU ASKED THE QUESTION IN
YOUR EPISODE "WHO CHEATS ON
THEIR PREGNANT GIRLFRIEND?"
>> MM-HMM.
AND CYBIL SAYS "A DOUCHE BAG,"
SO I GUESS THAT'S WHAT HE IS.
>> OKAY.
WELL, WE'LL LET PEOPLE AT HOME
JUDGE FOR THEMSELVES.
LET'S BRING OUT RYAN AND JAMIE'S
MOM, APRIL.
[applause]
HAVE A SEAT, GUYS.
SO, RYAN, DID YOU HEAR WHAT WE
WERE TALKING ABOUT?
>> UH, A LITTLE BIT.
>> DEFEND YOURSELF TO PEOPLE
AT HOME.
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, I JUST
WANT TO SAY NO ONE'S PERFECT,
YOU KNOW.
I DID MAKE PLENTY OF MISTAKES.
I AM GUILTY OF BEING A BAD
BOYFRIEND.
I DIDN'T CHEAT ON HER.
>> YOU DIDN'T CHEAT ON HER?
>> I DID BREAK UP WITH HER,
AND THE NEXT DAY, I DID HOOK UP
WITH A GIRL AND...
>> APRIL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> RYAN HAS A WAY OF TWISTING
THE TRUTH.
>> ISN'T THAT CALLED LYING?
>> YEAH, IN MY BOOK, IT IS.
>> APRIL, YOU LOOK DISTRAUGHT.
>> [sighs]
THE WHOLE THING'S VERY
STRESSFUL.
>> IT IS VERY STRESSFUL.
>> YEAH, AND IT DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE IT'S GOING TO GET ANY
BETTER.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT I EXPECTED.
>> DID YOU TALK ABOUT SEX?
>> WE DID, BUT JAMIE TRIED TO
TALK TO ME, AND IT'S MY FAULT.
SHE DID.
SHE ASKED ME TO PUT HER ON THE
PILL, AND I HAD MY HEAD IN THE
CLOUDS OR SOMETHING.
I'M NOT SURE--I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WAS GOING ON, AND...
I WAS LIKE, "NO, YOU NEED TO NOT
BE HAVING SEX."
I WAS STUPID, IN HINDSIGHT.
>> IT'S NOT STUPIDITY.
IT'S JUST HARD.
THESE ARE HARD THINGS TO DEAL
WITH.
GOING FORWARD, DO WE HAVE A
CIVIL SORT OF RELATIONSHIP
GOING FORWARD, OR YOU GUYS CAN'T
EVEN BE AROUND EACH OTHER?
>> WE DON'T SPEAK.
I'M JUST TO THE POINT WHERE--
>> SHE'S BLOCKED MY NUMBER,
SO I CAN'T EVEN ASK HOW MY
DAUGHTER'S DOING.
>> YOU SEE HER EVERY WEEK.
>> ONCE A WEEK FOR AN HOUR.
A COP ESCORTS ME IN AND ESCORTS
ME OUT, LIKE A CRIMINAL.
>> YOU JUST HAVE TO EARN YOUR
TRUST.
>> HOW COME WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME
YOU CAN TRUST ME TO BE AROUND
MY DAUGHTER...
>> BECAUSE I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
DOING ANYTHING YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO, 'CAUSE I KNOW
YOU'RE NOT HANGING OUT WITH THE
BAD PEOPLE OR DOING THE BAD
THINGS BECAUSE I'M THERE
WATCHING YOU.
BUT WHEN I'M NOT THERE, I DON'T
KNOW.
YOU COULD BE TAKING HER TO THE
POOL HALL.
GIRLS THAT YOU HANG OUT WITH.
YOU COULD BE TAKING HER
ANYWHERE, DOING WHATEVER.
>> WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
YOU COULD TALK TO MY STEPMOM.
WHY WOULD YOU DO WHAT YOU'VE
DONE SINCE I WAS PREGNANT?
>> WELL, LET ME ASK YOU THIS,
WHAT KIND OF RELATIONSHIP DO YOU
WANT RYAN TO HAVE WITH MIAH
IN THE FUTURE?
>> I WANT HIM TO BE AROUND.
>> YOU DO WANT HIM TO BE AROUND.
YOU WANT HIM TO BUILT THAT TRUST
AND HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH
HER.
>> I MEAN, LIKE, IF HE REALLY
DOES GOOD FOR A LONG TIME,
LIKE, IT'S NOT LIKE I'M GOING TO
KEEP HER AWAY FOREVER.
WHEN SHE GETS OLDER, SHE'S GOING
TO BE LIKE, "MOMMY, CAN I GO
WITH DADDY HERE?"
AND I WANT TO BE ABLE TO BE
LIKE, "YEAH, HONEY, GO ON."
>> DID YOU MISS JAMIE'S LABOR?
>> I WAS THERE FOR THE BABY
BEING BORN.
I WAS THERE AN HOUR BEFORE THE
BABY WAS BORN.
>> SO DO YOU WANT TO TRY TO SET
THE RECORD STRAIGHT ABOUT WHAT
REALLY HAPPENED THAT NIGHT?
>> I WAS AT MY FRIEND'S HOUSE.
>> WHO?
>> MATT.
>> OKAY, MATT'S HOUSE.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING THERE?
SHE'S HAVING A BABY?
>> I DIDN'T KNOW SHE WAS HAVING
A BABY YET.
>> YOU GUYS ARE HANGING OUT.
>> MY PHONE WAS DEAD.
>> HOW DID YOU GET A HICKEY ON
YOUR NECK?
>> HUH?
>> HOW DID YOU GET A HICKEY ON
YOUR NECK?
>> I TOLD YOU. A GIRL.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU HAD SEX
WITH ANOTHER GIRL.
>> YEAH, THAT WAS AFTER WE
BROKE UP.
WE WAS ALREADY BROKEN UP BEFORE
THAT.
>> TWO DAYS.
>> BY THE WAY...
>> I ADMITTED THAT WHEN I FIRST
CAME ON THE SHOW.
I MEAN, I SCREWED UP, YEAH.
I DIDN'T CHEAT ON HER, THOUGH.
THAT'S NOT CHEATING.
>> I KNOW AS A YOUNG GIRL,
THIS KIND OF STUFF HAS
MONUMENTAL MEANING, BUT THAT'S,
AGAIN, ANOTHER REASON WHY YOUNG
PEOPLE, YOU KNOW, CAN'T HANDLE
HAVING KIDS, BECAUSE THIS IS HOW
YOUNG PEOPLE TREAT EACH OTHER IN
RELATIONSHIPS.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE WITH THAT.
BUT WHEN YOU PUT A KID IN THERE,
IT HAS BIG MEANING.
>> AND THAT'S WHY WE KEEP--
THAT'S WHY WE NEED TO SEPARATE
AND, LIKE, COOL OFF.
HE CAN STILL HER, AND THEN WE'LL
MATURE, HE'LL BE ABLE TO SEE HER
STILL, AND THEN EVENTUALLY,
IT'LL BE ABLE TO BE A WORKING
RELATIONSHIP.
>> HOPEFULLY.
>> AGAIN, IT'S MESSY.
IT'S HARD TO SAY SOMETHING THAT
WRAPS UP STORIES LIKE THIS,
'CAUSE IT'S YOUR LIFE NOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE ONGOING.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I COMMEND YOU FOR
ALL--APRIL, THANK YOU FOR
STAYING IN HER LIFE.
JAMIE, KEEP GOING AT SCHOOL.
RYAN, I REALLY HOPE YOU SUCCEED.
IF YOU DO, I'LL BE THE FIRST ONE
TO CHEER YOU ON.
I HOPE SO.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, MORE WITH JAMIE
LATER WHEN THE MOMS GET TO ASK
EACH OTHER QUESTIONS.
BUT FOR NOW, WE'RE GOING TO STEP
ASIDE FOR A BREAK AND RETURN
WITH CLEONDRA.
NOW, THERE WERE MANY QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHERE BABY KYLEE SHOULD BE
STAYING, SO WHERE IS SHE,
AND WHERE IS CLEONDRA LIVING
RIGHT NOW?
THAT, ALONG WITH SOME BREAKING
NEWS ABOUT HER RELATIONSHIP
WITH KYLEE'S DAD, MARIO,
NEXT.
[applause]
>> WE'RE BACK WITH MORE LIFE
AFTER LABOR.
IT'S THE 16 AND PREGNANT FINALE
SPECIAL,HOSTED BY MYSELF,
DR. DREW.
OKAY, OUR NEXT MOM CLEONDRA IS
HERE WITH MY NOW.
SHE'S JOINED BY BABY KYLEE'S
FATHER, MARIO, AND BEFORE WE
TALK FURTHER, LET'S TAKE A LOOK
BACK AT CLEONDRA'S TIME BEING 16
AND PREGNANT.
>> WHEN WE FIRST OUT I WAS
PREGNANT, I WAS SCARED.
>> GOT A LITTLE BABY IN YOUR
STOMACH.
>> I THOUGHT THAT YOU WOULDN'T
END UP IN THE SITUATION
YOU'RE IN.
>> I JUST DON'T LIKE LOOKING
BACK ON IT, 'CAUSE IT STILL
DISAPPOINTS ME.
I FEEL LIKE YOU'LL STAY HERE
AT THE BEGINNING A LOT MORE.
>> I AIN'T GOING TO BE OVER
HERE, NO.
IF SHE DOESN'T MOVE IN, THIS
ISN'T GOING TO WORK.
I MEAN, ME AND HER ISN'T GOING
TO WORK.
>> NO!
AH...
>> BIG BREATH, CHIN TO YOUR
CHEST, AND PUSH.
[baby crying]
>> I MEAN, YOU CAN EASILY STAY
HERE.
>> I CAN STAY HERE TONIGHT.
I'M JUST NOT GOING TO.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE YOU DON'T EVEN
CARE ABOUT ME ANYMORE OR
NOTHING.
>> A BABY CHANGES THINGS.
A BABY CHANGES PEOPLE'S LIVES.
>> WHY DON'T YOU LET HER SPEND
THE NIGHT AT MY HOUSE SO YOU CAN
HAVE A DAY TO SLEEP?
>> IF YOU CAN'T COMPROMISE NOW,
YOU DAMN SURE AIN'T GOING TO BE
ABLE TO COMPROMISE TOGETHER
LIVING IN THE SAME HOUSE.
>> ALL RIGHT, CLEONDRA.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS?
HOW DO YOU FEEL WATCHING THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S A LOT.
>> IT'S A LOT TO TAKE IN.
>> YEAH.
>> HOW'S YOUR GUYS' RELATIONSHIP
NOW?
>> NOT DOING SO GOOD.
>> HOW COME?
>> WE JUST AREN'T GETTING ALONG
TOO WELL LATELY.
LIKE, THE PAST TWO WEEKS.
>> CLEONDRA LOOKS PISSED.
>> YEAH, SHE DOES.
>> WHAT ARE YOU PISSED ABOUT?
>> JUST OUR RELATIONSHIP.
IT'S A HOT MESS.
EVERYTHING'S JUST FALLING APART.
>> IT'S A HOT MESS.
WHAT'S SHE TALKING ABOUT, MARIO?
>> I'M NOT QUITE TOO SURE.
I GUESS SHE JUST--
WHAT'S SUCH A HOT MESS?
>> I MEAN, WE'RE JUST NOT
GETTING ALONG, AND EVERYTHING
SEEMS TO BE MY FAULT.
>> OH.
IS HE BLAMING YOU FOR
EVERYTHING?
>> SEEMS LIKE IT.
>> OR ARE YOU BLAMING HIM FOR
EVERYTHING?
>> NO.
HE SITS UP THERE AND SAYS WE
DON'T COMMUNICATE.
I TRY TO COMMUNICATE WITH HIM.
THEN HE GETS MAD ABOUT, LIKE,
HOW I'M FEELING.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
>> BROKEN.
>> YOU FEEL BROKEN?
HOW COME?
>> 'CAUSE WE'RE JUST FALLING
APART.
AND I JUST WANT KYLEE TO HAVE A
FAMILY--A MOM AND DAD IN HER
LIFE.
>> IS IT POSSIBLE, CLEONDRA,
THAT YOU'RE PUSHING MARIO AWAY?
>> I DON'T SEE HOW.
>> I GET THE FEELING YOU ARE
PUSHING HIM AWAY.
DO YOU WANT THIS TO WORK OUT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE NEVER GONE THROUGH A HARD
BREAK OR ANYTHING.
MARIO'S MY FIRST LOVE,
EVERYTHING.
>> BUT YOU WANT TO WORK IT OUT.
>> YEAH, I WANT TO WORK IT OUT.
>> SO IT STARTS LOOKING LIKE
YOU'RE TOO AFRAID THAT HE'S
GOING TO LEAVE, RIGHT?
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF YOU RISKED
GETTING BACK INTO THIS
RELATIONSHIP?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> MARIO, WHEN PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
ABANDONED, THEY EXPECT
ABANDONMENT, AND WHEN THEY DON'T
GET IT, IT FEELS CLINGY AND
VULNERABLE AND UNCOMFORTABLE
AND THEY USUALLY SABOTAGE IT.
SOUND FAMILIAR?
>> YES.
WE WERE FINE UP UNTIL SHE JUST
STARTED BEING OUT EVERYWHERE.
WE WERE FINE UP UNTIL--
>> I'M SORRY!
LOOK, I LIKE TO...
OKAY, BEING A TEEN PARENT,
YOU KNOW YOU DON'T GET TO DO
NOTHING.
>> YEAH, I DON'T KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT THAT.
WHAT DO I EVER GO TO DO?
>> YOU'RE IN SCHOOL STILL?
>> YES, AND I WORK A FULL-TIME
JOB.
>> WOW.
>> AND I DON'T COME HOME TILL
7:00 AT NIGHT.
>> THAT'S WHY HIS FAMILY'S
INVOLVED IN THE CHILDCARE?
>> YES.
EVERYBODY--WE HAVE, LIKE, THE
BEST SUPPORT SYSTEM.
SO IF WE NEED SOMEBODY TO WATCH
HER, THEY WILL WATCH HER.
>> DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
SPENDING ENOUGH TIME WITH HER?
>> NO, AND I HATE IT.
I HATE THAT...
>> THAT WHAT?
HATE THAT OTHER PEOPLE WATCH
HER?
YEAH.
WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY TO HAVE THAT,
THOUGH, RIGHT?
>> I KNOW, BUT I'D RATHER IT BE
ME THAN OTHER PEOPLE.
>> OF COURSE.
>> 'CAUSE IT'S LIKE, WITH MY
MOM, SHE RAISED FOUR KIDS BY
HERSELF AND WORKING TWO JOBS.
AND, I MEAN, SHE SAW US, BUT
IT WASN'T, LIKE, ENOUGH THAT A
MOM WANTS WITH THEIR CHILDREN.
>> AND YOU KNOW THAT FIRST-HAND.
MARIO, DO YOU LOVE CLEONDRA?
>> YEAH.
>> CAN YOU REALLY TELL HER THAT
IN A WAY THAT SHE CAN HEAR YOU?
PUT YOUR HAND RIGHT HERE ON HER
HEART.
I WANT YOU TO LOOK AT HIM.
>> I DO LOVE YOU.
>> CLEONDRA, YOU HAVE A TON
TO BE THANKFUL FOR.
HALF OF THE TEEN MOM, DADS DON'T
STICK AROUND.
MARIO IS SHOWING A LOT OF
WILLINGNESS.
THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES TO GET
RELATIONSHIPS BACK ON TRACK,
IS JUST WILLINGNESS.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THANK YOU GUYS
FOR SHARING WITH US AND BEING
WILLING TO BE OPEN AND COMMITTED
TO EACH OTHER, BECAUSE THAT'S
WHAT'S GOING TO BE IMPORTANT
FOR KYLEE, RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I HOPE YOU WORK THIS THROUGH.
WE'RE GOING TO STEP ASIDE
FOR A QUICK BREAK AND THEN
RETURN WITH KAYLA.
HER STORY IS COMING UP NEXT.
DON'T GO AWAY.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO THE 16 AND
PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL.
I AM DR. DREW, AND OUR NEXT TEEN
MOTHER IS KAYLA.
HERE IS HER JOURNEY.
>> I DIDN'T BELIEVE IT WHEN YOU
TOLD ME.
>> WHEN I TOLD YOU I WAS
PREGNANT?
>> YEAH.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'LL TRY TO BE
AROUND MORE WHEN THE BABY'S
HERE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> AND HOW COME YOU'RE NOT NOW?
I JUST WISH SHE WOULD SEE,
"OH, GEE, THERE'S A REASON MY
DAUGHTER'S UNHAPPY."
>> YEAH.
>> BUT SHE DOESN'T SEE IT THAT
WAY.
WHEN I WAS 13, I WAS
HOSPITALIZED FOR ANOREXIA.
IT'S SO HARD FOR ME BEING
PREGNANT AND GAINING ALL THIS
WEIGHT WITHOUT ANY CONTROL.
I FEEL REALLY LIGHT-HEADED.
I NEED TO STOP.
>> ALL SHE ATE WAS VANILLA
WAFERS THIS MORNING.
DO YOU WANT TO CALL YOUR DOCTOR?
>> HAVE HER GO TO LABOR AND
DELIVERY NOW.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO SCARED.
>> THE LIGHT-HEADED AND
DIZZINESS OFTEN TIMES WILL
HAPPEN IF YOU HAVEN'T EAT OR
DRINK A WHOLE LOT,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE PREGNANT.
>> MICHAEL!
I JUST FELT LIKE I'M, LIKE,
LEAKING.
>> NOT YET.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
A LOT OF PRESSURE HERE.
OH, CONGRATULATIONS.
>> HE'S PERFECT.
>> YES, HE IS.
>> [crying]
>> WHY WON'T HE GO TO SLEEP?
>> ARE YOU GOING BACK TO WORK
TOMORROW?
>> YEAH.
>> SERIOUSLY?
>> HE'S YOURS.
>> DOESN'T IT JUST SEEM, LIKE, A
LOT EASIER TO, LIKE, DROP OUT
AND GET YOUR GED?
>> I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU DO
THAT.
>> YOU GOT TO REALIZE YOU CAN'T
LIVE ANYWHERE FOR FREE.
IF MIKE'S GOING TO STAY HERE,
HE NEEDS TO PAY $300 A MONTH.
>> THE HEAT GOES OUT AND WE HAVE
TO GET A HOTEL ROOM, AND I HAVE
TO PAY FOR IT ENTIRELY BY
MYSELF.
BUT YOU'RE ALL NICE AND WARM IN
YOUR BOYFRIEND'S HOUSE, SO IT
WASN'T THAT BIG OF A CONCERN
TO YOU.
YOU WANT ME TO GO ON A DIET WITH
YOU?
>> JUST START WATCHING WHAT
WE'RE EATING.
YOU COULD PROBABLY DISCIPLINE
ME, CONSIDERING WHAT YOU'VE GONE
THROUGH.
>> YOU WERE LIKE MY BEST FRIEND
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT,
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T
EVEN STAND TO BE AROUND ME.
I JUST WANT THINGS TO GO BACK TO
THE WAY THEY USED TO BE.
>> ALL RIGHT, KAYLA.
WHAT ARE THE TEARS ABOUT?
>> IT'S WEIRD SEEING IT
ALTOGETHER.
>> ANYTHING PARTICULAR CUT
THROUGH TO YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
JUST STUFF WITH MY MOM.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK WAS GOING
ON WITH HER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE SHE THOUGHT THAT I
COULD JUST TAKE CARE OF MYSELF,
WHICH I COULD, BUT IT JUST HURT
THAT SHE WAS KIND OF LIKE,
"OKAY, YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
YOU'RE FINE."
THAT KIND OF THING.
>> WAS THAT THE FIRST TIME IN
YOUR LIFE THAT SHE'S MADE YOU
FEEL LIKE THAT?
>> NO.
>> WHEN ELSE?
>> WHEN MY PARENTS GOT DIVORCED.
>> WHERE'S YOUR DAD?
>> I LIVE WITH HIM NOW.
>> YOU LIVE WITH YOUR DAD
AND NOT WITH DEB?
>> THERE WAS A POINT WHERE SHE
MOVED AWAY FROM ALL OF US KIDS,
AND THAT WAS HARD.
IT WAS SO EASY FOR HER TO PICK
UP AND LEAVE.
>> IS THAT WHEN YOUR EATING
DISORDER STARTED?
HOW'S THE EATING DISORDER NOW?
>> IT'S PRETTY LOUD, AS THEY
CALL IT.
>> IT'S TALKING TO YOU?
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY.
AND HOW'S YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH
MIKE?
>> WE DON'T REALLY HAVE ONE.
>> YOU DON'T HAVE A
RELATIONSHIP WITH MIKE?
>> MM-MM.
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WE JUST BROKE UP, AND WE
DON'T REALLY TALK ANYMORE.
>> HOW DID THE BREAKDOWN
GO DOWN?
WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT FELT LIKE I WAS PUTTING ON
A SHOW FOR EVERYBODY, 'CAUSE
EVERYBODY EXPECTED US TO BE
TOGETHER AND MAKE THIS PERFECT
FAMILY AND GET MARRIED AND ALL
THIS STUFF.
AND THEN ONE DAY IT JUST,
LIKE...
WHY AM I CRYING SO MUCH?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
ONE DAY WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I JUST REALIZED I DIDN'T,
LIKE, FEEL FOR HIM WHAT YOU
SHOULD FEEL FOR SOMEBODY WHEN
YOU WANT TO SPEND THE REST OF
YOUR LIFE WITH HIM.
LIKE, I KNEW THAT ONLY REASON I
WAS WITH HIM WAS BECAUSE OF
PRESTON, AND THAT WASN'T FAIR TO
ANY OF US.
>> HMM.
YOUR MOM SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
YOU TWO GOING ON A DIET
TOGETHER.
>> WELL, I DON'T--
I DON'T THINK SHE MEANT ME TO BE
OFFENDED BY IT.
>> DID THAT KICK UP YOUR
SYMPTOMS?
>> THEY WERE ALREADY PRETTY BAD
AT THAT POINT, SO...
>> SO THEY DIDN'T GET WORSE.
>> MM-MM.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, LET'S TALK
MORE ABOUT THAT.
LET'S BRING DEB ON OUT HERE,
SHALL WE?
DEB?
[applause]
HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> ARE YOU?
SO KAYLA'S BEEN TALKING ABOUT
SOME HEAVY FEELINGS SHE'S
HAVING.
DID YOU HEAR ALL THAT?
>> I DID.
>> WE SEE HER IN THIS EPISODE
SAYING THAT SHE FELT ABANDONED
BY YOU.
IS SHE JUST OVERREACTING?
>> I THINK THAT ONCE KAYLA GOT
PREGNANT, I KIND OF LOOKED AT
HER AS...
GROWN UP,
THAT SHE JUST GREW UP REALLY
FAST.
AND I THINK THERE WAS JUST A LOT
THAT I SAW THAT I THOUGHT SHE
COULD DO ON HER OWN.
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO SAY TO
THAT?
>> I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND, BUT I
DON'T THINK THAT WAS THE REASON
TO, LIKE, RUN AWAY FROM ME.
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT TOOK PRECEDENT OVER YOU?
>> HER BOYFRIEND.
>> IS THAT TRUE?
>> MAYBE.
MAYBE.
>> NOW, WHEN YOU WERE LIVING IN
YOUR MOM'S HOUSE, WERE YOU LEFT
TO DEAL WITH THE UTILITIES
AND FOOD AND ALL THAT KIND OF
STUFF?
>> YEP.
>> HOW DID YOU GUYS DO THAT?
>> WE SCRAPED TOGETHER.
LIKE, THERE WERE TIMES WHERE
SHE WOULDN'T BUY GROCERIES FOR
MONTHS, AND ME AND MIKE WOULD
MAKE IT WORK, AND I'D BE,
LIKE...
>> HOW ABOUT THE UTILITIES?
I THOUGHT THERE WAS SOMETHING
IN THE SHOW ONE NIGHT WHERE YOU
DIDN'T HAVE HEAT?
>> UM, WELL, THAT'S WHEN THE
HEAT WASN'T WORKING, AND MY
MOM'S JUST LIKE, "WELL, GET A
HOTEL."
AND SO 'CAUSE SHE WAS AT HER
BOYFRIEND'S HOUSE AND SHE DIDN'T
CARE THAT HEAT WASN'T WORKING.
>> YOU WERE GOING TO PAY FOR THE
HOTEL ROOM?
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> I PAID FOR IT.
>> YOU PAID FOR THE HOTEL ROOM.
HOW DID YOU AFFORD THAT?
THAT'S WHAT I'M CONFUSED ABOUT.
>> SAVINGS.
>> DEB, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
TELL PEOPLE AT HOME WHO ARE
SITTING IN JUDGMENT OF YOU
AND WANT TO KNOW WHY YOU WEREN'T
THERE, WHY YOU'RE MORE UP WITH
YOUR BOYFRIEND, WHY KAYLA'S LEFT
FEELING LIKE THIS?
>> I KNOW I COULD HAVE DONE
BETTER.
I KNOW I COULD HAVE.
>> I DIDN'T HEAR YOU APOLOGIZE
HERE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN APOLOGIZING
TO HER?
>> I HAVE. I'M SORRY.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> BUT SHE REALLY NEEDS YOU.
>> MM-HMM.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, EATING
DISORDERS ARE REALLY COMMON
AMONGST TEENAGE GIRLS,
OBVIOUSLY, AND THERE IS SUPPORT
OUT THERE.
IF YOU NEED HELP, GET MORE
INFORMATION AT THE NATIONAL
EATING DISORDER ASSOCIATION
WEBSITE.
THAT IS:
ALL RIGHT, WELL, KAYLA FOUND
A SUPPORTIVE PARTNER IS
PRESTON'S FATHER, MIKE.
BUT AS WE'RE HEARING, THINGS ARE
A WHOLE LOT DIFFERENT NOW THAN
THEY WERE LAST TIME WE SAW THEM.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK,
AND THEN MIKE AND KAYLA WILL
GIVE US THE UPDATE.
SO DON'T MOVE.
[applause]
>> WE'RE BACK AT THE 16 AND
PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL.
I'M YOUR HOST, DR. DREW.
STILL HERE WITH US, KAYLA,
AND NOW JOINED AS WELL BY HER
BABY'S FATHER, MIKE.
NOW, KAYLA, IN MANY OF THESE
EPISODES WE HEAR ABOUT THE
BABY'S FATHER BEING A
SIGNIFICANT SOURCE OF STRESS
FOR THESE YOUNG GIRLS.
FOR YOU, IT SEEMED LIKE
HE WAS THE GLUE IN YOUR LIFE.
BUT THAT'S CHANGED.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, AS FAR AS A FATHER GOES,
HE'S STILL--HE'S AMAZING.
LIKE, HE, LIKE, SUPPORTS PRESTON
ENTIRELY, LIKE, AS FAR AS, LIKE,
FINANCIALLY GOES AND BUYING HIM
THINGS, AND HE'S ALSO--
LIKE, HE ADORES HIM.
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE STATISTICALLY
HE'S NOT LIKE OTHER TEEN DADS
AT ALL.
>> IS SHE RIGHT, MIKE?
>> UM, ACCORDING TO MY FAMILY,
LIKE, MY PARENTS, THEY SAY
FATHERHOOD SUITS ME.
>> [laughs]
>> SO I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S A
GOOD THING OR A BAD THING,
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I ABSOLUTELY LOVE PRESTON.
I WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR HIM
RIGHT NOW.
>> SO YOU'RE COMMITTED.
>> YES.
>> HE'S GOT YOU FOR LIFE.
>> YEP, HE DOES.
>> I UNDERSTAND YOU BROKE UP
RECENTLY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW WAS THAT FOR YOU, MIKE?
>> WHAT I FEEL HAPPENED IS,
LIKE, WHEN I STARTED MY NEW JOB,
I WAS GETTING UP EARLY, GOING TO
BED EARLY.
>> SO YOU WEREN'T AVAILABLE.
>> YEAH.
>> IS THAT ACCURATE?
I MEAN, HE WOULD, LIKE, GO TO
BED AND, LIKE, HE WOULDN'T
SAY GOOD NIGHT.
AND JUST LITTLE THINGS LIKE THAT
JUST STARTED GETTING TO ME.
>> HOW ABOUT WORKING ON THOSE
THINGS?
>> WE WERE WORKING ON IT FOR,
LIKE, THREE YEARS.
>> DO YOU STILL LOVE HIM?
>> AS PRESTON'S DAD.
>> DO YOU LOVE HER?
>> OF COURSE I DO.
>> ARE YOU STILL IN LOVE WITH
HER?
>> YES.
>> OH, BOY.
WHAT DO WE DO WITH THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU SEEING SOMEONE ELSE?
>> MM.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO THE CHEERFUL
GIRL I MET AND FELL IN LOVE
WITH?
>> STOP.
>> THAT'S HARD TO HEAR?
>> WELL, JUST, THINGS CAN'T BE
THE SAME AS THEY WERE WHEN
I WAS 15.
LIKE...
>> FOR SURE.
>> YEAH, AND YOU HAVE A BABY.
YOU CAN'T JUST...
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
>> CHANGES EVERYTHING.
>> I JUST THINK IT TOOK HAVING
PRESTON TO NOTICE THAT, LIKE,
THIS IS NOT--ALL MY LIFE HAS TO
BE, LIKE--I DON'T HAVE TO BE
STUCK WITH HIM.
>> THAT'S HEAVY.
DO YOU WORRY THAT THIS EATING
DISORDER IS GOING TO HURT KAYLA?
>> YEAH, AND IF PRESTON'S AROUND
HER WHEN IT'S HAPPENING, I'M
KIND OF SCARED FOR HIM TOO.
>> WORRIED ABOUT HIS SAFETY,
IF SHE PASSES OUT OR SOMETHING.
>> YEAH, IF HE'S, LIKE, ONE YEAR
OLD, LIKE, WHAT'S A ONE-YEAR-OLD
GOING TO DO?
>> WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THAT?
>> THERE'S NOTHING REALLY TO SAY
TO THAT.
IT'S JUST A BIG "WHAT IF?"
LIKE, THERE'S A MILLION
"WHAT IF"s WE CAN GO INTO,
BUT...
>> WELL, BUT IS IT A JUSTIFIED
FEAR?
>> I GUESS SO, YEAH.
>> OKAY.
I THINK THAT IF YOU GET HER
EATING DISORDER ADDRESSED
AND ASSESSED, I THINK SOME OF
THIS--ALL THIS AMBIVALENCE AND
STUFF WILL KIND OF SETTLE DOWN
A LITTLE BIT.
AT LEAST THERE WILL BE MORE
CLARITY.
>> HOPEFULLY.
>> 'CAUSE YOU'RE SORT OF
IN A VORTEX WITH YOUR EATING
DISORDER, AND THAT'S MAKING
EVERYTHING VERY CONFUSING,
ISN'T IT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> OKAY, BUT YOU HAVE COMMITTED
TO ME YOU WILL TALK TO SOMEBODY.
>> YEAH.
>> TELL ME WITH LOOKING ME IN
THE EYE AND TELL ME THAT.
>> I'LL TALK TO SOMEBODY.
>> OKAY. VERY GOOD.
>> PINKY PROMISE.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> NO.
>> PINKY PROMISE?
>> SHE'S NEVER GONE BACK ON A
PINKY PROMISE.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
COME ON. COME ON.
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, EXCELLENT.
ALL RIGHT, THANKS YOU GUYS FOR
JOINING US.
AND OUR NEXT TEENAGE MOTHER IS
KIANNA, AND HERE IS HER JOURNEY.
>> IT'S, LIKE, TWO MONTHS SINCE
WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER, BUT WE'RE
HAVING A BABY NOW.
>> TAKE CARE OF THE BABY
LIKE IT WAS A REAL LIVE BABY.
>> OKAY.
>> ROCK HER.
>> ROCK HER?
>> DO YOU THINK YOU'RE READY
TO HAVE A REAL BABY?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> HE JUST THINKS, "OH, IT'S A
BABY.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE OKAY."
WE'RE BOTH GOING TO HAVE TO GET
JOBS.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO STAY IN
SCHOOL BECAUSE THE BABY'S GOING
TO NEED BETTER.
>> I TOOK STEPS TO PREVENT THIS
FROM HAPPENING.
I MEAN, YOU STILL HAVE TIME
TO THINK ABOUT ADOPTION.
>> IF THAT'S WHAT YOU CHOOSE TO
DO, THAT'S WHAT YOU CHOOSE TO
DO.
YOU MIGHT GOING TO REGRET IT
ONE DAY WHEN YOU'RE GROWN.
I CAN GIVE UP ANYTHING.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE
SOMEBODY ELSE RAISE MY SON.
>> I'M WILLING TO KEEP THE BABY
IF YOU'RE GOING TO SIT HERE AND
HELP ME.
>> GOOD.
>> THE CONCERN IS, WITH ALL THE
SWELLING YOU'RE HAVING IN YOUR
LEGS, PREECLAMPSIA CAN BE
DANGEROUS FOR YOUR BABY.
>> SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE STILL
AT RISK.
WE WOULD LIKE TO JUST INDUCE
YOU.
>> OKAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO JUST GET YOU
PREPARED FOR A C-SECTION, OKAY?
[baby crying]
>> HOLD ON.
NO, NO, NO.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I'M TIRED.
WILL YOUR MAMA BRING YOU OVER
HERE?
>> I DOUBT IT.
SHE DON'T GET HOME TILL LATE.
>> OKAY.
I WISH THAT YOU COULD BE THERE
WITH US 24-7 TOO, LIKE, SO WE
COULD BE A FAMILY, INSTEAD OF
JUST BEING A FAMILY JUST ON THE
WEEKENDS.
>> ALL RIGHT, NOW I'M HERE WITH
KIANNA, HER MOTHER, RACHEL,
AND HER BABY'S FATHER, ZAK.
SO, KIANNA, YOU WERE
CONTEMPLATING CHOOSING ADOPTION,
IS THAT RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> BUT NOBODY ELSE SEEMED TO
THINK THAT WAS A GREAT IDEA.
>> HE DIDN'T LIKE THE IDEA OF
NOT RAISING HIS OWN SON.
>> ZAK DIDN'T LIKE THAT.
>> NO.
>> HOW ABOUT YOUR MOM?
>> SHE WOULD GO EITHER WAY
AND SUPPORT ME.
>> SO YOU WERE IN FAVOR OF
ADOPTION, MOM?
>> I WAS IN FAVOR OF ADOPTION,
BUT MORE IN FAVOR OF HER KEEPING
THE BABY.
>> WHAT STEPS DID YOU TAKE TO
PREVENT THIS, MOM?
>> WELL, WITH ME BEING A TEEN
MOM, OF COURSE, WHEN SHE CAME OF
AGE, I KNEW WHAT WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
TEENAGERS ARE TEENAGERS.
SO I PUT HER ON BIRTH CONTROL.
AND SO, I MEAN, THE ONLY THING I
EXPECTED FOR HER TO DO WAS TO
TAKE THE BIRTH CONTROL, AND AS
YOU CAN SEE, THAT DID NOT
HAPPEN.
>> SO NOW YOU'VE COMMITTED
TO PARENTING, AND ARE YOU
COMMITTED TO KIANNA?
>> YES.
>> FOR LIFE.
>> YEP.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO DO IT THE
HARD WAY.
>> THERE'S A RING RIGHT THERE.
>> OH, WHAT'S THAT NOW?
>> A RING.
>> THAT'S NICE.
SO THAT'S HOW YOUR RELATIONSHIP
HAS MOVED ALONG.
AND HOW DOES THAT FEEL?
>> IT MADE ME FEEL LIKE HE WAS
FOR REAL ABOUT US, AND HE WASN'T
GOING TO LEAVE ME.
>> OKAY.
SO ZAK'S BEEN A PRETTY GOOD
PARTNER.
>> MM-HMM.
>> ZAK, YOU'RE COMMITTED FOR
LIFE HERE.
YOU'RE ALL THE WAY IN.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
>> 16.
>> ARE YOU HAVING TROUBLE WITH
THAT?
STAYING COMMITTED?
>> I DON'T THINK SO.
>> YOU HAD SAID, ZAK, THAT YOU
DO WANT YOUR CHILD TO HAVE MORE
THAN THE FIVE MEMORIES THAT YOU
HAVE OF YOUR DAD.
YOU ONLY FIVE MEMORIES OF HIM.
>> YEP.
>> WERE THEY GOOD?
BAD.
YEAH, IT'S VERY EMOTIONAL FOR
YOU.
WHAT STEPS, ZAK, DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TAKING TO MAKE SURE THAT
YOUR BABY DOESN'T LIVE THE SAME
LIFE YOU DID?
>> THE RING.
THE RING.
>> THAT'S GOING TO KEEP YOU IN?
YEAH.
KIANNA?
YOU ALL IN WITH HIM?
>> MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU TRUST HER ALL THE WAY,
ZAK?
>> STARTING TO.
WHY WERE YOU NOT TRUSTWORTHY?
>> DIDN'T TRUST NOBODY, REALLY.
>> DIDN'T TRUST ANYBODY.
>> AFTER MY DAD.
>> OH.
THAT'S VERY COURAGEOUS OF YOU,
BY THE WAY, TO RISK A REAL
ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIP WITH
TRUST.
RACHEL, WHAT ARE YOU SEEING
HERE?
>> I'M SEEING A YOUNG COUPLE
THAT'S GOT A LONG WAY TO GO.
>> YEAH.
FOR YOU GUYS, FOR ZAK FIRST,
WHAT ARE YOUR HOPES FOR THE
FUTURE?
>> GET A GOOD JOB, EDUCATION.
>> KIANNA, HOW ABOUT YOU?
>> I WANT TO GO TO COLLEGE FIRST
THING AND GET A CAREER, AND I
JUST WANT TO MAKE THE BEST LIFE
AS POSSIBLE FOR KAY'DEN.
>> ZAK, YOU BEHIND HER ON THIS?
>> 100%.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I HOPE YOU DO IT.
KIANNA, ZAK, RACHEL, MOM,
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
KIANNA WILL CHAT WITH THE OTHER
MOMS IN JUST A BIT, BUT FIRST
IT'S TIME FOR ANOTHER BREAK.
WHEN LIFE AFTER LABORRETURNS,
I WILL CHAT WITH IZABELLA.
NOW, SHE ALIENATED FRIENDS AND
FAMILY BY HIDING HER PREGNANCY.
DOES SHE REGRET THAT DECISION,
AND WHY DID SHE DO IT?
I WILL BE ASKING HER THAT AND
MUCH MORE AFTER THE BREAK.
[applause]
>> AND WE'RE BACK.
I'M DR. DREW.
THIS IS LIFE AFTER LABOR,
AND HERE IS A VERY SOBERING
FACT.
LESS THAN HALF OF YOUNG TEEN
MOTHERS EVER GRADUATE FROM HIGH
SCHOOL.
NOW, IZABELLA, YOU'VE CONTINUED
TO STRUGGLE WITH YOUR EDUCATION.
WHERE DOES IT STAND TODAY?
>> UM, I GO TO SCHOOL FULL-TIME
NOW, AND I'M GETTING PRETTY GOOD
GRADES.
>> WHO TAKES CARE OF THE BABY?
>> MY MOM.
>> LUCKY TO HAVE THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO DIVE INTO
IZABELLA'S STORY AND CHAT WITH
HER BABY'S FATHER, JAIRO,
AS WELL.
BUT FIRST, HERE IS HER JOURNEY
ON 16 AND PREGNANT.
>> IZABELLA'S PREGNANT.
>> REALLY?
>> SHE'S BEEN PREGNANT FOR 7 1/2
MONTHS.
>> EVERY TIME SOMEONE CALLS ME,
I HAVE TO, LIKE, MAKE UP SOME
LAME EXCUSE, AND THEY PROBABLY
THINK THAT I'M JUST, LIKE, BEING
RUDE.
I AM GOING TO LEAVE TO GO ON
VACATION.
I WILL TOTALLY TRY TO BE THERE.
THAT WILL BE AWESOME.
>> WE SHOULD START TELLING
PEOPLE.
>> UM, WELL, I'M PREGNANT.
I TEXTED YOU AND I TOLD YOU TO
HAVE A GOOD DAY, AND YOU NEVER
EVEN ANSWERED.
I'VE KNOWN HER SINCE, LIKE, I
WAS SIX, AND NOW SHE DOESN'T
TALK TO ME.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS FOR
COLLEGE?
>> I STILL DON'T KNOW.
>> MY DAUGHTER'S ACTUALLY
SCHEDULED FOR INDUCTION
THIS MORNING.
>> AND PUSH.
HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD,
>> SO CUTE.
[baby crying]
>> SO HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
SCHOOL TOMORROW?
>> YEAH, I'M NOT SO WORRIED
ABOUT SEEING THE PEOPLE.
I'M MORE NERVOUS ABOUT LEAVING
ENRIQUE.
I LOVE YOU.
>> I HAVE BEEN LYING
TO YOU GUYS.
I HAVE BEEN TELLING YOU THAT
I AM DOING MY HIGH SCHOOL ONLINE
WHEN I REALLY HAVEN'T.
>> YOU KNOW, TRUST IS A LOT.
IT MEANS A LOT.
I DON'T KNOW THAT I WANT YOU TO
BE WITH MY DAUGHTER.
>> I LOVE HIM, AND I WANT HIM TO
BE AROUND, BUT I THINK WE'VE
GIVEN HIM ENOUGH OPPORTUNITIES
ALREADY.
>> ALL RIGHT, GUYS, WELL, WHEN
WE LEFT OFF, IZABELLA, YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WAS ON SHAKY
GROUNDS WITH JAIRO.
WHERE ARE WE NOW?
>> UM, LIKE, TEN TIMES BETTER.
>> HOW COME?
DID YOU GO TO SCHOOL?
>> YEAH, I STEPPED UP AND GOT
A JOB AND STARTED GOING TO
SCHOOL.
>> JOB AND SCHOOL?
>> YEAH.
>> AND DID IZABELLA'S DAD GET A
LITTLE COOLER AFTER THAT?
>> YEAH, WAY COOLER.
>> WAY COOLER?
IZABELLA, HIDING IT MUST HAVE
BEEN EXCRUCIATING.
>> YEAH.
>> OR WERE YOU IN SO MUCH
DENIAL, YOU DIDN'T WANT TO EVEN
BELIEVE IT YOURSELF?
>> UM, AT FIRST, I THINK IT
STARTED OUT THAT WAY
AT THE VERY BEGINNING,
AND THEN ONCE I JUST KEPT GOING
ON WITH IT AND NOT TELLING
ANYONE, IT JUST WAS HARDER TO
TELL THEM.
>> HOW DID PEOPLE REACT WHEN YOU
TOLD THEM?
>> UM, THEY WERE REALLY HURT,
I THINK.
>> AND DISAPPOINTED?
>> YEAH.
>> IS THAT HARD FOR YOU?
>> HOW'D YOU GET THROUGH THAT?
>> UM, WELL, 'CAUSE I HAVE
REALLY GOOD SUPPORT WITH MY
PARENTS AND JAIRO.
>> YOU SEEM VERY SAD ABOUT IT.
>> IT'S JUST HARD TO TALK
ABOUT T.
>> ABOUT DISAPPOINTING YOUR
PARENTS?
DID YOU TALK TO YOUR PARENTS
ABOUT SEX AND BIRTH CONTROL?
>> YEAH.
IT WAS JUST AN ACCIDENT,
OBVIOUSLY.
>> WERE YOU TAKING ANY
PRECAUTION?
>> YEAH.
WE WERE USING CONDOMS.
>> AND IT BROKE.
>> BROKE.
>> AND THEN RIGHT AFTER, I TOOK
THE MORNING AFTER PILL.
>> UH-HUH.
>> LIKE, THE NEXT MORNING.
>> GOOD.
>> AND IT DIDN'T WORK.
>> LET'S THINK ABOUT MORNING
AFTER PILLS.
IF YOU'RE ALREADY PREGNANT,
YOU'RE GOING TO STAY PREGNANT.
YOU KNOW.
SO YOU MUST HAVE JUST OVULATED.
>> MM-HMM.
THAT'S WHAT THE DOCTOR SAID.
IT WAS, LIKE, RIGHT ON.
>> WHAT ROLE DO YOUR PARENTS
PLAY IN ALL THIS?
>> THEY HELP BOTH OF US SO MUCH,
I THINK.
>> SO YOU'RE REALLY LUCKY TO
HAVE THEM.
THAT'S HOW YOU'RE ABLE TO GO TO
SCHOOL, I IMAGINE.
>> I COULDN'T DO ANY OF IT
WITHOUT THEM.
>> WELL, LET'S BRING IZABELLA'S
PARENTS UP HERE, ERIC AND VI.
COME ON IN, GUYS.
[applause]
WELCOME, GUYS.
I WANT TO SORT OF PICK UP WHERE
WE WERE HERE.
HOW HAS THIS BEEN FOR YOU?
>> SHE'S MY BABY, YOU KNOW.
YOU NEVER EXPECT THAT
TO HAPPEN TO YOU.
I MEAN, YOU THINK YOU'VE TALKED
TO YOUR KIDS ABOUT, YOU KNOW,
SEX AND ALL THOSE THINGS,
PROTECTION, AND THEN THIS COMES
UP, AND, I MEAN, IT'S
OVERWHELMING.
>> YEAH, IT'S OVERWHELMING.
>> YOU KNOW, BUT IT HAPPENS.
IT'S REALITY.
>> VI, WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ON THE RELATIONSHIP WITH JAIRO?
>> THEY'VE GOTTEN A LOT BETTER.
>> WHAT WAS THE PROBLEM?
>> HE'S A TEENAGER STILL,
AND, YOU KNOW, HE STILL WANTED
TO GO FUN WITH HIS FRIENDS.
AND, YOU KNOW, I THINK HE'S
BECOME REALLY RESPONSIBLE.
>> ERIC, WHEN YOU FOUND OUT HE
HAD BEEN LYING ABOUT HIS
EDUCATION, HOW'D YOU GET
THROUGH THAT?
>> I WAS VERY DISAPPOINTED,
BECAUSE I BELIEVED HIM.
I MEAN, I BELIEVED HIM.
BUT I THINK HE DID STEP UP
TO THE PLATE WHEN HE CAME TO US
AND SAID, "I HAD BEEN LYING."
AND THE ONLY THING WE ASKED OF
HIM IS, "WELL, OKAY, FINE.
YOU LIED.
PLEASE CHANGE IT AND DON'T LIE
TO US ANYMORE."
>> DID HE CHANGE IT?
>> HE DID.
HE ACTUALLY DID.
>> JAIRO, ARE YOU GOING TO BE
AROUND FOR THE LONG HAUL?
>> YEAH.
>> HOW DO WE KNOW THAT?
>> WE'RE ENGAGED.
>> YOU'RE ENGAGED.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
CAN I SEE THE RING?
OH, VERY NICE. LOVELY.
>> THANKS.
>> CONGRATULATIONS.
>> both: THANKS.
>> WELL, THANK YOU GUYS FOR
BEING HERE.
I MEAN, WELL DONE, MOM AND DAD.
I MEAN, IT'S--THEY'RE GREAT
KIDS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> THIS JUST SENT THEM OFF THE
RAIL QUITE A BIT.
>> MM-HMM, YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, STICK
AROUND, AND WE'RE GOING TO CHECK
BACK WITH YOU GUYS A LITTLE BIT
LATER.
BUT RIGHT NOW WE'RE GOING TO
REVISIT ANOTHER 16 AND PREGNANT
STORY.
THIS IS ALLIE AND HER PATH TO
WHERE SHE IS TODAY.
>> LIKE, I CAN'T GO TO MY MOM'S.
IF I COULD GO TO MY MOM'S HOUSE,
THEN ME AND JOEY ARE NOT
TOGETHER.
I KNOW IT'S YOUR MOM, BUT I
DON'T WANT TO BE HERE.
>> DRUGS HAVE REALLY JUST MESSED
UP HER MIND.
>> SO WHAT?
I'M A DOPE FIEND, BITCH.
WHAT?
I WANT HER OUT.
YOU ARE NOT TO STEP FOOT IN MY
[bleep] HOUSE.
YOU BITCH!
>> I'M NOT EVEN GOING TO
GRADUATE IF WE STAY OVER THERE.
>> GET YOUR [bleep] ASS OUT OF
MY [bleep] HOUSE.
>> ALLISON, YOU CAN COME HOME.
BUT LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
YOUR LIFE WILL DRASTICALLY TURN
AROUND.
>> [crying]
>> JOEY, GIVE HER YOUR HAND.
>> I DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
THAT WILL MAKE HER AGGRAVATED.
>> PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH, PUSH.
>> OH, MY GOD.
D.>> I'LL GET HIM.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I EVEN ASKED.
YOU DON'T HELP.
HE'S BEEN PISSING ME OFF LATELY
'CAUSE HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING.
HE'S NOT READY FOR THE
RESPONSIBILITY, AND IT'S A
LITTLE LATE TO NOT BE READY.
>> I SAID HE SMELLED, LIKE, A
WHILE AGO.
>> THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU CHANGE
HIM A WHILE AGO?
>> YEAH?
>> WOULD YOU BE WITH HIM NOW IF
IT WASN'T FOR HIM?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU'RE FRIGGIN' UNGRATEFUL.
>> I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
IT'S DONE.
>> WHEN DID WE BECOME SO BROKEN?
>> WHEN YOU STOPPED TAKING CARE
OF AYDENN.
>> 'CAUSE OF THAT?
>> YEAH.
>> [crying]
>> WELL, ALLIE, YOU SPECIFICALLY
STAYED IN TEXAS SO YOU AND JOEY
COULD PARENT TOGETHER, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> HOW'D THAT WORK OUT?
>> WE WERE BOTH NEW PARENTS,
SO IT WAS JUST ASSUMING, LIKE,
HE WASN'T READY OR WHATEVER,
SO I GAVE IT A COUPLE MONTHS--
WELL, LIKE, TWO--THEN HE STILL
WASN'T HELPING, AND I WAS
GETTING, LIKE, MAD.
LIKE, "WHY AREN'T YOU HELPING?"
>> A LOT OF THE DRAMA WE SAW ON
YOUR EPISODE INVOLVED RELATION
BETWEEN YOU AND JOEY'S MOM.
>> MM-HMM.
>> FIRST OF ALL, WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO TELL US ABOUT THAT
RELATIONSHIP?
>> WELL, I KNEW FROM THE START,
WHEN I MET HER, I COULD TELL SHE
WAS A LITTLE UNEASY ABOUT ME
BECAUSE I WAS THE FIRST GIRL
HE BROUGHT AROUND.
>> "UNEASY" IS AN
UNDERSTATEMENT.
IT GOT BAD.
>> YEAH.
>> SHE WAS ABUSIVE TOWARDS YOU.
>> HOW DID THAT AFFECT YOU?
>> THAT MADE ME WANT TO LEAVE.
THERE WAS SO MANY TIMES I WANTED
TO LEAVE.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU?
>> FOR JOEY.
I STAYED FOR HIM.
>> YOU SAID THAT JOEY WASN'T
READY TO BE A DAD.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
WERE YOU READY?
>> I WASN'T READY.
WE WERE BOTH NOT READY FOR THIS.
BUT I THINK THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
IS, I MEAN, I'M NOT SUPER
MATURE, BUT, I MEAN, LIKE, I
MATURED UP FOR AYDENN AND HE
DIDN'T.
THAT'S WHAT MADE ME MAD, AND
THAT'S WHY I BROKE UP WITH HIM.
>> YOU'RE STILL IN SCHOOL.
>> YES.
I HAVE ALL "A"s.
>> GOOD. CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANK YOU.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO GRADUATE?
>> YES, I AM. IN TWO MONTHS.
>> TWO MONTHS.
AND THEN WHAT?
>> AND THEN I'M GOING TO
A FOUR-YEAR UNIVERSITY, EITHER
IN TEXAS OR NEW JERSEY,
AND I WANT TO MAJOR IN
MATHEMATICS.
>> OH, NICE.
ISN'T THAT GOING TO BE TOUGH
WITH A BABY?
>> I THINK I CAN DO IT.
>> BUT YOU'RE ALONE.
DOES THAT MAKE YOU SAD?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> YEAH, THAT'S THE PART THAT
GETS ME.
YOU'RE NOT KIND OF ALONE;
YOU ARE VERY ALONE.
>> I DON'T CARE, THOUGH.
I JUST WANT AYDENN TO BE HAPPY.
>> I KNOW. I KNOW.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
FINANCIALLY, HOW DO YOU SUPPORT
THE BABY.
>> WELL, MY MOM SENDS MY MONEY
FROM NEW JERSEY BECAUSE I DON'T
HAVE A JOB.
THAT'S HOW I DO THAT.
>> WELL, TELL ME MORE NOW ABOUT
GRANDMA BELEN, BECAUSE IT SEEMED
LIKE SHE REALLY WAS BEING
HELPFUL AND TOOK YOU IN.
>> SHE REALLY WAS.
>> WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
>> I'M--SHE'S A VERY A GOOD
PERSON AND I'M VERY GRATEFUL
FOR HER TAKING ME IN,
BUT SHE'S GOING TO STICK UP FOR
HER OWN.
>> IS THAT WHAT HAPPENED?
>> YES.
SO IF ME AND JOEY GOT INTO A
FIGHT, EVEN IF JOEY'S WRONG--
REGARDLESS WHO WAS WRONG--
JOEY WAS ALWAYS RIGHT TO HER,
'CAUSE IT'S HER GRANDSON,
AND I UNDERSTAND THAT.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M SURE SHE
HATES ME NOW.
THE DAY WE BROKE UP, SHE WENT
OFF ON ME.
IT WAS A MESS.
>> WELL, JOEY AND HIS
GRANDMOTHER BELEN ARE GOING TO
JOIN US RIGHT HERE AFTER THIS
BREAK, AND PERHAPS JOEY WILL GET
TO SEE THE BABY FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN MONTHS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THAT,
AND, OF COURSE, THERE'S MUCH
MORE COMING UP NEXT.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO THE 16 AND
PREGNANT FINALE SPECIAL.
I'M DR. DREW, STILL HERE WITH
ALLIE, AND WE ARE JOINED NOW
BY HER BABY'S FATHER, JOEY,
AND HIS GRANDMOTHER, BELEN.
SO, JOEY, I'M GOING TO ASK YOU,
WE'VE BEEN TALKING TO ALLIE A
BIT, WHAT IS THE STATUS OF YOUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH ALLIE?
>> WE DON'T TALK.
>> THIS IS ALL VERY PAINFUL,
HUH?
>> YEAH, IT'S PAINFUL.
IT HAPPENED, LIKE, SO QUICK
AND...
>> THE DEPARTURE HAPPENED SO
QUICK?
>> YEAH, LIKE, JUST BEING THERE
AND GETTING UP AND LEAVING AND
TAKING YOUR KID, AND THEN YOU
CAN'T SEE HIM?
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM SINCE THE DAY
BEFORE SHE LEFT.
AND, LIKE, I TRY TO SEE HIM.
I DON'T WANT HER TO BE THERE
WHEN I SEE HIM.
>> HOW COME?
>> 'CAUSE I FEEL LIKE I DON'T
WANT ANYTHING TO DO WITH HER.
>> WHY DO YOU THINK ALLIE DID
WHAT SHE DID?
>> WE'RE JUST PROBABLY FADING
APART.
>> AND THEN HOW ABOUT YOU
PULLING YOUR WEIGHT WITH THE
BABY?
>> I COULD PROBABLY TRY HARDER.
>> YEAH.
BELEN, I GET THE SENSE THAT YOU
GOT HURT BY HER DEPARTURE.
YOU REALLY WERE ATTACHED TO HER.
>> YEAH, I WAS ATTACHED TO HER.
I REALLY WAS ATTACHED TO HER
AND I WAS ATTACHED TO THE BABY.
IT'S JUST LIKE...
>> SO THIS WAS PAINFUL FOR YOUR
TOO.
>> YEAH, IT WAS PAINFUL FOR ME.
FIRST OF ALL, HATS OFF.
THANK YOU FOR SUPPORTING THESE
KIDS.
I MEAN, GOD KNOWS WHERE THEY
WOULD HAVE BEEN WITHOUT YOU.
THIS IS TEEN PREGNANCY.
YOU KNEW WHERE THIS WAS GOING.
YOU SAW IT.
ALLIE, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SAY
ABOUT HOW YOU'RE FEELING ABOUT
BELEN?
>> I AM VERY THANKFUL FOR WHAT
YOU DID FOR ME.
I KNOW YOU--I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU
DIDN'T LIKE ME 'CAUSE YOU'RE
GOING TO TAKE YOUR OWN SIDE,
SO I'M NOT MAD, BUT IF YOU
WEREN'T HERE, ME AND JOEY
WOULDN'T EVEN HAD A CHANCE
TO TRY.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING ME IN.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT THAT I
DON'T LIKE YOU, ALLISON.
IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST THAT IT HURT ME TOO
BECAUSE I TURNED MY BACK ON MY
DAUGHTER BECAUSE I DEFENDED YOU,
BECAUSE I KNEW WHERE YOU WERE
COMING FROM.
I CAME FROM A BAD RELATIONSHIP.
>> JUST FOR PEOPLE AT HOME SO
THEY UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE SO
EMOTIONAL, I FEEL WHAT THIS IS.
DO YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN WHY
YOU'RE SO EMOTIONAL?
>> WELL, WHEN JOEY WAS YELLING
AT ME IN THE THING ABOUT HOW I'M
UNGRATEFUL, I DON'T FEEL BAD FOR
HIM, I'M NOT GOING TO LIE,
BUT I FEEL, LIKE, MORE HURT.
LIKE, I DIDN'T WANT TO HURT
BELEN AT ALL BECAUSE SHE'S THE
ONLY ADULT THAT TOOK ME IN.
>> YEAH. YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU'RE REALLY IMPORTANT TO HER,
AND I KNOW YOU'RE HOLDING BACK
TOO.
I CAN SEE IT.
>> WELL, I MEAN, I'M NOT GOING,
LIKE I SAID, I'M NOT GOING TO
LIE.
SHE WAS IMPORTANT IN MY LIFE.
>> I SEE IT.
>> WE WERE CLOSE.
>> BUT ON THE OTHER HAND, I DID
NOT LIKE THE TURNAROUND THAT SHE
MADE WHEN SHE STARTED TREATING
HIM REALLY MEAN.
THAT HURT ME.
>> IT'S VERY CONFLICTED.
I GET IT.
ALLIE, DO YOU EVER LEAVE THE
CHILD ALONE WITH ANYBODY?
>> NO.
>> NOBODY EVER GETS TO BE ALONE
WITH THE CHILD WITHOUT YOU
PRESENT?
>> WELL, MY FRIEND HAS BEEN
ALONE WITH HIM, BUT MY FRIEND'S
NOT GOING TO STEAL AYDENN FROM
ME.
AND, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
I KNOW HIS WHOLE FAMILY HATES
ME, SO THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO
DO SOMETHING.
>> I DID NOT HEAR BELEN SAY SHE
HATES YOU.
>> WELL, OKAY, NOT BELEN.
I DON'T KNOW IF JOEY DOES.
>> WHAT ABOUT BELEN BEING THE
MEDIATOR?
>> WELL, IF SHE WANTS TO BE
THERE, THAT'S FINE, BUT HE
NEVER--
>> INSTEAD OF YOU.
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
WHAT IF YOLANDA COMES OVER?
>> WHAT IF YOLANDA COMES OVER?
WELL, YOU'LL HAVE TO TRUST BELEN
TO TAKE CARE OF THAT.
>> WELL, IT'S HER DAUGHTER.
SHE'S GOING TO PICK HER DAUGHTER
OVER ME.
>> IN BELEN'S EYE, I DON'T KNOW
THAT.
I THINK THE BABY--SHE CAN PUT
THE BABY AHEAD OF MOST INTEREST,
I WOULD SAY.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T TRUST IT.
I DON'T TRUST AYDENN BEING
AROUND THEM WITHOUT ME,
AND I KNOW IT'S HIS DAD, HIS
FAMILY, BUT...
>> ALLIE, IT'S SCARY FOR YOU.
>> YEAH, I DON'T--
>> LET'S NOT TALK ABOUT TRUST.
LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU'RE SCARED.
>> YEAH.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT SHE THINKS
THAT, YOU KNOW, YOLANDA OR JOE
WILL TRY TO TAKE THE BABY.
BUT IF I'M IN THERE, THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO TAKE THE BABY.
FIRST OF ALL, ALLISON, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME TRYING TO
STEAL THE BABY.
YOU KNOW ME--I DON'T BABYSIT.
SO YOU KNOW ME.
IF YOU'RE FIVE MINUTES LATE,
I'LL BE ON THAT PHONE.
"YOU BETTER COME PICK UP THIS
BABY, 'CAUSE I'M GOING OUT
TONIGHT."
>> NOW, THE BABY IS HERE.
DO YOU WANT TO TAKE A RISK AND
BRING THE BABY OUT AND SEE HOW
THAT FEELS AND...
'CAUSE, I MEAN, YOU DO WANT THE
BABY TO HAVE A DADDY.
>> I'D LIKE TO SEE HIM.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM IN TWO
MONTHS.
>> I'D BE NICE FOR BELEN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> JOEY, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
US BRINGING THE BABY OUT?
IS THAT EXCITING FOR YOU?
>> HAVE A FEELING I'M GONNA CRY.
>> ALL RIGHT, WELL, JOEY HASN'T
SEEN AYDENN FOR MANY MONTHS.
ARE YOU READY?
OKAY, LAUREN, COME ON OUT.
THERE HE IS.
>> YAY.
>> COME ON, LAUREN.
HAVE A SEAT.
HAVE A SEAT, LAUREN.
>> HI, SWEETIE.
>> IT'S GOOD FOR AYDENN, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> IT IS GOOD FOR AYDENN.
>> I DON'T THINK HE LIKES ME.
[laughter]
>> HE'S JUST LIKE THAT.
>> HE'S JUST WAKING UP.
HE DOESN'T LIKE WAKING UP,
THAT'S WHAT HE DOESN'T LIKE.
>> THAT'S WHAT IT IS.
>> ACTUALLY HE'S JUST FALLING
ASLEEP.
>> JOEY, JUST TELL US WHAT
YOU'RE FEELING.
>> GOOD.
>> JOY?
>> HAPPINESS.
>> IF YOU GET THIS AS THE
BENEFIT, ISN'T IT VERY LITTLE TO
ASK THAT YOU LET ALLIE COME
ALONG WITH THE BABY,
EVEN IF SHE WAITS OUTSIDE AND
JUST--AS THE MOM, SHE JUST NEEDS
TO BE AROUND THE BABY.
>> YEAH.
>> MIGHT BE A COMPROMISE, RIGHT?
NOW, LAUREN, YOU'RE NEW TO US
OUT HERE.
YOU ARE ALLIE'S MOM.
>> YES.
>> AND YOU LIVE IN NEW JERSEY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> HOW DID YOU LOSE CONTROL OF
YOUR DAUGHTER LIKE THIS?
SHE MOVED TO TEXAS.
>> WELL, SHE MOVED TO TEXAS WITH
HER FATHER.
>> DID THAT SEEM LIKE A GOOD
DECISION IN RETROSPECT?
>> I BLAME MYSELF FOR THE FACT
THAT BECAUSE I LEFT HER WITH
HER DAD, DID SHE PERHAPS FEEL
ABANDONED OR THAT I DIDN'T LOVE
HER OR...
I JUST--I JUST WANTED TO DO THE
RIGHT THING.
>> WELL, LET'S ASK THIS, LAUREN,
'CAUSE WE SEE THIS IN THE
EPISODE THAT SHE TELLS YOU SHE'S
PREGNANT.
HOW COME YOU DIDN'T COME GET HER
RIGHT THEN?
>> SHE DIDN'T WANT TO GO.
>> YOU TRIED?
>> YES.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU WANT TO GO?
>> I WANTED TO STAY FOR JOEY.
>> STAY FOR JOEY.
SO, ALLIE, WHAT ROLE DOES LAUREN
PLAY IN YOUR LIFE NOW?
DO YOU FEEL LIKE SHE'S GOT YOUR
BACK?
>> YEAH.
>> IS SHE AROUND ENOUGH FOR YOU?
>> ALWAYS.
>> YET YOU STILL LIVE APART.
>> WE LIVE APART, BUT I'M ON THE
PHONE WITH HER ALL THE TIME.
I'M ALWAYS SENDING HER
WHATEVER--LIKE, WHAT I TOLD HER,
AS FAR AS THE BABY GOES,
WHATEVER YOU DON'T GET,
I GOT IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S TALK ABOUT
NEXT STEPS.
HERE YOU GUYS ARE, WE'VE HAD A
NICE CONVERSATION, WHEN YOU
LEAVE HERE, HOW IS THIS GOING
TO WORK GOING FORWARD?
JOEY?
>> MAYBE WE CAN TRY TO WORK
SOMETHING OUT.
>> YOU'RE OPEN TO TRY ANYTHING,
INCLUDING ALLIE BEING AROUND
WHEN THE BABY'S AROUND?
>> WELL, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
DEAL WITH IT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO DEAL WITH
IT.
>> BUT YOU'RE WILLING TO ALLOW
HIM TIME WITH THE BABY IF YOU
CAN BE AROUND?
>> YEAH.
>> BELEN AND LAUREN CAN BE
STABILIZING AND SUPPORTIVE
FEATURES IN THIS.
ARE YOU GUYS SOUNDING OFF ON
THIS?
OKAY.
THAT IT'S SOMETHING THAT
PROBABLY NEEDS TO BE A REAL
STRUCTURE TO IT AND TIMING AND
EVERYTHING, AND YOU GOTTA BE
KIND OF FLEXIBLE.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
>> NO.
>> NONE OF THIS IS EASY.
OKAY, I WANT TO REMIND ALL THE
VIEWERS THAT WE CAN ANSWER YOUR
QUESTIONS ABOUT SEX, AS WELL AS
IMPORTANT TIPS ABOUT TAKING
CONTROL OF YOUR SEX LIFE.
IT'S ALL THERE ON:
THANKS TO ALL OF YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
VERY COURAGEOUS.
A VERY COURAGEOUS EFFORT ON YOUR
PART.
WHEN WE COME BACK, ALLIE'S GOING
TO BE JOINED BY OUR NINE OTHER
TEEN MOMS, AND THEY WILL ASK
EACH OTHER QUESTIONS FOR THE
VERY FIRST TIME, SO DON'T
GO AWAY.
[applause]
>> WELCOME BACK TO LIFE AFTER
LABOR.
I'M DR. DREW.
NOW, WE SPENT A LOT OF TIME
DISCUSSING PREVENTION TODAY,
BUT THERE'S MUCH MORE
INFORMATION ONLINE.
SO HEAD ON OVER TO
16ANDPREGNANT.MTV.COM
AND GET YOURSELF EDUCATED.
I'M JOINED NOW BY ALL TEN OF OUR
TEEN MOMS, AND NOW IT'S TIME TO
LET YOU ASK EACH OTHER
QUESTIONS.
WHO HAS THE FIRST QUESTION?
>> YEAH, FOR ALLIE.
UM, HOW DID YOU DEAL WITH, LIKE,
YOUR BOYFRIEND'S MOM,
LIKE, KIND OF, LIKE, BASHING YOU
LIKE THAT?
>> WELL, I JUST KEPT SAYING TO
MYSELF, "THAT'S HIS MOM, AND
HE'S MY BOYFRIEND, SO I'M GOING
TO DEAL WITH IT FOR HIM,
REALLY."
>> STILL PRETTY ROUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> JENNIFER.
>> I HAVE A QUESTION FOR ALL THE
GIRLS.
DO YOU GUYS WORRY THAT YOUR KIDS
WILL GROW UP AND BE OUR AGE
AND MAKE THE SAME MISTAKES?
>> I HOPE HE WOULD WATCH MY
EPISODE AND...
>> YOU'RE GOING TO SHOW HIM THE
SERIES?
>> WATCH THIS.
>> WELL, IT'S KIND OF--
IT SHOULD BE A LITTLE HARDER
FOR THE GIRLS WHO HAVE GIRLS,
'CAUSE MOST OF US HAVE BOYS,
SO ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS MAKE
SURE THEY'RE PROTECTED.
>> STILL GOT TO WORRY ABOUT BOYS
THOUGH.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WORRIES ME JUST BECAUSE I
THINK I WOULD BE LIKE THE "YEAH,
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR BOYFRIEND
OVER" PARENT LIKE MY MOM WAS.
I THINK THAT'S WHERE ME AND
NATHAN WENT WRONG.
>> DO YOU THINK YOUR PARENTS
WERE NAIVE?
>> NO, I JUST ME AND NATHAN
JUST MANIPULATED THE SITUATION
TO WHERE WE WANTED IT.
>> YOU HAD A QUESTION, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, IT'S KIND OF JUST FOR
EVERYBODY.
DO YOU GUYS THINK, LIKE, YOUR
BOYFRIENDS, LIKE, SHOWED THEIR
TRUE COLORS AFTER THE BABY?
>> WHO HAS A RESPONSE TO THAT?
>> I DEFINITELY NOTICED THAT
RYAN CHANGED AFTER MIAH CAME.
I CHANGED MY NUMBER AND STUFF,
BUT HE COULD HAVE COME UP TO ME
AT SCHOOL AND BEEN LIKE, "HOW IS
MIAH? IS SHE OKAY?"
BUT FOR FOUR MONTHS, HE DID NOT
EVEN BOTHER TO TALK TO ME,
DIDN'T SAY, "DOES SHE NEED
ANYTHING?"
HE JUST COMPLETELY WAS LIVING
WITH HIS GIRLFRIEND, WORRIED
ABOUT HIM AND HER.
>> SO IS IT SAFE TO SAY HOW
THESE YOUNG BOYS, YOUNG MEN,
RELATE TO THE BABY TELLS YOU
EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW
ABOUT THEM?
>> all: YEAH.
>> DOES ANYBODY FEEL THAT
THEIR BABY DADDY IS NOT DOING AS
MUCH AS THEY ARE, AS THE MOM?
SO A FEW BABY DADDIES ARE
PULLING THEIR WEIGHT.
>> MM-HMM.
>> WHICH IS NICE, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> ANY COMMENTS?
ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE TO TELL
VIEWERS OUT THERE ABOUT YOUR
EXPERIENCE AS A TEEN MOM?
>> BIRTH CONTROL.
>> GET THE BIRTH CONTROL RIGHT.
>> TAKE IT CORRECTLY.
>> COULD USE IT CORRECTLY,
JORDAN?
>> YEAH, AND LONG ENOUGH
FOR IT TO WORK.
>> WELL, THANK YOU TO ALL OF YOU
FOR SHARING YOUR STORIES, AND
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING THIS
SEASON, AND NOW IT IS TIME TO
SEE THE BABIES.
BRING 'EM OUT.
[cheers and applause]
GO GET 'EM.
AND TO ALL OUR VIEWERS, PLEASE
REMEMBER THAT TEEN PREGNANCY IS
100% PREVENTABLE.
GO ONLINE AND LEARN ALL YOU CAN
ABOUT PREVENTION.
ALL THE FACTS ARE RIGHT THERE
AT 16ANDPREGNANT.MTV.COM.
I'M DR. DREW.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
[cheers and applause]
Captioning byCaptionMax
www.captionmax.com