>> [laughs]
HI, I'M ALEX, AND I'M GONNA BE
A SENIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL.
I LIVE IN NEFFS, PENNSYLVANIA,
WITH MY MOM, MY LITTLE BROTHER
AND SISTER, OUR THREE DOGS,
AND OUR RABBIT.
MY PARENTS GOT DIVORCED
WHEN I WAS YOUNG,
AND MY DAD MOVED AWAY,
SO MY MOM PRETTY MUCH RAISED US
ON HER OWN.
SHE ALWAYS TOLD ME THAT I NEED
TO BE RESPONSIBLE
AND INDEPENDENT.
>> I'VE TOLD YOU THAT FOR MANY,
MANY, MANY YEARS.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S WHY I HAVE TWO JOBS:
ONE AT A FAST-FOOD RESTAURANT
AND ANOTHER TEACHING KIDS DANCE.
ALL RIGHT, THOSE SHOULDERS NEED
TO BE HUGE.
I LOVE DANCE, AND I HOPE TO OPEN
MY OWN STUDIO SOMEDAY.
>> WHAT?
>> WHEN I'M NOT WORKING,
I'M HANGING OUT WITH MY
BOYFRIEND, MATT.
I FELL IN LOVE WITH HIM
TWO YEARS AGO, WHEN WE WERE
BOTH SOPHOMORES,
BECAUSE HE WAS SO SMART, SWEET,
FUNNY, AND DIFFERENT FROM
OTHER GUYS, IN A GOOD WAY.
BUT HE'S NEVER BEEN SUPER
RESPONSIBLE.
AND WHILE I'M FOCUSED ON GETTING
THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL,
MATT HAS ALWAYS BEEN IN AND OUT
OF TROUBLE.
MY FRIENDS DON'T GET WHY I'M
WITH HIM.
HE'S SMART, BUT--
>> HE'S AN IDIOT.
>> BUT MATT'S MY FIRST LOVE,
AND I'M HOPING HE'LL CLEAN UP
HIS ACT FOR GOOD,
BECAUSE I'M PREGNANT.
SO FAR, NOTHING HAS BEEN EASY
ABOUT MY PREGNANCY.
THERE'S A LOT TO PLAN FOR,
BUT ALL I WANT TO DO IS PUT
THINGS OFF.
>> WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO SIT DOWN
AND TALK ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW THAT.
I MEAN, I DID EVERYTHING THAT
I POSSIBLY COULD TO PREVENT
THIS SITUATION.
NOW HERE WE ARE.
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN OF ACTION?
JUST AS FAR AS HAVING A CHILD?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT ANYTHING?
>> I'M STILL FIGURING IT OUT.
>> WELL, YOU NEED TO MAKE
SOME DECISIONS.
>> I KNOW.
>> AND WHATEVER DECISIONS YOU
MAKE, YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH
THE CONSEQUENCES.
EVERYTHING HAS CONSEQUENCES.
>> THIS SITUATION IS MY MOM'S
WORST NIGHTMARE.
WHEN I STARTED HAVING SEX,
SHE TOOK ME TO THE DOCTOR
TO GET BIRTH CONTROL.
SO WHEN SHE FOUND OUT
THAT I WAS PREGNANT,
SHE WAS FURIOUS.
SHE SAID THAT I COULD EITHER PUT
THE BABY UP FOR ADOPTION,
OR I COULD KEEP THE BABY
AND FIND ANOTHER PLACE TO LIVE.
SINCE I FOUND OUT I'M HAVING
A GIRL, AND SHE'S DUE IN LESS
THAN A MONTH, IT'S BEEN REALLY
HARD TO MAKE A DECISION.
AND I KNOW MATT'S BEEN
STRUGGLING WITH IT AS WELL.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN A RELATIONSHIP THIS LONG.
>> IT'S LIKE, IT FEELS LIKE
TWO YEARS KIND OF FLEW BY
PRETTY FAST, LIKE, EVEN THIS
WHOLE NINE MONTHS KIND OF WENT
BY PRETTY FAST.
LIKE, I THINK ABOUT IT, LIKE,
BACK IN NINTH GRADE WHEN WE
FIRST MET AND STUFF, LIKE,
IN SCHOOL AND EVERYTHING, LIKE,
YOU NEVER REALLY WOULD ENVISION
THIS KIND OF THING.
>> BEFORE IT WAS MATH CLASS,
AND THEN IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE,
NOW IT'S, LIKE, THERE'S A BABY.
>> WELL, WE DID MOVE
PRETTY FAST.
YOU WERE PRETTY MUCH AT MY
HOUSE, LIKE, EVERY WEEKEND,
AND THEN WE'RE HERE.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> YOU JUST WANT TO STOP HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> IT'S HOT.
>> I GOT TO SIT.
I LOVE YOU MORE THAN ANYTHING.
YOU'VE BECOME, LIKE,
MY BEST FRIEND.
>> I LOVE YOU, AND I CARE
ABOUT YOU; IT'S JUST, AT THIS
POINT IN TIME, LIKE, WE HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT OTHER THINGS.
LIKE, I WANT WHAT'S BEST
FOR HER, AND SOMETIMES I THINK,
LIKE, YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOUR MOM'S
RIGHT WITH ADOPTION,
BECAUSE IT'D PROVIDE HER WITH
EVERYTHING SHE REALLY DOES NEED,
YOU KNOW.
ON THE SAME TOKEN, I HONESTLY
DON'T WANT TO MISS ANYTHING,
IN, LIKE, A SELFISH KIND OF WAY,
LIKE, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HOW DO YOU FEEL LIKE?
>> I DON'T THINK THAT I CAN GIVE
HER UP, BUT THE THING THAT I'M
WORRIED AND SCARED OF THE MOST
IS DOING IT ON MY OWN.
>> I'M REALLY GONNA TRY MY BEST
TO BE THERE AS MUCH AS I CAN
POSSIBLY, LIKE, HELP.
>> YEAH.
IT'S JUST TOUGH, BECAUSE I'M SO
SCARED ABOUT EVERYTHING.
>> WE'LL SEE,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, WITH TIME, IT'LL--
WE'LL SEE HOW IT GOES, YOU KNOW?
>> I WISH MATT SOUNDED MORE
CONFIDENT ABOUT BEING A DAD.
HE HASN'T BEEN VERY RELIABLE
IN THE PAST.
HE DISAPPEARS A LOT,
HE PARTIES WAY TOO MUCH,
AND HE'S BEEN ON PROBATION.
BUT HE NEEDS TO PULL IT
TOGETHER, 'CAUSE IF I KEEP
THE BABY, I'M GOING TO NEED
HIM THERE.
IT'S THE SUMMER BEFORE
SENIOR YEAR, AND I THOUGHT
I'D BE SPENDING ALL MY TIME
AT THE STUDIO.
BUT AT 8 1/2 MONTHS PREGNANT,
IT'S BECOME A LOT HARDER
TO DANCE.
>> READY?
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, AND--
ONE AND A TWO AND AN UP, BACK.
AND ONE AND TWO AND THREE, FOUR,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, AND EIGHT.
OKAY.
>> [grunts]
>> YOU LOOK TIRED.
>> I'M SO OUT OF IT.
>> OH, MY GOD, SHE'S RIDICULOUS.
I HAVEN'T BEEN SLEEPING AT ALL.
I ROLL CONSTANTLY
BACK AND FORTH.
>> HOW DID YOU FEEL WHEN YOU
FIRST FOUND OUT?
>> I WAS SCARED OUT OF MY
FREAKING MIND.
I CRIED ALL THE WAY
TO THE BUS STOP.
I CRIED ALL THE WAY TO SCHOOL.
AND THEN I DID HAVE A LOT OF,
LIKE, REGRET WHEN I FOUND OUT.
>> DO PEOPLE, LIKE, STARE AT YOU
IN SCHOOL?
>> OH, MY GOSH, YEAH.
>> I CAN IMAGINE, LIKE--
>> YEAH.
>> DO PEOPLE, LIKE, CALL YOU
NAMES AND STUFF, NOW THAT YOU
GOT PREGNANT?
>> YEAH, I'VE GOTTEN SLUT,
WHORE.
>> THAT'S A SHAME.
>> THAT'S HORRIBLE.
>> I MEAN, MATT AND I WERE USING
PROTECTION, AND I WAS ON
BIRTH CONTROL, AND IT JUST KIND
OF WAS LIKE AN "OOPSIE"
KIND OF THING.
HIM AND I WERE LIKE, "OH, SHOULD
WE GO GET PLAN "B"?
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?"
AND THEN I WENT THERE.
IT'S FREAKING $50.
>> all: YEAH.
>> I'M LIKE, OKAY.
>> WOULD YOU GIVE THE BABY UP
FOR ADOPTION?
WOULD YOU WANT--WOULD YOU FEEL
LIKE YOU COULD BE MORE
OF A TEENAGER?
>> I'M STILL IN BETWEEN.
IT IS REALLY HARD, YOU KNOW?
I'M MORE TOWARDS KEEPING THE
BABY, BUT IT'S LIKE I'M STARTING
TO LOOK AT IT AS, "WHAT'S GOING
TO BE BETTER FOR HER,
SOMEONE WHO CAN GIVE HER
EVERYTHING PLUS THAT, OR SOMEONE
WHO'S GOING TO STRUGGLE
TO GIVE HER EVERYTHING?"
I'M IN A REALLY TRICKY
SITUATION, AND IT ISN'T GETTING
ANY EASIER, SINCE EVERYONE IN MY
FAMILY IS WONDERING WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO.
>> SO WHAT REALLY DOES IT FEEL
LIKE, THOUGH?
>> LIKE BEING PUNCHED ON THE
INSIDE OF YOUR STOMACH.
>> ARE YOU READY?
>> NO.
>> ARE YOU ALLOWED TO KEEP IT?
IS IT, LIKE, AGAINST THE LAW FOR
YOU TO KEEP IT?
>> NO, IT'S NOT AGAINST THE LAW
FOR ME TO KEEP IT.
>> DO YOU WANT TO KEEP IT?
>> I WANT TO KEEP IT.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
BUT DO YOU THINK THAT IT'S THE
BEST THING FOR ME TO?
>> YOU CAN BE HONEST, HONEY.
>> YOU'RE STILL IN SCHOOL.
>> YEAH.
>> PEOPLE ARE GONNA PICK ON YOU
AND WHATEVER.
>> WELL, EVEN WITHOUT A BABY,
PEOPLE PICK ON YOU.
>> YEAH, BUT NOT AS MUCH WHEN
YOU'RE WITH A BABY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD ADOPT IT,
'CAUSE YOU'RE A LITTLE
TOO YOUNG.
>> IT'S HARD TO KEEP A BABY.
>> IT'S JUST NOT THE RIGHT TIME.
>> WITH MY BABY DUE IN JUST TWO
WEEKS, I REALLY NEED TO COME
TO A DECISION, AND MY MOM IS
LOSING PATIENCE.
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO WITH
YOUR LIFE?
>> OWN THE DANCE STUDIO.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN DO THIS
WITHOUT FINISHING SCHOOL?
>> NO.
>> NOW, DO YOU THINK THAT YOU
CAN FINISH SCHOOL AND GO TO
COLLEGE WITH AN INFANT?
AND HOW DOES THAT MAKE YOU FEEL?
>> LIKE COMPLETE [bleep].
>> THERE WILL BE NO BABIES IN
THIS HOUSE, AND I TOLD YOU THAT.
THAT WAS ACTUALLY ONE FORM
OF BIRTH CONTROL.
>> I KNOW.
>> I'M NOT GONNA RAISE A CHILD,
SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> IF I KEPT HER, I'D HAVE TO GO
LOOK FOR SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> DO YOU THINK MATT WOULD GIVE
YOU ANY MONEY TO HELP RAISE
THIS CHILD?
>> HIS MIND IS SOMEWHERE ELSE,
AND IT ALWAYS IS.
>> HONEY, HE'S A KID.
THAT'S WHY KIDS SHOULDN'T TRY
TO BE PARENTS.
>> I KNOW WHAT'S BEST.
>> AND WHAT IS THAT?
>> ADOPTION.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
ADOPTION?
>> I THINK IT'S A GOOD OPTION.
I REALLY DO.
IT JUST--
MY HEART JUST SAYS NO.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF FAMILIES
OUT THERE THAT WOULD HAVE
UNLIMITED VISITATION.
>> THAT'S THE THING, THOUGH,
LIKE, IT'S NOT AS MUCH
AS I WANT.
[crying]
>> YOU'RE 17.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU NEED TO BE A KID.
>> I KNOW WHAT I WANT,
AND I KNOW WHAT'S BEST.
AND I WISH I COULD HAVE WHAT I
WANT, BUT I KNOW THAT I CAN'T.
>> SO WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
>> I REALLY JUST--I DON'T HAVE
AN ANSWER.
>> TALKING TO MY MOM ABOUT THE
BABY WAS REALLY PAINFUL.
I KNOW ADOPTION IS THE LOGICAL
CHOICE FOR ME, BUT RIGHT NOW,
ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS BEING A MOM.
>> both: OHH!
>> OH, HERE'S NEWBORN.
>> [gasps]
PULL THAT DOWN.
[gasps]
OH, MY GOD.
HOW MUCH IS IT?
>> $27.
>> OH.
>> HOW MUCH PER HOUR DO YOU GET?
>> I GET 7 BUCKS AN HOUR.
>> THAT'D BE FOUR HOURS
FOR THAT.
>> JUST TO GET--
>> AN OUTFIT.
AND THAT'S BEFORE TAXES.
GIRAFFE.
>> $29.
>> DID YOUR MOM
GET YOU ANYTHING?
>> NO.
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO BE
FINANCIALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR HER,
SO HOPEFULLY MATT WILL BE
HELPING OUT AND STUFF.
KEEPING THE BABY WILL BE REALLY
EXPENSIVE, ESPECIALLY IF MY MOM
KICKS ME OUT OF THE HOUSE.
SO EVEN THOUGH I'M ALMOST
NINE MONTHS PREGNANT, I WALK
A MILE TO MY JOB, JUST TO EARN
A MINIMUM-WAGE PAYCHECK.
BUT I'M NOT SURE IF THAT WILL BE
ENOUGH TO SUPPORT A BABY,
SO I NEED TO TALK TO MATT
ABOUT ALL THIS.
BUT HE'S BEEN REALLY FLAKY
LATELY.
>> WAS THERE FOUR OF US?
OH, YEAH, THERE IS.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE MATT'S NOT HERE,
LIKE USUAL.
>> DID YOU CALL HIM AGAIN?
>> WELL, HE WAS LIKE,
"OKAY, I'M GOING TO BE HERE IN
TEN MINUTES."
BUT IT'S BEEN, LIKE--
>> 45.
>> YEAH.
>> HE PROBABLY DOESN'T EVEN
KNOW WHERE IT IS.
>> NO, HE KNOWS WHERE IT IS.
HE'S BEEN, UH, KICKED OUT
OF HERE BEFORE.
>> OH.
>> CLASSY.
>> IT'S SO HARD TO SWING
OVER MY BELLY.
>> OHH!
>> all: OHH!
>> IS THAT YOUR PHONE GOING OFF?
>> MATT.
>> HELLO, YEAH?
>> WHERE ARE YOU?
>> WELL, CAN YOU PLEASE HURRY,
'CAUSE I WOULD LIKE TO SPEND
AT LEAST SOME TIME TOGETHER.
>> BYE.
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
HE TOLD ME HE'S ON HIS WAY.
>> YOU WANT TO SEE HIS DAUGHTER
BE BORN, BUT, LIKE, IS HE EVEN
GOING TO SHOW UP?
>> I HAVE A FUNNY FEELING HE'S
JUST GOING TO, LIKE, DISAPPEAR
RIGHT WHEN YOU NEED HIM.
>> MAYBE HE'LL GROW A PAIR
AND MAN UP FOR ME.
>> HE OBVIOUSLY HAS A PAIR.
LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
[laughter]
>> UGH.
MATT NEVER SHOWED UP.
NOW THAT MY DUE DATE
IS SO CLOSE, I REALLY NEED
HIS SUPPORT.
>> PLEASE LEAVE YOUR MESSAGE.
>> MATT, TOMORROW WE HAVE
AN ULTRASOUND AT 4:00.
LIKE, YOU REALLY
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WE NEED TO HAVE A SERIOUS
CONVERSATION.
OH, MY GOD.
MATT DID TURN UP
TO MY APPOINTMENT,
BUT IT LOOKED LIKE HE'D BEEN OUT
PARTYING ALL NIGHT.
>> THERE'S HER HEART.
>> I'M HAPPY YOU CAME.
>> MM-HMM.
>> ARE YOU GETTING EXCITED,
MATT?
>> SURE.
>> [sighs]
I REALLY LIKE ARABELLA.
>> MM-HMM.
>> OH, SHE IS TOTALLY FACING
YOUR SPINE, NOT SHOWING US
HER FACE.
>> SHE'S STUBBORN.
>> WHO'S THAT TAKE AFTER,
YOU OR DAD?
>> DEFINITELY HIM.
>> DEFINITELY DAD?
[laughs]
>> HOW SOON DO YOU THINK?
>> SHE IS DEFINITELY IN POSITION
AND READY TO GO.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IF WE DO PARENT, I'M LEANING
TOWARDS NAMING HER ARABELLA.
WITH MATT BEING SO OUT OF IT,
I CAN'T EVEN TALK TO HIM TO HELP
ME MAKE A DECISION.
>> HOW'S YOUR SUMMER BEEN
SO FAR?
>> IT'S BEEN PRETTY GOOD.
HOW'S YOURS?
>> UGH, LONG.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE READY
TO POP NOW.
COME OUT, BABY.
>> NO, WE DON'T WANT HER TO COME
OUT JUST YET.
WE WANT HER TO STAY IN HERE
FOREVER.
>> FOREVER?
>> FOREVER AND EVER AND EVER.
>> YOU WANT TO HAVE A BIG BUTT
FOREVER?
>> I COULD HAVE A BIG BUTT
FOREVER.
I'LL LIVE WITH THAT.
>> [laughs]
OKAY, BUT WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO
MAKE THE FINAL DECISION?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO.
>> WHAT DOES MATT THINK?
>> LIKE, I'VE BEEN TRYING TO
TALK TO MATT AND JUST FIGURE OUT
WHERE HIS HEAD IS.
IT JUST SEEMS A LOT LIKE HE'S
STILL OBSESSED WITH SPENDING
TIME WITH HIS FRIENDS.
AND HE GOES M.I.A. ALL THE TIME.
>> DO YOU REALLY FEEL YOU CAN
TRUST HIM WHEN THE BABY'S BORN?
>> WITH MATT BEING SO OUT OF IT,
I CAN'T EVEN TALK TO HIM TO HELP
ME MAKE A DECISION.
AND WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S
GOING TO BE OUR SENIOR YEAR.
>> OH, MY GOSH, I KNOW.
>> REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE BACK
IN, LIKE, ELEMENTARY SCHOOL,
WHEN I FIRST MET YOU.
>> OH, YES.
ARE YOU EXCITED TO DO, LIKE,
PROM AND SENIOR WEEK?
>> YEAH.
DO YOU THINK THAT YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE PROBLEMS NEXT YEAR WITH
THE BABY?
>> I'M REALLY SCARED OF THAT,
LIKE, TRYING TO DO THAT THE SAME
TIME I'M TRYING TO TAKE CARE OF
HER AND DO A JOB.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I'M GONNA
DO IT.
>> WHAT IF YOU DID GIVE HER UP?
LIKE, YOU'D BE ABLE TO, LIKE,
GO OUT WITH YOUR FRIENDS, JUST
LIVE YOUR HIGH SCHOOL YEARS.
>> YEAH.
>> LIKE, YOU'D BE ABLE TO DO THE
THINGS THAT, LIKE, I'M DOING.
>> YEAH.
I HAVE STARTED TO CONSIDER
ADOPTION A LITTLE BIT.
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, LIKE, MY
MOM'S THERE TO SUPPORT YOU.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND, UM, YOU KNOW, LIKE,
MY MOM CAN'T HAVE KIDS.
SO SHE ASKED ME IF, UM--
IF YOU WOULD CONSIDER HER, LIKE,
TAKING THE BABY
AND ADOPTING THE BABY.
>> REALLY?
UM--
>> AND I KNOW THAT'S A BIG
DECISION, BUT, LIKE, YOU'RE
CLOSE WITH US AND STUFF, SO,
YOU COULD, LIKE, COME SEE HER,
WHATEVER.
IT'S JUST SOMETHING, LIKE,
IF YOU WANT TO CONSIDER IT.
>> I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT
ABOUT BRIANNA'S OFFER.
I WANT TO TALK TO MATT
ABOUT IT, BUT I STILL CAN'T GET
AHOLD OF HIM.
SO I'M GOING TO MEET WITH
BRIANNA'S PARENTS ON MY OWN.
>> UM, I HAD TOLD ALEX WHEN WE
WERE OUT THAT YOU GUYS ARE
LOOKING TO ADOPT.
>> IT'S LIKE, I WANT TO LOOK AT
ALL THE OPTIONS THAT I
POSSIBLY HAVE.
>> SHE'S BEEN WANTING TO ADOPT.
PHYSICALLY, HER AND I CAN'T
HAVE ANOTHER CHILD TOGETHER.
>> I WANT ANOTHER BABY,
WHETHER THAT'S ADOPTING YOUR
BABY OR FOSTERING A BABY
TO ADOPT.
>> NOW, IF SHE DOESN'T WANT TO
GIVE IT UP RIGHT AWAY, WOULD YOU
GUYS, LIKE, DO IT LATER ON?
>> YEAH, THIS ISN'T WHERE AS
SOON AS THE BABY COMES OUT,
WE'RE GOING TO SAY, "OKAY, WE'RE
THE ADOPTIVE PARENTS NOW.
WE'RE MOM AND DAD, PERIOD,
END OF DISCUSSION."
NO.
IF YOU ARE TOTALLY AT WIT'S END
AND YOU HAVE TO GIVE THIS BABY
UP, THAT'S WHERE WE'D LIKE TO
STEP IN, BUT UP UNTIL THAT
POINT, SHE'S YOURS.
>> IF WE WOULD ADOPT THE BABY,
YOU WOULD STILL BE IN
THE BABY'S LIFE.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> IS MATT OKAY WITH THAT?
>> HE DOESN'T KNOW WHAT
HE WANTS.
I HOPE THAT HE'S GONNA GIVE SOME
TYPE OF SUPPORT.
I'M GOING TO TALK TO HIM, BUT IF
WE GO DOWN THAT ROAD, I REALLY
WOULD RATHER CHOOSE YOU TO BE
THE PARENTS THAN PICK SOMEONE
THAT I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
>> WHAT DO YOUR PARENTS FEEL
ABOUT THIS?
>> MY MOM IS JUST REALLY PUSHING
FOR THE ADOPTION AND FORCING
ONE OPINION AND ONE OPINION ONLY
DOWN MY THROAT.
>> AND YOU DON'T WANT THAT?
YOU WANT TO KEEP THE BABY?
>> WELL, I DO.
BUT SHE'S MAKING IT SO THAT IT
IS SO HARD FOR ME TO KEEP THE
BABY WITH, YOU KNOW, NOT
ALLOWING ME TO STAY IN THE
HOUSE, WITH--
>> IF YOU TAKE CARE OF THE BABY,
WHERE ARE YOU PLANNING ON GOING?
>> IT'S LIKE, I HAVE TO FIND
SOMEWHERE TO GO.
>> IT'S A BIG DECISION.
IT'S A BIG DECISION.
[sighs]
I WANT TO SEE WHAT'S BEST FOR
YOU AND THE BABY.
I DON'T WANT YOU BEING OUT
ON THE STREET.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW IT WOULD
WORK, BUT WE HAVE A NEXT-DOOR
NEIGHBOR THAT HAS A BEDROOM.
IT MIGHT BE ANOTHER OPTION.
>> SHE NEEDS SOMEBODY TO STAY
WITH HER, 'CAUSE SHE WANTS TO
STAY IN THE HOUSE, BUT SHE CAN'T
AFFORD IT.
YOU AND THE BABY WOULD HAVE
SOMEWHERE TO LIVE.
>> YOU'D BE RIGHT NEXT DOOR.
>> RIGHT NEXT DOOR TO US.
THE THING IS, WE NEED TO WAIT
TILL THE BABY'S BORN,
BECAUSE EVERY DAY THINGS ARE
GOING TO CHANGE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LIKE, YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW MUCH.
IF I MOVE NEXT DOOR, THEN I CAN
WAIT UNTIL AFTER THE BABY IS
BORN TO MAKE THE BIG DECISION.
>> HEY, BRENDA.
>> HI, BRENDA.
THIS IS ALEX, MY FRIEND.
>> HI, ALEX.
>> HEY.
>> BOY, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE--
SOON.
>> YEAH.
>> WELL, I'LL SHOW YOU THE ROOM,
SEE IF YOU'RE INTERESTED.
IT'S BIG ENOUGH FOR YOU
AND THE BABY.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY?
THIS IS THE ROOM THAT I HAVE,
AND IT DOES HAVE A BIG
WALK-IN CLOSET.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
THE ROOM?
>> IT'S REALLY ROOMY, AND I'M
REALLY HAPPY THAT YOU HAVE THIS
SPACE AVAILABLE.
LIKE, I LIKE IT.
I REALLY DO.
>> NOW, THE RENT IS $552
A MONTH, SO IT WOULD BE HALF.
>> OKAY.
THE FIRST OF EVERY MONTH.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO BE ABLE TO
AFFORD THAT WITH A NEWBORN?
>> I'VE GOT A JOB.
I ALSO HELP OUT
AT A DANCE STUDIO.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M TOTALLY OKAY WITH THAT.
I'M RELIEVED TO HAVE A PLACE
TO GO IF I TRY KEEPING THE BABY,
BUT I REALLY NEED TO KNOW WHAT
MATT THINKS.
>> OHH.
[mumbling]
>> SHE POOPED.
>> OHH!
SHE POOPED ON ME.
HANDS OFF.
>> [laughs]
LET ME GRAB A PAPER TOWEL.
>> GNARLY.
GO BACK IN YOUR CAGE.
TAKE IT. TAKE IT. TAKE IT.
>> OH, COME HERE, HONEY.
>> SHE JUST DROPPED A DEUCE
ON ME.
THAT'S DISRESPECTFUL.
>> OH, MY GOSH, YOU'RE
RIDICULOUS.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I DID MEET WITH
BRENDA, BRIANNA'S NEIGHBOR.
SHE HAD OFFERED ME SOMEWHERE
TO STAY.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED.
LIKE, IT'S A PLACE YOU
COULD STAY.
>> BUT, YOU KNOW, ARE YOU GONNA
HELP OUT?
I JUST--I WANT YOU TO BE
COMFORTABLE WITH WHATEVER
DECISION WE COME UP WITH.
LIKE, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
ADOPTION?
LIKE, I MEAN, WE HAVEN'T
REALLY--
>> I THINK THAT SOME PEOPLE,
IT'S REALLY THE BEST OPTION
FOR THEM.
>> UM, BRIANNA'S MOM AND DAD
OFFERED TO ADOPT THE BABY.
IT WOULD BE AN EXTREMELY OPEN
ADOPTION.
>> IF IT'S THAT OPEN, THAT'S--
THAT'S A GOOD THING.
LIKE, AT LEAST I'M THINKING
ABOUT THE IDEA, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, THIS SEEMS LIKE A PRETTY
GOOD IDEA.
WITH THIS, SHE'S RIGHT DOWN
THE STREET, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, THAT'S AN OFFER THAT YOU
MIGHT NOT FIND ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> BUT I WANT, LIKE--
I'M LIKING THE FEELING OF BEING
CALLED, "MOMMY."
>> YEAH, SEE YOU ARE.
YOU HAVE TO PUT HER BEFORE
YOURSELF AND SAY, "WHAT'S GOING
TO GIVE HER THE BEST
OPPORTUNITIES TO HAVE A
SUCCESSFUL LIFE?"
THAT REQUIRES UBER MATURITY,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE, THAT'S JUST IT.
>> I JUST DON'T WANT TO NOT TRY.
>> WITH YOUR JOB NOW, CAN YOU
PAY FOR RENT AND FOOD FOR
YOURSELF?
CAN YOU PAY FOR ALL THAT ON HOW
MUCH MONEY YOU'RE MAKING
RIGHT NOW?
I DON'T THINK SO.
>> I COULD TRY.
>> WOULD YOU BE ABLE TO?
IT'S NOT, "I CAN TRY."
YOU HAVE TO KNOW FOR A FACT YOU
CAN, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT
TO HAPPEN.
>> I CAN'T ON MY OWN.
>> YOU CAN'T WITH ME THERE
EITHER.
YOU CAN'T IF SOMEONE EVEN
HELPS US.
WE'RE WORKING PART-TIME,
MINIMUM-WAGE JOBS
IN HIGH SCHOOL, NOT EVEN
COLLEGE YET.
>> I THINK IF WE BOTH PUT IN
150% OF OUR EFFORT, IT COULD
BE POSSIBLE.
>> I DISAGREE.
>> IT SUCKS THAT MATT DOESN'T
THINK WE CAN HANDLE
BEING PARENTS.
I'M DUE THIS WEEK, AND I STILL
HAVEN'T MADE A DECISION.
BRIANNA'S PARENTS OFFERED
TO ADOPT THE BABY,
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, THEY'VE BEEN
WANTING TO ADOPT AND BECAUSE I
DO KNOW THEM SO WELL.
AND IT WOULD BE LIKE GIVING
THEM TO SOMEONE THAT ISN'T
A STRANGER TO ME.
>> THEY HAVE A STABLE HOME.
IT VERY WELL COULD BE A WIN-WIN.
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT IT?
>> IT SCARES ME, BECAUSE SHE IS
SO CLOSE, AND I WOULD GET AS
MUCH VISITATION AS I POSSIBLY
COULD EVER ASK FOR, BUT AM I
GOING TO BE OKAY WITH
WATCHING HER--
>> SOMEBODY ELSE RAISE HER,
AND HER CALLING SOMEBODY ELSE
"MOMMY" AND "DADDY."
>> EXACTLY.
WELL, WE ALSO TALKED ABOUT HOW
BRIANNA'S NEIGHBOR ALSO OFFERED
ME SOMEWHERE TO STAY.
SHE'S LOOKING FOR A ROOMMATE.
I WOULD BE PAYING BASICALLY
HALF THE RENT AND HALF
THE ELECTRICITY.
>> ARE YOU PREPARING TO TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE KEEPING THE BABY
AT BRENDA'S HOUSE?
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
>> HONEY, YOU KNOW WHAT DATE
IT IS?
>> I KNOW IT'S DAYS AWAY.
I KNOW THAT.
I--I'M SO SCARED OF WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN AT THE HOSPITAL,
BECAUSE I DON'T EVEN KNOW.
WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
WE'RE DOING, SO I TOOK MATT TO
TALK TO BRIANNA'S PARENTS.
>> SO WHAT DID ALEX SAY TO YOU
ABOUT THIS?
>> PRETTY MUCH THAT JUST YOU
GUYS ARE INTERESTED IN ADOPTION
AND VERY OPEN, I GUESS.
>> I WANT A BABY, BAD.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO DO THIS AND
THEN, IN A YEAR OR TWO, YOU GUYS
SAY, "OKAY, I WANT MY BABY."
>> YEAH.
YOU WOULD BE THE MOM.
YOU WOULD SAY WHEN AND WHERE I
WOULD BE ABLE TO VISIT, HOW MUCH
I WOULD BE ABLE TO VISIT.
>> WE'RE NOT PUSHING FOR,
YOU KNOW, TO PUSH YOU OUT OF
THE BABY'S LIFE.
WE'RE HERE TO HELP.
>> ALEX, WHERE--
HAVE YOU GUYS TALKED ABOUT THIS?
>> A COUPLE TIMES.
>> WHEN IT COMES DOWN TO IT,
I REALLY DON'T HAVE NEAR
AS MUCH SAY AS SHE DOES,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
>> YOU NEED TO PROVIDE FOR HER.
THAT'S WHAT A DAD DOES.
>> YEAH, BUT SHE'S A SENIOR.
I'M GONNA BE A JUNIOR.
I HAVE TWO MORE YEARS OF SCHOOL.
SHE HAS ONE.
PLUS, YOU'RE WORKING
A MINIMUM-WAGE JOB.
THAT BARELY WOULD MAKE ENDS MEET
FOR YOURSELF.
IT'S A DIFFICULT DECISION.
>> HE'S THINKING GOOD.
ARE YOU--DID YOU LISTEN TO HIM?
>> YEAH, I AM LISTENING.
>> I THINK THE MOST LOGICAL
THING TO DO, LIKE, I WOULD SAY,
WOULD BE ADOPTION.
BUT IT COMES DOWN TO HER.
I KNOW YOU FEEL HER AND STUFF
LIKE THAT, BUT IN THIS
SITUATION, EVERYBODY, NO MATTER
WHICH ROUTE YOU CHOOSE,
HAS TO MAKE SACRIFICES.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE
EVERYBODY HAPPY.
>> NO.
>> NO MATTER WHAT DECISION
YOU MAKE.
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS,
YOU HAVE TO MAKE SURE THAT
SHE HAS EVERYTHING THAT SHE
COULD HAVE.
>> IT'S A BIG DECISION, AND
THE BABY'S GOING TO BE HERE.
WITH HEARING HIM
AND ALL EVERYTHING ELSE,
WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
>> THAT ADOPTION IS PROBABLY
GOING TO BE THE BEST BET.
>> BELIEVE ME, I'M NOT TAKING
SIDES OR ANYTHING.
>> YEAH.
>> WE'RE NOT PUSHING YOU, LIKE,
"OH, WE WANT THE BABY.
WE WANT THE BABY."
>> OH, YEAH, I KNOW.
>> AND, YOU KNOW,
YOU JUST GO AWAY.
>> I DO WANT A BABY.
>> OH, I KNOW YOU DO, BUT WE GOT
TO GIVE THEM THE CHANCE.
WAIT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
THE BABY COMES, BECAUSE YOU
DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, YOU WOULD BE SURPRISED
OF WHAT A BABY WILL DO
TO EVERYBODY.
>> EVEN THOUGH I'M LEANING
TOWARDS LETTING BRIANNA'S FAMILY
ADOPT THE BABY, I UNDERSTAND
THAT THEY WANT ME TO BE SURE,
SO I DECIDED TO MOVE SOME OF MY
STUFF IN NEXT DOOR.
>> AND DROP IT.
>> READY, MOMMY?
>> YEP.
SINCE I DON'T HAVE EVERYTHING
SET UP YET, I'M SPENDING THE
NIGHT AT BRIANNA'S.
>> YOU'RE A GOOD BOY.
>> WHEN I WOKE UP THE NEXT
MORNING, I WAS IN REALLY
BAD PAIN.
UGH.
OH, MY GOD.
BRI, I'M HAVING A CONTRACTION.
>> YOU GETTING ANOTHER ONE?
>> TODAY MIGHT BE THE DAY, GIRL.
>> THAT BABY'S A-COMIN'.
>> [exhaling sharply]
>> YOU GET A CONTRACTION?
>> MM-HMM.
[exhaling sharply]
[phone chirping]
I'M TEXTING MY MOM.
>> SHE'S ON HER WAY.
>> IS SHE?
OH, OKAY.
IT'S PROBABLY MATT.
>> OH, GENNA.
"HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?"
>> HI, GUYS.
>> HEY.
MOMMY'S HERE.
>> HI, SWEETHEART.
HOW YOU DOING, HONEY?
>> GOOD.
>> SHE'S HAD A CONTRACTION.
>> HOW FAR APART ARE THEY
RIGHT NOW?
>> BETWEEN 10 AND 15 MINUTES.
>> OKAY, I'M GONNA GRAB
YOUR THINGS.
I LOVE YOU, HONEY, ALL RIGHT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> I'LL SEE YOU IN A LITTLE BIT,
THEN, OKAY?
>> OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
>> SO DID YOU TALK TO MATT?
>> NO.
[panting]
>> YOU THINK HE'S GONNA
COME DOWN?
>> OH, YEAH.
[line ringing]
DON'T TELL ME HE [bleep]
WENT M.I.A.
I'VE BEEN IN LABOR FOR THE PAST
FOUR HOURS, AND HE HASN'T
DONE [bleep].
>> YOU'VE GOT TO STAY CALM.
>> I'M GONNA GO DOWN THERE, AND
I'M GONNA HAVE A FACE-TO-FACE
CONVERSATION WITH HIM.
THERE HE GOES.
KEEP GOING.
HE'S--HE'S AN IDIOT.
WE NEED TO TALK NOW.
I'M GOING INTO [bleep] LABOR.
[crying]
OH, GOD.
I NEED TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> TAKING HER TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> ALL RIGHT, BYE.
>> [breathing heavily]
OH, GOD.
>> [crying]
>> IT'S OKAY.
ONCE THE EPIDURAL'S IN, YOU'RE
NOT GONNA FEEL ANYTHING, OKAY?
>> AFTER I GOT MY EPIDURAL,
I WAS ABLE TO GET SOME REST.
AND MATT STAYED BY MY SIDE
THE WHOLE NIGHT.
AFTER 18 HOURS INTO MY LABOR,
IT WAS FINALLY TIME TO PUSH.
>> AND PUSH, HARD, HARD, HARD,
HARD, TWO, THREE.
EVEN HARDER, FOUR, FIVE, SIX,
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
[baby crying]
[gentle guitar music]
>>  I HEAR YOU
IN MY HEAD
I NEED YOU HERE
INSTEAD
I NEVER WANTED
ANYBODY ELSE
I NEVER NEEDED
>> MY MOM HAS TO GO HOME TO TAKE
CARE OF MY BROTHER AND SISTER,
SO FOR OUR FIRST NIGHT, MATT AND
I GOT TO BOND WITH ARABELLA
ON OUR OWN.
AFTER SPENDING TWO DAYS
WITH THE BABY, I CAN'T IMAGINE
GIVING HER TO SOMEONE ELSE.
MATT AND I ARE HEADED
TO HIS HOUSE TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO.
YOU WANT TO HOLD HER?
>> MM-HMM.
[whispering] BABY GIRL.
>> ARE YOU HAPPY
TO HAVE HER HOME?
>> MM-HMM.
IT'S AMAZING.
>> I WANT THIS TO BE A FAMILY.
I DO.
>> YEAH.
WELL, I WANT TO BE THERE.
I WANT TO BE PART OF IT.
>> ALL I ASK IS THAT YOU'RE
COMMITTED TO HER,
BECAUSE THE LAST THING I WANT
IS FOR HER TO HAVE
A BROKEN FAMILY.
>> YEAH.
>> HONESTLY, I'M NOT GONNA
CHASE YOU DOWN TO COME SEE HER.
>> AND YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE TO.
LIKE, I'M BUILDING A
RELATIONSHIP WITH HER RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, THAT'S MY MAIN FOCUS.
>> I JUST HOPE THAT THE WAY
THAT YOU ARE NOW STICKS.
EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT SURE MATT
WILL ACTUALLY HELP ME OUT,
I'M READY TO LET EVERYONE KNOW
WHAT I'M THINKING.
I THINK IT'S PRETTY SET RIGHT
NOW THAT SHE'S MINE FOR NOW.
>> I AM SO SORRY.
HOW DO YOU SEE YOURSELF LIVING
AND SURVIVING?
>> THERE WOULD BE SCHOOL,
BABY, WORK.
>> THAT'S NOT CLEAR ENOUGH.
I MEAN, HOW DO YOU SEE YOUR
LIFE GOING?
>> I THINK, ALL IN ALL, WHAT
YOUR MOM IS JUST TRYING TO SAY
TO YOU IS THE REALITY
PART OF IT.
>> YOU'RE TALKING, LIKE, $600,
$700 A MONTH, IS WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA BE SPENDING.
YOU GOT TO THROW ON TOP OF THE
RENT GAS AND CAR EXPENSES.
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN EARNED A THIRD
OF THAT YET, LET ALONE HAVING
A CHILD AND SCHOOL.
>> I UNDER--
OH, MY GOD.
>> NOBODY WANTS TO SEE YOU FAIL.
WE ALL LOVE YOU.
WE ALL LOVE HER.
OKAY?
AND EVERYBODY JUST WANTS
WHAT'S BEST.
IT IS YOUR DECISION,
BUT I'M SCARED THAT YOU'RE
GOING TO BE TURNING TO
THE WRONG SUPPORT NETWORK.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"WRONG SUPPORT NETWORK?"
>> YOU'VE HIT THAT POINT WHERE
YOU'RE SITTING IN THE BATHROOM,
YOU'RE CRYING YOUR EYES OUT,
YOU CAN'T GET THE BABY TO STOP
CRYING, MATT'S NO HELP,
YOU CAN'T MAKE ENDS MEET,
YOU HAVE ZERO IN YOUR BANK
ACCOUNT, AND THE RENT'S DUE.
>> THEN I'M OUT OF LUCK.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM WITH--
>> HONEY, I KNOW.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M SCARED, BECAUSE I KNOW
THE HARD PART'S COMING.
HONEY, I AM NOT TRYING
TO MAKE YOU FEEL BAD.
NOW THAT YOU HAVE HER, YOU CAN'T
BE WISHY-WASHY, OKAY?
JUST KNOW--KNOW WHO'S GONNA BE
THERE FOR YOU.
>> AS HARD AS IT WAS TO TELL
EVERYONE I'M KEEPING MY BABY,
NOW I HAVE TO PROVE THAT I CAN
DO IT ON MY OWN, AND THAT STARTS
BY SETTING UP OUR NEW PLACE.
WE ARE HOME SWEET HOME.
YOU OKAY, SWEET PEA?
[laughter]
>> SHE POOPED.
[baby crying]
YOU HAVE IT ON YOUR HANDS.
[laughing]
SO HOW YOU FEELING ABOUT
SPENDING YOUR FIRST NIGHT
OVER HERE?
>> I'M NERVOUS.
>> IS MATT GONNA COME BACK
TONIGHT?
>> I TOLD HIM, YOU KNOW,
IF HE WANTS.
IT'S UP TO HIM.
[baby crying]
SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
ARABELLA.
[baby fussing]
I CAN'T BELIEVE MATT DISAPPEARED
ON ARABELLA'S FIRST NIGHT HOME.
AND TO MAKE THINGS WORSE,
MY EXPENSES ARE PILING UP.
>> COME HERE, BABY GIRL.
NOW, DO WE WANT TO TALK ABOUT
PAYING BILLS AND STUFF?
>> UM...
AUGUST 1ST, I'M GOING TO BE
WRITING YOU A CHECK,
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
OR, WELL, OBVIOUSLY I'LL WRITE
IT BEFORE, BUT I'LL PUT THE DATE
AT THE TOP FOR AUGUST 1ST.
EVEN THOUGH I'M WRITING BRENDA A
CHECK, I DON'T HAVE ENOUGH CASH
IN MY ACCOUNT TO COVER RENT.
I THOUGHT I'D BE BACK TO WORK
BY NOW, BUT LOOKING AFTER ABABY
IS A FULL-TIME JOB.
I NEED MATT'S HELP, BUT WHEN
HE FINALLY SHOWED UP,
HE LOOKED LIKE HE'D BEEN
PARTYING ALL NIGHT.
>> I THINK SHE WENT
TO THE BATHROOM.
YOU MIGHT HAVE TO CHANGE
HER ONESIE.
ALEX, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YEAH, WATCH HER HEAD.
[baby crying]
>> I NEED YOUR HELP WITH THIS.
IT WAS NICE, 'CAUSE YOU STAYED
WITH ME IN THE HOSPITAL,
AND I WAS ABLE TO SLEEP.
YOU'RE NOT HERE NOW.
IT'S TOUGH ON ME.
>> I'LL HELP AGAIN.
>> I MEAN, I AM GONNA NEED A LOT
OF FINANCIAL SUPPORT FROM YOU.
>> YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
>> HOW IS, LIKE, YOUR PLANS
WITH A JOB?
>> I'LL PROBABLY GET ONE
SOMEWHERE, LIKE A FACTORY.
>> OKAY.
>> IT'LL BE FINE.
I'LL DO MY BEST.
THAT'S ALL I CAN DO.
WHAT?
>> YOU JUST LOOK REALLY SICK.
>> I'M TIRED.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
I BARELY SLEPT AT ALL
LAST NIGHT.
>> LET'S SEE.
SHE WAS UP AT 3:30.
THEN SHE WAS UP AT 5:30.
SHE WAS UP AT 6:00.
>> SORRY, I'M JUST TIRED.
>> DO YOU WANT TO GET GOING,
THEN, SO YOU CAN GET SOME SLEEP?
>> LET ME HOLD HER QUICK
BEFORE I GO.
I GOT HER.
I'LL PROBABLY COME SEE YOU
TOMORROW.
THERE YOU GO.
>> UGH.
IT'S BEEN OVER A WEEK SINCE I
ASKED MATT FOR MONEY, BUT I
HAVEN'T SEEN A DIME,
AND I'M STILL DOING EVERYTHING
ON MY OWN.
[baby crying]
ARABELLA!
IF THIS IS HOW MATT'S GOING TO
BE, I'M STARTING TO THINK I NEED
TO MOVE BACK IN WITH MY MOM.
I REALLY WANT TO BE BACK
WITH MY FAMILY,
BECAUSE THIS IS WHERE I FEEL
COMFORTABLE.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S MORE
SPACE HERE.
>> YOU CAN LIVE HERE.
THIS IS YOUR HOME, OKAY?
YOU AREN'T BY YOURSELF, AND I
WILL HELP YOU IF I CAN.
BUT ALL I WANT YOU TO REALIZE
IS, THE LACK OF PLANNING IS NOT
BEING A RESPONSIBLE PARENT.
>> I KNOW, AND I'M TRYING TO GET
IT TOGETHER.
>> NOT REALLY.
RIGHT NOW, YOU ARE CURRENTLY
CATCHING UP EVERYTHING THAT
SHOULD HAVE BEEN DONE
SIX MONTHS AGO.
>> BUT SIX MONTHS AGO, WE DIDN'T
THINK I WAS KEEPING THE BABY.
YOU KNOW, THREE WEEKS AGO, NONE
OF US REALLY THOUGHT--
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE PREPARED
FOR THE NEXT SIX MONTHS?
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
YOU DIDN'T PLAN.
YOU DIDN'T PREPARE.
AND THEN YOU WOUND UP
IN A SITUATION THAT ESCALATED
OUT OF CONTROL.
IT IS WHAT IT IS.
NOW WE'VE GOT TO LOOK TOWARDS
WHAT'S NEXT.
SCHOOL'S STARTING.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> THIS HELTER-SKELTER LIFESTYLE
HAS TO STOP, ALL RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I'M GLAD MY MOM IS OKAY
WITH ME MOVING BACK IN,
BUT I'M WORRIED ABOUT THE RENT
I OWE BRENDA.
MY MOM AND I WERE TALKING
AND EVERYTHING, AND I ONLY HAVE
$300 IN THE BANK ACCOUNT.
AND RENT WOULD BE $260.
THAT LEAVES ME WITH
PRACTICALLY NOTHING.
>> BROKE DOESN'T FLY
WITH A BABY.
>> I KNOW.
SO MY MOM OFFERED ME TO STAY
WITH HER.
>> OH, THAT'S GOOD.
>> BUT, LIKE, I DON'T THINK
BRENDA CAN AFFORD THE RENT,
AND NOW BRI AND HER MOM, THEY
WERE SAYING THAT I SHOULD STILL
PAY BRENDA THE RENT FOR AUGUST.
>> IT'S JUST A BOGUS SITUATION.
>> WELL, I TOLD THEM I'LL PICK
UP ALL MY STUFF.
YOU KNOW, DON'T TOUCH IT.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF ALL OF IT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT
DOING ANYTHING.
I TEXTED BRENDA, TELLING HER
I CAN'T PAY THE RENT, BUT I
HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER IN PERSON,
BECAUSE MY MOM QUICKLY THREW
TOGETHER A WELCOME PARTY FOR
ARABELLA.
>> YOU ARE WIDE AWAKE NOW.
>> SHE'S OPENING PRESENTS!
[laughter]
>> YEAH.
>> THINK OF ALL THE MONEY YOU'RE
GOING TO SAVE.
>> THANK HEAVEN
FOR LITTLE GIRLS.
>> THAT'S CUTE.
>> OH, MY...
>> all: AWW!
>> CUTE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
BRENDA TEXTED ME AND TOLD ME
THAT IF I DON'T COME RIGHT NOW
TO GET MY STUFF, IT'S GOING
ON THE CURB.
>> BUT NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
IT IS A SHOWER, OKAY?
>> IT'S A BABY SHOWER.
>> NO, IT'S A WELCOME PARTY,
OKAY?
WE'LL WORK IT OUT.
AT SOME POINT THIS EVENING,
I WILL GO, AND I WILL TAKE CARE
OF IT, OKAY?
>> NO, BECAUSE SHE WANTS ME
THERE NOW.
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU'RE IN THE MIDDLE OF WHAT YOU
NEED TO BE DOING.
>> THAT'S WHAT I TOLD HER.
AND THAT DOESN'T MEAN [bleep]
TO HER.
I'M GRABBING MY STUFF,
AND I'M LEAVING.
>> I'LL GO ALONG.
SLOW--SLOW DOWN.
>> OHH...
>> THERE'S YOUR STUFF,
ON THE CURB.
>> I'M CALLING MY MOM.
THOSE ARE HERS.
THEY'RE NOT MINE.
MOM, MY BED--ALL MY [bleep] IS
SITTING OUT IN THE FREAKING
DRIVEWAY.
IT'S [bleep] DISGUSTING!
HAS ANYONE EVER HEARD OF
FREAKING SOPHISTICATION?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THE PROBLEM IS,
ALEX?
AND I'M GONNA SAY THIS.
YOU'VE NEVER REALLY FIGURED OUT
EXACTLY HOW YOU'RE GONNA
GET THROUGH THE NEXT
COUPLE OF MONTHS.
GET IT TOGETHER.
>> ALWAYS MAKE SURE THE FLARES
OF THE DIAPER COME OUT,
'CAUSE IT HELPS PROTECT
ALL THE POOPIES IN IT.
THANK YOU, THOUGH, DUDE.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK HOME
WITH MY FAMILY.
MY GRANDFATHER EVEN OFFERED
TO GIVE ME A CAR SO I CAN GET TO
SCHOOL AND TO WORK WITHOUT
RELYING ON MY MOM.
>> LET'S GIVE IT A TRY.
IT'S GOT 160,000 MILES ON IT.
IT'S GOT ANOTHER 100,000 LEFT.
LET'S GO.
PUT ON YOUR TURN SIGNAL.
MAKE A LEFT.
I THINK YOU'RE A NATURAL.
>> CAN I SAY HI?
I GOTCHA.
HI, BUDDY, HOW ARE YOU?
HI!
YOU HAVE TO FORM A PLAN.
YOU KNOW THIS.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> BUT, I MEAN, EVEN DAY CARE
FOR WHEN YOU'RE WORKING AND
EVERYTHING ELSE.
LIKE, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO
WHEN YOU GO BACK TO SCHOOL?
ONE OF THE REASONS WHY I SAID
ADOPTION WAS YOUR BEST OPTION,
IS BECAUSE I'VE GOT A LOT OF
DIFFERENT THINGS THAT I JUGGLE,
OKAY?
>> I KNOW THAT, MOM.
>> I HAVE GOT TO GO, OKAY?
I GOT TO CHANGE.
I GOT STUFF TO DO.
WE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE SOON.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> UM, I HAD
A COUPLE OF QUESTIONS.
I'LL BE ATTENDING SCHOOL
FOR 30 HOURS A WEEK.
HOW MUCH WOULD YOUR RATES BE?
>> OKAY.
>> UM, IT'S A LITTLE BIT
OUT OF MY RANGE.
UM...
>> OKAY.
>> DAY CARES ARE JUST
RIDICULOUSLY EXPENSIVE,
AND, FINANCIALLY, IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE TO DO IT.
>> SO WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> I TALKED TO THE SCHOOL ABOUT
SWITCHING TO CYBER SCHOOL.
BASICALLY, MY HIGH SCHOOL
EDUCATION, I'M GONNA BE GETTING
OVER THE COMPUTER.
>> MY CONCERN IS, IF YOU GO TO
CYBER SCHOOL, HOW ARE YOU GONNA
MAINTAIN YOUR GRADES.
>> IT'S GONNA BE HARD.
>> THE LACK OF SOCIAL
INTERACTION--
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THAT?
>> I'M BUMMED ABOUT IT, 'CAUSE,
LIKE, I'M GONNA MISS, LIKE,
GENNA AND RAY.
IT'S SOMETHING I HAVE TO DO.
LIKE, I MADE THIS DECISION.
IT'S A SACRIFICE I HAVE TO
GIVE UP.
EVEN THOUGH MATT'S STILL NOT
BEEN AROUND, SUMMER'S ALMOST
OVER, I'M I'M TRYING TO SQUEEZE
IN AS MUCH TIME WITH MY FRIENDS
AS I CAN,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I'M SWITCHING
TO ONLINE CLASSES FOR MY
SENIOR YEAR.
AHH, A SQUIRREL!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> GO, SQUIRREL, GO!
>> YOU AND I ARE TAKING PICTURES
TODAY, BABY.
>> SHE'S LIKE, "I DON'T WANT
TO BE HERE."
>> YES, YOU DO.
>> YOU DO WANT TO BE HERE.
>> I'M GONNA, LIKE, MISS YOU
GUYS SO MUCH,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT LIKE I'LL BE
WITH YOU GUYS.
I'LL BE AT HOME.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M NOT GONNA LIE.
THAT SUCKS, DUDE.
>> THAT'S AWFUL.
>> IT'S SENIOR YEAR, DUDE.
WE FINALLY, YOU KNOW--
FOUR YEARS.
>> YOU WERE GOING TO ORGANIZE
THE PRANK.
>> THAT'S TRUE.
>> I MEAN, WE WERE GONNA GET THE
FRICKIN', LIKE, SENIOR TERRACE
FOR LUNCH.
AND WE GOT PROM, AND, LIKE,
EVERY DAY WE RULE THE SCHOOL.
LIKE, THIS IS OUR TIME NOW.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE IT'S NOT
REALLY FAIR THAT MATT GETS TO,
YOU KNOW, GO TO SCHOOL
AND SEE ALL HIS FRIENDS,
AND YOU GET WHAT?
YOU GET CYBER SCHOOL.
>> YOU LOSE YOUR SENIOR YEAR.
>> WHAT IS HE SACRIFICING
FOR YOU RIGHT NOW?
>> THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
ABOUT IT.
LIKE, WE MADE THIS MISTAKE,
AND, YOU KNOW, IF HE DOESN'T
OWN UP TO IT, ONE OF US HAS TO,
AND I--IT'S GONNA BE ME.
>> I JUST DON'T THINK
THAT'S FAIR.
>> SMILE FOR THE FIRST DAY
OF SCHOOL, GUYS.
SCHOOL STARTS TODAY,
AND EVERYONE IS HEADING BACK
TO CLASS, EXCEPT ME.
HELLO?
>> UH, YEAH, SURE.
>> UH, YEAH, I'LL BE LEAVING
AFTER KILLIAN AND STUFF.
>> BYE.
>> MATT?
>> HE WOKE UP LATE.
>> SEE YA!
>> BYE.
>> LET'S GO.
>> MATT!
>> WHAT?
>> HOW?
I'M SERIOUS.
>> NO.
>> YOU SMELL, MATT.
>> MATT, I'M SORRY.
IT'S HARD TO TRUST YOU.
>> YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
DAZING IN AND OUT WITH YOUR
EYES CLOSED.
>> [sighs]
>> WHAT?
>> NOTHING, YOU'RE JUST--
YOU'RE LUCKY.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO BE GOING TO
SCHOOL RIGHT NOW INSTEAD OF
HAVING TO STAY HOME.
I WISH I WAS YOU.
I WISH I HAD YOUR AVAILABILITY
TO JUST DO WHATEVER.
>> IT'D BE A LOT EASIER ON ME
IN LIFE.
[baby crying]
>> I'M TRYING NOT TO FOCUS ON
MATT AND KEEP UP WITH MY
ONLINE CLASSES.
I'M DOING MY BEST NOT TO GIVE UP
EVERYTHING, LIKE MY TWO JOBS.
AND, LUCKILY, MY BOSS AT THE
DANCE STUDIO SAID I COULD COME
BACK AND BRING ARABELLA WITH ME.
HI, MISS LEANN.
>> HELLO, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> HOW'S THE BABY?
>> ALEX!
LET ME SEE THE BABY.
[laughter]
AWW, SHE'S SO CUTE.
>> WOW.
>> YOU TIRED?
>> YEAH.
>> AWW.
>> SO WHAT ARE SOME OF THE
HARDEST THINGS ABOUT HAVING
THE BABY NOW?
>> LIKE, MY SOCIAL LIFE IS
SLOWLY DETERIORATING.
IF I WANT TO DO SOMETHING
AND I CAN'T FIND A BABYSITTER,
I CAN'T GO OUT.
>> LIKE, THE WEEKS BEFORE, HE
SPENT EVERY SINGLE DAY WITH ME
IN THE HOSPITAL.
AND THEN NOW, IT'S LIKE HE COMES
AROUND EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
HE'LL--HE'S VISITED HER MAYBE
TWICE IN A WEEK.
>> OH, NO, THAT'S BAD.
>> THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
>> YEAH, THAT'S--
>> SO HE HARDLY EVER SEES HER?
>> THAT'S MATT.
>> HE BASICALLY HAS PARTYING
AND HIS FRIENDS ON HIS MIND.
BUT HIS PRIORITY SHOULD BE
THE BABY, NOTHING ELSE.
>> DO YOU WANT TO START WARMING
THEM UP FOR CLASS FOR ME?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> DO YOU NEED TO BRING
THE BABY?
>> YEAH, I'LL JUST SET HER
IN THE CORNER.
>> HI.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO,
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
STAY TOGETHER.
[laughter]
OKAY, SO THAT NEEDS
TO BE BIGGER.
SO JUMP OUT AND GO BOOM.
[baby fussing]
>> OHH!
>> IT'S ALL OVER THE SIDE.
>> SHE PUKED.
>> GO TO THE BEGINNING
OF THE DANCE AGAIN.
SHE JUST THREW UP ON THE FLOOR.
I CAN'T HAVE HER, LIKE,
IN HERE WHILE I'M TEACHING
AND DANCING.
>> GOOD LUCK CLEANING THAT UP.
>> GO BACK, OPENING LINES.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, READY?
>> YOU'VE GOT THEM, JERMAINE?
>> YEAH, I GOT IT.
GO.
JUST GO, GO, GO, GO.
>> SHE PROJECTILE VOMITED
ONTO THE FLOOR.
HAVING ARABELLA IN THE STUDIO
WITH ME DIDN'T WORK OUT AT ALL.
AND I DEFINITELY WON'T BE ABLE
TO TAKE HER TO MY OTHER JOB,
SO I ASKED MATT TO COME OVER
AND WATCH HER WHILE I WORK.
AND SURPRISINGLY, HE SAID YES.
I GOT TO GET READY FOR WORK.
>> WHO'S WATCHING HER?
'CAUSE JULIE AND I ARE GOING
OUT TO DINNER.
YES.
>> MATT'S SUPPOSED TO.
I GOT TO CALL HIM.
>> DOES HE KNOW HE'S
WATCHING HER?
>> YES.
>> I MEAN, YOU'RE SURE?
[baby fussing]
>> ABSOLUTELY, POSITIVELY SURE?
>> I'LL CALL HIM.
>> THANK YOU.
[line ringing]
DO YOU HAVE A BACKUP PLAN?
SO WHAT HAPPENS IF HE DOESN'T
SHOW UP?
>> PLEASE LEAVE YOUR MESSAGE
FOR 484--
>> I'M GONNA KICK HIM.
>> NO, I MEAN WHAT HAPPENS
IF HE DOESN'T SHOW UP?
I HAVE PLANS.
I'M NOT TRYING TO BE A JERK,
HONEY, BUT IT'S MORE RESPONSIBLE
TO SET UP A SITTER THAT YOU KNOW
IS GONNA BE THERE.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANYBODY
FREAKING ELSE!
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S
NOT HERE.
>> [sniffling]
JUST PICK UP THE FRICKING PHONE.
[line ringing]
>> female announcer:
DON'T GO AWAY.
THIS EPISODE OF 16 AND PREGNANT
CONTINUES RIGHT NOW.
>> MATT NEVER SHOWED UP
TO WATCH ARABELLA, SO I COULDN'T
GO TO WORK, AND MY MOM
IS GETTING FED UP.
>> WHY WOULDN'T HE WANT
TO BE HERE?
>> I...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING
THROUGH HIS HEAD.
I DON'T CONTROL HIM.
I DON'T--
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
>> RELYING ON HIM IS ONLY GOING
TO FRUSTRATE YOU.
>> I'M NOT RELYING ON HIM.
>> YOU RELIED ON HIM
ON SATURDAY,
AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
THE BEST THING THAT YOU COULD DO
FOR ARABELLA IS TO WALK AWAY
AND START GETTING YOUR LIFE
TOGETHER.
>> EVERYONE KEEPS PUSHING AND
PUSHING AND PUSHING AND TELLING
ME WHAT TO DO, WHEN IT'S HARD
FOR ME TO DO THAT BECAUSE I
CARE ABOUT HIM.
>> AND YOU'RE STICKING UP FOR
THE PERSON YOU CARE ABOUT.
IT'S COMPLICATING THE SITUATION.
IT'S CONVOLUTING WHERE YOUR
RESPONSIBILITIES LIE.
>> I'M TRYING TO PREVENT HER
FROM NOT HAVING A FATHER.
THAT IS MY PRIORITY.
>> NO.
>> MY PRIORITY IS MAKING SURE
THAT SHE HAS ANOTHER PARENT,
THAT SHE DOES HAVE A DAD,
BECAUSE I BARELY HAD A DAD,
AND LOOK HOW I AM.
>> BUT THE PROBLEM IS, IT'S NOT
WHAT IS BEST FOR ARABELLA.
AS MUCH AS YOU LOVE HIM,
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT?
>> THREE DAYS LATER,
MATT FINALLY SHOWED UP, AND I
COULDN'T EVEN LOOK AT HIM.
[baby crying]
THERE'S A LOT OF STUFF THAT
NEEDS TO BE SAID.
I'M STARTING TO GET REALLY
UPSET AND TO THE POINT WHERE I
JUST CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
LIKE, I'M REALLY UPSET
ABOUT SATURDAY.
>> OH, I HAD [bleep] TO DO.
BUT, OKAY, BEFORE THAT--
>> I STARTED WORKING AGAIN.
>> BUT, SEE, I WAS--
>> BUT WHERE ARE YOU, MATT?
>> OKAY.
>> I NEED YOU TO WATCH HER,
AND YOU FLAKE OUT!
>> MAYBE I'M NOT HERE
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
>> THAT'S HOW IT SHOULD BE!
I HAVE [bleep] TO DO.
I CAN'T DO IT, BECAUSE I NEED
TO TAKE CARE OF HER.
>> YOU KNOW, ONE THING ABOUT
BABIES IS, THEY PICK UP ON
YELLING, AND YOU DO AN AWFUL LOT
OF YELLING, SO SHE--
>> YEAH, I YELL AT YOU,
BECAUSE YOU AREN'T AROUND!
>> ALL RIGHT, BUT EVERYONE KNOWS
WHERE I STOOD.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"WHERE YOU STOOD?"
>> I POINTED OUT, HOW MANY
TIMES, HOW HARD IT WOULD BE.
WE'RE TWO TEENAGERS, SO THAT
WOULD BE ONE REASON ON WHY,
YOU KNOW, YOU WOULD GIVE--
THAT A VIABLE OPTION WOULD BE
ADOPTION.
THEN YOU WOULD SIT DOWN, AND
YOU'D THINK OF ANOTHER REASON.
"OKAY, MATT HAS NO JOB.
THAT'S GONNA BE HARD.
GETTING A PLACE TO LIVE.
THAT'S GONNA BE HARD."
>> OKAY, BUT SOMETHING CAME OVER
ME AT THE HOSPITAL, AND I
COULDN'T GET RID OF HER.
>> YOU DIDN'T EVEN SIT DOWN
AND THINK OF ALL THIS STUFF.
>> YES, I DID, EVERY DAMN DAY,
WHEN YOU WENT DISAPPEARING.
>> MM, PLEASE?
>> GROW UP, MATT.
YOU'RE GONNA BE 18.
>> [bleep] THIS.
I'M DONE.
>> YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE DECISION
IF YOU WANT TO ACTUALLY BE
A PART OF THIS.
>> UH, I'M TRYING MY BEST.
>> WOULD YOU RATHER MISS THE
MOST CRUCIAL POINTS IN HER LIFE?
>> YOU CANNOT YELL AT ME.
WHY ARE YOU RAISING YOUR VOICE?
>> BECAUSE YOU DON'T GET
WHAT YOU DO.
>> YOU'RE COOL.
>> ALL YOU ARE TO ME
IS A HEADACHE.
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M YOUR EXCEDRIN,
THEN, THERE YOU GO.
SEE IF YOU EVER [bleep]
SEE ME AGAIN.
>> HEY, THEN YOUR DAUGHTER
MISSES OUT, NOT ME.
>> EVERYBODY WILL MISS OUT
ON A LOT.
>> ALL YOU'RE GONNA BE IS A
CHECK IN THE DAMN [bleep] MAIL.
>> I WON'T EVEN BE THAT,
WHERE I'M GOING.
>> MATT!
>> [bleep].
WHAT?
>> I'M TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT THE [bleep] IS GOING
THROUGH YOUR HEAD!
WHETHER YOU WANT TO SEE THAT
LITTLE GIRL WHO IS SITTING
IN THAT ROOM OR IF YOU WANT TO
WALK AWAY AND GO HANG OUT WITH
YOUR CRACKHEAD FRIENDS.
YOU'RE A [bleep] DEADBEAT DAD.
DO YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU ARE NOTHING.
YOU ARE A PART OF HER FAMILY,
BUT YOU CAN'T BE A [bleep] MAN.
ALL YOU DO, EVERY DAY,
IS HURT ME.
I DON'T WANT YOU ANYWHERE NEAR
MY DAUGHTER ANYMORE.
[crying]
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO SIT
HERE AND KEEP WAITING FOR MATT
TO JUST GROW UP AND DO WHAT
HE NEEDS TO.
AND I'M SCARED OF HAVING
TO DO IT BY MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT TO BE
A SINGLE MOM, BUT NOW I HAVE TO.
[baby crying]
ARABELLA.
I LOVE MATT TO DEATH,
BUT HE'S NOT THE PERSON THAT I
FELL IN LOVE WITH TWO YEARS AGO.
>> WHEN WAS THAT?
>> THE END OF AUGUST,
BEFORE SOPHOMORE YEAR.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> YEAH, LIKE RIGHT
IN THE BEGINNING.
>> SO MUCH HAS CHANGED.
>> IN THE BEGINNING OF MY
PREGNANCY, IT WAS REALLY,
REALLY SCARY.
I REALLY DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> ARE YOU OKAY WITH EVERYTHING?
>> I'M STARTING TO GET VERY
STRESSED, NOW THAT WE'RE
GETTING FARTHER INTO HER BEING
OLDER NOW.
ADOPTION IS AN AMAZING CHOICE.
I THINK IT GIVES A LOT OF
OPPORTUNITIES FOR THE MOTHER
AS WELL AS THE BABY.
BUT THE PROBLEM I HAD WAS,
I COULDN'T LET GO.
I DIDN'T WANT TO LET GO.
CAN YOU HELP ME?
IF YOU COULD CHANGE HER QUICK.
NOW THAT SHE'S BORN,
MY FAMILY HAS STEPPED UP,
AND NOW THEY STAND BEHIND ME,
AND THEY HELP ME AS MUCH AS
THEY CAN.
BUT THEY DON'T DO
EVERYTHING FOR ME.
I'M GONNA BE PAYING FOR
EVERYTHING THAT SHE NEEDS
ON MY OWN, AND IT'S GONNA BE
TOUGH FOR ME TO AFFORD COLLEGE.
SAY, "MOMMY HAS TO DO HER WORK."
WILL YOU BE GOOD WHILE MOMMY
DOES HER WORK?
SINCE SHE'S BEEN BORN, I'VE HAD
TO MAKE A LOT OF SACRIFICES
FOR HER.
I'VE GIVEN UP ALL MY FRIENDS.
I'VE GIVEN UP MY SENIOR YEAR
OF HIGH SCHOOL.
BEFORE I GOT PREGNANT, MY
NUMBER ONE GOAL AND PRIORITY
WAS TO OWN MY OWN DANCE STUDIO.
I STILL CAN FULFILL THAT GOAL...
>> ALEX?
>> BUT IT'S GONNA TAKE ME
A LOT LONGER, AND I DON'T WANT
TO THROW IT OUT THE WINDOW
BECAUSE I HAD A BABY.
>> announcer: ON THE NEXT
16 AND PREGNANT:
>> TY WON'T GET TO SEE THE
BABY BECAUSE SHE HAS A PROBLEM
WITH TYLER.
>> HE'S DISRESPECTFUL.
I DON'T LIKE HIM.
>> "HOW IS HE GONNA RAISE
A BLACK BABY?"
>> SHE IS NOT GONNA KEEP MY SON
AWAY FROM ME.
>> YOU'RE MINE,
AND WHAT'S YOURS IS MINE.
>> IT'S NOT YOUR KID.
I'M GONNA TELL HER THAT I'M