>> I LOOK CUTE.
I'M IZABELLA.
I'M 16 YEARS OLD, AND I LIVE
IN DRAPER, UTAH.
WE MIGHT LIVE IN A TOTALLY
MORMON STATE, BUT MY PARENTS
ARE PRETTY SERIOUS CATHOLICS.
MY DAD WORKS FOR THE AIRLINES,
AND MY MOM HAS A DAY CARE
BUSINESS, BUT THEIR MAIN
PRIORITY IS ME AND MY LITTLE
BROTHER'S EDUCATION.
>> SO WITH YOUR TEST,
ARE YOU READY FOR IT?
>> I'M NOT DONE STUDYING YET.
THEY SEND US TO CATHOLIC SCHOOL,
AND I'M GETTING READY TO GO BACK
FOR MY SOPHOMORE YEAR.
BECAUSE I WANT TO GO TO MED
SCHOOL, I'M IN ALL A.P. COURSES,
AND I'M CONSTANTLY STUDYING.
THE ONLY THING I TAKE MORE
SERIOUSLY THAN MY CLASSES
IS DRILL TEAM.
ALL OF MY BEST FRIENDS
ARE ON THE SQUAD WITH ME,
EXCEPT FOR MY BEST, BEST FRIEND
CASSIDY.
WE'VE BEEN SEEING LESS OF EACH
OTHER SINCE I STARTED SPENDING
ALL MY TIME WITH MY BOYFRIEND,
JAIRO.
HE'S A BIT OF A SLACKER IN
SCHOOL AND CARES MUCH MORE
ABOUT HIS HAIR AND HIS CAR
THAN HIS GRADES, BUT HE'S
SWEET AND REALLY UNDERSTANDS ME.
EVEN THOUGH WE'VE ONLY BEEN
DATING FOR THREE MONTHS,
WE'VE GOTTEN REALLY CLOSE.
I'VE BEEN AVOIDING ALL
MY FRIENDS THE WHOLE SUMMER
AND SPENDING EVERY SECOND
WITH JAIRO, BECAUSE I'M JUST
TOO SCARED TO TELL EVERYONE
THAT I'M PREGNANT.
[chime dings]
I WAS SO ASHAMED WHEN I FOUND
OUT I WAS PREGNANT AT THE END OF
THE SCHOOL YEAR THAT I DECIDED
TO KEEP THE BABY A SECRET
THROUGH THE SUMMER.
BUT NOW I'M DUE IN A MONTH,
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER
I CAN IGNORE MY FRIENDS
OR HIDE MY BIG BELLY.
I'M LUCKY THAT MY MOM
IS UNDERSTANDING AND HELPS
AS MUCH AS SHE CAN.
HOW DO YOU THINK, LIKE,
MY FRIENDS ARE GONNA REACT?
>> THEY SHOULD BE SUPPORTIVE.
I MEAN, YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
HAVE BEEN IN THE SAME SCHOOL
FOR YEARS.
I MEAN, YOU'VE BEEN GOING TO
THIS SCHOOL SINCE PRESCHOOL.
THEY SHOULD BE THERE FOR YOU,
BUT I DON'T KNOW IF THEY WILL.
EVEN IF THEY ARE MEAN AND HAVE
BAD THINGS TO SAY, WE CAN'T LET
IT GET TO US, YOU KNOW?
YOU STILL HAVE A FEW MORE YEARS
OF SCHOOL, AND THAT'S WHAT
YOU NEED TO FOCUS ON,
IS GETTING THROUGH SCHOOL.
>> DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN I, LIKE,
FIRST TOLD YOU THAT I WAS
PREGNANT?
DID YOU KNOW ALREADY?
>> I KIND OF HAD A FEELING,
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T SEEM
YOURSELF.
YOU WEREN'T AS OPEN.
YOU WEREN'T TALKING AS MUCH
AS YOU NORMALLY DO.
AND THEN IT--I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S LIKE I WANTED TO KNOW,
BUT THEN WHEN YOU CONFIRMED IT,
I DIDN'T KNOW IF I WANTED
TO KNOW ANYMORE.
AT FIRST, I DIDN'T FACE REALITY,
I THINK.
>> ARE YOU DISAPPOINTED IN ME?
>> OBVIOUSLY, I GUESS WE HAVE
TO LOOK AT IT AS, YOU KNOW,
IT'LL JUST BE AN ADDITION
TO OUR FAMILY, AND WE KIND OF
NEED TO GO FROM THAT.
I KNOW...
>> YOU'RE GONNA HELP ME TAKE
CARE OF HIM, RIGHT?
>> [laughs]
OF COURSE.
>> IS THE LASAGNA, LIKE,
BURNING OR SOMETHING?
>> NO, WHY?
[laughs]
>> MOM...
>> I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE
THE STOVE WAS STILL ON.
YOU'RE DISTRACTING ME TOO MUCH.
>> SUMMER IS OVER IN TWO WEEKS.
SINCE I STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN UP
THE COURAGE TO TELL ANYBODY
OUTSIDE MY PARENTS AND JAIRO,
I ONLY LEAVE MY HOUSE IF WE GO
TO THE OTHER SIDE OF TOWN.
>> I'M GONNA NEED TO STOP
FOR GAS RIGHT NOW,
'CAUSE I'M ON EMPTY.
>> THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD GO,
LIKE, FARTHER?
>> NO, I HAVE TO STOP RIGHT NOW,
UNLESS YOU WANT TO GET OUT
AND PUSH MY CAR.
>> BABE, I DON'T WANT
TO STOP THERE.
>> WHY?
>> BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
PEOPLE THERE.
IS THIS FOR SURE NECESSARY?
I MEAN, WE CAN'T EVEN GO, LIKE,
A COUPLE EXTRA MILES.
>> IT--I NEED IT RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, I'LL BE SURPRISED
IF IT MAKES IT DOWN TO THIS
GAS STATION.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
WHATEVER.
[sighs]
FINE.
[cell phone ringing]
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> I AM NOT 100% POSITIVE YET,
BECAUSE MY DAD, HE WORKS REALLY
LATE TONIGHT, AND I HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO ASK HIM.
>> YEAH, FOR SURE.
I MISS YOU GUYS TOO.
OH, GOSH.
LIKE, I FEEL SO DUMB, YOU KNOW?
EVERY TIME SOMEONE CALLS ME,
I HAVE TO, LIKE, MAKE UP
SOME LAME EXCUSE, AND THEY
PROBABLY THINK THAT I'M JUST,
LIKE, BEING RUDE AND BLOWING
THEM OFF, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'S BETTER TELLING THEM
NOW THAN WHEN THE BABY IS BORN.
DON'T YOU THINK?
>> I KNOW.
THAT WOULD BE KIND OF SERIOUS.
PEOPLE WOULD BE LIKE, "UH, OKAY,
THAT'S KIND OF RUDE."
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE, LIKE,
NO FRIENDS.
[sighs]
[clippers buzzing]
I'M PRETTY SURE YOU'RE MORE
PARTICULAR ABOUT YOUR HAIR
THAN I AM.
I GET MY HAIR CUT, LIKE,
EVERY SIX MONTHS.
>> I GET MINE EVERY FIVE DAYS.
>> I KNOW.
JAIRO?
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH, ARE--IS SHE PREGNANT?
>> [speaking Spanish]
>> SIX MONTHS PREGNANT.
>> SHE'S HAVING A BOY TOO.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YEAH.
[clippers buzzing]
>> I REALLY AM EXCITED ABOUT
THE BABY, BUT I'M STILL NOT
READY FOR EVERYBODY TO KNOW
ABOUT IT.
>> I AM GONNA LEAVE TO GO
ON VACATION.
I WILL TOTALLY TRY TO BE THERE.
THAT WOULD BE AWESOME.
OH, MY GOSH, YOU KNOW,
THAT SOUNDS LIKE SO MUCH FUN,
BUT I...
>> OKAY, HAVE A GOOD TRIP.
>> I'VE BEEN AT IT SO LONG;
I'M OUT OF EXCUSES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M GOING TO BE STUDYING FROM
HOME UNTIL THE BABY IS BORN,
AND WITH SCHOOL STARTING
IN TWO WEEKS, EVERYONE IS GOING
TO BE WONDERING WHERE I AM.
MY DUE DATE IS LESS THAN A MONTH
AWAY, AND I NEED TO TELL CASSIDY
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
HEY, COULD YOU PLEASE
GRAB MY MOM'S PHONE?
IT'S ON THE COUNTER, CHARGING.
AND THEN COULD YOU PLEASE
GRAB, LIKE, A JACKET FROM
MY ROOM, JUST SO I CAN CARRY IT
IN FRONT OF ME?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THANKS.
THANK YOU.
>> BYE.
>> BYE. I LOVE YOU.
>> I LOVE YOU TOO.
>> WISH HER LUCK.
>> HUH?
>> WITH ME LUCK.
>> GOOD LUCK.
>> BYE.
[mellow acoustic music]
*
[knocking at door]
>> OH, MY GOD, CAN YOU...
[groans]
>> OH, MY GOD.
[both laugh]
>> UM...
WELL, I'M PREGNANT.
[laughs]
OBVIOUSLY.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO WAIT
TO TELL ME.
OH...
>> [laughs]
DID YOU KNOW?
>> I HEARD, BUT I DIDN'T HEAR IT
FROM YOU, SO...
>> I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO TELL
ANYONE, 'CAUSE I WAS SO SCARED
OF, LIKE, WHAT THEY WOULD SAY,
AND...
LIKE, DID YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHEN WE WERE AT SCHOOL
AND STUFF?
>> MM-MM.
>> 'CAUSE IT WAS, LIKE,
SINCE JANUARY.
>> I KNOW, NONE.
>> I KEPT, LIKE, WANTING
TO TELL YOU, BUT I COULDN'T
BRING MYSELF TO DO IT, YOU KNOW?
>> SO WHEN ARE YOU DUE?
>> LIKE, SEPTEMBER 28TH.
>> IS IT A GIRL OR BOY?
>> A BOY.
>> OH...
>> I DIDN'T START SHOWING
UNTIL, LIKE, TWO WEEKS AGO.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> I WAS SO SCARED.
[sighs]
JUST 'CAUSE I DON'T WANT
PEOPLE--LIKE, ESPECIALLY
THEIR PARENTS, I DON'T WANT THEM
TO BE LIKE, "OH, YOU CAN'T HANG
OUT WITH HER," YOU KNOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> "'CAUSE THEN YOU MIGHT
GET PREGNANT."
YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
NO, I'LL SUPPORT YOU.
>> YOU'LL STILL BE FRIENDS
WITH ME?
>> YES. OF COURSE.
>> SORRY, I REALLY DON'T
WANT TO CRY.
>> NO, IT'S OKAY.
>> 'CAUSE I HATE CRYING.
>> IT'S CRAZY, THOUGH, LIKE...
[laughs]
>> MM-HMM.
[exhales]
[chime dings]
I'M RELIEVED CASSIDY ISN'T UPSET
I KEPT MY PREGNANCY A SECRET,
BUT I'M NOT SURE EVERYONE ELSE
WILL BE QUITE AS UNDERSTANDING.
>> AM I GONNA CUT THE TOMATOES,
OR ARE YOU JUST...
>> YOU HAVE TO PUT THEM
ON A PLATE, 'CAUSE OTHERWISE,
IT'S GONNA DRAIN.
>> I'M GLAD I WAS ABLE TO FACE
CASSIDY WITH THE NEWS
I'M PREGNANT.
SHE'S ALSO AGREED TO HELP ME
KEEP UP WITH MY HOMEWORK
UNTIL I GET BACK TO SCHOOL.
NOW THAT THAT'S OVER,
MY PARENTS HAVE DECIDED
IT'S TIME TO START TELLING
THE REST OF MY FAMILY,
STARTING WITH MY AUNT AND UNCLE.
>> HEY!
>> WHAT'S UP?
HI, BRENNA!
SO COME ON IN.
COME ON IN.
>> HI.
>> WE ACTUALLY--
WE'RE GONNA TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING.
>> WHAT?
YOU HIT THE LOTTERY?
>> WHO HIT THE LOTTERY?
>> IZABELLA'S PREGNANT.
>> REALLY?
>> SHE'S BEEN PREGNANT FOR
7 1/2 MONTHS.
>> 8.
>> OH, 8 MONTHS.
>> THAT IS...A BIG SURPRISE.
AND I WOULD EXPECT FOR
YOU GUYS TO TELL US SOONER.
I MEAN, WAY SOONER.
>> I'M IN SHOCK.
OH, MY GOSH.
THAT'S...
>> AT FIRST, IT WAS BECAUSE
WE REALLY DIDN'T WANT HER
TO HAVE TO DEAL WITH THE DRAMA
AT SCHOOL.
WE DIDN'T WANT THE GOSSIP.
WE DIDN'T WANT ANY OF THAT.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S ENOUGH OF
THAT ANYWAY.
>> SHE WENT SIX MONTHS
TO SCHOOL PREGNANT, RIGHT?
>> YES.
>> AND YOU HID IT?
>> MM-HMM, NO ONE KNEW.
AND THEN IT KIND OF JUST
WENT FROM THERE.
SHE'S LIKE, "WELL, I'LL TELL
PEOPLE IN THE SUMMER,
YOU KNOW, AFTER SCHOOL'S OUT."
>> AND SO IT WAS EASIER FOR ME
EVEN TO DEAL WITH IT THAT WAY,
YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE WHEN I TELL PEOPLE
ABOUT IT, LIKE, IT'S JUST...
I GUESS IT MAKES IT MORE REAL,
AND, LIKE, I DIDN'T WANT IT
TO BE REAL, YOU KNOW.
>> IT JUST SHOWS YOU THAT
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW CLOSE YOU
ARE TO YOUR DAUGHTER AND STUFF.
'CAUSE YOU GUYS ARE REALLY
CLOSE.
LOOK WHAT'S HAPPENED.
I MEAN, I JUST FEEL FOR YOU,
'CAUSE, I MEAN, YOUR LIVES
ARE GONNA CHANGE.
IT'S HARD, YOU KNOW?
ESPECIALLY FOR YOU, AS A GIRL.
YOU KNOW, FOR HIM, IT'S, LIKE,
YOU KNOW, HIGH FIVES AND STUFF,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST THE TRUTH,
IT'S THE TRUTH, YOU KNOW?
BUT FOR YOU, I MEAN, YOU'RE
THE ONE THAT'S GONNA HAVE TO,
YOU KNOW, STAY HOME AND WATCH
THE BABY AND STUFF, YOU KNOW?
I...
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M KIND OF DISAPPOINTED.
I WISH YOU GUYS WOULD HAVE
TOLD US EARLIER TOO.
>> I HATE THAT I HURT
MY UNCLE'S FEELINGS,
BUT I'M RELIEVED THAT EVERYONE
CLOSE TO ME NOW KNOWS
THAT I'M PREGNANT.
[church organ music playing]
*
NOW THAT THE WORD IS OUT,
I DON'T HAVE TO HIDE ANYMORE.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
GOING BACK TO CHURCH?
>> YOU STILL DON'T WANT TO GO
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, THEY MIGHT
JUDGE YOU, I GUESS.
>> EVEN THOUGH IT'S PROBABLY
GOOD THAT, IN MY SITUATION,
I'M STILL GOING TO CHURCH,
THEY'RE PROBABLY GONNA BE, LIKE,
"OH, MY GOD, HOW DARE SHE GO
TO CHURCH WHEN SHE'S PREGNANT?"
*
[chime dings]
WORD OF MY PREGNANCY HAS BEEN
SPREADING AROUND SCHOOL, BUT
SINCE I'M DOING MY ASSIGNMENTS
FROM HOME, I HAVEN'T SEEN ANY
OF MY OTHER FRIENDS.
SO MY MOM IS THROWING TOGETHER
A LAST-MINUTE BABY SHOWER,
SO I CAN SEE ALL OF THEM
BEFORE ENRIQUE COMES.
BUT MORE PEOPLE ARE PROBABLY
GONNA BE COMING FROM THIS WAY.
NO, YOU NEED TO...
LOOK, IF IT'S FACING THIS WAY,
THE ARROW GOES THAT WAY.
SO YOU NEED TO TAKE THESE OUT
AND PUT THEM IN THE OTHER WAY.
>> IS THAT BETTER FOR YOU, MISS?
>> YEAH.
I'M EXCITED TO FINALLY SEE
ALL MY FRIENDS, BUT IT LOOKS
LIKE ONE OF THEM WILL BE
MISSING.
SO KAYLIE JUST TEXTED ME AND
SAID NOW CASSIDY CAN'T GO.
>> WHY CAN'T CASSIDY COME?
HUH?
>> WELL, CASSIDY DIDN'T EVEN--
CASSIDY DIDN'T EVEN TELL ME
SHE WAS OR WASN'T GONNA.
>> I KNOW, BUT IT'S KIND OF
RUDE THAT SHE'S NOT COMING.
>> WELL, SHE NEVER TOLD ME
SHE WAS, SO IT DOESN'T REALLY
MATTER.
>> DO YOU CARE?
>> NO.
[acoustic music]
*
[people murmuring]
>> YOU'RE SO GORGEOUS.
>> GOSH, IT'S SO EXCITING.
>> DOES IT FEEL WEIRD
WHEN HE KICKS?
>> YEAH.
IT FEELS LIKE THERE'S, LIKE,
A FISH SWIMMING INSIDE OF ME.
[laughter]
THAT'S WHAT IT FEELS LIKE.
WOW.
THEY HAVE LITTLE BEARS ON THEM.
OH, THAT'S CUTE.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE IN MY COMPUTER CLASS.
>> REALLY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YEAH, MINE TOO.
>> WE'RE IN THE SAME COMPUTER
CLASS.
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT I'M SAYING.
[laughter]
>> YOU'RE IN MY HOME ROOM TOO.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> WOW.
>> I KNOW.
>> DO THEY, LIKE, CALL ME
FOR ROLL OR SOMETHING?
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I'VE DONE ROLL
ONCE, AND I'M LIKE, "IZABELLA.
ERR..."
I MISS YOU.
>> I TOOK A MATH COURSE,
LIKE, OVER THE SUMMER,
SO I'M IN PRECALCULUS THIS YEAR.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
I'M STILL IN GEOMETRY.
>> YEAH, ME TOO.
>> ME TOO!
>> YOU THINK PEOPLE ARE GONNA
BE MEAN WHEN YOU COME BACK
TO SCHOOL?
>> YEAH, I'M SURE PEOPLE
ARE GONNA BE RUDE TO ME,
BUT, I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT
I'M EXPECTING, SO IT DOESN'T
REALLY MATTER.
>> WHO DID YOU TELL FIRST?
>> CASSIDY.
>> IZABELLA, IS CASS COMING?
>> NO.
>> SHE'S NOT COMING?
>> MM-MM.
>> WHY?
>> UM, I GUESS SOMETHING ABOUT
HER GRANDMA.
>> SHE TOLD ME ALL OF HER
COUSINS ARE IN TOWN OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
>> PROBABLY NOT TRUE.
JUST KIDDING.
>> I'M NOT OFFENDED.
I'LL BE OKAY.
I'M BUMMED THAT CASSIDY DIDN'T
COME, BUT I'M GLAD MY DAYS OF
HIDING FROM FRIENDS ARE OVER.
BYE!
>> SO WHEN ARE YOU GONNA TELL ME
ABOUT YOUR BIG DAY TODAY?
>> EVERYONE'S, LIKE, BLUSHING,
AND IT WAS REALLY WEIRD.
THEY'RE LIKE, "SO...
HOW WAS YOUR SUMMER?"
[laughter]
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER,
LIKE, MORE RELIEVED AND STUFF,
THAT I DON'T HAVE TO KEEP, LIKE,
HIDING FROM PEOPLE.
EVEN THOUGH I FEEL BETTER,
TELLING EVERYBODY THAT
I'M PREGNANT HAS BROUGHT UP
SOME FEELINGS FROM MY PARENTS.
>> I MEAN, IT WAS REALLY,
REALLY HARD ON ME, IZABELLA.
I THOUGHT I'D FAILED.
[chuckles]
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
I DIDN'T BELIEVE THAT,
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD BE PREGNANT.
WE TEND TO THINK, "OH,
IT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN TO US."
I MEAN, I THOUGHT THAT
MANY TIMES.
I'M LIKE, "I'M DREAMING HERE.
IT CAN'T BE."
>> SO DO YOU STILL BLAME ME?
>> I DON'T KNOW...
IF YOU WANT A STRAIGHT ANSWER,
YES, I DO BLAME YOU,
BECAUSE I KEPT ON TELLING YOU,
"YOU NEED TO TALK TO HER."
'CAUSE YOU'RE THE ONE REALLY
CLOSEST TO HER.
I MEAN, I'VE TOLD YOU MANY
TIMES, YOU KNOW, "BE THE MOM,
NOT THE BUDDY, NOT THE FRIEND."
>> IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BE
SUCH A STRICT MOM,
BECAUSE I THINK IT'S BECAUSE
MY MOM WAS SO STRICT.
LIKE, SHE WAS TOO STRICT.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S ONE
OF THE REASONS WHY I'M--
I TRY TO BE FRIENDS,
OR I TRY TO BE A BUDDY WITH THEM
BECAUSE I WISH I HAD THAT
WITH MY OWN MOM.
SO, YEAH, THAT'S ONE
OF MY FAULTS.
I'M TOO SOFT WITH HER.
>> I LIKE THE WAY YOU ARE,
THOUGH.
'CAUSE, LIKE, LOOK AT ALL
THE OTHER MOMS.
THAT'S WHY THEIR...
THEIR DAUGHTERS, LIKE,
HATE THEM.
>> YEAH, BUT THEIR DAUGHTERS
AREN'T PREGNANT.
>> THANKS.
>> WHAT?
I'M SAYING...
>> I WAS SCARED TO LOSE MY
FRIENDS BECAUSE I GOT PREGNANT,
BUT UNTIL NOW, I DIDN'T KNOW
HOW MUCH TROUBLE I'D CAUSED
BETWEEN MY MOM AND DAD.
>> CASSIDY IS SUPPOSED TO BE
KEEPING ME UP ON ASSIGNMENTS,
BUT SHE HASN'T RETURNED ANY OF
MY TEXTS SINCE SHE MISSED
MY BABY SHOWER.
IT SUCKS SHE'S NOT BEEN AS
SUPPORTIVE AS I THOUGHT
SHE'D BE, ESPECIALLY BECAUSE
MY DUE DATE IS TWO WEEKS AWAY.
>> IZABELLA?
[cuff hissing]
IT'S HIGH.
>> IT'S HIGH?
>> A LITTLE BIT HIGH.
HE'LL TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
HE SHOULD BE RIGHT IN.
[tape measure clicking]
>> SO YOU'RE CURRENTLY MEASURING
37 1/2 CENTIMETERS, SO RIGHT
ABOUT ON PERFECT FOR GROWTH,
SO...
BLOOD PRESSURE IS UP A LITTLE
BIT, SO I'M THINKING THAT
AT 38 WEEKS AND WITH THE BLOOD
PRESSURE PROBLEM, NO GOOD
IS GONNA COME OUT OF KEEPING YOU
PREGNANT FOR, LIKE, ANOTHER
WEEK, AND SO I THINK SOMETIME
THIS WEEK, WE'RE GONNA PROBABLY
END UP INDUCING YOU.
HOW DOES FRIDAY SOUND TO YOU?
>> WOW.
>> SO DOES SEPTEMBER 17TH
SOUND LIKE AN OKAY BIRTHDAY
FOR THIS KIDDO?
>> YEP.
NOW THAT WE KNOW I'M DELIVERING
AT THE END OF THE WEEK, JAIRO
AND I NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
AFTER THE BABY IS BORN.
WHEN I GO BACK TO HIGH SCHOOL,
MY MOM IS GOING TO TAKE ENRIQUE
INTO HER DAY CARE, SO WE'RE
ALL SET DURING THE DAY,
BUT I'M GOING TO NEED SOME
HELP AT NIGHT.
>> HI.
I'M GETTING BIGGER, HUH?
>> UH-HUH.
>> HOW DO YOU FEEL?
TIRED?
>> YEAH, I'M REALLY TIRED.
>> YEAH?
>> JAIRO IS PICKING UP
SOME CLOTHES BECAUSE MY PARENTS
SAID HE COULD MOVE INTO OUR
HOUSE WHEN THE BABY IS BORN.
EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE SAD
TO SEE HIM GO, JAIRO'S PARENTS
ARE OKAY WITH HIM MOVING IN
WITH ME.
MY PARENTS, HOWEVER, WILL ONLY
LET HIM DO IT UNDER TWO
CONDITIONS:
HE ENROLLS IN COLLEGE,
AND WE DON'T SLEEP
IN THE SAME BED.
SINCE I REALLY WANT HIM TO STAY,
I'M GOING TO HELP JAIRO KEEP
HIS END OF THE DEAL.
SO WHAT ARE YOUR PLANS
FOR COLLEGE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I'M PLANNING ON GOING INTO
"SLICK."
>> SALT LAKE COMMUNITY COLLEGE?
>> TRY TO GET A CAREER.
AND THEN...
>> LIKE, WHAT KIND OF CAREER?
>> I STILL DON'T KNOW.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN?
>> NO.
>> AT ALL?
>> THERE'S SO MUCH THINGS TO DO.
>> LIKE, WHAT ABOUT CARS?
YOU LOVE CARS.
>> BEING A MECHANIC
IS A DIRTY JOB.
>> [laughs]
WELL, IF YOU ENJOY IT,
I DON'T THINK IT MATTERS.
LIKE, WHAT ELSE WOULD YOU THINK
THAT YOU'D WANT?
>> I SERIOUSLY DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S SO MANY THINGS.
>> I WISH JAIRO WOULD PUT
MORE THOUGHT INTO THIS,
BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO BE HARD
TO STAY ON TOP OF HIS SCHOOL
AND MINE.
[line ringing]
CASSIDY IS SUPPOSED TO BE
FORWARDING ME MY HOMEWORK
UNTIL I GO BACK TO SCHOOL,
BUT SHE'S BEEN BLOWING ME OFF,
AND WHEN I AM ABLE TO GET HER
ON THE PHONE, SHE'S SUPER
DISTANT.
YOU DON'T HAVE A SHORT DAY
TOMORROW, DO YOU?
>> NO.
>> WELL, I WAS WONDERING IF
MAYBE YOU WANT TO HANG OUT
SOMETIME.
>> SURE, WHATEVER.
>> HUH?
>> I SAID, YEAH.
>> LIKE, TOMORROW?
>> YEAH, SURE.
>> OKAY.
>> WHATEVER.
ANYWAYS, THOUGH, I TEXTED YOU,
AND I TOLD YOU TO HAVE A GOOD
DAY, AND YOU NEVER EVEN
ANSWERED.
>> DUDE, I KNOW, I'M SORRY.
I, LIKE, I NEVER--
>> YOU NEVER WHAT?
HELLO?
[chime dings]
IT BUMS ME OUT THAT CASSIDY
IS ABANDONING ME WHEN I NEED HER
THE MOST, BUT IT MAKES ME
GRATEFUL THAT MY MOM IS THERE
FOR ME.
>> OH, LET'S NOT WORRY ABOUT IT
UNTIL WE HAVE A REASON TO WORRY
ABOUT IT.
>> WE DO HAVE A REASON TO WORRY
>> I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET STRESSED OUT.
IT'S NOT GOOD.
>> I MEAN, I'VE KNOWN HER
SINCE, LIKE, I WAS SIX, SO...
THAT'S REALLY WEIRD, 'CAUSE
I TOTALLY TRUSTED HER, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE THOUGHT THAT,
IF ANYONE, SHE'D BE THE PERSON
THAT WOULDN'T TELL OR WOULD
BE THERE TO SUPPORT ME
AND EVERYTHING.
AND NOW SHE DOESN'T TALK TO ME,
AND SHE DOESN'T--I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S LIKE SHE DOESN'T CARE.
>> OBVIOUSLY, YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT
GONNA BE HOW IT WAS BEFORE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE
ON THE DRILL TEAM.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE, YOU KNOW,
HANGING OUT WITH YOUR FRIENDS
AS MUCH, AND A LOT
IS GONNA CHANGE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE, 'CAUSE IT IS
PART OF YOUR LIFE NOW.
I MEAN, IT'S SOMETHING THAT
YOU HAVE TO EMBRACE, AND YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE A LITTLE BABY.
HOPEFULLY, SHE CAN BE THERE
FOR YOU.
BUT IF NOT, THEN, YOU KNOW,
AT LEAST YOU HAVE YOUR FAMILY,
AND YOU HAVE JAIRO.
>> I'M NERVOUS ABOUT GETTING
INDUCED TOMORROW, BUT BEING
PREGNANT HAS TAKEN A TOLL
ON MY BODY.
ARE MY LEGS SWELLING UP?
>> YEAH, THIS ONE,
IT'S SWOLLEN UP.
>> GOSH.
I'M SO DONE BEING PREGNANT.
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> IT'S NOT SOON ENOUGH FOR ME.
>> [laughs]
>> I'M SERIOUS.
YOU'RE LUCKY; YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GO THROUGH ANYTHING.
IT'S NOT FAIR AT ALL.
YOU JUST GET TO HAVE A LITTLE
BABY IN THE END.
OH...
>> LABOR AND DELIVERY.
THIS IS AMY.
HOW CAN I HELP YOU?
>> YEAH, HI, AMY.
MY DAUGHTER IS ACTUALLY
SCHEDULED FOR AN INDUCTION
THIS MORNING, SO THEY TOLD US
TO CALL AT 6:00.
>> OKAY, WE HAVE HER SCHEDULED
TO COME IN AT 7:00.
>> PERFECT.
[tapping]
[hair dryer whirring]
>> HI.
>> HI, WE'RE HERE FOR
AN INDUCTION APPOINTMENT.
>> ALL RIGHT, COME ON DOWN
THIS WAY.
WE'LL GET YOU READY.
>> SEPTEMBER 17TH.
HOPEFULLY HE'S BORN TODAY.
LET'S ENJOY HER SMILEY FACE
RIGHT NOW.
>> MM-HMM.
[laughter]
>> THAT'S IT.
PITOCIN'S STARTED.
THAT EASY.
>> IT'S STARTING TO HURT.
>> JUST BREATHE.
>> ARE YOU GONNA WANT ME
RIGHT NEXT TO YOU SOMEWHERE?
>> FOR WHAT?
>> WHEN...
>> YOU'RE GONNA HOLD A LEG.
>> HE DOESN'T WANT TO.
>> [gasps]
YOU AT LEAST WANT TO BE UP HERE
BY HER HEAD, OKAY?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU AT LEAST WANT TO SEE
THE BABY.
>> IF I'M UP THERE BY HER HEAD,
DO I SEE ANYTHING?
>> YOU HAVE FREE WILL
OVER YOUR EYES.
>> YES.
[laughter]
>> I COULD JUST CLOSE MY EYES
THE WHOLE TIME.
>> YOU CAN CLOSE YOUR EYES.
>> YOU CAN, LIKE, HOLD MY HAND
OR SOMETHING.
A FEW HOURS AFTER THEY STARTED
ME ON PITOCIN, MY CONTRACTIONS
STARTED GETTING REALLY PAINFUL.
>> JUST TAKE SOME BIG, SLOW,
DEEP BREATHS.
THERE YOU GO, PERFECT.
>> OKAY, YOU STILL ARE 2,
MAYBE 2 1/2.
USUALLY GETTING UP TO
4 CENTIMETERS TAKES THE LONGEST
TIME, AND THEN YOU TEND TO GO
A LITTLE BIT FASTER AFTER THAT,
SO WE'LL SEE YOU A LITTLE BIT
LATER, SO--WHEN THINGS KIND OF
GET GOING MORE.
>> OKAY.
>> THANKS, DOCTOR.
>> OKAY, SO THEY MIGHT START
GETTING MORE UNCOMFORTABLE.
>> [sobs]
>> YOU'RE ALMOST THERE.
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> IT'S NOT OKAY.
[groans]
>> WE'RE ALMOST AT THE END.
>> WHATEVER WORKS ON OUR--
ON OUR SCALE.
>> ALL RIGHT, TELL ME WHAT
YOUR PAIN IS.
SO ZERO IS NO PAIN.
TEN IS, YOU GOT HIT BY A CAR
AND LEFT ON THE SIDE OF
THE ROAD.
>> LIKE, AN EIGHT.
>> AN EIGHT.
OKAY, THAT'S A GOOD TIME
TO GET AN EPIDURAL, OKAY?
[oxygen hissing]
>> JUST A TOUCH...
YEP, THERE'S NO CERVIX AT ALL
ANYMORE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
>> 14 HOURS AFTER I STARTED
LABOR, I WAS FINALLY READY
TO PUSH.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S HAVE A BABY.
PUSH.
HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD.
>> SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE.
>> [exhales]
>> GOOD WORK.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD.
NINE, TEN.
>> [exhales]
IS IT GETTING ANY CLOSER?
>> YEAH, IT'S CLOSER,
BUT YOU'RE STILL GONNA BE
PUSHING FOR A WHILE, OKAY?
SO I KNOW YOU WANT IT TO BE,
LIKE, THERE RIGHT NOW,
BUT IT'S NOT THERE RIGHT NOW,
OKAY?
>> REAL HARD.
KEEP IT GOING.
EIGHT, NINE.
FABULOUS.
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE.
>> [exhales]
>> YOU GUYS ARE ABOUT TO BE
PARENTS, LIKE, REALLY SOON.
AND YOU'RE ABOUT TO--
>> IT'S FOREVER DIFFERENT.
>> YOU'RE ABOUT TO NOT BE
PREGNANT TOO, WHICH IS, I GUESS,
KIND OF ANOTHER ADDED BONUS
FEATURE, SO...
>> THERE YOU GO.
SEVEN, EIGHT, NINE, TEN.
>> GOT TO DO ONE MORE.
>> AND AGAIN.
AND PUSH.
HARD, HARD, HARD, HARD.
KEEP IT GOING, JUST LIKE THAT.
NICE.
>> LOOK UP.
>> RIGHT HERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> * BUT YOU'RE MINE
* YEAH, YOU'RE MINE
* ALL THE TIME
* YOU KNOW
* I BELIEVE
* I'M BETTER BY YOUR SIDE
[chime dings]
>> SO I'M GONNA BE TAKING YOU
INTO THE NURSERY.
WE'RE GONNA GIVE THE BABY
HIS FIRST BATH.
[Enrique crying]
GONNA SQUIRT SOME SOAP ON HIM.
OKAY, SO, DAD, JUST GET IN THERE
AND JUST START SCRUBBING, OKAY?
GET UNDER THAT NECK REALLY GOOD.
>> I WAS KIND OF HOPING TO SEE
SOME OF MY FRIENDS HERE,
BUT IT'S ENOUGH FOR ME
THAT OUR FAMILIES ARE HERE
TO SUPPORT US.
>> YOU CAN GIVE HIM THE LITTLE
MANLY COMB-OVER.
THERE.
THAT LOOKS GOOD.
>> HI.
>> OH...
>> YOU WANT TO HOLD HIM?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, YEAH, PUT SOME
ANTIBACTERIAL STUFF ON.
IT'S OVER BY JAIRO.
>> YOU PREPARED TO TAKE CARE
OF A KID?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU SURE?
>> MM-HMM.
>> IT'S CRAZY.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO SCHOOL?
WHEN?
>> WHEN?
IT ALREADY STARTED, DUDE.
SCHOOL STARTED, LIKE,
TWO WEEKS AGO.
>> YOU'RE ALREADY STARTED?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT ARE YOU STUDYING FOR?
>> POLITICAL SCIENCE.
>> HOW LONG ARE YOU GONNA
BE THERE FOR?
>> WELL, MAYBE FOUR YEARS.
AND THEN AFTERWARDS,
PROBABLY GO TO LAW SCHOOL.
YOU GONNA FINISH UP HIGH SCHOOL?
>> I ALREADY FINISHED.
I FINISHED OVER THE SUMMER.
E.H.S.
>> E.H.S.?
>> YEAH, ELECTRONICAL
HIGH SCHOOL.
>> YOU APPLY TO GO TO COLLEGE
OR...
WHERE ARE YOU APPLYING TO GO TO?
>> I DON'T KNOW YET.
>> DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
TO STUDY?
>> MM-MM.
I DON'T KNOW YET.
I NEED TO--I HAVEN'T THOUGHT
ABOUT IT.
>> BETTER DO WELL
TO RAISE THAT KID.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU GOT TO DREAM HIGH.
YOU DON'T WANT HIM TO TURN OUT
TO BE, LIKE, ANOTHER LITTLE
GANGSTER, DUDE.
BETTER NOT RAISE HIM THAT WAY
EITHER.
>> NOW THAT OUR BABY IS HERE,
IT'S REALLY TIME JAIRO FIGURES
THIS OUT, BECAUSE NO COLLEGE
MEANS NO LIVING IN MY HOUSE.
>> AFTER TWO DAYS IN THE
HOSPITAL, IT'S TIME TO GO HOME.
>> AH, HEARD THE CLICK.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR EVERYTHING.
[door creaks open]
>> SO HE'S NOT EATING?
>> NO, HE WAS FOR A SECOND.
NOW HE'S FALLING ASLEEP.
MAMA?
MAMA!
>> [sighs]
YEAH?
>> ARE YOU DEAF?
>> WHAT'S WRONG?
>> I NEED YOUR HELP.
HE WON'T EAT.
AND I'M EXHAUSTED,
AND I CAN'T...
[Enrique belches and cries]
THAT'S WHY I NEED YOU.
>> [shushes]
I'M GONNA GO GET THE OTHER ONE,
SO YOU CAN HOLD HIM.
[crying continues]
[Enrique cooing]
IS HE NURSING NOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> GOOD.
THAT'S ALL IT TAKES.
[Enrique crying]
>> MY MOM'S A BIG HELP,
BUT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
IT'S UP TO ME AND JAIRO,
AND IT'S PRETTY EXHAUSTING.
I'M TRYING TO STAY ON TOP
OF MY SCHOOLWORK.
>> 'CAUSE THERE'S THREE
SECTIONS.
>> OKAY.
>> JAIRO HAS BEEN PREPARING
TO GO TO COMMUNITY COLLEGE,
AND MY MOM HAS BEEN WATCHING
ENRIQUE.
>> ARE YOU STRONG?
>> IT'LL BE HARD TO LEAVE
ENRIQUE, BUT I THINK JAIRO AND I
ARE READY TO GO BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
SO YOU ARE GOING BACK TO SCHOOL?
>> YEAH, TOMORROW.
>> SO ARE YOU EXCITED ABOUT IT
OR...OR NOT?
>> I'M NERVOUS.
I'M REALLY NERVOUS.
IT'S LIKE THE FIRST DAY OF
SCHOOL, SO IT'S NERVE-RACKING.
>> AND SO WHO'S GONNA WATCH HIM?
YOUR MOM?
>> MM-HMM.
>> ARE YOU STAYING HERE?
>> ARE YOU GOING BACK TO SCHOOL
OR ANYTHING?
>> COLLEGE OR SOMETHING.
>> YEAH, I MEAN...
>> MM, YEAH, THAT'S WHY
I HAVE A MEETING TOMORROW.
>> DID YOU--I THOUGHT YOU
DIDN'T GRADUATE.
>> YEAH, ONLINE.
>> OH, YOU DID?
YOU DID THAT?
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
MOST IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW,
THERE'S A BABY.
HE SHOULD BE WORKING, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, NOW YOU HAVE
RESPONSIBILITIES, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I LOVE THAT HE'S
INVOLVED IN THIS, YOU KNOW?
BUT THESE TWO ARE MAKING IT
TOO EASY FOR YOU GUYS.
>> WE PREFER HELPING THEM OUT
FOR FOUR YEARS, SO THEY CAN GET
A GOOD BACHELOR'S DEGREE
AT LEAST IN SOMETHING,
SO HE CAN GO OUT THERE AND
NOT JUST WORK FOR MCDONALD'S.
>> I...
YOU KNOW, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA,
BUT THIS IS LIFE.
YOU KNOW, LIFE IS--
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU HAVE TO STEP UP,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU HAVE
TO BE A MAN AND GET A JOB, AND--
EVEN IF IT'S A PART-TIME JOB
AFTER SCHOOL.
>> GETTING A JOB, ESPECIALLY
RIGHT NOW, IT'S NOT EASY,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE UNDER 18.
>> WHEN I WAS IN COLLEGE,
YOU WOULD--YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER
YOU GOING VROOM-VROOM-VROOM
IN THE CAR.
>> YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
>> JUST HAVING FUN,
BACK AND FORTH.
>> YEAH, 'CAUSE I WAS
A TEENAGER.
I WAS DOING THE TEENAGER THINGS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DIDN'T HAVE A CHILD
WHEN I WAS 17 YEARS OLD.
I DIDN'T.
>> SO WE'RE BAD FOR TRYING
TO HELP THEM?
>> LET THEM GROW UP.
YOU GUYS NEED TO GROW UP NOW,
'CAUSE NOW YOU HAVE A BABY.
THAT'S ALL.
>> EVEN THOUGH IT'S NOT NORMAL,
I DON'T THINK THAT THAT MEANS
THAT WE CAN'T STILL GO ON WITH
WHAT OUR PLANS WERE BEFORE
WE HAD THE BABY.
BECAUSE WE HAVE THE SUPPORT
FROM MY PARENTS, WE SHOULDN'T
JUST BE THINKING ABOUT, LIKE,
SHORT-TERM THINGS.
SO I THINK IT'S AWESOME
THE WAY THAT MY PARENTS
ARE HELPING US, BECAUSE IT'S
GONNA LET US STILL HAVE GOOD
LIVES IN THE END AND NOT BE
RUINED JUST BECAUSE WE HAD
A CHILD SO YOUNG.
WE'RE REALLY LUCKY MY PARENTS
HAVE DECIDED TO SUPPORT US.
I JUST HOPE JAIRO AND I DON'T
LET THEM DOWN.
[Enrique crying]
>> TODAY IS MY FIRST DAY
BACK TO SCHOOL.
I'M HAPPY MY MOM CAN WATCH
ENRIQUE, BUT I'M SAD
TO LEAVE HIM.
JAIRO IS ENROLLING AT COMMUNITY
COLLEGE TODAY, AND I KNOW
HE'S GOING TO MISS THE BABY TOO.
I LOVE YOU, OKAY?
MWAH.
MOM, YOU HAVE TO TAKE HIM.
THAT'S MY SON.
BYE.
IT'S GOING TO BE WEIRD BEING
AROUND ALL MY FRIENDS AGAIN,
ESPECIALLY CASSIDY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
BYE.
>> YEP.
SO I TEXTED HER TO SEE IF SHE
WANTED TO MEET UP BEFORE CLASS
TO CLEAR THE AIR.
>> I GUESS IT KIND OF HURT
MY FEELINGS THAT YOU DIDN'T
TELL ME, BUT, LIKE...
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S, LIKE, A BIG THING
TO SAY, AND...
>> IT'S A HARD THING.
>> YEAH.
I JUST WISH YOU WOULD HAVE
TOLD ME, SO I COULD HAVE,
LIKE, BEEN THERE FOR YOU,
LIKE, THE WHOLE TIME.
>> IT WAS A VERY HARD DECISION.
DO YOU THINK THAT WE'LL EVER BE
AS CLOSE AS WE USED TO BE?
YOU USED TO HAVE, LIKE,
OUTFITS AT MY HOUSE
AND, LIKE, A TOOTHBRUSH
AND PAJAMAS AND...
>> I...LIKE, I WANT TO HANG OUT
WITH YOU MORE.
I MISS YOU, LIKE, BEING AROUND.
>> I KNOW.
I MISS YOU TOO.
>> SO WE SHOULD CHANGE THAT.
>> OKAY.
SO YOU'RE GONNA START COMING
TO THINGS NOW IF I ASK YOU?
>> YES.
[laughter]
>> I'M HAPPY CASSIDY AND I ARE
GOING TO TRY AND WORK THINGS OUT
BECAUSE I REALLY WANT HER
BACK IN MY LIFE.
[school bell rings]
MY FIRST DAY BACK TO SCHOOL
IS FINALLY OVER, AND I'M
LOOKING FORWARD TO GETTING HOME
TO SEE ENRIQUE.
HI.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
WHY CAN'T YOU TALK TO ME?
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE TALKING
RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
>> MY DAY MIGHT HAVE GONE OKAY,
BUT IT'S OBVIOUS THAT JAIRO'S
DAY DID NOT GO VERY WELL.
WHY ARE YOU UPSET?
>> I'M NOT.
>> YES, YOU ARE.
SO, UM, ABOUT YOUR WHOLE
SCHOOL THING, WHEN ARE YOU
GONNA START?
>> HOPEFULLY SOON.
>> LIKE, WHEN?
>> I DON'T KNOW, TWO WEEKS.
>> I'M JUST SAYING, JAIRO,
YOU NEED TO START...
I DON'T KNOW.
>> BEING MORE RESPONSIBLE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
>> YEAH.
>> MM-KAY.
>> AND PUTTING AN EFFORT
INTO YOUR SCHOOL MORE.
>> MM-KAY, THEN.
>> DO YOU NOT AGREE WITH
WHAT I'M SAYING OR--
>> NO, I DO AGREE WITH YOU.
>> THEN WHY ARE YOU ACTING
LIKE THIS?
>> ACTING LIKE WHAT?
>> RUDE.
ISN'T THAT WONDERFUL?
[engine revs]
SOMETHING REALLY MUST NOT HAVE
GONE RIGHT AT THE COMMUNITY
COLLEGE, BECAUSE I'VE NEVER SEEN
JAIRO STORM OFF LIKE THAT.
>> [clears throat]
>> SO WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I WAS JUST TALKING TO JAIRO
ABOUT WHAT HE NEEDS TO DO,
AND HE JUST GOT UPSET, I GUESS.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE GETS
EMBARRASSED OR...
I REALLY COULDN'T TELL YOU.
[Enrique cooing]
HE CAN'T SEE ME.
[laughter]
HEY, BIG BOY.
I LOVE YOU.
>> IT'S HARD, MAYBE,
AND IT'S FRUSTRATING.
AND IF HE DOESN'T WANT TO
HEAR IT, YOU KNOW,
THAT'S--THAT'S A PROBLEM.
>> WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
CALL HIM OR...
>> AND TELL HIM I WANT TO SIT
DOWN AND TALK TO HIM ABOUT
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> AFTER SPENDING MOST OF
THE DAY AWAY FROM THE HOUSE,
JAIRO FINALLY CAME BACK.
>> SO YOU CAME BACK, THANKS.
BUT WHY DID YOU COME BACK?
>> 'CAUSE I WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT...
>> I WAS CONFUSED, BECAUSE
I THOUGHT I HAD ALL MY CREDITS
ALREADY, BUT THE COUNSELOR FROM
THE INTERNET HIGH SCHOOL TOLD ME
THAT I'M MISSING A COUPLE.
>> WHAT?
>> BUT YOU TOLD US YOU ALREADY
GRADUATED ONLINE.
>> I HAVE BEEN LYING
TO YOU GUYS.
I HAVE BEEN TELLING YOU THAT
I AM DOING MY HIGH SCHOOL
ONLINE WHEN I REALLY HAVEN'T
BEEN DOING IT.
AND I DO FEEL GUILTY THAT
I'VE BEEN LYING TO YOU.
>> YOU DECEIVED US.
YOU KNOW, TRUST IS A LOT.
IT MEANS A LOT.
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST
BE SITTING HERE.
YOU NEED TO BE RESPONSIBLE.
IF YOU DON'T SHOW US THAT
YOU'RE REALLY PUSHING YOURSELF,
THAT YOU'RE REALLY TRYING,
I DON'T KNOW THAT I WANT YOU
TO BE WITH MY DAUGHTER.
>> COME ON.
LET'S GET YOU IN THE BATH.
LET'S HURRY.
I'M REALLY HURT THAT JAIRO LIED
TO US ABOUT GRADUATING,
AND MY DAD IS NOT TOO HAPPY
ABOUT IT EITHER.
>> I MEAN, THE LAST THING YOU
WANT, IN MY OPINION, IS TO BE
HELD BACK, AND HE'S GOING
THAT WAY WITH YOU.
IF HE DOES NOT CHANGE HIS WAYS,
HE WILL HOLD YOU BACK.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
I KNOW.
I'VE TOLD HIM THAT BEFORE.
>> HE'S NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
I'M SORRY.
IF ANYTHING, HE SHOULD BE
YOUR SUPPORT, YOUR BACKBONE.
>> I LOVE HIM, AND I WANT HIM
TO BE AROUND, BUT I THINK
WE'VE GIVEN HIM ENOUGH
OPPORTUNITIES ALREADY.
IF HE DECIDES TO LEAVE BECAUSE
HE CAN'T GRADUATE--HE CAN'T GET
A JOB, HE DOESN'T LIKE BEING
PUSHED--THAT'S LIFE.
EITHER HE CAN DO IT,
OR HE CAN'T.
AND IF HE DECIDES THAT HE CAN'T,
WE NEED TO KNOW SOONER
RATHER THAN LATER.
SERIOUS BREAKFAST.
I REALLY WANT THINGS TO WORK OUT
WITH JAIRO, BUT IF HE DOESN'T
GET HIS ACT TOGETHER, I'M NOT
SURE MY DAD IS GOING TO STAND
FOR IT.
>> I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
MY DAUGHTER, AS YOU KNOW,
IS TAKEN CARE OF.
I MEAN, MY PRIORITY IS IZABELLA
AND ENRIQUE.
I KNOW HOW MUCH YOU LIKE
BEING HERE, RIGHT?
I THINK.
YOU KNOW, GIVE US A TIMELINE.
SO BY WHEN...
>> BY MAY, YEAH, FOR SURE,
GRADUATING.
>> BY MAY, TO GRADUATE?
>> IF NOT, I'LL COMMUNICATE
WITH YOU GUYS AND TELL YOU
WHAT'S GOING ON.
>> OKAY.
AND IF YOU DON'T, THEN YOU GO
LIVE WITH YOUR--BACK TO YOUR
HOUSE, UNTIL YOU GET A JOB.
IS THAT FAIR, OR IS THAT
NOT FAIR?
>> SO IF I DON'T DO WHAT YOU
GUYS ARE EXPECTING ME TO DO,
UM, YOU THINK YOU CAN HANDLE
ENRIQUE ON YOUR OWN?
>> WELL, NO, I'M NOT SAYING THAT
YOU'RE NOT GONNA HELP ME,
'CAUSE THAT WOULDN'T BE FAIR.
JUST--YOU CAN'T BE WITH US
ALL THE TIME AND LIVE HERE
AND STUFF.
>> [coos]
>> IF JAIRO WASN'T WITH ME,
I WOULD OBVIOUSLY BE SAD.
WE'VE GONE THROUGH SO MUCH
TOGETHER, AND I REALLY LOVE HIM
AND CARE ABOUT HIM.
I HOPE THAT THIS CHANGES THINGS
AND OPENS HIS EYES TO SEE
THAT THIS IS SERIOUS.
HAVING A BABY WHILE I'M STILL
IN HIGH SCHOOL IS EXTREMELY
HARD, AND I WISH THAT I COULD BE
HOME WITH HIM, BUT I KNOW THAT
HE'LL BE PROUD OF ME
WHEN HE GROWS UP.
HE'LL BE PROUD THAT I WENT BACK
TO SCHOOL.
I WOULD SAY MY PRIORITIES
HAVE CHANGED A LOT.
MY NUMBER ONE PRIORITY NOW
IS MY FAMILY, AND IT DIDN'T
USED TO BE THAT WAY.
I WOULD SAY MY FIRST PRIORITY
USED TO BE MY FRIENDS, PROBABLY,
BEING POPULAR AND HANGING OUT
WITH ALL THE RIGHT PEOPLE.
>> IN THE NAME OF THE FATHER...
>> [crying]
>> AND OF THE SON.
>> NOT EVERYONE IS WHAT
THEY SEEM.
WHEN I GOT PREGNANT,
A LOT OF THE FRIENDS
THAT I WAS CLOSEST TO,
THEY WEREN'T THERE FOR ME
ANYMORE.
I WOULDN'T HAVE THOUGHT THAT
THEY COULD JUST ABANDON ME
LIKE THAT.
IF MY FAMILY WASN'T SO
SUPPORTIVE, I DEFINITELY
COULDN'T BE SO STRONG MYSELF.
WHEN I TOLD MY PARENTS I WAS
PREGNANT, THEY WERE THERE
FOR ME.
IF MY MOM WASN'T HERE
TO TAKE CARE OF ENRIQUE,
I PROBABLY WOULDN'T GO BACK
TO SCHOOL.
MY FAMILY MEANS A LOT MORE
TO ME NOW, BECAUSE THEY WERE
THE MAIN PEOPLE THERE FOR ME
WHILE I WAS PREGNANT.
YOU KNOW, FRIENDS COME AND GO,
BUT FAMILY IS FOREVER.
Captioning by CaptionMax
www.captionmax.com
[cheers and applause]
>> ONE NIGHT OF FUN
CAN RUIN EVERYTHING.
>> IT'S NOT GONNA BE EASY
BEING A KID WITH A KID.
IT'S A STRUGGLE.
>> WHEN I THINK ABOUT IT,
I'M LIKE, "I'M NOT GONNA BE
ABLE TO TAKE CARE OF HIM.
I'M NOT GONNA GRADUATE.
I'M NOT GONNA BE A VET."
>> SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT ADOPTION?
>> YOU'RE JUST LOOKING
FOR EXCUSES TO GIVE HIM UP.
>> I'M NOT GONNA LET HAVING
A BABY RUIN MY DREAMS.
>> I'D GIVE UP ANYTHING.
I JUST WANT TO RAISE MY SON.