Idol can make dreams come
Idol can make dreams come true in a lot of ways.
People come from tiny little
True in a lot of ways. People come from tiny little towns.
People come from tiny little towns. They don't have the
Towns. They don't have the opportunities.
They don't have the opportunities. When we can give 'em that
Opportunities. When we can
give 'em that opportunity and take that raw
When we can give 'em that
opportunity and take that raw talent to the next level,
Opportunity and take that raw
talent to the next level, that's what I love.
When the door closes, there's
When the door closes, there's no going back.
Brecken and bailey, I love
Brecken and bailey, I love you.
Behind you, the life you've
Behind you, the life you've always known.
?They say los angeles
?They say los angeles ?Is a desolate land
In front of you, the life
In front of you, the life you've always wanted.
The winner of american idol
You've always wanted. The winner of american idol is...
The winner of american idol is... and when it's your turn...
Is... and when it's your turn... okay.
AND WHEN IT'S YOUR TURN... OKAY. All: TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
OKAY. All: TAKE A DEEP BREATH. WILL YOU BE READY?
Take a deep breath. Will you be ready? All right, let's get after
Will you be ready? All right, let's get after it.
All right, let's get after it. We're ready.
It. We're ready. Give it to us.
We're ready. Give it to us.
Give it to us. ?
What else could bring us to the mountains of northern utah...
The mountains of northern utah... heading out to salt lake to
Utah... heading out to salt lake to try out for american idol.
Heading out to salt lake to try
out for american idol. Than the chance of finding an
Try out for american idol.
Than the chance of finding an american superstar?
Than the chance of finding an
american superstar? When american idol came to
American superstar? When american
idol came to salt lake, I had to jump at the
When american idol came to salt lake,
I had to jump at the opportunity.
Salt lake, I had to jump at the opportunity.
Opportunity. ?
I quit my job, and I sold my
I quit my job, and I sold my truck to get here.
But to make it to hollywood,
They'll have to sell their
Talent to our judges--keith
Urban, harry connick, jr., and
Jennifer lopez.
No other show has really produced the stars like idol has.
Produced the stars like idol has. We really take the time to go
Has. We really take the time to go through so many people.
We really take the time to go through so many people.
It's not a show that's cast like
Through so many people. It's not
a show that's cast like some of the other shows.
It's not a show that's cast like
some of the other shows. I feel like this is the day
Some of the other shows. I feel
like this is the day that holds my destiny in hand.
I feel like this is the day that
holds my destiny in hand. Now that it's here and real
That holds my destiny in hand.
Now that it's here and real and close--
Now that it's here and
real and close-- the light comes on, head in.
And close-- the light comes on, head in. Good luck, bro.
The light comes on, head in.
Good luck, bro. I have no clue how it's gonna
Good luck, bro. I have no
clue how it's gonna go down in there today.
I have no clue how it's gonna
go down in there today. Just breathe. Breathe.
Go down in there today. Just breathe. Breathe. Oh, man.
Just breathe. Breathe. Oh, man. I hope I'm ready.
Oh, man. I hope I'm ready. As ready as I'm ever gonna be.
I hope I'm ready. As ready as I'm ever gonna be.
As ready as I'm ever gonna be. ?
? Hello.
? Hello. How are you?
Hello. How are you? Good.
How are you? Good. Excellent.
Good. Excellent. Good.
Excellent. Good. Tell us about yourself.
Good. Tell us about yourself. Well, my name's austin wolfe,
Tell us about yourself. Well, my name's austin wolfe,
I am 16, and I'm from park city,
Well, my name's austin wolfe, I am 16,
and I'm from park city, which is 30 minutes from here.
I am 16, and I'm from park city,
which is 30 minutes from here. Your name's austin wolfe?
Which is 30 minutes from here. Your name's austin wolfe? Yeah.
Your name's austin wolfe? Yeah. God, that's a great name,
Yeah. God, that's a great name, isn't it?
God, that's a great name, isn't it? Thank you.
Isn't it? Thank you. Why don't I have a name like
Thank you. Why don't I have a name like that?
Why don't I have a name like that? That's just a show biz name.
That? That's just a show biz name. You have an awesome name.
That's just a show biz name.
You have an awesome name. Ah, my name?
You have an awesome name. Ah, my name? No, I don't.
Ah, my name? No, I don't. You can be austin wolfe, jr.
No, I don't. You can be austin wolfe, jr. Yeah.
You can be austin wolfe, jr. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Exactly.
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. What are you gonna sing?
Exactly. What are you gonna sing? I'm gonna sing radioactive by
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing radioactive by imagine dragons.
I'm gonna sing radioactive all right, crush it.
All right, crush it. Crush it for us.
?I'm waking up to ash
?And dust
?I wipe my brow
?And I sweat my rust
?I'm breathing in ?The chemicals
?I'm breathing in ?The chemicals ?Mm-mm, ah, ah
?I'm breaking in
?I'm breaking in ?Shaping up
?I'm breaking in ?Shaping up ?And checking out
?Shaping up ?And checking out ?On the prison bus
?And checking out ?On the prison bus ?This is it, the apocalypse
?On the prison bus ?This is it, the apocalypse ?Whoa
?This is it, the apocalypse ?Whoa ?I'm breaking up
?Whoa ?I'm breaking up ?I feel it in my bones
?I'm breaking up ?I feel it in my bones ?Enough to make
?I feel it in my bones ?Enough to make ?My systems go
Ah, good lungs.
?Welcome to the new age
?Welcome to the new age ?To the new age
?Welcome to the new age ?To the new age ?Welcome to the new age
?To the new age ?Welcome to the new age ?To the new age, whoa
?Welcome to the new age ?To the new age, whoa ?Whoa, I'm
?To the new age, whoa ?Whoa, I'm ?Radioactive
?Whoa, I'm ?Radioactive ?Radioactive
?Radioactive ?Radioactive ?Whoa
Good lord.
Austin, I feel like you have
Austin, I feel like you have the whole package going on.
Yeah.
Do you feel that way?
Yeah, I do, yeah.
Yeah, I do, yeah. It almost, at first, reminded
Yeah, I do, yeah. It almost, at first,
reminded me of hayley williams a little
It almost, at first, reminded me of hayley williams a little bit.
Yeah.
The way you sing.
The way you sing. Like, you know, from paramore.
Yeah, I love her.
I do too.
I do too. I think she's great.
Your pitch is great.
Yeah, you're a talented...
Thank you.
Young lady.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes. Shall we vote?
What a great song to do too.
Yeah.
I love that song.
It's a great song.
It's one of my favorite
It's one of my favorite songs.
Are you dying to know what we
Are you dying to know what we think?
I really am.
Shall we say one, two, three?
all: YES!
all: YEAH!
Of course.
Thank you.
Austin.
Austin. You're a force to be reckoned
Austin. You're a force to be reckoned with, baby.
all: YEAH.
all: THANK YOU.
Thank you.
The best part.
Yeah.
The screams--I love that.
I went in there, and I was
I went in there, and I was talking to them, and she wasn't
I went in there, and I was talking to them,
and she wasn't smiling or anything.
Sure.
And then I started singing,
And then I started singing, and she was like...
I was like, "Oh, thank god."
And she was like... I was like,
"Oh, thank god." Are you kidding me?
Each city has its own kinda
Each city has its own kinda feel to it, and that's so
Each city has its own kinda feel to it, and that's so exciting.
Feel to it, and that's so exciting.
It makes you realize, like, what
Exciting. It makes you realize,
like, what an incredible country we live in
It makes you realize, like, what an
incredible country we live in because there's so much regional
An incredible country we live
in because there's so much regional difference.
Hi.
What's your name?
I'm kylee adamson.
And what do you do for a
And what do you do for a living?
I'm a lumberjack.
Come on.
You are?
Yeah, I swing an axe.
Yeah, I like that.
I really hope you can sing.
I really hope you can sing. I do 'cause I like her already.
Okay.
?It's amazing
?How you can speak
?Right to my heart
?Without saying a word ?You
can light up the dark ?Try as I may I could never
?You can light up the dark ?Try
as I may I could never ?Explain what I hear when you
?Try as I may I could never
?Explain what I hear when you ?Don't say a thing
All right!
Cool, cool.
As soon as you started
As soon as you started singing, it was like you had me
As soon as you started singing,
it was like you had me immediately.
Wow.
The fact that you, you know,
The fact that you, you know, use an axe for a living is
use an axe for a living is extremely intimidating to me.
I'm not trying to intimidate
I'm not trying to intimidate you.
It's a yes for me.
Keith urban just said yes?
both: IT'S A YES FOR ME TOO.
both: OH, MY GOSH.
Three yeses.
They're amazing.
They are.
Oh!
Especially when they all say
Especially when they all say yes.
Hi.
You guys are beautiful
You guys are beautiful people.
I was thinking the same thing
I was thinking the same thing about you.
Your smile is ridiculous.
Oh, thank you.
Wow!
What's your name?
Tessa.
Hi, I'm michael simeon.
He looks like he's got a cool
He looks like he's got a cool name.
He looks like he's got a cool name. What's your name?
Keith. It is cool.
Ah!
Yeah!
?They keep trying
?To tell me
Nice voice, man.
All right.
?It's not a silly little
?Moment
?It's not the storm
?Before the calm ?This is a deep and dying ?Breath of
?This is a deep and dying ?Breath of ?The love that we've been
?Breath of ?The love that we've been ?Working on
?The love that we've been ?Working on ?Can't seem to hold you
?Working on ?Can't seem to hold you ?Like I want to
?Can't seem to hold you
?Like I want to ?So I can feel you in my arms
?Well, there is something
?Well, there is something ?Going down
Yep.
?Like a storm
?In the sky, ooh
?I ain't gonna be played
?By your behavior
?How can I trust someone
?Who's lying to me ?So bow out, go ?Now I said bow out and leave
?So bow out, go ?Now I said bow out and leave ?I said take
?Now I said bow out and leave ?I said take ?Your stuff and go
?I said take ?Your stuff and go ?'cause you're not for me, no
You're a star.
Wow!
Thank you.
Okay, I said it.
Thank you so much.
You are a star.
I love your tone.
I love your tone. I love your vibrato.
And I know there's so much
And I know there's so much more that you can grow.
I mean, I know I'm a decent
I mean, I know I'm a decent singer and everything, but I
I mean, I know I'm a decent singer and everything,
but I didn't think I was good enough
Singer and everything, but I
didn't think I was good enough to be american idol.
I would rethink yourself with
I would rethink yourself with regard to confidence because I
I would rethink yourself with regard
to confidence because I think you're a lot better maybe
Regard to confidence because I think
you're a lot better maybe than you are giving yourself
Think you're a lot better
maybe than you are giving yourself credit for.
It's a yes for me.
Yeah, it's a yes.
It's a yes.
Wow!
Thank you so much.
Ticket!
Oh, my god.
And they all come to american
And they all come to american idol.
Maybe.
Welcome back to utah where, in the early going,
salt lake has already produced a variety
In the early going, salt lake
has already produced a variety of potential stars.
Has already produced a variety
of potential stars. But as our superstar judges
Of potential stars. But as our
superstar judges know, when you cast your net as
But as our superstar judges know,
when you cast your net as wide as we do...
Know, when you cast your net as wide as we do...
hey, there's a microphone in
Wide as we do... hey, there's a microphone in here and a camera.
Hey, there's a microphone in here and a camera.
You're bound to catch some
Here and a camera. You're bound to catch some strange fish.
?Nothing's impossible
?I have found we're critiquing
somebody and giving them comments on national
We're critiquing somebody and
giving them comments on national television.
Giving them comments on national television.
There's millions of people
Television. There's millions of people watching.
There's millions of people watching. ?I love rock and roll
Watching. ?I love rock and roll ?So put another dime
?I love rock and roll ?So put another dime ?In the jukebox, baby
?So put another dime ?In the jukebox,
baby their friends and family are
?In the jukebox, baby their friends and family are watching.
Their friends and family are watching.
I never forget that, you know.
Watching. I never forget that,
you know. It's an interesting tone.
I never forget that, you know.
It's an interesting tone. What can I say?
I try and be as honest as I can
What can I say? I try and be
as honest as I can without sort of completely
I try and be as honest as I can
without sort of completely humiliating someone.
Without sort of completely
humiliating someone. ?All you need is love
Humiliating someone.
?All you need is love if you want to sing, like,
?All you need is love if you want to sing,
like, for real and live and do that
If you want to sing, like, for real
and live and do that professionally, you'd do really
For real and live and do that professionally,
you'd do really well to get some help.
Professionally, you'd do really well to get some help. All right.
Well to get some help. All right. I don't like to see anybody's
All right. I don't like to
see anybody's feelings get hurt, but, believe
I don't like to see anybody's feelings get hurt,
but, believe you me, if you could have heard
Feelings get hurt, but, believe you me,
if you could have heard some of these people--
You me, if you could have heard
some of these people-- I did not know what language
Some of these people-- I did
not know what language you were just singing in.
I did not know what language you
were just singing in. I swear I did not know that was
You were just singing in.
I swear I did not know that was english.
Man, I look like mother theresa.
English. Man, I look like mother theresa. I promise ya.
Man, I look like mother theresa. I promise ya.
I promise ya. I'm probably the most
I'm probably the most obnoxious guitar player in the
I'm probably the most obnoxious
guitar player in the world 'cause, like, if I have
Obnoxious guitar player in the world 'cause,
like, if I have one in my hands, I can't stop,
World 'cause, like, if I have one in my hands,
I can't stop, 'cause, like, I can't just,
One in my hands, I can't stop,
'cause, like, I can't just, like, sit here.
'cause, like, I can't just,
like, sit here. Yeah, he's the same way.
Like, sit here. Yeah, he's the same way.
My name's alex preston, and
Yeah, he's the same way.
My name's alex preston, and I'm 20 years old.
My name's alex preston,
and I'm 20 years old. I'm from mont vernon,
I'm 20 years old. I'm from mont vernon, new hampshire.
I'm from mont vernon, new hampshire.
Music means everything to me.
New hampshire. Music means everything to me.
I mean, like, that's just what I
Music means everything to me.
I mean, like, that's just what I love to do.
And I love to write songs.
Love to do. And I love to write songs.
Like, even if the songs suck, I
And I love to write songs. Like,
even if the songs suck, I love to write 'em still, you
Like, even if the songs suck,
I love to write 'em still, you know.
Love to write 'em still, you know. I'm a really shy person.
Know. I'm a really shy person. I was a total band geek.
I'm a really shy person.
I was a total band geek. I was in marching band.
That just broke me out of my
I was in marching band.
That just broke me out of my shell and just got me
That just broke me out of my
shell and just got me completely ready for this
Shell and just got me completely ready for this competition.
Alex decided to take a year
Off of college, and, you know,
We didn't know what to think,
But it's--you know, he had to
Follow his heart, and he did,
And--
?
We'll see. I'm ready to go at it with all I have.
I'm ready to go at it with all I have. Hey, how you all doing?
All I have. Hey, how you all doing? Hi.
Hey, how you all doing? Hi. Hello.
Hi. Hello. What's your name?
Hello. What's your name? My name's alex preston.
What's your name? My name's alex preston. What are you gonna sing
My name's alex preston. What are you gonna sing today?
What are you gonna sing today? I'm gonna start off with an
Today? I'm gonna start off with an original.
I'm gonna start off with an original.
I know it's risky, but I'm just
Original. I know it's risky, but I'm just gonna try it out.
I know it's risky, but I'm just gonna try it out. We like risky.
Gonna try it out. We like risky. All right. Let's do it.
?Then the kick drum starts
?Playing
?In my, just my beating
?Heart
?Nowhere to go ?No one to see ?Is it the finish line
?No one to see ?Is it the finish line ?Or the start
?Is it the finish line ?Or the start ?So I look into your
?Or the start ?So I look into your ?
?So I look into your ? ?And I see only sunlight
? ?And I see only sunlight ?And trees
?And I see only sunlight ?And trees ?Oh, it makes me wonder
?And trees ?Oh, it makes me wonder ?Oh, lord, it makes me wonder
?Oh, it makes me wonder ?Oh,
lord, it makes me wonder ?Can you even see me
?Oh, lord, it makes me wonder ?Can you even see me ?Yeah, oh
?Can you even see me ?Yeah, oh ?Cross that river
?Yeah, oh ?Cross that river ?To the other side
?Cross that river ?To the other side ?I promise you
?To the other side ?I promise you ?That it's nicer here
?I promise you ?That it's nicer here ?Take your hands
?That it's nicer here ?Take your hands ?From your face
?Take your hands ?From your face ?Don't hide
?From your face ?Don't hide ?There is no reason
?Don't hide ?There is no reason ?For your fear
?There is no reason ?For your fear ?No reason for your fear
?For your fear ?No reason for your fear mm.
?No reason for your fear mm. That's an original?
Mm. That's an original? Right on.
That's an original? Right on. Yeah. Yeah, I wrote that.
Right on. Yeah. Yeah, I wrote that. Good lord.
Yeah. Yeah, I wrote that. Good lord. How do you know those
Good lord. How do you know those harmonies you were playing?
How do you know those harmonies you were playing? I don't know.
Harmonies you were playing?
I don't know. I just feel it, and then--
I don't know. I just feel it,
and then-- do you know what I'm asking
I just feel it, and then-- do you know what I'm asking you?
Do you know what I'm asking you? Like, sometimes when people
You? Like, sometimes when people kinda pick up the guitar to play
Like, sometimes when people kinda
pick up the guitar to play because it's somethin' to do,
Kinda pick up the guitar to play
because it's somethin' to do, they play basic triads and
Because it's somethin' to do,
they play basic triads and stuff, and you're playing some
They play basic triads and stuff,
and you're playing some harmonies that are a little bit
Stuff, and you're playing some
harmonies that are a little bit more advanced than that.
Harmonies that are a little bit more advanced than that. Mm-hmm.
More advanced than that. Mm-hmm. And percussive too.
Mm-hmm. And percussive too. Yeah, the rhythm and the
And percussive too. Yeah, the rhythm and the harmony thing.
Yeah, the rhythm and the harmony thing. Well, I was in jazz band
Harmony thing. Well, I was in jazz band throughout high school.
Well, I was in jazz band throughout high school. Okay.
Throughout high school. Okay. So I was forced to learn how
Okay. So I was forced to learn how to read music.
So I was forced to learn how to read music.
I don't take lessons or
To read music. I don't take lessons or anything.
I don't take lessons or anything. Mm-hmm.
Anything. Mm-hmm. I just do it all myself.
Mm-hmm. I just do it all myself. I use my fingers 'cause I can't
I just do it all myself. I use
my fingers 'cause I can't use a pick, really.
I use my fingers 'cause I can't use a pick, really. It's great.
Use a pick, really. It's great. I just--I love using my
It's great. I just--I love using my fingers and...
I just--I love using my fingers and... oh, yeah.
Fingers and... oh, yeah. I love hitting the guitar and
Oh, yeah. I love hitting
the guitar and making a drum sound, 'cause I'm
I love hitting the guitar and
making a drum sound, 'cause I'm also a drummer.
Making a drum sound,
'cause I'm also a drummer. Your tone is soft.
Also a drummer. Your tone is soft. It's nice, though.
Your tone is soft. It's nice, though. Thank you.
It's nice, though. Thank you. I saw, like, how you
Thank you. I saw, like, how you literally, when you were
I saw, like, how you literally,
when you were singing with the guitar, you
Literally, when you were singing with the guitar,
you were super comfortable, looking
Singing with the guitar, you were super comfortable,
looking at each one of our eyes and
Were super comfortable, looking at
each one of our eyes and making sure that--you know what
At each one of our eyes and making
sure that--you know what I mean--really trying to
Making sure that--you know what
I mean--really trying to make that connection.
I mean--really trying to
make that connection. And I really like that.
Make that connection. And I really like that.
I feel like that's a sign of a
And I really like that. I feel
like that's a sign of a very comfortable performer.
I feel like that's a sign of a very
comfortable performer. So I love you and everything
Very comfortable performer.
So I love you and everything about you right now.
So I love you and everything
about you right now. Okay, let's do this.
About you right now. Okay, let's do this. That's a yes from me.
Okay, let's do this. That's a yes from me. Yes. Yes.
That's a yes from me. Yes. Yes. It's a yes from me too.
Yes. Yes. It's a yes from me too. Yes, that's it. Come on.
It's a yes from me too. Yes,
that's it. Come on. Can I shake all of your
Yes, that's it. Come on. Can I shake all of your hands?
Can I shake all of your hands? Sometimes it's just easy.
Hands? Sometimes it's just easy. Yeah.
Sometimes it's just easy. Yeah. Thank you so much.
Yeah. Thank you so much. A real singer, a real guitar
Thank you so much. A real singer,
a real guitar player, a real songwriter, a
A real singer, a real guitar player,
a real songwriter, a real musician.
Player, a real songwriter, a real musician. Nice work, man.
Real musician. Nice work, man. What a concept.
Nice work, man. What a concept. Have a good one.
What a concept. Have a good one. Yeah, you too.
Have a good one. Yeah, you too. I'll see y'all later.
Yeah, you too. I'll see y'all later. See ya in hollywood.
I'll see y'all later. See ya in hollywood. Yeah, man.
See ya in hollywood. Yeah, man. I'd go see that guy.
Yeah, man. I'd go see that guy. Yeah, he's good.
I'd go see that guy. Yeah, he's good. I'd go watch him.
Yeah, he's good. I'd go watch him. Go, alex.
I'd go watch him. Go, alex. Got it.
Go, alex. Got it. That was a great original.
Got it. That was a great original. It was.
That was a great original. It was. This ticket means everything,
It was. This ticket means everything, man.
This ticket means everything, man. Like, I'm so stoked to grow as
Man. Like, I'm so stoked
to grow as an artist, and that's all I can
Like, I'm so stoked to grow as an artist,
and that's all I can do, you know.
An artist, and that's all I can do,
you know. I was like--started thinking,
Do, you know. I was like--started thinking,
"Have I heard this song before?"
I was like--started thinking,
"Have I heard this song before?" By the end.
By the end. Hello?
Hello? Hey, ma.
Hello? Hey, ma. Allie?
Hey, ma. Allie? Hey, I'm on camera right now,
Allie? Hey, I'm on camera right now, but I'm going to hollywood.
Hey, I'm on camera right now, but I'm going to hollywood.
But I'm going to hollywood.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! ?
This is you, harry. Hey, gang. Hi.
Hey, gang. Hi. How you doing?
Hi. How you doing? Hi.
How you doing? Hi. Hello. I'm good.
Hi. Hello. I'm good. What's going on?
Hello. I'm good. What's going on? You're rockin' the fanny pack.
What's going on? You're
rockin' the fanny pack. I'm rockin' the fanny.
You're rockin' the fanny pack.
I'm rockin' the fanny. Yeah. A belly pack?
I'm rockin' the fanny. Yeah.
A belly pack? But I think I wear it well,
Yeah. A belly pack? But I think I wear it well, you know.
But I think I wear it well,
you know. You had to know we were gonna
You know. You had to know
we were gonna ask what was inside of that
You had to know we were gonna ask what was inside of that thing.
Ask what was inside of that thing. Would you like to see?
Thing. Would you like to see? I don't know.
Would you like to see? I don't know. It's been checked.
I don't know. It's been checked. It's been checked.
It's been checked. It's been checked.
Well, just the necessities of
It's been checked. Well, just the necessities of life.
Well, just the necessities of life. Okay.
Life. Okay. A makeup brush.
Okay. A makeup brush. Okay, your stuff.
A makeup brush. Okay, your stuff. No one wants to be shiny.
Okay, your stuff. No one wants to be shiny. Right.
No one wants to be shiny. Right. I feel like I'm on
Right. I feel like I'm on let's make a deal.
I feel like I'm on let's make a deal.
Eyeliner, a little notebook.
Let's make a deal. Eyeliner,
a little notebook. What's in the notebook?
Eyeliner, a little notebook.
What's in the notebook? This is just my book of
What's in the notebook? This is just my book of notes.
This is just my book of notes. Right. That's perfect.
Notes. Right. That's perfect. If you pull out a boiled egg
Right. That's perfect. If you pull
out a boiled egg and a safety pin, you win what's
If you pull out a boiled egg and a safety pin,
you win what's behind door number three.
And a safety pin, you win what's
behind door number three. Is this as close to a boiled
Behind door number three. Is this as close to a boiled egg?
Is this as close to a boiled egg? How about that?
Egg? How about that? That's funny.
How about that? That's funny. She has a little egg.
That's funny. She has a little egg. We can be--
She has a little egg. We can be-- it's amazing.
We can be-- it's amazing. It's chapstick.
It's amazing. It's chapstick. I'm channeling...
It's chapstick. I'm channeling... I love that chapstick.
I'm channeling... I love that chapstick. Monty hall right now.
I love that chapstick. Monty hall right now. Thank you.
Monty hall right now. Thank you. I don't even know your name.
Thank you. I don't even know your name. Tell us your name.
I don't even know your name. Tell us your name. I'm samantha.
Tell us your name. I'm samantha. And where are you from?
I'm samantha. And where are you from? I grew up in louisiana.
And where are you from? I grew up in louisiana. Where?
I grew up in louisiana. Where? Hammond.
Where? Hammond. What are you planning on
Hammond. What are you planning on singing for us?
What are you planning on singing for us?
I'm gonna sing an original.
Singing for us? I'm gonna sing an original.
This is called from birth.
?
?I require that you listen
?'cause these words
?I ain't dismissin'
?A vision source by spiteful
?Apprehension attention ready ?To set and let go
?Apprehension attention ready
?To set and let go ?Let the fire feed itself
?Let desire feed your goals
?Let the fire feed itself ?Let
desire feed your goals ?Many of a time I fall
?Let desire feed your goals
?Many of a time I fall ?It's a mystery if my feet
?Many of a time I fall ?It's
a mystery if my feet ?Are gonna land at all
?It's a mystery if my feet
?Are gonna land at all ?Still I'm crawling
?Are gonna land at all ?Still I'm crawling ?Be my savior
?Still I'm crawling ?Be my savior ?When it's said and done
?Be my savior ?When it's said and done ?I can almost taste
?When it's said and done
?I can almost taste ?Redemption on the tip
?I can almost taste ?Redemption on the tip ?Of my tongue
?Redemption on the tip ?Of my tongue ?I hear my demons screaming
?Of my tongue ?I hear my demons screaming thank you.
?I hear my demons screaming thank you. Yeah.
Thank you. Yeah. Can you give us a little
Yeah. Can you give us a little somethin' that somebody else
Can you give us a little
somethin' that somebody else wrote just so we...
Somethin' that somebody else wrote just so we... sure.
Wrote just so we... sure. Can compare it to someone.
Sure. Can compare it to someone. Can have a point of
Can compare it to someone. Can have a point of reference, yes.
Can have a point of reference, yes. Jeffersons theme song.
Reference, yes. Jeffersons theme song. Familiar? Yeah?
Jeffersons like the tv show,
Like the tv show, the jeffersons?
Like the tv show, the jeffersons? Yes.
The jeffersons? Yes. Really?
Yes. Really? Man, that's awesome.
Really? Man, that's awesome. Whoo-hoo!
Man, that's awesome. Whoo-hoo! Okay, here we go.
Whoo-hoo! Okay, here we go. ?Fish don't fry
Okay, here we go. ?Fish don't fry ?In the kitchen
?Fish don't fry ?In the kitchen hello.
?In the kitchen hello. ?Beans don't burn
Hello. ?Beans don't burn ?On the grill
?Beans don't burn ?On the grill ?Took a whole lotta tryin'
?On the grill ?Took a whole lotta tryin'
?Just to get up that hill
?Took a whole lotta tryin'
?Just to get up that hill ?Now we're up
?Just to get up that hill ?Now we're up ?In the big leagues
?Now we're up ?In the big leagues ?Takin' our turn at the bat
?In the big leagues ?Takin' our turn at the bat whoo!
?Takin' our turn at the bat whoo! ?As long as you're here
Whoo! ?As long as you're here ?It's you and me, baby
?As long as you're here ?It's you and me,
baby ?There ain't nothin' wrong
?It's you and me, baby
?There ain't nothin' wrong ?With that, yeah
?There ain't nothin' wrong ?With that, yeah ?We're movin' on up
?With that, yeah ?We're movin' on up ?Movin' on up
?We're movin' on up ?Movin' on up cool, cool.
?Movin' on up cool, cool. Okay.
Cool, cool. Okay. Yeah, if you hadn't told me
Okay. Yeah, if you hadn't
told me you were from louisiana, I would
Yeah, if you hadn't told me you
were from louisiana, I would know just from this.
You were from louisiana, I would know just from this. Yeah.
Know just from this. Yeah. That's--I've never heard
Yeah. That's--I've never heard anybody in any audition in my
That's--I've never heard anybody
in any audition in my life sing movin' on up, so--
Anybody in any audition in my life sing movin' on up,
so-- I mean, it's such a great tune.
Life sing movin' on up, good.
We all love that tune.
It is. It is.
And I think that was actually
And I think that was actually very, very smart.
And I think that was actually very,
very smart. You have some interesting things
Very, very smart. You have some interesting things to offer.
You have some interesting things to offer. I'll be honest.
To offer. I'll be honest. I wasn't very impressed with
I'll be honest. I wasn't very impressed with your voice.
I wasn't very impressed with your voice.
I was more impressed with the
Your voice. I was more impressed with the choice that you made.
I liked your voice.
I liked your voice. And you had your own style, your
I liked your voice. And you had your own style,
your phrasing, your--all your--
And you had your own style, your phrasing,
your--all your-- everything was just kinda
Phrasing, your--all your--
everything was just kinda like, "Okay, I didn't see that
Everything was just kinda like, "Okay, I didn't see that coming."
Like, "Okay, I didn't see that coming." So it was surprising and
Coming." So it was surprising and spontaneous.
So it was surprising and spontaneous. And I really enjoyed it.
Cool.
Yeah, I applaud the
Yeah, I applaud the originality.
Thanks.
I mean, starting with that
I mean, starting with that spoken word.
It was almost like a macklemore
Spoken word. It was almost like a macklemore song.
Yeah.
And then the second song, the
And then the second song, the jeffersons thing, was fantastic
And then the second song, the jeffersons thing,
was fantastic because it showed a great range
Jeffersons thing, was
fantastic because it showed a great range in you.
Cool.
And it really played to your
And it really played to your strengths as a singer, in my
And it really played to
your strengths as a singer, in my opinion.
Well, thank you.
So I think that was a good
So I think that was a good move.
Thank you very much.
I can kick off the voting and
I can kick off the voting and say yes.
Awesome.
Yes.
Cool.
Holler!
You're going to hollywood.
Nice!
Nice! Oh, my gosh.
Nice! Oh, my gosh. Look at that thing. Whoo!
Oh, my gosh. Look at that thing.
Whoo! I've been dreaming about this
Look at that thing. Whoo! I've been dreaming about this one.
I've been dreaming about this one. All right.
All right, good luck to you.
Congrats, baby.
We gonna have some fun in
We gonna have some fun in hollywood.
We gonna have some fun in hollywood. Oh, my goodness.
Ticket.
both: WHOO!
both: YEAH, THAT WILL BE THE FIRST
Yeah, that will be the first and only time we hear that theme
Yeah, that will be the
first and only time we hear that theme song.
I cannot believe she sang
I cannot believe she sang movin' on up.
I cannot believe she sang movin' on up. It's very cool.
Movin' on up. It's very cool. It's really cool.
It's very cool. It's really cool. That's just smart.
It's really cool. That's just smart. Yeah, it is.
That's just smart. Yeah, it is. I dig that.
Yeah, it is. I dig that. When you have that voice,
I dig that. When you have that voice, particularly.
When you have that voice, particularly. ?I'm going to hollywood
Particularly. ?I'm going to hollywood ?Yeah
?I'm going to hollywood ?Yeah hollywood. Yep.
?Yeah hollywood. Yep. That's where I'm going.
What's your name?
My name's ellie duke.
Nice.
It is a good name, right?
Mm-hmm.
My name is bhaya.
My name is bhaya. It's b-h-a-y-a.
That's so beautiful.
That's like the greatest
That's like the greatest stage name I've ever heard.
My name's evan sharp.
Evan sharp.
Evan sharp. Oh, please don't be.
My name's julie awful.
Julie awful?
Yes.
Like awful, like it's awful?
It's pretty close to that.
It's pretty close to that. Yeah.
Yeah.
And where you from?
I am from dallas, texas, but
I am from dallas, texas, but I'm in school at oxford, and
I am from dallas, texas, but I'm in school at oxford,
and that's where the bus tour was.
Oh, you were one of the bus
Oh, you were one of the bus contestants?
Yes. Yes.
Cool.
What was that like?
Once again, this season we
Once again, this season we sent the iconic idol bus across
Once again, this season we sent the
iconic idol bus across the country in search of our
Sent the iconic idol bus across the
country in search of our nation's most captivating
The country in search of our nation's most captivating voices.
I'm so excited!
I'm so excited! Whoo!
We traveled over 5,000 miles
We traveled over 5,000 miles to ensure that no voice was left
to ensure that no voice was left unheard.
I'm really happy that they
I'm really happy that they finally came here.
And it was mission
And it was mission accomplished as small town
And it was mission accomplished
as small town america delivers some big
Accomplished as small town america delivers some big voices.
Now the best of the south
Now the best of the south have been brought to salt lake
Now the best of the south have
been brought to salt lake city to sing for our judges.
Hello.
Hi. How you doing?
Hi.
Good. How are you all doing?
What's your name?
Well, I'm lebryant crew.
Well, I'm lebryant crew. I'm from el dorado, arkansas.
Well, I'm lebryant crew. I'm from el dorado,
arkansas. I'm 24 years old.
Cool.
Cool. Well, yeah, let's get started.
Cool. Well, yeah, let's get started. Let's hear it.
?My baby don't stand
?No cheating, my babe
I'm gonna move around a little
Bit.
?Oh, yes, she don't stand ?No cheating, my baby, oh
?Oh, yes, she don't stand ?No cheating, my baby, oh ?My baby
?No cheating, my baby, oh ?My baby I am a minister, yes.
?My baby I am a minister, yes. Being the first preacher to win
I am a minister, yes. Being the
first preacher to win american idol, that's good
Being the first preacher to win american idol,
that's good stuff, you know.
American idol, that's good stuff,
you know. It'll give hope to all the
Stuff, you know. It'll give hope to all the preachers there is.
It'll give hope to all the preachers there is.
Preachers there is. ?Hey, my babe
?Hey, my babe ?I know she love me
?Hey, my babe ?I know she love me ?She don't do nothin' but
?So how do I love you
?When you go
I'm singing my own song because
I feel like I only have one shot
To show them what I can do.
?Please tell me why couldn't
?You stay just one more day ?So I could say
?You stay just one more day ?So I could say ?I love you
What'd you think?
I like this guy.
Yeah?
You're a performer.
You're a performer. I respond well to performers.
Okay.
I love the talking in
I love the talking in between.
That was good.
I loved it.
Thank you.
You had me immediately.
It was really, really pretty.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say yes too.
It's three yeses.
I'm going to hollywood, baby!
I'm going to hollywood, baby! ?
I got three yeses, so I'm
I got three yeses, so I'm super excited.
See ya, salt lake.
See ya, salt lake. I'm going to hollywood, baby!
He's got a show business...
Yeah.
About him.
Totally. Yeah.
I like that. I like that.
Oh, it's ed sheeran.
Hello?
How you doing, man?
Yes, it is ed sheeran.
Good to see ya.
What are you doing here?
Not ed sheeran.
Right.
I'm dj bradley.
Hi, dj.
Hi.
What are you gonna sing for
What are you gonna sing for us?
Hometown glory by adele.
Hometown glory mm-hmm.
Hometown glory okay.
?I've been walking
?In the same way as I did
?Missing out the cracks ?In the pavement ?Tutting my heel
?In the pavement ?Tutting my heel ?Strutting my feet
?Tutting my heel ?Strutting my feet ?Is there anything I can do
?Strutting my feet ?Is there anything I can do ?For you, dear
?Is there anything I can do
?For you, dear ?Oh, is there anyone I can
?For you, dear ?Oh, is there anyone I can ?Call, no and please
?Oh, is there anyone I can ?Call, no and please ?And thank you
I like the sound of his
I like the sound of his voice.
?Not lost, just wandering
?Not lost, just wandering ?'round my hometown
?'round my hometown ?The memories are so fresh
?'round my hometown ?The
memories are so fresh ?'round my hometown
?The memories are so fresh
?'round my hometown ?Ooh, the people I have met
You have, like, a quirky
You have, like, a quirky thing going on.
You have a quirky vibe.
Yes, but I kinda like it.
Yes, but I kinda like it. You have a lot of personality in
You have a lot of personality in your voice too.
And the sound of your voice I
Your voice too. And the sound
of your voice I found to be really pleasant.
Thank you.
Different kind of.
Not ed sheeran.
No, not ed sheeran-y.
No, no.
No, no. You got your own thing going
No, no. You got your own thing going on, man.
There's kinda this kinda,
There's kinda this kinda, like, you know, mysterious
There's kinda this kinda, like, you know,
mysterious musician thing going on, looking
Like, you know, mysterious musician thing going on,
looking down, and the hair is in the
Musician thing going on, looking down,
and the hair is in the face, and all that kinda stuff,
Down, and the hair is in the face,
and all that kinda stuff, which is kinda cool.
Okay.
But I would like too, to
But I would like too, to kind of have you come out of
But I would like too, to kind
of have you come out of that shell a little bit.
Kind of have you come out of
that shell a little bit. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I'm really working on
Yeah, I'm really working on it, actually.
Right.
I kinda like it.
Dj, is that--I mean, is that
Dj, is that--I mean, is that what you want?
Some people are comfortable in
What you want? Some people are comfortable in that spot.
I love writing my own stuff.
Yeah.
And I love putting my own
And I love putting my own spin on things 'cause, you
And I love putting my own spin on things 'cause, you know--
What do you think, baby?
Yeah.
Yeah. I just--I had mixed feelings
Yeah. I just--I had mixed feelings the whole time 'cause there's
I just--I had mixed feelings the whole
time 'cause there's somethin' about your voice that
The whole time 'cause there's
somethin' about your voice that I really like.
Yeah.
But it was a balance between
But it was a balance between sort of mysterious versus
sort of mysterious versus disinterested.
Yeah.
And it erred too much
And it erred too much sometimes into the sort of
And it erred too much sometimes
into the sort of disinterested side, which makes
Sometimes into the sort of disinterested side,
which makes me disinterested.
Disinterested side, which makes me disinterested.
I got to find something riveting
Me disinterested. I got to find
something riveting in there that glues me to you.
I got to find something riveting in
there that glues me to you. And for me, it wasn't quite
In there that glues me to you.
And for me, it wasn't quite enough there.
Okay.
I know exactly what you're
I know exactly what you're saying.
Yeah.
I was really lucky the other
I was really lucky the other day 'cause I got a chance to do
I was really lucky the other day
'cause I got a chance to do this little thing with paul
Day 'cause I got a chance to do this
little thing with paul simon, and he does not move.
This little thing with paul simon,
and he does not move. He doesn't sing loud.
Simon, and he does not move. He doesn't sing loud.
But he also has 800 number one
He doesn't sing loud. But he
also has 800 number one songs that everybody knows.
But he also has 800 number one songs
that everybody knows. I'm out there jumping on the
Songs that everybody knows.
I'm out there jumping on the piano, I'm tap--
Whoo!
I'm doing--I mean, but that's
I'm doing--I mean, but that's just--that's me.
And if you were a young paul
Just--that's me. And if you
were a young paul simon--like, I see exactly
And if you were a young paul simon--like,
I see exactly what you're saying 'cause it
Simon--like, I see exactly what
you're saying 'cause it borderlines on disinterest.
Okay.
Shall we vote?
Shall we vote? I'm gonna say yes.
Okay.
I think there's a blossom to
I think there's a blossom to be had here.
Do you?
I do. I really do.
I'm still on the fence.
You got it. Nice job, man. Congratulations, bro.
Something interesting.
Yeah. Even if it's a spark.
Hello?
Hey, dad.
Hey, dad. I made it to hollywood.
There you go, baby!
Yeah.
That's my boy!
You may still be wondering
What happened to julie awful.
You be the judge.
?I know you haven't made
?Your minds up yet
?But I would
?Never do you wrong
?No
?I've known it
?From the moment that we met
Hollywood or home?
Chime in right now using the
Hashtags below, and we'll see if
You're right after the break.
Before the break, we asked if
Have good news or bad news for
Julie awful.
?No doubt in my mind
?Where you belong
Cute.
I like your voice.
It just wasn't--you just
Didn't have the confidence to go
Right.
Now, I hate using that term
Over and over again, but
Sometimes that's what it is.
Absolutely.
There's enough of a pretty
Voice there to maybe explore.
I'm gonna say yes.
I got to say no.
Ooh. I can do this.
I got this.
I know you think you have it.
I know you think you deserve
Another shot, and I think that
You deserve another shot, so
Welcome to hollywood.
Whoo!
He's a cruel person.
Two yeses.
I have to tell you something.
Go ahead.
My mom best friend--she's
Like my second mom--she has
Second-row seats to your
Concert in dallas, and she's
Gonna be holding a sign.
She's gonna be holding up a
She's gonna be holding up a sign with her face on it.
Thank you so much.
Bring it.
See ya in hollywood, julie.
Tell your mom's second
Tell your mom's second cousin's friend's uncle that I
Tell your mom's second cousin's
friend's uncle that I appreciate him thinking he knows
Cousin's friend's uncle that
I appreciate him thinking he knows who I am.
I am a good little distance
I am a good little distance from my house right now.
I'm from spokane, washington,
I'm from spokane, washington, and we drove 11 1/2 hours to get
and we drove 11 1/2 hours to get here.
I'm from richmond, virginia.
I'm from richmond, virginia. It's 1,000 or so miles.
I mean, it's a long distance.
Is it? Yeah.
Yeah.
It's probably 2,000.
I am so nervous.
What's it been like for you
What's it been like for you so far?
What's it been like for you so far? A little nerve-racking just
So far? A little nerve-racking just waiting?
Yeah, just putting on a
Yeah, just putting on a brave face for the family.
Are you prepared for this
Are you prepared for this audition?
I'm as prepared as I'll ever
I'm as prepared as I'll ever be.
I'm as prepared as I'll ever be. Music is what I want to do with
Be. Music is what I want
to do with my life, and so this is a huge
Music is what I want to do with my life,
and so this is a huge opportunity for me.
What's the time, baby,
What's the time, baby, by the way?
It's 3:47, baby.
It's 3: 3:47.
3: god. Where'd the day go?
Hi, baby.
How are you?
I'm pretending like I'm okay.
Wow!
She sounded like she was
She sounded like she was singing right there.
That's honest.
I swear, it's like--
You went...
both: ?AHH
both: SING YOUR ANSWERS TO
Sing your answers to everything.
You sing--yeah, you just
You sing--yeah, you just started singing without even
You sing--yeah, you just started
singing without even knowing you were singing.
?What's your name, baby
My name's kenzie.
We're just gonna sing
We're just gonna sing everything.
Yeah.
?How you doing, harry
?Pretty good, keith
?It's so great
And what are you gonna sing
And what are you gonna sing tonight?
I'm gonna sing I'm gonna find
I'm gonna sing I'm gonna find another you by john mayer.
I'm gonna sing I'm gonna find another you okay.
Another you okay, let's see if I'm ready
Okay, let's see if I'm ready for this.
Deep breath.
Yeah.
?So go on now, baby
?And make your little getaway
?My pride should keep me ?Company
Whoo.
?And you just gave yours
?And you just gave yours ?All away and now I
She is 16, you guys.
?Dress myself for two
?Dress myself for two ?One's for me and one's
?Dress myself for two ?One's for me and one's ?For someone new
?One's for me and one's
?For someone new ?I'm gonna do some things
?For someone new ?I'm
gonna do some things ?You wouldn't let me do
?I'm gonna do some things ?You wouldn't let me do ?And I, ooh
?You wouldn't let me do ?And I, ooh ?I'm gonna find
?And I, ooh ?I'm gonna find ?Another you
All right, I've heard enough.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, me too. You have everything going on.
And she played a diminished
And she played a diminished chord.
And she's 16.
Exactly.
That did it for me.
Exactly. You had him at diminished.
It's like, wow.
It's like, wow. We should vote.
Yeah, it's a yes for me.
Thank you.
I'm gonna say yes too.
That's three yeses.
That's three yeses. You're going to hollywood.
You're the best.
You're the best. Thank you.
Congrats.
Oh, thank you so much.
See ya in hollywood.
Thank you, thank you, thank
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
She's one of my faves.
Yeah, me too.
She's one of my faves. She is great.
I am going to hollywood.
I am going to hollywood. You're gonna make me cry.
Actually hearing some good
Actually hearing some good singers today.
Yeah.
Hi, baby.
Hello.
Hi.
What's your name?
Paisley van patten.
How long have you been
How long have you been playing, singing?
How long have you been playing, singing? Do you play?
I've been playing, singing--
I've been playing, singing-- I lived in nashville for
I've been playing,
singing-- I lived in nashville for about seven years.
Why did you live in nashville
Why did you live in nashville for seven years?
I got my first record deal
I got my first record deal when I was 15, and I just kind
I got my first record deal when I was 15,
and I just kind of hit the ground running.
When I was 15, and I just kind of hit
the ground running. I had the car, the producer, the
Of hit the ground running.
I had the car, the producer, the glamour.
I had the car, the producer,
the glamour. And that's where I made a
Glamour. And that's where I made a within a year, everything was
And that's where I made a within a year, everything was gone.
Within a year, everything was gone.
I had to come to grips with that
Gone. I had to come to grips with that I was an alcoholic.
I had to come to grips with
that I was an alcoholic. It took over my life.
I was an alcoholic. It took over my life.
I came back home to salt lake
It took over my life. I
came back home to salt lake and got some help.
I came back home to salt lake and got some help. I'm so happy--
And got some help. I'm so happy-- I really blew it.
I'm so happy-- I really blew it. I really did blow it with my
I really blew it. I really did blow it with my addiction.
I really did blow it with my addiction.
That's why this american idol
Addiction. That's why this
american idol has been so important to me, is
That's why this american idol has been
so important to me, is because I'm sober, and I'm doing
Has been so important to me, is because I'm sober,
and I'm doing the deal, and I'm still chasing
Because I'm sober, and I'm doing the deal,
and I'm still chasing my dream.
The deal, and I'm still chasing my dream. And that's huge.
My dream. And that's huge. I can relate.
And that's huge. I can relate. But I've been sober for
I can relate. But I've been sober for 2 1/2 years now.
BUT I'VE BEEN SOBER FOR 2 1/2 YEARS NOW. Both: GOOD FOR YOU.
2 1/2 YEARS NOW. Both: GOOD FOR YOU. YEAH, THANK YOU.
both: GOOD FOR YOU. YEAH, THANK YOU. AWESOME.
Yeah, thank you. Awesome. Good for you, paisley.
Awesome. Good for you, paisley. And what are you doing right
Good for you, paisley. And what are you doing right now?
And what are you doing right now? Right now just working on
Now? Right now just working on that and second chances,
Right now just working on
that and second chances, really, you know.
That and second chances, really,
you know. Trying to see if I still...
Really, you know. Trying to see if I still... I love that.
Trying to see if I still... I love that. Got this, sober.
I love that. Got this, sober. I believe in that.
Got this, sober. I believe in that. Absolutely.
I believe in that. Absolutely. Yeah.
Absolutely. Yeah. Do you have support now?
Yeah. Do you have support now? I do. Amazing support.
Do you have support now? I do. Amazing support. Who from?
I do. Amazing support. Who from? My family.
Who from? My family. I was engaged, and then he was
My family. I was engaged,
and then he was not supportive of this american
I was engaged, and then he was not
supportive of this american idol thing, I think, just
Not supportive of this american idol thing,
I think, just because of everything we've been
Idol thing, I think,
just because of everything we've been through.
Because of everything we've been through.
And he said, "You do this, and
Through. And he said, "You do this, and we're done."
Oh, did he think maybe he
Oh, did he think maybe he would lose you to whatever
Oh, did he think maybe he would
lose you to whatever potential success you would
Would lose you to whatever potential success you would have?
Yeah, and, you know, he's a
Yeah, and, you know, he's a really, really amazing man.
Yeah, and, you know, he's a really,
really amazing man. I just--I have to do this.
Really, really amazing man.
I just--I have to do this. It's in me, you know.
We know. We get that.
You have to do it, so...
What are you gonna sing
What are you gonna sing today?
I'm gonna sing when the
I'm gonna sing when the lights go down by faith hill.
I'm gonna sing when the lights go down okay, great song, baby.
Lights go down all right.
Hit it.
?When the lights go down
?He'll be filling a pan
?With a broom in his hand
?In some dive across town
?He'll be wiping the bar
?And mopping the floor ?Counting his tips
?And mopping the floor ?Counting his tips ?And locking the doors
?Counting his tips ?And locking the doors ?Wrestling the devil
?And locking the doors
?Wrestling the devil ?That tells him to pour
?Wrestling the devil ?That tells him to pour ?Another round
?That tells him to pour ?Another round ?When the lights
?Another round ?When the lights ?Go down and there's
?When the lights ?Go down and there's ?Nothing left to be
?Go down and there's ?Nothing left to be ?When the lights go down
?Nothing left to be ?When the lights go down ?And the truth is
?When the lights go down
?And the truth is ?All you see when you feel
?That hole inside your soul
?All you see when you feel ?That hole inside your soul ?Wondering
?That hole inside your soul ?Wondering ?What you're made of
?Wondering ?What you're made of ?Well, we all find out
?What you're made of ?Well,
we all find out ?When the lights go down
Hmm.
?When the lights go down
Nice.
Good. Nice control.
I love your voice, baby.
Thank you.
I love that you sang that
I love that you sang that song.
Good control.
I also love that you sang it
I also love that you sang it very subdued, you know.
I also love that you sang it very subdued,
you know. You just kinda stayed--it
Very subdued, you know. You just kinda stayed--it was good.
Thank you.
That was a good thing to do
That was a good thing to do for me for that song.
That takes a lot of
That takes a lot of confidence.
That takes a lot of confidence. I like that you had a lot of
Confidence. I like that you had a lot of control there too.
I like that you had a lot of control there too.
It's hard to control your voice
Control there too. It's hard to
control your voice when you're singing that softly.
It's hard to control your voice when
you're singing that softly. So it was really, really pretty.
Thank you.
Yeah, I loved it.
Yeah, I did too.
Yeah, I did too. You know, what really spoke to
Yeah, I did too. You know,
what really spoke to me was you seem like a gentle
You know, what really spoke to me
was you seem like a gentle person who's found some
Me was you seem like a gentle person who's found some happiness.
Oh, thank you.
And it was nice to couple
And it was nice to couple that with the sound of your
And it was nice to couple that with the sound of your voice.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Wow.
And you feel good about all
And you feel good about all this right now?
I do.
Yeah.
And you would think--
'cause she's still new, a
'cause she's still new, a newbie, fresh.
both: YEAH.
both: FRAGILE.
Thank you.
Raw.
Raw. Raw is a good place to be for an
Raw. Raw is a good place to be for an artist.
Yeah.
It really is where the truth
It really is where the truth comes out.
Yeah. For real.
Yeah. For real. Yeah.
It's a yes from me.
Yes from me too.
It's a yes.
Oh, my god! You guys.
Oh, my god! You guys. Thank you.
Oh, my god! You guys. Thank you. I was so worried I was gonna do
Thank you. I was so worried I was gonna do a cher impression.
Well, you can't leave without
Well, you can't leave without doing the cher impression.
Oh, my.
Oh, my. You want me to do--
Yeah, well, you have to do
Yeah, well, you have to do the cher.
Yeah, well, you have to do the cher. You can't leave us--
The cher. You can't leave us-- here, back on the mark.
Okay.
Don't drop that and then run.
Okay, hold on.
Okay, hold on. Oh, I got it.
Okay, hold on. Oh, I got it. Okay.
Oh, hang on.
?Do you believe in life
?Do you believe in life ?After love
Yes!
That's it?
I was like, "If they're not
I was like, "If they're not gonna pick me, I can be on the
I was like, "If they're not gonna pick me,
I can be on the bloopers, right?"
Hey, you would have gone to
Hey, you would have gone to hollywood just for that.
hollywood just for that. That's all you needed to do.
Hollywood just for that.
That's all you needed to do. You could have spared us all
That's all you needed to do.
You could have spared us all that other stuff.
See ya in hollywood, baby.
See you!
That is awesome.
Wow!
That made my day.
That's how you do it.
Good for her.
I knew it!
I got a hug from keith urban.
I got a hug from keith urban. This is never getting washed.
All right.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. It's such a fresh start.
Oh, my gosh. It's such a fresh start. Like, this means this could
It's such a fresh start.
Like, this means this could finally be it.
Like, this could really--this
Finally be it. Like, this
could really--this could really be it this time.
Like, this could really--this could
really be it this time. And I'm so blessed and so
Could really be it this time.
And I'm so blessed and so grateful right now.
That's good television.
But with day one drawing to a close, there are still potential
But with day one drawing to a close,
there are still potential stars sweating it out.
You got this.
?And I won't give up on us
?Even if the skies get rough
?I'm giving you all my love
That's cool. The people who make it to the
That's cool. The people who
make it to the top 20, top 10, really have to
The people who make it to the top 20,
top 10, really have to be the best out there.
Okay.
It's a no for me.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say yes. I want to see you one more time
I'm gonna say yes. I want to see you one more time in hollywood.
Okay.
She looks at me.
I knew that was coming.
all: AWW.
all: IT'S OKAY.
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo!
I think people like watching
I think people like watching american idol 'cause you never
I think people like watching american
idol 'cause you never know what you're gonna get.
American idol I'm here, you guys.
I'm here, you guys. I'm here!
He's here!
With you! I'm here!
Yeah!
?Go dirty dancing
?In the moonlight
?And take me down
?Come on
?Maybe we'll live
?And learn
all: DIDN'T MAKE IT.
Didn't make it.
Mwah. Mwah.
What do you do for fun?
I go fishing, and I play
I go fishing, and I play music.
And what do you fish for?
I fish for bluegill and
I fish for bluegill and women.
Hi, baby.
Hello.
And what do you catch more
And what do you catch more of?
Bluegill.
Yeah?
?I want to run through
?The halls of my high school
What cracks me up?
What cracks me up? I don't know.
What cracks me up? I don't know. Just, you know--just people.
I don't know. Just, you know--just people.
?I've always been
?Different with one foot
?Over the line
Don't give me the wink.
Don't give me the wink. Don't give me the wink.
Yes.
Got it.
I think you have to have
I think you have to have talent.
I made it!
It's not about gimmicks.
It's not about gimmicks. You just got to get up there and
It's not about gimmicks. You
just got to get up there and sing and touch america.
That's-- my name is cj harris.
My name is cj harris. I'm from jasper, alabama.
My name is cj harris. I'm from jasper,
alabama. I play music for a living.
I'm from jasper, alabama. I play music for a living.
That's what I've been doing ever
I play music for a living.
That's what I've been doing ever since I was a little boy.
That's what I've been doing ever since
I was a little boy. When I was a younger boy, I had
Since I was a little boy. When I was a younger boy,
I had some problems with my parents.
Regardless of what you've been through in life,
you can be strong through it, and you can
Been through in life, you can be strong through it,
and you can be anything that you want to be.
Strong through it, and you can be anything
that you want to be. My father passed away a year ago
Be anything that you want to be. My
father passed away a year ago of a massive heart attack.
My father passed away a year ago of
a massive heart attack. It just come out of nowhere.
Of a massive heart attack. It just
come out of nowhere. He died at a very young age.
I see myself through him all the time
and often sit there, and I think about my dad, and, you
Time and often sit there, and I think about my dad,
and, you know, it's made me a better man.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey. How you doing, man?
Excellent, man.
Excellent, man. How you doing?
I'm doin' good.
I'm doin' good. It's an honor to be up here,
I'm doin' good. It's an honor to be up here, man.
It's good to see you too.
Oh, man.
Yes!
What's your name?
My name is cj harris, and
My name is cj harris, and I'm--
Cj harris.
Yes.
Yes. I'm from jasper, alabama.
Jasper, alabama.
Yeah. Yes, sir.
You're a long way from home,
You're a long way from home, man.
I'm auditioning for
I'm auditioning for american idol.
I'm auditioning for american idol. I feel like this is my time to
American idol. I feel like this is my time to be here.
I feel like this is my time to be here.
I grew up listening to you, man.
Be here. I grew up listening to you,
man. You guys, man, I appreciate you
I grew up listening to you, man. You guys,
man, I appreciate you all giving me an opportunity to
You guys, man, I appreciate
you all giving me an opportunity to be up here.
All giving me an opportunity to be up here.
And what are you gonna sing?
Be up here. And what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing soulshine by
And what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing soulshine by the allman brothers.
I want to dedicate it to my dad.
Hit it.
Hit it. ?
?When you can't find
?The light that guides you
?Through a cloudy day
?When the stars ain't shining ?Bright ?And it feels like you lost
?Bright ?And it feels like you lost ?Your way
?And it feels like you lost ?Your way ?When the candlelights
?Your way ?When the candlelights ?From home
?When the candlelights ?From home ?Burn so very far away
?From home ?Burn so very far away ?Yeah, sometimes
?Burn so very far away ?Yeah, sometimes ?I get a cool wind
?Yeah, sometimes ?I get a cool wind ?Burning through
?I get a cool wind ?Burning through ?My aching bones
?Burning through ?My aching bones ?I think back to what
?My aching bones ?I think back to what ?My daddy said
?I think back to what ?My daddy said ?He said, boy, in this life
?My daddy said ?He said, boy, in this life ?Before the dawn
?He said, boy, in this life ?Before the dawn ?Let your soul shine
Hmm.
?It's better than sunshine
?It's better than sunshine ?It's better than moonshine
?It's better than sunshine ?It's
better than moonshine ?Damn sure better than rain
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Cool, man.
Yeah, yeah. Cool, man. Beautiful.
Thank you, guys.
You know, it wasn't perfect.
You know, it wasn't perfect. It wasn't like--
He sang it right to you.
But I really liked it.
Thank you.
I like you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I like that voice coming out
I like that voice coming out of you.
Thank you.
And watching what you do.
And watching what you do. And I don't know.
There was things that you do
And I don't know.
There was things that you do consistently wrong.
I understand completely.
But we could fix that.
But we could fix that. I liked it.
But we could fix that. I liked it. I liked it a lot.
Yeah, I--
I like you.
Jennifer took the words out
Jennifer took the words out of my mouth.
I think there's probably better
Of my mouth. I think there's
probably better guitar players around, there's
I think there's probably better guitar players around,
there's probably better singers around.
True.
But there's something about
But there's something about the entirety of what you are.
But there's something about the
entirety of what you are. It's really a--kind of a
The entirety of what you are.
It's really a--kind of a vibe that you have...
Yes, sir.
That was very pleasant.
That was very pleasant. I mean, you had my attention
That was very pleasant. I mean,
you had my attention through the entire tune.
How you doing?
Anxious.
Are you a little nervous, a
Little anxious?
Not nervous. Anxious.
Anxious.
Yeah.
Yep.
Yep. He deserves it more than anybody
Yep. He deserves it more than anybody does.
You know what it was for me?
You know what it was for me? It's like you sing 'cause you
It's like you sing 'cause you have to sing, not 'cause you
It's like you sing 'cause you have to sing,
not 'cause you want to sing.
Mm.
And I mean that in the
And I mean that in the deepest way.
You're right.
And that's why it's so
And that's why it's so believable and real.
And it's greater than the sum of
Believable and real. And it's
greater than the sum of the parts, you know.
Yep. I agree.
It's just--I just believed
It's just--I just believed it, and I felt it.
Thanks, man.
So it's a yes from me.
Yes from me too, bro.
Yes from me too.
Yes from me too. Welcome to hollywood, baby.
Cj, you're going to
Cj, you're going to hollywood, man.
Cj, you're going to hollywood, man. Come on.
Thank you, man.
Dude, come here.
Come here. Good job.
Thank you.
Good job.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Give me a hug. Mm.
We'll see ya in hollywood.
See ya in hollywood, cj.
All right.
Nice touch on the guitar,
Nice touch on the guitar, bro.
Thanks, man.
Yeah, man.
I just gotta say when some
I just gotta say when some people play, it feels like
I just gotta say when some people play,
it feels like there's more notes coming out
People play, it feels like there's
more notes coming out than when certain people play.
Yeah, I know.
It's like, "Wow!"
Yeah, no, he's--he had a
Yeah, no, he's--he had a nice rhythmic touch.
That's a really good point to
That's a really good point to make.
He sounds like he has to sing.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. It's a great--
What about how he cried
What about how he cried instantly?
Oh, don't.
He was, like, breaking my
He was, like, breaking my heart.
Oh, my goodness.
Congratulations, man.
Congratulations, man. You did it.
Congratulations, man. You did it. You got it.
You did it. You got it. Good job, buddy.
I'm so happy, man.
I'm so happy, man. Words can't even explain.
Cj, welcome to hollywood.
Thanks, man.
You did it. See ya later.
This is for my family and all
This is for my family and all the people who believed in me
This is for my family and
all the people who believed in me from day one.
The people who believed in me from day one. Thank you.
Which way we going, this way?
Sure.
I like it because you guys are, like, in gray and black.
Yeah.
And all, like, rock and
And all, like, rock and rollery.
We're like you're security.
We're like you're security. Like you're security.
No, you're not.
Out of the way, please.
Out of the way, please. Out of the way, please.
Day two begins in salt lake
Day two begins in salt lake city as our search for a
city as our search for a superstar continues.
City as our search for a superstar continues.
Hello, hello, hello, hello,
Superstar continues. Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello.
What do you think of when you
What do you think of when you think of salt lake?
The skiing.
We don't really have, like, a
We don't really have, like, a ton of skiing in the bronx.
Ton of skiing in the bronx. We're here!
We made it.
This is how we travel
Everywhere.
Well, the judges are pumped
Well, the judges are pumped and ready.
Well, the judges are pumped and ready. If only that energy could
And ready. If only that
energy could somehow reach the holding room.
Tequila is in the building!
Tequila is in the building! Make some noise!
How'd you get the name
How'd you get the name tequila?
I had nothin' to do with
I had nothin' to do with that.
I had nothin' to do with that. My mom named me.
That. My mom named me. I'm gonna get the golden ticket.
My mom named me. I'm gonna get the golden ticket. I'm excited!
Hi, guys.
Good luck.
Lots of guitars again.
Lots of guitars. Man.
Lots of guitars. Man. What's the difference between a
What's the difference between a banjo and a trampoline?
What's that?
Nice people take their shoes
Nice people take their shoes off before they jump on a
Nice people take their
shoes off before they jump on a trampoline.
It's just endless.
It's just endless. It's all good.
Here we go!
How are you?
Good.
We're good. How are you?
What's your name?
Tequila wilson.
Tequila?
Mm-hmm. Yes.
Like the drink tequila?
Yes!
And where you from?
I am from winston-salem,
I am from winston-salem, north carolina.
Are you part of some kind of
Are you part of some kind of musical community?
I sing in my church.
I sing in my church. Funerals.
I sing in my church. Funerals. I work at a funeral home.
Mm-hmm.
Really?
So I sing for the dead.
Harry does, too, sometimes.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Most of--90% of my concerts.
What are you gonna sing for
What are you gonna sing for us today?
Someone like you by adele.
Someone like you okay, let's get to it.
Someone like you you ready?
Yeah.
?Never mind, I'll find
?Someone like you
?I wish nothing but the best ?From you too ?Don't forget me
?From you too ?Don't forget me ?I beg
?Don't forget me ?I beg ?I remember you said
?I beg ?I remember you said ?Sometimes it lasts in love
?I remember you said ?Sometimes
it lasts in love ?Sometimes it hurts instead
?Sometimes it lasts in love ?Sometimes it hurts instead ?Oh
?Sometimes it hurts instead ?Oh ?Don't forget me
?Oh ?Don't forget me ?I beg
?Don't forget me ?I beg ?I remember
?I beg ?I remember ?I remember you said
?I remember ?I remember you said ?Sometimes it lasts in love
?I remember you said ?Sometimes
it lasts in love ?Sometimes it hurts instead
Okay.
Okay. You know, some people just open
Okay. You know, some people
just open their mouth, and it doesn't even
You know, some people just open their mouth,
and it doesn't even matter.
Yeah, right.
Okay, I started getting the
Okay, I started getting the goosies from the bottom to all
goosies from the bottom to all the way up.
You got goosies on your legs
You got goosies on your legs today?
On the legs.
On the legs. On the legs today.
I have a quick church
I have a quick church question.
I have a quick church question. How does the church community
Question. How does the
church community feel about you singing secular
How does the church
community feel about you singing secular music?
I really don't care...
Mm-hmm.
What they think.
What they think. I'm here to win american idol.
Of course, I'm gonna promote god
I'm here to win american idol. Of course,
I'm gonna promote god because I love him, but I really
Of course, I'm gonna promote god because I love him,
but I really don't care what they think.
Because I love him,
but I really don't care what they think. Right.
Don't care what they think. Right. You got to follow your dream.
Right. You got to follow your dream. My dream.
You got to follow your dream.
My dream. This is my dream, not theirs.
My dream. This is my dream, not theirs. You feel like they can
This is my dream, not theirs.
You feel like they can coexist, your faith and...
You feel like they can coexist, your faith and... yeah.
Coexist, your faith and... yeah. And singing music...
Yeah. And singing music... yeah.
And singing music... yeah. Outside the church?
Yeah. Outside the church? We're supposed to go out in
Outside the church? We're
supposed to go out in the world and reach other
We're supposed to go out in the world and reach other people.
The world and reach other people. I happen to agree with you.
People. I happen to agree with you. What do you think, keith?
I happen to agree with you. What do you think,
keith? I think you're the real deal.
What do you think, keith? I
think you're the real deal. It's a beautiful voice.
I think you're the real deal. It's a beautiful voice. Thank you.
It's a beautiful voice. Thank you. You carry a great message,
Thank you. You carry a great message, tequila.
You carry a great message, tequila. Thank you.
Tequila. Thank you. I like your spirit, baby.
Thank you. I like your spirit, baby. Thank you.
I like your spirit, baby. Thank you. Shall we vote?
Thank you. Shall we vote? I just wanted to call you
Shall we vote? I just wanted to call you tequila.
I just wanted to call you tequila. Yes!
Tequila. Yes! It's a yes for me.
Yes! It's a yes for me. Yes from me.
It's a yes for me. Yes from me. Yes from me.
Yes from me. Yes from me.
Yes from me. Okay.
Okay. Yeah!
Okay. Yeah! Whoo!
Yeah! Whoo! That was very church-y.
Whoo! That was very church-y.
That was very church-y. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Can I shake your hand?
Yeah. Yeah. Can I shake your hand? Yeah.
Can I shake your hand? Yeah. Come here.
Yeah. Come here. Oh...
Come here. Oh... come here, baby.
Oh... come here, baby. Beautiful.
Come here, baby. Beautiful. Hey, girl.
Beautiful. Hey, girl. You're so beautiful.
Hey, girl. You're so beautiful. Thank you.
You're so beautiful. Thank you. Thanks, tequila.
Thank you. Thanks, tequila. Thank you.
Thanks, tequila. Thank you. You're cute.
Thank you. You're cute. You're cute too.
You're cute. You're cute too. Bye, y'all.
You're cute too. Bye, y'all.
Bye, y'all. She got a set of lungs on
She got a set of lungs on her.
She got a set of lungs on her. Congratulations.
Her. Congratulations. Thank you!
Congratulations. Thank you! Hey! What's up?
Thank you! Hey! What's up? I didn't know that was you.
Hey! What's up? I didn't know that was you.
I didn't know that was you. I'm going to hollywood!
I'm going to hollywood! So tequila gets a taste of
I'm going to hollywood! So tequila
gets a taste of success as she gets the first
So tequila gets a taste of success
as she gets the first golden ticket to hollywood on
Success as she gets the first golden
ticket to hollywood on day two of salt lake city,
Golden ticket to hollywood on day
two of salt lake city, leaving the other contestants to
Day two of salt lake city, leaving
the other contestants to contemplate their own chances.
Leaving the other contestants to
contemplate their own chances. It can be hard, so give it my
Contemplate their own chances.
It can be hard, so give it my best.
It can be hard, so give it my best. It's all or nothin'.
Best. It's all or nothin'.
It's all or nothin'.
Yeah. What does that make you? An auditioner.
What does that make you? An auditioner. We are idol!
An auditioner. We are idol!
We are idol! My name's chase thornton.
My name's chase thornton. I'm from clearfield city, utah,
My name's chase thornton.
I'm from clearfield city, utah, and I'm 20 years old.
And I'm a male model and busser.
And I'm 20 years old. And I'm
a male model and busser. What kind of modeling?
And I'm a male model and busser.
What kind of modeling? Mostly runway.
What kind of modeling? Mostly runway. Right.
Mostly runway. Right. But I've done print and promo
Right. But I've done print and promo modeling too.
But I've done print and promo modeling too.
How psyched are you to be
Modeling too. How psyched are you to be singing tonight?
How psyched are you to be singing tonight? I'm so excited.
Singing tonight? I'm so excited. Everyone's so good.
I'm so excited. Everyone's so good. And you are too.
Everyone's so good. And you are too. We'll see.
And you are too. We'll see. Hearing, like, these different
We'll see. Hearing, like,
these different voices and different sounds
Hearing, like, these different voices
and different sounds coming out of these bodies, it's
Voices and different sounds coming out of these bodies,
it's insane, but I think I'm ready
Coming out of these bodies,
it's insane, but I think I'm ready for this.
Hi. Hi. How are ya?
Hi. How are ya? Good.
How are ya? Good. Good.
Good. Good. Hi.
Good. Hi. Hi.
Hi. Hi. What's your name?
Hi. What's your name? Chase.
What's your name? Chase. Chase...
Chase. Chase... thornton.
Chase... thornton. Chase thornton.
Thornton. Chase thornton. Chase thornton.
Chase thornton. Chase thornton. What do you do?
Chase thornton. What do you do? I'm a busser and a male
What do you do? I'm a busser and a male model.
I'm a busser and a male model. What sort of things do you
Model. What sort of things do you model?
What sort of things do you model? Mostly runway.
Model? Mostly runway. You model runways?
Mostly runway. You model runways? Mostly, yeah.
You model runways? Mostly, yeah. Are they heavy?
Mostly, yeah. Are they heavy? I model for runways.
Are they heavy? I model for runways.
I model for runways. No big deal.
No big deal. That's cool.
No big deal. That's cool. And what are you gonna sing
That's cool. And what are you gonna sing today?
And what are you gonna sing today? I'm gonna sing bruno mars,
Today? I'm gonna sing bruno mars, when I was your man.
I'm gonna sing bruno mars, when I was your man. Okay.
?Although it hurts
?I'll be the first
?To see that ?I was wrong ?Oh
?I was wrong ?Oh ?I know I'm probably
?Oh ?I know I'm probably ?Much too late
?I know I'm probably ?Much too late oh, stop.
?Much too late oh, stop. I'm not sure what key you're in,
Oh, stop. I'm not sure what key you're in, man.
I'm not sure what key you're in, man. I'm like, uh...
Man. I'm like, uh... for me, if you really want to
I'm like, uh... for me,
if you really want to sing, I would take lessons.
For me, if you really want to sing, I would take lessons. Okay.
Sing, I would take lessons. Okay. I don't know what pitch or
Okay. I don't know what pitch or key.
I don't know what pitch or key. The song was wandering
Key. The song was wandering everywhere.
The song was wandering everywhere. I could--I--
Everywhere. I could--I-- did it vary a lot?
I could--I-- did it vary a lot? Yes.
Did it vary a lot? Yes. Yeah.
Yes. Yeah. Ooh.
Yeah. Ooh. Yeah.
Ooh. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Okay. It's a no for me.
Okay. It's a no for me. Me too. Sorry.
It's a no for me. Me too. Sorry. I'm sorry, sweetie.
Me too. Sorry. I'm sorry, sweetie. Thank you, though.
I'm sorry, sweetie. Thank you, though. Thanks for coming, man.
Thank you, though. Thanks for coming, man. Thank you so much.
Thanks for coming, man. Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so much. Thank you. Hey, guys.
Thank you. Hey, guys. No go. No go.
Hey, guys. No go. No go. That was one of the weirdest
No go. No go. That was
one of the weirdest voices I've ever heard.
That was one of the weirdest
voices I've ever heard. You have to give him a little
Voices I've ever heard.
You have to give him a little bit of a chance.
You have to give him a little bit of a chance. What?
Bit of a chance. What? You were like, "Stop."
What? You were like, "Stop." I was like, "Let him sing a
You were like, "Stop." I was like, "Let him sing a little bit."
I was like, "Let him sing a little bit." Yeah, I agree.
Little bit." Yeah, I agree. You can tell.
Yeah, I agree. You can tell. No, you can tell.
You can tell. No, you can tell. I mean, I know you can tell.
No, you can tell. I mean, I know you can tell.
I mean, I know you can tell. ?
? I don't think it was nerves.
? I don't think it was nerves. I chose to make it a belt.
I don't think it was nerves. I chose
to make it a belt. They didn't like it, apparently.
I chose to make it a belt.
They didn't like it, apparently. Oh, my god.
Now it's time to put your
Idol knowledge to the test.
Which idol alum and teen choice
Award winner calls utah home?
Is it kris allen or david
Archuleta?
Get your answers out there using
The hashtags below.
And find out the result after
The break.
Choice award winner calls utah
Home?
The answer is david archuleta.
Good luck to you.
What'd they say?
They loved my voice, and they
They loved my voice, and they just said I'm not ready.
She's almost there.
Yeah, she's not ready.
Yeah, she's not ready. The 90% of what it takes to be
Yeah, she's not ready. The 90%
of what it takes to be a superstar is really a lot
The 90% of what it takes to be a
superstar is really a lot more than how talented you are.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
It's getting up at 4:00 in
It's getting up at 4:00 in the morning and doing 16
It's getting up at 4:00 in the
morning and doing 16 interviews before you go to a
The morning and doing 16 interviews
before you go to a photo shoot, before you go to a
Interviews before you go to a photo shoot,
before you go to a sound check, and then go on
Photo shoot, before you
go to a sound check, and then go on stage.
It's a no for me.
Me too.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Vocal fatigue, physical
Vocal fatigue, physical fatigue, mental fatigue, missing
Vocal fatigue, physical fatigue, mental fatigue,
missing family and friends, and...it's
Fatigue, mental fatigue, missing family and friends,
and...it's a lot of mental energy as well,
Family and friends, and...it's a
lot of mental energy as well, and emotional maturity.
A lot of mental energy as well,
and emotional maturity. So I don't know how on earth I
And emotional maturity. So I don't know how on earth I made it.
Hello.
Hi.
?And you may find
?That if you wait for her
?To come to you
?She'll come in time
?So remember, russian girl
?That you're the one ?That makes me laugh
?That you're the one ?That makes me laugh ?And without
?That makes me laugh ?And without ?Your witty sarcasm
?And without ?Your witty sarcasm ?This world would fall flat
Thank you.
Thank you. It's a no from me.
Thank you. It's a no from me. You're not quite ready.
I disagree.
I disagree. I'm gonna say yes.
No, guys. Sorry.
No, guys. Sorry. But it was a cool experience,
and it was fun meeting all of
But it was a cool experience, and it was fun meeting all of them.
You guys are crazy. Crazy.
We let the big one slip away?
I think you let a good one
I think you let a good one slip away.
When I started out, there was
A tv talent show...
I would like now to introduce
Keith urban, 16 years of age, a
New face.
I sang a song. ?I'm all out of love ?What am I without you
?I'm all out of love ?What
am I without you one of the judges was giving
?What am I without you one of
the judges was giving some constructive feedback.
Keith, what actually showing
Keith, what actually showing up in your voice is just some
Keith, what actually showing up
in your voice is just some immaturity, that's all.
But it didn't faze me 'cause
But it didn't faze me 'cause everyone's got an opinion, you
But it didn't faze me 'cause everyone's got an opinion, you know.
You have to do exercises.
You have to do exercises. Now, either you get to a teacher
You have to do exercises. Now,
either you get to a teacher or somebody like that who can
Now, either you get to a teacher or
somebody like that who can give you these intervals--
You got to know what to
You got to know what to discard 'cause we're just giving
You got to know what to discard
'cause we're just giving our opinion, and I always say,
Discard 'cause we're just giving our opinion,
and I always say, "It's just my opinion.
Our opinion, and I always say,
"It's just my opinion. I mean, what I say you should
"It's just my opinion. I mean,
what I say you should change, harry may say, 'that's
I mean, what I say you should change,
harry may say, 'that's what I love about you, don't
Change, harry may say,
'that's what I love about you, don't change that at all.'"
What I love about you, don't change that at all.'"
That can start helping you come
Change that at all.'" That
can start helping you come to life as an artist.
Would I have auditioned?
Maybe.
Maybe if it was around when I
Was comin' up, but I don't know.
From boogie-down bronx,
Jennifer lopez.
I don't know if I would have,
you know--if that would have been my journey.
You know--if that would have been my journey.
I think my journey was meant to
Been my journey. I think my
journey was meant to be in the way that it was.
?
? I'm glad there was no american
? I'm glad there was no american idol when I started out
I'm glad there was no american
idol when I started out because I promise you I
Idol when I started out
because I promise you I wouldn't have won.
I don't think I would have
Auditioned because of that.
There is no doubt that this fifth-grade student has a
There is no doubt that this
fifth-grade student has a bright musical career ahead of
Fifth-grade student has a bright musical career ahead of him.
Which is why it's amazing to
Which is why it's amazing to me when I see these contestants
Which is why it's amazing to me
when I see these contestants come in and they audition.
Me when I see these
contestants come in and they audition. It's hard.
Do you think you'll be a
Do you think you'll be a professional musician?
If I practice hard enough.
If I practice hard enough. But now we need american idol.
If I practice hard enough. But now
we need american idol. It is the way that new music
But now we need american idol.
It is the way that new music gets heard.
72800, please come forward.
Gets heard. 72800, please come forward. Go, emily.
Go, emily. It'll be such a big deal for
Go, emily. It'll be such a
big deal for me if I get that golden ticket.
It'll be such a big deal for me if I
get that golden ticket. I've been dreaming about being
Me if I get that golden ticket.
I've been dreaming about being on american idol ever since I
I've been dreaming about being on
american idol ever since I knew what the show was, so it
On american idol ever since I knew what the show was,
so it would be really awesome if I got
Knew what the show was,
so it would be really awesome if I got it.
Hi.
Hey.
How's it goin'?
Good. How are you?
I like that mustard color.
Thank you very much.
Is that one of your favorite
Is that one of your favorite colors?
I mean, I can't say it is,
I mean, I can't say it is, but it matches the skirt, so I
but it matches the skirt, so I went with it.
Yeah, it looks good.
Yeah, it looks good. So what do you have for us
Yeah, it looks good. So what do you have for us today?
So what do you have for us today? What are you gonna sing?
I'll be singing valerie by
I'll be singing valerie by amy winehouse.
I'll be singing valerie cool.
?Well, sometimes
?I go out by myself
?And I look across the water
?
?Well since I've come on home ?Well,
my body's been a mess ?And I miss that ginger hair
?Well, my body's been a mess
?And I miss that ginger hair ?And the way
?And I miss that ginger hair ?And the way ?You like to dress
?And the way ?You like to dress ?Won't you come on over
?You like to dress ?Won't you come on over ?Start making a fool
?Won't you come on over ?Start making a fool ?Out of me
?Start making a fool ?Out of me ?Why don't you
?Out of me ?Why don't you ?Come on over, valerie
Cool.
Cool. Your voice is great, baby.
Cool. Your voice is great, baby. Really, really good.
Thank you so much.
I feel like you're the real
I feel like you're the real thing.
I feel like you're the real thing. I really feel--I feel like
Thing. I really feel--I feel like it's a natural, natural thing
I really feel--I feel like it's a natural,
natural thing for you to sing and play that
It's a natural,
natural thing for you to sing and play that guitar.
Thank you.
You know, when I was
You know, when I was listening to you, I'm thinking,
You know, when I was listening to you,
I'm thinking, "This is gonna be a really good
Listening to you, I'm thinking,
"This is gonna be a really good year on american idol."
"This is gonna be a really
good year on american idol." It's a yes for me.
Year on american idol." It's a yes for me. Thank you.
It's a yes for me. Thank you. I say it's definitely worth
Thank you. I say it's definitely worth another look.
I say it's definitely worth another look. I say yes too, emily.
Another look. I say yes too, emily. Thank you so much.
I say yes too, emily. Thank you so much. Oh, my goodness.
Thank you so much. Oh, my goodness. Congratulations!
Oh, my goodness. Congratulations!
Congratulations! Do you have any mustard
Do you have any mustard clothing, harry?
Do you have any mustard clothing, harry? Mustard underwear?
Clothing, harry? Mustard underwear? Yeah.
Mustard underwear? Yeah. Well, they started off white.
Yeah. Well, they started off white. So when they--
Well, they started off white. So when they--
So when they-- you are so--
You are so-- and that being said, has salt
You are so-- and that being said,
has salt lake city got itself in a
And that being said, has salt lake city got itself in a groove?
Lake city got itself in a groove? Oh, yeah.
Groove? Oh, yeah. We shall see.
Oh, yeah. We shall see.
We shall see. My name is dexter roberts.
My name is dexter roberts. I'm 22 years old.
My name is dexter roberts.
I'm 22 years old. I'm from fayette, alabama.
I'm 22 years old. I'm from fayette,
alabama. What you do back there in
I'm from fayette, alabama. What you do back there in alabama?
What you do back there in alabama? I do everything, man.
Alabama? I do everything, man. Back in fayette, I'm a farmhand,
I do everything, man. Back in fayette,
I'm a farmhand, I drive a tractor almost all
Back in fayette, I'm a farmhand,
I drive a tractor almost all day, and I train dogs too.
I drive a tractor almost all day,
and I train dogs too. I train 'em to hunt ducks.
Day, and I train dogs too. I
train 'em to hunt ducks. And this right here is my
I train 'em to hunt ducks.
And this right here is my mallard call.
I can actually do a duck call
Mallard call. I can actually do a duck call with my mouth.
How you doing, man? Doin' good, doin' good, doin' good.
Doin' good, doin' good, doin' good. What's your name?
Good. What's your name? How are you all?
What's your name? How are you all? Dexter roberts.
How are you all? Dexter roberts. Dexter roberts.
Dexter roberts. Dexter roberts. Yes, sir.
Dexter roberts. Yes, sir. I'm from fayette, alabama.
Yes, sir. I'm from fayette, alabama. Is that a stage name?
I'm from fayette, alabama.
Is that a stage name? That's your real name?
Is that a stage name? That's your real name? That's my real name.
That's your real name? That's my real name. That's a good name.
That's my real name. That's a good name. It's crazy.
That's a good name. It's crazy. Thank you.
It's crazy. Thank you. And what's the bbff kennels
Thank you. And what's the bbff kennels hat about?
And what's the bbff kennels hat about? It's one of my friends.
Hat about? It's one of my friends. I train dogs.
It's one of my friends. I train dogs.
What's the "Bbff" Stand for?
I train dogs. What's the "Bbff" Stand for?
Bang, bang, flop, flop.
What's the "Bbff" Stand for? Bang, bang, flop, flop.
Bang, bang, flop, flop. Speaking of harry's
Speaking of harry's concerts--
Speaking of harry's concerts-- yeah.
Concerts-- yeah.
Yeah. What are you gonna sing for
What are you gonna sing for us today, dexter?
What are you gonna sing for us today,
dexter? I'm gonna sing I like to
Us today, dexter? I'm gonna sing I like to drive by casey james.
I'm gonna sing I like to drive okay.
?
?I don't care
?If it's a highway
?Or a dirty country road
?I don't know ?If I'm leavin' ?Or goin' home
?If I'm leavin' ?Or goin' home ?I don't know if it's
?Or goin' home ?I don't know if it's ?The sound
?I don't know if it's ?The sound ?Of that tuned-up radio
?The sound ?Of that tuned-up radio ?I don't know if
?Of that tuned-up radio ?I don't know if ?It's the smell
?I don't know if ?It's the smell ?Of that burnin' smoke
?It's the smell ?Of that burnin' smoke ?So here I go, whoa
?Of that burnin' smoke ?So here I go, whoa ?'cause I'm headed out
?So here I go, whoa ?'cause I'm headed out ?To nowhere
?'cause I'm headed out ?To nowhere ?Like a bullet from a gun
?To nowhere ?Like a bullet from a gun ?Puttin' miles on me
?Like a bullet from a gun ?Puttin' miles on me ?And my wheels
?Puttin' miles on me ?And my wheels ?Stop rolling on
?And my wheels ?Stop rolling on ?Slide on over, baby
?Stop rolling on ?Slide on over,
baby ?And I'll take you for a ride
?Slide on over, baby ?And I'll
take you for a ride ?'cause I just like to drive
Right on. Cool.
Thank you.
Who do you listen to?
Who do you listen to? What singers have influenced
Who do you listen to? What singers have influenced you?
I listen to you a lot.
Thank you.
But I listen to--I listen
But I listen to--I listen to brett eldrege, florida
But I listen to--I listen to brett eldrege,
florida georgia line and...
Huh.
Listen to a lot of blues
Listen to a lot of blues stuff.
Listen to a lot of blues stuff. I listen to all kinds of music.
Stuff. I listen to all kinds of music. I love music.
I like the mix of all those
I like the mix of all those things in your voice.
Thank you.
I can hear the blues
I can hear the blues influence...
Thank you.
And the bluegrass, country,
And the bluegrass, country, all of it in there.
Thank you.
I loved when you were
I loved when you were playing, I was like, wait a
I loved when you were playing, I was like, wait a minute.
Playing, I was like, wait a minute. It's kinda like doin' this
Minute. It's kinda like doin' this thing the way he was playing
It's kinda like doin' this
thing the way he was playing and singing.
Thing the way he was playing and singing. You know what I mean?
And singing. You know what I mean? There was something about it
You know what I mean? There was
something about it that was off the rhythm to me.
There was something about it that was
off the rhythm to me. I was almost gonna look at you
That was off the rhythm to me. I
was almost gonna look at you and say--'cause I didn't
I was almost gonna look at you
and say--'cause I didn't know the song--I was like,
And say--'cause I didn't know
the song--I was like, "Is he off the rhythm?
Know the song--I was like, "Is he off the rhythm?
Or is he just playing, and it's
"Is he off the rhythm? Or is he just playing,
and it's really amazing right now?"
He was just groovin'.
Yeah.
Thank you.
By the way, I did think that
By the way, I did think that too.
By the way, I did think that too. But that's what it felt like to
Too. But that's what it felt like to me.
But that's what it felt like to me. It was really impressive.
Thank you.
You just seem like the kinda
You just seem like the kinda guy who sings to get through the
You just seem like the
kinda guy who sings to get through the day.
Guy who sings to get through the day.
And you happen to sing well and
Day. And you happen to sing well and play well.
Thank you.
And I love the idea of that.
I just think it's--you
I just think it's--you know, it sounds very authentic
I just think it's--you know, it sounds very authentic to me.
I'm gonna say yes.
Yes!
I'm gonna say yes too.
Thank you!
Yes for me too.
Yeah!
All right.
Thank you.
Dexter!
Good to meet you, man.
Yeah, dex.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah, man, nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I see somethin'.
To hollywood, boys!
Yes!
Congratulations, man.
Thank you. Thank you.
Good job in there.
I guess 'cause I don't play,
I guess 'cause I don't play, it seems like a miracle to me.
I guess 'cause I don't play, it
seems like a miracle to me. Do you know what I mean?
It seems like a miracle to me. Do
you know what I mean? When you can play on one beat...
It is--it's cool.
And sing on the other beat.
Harry's good at that.
Keith's pretty darn good at
Keith's pretty darn good at it too.
I guess it's like dancing a
I guess it's like dancing a little bit, when you're dancing,
I guess it's like dancing a little bit,
when you're dancing, doing one thing and singing.
It's exactly like that.
Why do you think they put you
Why do you think they put you through?
Because I've worked hard, and
Because I've worked hard, and I've paid my dues, and I think
Because I've worked hard, and I've paid my dues,
and I think this is my shot.
When you have a completely open mind
and a performer comes in and pours their heart out...
?At last
?Mm
?Since my love
And each moment is treated individually.
?Life is like a song
?Life is like a song ?Oh yeah
I like your voice.
Thank you.
I feel like, gosh, you just
I feel like, gosh, you just need a little more time, baby.
Can I sing another song for
Can I sing another song for you?
No, I don't think so.
No, I don't think so. I disagree with keith.
Do you?
I think you could do really
I think you could do really great.
I like the whole concept of
I like the whole concept of diamond in the rough.
Yeah.
But there was too much rough.
Okay.
I think you need a little bit
I think you need a little bit more time.
I don't think so.
I don't think so. Okay.
I don't think so. Okay. I think we should vote.
It's a no for me.
Okay.
I'm gonna say yes.
And it's a no for me.
And it's a no for me. I'm sorry.
Oh...
Thank you, guys.
Baby, come back again, huh?
Okay. Thanks.
Yeah, you bet, ally.
Hopefully, our next
Hopefully, our next contestant can catch the judges'
Hopefully, our next contestant can catch the judges' attention.
My name is briston maroney.
My name is briston maroney. I'm 15 years old.
I'm from knoxville, tennessee.
And I am a sophomore in high
School.
Sit. Sit. Music in my family is really number one priority.
Music in my family is really
number one priority. Music is family for us.
Number one priority. Music is family for us.
It started off with my great,
Music is family for us. It
started off with my great, great grandfather was a
It started off with my great,
great grandfather was a recording artist in nashville.
Great grandfather was a recording
artist in nashville. The guitar that I play was his,
Recording artist in nashville.
The guitar that I play was his, and it's been passed down
The guitar that I play was his,
and it's been passed down through each generation in my
And it's been passed down through each generation in my family.
Through each generation in my family. Playing this guitar, I feel
Family. Playing this guitar, I feel everything that it's been
Playing this guitar, I feel everything that it's been through.
Everything that it's been through.
As crazy as that sounds, I feel
Through. As crazy as that sounds,
I feel like it's seen a lot, and the
As crazy as that sounds, I feel like it's seen a lot,
and the stories come out when it's
Like it's seen a lot, and the stories come out when it's played.
Stories come out when it's played.
Being so young and being able to
Played. Being so young and
being able to have this shot means a lot.
Being so young and being able to have
this shot means a lot. And it could really be the kick
Have this shot means a lot. And it
could really be the kick start to take me places that
And it could really be the kick
start to take me places that I've dreamed of going.
Start to take me places that I've dreamed of going. Hello.
Hello.
How are ya?
Good. How are you?
Doing excellent.
Doing excellent. Thank you very much.
Excellent. What's your name?
I'm briston maroney.
Hi, briston.
Hi.
How old are you?
I'm 15.
Oh, you're just a little
Oh, you're just a little baby.
Wow!
Yes, ma'am.
With a cool vintage gibson.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. It's my grandfather's.
Where you from?
Knoxville, tennessee.
How long you been playing?
A long time.
A long time?
Five or six years.
Who taught you?
My father started me off, and
My father started me off, and just kinda went from there.
So your dad plays?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am. I've got a long, long line of
Yes, ma'am. I've got a long, long line of music, actually.
I've got a long, long line of music,
actually. This guitar belonged to my great
Music, actually. This guitar belonged to my great grandfather.
Mm.
Oh, wow!
Great grandfather.
Yes. He was in nashville.
Yes. He was in nashville. One of those guys.
That is so cool.
And just passed down to--
So musical family?
Definitely. Yes, ma'am.
What did he do in--was he
What did he do in--was he a recording artist?
Yes, sir, he was a recording
Yes, sir, he was a recording artist, yeah.
So what was his name?
Grandpa.
That's all right.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure. I don't know his first name, to
I'm not sure. I don't know his first name, to be honest.
Okay, baby.
Okay, baby. What are you gonna sing?
Can't always get what you
Can't always get what you want.
Can't always get what you want. Okay.
Want. Okay. Rolling stones.
Okay. Rolling stones. Wow. Song choices.
?
?I saw her today
?At the reception
So unique.
?A glass of wine ?In her hand ?And I knew she would
?In her hand ?And I knew she would ?Make the connection
?And I knew she would ?Make the connection ?At her feet stood
?Make the connection ?At her feet stood ?A footloose man
?At her feet stood ?A footloose man ?You can't always
?A footloose man ?You can't always ?Get what you want
?You can't always ?Get what you want ?You can't always
?Get what you want ?You can't always ?Get what you want
?You can't always ?Get what you want whoo!
?Get what you want whoo! Mm.
Whoo! Mm. ?You can't always
Mm. ?You can't always ?Get what you want
?You can't always ?Get what you want ?But if you try sometimes
?Get what you want ?But if you try sometimes ?You just might find
?But if you try sometimes
?You just might find ?You get what you need
?You just might find ?You get what you need wow, baby!
?You get what you need wow, baby! Thank you.
Wow, baby! Thank you. You have such a unique voice.
Thank you. You have such a unique voice.
You know, it's not everybody
You have such a unique voice. You know,
it's not everybody gonna come in here and sound
You know, it's not everybody
gonna come in here and sound like that.
Gonna come in here and sound like that. No.
Like that. No. And you're 15 years old.
No. And you're 15 years old. Yes, ma'am.
And you're 15 years old. Yes, ma'am. Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am. Thank you very much. It's like--
Thank you very much. It's like-- I'm flattered.
It's like-- I'm flattered. Yeah, this is good.
I'm flattered. Yeah, this is good. The only thing is that very
Yeah, this is good. The only
thing is that very affected style of singing--
The only thing is that very affected
style of singing-- I would hope that there'd be
Affected style of singing-- I would
hope that there'd be other colors that come out from
I would hope that there'd
be other colors that come out from there.
Other colors that come out from there. Yes, sir. Definitely.
There. Yes, sir. Definitely. I understand.
Yes, sir. Definitely. I understand. But in the midst of that, I
I understand. But in the midst of that,
I would hope that you don't also
But in the midst of that, I would
hope that you don't also lose yourself 'cause you've got
Would hope that you don't also lose
yourself 'cause you've got something really cool in there
Lose yourself 'cause you've
got something really cool in there too, man.
Something really cool in there too, man. Thank you very much.
Too, man. Thank you very much. I understand.
Thank you very much. I understand. Yeah, I agree with both
I understand. Yeah, I agree with both jennifer and keith.
Yeah, I agree with both jennifer and keith.
I'm just worried you're gonna
Jennifer and keith. I'm
just worried you're gonna lose your voice, bro.
I'm just worried you're gonna lose your voice,
bro. Yes, sir. I understand.
Lose your voice, bro. Yes,
sir. I understand. But that's your sound.
Yes, sir. I understand. But that's your sound.
It sounds a lot worse than it
But that's your sound.
It sounds a lot worse than it feels, I promise.
Feels, I promise. Shall we vote?
Shall we vote? Hmm.
Shall we vote? Hmm. Dad, how are you feeling?
Hmm. Dad, how are you feeling? I'm nervous. Nervous for him.
Dad, how are you feeling? I'm nervous.
Nervous for him. I just hope that his hard work
I'm nervous. Nervous for him. I
just hope that his hard work and dedication pays of.
I just hope that his hard work and dedication pays of. Thank you.
And dedication pays of. Thank you. Thanks for coming, man.
Thank you. Thanks for coming, man. Thank you.
Thanks for coming, man. Thank you. Thank you, guys.
Thank you. Thank you, guys. It's a pleasure.
Thank you, guys. It's a pleasure.
It's a pleasure. ?
You got it? Congratulations. Great job.
Congratulations. Great job. Thank you.
Great job. Thank you. Let's go tell everybody.
Thank you. Let's go tell everybody. Hollywood week when the
Let's go tell everybody.
Hollywood week when the singer who comes out like that
Hollywood week when the singer who
comes out like that and everybody just hushes and
Singer who comes out like
that and everybody just hushes and kinda goes...
And everybody just hushes and kinda goes... that's great.
Kinda goes... that's great. "Wow."
That's great. "Wow." I hope he's that guy.
"Wow." I hope he's that guy. Come on in here.
I hope he's that guy. Come on in here.
Come on in here.
Who are these people?
Who are these people? Like, that guy is some sophomore
Who are these people? Like,
that guy is some sophomore in high school.
Like, that guy is some sophomore in high school. Crazy.
In high school. Crazy. Who are these people?
Crazy. Who are these people? 73351, come on up.
Who are these people? 73351,
come on up. You brought a few people with
73351, come on up. You brought a few people with you.
You brought a few people with you. Yes.
You. Yes. Basically, like, 50 people.
Yes. Basically, like, 50 people. This is a family affair.
Basically, like, 50 people. This is a family affair. Yes.
This is a family affair. Yes. What's your name?
Yes. What's your name? My name is leia lotulelei,
What's your name? My name is leia lotulelei,
but they call me "Fish."
My name is leia lotulelei, but they call me "Fish." Fish.
But they call me "Fish." Fish. Fish?
Fish. Fish? I'm sabrina lentini, and I am
Fish? I'm sabrina lentini, and I am 15 years old.
I'm sabrina lentini, and I am 15 years old. 15.
15 years old. 15. Yeah.
15. Yeah. Wow!
Yeah. Wow! That's crazy.
Wow! That's crazy. That's just crazy.
That's crazy. That's just crazy. My name is carson henline.
That's just crazy. My name is carson henline.
What are you looking at,
My name is carson henline. What are you looking at, baby?
What are you looking at, baby? This is, like, legit.
Baby? This is, like, legit. Yeah.
This is, like, legit. Yeah. Oh, it's legit.
Yeah. Oh, it's legit. In my eighth-grade yearbook,
Oh, it's legit. In my eighth-grade yearbook,
I was voted most likely to be
In my eighth-grade yearbook, I was
voted most likely to be on american idol, and here I am.
I was voted most likely to be on american idol, and here I am.
?You know we're heading
?Separate ways
?And it feels like
?I am just too close
?To love you
?I came across a place
?In the middle of nowhere
?With a big black horse
?And a cherry tree
?Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Yes?
Are you excited?
Yes.
Yeah?
I am.
Your grandson "Fish" In
Your grandson "Fish" In there singing.
You know, he's singing right
There singing. You know, he's singing right now.
Oh!
?They say she's
?In the class a team
?Stuck in her daydream ?Been
this way since 18 ?But lately her face seems
Mm.
?Slowly sinking wasting
Great job.
For me, it wasn't strong
For me, it wasn't strong enough today.
I disagree.
I've just been waiting 13
I've just been waiting 13 years to audition for this
I've just been waiting 13 years
to audition for this 'cause this is my dream.
Years to audition for this 'cause this is my dream.
I thought it was really good.
It's a no for me.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say yes. It's up to you, keith.
Oh, my god.
Harry said no, but--
But you know what?
But you know what? Two yeses equal a golden
But you know what? Two yeses equal a golden ticket.
Two yeses equal a golden ticket. Congratulations.
I'm sorry, baby. Not today.
I'm sorry, baby. Not today. Okay?
It's okay.
Thank you, though.
Just come back next year and do
Just come back next year and do my best.
Still young.
Still young. Got some time to grow.
I think we should vote.
I think we should vote. There's a lot of people waiting.
It's a yes for me.
Yes for me.
It's a yes.
Yeah!
Does anyone have any
Does anyone have any earplugs?
Does anyone have any earplugs? It's about to get really loud
Earplugs? It's about to get really loud out there.
It's about to get really loud out there. Oh, here it comes.
Yes, I'm listening.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Five, four, three, two, one. Hey, wait.
Hey, wait. That wasn't 30 people.
Whoo!
That was like a golf clap.
That was like two people.
Yeah.
Hi.
How's it going?
It's different with
Everybody.
You want to say, "Oh, as soon as
They walk in, I know."
And sometimes that does happen.
Sometimes nerves take over in that moment.
You know, they come in, all
That moment. You know, they come in,
all those lights are shining at
You know, they come in, all those
lights are shining at them, the three of us are
Those lights are shining at them,
the three of us are sitting there.
Them, the three of us are sitting there.
Some people, it takes 'em a
Sitting there. Some people, it takes 'em a minute.
Some people, it takes 'em a minute.
You can kinda see a little bit
Minute. You can kinda see
a little bit of something, and then all of a
You can kinda see a little bit of something,
and then all of a sudden something will happen.
Hey, what's going on?
Hi.
What's your name?
I'm johnny.
Johnny who?
Newcomb.
Johnny newcomb.
Johnny newcomb. What are you gonna play for us?
Last kiss by pearl jam.
Last kiss all right, let's get after
Last kiss all right, let's get after it.
?Oh where oh where
?Can my baby be
?The lord took her
Did you expect that?
So I've got to be good
So I've got to be good ?So I can see my baby
So I've got to be good ?So
I can see my baby ?When I leave this world
Nice.
When eddie vedder sings, I--
When eddie vedder sings, I-- that really is eddie vedder.
When eddie vedder sings, I-- that
really is eddie vedder. I just don't believe that's your
That really is eddie vedder.
I just don't believe that's your voice.
I just don't believe that's your voice. I think you're highly
Voice. I think you're highly impressionable because of your
I think you're highly impressionable
because of your age, which is--you have to be.
Impressionable because of your age,
which is--you have to be. I think you're doing the right
Age, which is--you have to be.
I think you're doing the right thing.
You're emulating your heroes.
Thing. You're emulating your heroes. But I think you're--it's a
But I think you're--it's a little premature for you to be
But I think you're--it's a little
premature for you to be in american idol right now.
Little premature for you to
be in american idol yeah, I think the same thing,
In american idol yeah, I think the same thing, johnny.
Yeah, I think the same thing, johnny. My advice always is, like,
Johnny. My advice always is,
like, perhaps sometimes you listen to
My advice always is, like,
perhaps sometimes you listen to a lot of different people, and
Perhaps sometimes you listen to a lot
of different people, and you start bringing in elements
A lot of different people, and you
start bringing in elements to create your own thing.
You start bringing in elements
to create your own thing. I mean, that can work.
To create your own thing. I mean,
that can work. I'm just saying otherwise,
I mean, that can work. I'm just saying otherwise,
you're gonna end up sounding too
I'm just saying otherwise,
you're gonna end up sounding too derivative of somebody.
Yeah.
Yeah. No, I think it's impressive that
Yeah. No, I think it's impressive that you sing like that.
No, I think it's impressive that
you sing like that. I think what I was waiting for
You sing like that. I think
what I was waiting for was to see more of a range.
Could I try one more?
Could I try one more? I think I could change your
Could I try one more? I think I could change your mind.
Change my mind. Go ahead.
?
? ?Never would have hitchhiked
? ?Never would have hitchhiked ?To birmingham
?Never would have hitchhiked ?To birmingham ?If it hadn't been
?To birmingham ?If it hadn't been ?For love
?If it hadn't been ?For love ?Never would have run
?For love ?Never would have run ?Through the blinding rain
?Never would have run
?Through the blinding rain ?Without one dollar
?Through the blinding rain ?Without one dollar ?To my name
?Without one dollar ?To my name ?If it hadn't been
?To my name ?If it hadn't been ?If it hadn't been
?If it hadn't been ?If it hadn't been ?For love
?If it hadn't been ?For love ?Four cold walls
?For love ?Four cold walls ?Without parole
I think he's too good to say
I think he's too good to say no to.
?Oh, lord, have mercy
He's too good at it to say no
He's too good at it to say no to.
You know what?
You know what? You did change my mind.
What?
Because you're too good at
Because you're too good at what you're doing to say no to.
Because you're too good at what
you're doing to say no to. So it's a yes for me.
I think you look really
I think you look really scared, and it's more than
I think you look really scared, and it's more than nerves.
Scared, and it's more than nerves. I just don't think you've had
Nerves. I just don't think you've had enough experience playing.
I just don't think you've had
enough experience playing. And I still stick to what I
Enough experience playing. And I still stick to what I said.
And I still stick to what I said. I think it's derivative, which
Said. I think it's derivative, which is fine, but I don't think
I think it's derivative, which is fine,
but I don't think you're ready yet, so it's a no
Is fine, but I don't think you're ready yet, so it's a no for me.
It's up to you, keith.
Aw!
To crush this kid's dreams.
Man! What?
Or to let him through.
Or to let him through. It's up to you.
You know what?
You know what? If you have a real dream, it's
You know what? If you have a real dream, it's un-crushable.
If you have a real dream, it's un-crushable.
I just want everyone to hear
Un-crushable. I just want everyone to hear that clearly.
I just want everyone to hear that clearly. Um...
One more shot.
It's a yes for me, johnny.
Yay!
Thank you so much.
Bring it in hollywood, man!
Hollywood!
You've got to bring it.
Got to loosen up.
Can I shake y'all's hands?
Absolutely.
You got to loosen up, because
You got to loosen up, because all we have--the music is
You got to loosen up, because all
we have--the music is there, the lyrics are there.
All we have--the music is there,
the lyrics are there. All we bring to it is feeling,
There, the lyrics are there.
All we bring to it is feeling, as a singer.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
You're welcome. If you don't have that, you have
You're welcome. If you don't have that, you have nothing.
He's comin'.
He's comin'. You ready?
Yeah, baby!
Yeah, baby! It's a celebration!
Yes, it is.
Yes, it is. You did it.
I almost didn't get through,
I almost didn't get through, but--
But you did.
You got to get it together,
You got to get it together, whatever they told you, man.
Next.
I would eat a box of oreos...
You sound like a dentist.
Just to go to the dentist and
Just to go to the dentist and have you clean my teeth.
It's business.
If that's what my dentist
If that's what my dentist looked like, I'd eat a box of
If that's what my dentist looked like,
I'd eat a box of oreos just to go to the dentist
Looked like, I'd eat a box of oreos
just to go to the dentist and have you clean my teeth.
Absolutely.
If that's what my dentist
If that's what my dentist looked like.
Every time.
I'd eat a box of oreos.
You'd rip them out, actually.
Yes. Absolutely.
You'd be pulling your own
You'd be pulling your own teeth.
Hello, sweet pea.
Hello.
Hi, baby.
Hi.
Hi. I'm kimberly toste.
So have you performed before?
I trained in opera.
Okay.
For many years.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing barracuda by
I'm gonna sing barracuda by heart.
I'm gonna sing barracuda fantastic.
Kickin' it old school.
Yeah.
?No right no wrong
?No right no wrong ?Selling a song
?No right no wrong ?Selling a song ?A name
Wow!
?Whisper game
?Whisper game ?And if the real thing
?Whisper game ?And if the real thing ?Don't do the trick
?And if the real thing ?Don't do the trick ?You better make up
?Don't do the trick ?You better make up ?Something quick
?You better make up ?Something quick ?You're gonna burn burn
?Something quick ?You're gonna burn burn ?Burn burn
?You're gonna burn burn ?Burn burn ?Burn it to the wick
?Burn burn ?Burn it to the wick ?Oh barracuda
Okay.
Okay. Barracuda, not so much.
Okay. Barracuda, I really admire the fact that
Barracuda, I really admire
the fact that you said, "I'm gonna audition
I really admire the fact that you said,
"I'm gonna audition for american idol."
You said, "I'm gonna audition for american idol." Yeah.
For american idol." Yeah. And it's that type of spirit
Yeah. And it's that type
of spirit that will make you successful in
And it's that type of spirit that
will make you successful in what I think all three of us
That will make you successful in what
I think all three of us believe, which is the world of
What I think all three of us believe,
which is the world of probably opera.
Believe, which is the world of probably opera. I have to say no.
Probably opera. I have to say no. Oh, please.
I have to say no. Oh, please. It's a no for me too,
Oh, please. It's a no for me too, sweetie.
It's a no for me too, sweetie. Yeah, it's a no for me.
Sweetie. Yeah, it's a no for me. Thank you.
Yeah, it's a no for me. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you. She hates you.
Thank you. She hates you. That was off the hook.
She hates you. That was off the hook. Loud, man.
That was off the hook. Loud, man. She hates me?
Loud, man. She hates me? She hates you.
She hates me? She hates you. That's all right.
She hates you. That's all right. It was so loud. Like, bzz.
That's all right. It was so loud.
Like, bzz. I'm like, "Man, she's causing
It was so loud. Like, bzz. I'm like, "Man, she's causing damage.
I'm like, "Man, she's causing damage. I could blow a gasket up in
Damage. I could blow a gasket up in here."
I could blow a gasket up in here." I almost lost a filling.
Here." I almost lost a filling. Yeah, yeah.
I almost lost a filling. Yeah, yeah. I want the judges to feel
Yeah, yeah. I want the
judges to feel that I'm not just another person
I want the judges to feel that I'm
not just another person walking through that door.
That I'm not just another person
walking through that door. It would be really cool to
Walking through that door. It would
be really cool to get validation from people that
It would be really cool to get
validation from people that live it every day.
Get validation from people that live it every day.
If I don't make it, I'm gonna
Live it every day. If I don't make it,
I'm gonna take their advice, and then I'm
If I don't make it, I'm gonna take their advice,
and then I'm gonna do the best that I can no
Take their advice, and then
I'm gonna do the best that I can no matter what.
Gonna do the best that I can no matter what.
The best piece of advice
Matter what. The best piece of advice you've ever been given.
you've ever been given. My mom told me not to be a
You've ever been given. My mom told me not to be a baby.
My mom told me not to be a baby. I called her when I was doing my
Baby. I called her when I was doing my first job, and I cried.
I called her when I was doing my first job,
and I cried. I was like, you know, "I'm the
First job, and I cried. I was like,
you know, "I'm the only one without a solo."
I was like, you know, "I'm the only
one without a solo." And she was like, "Don't ever
Only one without a solo." And she was like,
"Don't ever call me crying.
And she was like, "Don't ever call me crying.
That's the business you chose.
Call me crying. That's the
business you chose. You better toughen up."
That's the business you chose. You better toughen up." Wow.
You better toughen up." Wow. And I was like, "Okay.
Wow. And I was like, "Okay. Bye, mom."
And I was like, "Okay. Bye, mom." I hope that the judges see
Bye, mom." I hope that the
judges see the raw potential that I have.
I hope that the judges see the raw
potential that I have. That's why I came on american
The raw potential that I have.
That's why I came on american idol this year.
That's why I came on american idol how's it going?
Idol hi.
It's good.
It's good. How are you guys?
Good. Good. What's your name?
Carmen. Carmen delgina.
Carmen. Okay.
Carmen. Okay. Do you want to make a career out
Carmen. Okay. Do you want to make a career out of this?
Yeah, I definitely want to be
Yeah, I definitely want to be an entertainer.
Does that run in your family?
Yeah. My dad is wonder mike.
From the sugarhill gang?
Yeah.
Oh, my god! Are you kidding?
Everybody make some noise!
Everybody make some noise! ?I said hip hop
?I said hip hop ?The hippie to the hippie
?I said hip hop ?The hippie to the hippie ?The hip hip hop
?The hippie to the hippie
?The hip hip hop ?And you don't stop a rockin'
Music definitely runs in my
Music definitely runs in my family.
Music definitely runs in my family. ?Now what you hear
Family. ?Now what you hear ?Is not a test
?Now what you hear ?Is not a test ?I'm rappin' to the beat
?Is not a test ?I'm rappin'
to the beat to me, you know, he was never
?I'm rappin' to the beat to me,
you know, he was never wonder mike.
To me, you know, he was never wonder mike. He was just dad.
Wonder mike. He was just dad. But having a rap legend as my
He was just dad. But having a
rap legend as my father has always inspired me to
But having a rap legend as my father
has always inspired me to follow my dreams of being a
Father has always inspired me
to follow my dreams of being a professional singer.
I remember the first time I
I remember the first time I heard that song, it was like it
I remember the first time I heard that song,
it was like it changed my life.
Really?
Are you guys pretty tight?
Yeah, I love my dad.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Is he proud of you for being
Mm-hmm. Is he proud of you for being here today?
Is he proud of you for being here today?
Is this what he wants you to do?
Is he here?
He is here.
Still got the moves?
Yeah.
Yeah. Ah, what.
Yeah, check it.
Okay, let's get to it.
?Sometimes I feel
?I've got to
?Run away ?I've got to ?Get away
?I've got to ?Get away ?From the pain you drove
?Get away ?From the pain you drove ?In the heart of me
?From the pain you drove ?In the heart of me ?The love we share
?In the heart of me ?The love we share ?Seems to go nowhere
?The love we share ?Seems to go nowhere ?And I've lost my life
?Seems to go nowhere ?And I've lost my life ?For I toss and turn
?And I've lost my life
?For I toss and turn ?I can't sleep at night
Thank you. Thank you.
Mm.
Boy, I wish I could make
Boy, I wish I could make people be quiet in my house when
Boy, I wish I could make people
be quiet in my house when I raise my hand like that.
People be quiet in my house
when I raise my hand like that. It never works.
I raise my hand like that. It never works. I try all the time.
It never works. I try all the time. That was amazing.
I try all the time. That was amazing. I felt very powerful.
Here's what I think.
Here's what I think. I think you're a talented young
Here's what I think. I think
you're a talented young woman, but your vocals I don't
I think you're a talented young woman,
but your vocals I don't think are strong enough to get
Woman, but your vocals I don't
think are strong enough to get you to the end.
Think are strong enough to get you to the end.
So while keith and jennifer
You to the end. So while keith
and jennifer comment, I'm gonna think about
So while keith and jennifer comment, I'm gonna think about it.
Yeah.
Yeah. You have a god-given voice.
Yeah. You have a god-given voice. It just was very inconsistent.
You have a god-given voice. It just
was very inconsistent. So it's gonna be hard to say no
It just was very inconsistent. So it's
gonna be hard to say no to you, but also, you're making
So it's gonna be hard to say no to you,
but also, you're making it tough to say yes.
Here's the thing for me.
Here's the thing for me. It's like I felt like something
Here's the thing for me. It's like
I felt like something was disconnecting this beautiful
It's like I felt like something was
disconnecting this beautiful voice of yours with your...
Delivery.
Your being.
Your being. You've got real talent, and I
Your being. You've got real talent,
and I just think you need to get your
You've got real talent, and I just think
you need to get your confidence back, and I'd love to
Just think you need to get your confidence back,
and I'd love to give you that.
Confidence back, and I'd love to give you that.
So for me, it's a yes tonight.
It's a yes for me too.
It's a yes for me too. I really feel you need to
It's a yes for me too. I really feel you need to practice.
Please go get your dad.
Can I meet your dad?
Yeah, bring your dad, baby.
Go--yeah, bring this out
Go--yeah, bring this out to him first.
Okay, they're gonna send ya
Okay, they're gonna send ya in.
Plus, like, this is a
Plus, like, this is a naturally gifted person.
Dude.
Hi.
Hey.
I am a-wonder mike.
I'd like to say hello.
He's like--he's ready to
He's like--he's ready to audition.
?To the black to the white
?To the black to the white ?The red and the brown
Harry.
Harry. Very good to meet you.
Nice to see you.
How you doin'?
Nice to meet you. Jennifer.
Nice to meet ya.
Good to meet you, man.
I love all your guys' stuff.
I love all your guys' stuff. Man.
She got it.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Here comes mommy.
Mommy.
Congratulations.
Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! Whoo! ?
Hey.
Hello. Hi, guys.
How's it goin'?
Good. How are you?
Good. What's your name?
My name cassandra casinera,
My name cassandra casinera, and I am 16 years old.
What are you gonna sing?
Chasing pavements by adele.
Chasing pavements yeah.
Chasing pavements okay.
Oh, but before I start, j-lo,
Oh, but before I start, j-lo, I just want to say you look so
I just want to say you look so beautiful in person.
Thank you.
And my uncle, he wanted me to
And my uncle, he wanted me to give you his number.
And my uncle, he wanted me
to give you his number. So here's his number.
Give you his number. So here's his number.
Can I have it?
"Please call or text to say
"Please call or text to say hi."
His name's jay julio.
Yes.
Yes. He said--put that right there.
I can make that work.
Wow. But thank you.
Wow. But thank you. I'm flattered.
All right, go for it.
?If I tell the world
?If I tell the world ?I'll never say enough
?If I tell the world ?I'll never say enough ?'cause it was
?I'll never say enough ?'cause it was ?Not said to you
?'cause it was ?Not said to you ?And that's exactly
?Not said to you ?And that's exactly ?What I need to do
?And that's exactly ?What I need to do ?If I
?What I need to do ?If I ?End up with you
?If I ?End up with you ?Should I give up
?End up with you ?Should I give up ?Or should I just
?Should I give up ?Or should I just ?Keep chasing pavements
?Or should I just ?Keep chasing pavements
?Even if it leads nowhere
?Keep chasing pavements ?Even
if it leads nowhere ?Or would it be a waste
?Even if it leads nowhere ?Or
would it be a waste ?Even if I knew my place
?Or would it be a waste ?Even
if I knew my place ?Should I leave it there
?Even if I knew my place
?Should I leave it there ?Should I give up
?Should I leave it there ?Should I give up ?Or should I just
?Should I give up ?Or should I just ?Keep chasing pavements
?Or should I just ?Keep chasing pavements ?Even if it
?Keep chasing pavements ?Even if it ?Leads nowhere
Ooh.
Frankly, I don't think you're
Frankly, I don't think you're ready.
I thought it was all right, but
Ready. I thought it was all right,
but if you're gonna sing all of
I thought it was all right, but if
you're gonna sing all of those runs, there are people who
If you're gonna sing all of those runs,
there are people who are better than you at that.
And you missed too many of 'em
For me.
Yeah, I just thought I'd add
Yeah, I just thought I'd add a different taste to it.
I got you.
Yeah.
I personally am not
I personally am not impressed by that.
Okay.
What do you guys think?
I disagree.
I disagree. I really liked it.
I disagree. I really liked it. I thought you had a lot of good
I really liked it. I thought you had a lot of good control.
I thought you had a lot of good control.
I think your voice is something
Control. I think your voice
is something that is definitely worthy of
I think your voice is something
that is definitely worthy of going to hollywood.
Thank you.
I hear what both of them are
I hear what both of them are saying, and I think...
Yeah.
There's certain artists that
There's certain artists that have a raw talent that it can
There's certain artists that have
a raw talent that it can blossom in hollywood week.
Have a raw talent that it can blossom
in hollywood week. I think you would do well out
Blossom in hollywood week. I think you would do well out there.
All right.
Should we vote?
Yes.
It's a yes for me.
Okay, going to hollywood.
Yes for me!
All right!
Thank you so much!
It only takes two.
Thank you so much, you guys.
Thank you.
You're welcome, baby.
Bye, cassandra.
Congratulations.
Don't try to kiss up now.
Oh, believe me, I'm not.
After you said no.
I can't be nice?
Don't be like, "Okay, baby,
Don't be like, "Okay, baby, yeah, nice, no, no, yeah.
yeah, nice, no, no, yeah. Okay, good luck."
So don't do what you do?
Mm, I don't do that.
Can I call jay now?
Yes.
Let me call jay.
What are you--
What are you-- what are you doing?
He might be hot.
God, I need you to help me pull through this, please.
The best part about this job
The best part about this job is the singers, you know.
The best part about this job is the singers,
you know. It's such a big opportunity.
Is the singers, you know. It's
such a big opportunity. And they know that this is a
It's such a big opportunity. And they know that this is a moment.
And they know that this is a moment.
And if they seize the moment,
Moment. And if they seize the moment,
their whole life could change.
?Swing low
Mm-hmm.
?Sweet chariot
You have an amazingly big voice, which is always so
You have an amazingly big voice, which is always so impressive.
Voice, which is always so impressive.
There were some things that were
Impressive. There were some
things that were not, you know, perfect, but it
There were some things that were not,
you know, perfect, but it doesn't have to be a perfect
Not, you know, perfect,
but it doesn't have to be a perfect audition.
Doesn't have to be a perfect audition.
Just you have to move us in some
Audition. Just you have to move us in some way.
Just you have to move us in some way. I'm gonna say yes.
Believe, believe, believe.
I'm gonna say yes!
Yes!
All you need is two!
Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Thank god. Hey!
Believe, believe, believe.
Well, I think idol can make
Well, I think idol can make dreams come true in a lot of
Well, I think idol can make dreams come true in a lot of ways.
Dreams come true in a lot of ways. In a lot of cases, people come
Ways. In a lot of cases, people come from tiny little towns, they
In a lot of cases, people come from tiny little towns,
they don't have the opportunities.
From tiny little towns, they don't
have the opportunities. And when we can give 'em that
Don't have the opportunities. And
when we can give 'em that opportunity and take that raw
And when we can give 'em that opportunity
and take that raw talent to the next level, that's
Opportunity and take that raw
talent to the next level, that's what I love.
I'm casey thrasher.
I'm casey thrasher. I'm 22 years old.
I'm from tuscaloosa, alabama.
I'm 22 years old. I'm from tuscaloosa,
alabama. I'm kinda between living
I'm from tuscaloosa, alabama.
I'm kinda between living situations right now.
This is my aunt's house that
Situations right now. This is my
aunt's house that I've been staying at for a while
This is my aunt's house
that I've been staying at for a while now.
I've been staying at for a while now.
It's not much, but it's all I
Now. It's not much, but it's all I got.
It's not much, but it's all I got. And I have a really precious
Got. And I have a really precious reason right here.
And I have a really precious reason right here. Two of 'em.
Reason right here. Two of 'em. I just want to provide a good
Two of 'em. I just want to
provide a good life for bailey and brecken.
I just want to provide a good life
for bailey and brecken. That's what this is all about at
Life for bailey and brecken.
That's what this is all about at the end of the day for me,
That's what this is all about at
the end of the day for me, regardless of how I do it.
The end of the day for me,
regardless of how I do it. I've done every crummy job you
Regardless of how I do it. I've done
every crummy job you can possibly do just to try to
I've done every crummy job you
can possibly do just to try to make ends meet.
Can possibly do just to try to make ends meet.
But being able to do what I love
Make ends meet. But being able
to do what I love as a means to provide for them
But being able to do what I love as a
means to provide for them and give them a good life, that
As a means to provide for them
and give them a good life, that needs to be music.
And give them a good life, that needs to be music.
It's difficult, but got to keep
Needs to be music. It's difficult, but got to keep believing.
It's difficult, but got to keep believing.
Believe, believe, believe.
Believing. Believe, believe, believe. I want this, and I need it.
Believe, believe, believe. I want this,
and I need it. I need it for all of us.
I want this, and I need it.
I need it for all of us. Do you hope daddy makes
I need it for all of us. Do you hope daddy makes american idol?
Do you hope daddy makes american idol? Uh-huh.
American idol? Uh-huh. I do too.
Uh-huh. I do too. Say, "My daddy's gonna make
I do too. Say, "My daddy's gonna make american idol."
Say, "My daddy's gonna make american idol."
My daddy's making m'idol.
American idol." My daddy's making m'idol. Hi.
My daddy's making m'idol. Hi. How old are your kids?
Hi. How old are your kids? 2 1/2 and 6 months.
How old are your kids? 2 1/2 and 6 months. Wow, man.
2 1/2 and 6 months. Wow, man. Whoo!
Wow, man. Whoo! And you're touring all the
Whoo! And you're touring all the time.
And you're touring all the time. 22.
Time. 22. It's a constant battle.
22. It's a constant battle.
It's a constant battle. I know that drill, then.
I know that drill, then. You want to be with 'em, but you
I know that drill, then. You want to be with 'em,
but you got to make the money too, be
You want to be with 'em, but you got
to make the money too, be away from the family, you know.
Got to make the money too, be away from the family,
you know. That's right. That's right.
Away from the family, you know. That's right.
That's right. I'm doing all this for them.
That's right. That's right.
I'm doing all this for them. That's cool.
I'm doing all this for them.
That's cool. And what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing a song that I
And what are you gonna sing? I'm
gonna sing a song that I actually chose because of an
I'm gonna sing a song that I actually
chose because of an experience I had with you that
Actually chose because of an
experience I had with you that you'd probably be--
Experience I had with you that you'd probably be-- which was?
You'd probably be-- which was? Should we leave?
Which was? Should we leave? No, you shouldn't leave.
Should we leave? No, you shouldn't leave.
No, no, no. Stay. Please.
No, you shouldn't leave. No, no,
no. Stay. Please. Last year I met you at the cma
No, no, no. Stay. Please. Last
year I met you at the cma awards in nashville, and you
Last year I met you at the cma awards in nashville,
and you were humble enough to come over
Awards in nashville, and you were
humble enough to come over to the gate and be nice to me
Were humble enough to come over
to the gate and be nice to me and speak to me.
To the gate and be nice to me and speak to me.
And I said, "Keith, I'm gonna do
And speak to me. And I said, "Keith,
I'm gonna do my best for ya to see my face
And I said, "Keith, I'm
gonna do my best for ya to see my face again."
My best for ya to see my face again."
And you said, "I believe in you,
Again." And you said, "I believe in you, brother."
And you said, "I believe in you, brother."
Brother." Right on. And here you are.
Right on. And here you are. Here I am.
Right on. And here you are.
Here I am. So I'm gonna sing believe by
Here I am. So I'm gonna sing believe by brooks & dunn.
So I'm gonna sing believe you're gonna sing believe.
You're gonna sing believe. Great song.
You're gonna sing believe. Great song. I got here by believing.
?I can't quote the book
?The chapter or the verse
?But you can't tell me ?It all ends with ?A slow ride in a hearse
?It all ends with ?A slow ride in a hearse ?You know I'm more
?A slow ride in a hearse ?You know I'm more ?And more convinced
?You know I'm more ?And more convinced ?The longer that I live
?And more convinced ?The longer that I live ?No, this can't be
?The longer that I live ?No, this can't be ?No, this can't be
?No, this can't be ?No, this can't be ?No, this can't be
?No, this can't be ?No, this can't be ?All there is
?No, this can't be ?All there is ?Lord, I raise my hands
?All there is ?Lord, I raise my hands ?Bow my head
?Lord, I raise my hands ?Bow my head ?I'm finding more
?Bow my head ?I'm finding more ?And more truth
?I'm finding more ?And more truth ?To the words written in red
?And more truth ?To the words written in red ?They tell me that
?To the words written in red
?They tell me that ?There's more to life
?Than just what I can see
?There's more to life ?Than just what I can see ?Believe
?Than just what I can see ?Believe ?Oh, I
?Believe ?Oh, I ?I believe
?Oh, I ?I believe ?
?I believe ? ?I believe
? ?I believe all right.
?I believe all right. Like halfway through that you
All right. Like halfway
through that you got frustrated with something.
Like halfway through that you got
frustrated with something. And then I thought you channeled
Got frustrated with something.
And then I thought you channeled it into your voice.
And then I thought you channeled
it into your voice. It was really appealing.
It into your voice. It was really appealing. I was feeling it.
It was really appealing. I was feeling it.
I just can't help but think
I was feeling it. I just can't
help but think about my children and my life
I just can't help but think
about my children and my life and my family.
About my children and my life and my family. Yeah, I get it, man.
And my family. Yeah, I get it, man. What'd you think, jen?
Yeah, I get it, man. What'd you think, jen? I love you.
What'd you think, jen? I love you. Everything wasn't 100% perfect
I love you. Everything wasn't
100% perfect throughout the whole thing, but
Everything wasn't 100% perfect
throughout the whole thing, but it had so much feeling.
Throughout the whole thing, but
it had so much feeling. There is a real voice there.
It had so much feeling. There is a real voice there.
I believed what you were saying.
There is a real voice there.
I believed what you were saying. I just loved it.
I believed what you were saying. I just loved it. I really did.
I just loved it. I really did. I really, really felt like I was
I really did. I really,
really felt like I was watching a performance, and I
I really, really felt like
I was watching a performance, and I was in it.
Watching a performance, and I was in it. I was there with you.
Was in it. I was there with you. Thank you, jen.
I was there with you. Thank you, jen. Your drive is extremely
Thank you, jen. Your drive is extremely strong.
Your drive is extremely strong. I mean, you have two kids.
Strong. I mean, you have two kids.
You're talking about doing this
I mean, you have two kids.
You're talking about doing this for your family.
You're talking about doing
this for your family. I really respect that.
For your family. I really respect that.
You're gonna be the kinda guy
I really respect that. You're
gonna be the kinda guy that thinks about every single
You're gonna be the kinda guy that
thinks about every single performance, goes home, and does
That thinks about every single performance,
goes home, and does practical things to get better
Performance, goes home,
and does practical things to get better every week.
Practical things to get better every week.
That's what I think about you.
Every week. That's what I think about you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
That's what I think about you. Thank you.
Thank you so much. What I loved about it is
Thank you. Thank you so much.
What I loved about it is there's that mix of, like, such
What I loved about it is there's that mix of,
like, such hunger and desire and
There's that mix of, like, such
hunger and desire and desperation and want to be able
Hunger and desire and desperation
and want to be able to, like, get a break, just get
Desperation and want to be able to,
like, get a break, just get a dang break, you know.
To, like, get a break, just get a dang break,
you know. And I felt a little of that,
A dang break, you know. And I felt a little of that, man.
And I felt a little of that, man. I'd love to give you that break
Man. I'd love to give you that break tonight.
I'd love to give you that break tonight. It's a yes for me.
Tonight. It's a yes for me. Yes for me.
It's a yes for me. Yes for me. Yes for me.
Yes for me. Yes for me. Thank you, casey thrasher!
Yes for me. Thank you, casey thrasher! Come on, casey!
Thank you, casey thrasher! Come on, casey! That was awesome.
Come on, casey! That was awesome.
That was awesome. That's a beautiful thing for
That's a beautiful thing for your kids.
That's a beautiful thing for your kids. Be a good daddy.
Your kids. Be a good daddy. Absolutely.
Be a good daddy. Absolutely. Yeah.
Absolutely. Yeah. See ya in hollywood.
Yeah. See ya in hollywood. Wow.
See ya in hollywood. Wow. From the chain link fence at
WOW. FROM THE CHAIN LINK FENCE AT CMAs TO HOLLYWOOD.
FROM THE CHAIN LINK FENCE AT CMAs TO HOLLYWOOD. WHOO!
CMAs TO HOLLYWOOD. WHOO! I HAD A LOT OF PEOPLE DOUBT
Whoo! I had a lot of people doubt me.
I had a lot of people doubt me. I've overcome a lot of
Me. I've overcome a lot of obstacles, and I finally got a
I've overcome a lot of obstacles,
and I finally got a break and a chance for someone
Obstacles, and I finally got
a break and a chance for someone to hear me.
Break and a chance for someone to hear me.
I want to say god bless you,
To hear me. I want to say god bless you, keith.
I want to say god bless you, keith. He's got that direction, man.
Keith. He's got that direction, man. Yeah.
He's got that direction, man. Yeah. He's not gonna quit, that
Yeah. He's not gonna quit, that guy.
He's not gonna quit, that guy. You have the work ethic.
Guy. You have the work ethic. Big part of it.
You have the work ethic. Big part of it. Yeah, hell, yeah, man.
Big part of it. Yeah, hell, yeah, man. Hello.
Yeah, hell, yeah, man. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello. Guess what?
Hello. Guess what?
Guess what? Daddy made american idol.
Daddy made american idol.
Daddy made american idol. He's laughing.
He's laughing. Great!
He's laughing. Great! Great.
Great! Great. It means like a million bucks to
Great. It means like a million bucks to me.
It means like a million bucks to me. Other than the days that my
Me. Other than the days that my children were born, this is the
Other than the days that my children were born,
this is the best day of my life.
Children were born, this is the
best day of my life. Was salt lake city a success?
Best day of my life. Was salt lake city a success? Yes.
Was salt lake city a success? Yes. Yeah.
Yes. Yeah. It was a success, right?
Yeah. It was a success, right? It was successful.
It was a success, right? It was successful. Yes, it was.
It was successful. Yes, it was. Absolutely.
Yes, it was. Absolutely. You know it.
Absolutely. You know it. It seemed like a great day.
You know it. It seemed like a great day. You felt it.
It seemed like a great day.
You felt it. Do you think we found some
You felt it. Do you think we found some stars here?
Do you think we found some stars here? I think we did.
Stars here? I think we did. I think we did.
I think we did. I think we did. ?Oh, we can do
I think we did. ?Oh, we can do ?Anything we want
?Oh, we can do ?Anything we want no doubt about it.
?Anything we want no doubt about it. Our trip west delivered the
No doubt about it. Our trip
west delivered the stars we were counting on.
Our trip west delivered the stars we were counting on. ?
Stars we were counting on. ? Nine hometown heroes from utah
? Nine hometown heroes from utah are heading to hollywood,
Nine hometown heroes from utah
are heading to hollywood, joined by singers from
Are heading to hollywood,
joined by singers from california, nevada, washington,
Joined by singers from california,
nevada, washington, and 10 other states.
California, nevada, washington,
and 10 other states. In all, 30 contestants are
And 10 other states. In all,
30 contestants are flying their flags for the salt
In all, 30 contestants are flying
their flags for the salt lake audition, taking our
Flying their flags for the salt lake audition,
taking our hollywood week total to 193.
Lake audition, taking our hollywood week total to 193. Excuse me.
Hollywood week total to 193.
Excuse me. They won't--this is gonna be
Excuse me. They won't--this is gonna be edited out, right?
They won't--this is gonna be edited out,
right? It was a great day.
Edited out, right? It was a great day. Both days were great.
It was a great day. Both days were great. Hey.
Both days were great. Hey. How you doin'?
Hey. How you doin'? Okay.
How you doin'? Okay. Bye, salt lake city.
Okay. Bye, salt lake city. We sent more people through
Bye, salt lake city. We sent
more people through today, I think, than any other
We sent more people through today,
I think, than any other day so far.
Today, I think, than any other day so far.
We're running low at home.
Day so far. We're running low at home. That's a testament to the
That's a testament to the level of talent we saw.
That's a testament to the
level of talent we saw. Roll. Let's roll.
Level of talent we saw. Roll. Let's roll. Tomorrow night...
Roll. Let's roll. Tomorrow night... omaha, here we are.
Tomorrow night... omaha, here we are. It's our last stop on the
Omaha, here we are. It's our
last stop on the audition tour as we head to the
It's our last stop on the
audition tour as we head to the heartland of america.
Audition tour as we head to the
heartland of america. I think we're here, guys.
Heartland of america. I think we're here,
guys. Omaha, nebraska, where the
I think we're here, guys. Omaha,
nebraska, where the talent runs deep.
Omaha, nebraska, where the talent runs deep.
You have a really beautiful
Talent runs deep. You have a really beautiful voice.
You have a really beautiful voice. I really dug it.
Voice. I really dug it. It's the best of the midwest.
I really dug it. It's the best of the midwest. I love him.
It's the best of the midwest. I love him. I think you're great.
I love him. I think you're great. As the judges hand out the
I think you're great. As the
judges hand out the final golden tickets to
As the judges hand out the final golden tickets to hollywood.
Final golden tickets to hollywood. You're going to hollywood!
Hollywood. You're going to hollywood! Whoo! Yeah!
You're going to hollywood! Whoo! Yeah! Whoo!
Whoo! Yeah! Whoo! No.
Whoo! No. Oh, my god, j.Lo, you can't
No. Oh, my god, j.Lo, you can't say that when I'm about to do--
Oh, my god, j.Lo, you can't say
that when I'm about to do-- you're headed in the wrong
Say that when I'm about
to do-- you're headed in the wrong direction.
You're headed in the wrong direction. That's not enough for me.
Direction. That's not enough for me. Make me cry.
That's not enough for me. Make me cry. I'm freakin' out, man.