Hey, can I say something to
The kids?
Yes.
Hey, listen. So here's a pet peeve of mine.
I'm speaking for harry right
So here's a pet peeve of mine. I'm speaking for harry right now.
I'm speaking for harry right now. At the top of my list of pet
Now. At the top of my list of pet peeves is hearing people bitch
At the top of my list of pet peeves
is hearing people bitch about they don't feel good.
Peeves is hearing people bitch about
they don't feel good. "I lost my voice and I'm sick."
About they don't feel good.
"I lost my voice and I'm sick." It's whiny.
"I lost my voice and I'm sick."
It's whiny. That sucks the energy out of
It's whiny. That sucks the energy out of what you're about to do.
That sucks the energy out
of what you're about to do. You have a choice.
What you're about to do. You have a choice.
If you tell us that you're sick
You have a choice. If you tell
us that you're sick then we're gonna be thinking
If you tell us that you're sick then
we're gonna be thinking about you being sick, and it's
Then we're gonna be thinking about you being sick,
and it's gonna take away from you.
About you being sick, and it's gonna
take away from you. If you're sick and you don't say
Gonna take away from you. If you're
sick and you don't say it, 95% of us are not gonna even
If you're sick and you don't say it,
95% of us are not gonna even know.
It, 95% of us are not gonna even know.
How many gigs have I done when I
Know. How many gigs have I done when I feel like crap?
How many gigs have I done
when I feel like crap? Nobody says anything.
Feel like crap? Nobody says anything. They don't know.
Nobody says anything. They don't know.
Don't tell us how to feel for
They don't know. Don't tell us
how to feel for you, ever, for the rest of your
Don't tell us how to feel for you,
ever, for the rest of your performing careers.
You, ever, for the rest of your
performing careers. If I go spend some money to
Performing careers. If I go
spend some money to hear somebody, I'm sorry if
If I go spend some money to hear somebody,
I'm sorry if you're not feeling well.
Hear somebody, I'm sorry if
you're not feeling well. I paid to see your show.
You're not feeling well.
I paid to see your show. This is show business.
I paid to see your show. This is show business. We don't care.
This is show business. We don't care. I don't care.
We don't care. I don't care. Just suck it up.
Yeah.
Sing.
Sing. Just--it's entertainment.
?
Sorry, baby, it's the end of
Sorry, baby, it's the end of the line.
Nights of sleepless
Nights of sleepless anxiety...
I got three hours of sleep
I got three hours of sleep last night, which is more than
I got three hours of sleep last night,
which is more than the last two nights.
Tonight, we reveal the
Tonight, we reveal the 15 guys and the 15 girls who
Tonight, we reveal the 15 guys
and the 15 girls who will get the chance to sing for
15 guys and the 15 girls who will get
the chance to sing for america's vote in next week's
Will get the chance to sing
for america's vote in next week's live shows.
America's vote in next week's live shows.
Live shows. ?
? Our remaining contestants arrive
? Our remaining contestants arrive to face the final judgment.
I'm trying to take in all
I'm trying to take in all this experience while I can, and
I'm trying to take in all this
experience while I can, and I hope that I'm still here
This experience while I can,
and I hope that I'm still here tomorrow.
I hope that I'm still here tomorrow. ?
I'm ready for the
I'm ready for the opportunity, so all I need is
That "Yes."
Yesterday, each remaining
Contestant gave a final solo
Performance at the dolby theater
In hollywood.
?See when you close ?Your eyes ?Maybe one day
?Your eyes ?Maybe one day ?You'll understand why
For some, it was an
For some, it was an opportunity to cap off a solid
For some, it was an opportunity
to cap off a solid week of performances and
Opportunity to cap off a solid
week of performances and reaffirm their place in the
Week of performances and reaffirm their place in the top 30.
?Welcome to the new age
?Welcome to the new age ?To the new age
?Welcome to the new age ?To the new age ?Welcome to the new age
Yes, yes, yeah.
That's right.
I like that.
But for others, yesterday's
But for others, yesterday's time in the spotlight proved
But for others, yesterday's time
in the spotlight proved just too much to handle.
?Everywhere
Oop, uh-oh.
Playing two different places.
Yeah.
But the judges will consider
But the judges will consider not only yesterday's
not only yesterday's performance, but their entire
Not only yesterday's performance,
but their entire idol journey to date in
Performance, but their entire idol
journey to date in determining who moves on to the
Idol journey to date in determining
who moves on to the live stage and who will watch
Determining who moves on to the live
stage and who will watch from home wondering what could
Live stage and who will
watch from home wondering what could have been.
From home wondering what could have been.
Our contestants will have to sit
Have been. Our contestants
will have to sit here in agony in our holding
Our contestants will have to sit here
in agony in our holding room, waiting for their name to
Here in agony in our holding room,
waiting for their name to be called.
Room, waiting for their name to be called.
When they hear their name,
Be called. When they hear their name,
they'll walk through this door
When they hear their name,
they'll walk through this door and board the elevator to head
They'll walk through this
door and board the elevator to head upstairs.
And board the elevator to head upstairs.
With so much on the line, you
Upstairs. With so much on the line,
you can only imagine the pressure as
With so much on the line, you can
only imagine the pressure as they wait for these doors to
Can only imagine the pressure as they
wait for these doors to open, and when they do, it's
They wait for these doors to open,
and when they do, it's time to take that long walk
Open, and when they do, it's time
to take that long walk towards our judges--keith,
Time to take that long walk towards
our judges--keith, jennifer, and harry--who have
Towards our judges--keith, jennifer,
and harry--who have had the difficult job of
Jennifer, and harry--who have
had the difficult job of narrowing down this very
Had the difficult job of
narrowing down this very talented group of singers.
Narrowing down this very talented group of singers.
Once each of them arrive here,
Talented group of singers. Once
each of them arrive here, they'll sit in the chair for
Once each of them arrive here,
they'll sit in the chair for what will be the final judgment.
I'm very nervous at the
Moment.
All right, who gets to go
All right, who gets to go first?
All right, who gets to go first? Who wants to go first?
First? Who wants to go first? Everybody wants to go--almost
Who wants to go first?
Everybody wants to go--almost everyone wants to go first, half
Everybody wants to go--almost
everyone wants to go first, half of you, okay.
Everyone wants to go first, half of you,
okay. The first person to take the
Of you, okay. The first person to take the ride upstairs--emily.
The first person to take the ride upstairs--emily. Where's emily?
Ride upstairs--emily. Where's emily? Emily, come on.
Where's emily? Emily, come on. Let's go.
Emily, come on. Let's go.
Let's go. How you doing?
Good.
Ready?
Yeah.
No palm sweat?
No palm sweat? No, they're all right.
You're not that nervous.
No, I am.
Head on through.
Head on through. Good luck.
Head on through. Good luck. Emily piriz first auditioned in
Good luck. Emily piriz first
auditioned in atlanta, and has always been a
Emily piriz first auditioned in atlanta,
and has always been a confident yet quiet contender.
I feel like my performances
I feel like my performances definitely have been a little
definitely have been a little under-the-radar.
Definitely have been a little under-the-radar.
Under-the-radar. I think yesterday, I kind of
I think yesterday, I kind of stood out a little bit.
It showed them that I'm here to
Stood out a little bit. It showed them that I'm here to stay.
?I lit a fire
?With the love
?You left behind
?And it burned wild ?And crept up ?The mountainside
Hello.
Hello. ?Followed your ashes
Hello. ?Followed your ashes ?Into outer space
?I can't look at this place
?I can't look at the stars
?They make me wonder ?Where you are ?Stars
?Where you are ?Stars ?Up on heaven's boulevard
?Stars ?Up on heaven's boulevard ?And if I know you at all
?Up on heaven's boulevard ?And
if I know you at all ?I know you've gone too far
?And if I know you at all ?I know you've gone too far ?So I
?I know you've gone too far ?So I ?Can't look at the stars
?So I ?Can't look at the stars ?
?Can't look at the stars ? ?Stars
Ah, ha ha.
?Oh, they make me wonder
?Oh, they make me wonder ?Where you are
?Oh, they make me wonder ?Where you are ?Stars
?Where you are ?Stars ?Up on heaven's boulevard
Whoa!
?And if I know you at all
?And if I know you at all ?I know you've gone too far
?And if I know you at all ?I know you've gone too far ?So I
?I know you've gone too far ?So I ?Can't look at the stars
?So I ?Can't look at the stars
But will emily's final
But will emily's final performance be enough to get her
performance be enough to get her into the top 30?
So classic.
So classic. I love the way she looks.
She looks absolutely
She looks absolutely gorgeous.
She looks absolutely gorgeous. I've always thought she was
Gorgeous. I've always
thought she was pretty, but she was--she looked
I've always thought she was pretty,
but she was--she looked really like a movie star.
Oh, here we go.
Hi.
How you doing, emily?
Good.
It's good to see you, emily.
You too.
Emily, what's your heritage?
Emily, what's your heritage? We were trying to figure out
We were trying to figure out what your background is.
I'm cuban.
Cuban, okay.
You are.
We couldn't--
Latinas in the house.
Couldn't place it.
Okay, sweetie, we have to get
Okay, sweetie, we have to get down to business.
I think you really came up
Down to business. I think
you really came up during hollywood week.
I think you really came up during hollywood week.
I was a big fan of yours from
During hollywood week.
I was a big fan of yours from the beginning.
Unfortunately, these guys don't
The beginning. Unfortunately,
these guys don't always...agree with me.
Thank you so--
Thank you so-- can I give you guys--
Congratulations.
Good job.
Thank you so much.
You bet, emily.
Thank you.
Happy for you, emily.
See you soon.
Bye.
We do have a latina in there.
There you go.
Hey, yeah.
Yes.
Oh, my gosh.
Whoo!
All right!
All right! All right.
I'm feeling like this isn't
I'm feeling like this isn't really real right now.
really real right now. I'm, like, shaking still.
Really real right now. I'm,
like, shaking still. I'm actually top 30 on
I'm, like, shaking still. I'm actually top 30 on american idol.
I'm actually top 30 on american idol.
Like, this has been my dream
American idol. Like, this
has been my dream since I was little, and it's
Like, this has been my dream since I was little,
and it's crazy that it's actually coming
Since I was little,
and it's crazy that it's actually coming true.
Crazy that it's actually coming true.
Thank you, thank you very much.
True. Thank you, thank you very much. I am in the top 30.
Thank you, thank you very much. I am in the top 30.
My name is emily piriz, and I am
I am in the top 30. My name is emily piriz,
and I am your next american idol.
My name is emily piriz, and I am
your next american idol. Hoping to win the first slot
Your next american idol. Hoping
to win the first slot for the guys was spencer lloyd.
Hoping to win the first slot for
the guys was spencer lloyd. This week has been very
For the guys was spencer lloyd.
This week has been very interesting to say the least.
This week has been very interesting
to say the least. You know, there's been a lot of
Interesting to say the least. You know,
there's been a lot of different things thrown at us,
You know, there's been a lot of different
things thrown at us, and there's a lot on the line
Different things thrown at us,
and there's a lot on the line today.
And there's a lot on the line today.
Spencer lloyd's journey began
Today. Spencer lloyd's
journey began in austin, texas, where his good
Spencer lloyd's journey began in austin,
texas, where his good looks caused quite a stir.
In austin, texas, where his
good looks caused quite a stir. Oh, my god.
Looks caused quite a stir. Oh, my god. Are your eyes blue?
Oh, my god. Are your eyes blue? Green?
Are your eyes blue? Green? Green, mix of brown,
Green? Green, mix of brown, something.
Green, mix of brown, something. You're a pretty guy.
Something. You're a pretty guy. So that's a yes from jen.
You're a pretty guy. So that's a yes from jen.
And a no from me and keith.
So that's a yes from jen. And a no from me and keith.
And a no from me and keith. Well, spencer definitely has
Well, spencer definitely has the look, but does he have the
Well, spencer definitely has the look,
but does he have the talent to take him to the
The look, but does he have the talent to take him to the top 30?
Talent to take him to the top 30? How you doing, spencer?
Top 30? How you doing, spencer? I'm doing pretty good.
How you doing, spencer? I'm doing pretty good. Take a seat, man.
I'm doing pretty good. Take a seat, man. Yes, sir.
Take a seat, man. Yes, sir. How you feeling?
Yes, sir. How you feeling? A little nervous, you know.
How you feeling? A little nervous, you know. Okay, spencer, so...
A little nervous, you know.
Okay, spencer, so... when you started off in
Okay, spencer, so... when
you started off in hollywood week, for me, you
When you started off in hollywood week,
for me, you were, like, one of the
Hollywood week, for me, you were, like, one of the front-runners.
Were, like, one of the front-runners. I was like, "Wow."
Front-runners. I was like, "Wow." When I saw you sit at the piano
I was like, "Wow." When I saw you
sit at the piano and sing that song super simple,
When I saw you sit at the piano and
sing that song super simple, I felt like, "Okay, this guy
And sing that song super simple,
I felt like, "Okay, this guy really stands out."
?And I
?Am feeling so small
?It was over my head ?And
I know nothing at all yesterday, in the final
?And I know nothing at all yesterday,
in the final performance round, spencer did
Yesterday, in the final performance round,
spencer did an original song.
Performance round, spencer did an original song.
It didn't quite have the same
An original song. It didn't
quite have the same impact on the judges.
?Don't me wrong
?Makeup can go a long way
?And some cute clothes
?Help you get through the day
?Make sure your nails
?Are filed
?And go ahead and polish
?That beautiful smile
?All I'm saying is
?Just be yourself
?And don't get caught up ?In everybody else ?Just be you
?In everybody else ?Just be you ?And make that your goal
?Just be you ?And make that your goal ?'cause who you are
?And make that your goal ?'cause who you are ?Is beautifu-u-ul
?'cause who you are ?Is
beautifu-u-ul even though it showed us that
?Is beautifu-u-ul even though
it showed us that you wrote and--obviously, you
Even though it showed us that you
wrote and--obviously, you play guitar and piano, all of
You wrote and--obviously, you
play guitar and piano, all of that stuff was good.
Play guitar and piano, all of that stuff was good.
We all--we take everything into
That stuff was good.
We all--we take everything into consideration.
The song itself wasn't, you
Consideration. The song itself wasn't,
you know, something that really
The song itself wasn't, you know,
something that really showcased you in the best way, I
Know, something that really showcased
you in the best way, I thought, and so did keith and...
Showcased you in the best way,
I thought, and so did keith and... we agree.
Thought, and so did keith and... we agree. And harry on that.
We agree. And harry on that. So when we were coming down to
And harry on that. So when we
were coming down to it, it became a really, really
So when we were coming down to it, it became a really,
really tough decision, as much as we
It, it became a really,
really tough decision, as much as we love you.
Tough decision, as much as we love you.
And we've made a decision.
Okay, spencer, so when you
Sang your original song,
Honestly, I think it worked
Against you.
So when we were coming down to it, it became a really,
really tough decision, as much as we
It, it became a really,
really tough decision, as much as we love you.
Yes, we do.
Yes, we do. Yes, we do, spencer.
You showed us some star
You showed us some star quality, and we would be honored
You showed us some star quality,
and we would be honored if you would.
Thank you.
So we have the first of our
So we have the first of our top 15 guys.
Thank you, guys.
You're welcome.
It's a big challenge and
It's a big challenge and there's a lot of talented
It's a big challenge and there's
a lot of talented musicians here, and I'm really
There's a lot of talented musicians here,
and I'm really hoping that, you know, I could
Musicians here, and I'm really hoping that,
you know, I could go a long ways with this.
We'll see how it goes.
Next to take the ride
Next to take the ride upstairs, jillian jensen.
Next to take the ride upstairs, jillian jensen. Jillian.
Upstairs, jillian jensen. Jillian.
Yesterday, jillian chose as her
Final performance piece an
Original song, a risky but
Calculated decision.
The reason I decided to do this song today was,
I guess, because I wanted to show you
This song today was, I guess,
because I wanted to show you guys exactly who I am as an
Because I wanted to show you guys
exactly who I am as an artist, 'cause I think the point
Guys exactly who I am as an artist,
'cause I think the point of american idol isn't just to
Artist, 'cause I think the point of
american idol isn't just to find someone as a winner of this
Of american idol isn't
just to find someone as a winner of this year.
Find someone as a winner of this year.
It's supposed to find someone
Year. It's supposed to
find someone that's supposed to continue on
It's supposed to find someone
that's supposed to continue on in the industry and have
That's supposed to continue on in
the industry and have longevity, and I'm a writer.
In the industry and have longevity,
and I'm a writer. Like, that's what I do, you
Longevity, and I'm a writer.
Like, that's what I do, you know, so--
Well said, very well said.
Well said, very well said. ?
?Then you put your arm
?Around me
?Couldn't help ?But want you more ?You held me tight
?But want you more ?You held me tight ?I fell slowly
?You held me tight ?I fell slowly ?But my heart is sore
?I fell slowly ?But my heart is sore ?Sore
?But my heart is sore ?Sore ?Let me live there
?Sore ?Let me live there I'm extremely confident in
?Let me live there I'm extremely confident in what I've given.
I'm extremely confident in what I've given.
I hope that translated to them.
What I've given. I hope that translated to them. Thank you.
Thank you. I hope they're gonna say yes.
How you doing, jillian?
Good.
Good. One of the hardest things I've
Good. One of the hardest
things I've ever been a part of is putting
One of the hardest things I've
ever been a part of is putting together the top 30 for
Ever been a part of is putting
together the top 30 for american idol-- 15 boys,
Together the top 30 for american idol-- 15 boys,
15 girls--because you start
American idol-- 15 boys, 15
girls--because you start thinking about all of the
15 girls--because you start
thinking about all of the characteristics that make up
Thinking about all of the
characteristics that make up being the american idol.
Characteristics that make up being the american idol.
I mean, we're looking for people
Being the american idol. I mean,
we're looking for people who can really--really win, and
I mean, we're looking for people who can
really--really win, and then you start thinking, "Is it
Who can really--really win,
and then you start thinking, "Is it about singing?
Then you start thinking,
"Is it about singing? Is it about artistry?
About singing? Is it about artistry? What's it about?"
Is it about artistry? What's it about?" There's so many--so many
What's it about?" There's
so many--so many qualities, you know, and the
There's so many--so many qualities,
you know, and the three of us have different
Qualities, you know, and the three of us have different opinions.
Three of us have different opinions. Sometimes we all agree,
Opinions. Sometimes we all agree, sometimes we don't.
Sometimes we all agree, sometimes we don't. Oh, man.
Sometimes we don't. Oh, man.
Oh, man. You're in the top 15.
Congratulations.
Feel so lucky.
Feel so lucky. Thank you.
You earned it.
Thank you, hon.
Thank you, hon. Thank you.
I'm sorry, I'm just really
I'm sorry, I'm just really happy, 'cause, like--
Listen--
We're happy for you.
This was, like, the hardest
This was, like, the hardest round, you know what I mean?
It's hard.
?
? ?
? I'm so happy.
Congratulations.
Congratulations. ?
Congratulations. ? You should be so happy.
I'm so ecstatic.
I'm sorry, I'm not crying
I'm sorry, I'm not crying 'cause it's like--I'm just
'cause it's like--I'm just freaking out right now.
You are crying.
You are crying. Are you not crying?
I am crying.
You are crying, yes.
I'm not--
Well, she may not know
Well, she may not know whether she's crying or not, but
Well, she may not know whether she's crying or not,
but one thing's certain--jillian is
Whether she's crying or not,
but one thing's certain--jillian is in the top 30.
Oh, thank you, guys.
Up next, where's madelyn?
Up next, where's madelyn? Madelyn?
Up next, where's madelyn? Madelyn? Come on up, madelyn.
Madelyn? Come on up, madelyn.
Come on up, madelyn. We first met madelyn patterson
We first met madelyn patterson in austin...
Yes!
And her journey on
And her journey on american idol has been an
And her journey on american idol has been an emotional one.
American idol it's just hard, you know?
It's just hard, you know? I've worked really hard to be
It's just hard, you know? I've worked really hard to be here.
Bring it in, guys.
Bring it in, guys. We got this.
Making it in the top 48 out
Making it in the top 48 out of the thousands and thousands
Making it in the top 48 out of the
thousands and thousands of people that have tried out,
Of the thousands and thousands of
people that have tried out, I mean, that's really saying
Of people that have tried out,
I mean, that's really saying something.
It's really cool to feel so
Something. It's really cool to feel so accomplished.
It's really cool to feel so accomplished. I'm sorry.
Accomplished. I'm sorry.
And yesterday, madelyn showed
And yesterday, madelyn showed the judges exactly the kind of
And yesterday, madelyn showed the
judges exactly the kind of artist she wants to be.
THE JUDGES EXACTLY THE KIND
OF ARTIST SHE WANTS TO BE. Patty Griffin's
Artist she wants to be.
?Some days I look down
?Afraid I may fall
?And though the sun shines ?I see nothing at all ?Nothing at all
?I see nothing at all ?Nothing at all ?Oh, I hear
?Nothing at all ?Oh, I hear ?Oh, I hear your sweet voice
?Oh, I hear ?Oh, I hear your sweet voice how you doing, madelyn?
?Oh, I hear your sweet voice how you doing, madelyn? Hi.
How you doing, madelyn? Hi. Take a seat, baby.
Hi. Take a seat, baby. Okay.
Take a seat, baby. Okay. What's the matter?
Okay. What's the matter? I'm just nervous.
What's the matter? I'm just nervous. You're nervous.
I'm just nervous. You're nervous. Nervous?
You're nervous. Nervous? Did you get much sleep last
Nervous? Did you get much sleep last night?
Did you get much sleep last night? I tried to.
Night? I tried to. Yeah.
I tried to. Yeah. We first want to say that making
Yeah. We first want to say
that making this decision has been difficult
We first want to say that
making this decision has been difficult for us.
This decision has been difficult for us.
We've spent an extraordinarily
For us. We've spent an extraordinarily long time going through
long time going through everybody's performances, and
Long time going through
everybody's performances, and you've had some great
Everybody's performances,
and you've had some great performances, there's no
You've had some great performances, there's no question about it.
Performances, there's no question about it. Right.
Question about it. Right. And unfortunately, we have to
Right. And unfortunately, we have to say good-bye tonight.
And unfortunately, we have to say good-bye tonight. Okay.
Say good-bye tonight. Okay. I understand.
Okay. I understand. But we really appreciate
I understand. But we
really appreciate everything you've done up to
But we really appreciate everything you've done up to now.
Everything you've done up to now. I appreciate it a lot, y'all,
Now. I appreciate it a lot, y'all, for real.
I appreciate it a lot, y'all, for real. You bet.
For real. You bet. Thank you for sharing your
You bet. Thank you for sharing your talent.
Thank you for sharing your talent. Keep working hard.
Talent. Keep working hard. Thank you.
Keep working hard. Thank you. Thank you, sweetheart.
Thank you. Thank you, sweetheart. Thank you so much.
Thank you, sweetheart. Thank you so much. You're welcome.
Thank you so much. You're welcome. Thank you.
You're welcome. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. ?
? What's the verdict?
? What's the verdict? A
What's the verdict? A but it's okay.
A but it's okay. They really want me to come back
But it's okay. They really want
me to come back next year, so I'm probably gonna
They really want me to come back next year,
so I'm probably gonna do that.
Next year, so I'm probably gonna do that.
Do that. Though leaving the
Though leaving the competition is tough, saying
Though leaving the competition is tough,
saying good-bye to the friendships made
Competition is tough, saying
good-bye to the friendships made can be even tougher.
Good-bye to the friendships made
can be even tougher. Hey, you better stay in this,
Can be even tougher. Hey, you better stay in this, okay?
Hey, you better stay in this, okay?
Okay? And you too.
And you too. This little girl, y'all, this
And you too. This little girl,
y'all, this girl right here, she's so
This little girl, y'all, this girl right here, she's so special.
Girl right here, she's so special.
Special. And as madelyn gave final
And as madelyn gave final farewells, others were dealt the
And as madelyn gave final farewells,
others were dealt the same fate, including salt lake
Farewells, others were dealt the same fate,
including salt lake city contestant michael simeon.
Same fate, including salt lake city
contestant michael simeon. I'm gonna make it short and
City contestant michael simeon.
I'm gonna make it short and sweet for you, baby.
I'm gonna make it short and sweet for you,
baby. You did not make it into the
Sweet for you, baby.
You did not make it into the top 15 this year.
Top 15 this year. ?
? As well as lebryant crew.
? As well as lebryant crew. Unfortunately, today it's a
As well as lebryant crew. Unfortunately, today it's a no from us.
Unfortunately, today it's a no from us. ?
No from us. ? And we said good-bye to
? And we said good-bye to sabrina lentini, also from the
And we said good-bye to sabrina lentini,
also from the salt lake city auditions.
Sabrina lentini, also from the
salt lake city auditions. This is not your year.
Salt lake city auditions. This is not your year.
But you did great this week.
This is not your year.
But you did great this week. You really did.
But you did great this week. You really did. Okay.
You really did. Okay. No?
Okay. No? No.
No? No. No?
No. No? No.
No? No. Aw.
No. Aw. Come on, come on.
Aw. Come on, come on. If anything, this "No" Makes
Come on, come on. If anything,
this "No" Makes me want it even more.
If anything, this "No"
Makes me want it even more. I don't know, man.
Me want it even more. I don't know,
man. They're sending some amazing
I don't know, man. They're sending some amazing people home.
They're sending some amazing people home. Atlanta contestant
People home. Atlanta contestant george lovett wasn't about to
Atlanta contestant george lovett
wasn't about to give up on his dream, and was
George lovett wasn't about to give up on his dream,
and was determined to go down fighting
Give up on his dream, and was
determined to go down fighting in yesterday's final
Determined to go down fighting in yesterday's final performance.
?Even if the sky
?Gets rough
?I'm giving you all my love I
really hope that I stood out to them, you know?
I really hope that I stood out to them,
you know? I really hope that they can see
Out to them, you know? I
really hope that they can see the potential in me.
I really hope that they can
see the potential in me. ?Well, in the end
The potential in me. ?Well, in the end ?You're still my friend
?Well, in the end ?You're still my friend ?At least I did intend
?You're still my friend ?At least I did intend ?For us to work
?At least I did intend ?For us to work ?We didn't break
?For us to work ?We didn't break ?We didn't burn
?We didn't break ?We didn't burn ?We had to learn how to bend
?We didn't burn ?We had to learn how to bend
?Without the world caving in
?We had to learn how to bend
?Without the world caving in I was worried about you in
?Without the world caving in I was
worried about you in the beginning, but I'm gonna ask
I was worried about you in the beginning,
but I'm gonna ask you to be in the top 15.
The beginning, but I'm
gonna ask you to be in the top 15. Oh, my--
You to be in the top 15. Oh, my-- we want to ask you to be in
Oh, my-- we want to ask you to be in the top 15.
We want to ask you to be in the top 15.
The top 15. Ah! Oh, thank you.
Ah! Oh, thank you. ?Said I won't give up on us
Ah! Oh, thank you.
?Said I won't give up on us ?Even if the sky, yeah
?Said I won't give up on us
?Even if the sky, yeah I made it, y'all.
?Even if the sky, yeah I made it, y'all. I want this so bad.
I made it, y'all. I want this so bad. ?Giving you all my love
I want this so bad. ?Giving you all my love
?God knows you're worth it
?Giving you all my love ?God knows you're worth it ?Yeah
?God knows you're worth it ?Yeah hey.
?Yeah hey. Great job!
Hey. Great job!
Judgment here on idol.
Tonight, the judges choose the 15
guys and 15 girls that will make up the top 30 in next
15 guys and 15 girls that will
make up the top 30 in next week's live shows.
Make up the top 30 in next week's live shows. Hope for the best.
Week's live shows. Hope for the best.
That's all you can do at this
Hope for the best. That's all you can do at this point.
That's all you can do at this point. They've already made their
Point. They've already made their decision, so--
Yesterday, each contestant
Sang one last time for the
Judges, performing either a song
Off a list with band
Accompaniment...
?Wide open spaces and on occasions, keith accompaniment...
AND ON OCCASIONS, KEITH ACCOMPANIMENT... both ?ROOM TO MAKE
ACCOMPANIMENT... both ?ROOM TO MAKE ?HER BIG MISTAKES
both ?ROOM TO MAKE ?HER
BIG MISTAKES OR AN ORIGINAL, COMPLETELY ON
?Her big mistakes or an original, completely on their own.
Or an original, completely on their own. ?I've been looking
Their own. ?I've been looking ?For the answer
?I've been looking ?For the answer ?I been waiting for the light
?For the answer ?I been
waiting for the light but sometimes, singing an
?I been waiting for the light but sometimes,
singing an original can actually expose a
But sometimes, singing an
original can actually expose a lack of originality.
Original can actually expose
a lack of originality. Sweet home alabama.
Lack of originality. Sweet home alabama. ?But that doesn't mean
Sweet home alabama. ?But that doesn't mean ?They're right
?But that doesn't mean ?They're right huh?
?They're right huh? Sweet home alabama.
Huh? Sweet home alabama. ?And now I wish
Sweet home alabama. ?And now I wish ?I never fell
?And now I wish ?I never fell yesterday, most contestants
?I never fell yesterday,
most contestants who sang original songs didn't
Yesterday, most contestants who sang
original songs didn't have much luck impressing the
Who sang original songs
didn't have much luck impressing the judges.
Have much luck impressing the judges.
Isn't it funny when you hear
Judges. Isn't it funny when you hear people's songs?
Isn't it funny when you
hear people's songs? 'cause songwriting's a
People's songs? 'cause songwriting's a particular thing.
'cause songwriting's a particular thing.
You can either do it, or you
Particular thing. You can either do it, or you can't, really.
You can either do it, or you can't,
really. But that didn't faze boston
Can't, really. But that didn't faze boston auditioner sam woolf.
But that didn't faze boston
auditioner sam woolf. Choosing to play an
Auditioner sam woolf. Choosing to play an original...was my first
Choosing to play an original...was my first instinct.
Original...was my first instinct. I knew it was a risk, but I'm
Instinct. I knew it was a risk, but I'm just gonna go for it.
I knew it was a risk, but I'm just gonna go for it. Hey, guys.
Just gonna go for it. Hey, guys. Hi, baby.
Hey, guys. Hi, baby. Gonna be playing an original
Hi, baby. Gonna be playing an original song, and--
Gonna be playing an original song,
and-- I wrote it when my mom moved
Song, and-- I wrote it when
my mom moved away a few years ago, and just,
I wrote it when my mom moved away a few years ago,
and just, I wrote how I felt during that
Away a few years ago, and just,
I wrote how I felt during that time, so...
I wrote how I felt during that time, so... mm-hmm.
Time, so... mm-hmm. Hope you guys like it.
Mm-hmm. Hope you guys like it. It's called I tried.
Hope you guys like it. It's called I tried. I tried.
?Well, it's been hard
?To figure out
?Where I'm going
?
?And it's been hard ?To keep this down ?Without them knowing
?To keep this down ?Without them knowing ?
?Without them knowing ? ?I have to find a way
? ?I have to find a way ?To hide the pain
?I have to find a way ?To hide the pain ?But nothing makes me
?To hide the pain ?But nothing makes me ?Want to have to change
?But nothing makes me ?Want to have to change ?So maybe it's time
?Want to have to change ?So maybe it's time ?To let free
?So maybe it's time ?To let free ?Forget about the things
?To let free ?Forget about the things ?When it was we
?Forget about the things ?When it was we ?I'm losing my mind
?When it was we ?I'm losing my mind ?Now I see
?I'm losing my mind ?Now I see ?Well, I tried
?Now I see ?Well, I tried ?Well, I tried
?Well, I tried ?Well, I tried ?Well, I tried
I'm feeling very anxious, but I want good news,
so we'll see what happens.
I want good news, so we'll see what happens. Hey, man.
What happens. Hey, man. You guys doing?
Hey, man. You guys doing? Hello.
You guys doing? Hello. How you doing?
Hello. How you doing? How are you?
How you doing? How are you? Good, how are you?
How are you? Good, how are you? Doing good?
Good, how are you? Doing good? Yup.
Doing good? Yup. Hanging in there?
Yup. Hanging in there? Hanging in there, yeah.
Hanging in there? Hanging in there,
yeah. I have to say, this was the
Hanging in there, yeah. I have to say,
this was the most intense week ever.
I have to say, this was the most
intense week ever. And I think it was because we
Most intense week ever. And I
think it was because we had so many great people, you
And I think it was because we had so many great people, you know?
Had so many great people, you know? At the end of the day, we're
Know? At the end of the day, we're really looking for--and the
At the end of the day, we're really
looking for--and the difficult task for us, I think,
Really looking for--and the difficult task for us,
I think, was kind of honing it down to
Difficult task for us, I think,
was kind of honing it down to who is the american idol?
Was kind of honing it down to
who is the american idol? Who could be that person?
Who is the american idol?
Who could be that person? Who has that whole package?
Who could be that person? Who has that whole package? You know?
Who has that whole package?
You know? And so at the end of the day...
we really believe that that
And so at the end of the day...
we really believe that that could be you.
We really believe that that could be you. Oh, my god.
Could be you. Oh, my god. So you made it into the
Oh, my god. So you made it into the top 15.
So you made it into the top 15. Congratulations, sam.
Top 15. Congratulations, sam. Oh, my god.
Congratulations, sam. Oh, my god. Thanks so much.
Oh, my god. Thanks so much. You bet.
Thanks so much. You bet. Thank you so much.
You bet. Thank you so much. Hey, hey, sam, what did you
Thank you so much. Hey, hey,
sam, what did you think we were gonna say?
Hey, hey, sam, what did you
think we were gonna say? I don't--I didn't know.
Think we were gonna say? I don't--I didn't know. I-I--honestly--
I don't--I didn't know.
I-I--honestly-- what did your gut tell you?
You never know, you know,
What did your gut tell you? You never know,
you know, 'cause there's a lot of good
You never know, you know,
'cause there's a lot of good people here, and--
'cause there's a lot of good people here,
and-- we're happy for you, man.
People here, and-- we're happy for you, man. You're one of them.
We're happy for you, man. You're one of them. Thanks a lot, guys.
You're one of them. Thanks a lot, guys. Be great.
Thanks a lot, guys. Be great. Thanks a lot.
Be great. Thanks a lot. Congrats, bro.
Thanks a lot. Congrats, bro. Phew!
That makes me happy for him. It makes me really happy for him.
It makes me really happy for him.
Him. He keeps amazing me, and
He keeps amazing me, and he still does.
He still does. And I love him.
And I love him.
And I love him. Congratulations.
Congratulations. So sam is through to the top 30
Congratulations. So sam is
through to the top 30 and will appear on next week's
So sam is through to the top 30 and
will appear on next week's live show, but for others, a
And will appear on next week's live show,
but for others, a path to stardom faces still
Live show, but for others, a path
to stardom faces still another bump in the road.
Path to stardom faces still
another bump in the road. I'm so nervous, so nervous.
Another bump in the road. I'm so nervous,
so nervous. I don't know what they're gonna
I'm so nervous, so nervous. I don't know what they're gonna say.
I don't know what they're gonna say. Except I want to know, but I
Say. Except I want to know, but I don't at the same time.
Except I want to know, but I
don't at the same time. This is a-a wonderful and
Don't at the same time. This
is a-a wonderful and complex journey that you all
This is a-a wonderful and
complex journey that you all have taken.
Complex journey that you all have taken. We made our decision.
Have taken. We made our decision. And it's a no.
We made our decision. And it's a no. No?
And it's a no. No? Oh.
No? Oh. The talent is just so great
Oh. The talent is just so great this year, it's just--they can't
The talent is just so great this year,
it's just--they can't pick everybody, you know?
This year, it's just--they can't pick everybody,
you know? Can't pick everybody.
Pick everybody, you know? Can't pick everybody.
Unfortunately, today it's a
Can't pick everybody. Unfortunately,
today it's a no from us, but you know, talent
Unfortunately, today it's a no from us,
but you know, talent and gift is very much like
No from us, but you know, talent and
gift is very much like running water, and when it hits
And gift is very much like running water,
and when it hits something, it just goes around
Running water, and when it hits something,
it just goes around it and keeps flowing.
Something, it just goes around
it and keeps flowing. I respect them so much, and
It and keeps flowing. I respect them so much,
and I tot--I understand.
I respect them so much,
and I tot--I understand. I know it was tough.
I tot--I understand. I know it was tough.
I know it was really hard for
I know it was tough. I know it was really hard for them.
I know it was really hard for them.
And with so much disappointment
Them. And with so much disappointment flooding the holding room,
flooding the holding room, detroit auditioner keri lynn
Flooding the holding room,
detroit auditioner keri lynn roche was determined to head in
Detroit auditioner keri lynn roche
was determined to head in with the right attitude.
Roche was determined to head in
with the right attitude. I mean, I really want it, and
With the right attitude. I mean, I really want it,
and I think I deserve a spot, for
I mean, I really want it, and I think I deserve a spot, for sure.
I think I deserve a spot, for sure. I think I'll get a spot.
Sure. I think I'll get a spot. And yesterday, keri gave a
I think I'll get a spot. And yesterday,
keri gave a soulful performance to try to do
And yesterday, keri gave a
soulful performance to try to do just that.
SOULFUL PERFORMANCE TO TRY TO DO JUST THAT. Etta James's
Just that.
?Something deep
?Deep in my soul
?Said "Cry, girl"
?Cry, cry ?When I saw you and her ?Walking by
?When I saw you and her ?Walking by ?
?Walking by ? ?I would rather
? ?I would rather ?I would rather be blind, boy
?I would rather ?I would rather be blind, boy ?
?I would rather be blind, boy ? ?Than to see you
? ?Than to see you ?Walk away from me, child
?Than to see you ?Walk away from me, child ?
?Walk away from me, child ? ?And baby, hey, baby
? ?And baby, hey, baby ?
?And baby, hey, baby ? ?Please don't walk away
? ?Please don't walk away right.
?Please don't walk away right. Let's do it.
Right. Let's do it. ?'cause I would rather
Let's do it. ?'cause I would rather ?I'd rather be blind
?'cause I would rather ?I'd
rather be blind we're listening to so many
?I'd rather be blind we're listening to so many great singers.
We're listening to so many great singers.
I mean, you've heard 'em.
Great singers. I mean, you've heard 'em.
You've been there this week.
I mean, you've heard 'em. You've been there this week. Totally.
You've been there this week. Totally. ?Than see you walk away
Totally. ?Than see you walk away ?From me, child
?Than see you walk away
?From me, child but we do only have 15 girls
?From me, child but we do only have 15 girls to choose.
But we do only have 15 girls to choose.
It was so close, just so you
To choose. It was so close, just so you know.
It was so close, just so you know. It was so close.
Know. It was so close. Can we blank on that?
It was so close. Can we blank on that?
I don't think she's a strong
Can we blank on that? I don't think she's a strong enough singer.
I don't think she's a strong enough singer. I'm on the fence.
Enough singer. I'm on the fence. It's a stylized voice.
I'm on the fence. It's a stylized voice.
It's whether we like it or not.
It's a stylized voice. It's whether
we like it or not. But today, baby, it's a no.
It's whether we like it or not. But today, baby, it's a no. Okay.
But today, baby, it's a no. Okay. ?Than to see you walk away
Okay. ?Than to see you walk away gosh, we're letting good ones
?Than to see you walk away gosh, we're letting good ones go.
Gosh, we're letting good ones go. ?From me
Go. ?From me ?Child
?From me ?Child
?Child thank you.
Welcome back to hollywood and
Final judgment.
So far, 3 guys and 2 girls are through to the top 30,
which still leaves 25 spots remaining,
Through to the top 30, which still
leaves 25 spots remaining, and in the holding room,
Still leaves 25 spots remaining,
and in the holding room, contestants are beginning to
And in the holding room,
contestants are beginning to realize just how difficult it is
Contestants are beginning to realize
just how difficult it is to get into next week's live
Realize just how difficult
it is to get into next week's live show.
Two people didn't make it,
Two people didn't make it, and they're amazing.
It's a little hard to see that.
Up next, malaya.
Up next, malaya. Where's malaya?
Up next, malaya. Where's malaya? Come on, malaya.
Where's malaya? Come on, malaya.
You're nervous, okay.
Come on, let's go. You did all the work.
Let's see if it paid off.
You did all the work. Let's see if it paid off.
Our resident tuba player first
Let's see if it paid off. Our resident
tuba player first came to us in detroit, michigan.
?I'm not expecting sorry
This 16-year-old found out
This 16-year-old found out that hollywood is a long way
This 16-year-old found
out that hollywood is a long way from home.
?
I been crying for three days.
I'm tired of crying.
No! Get stronger.
No! Get stronger. I want us to smash this.
Congratulations, you're on to
Congratulations, you're on to the next round.
And yesterday, malaya's final
Performance got off to a rocky
Start.
?Ever felt like you
?Were dreaming
?Just to find
?That you're awake
?Will lift you up
?And guide you on your way
Stop her. ?I believe in the impossible
Go back onstage and make sure
Go back onstage and make sure that you guys are all in the
Go back onstage and make
sure that you guys are all in the same place.
We had two different keys
We had two different keys going on.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, let's go. ?
? ?I can see it in the stars
? ?I can see it in the stars ?Across the sky
?I can see it in the stars ?Across the sky ?
?Across the sky ? ?Dreamt 100,000 dreams before
? ?Dreamt 100,000 dreams before ?Now I finally realize
?Dreamt 100,000 dreams before
?Now I finally realize ?You see I've waited
?Now I finally realize ?You see I've waited ?All my life
?You see I've waited ?All my life ?For this moment to arrive
?All my life ?For this moment to arrive ?And finally
?For this moment to arrive ?And finally ?Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
?And finally ?Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ?I believe in the impossible
?Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ?I
believe in the impossible ?If I reached deep
?I believe in the impossible
?If I reached deep ?Within my heart, yeah
?If I reached deep ?Within my heart,
yeah ?'cause anything is possible
?Within my heart, yeah
?'cause anything is possible ?When you believe
?'cause anything is possible ?When you believe ?Lifting me higher
?When you believe ?Lifting me higher ?I believe in love
?Lifting me higher ?I believe in love ?Love keeps lifting me
?I believe in love ?Love keeps lifting me ?Higher
?Love keeps lifting me ?Higher ?Higher, higher, higher
?Higher ?Higher, higher, higher ?Higher
?Higher, higher, higher ?Higher yeah!
?Higher yeah! ?
Yeah! ? Yeah!
? Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Thank you.
Yeah! Thank you. Get it, mama.
Thank you. Get it, mama.
Get it, mama.
Thank you.
Thank you. I can see my little self being
Thank you. I can see my little self being the next american idol.
I can see my little self
being the next american idol. Hey, "Ma-lay-a."
The next american idol. Hey, "Ma-lay-a." Hi.
Hey, "Ma-lay-a." Hi. It's "Ma-lie-a."
Hi. It's "Ma-lie-a." It's malaya.
It's "Ma-lie-a." It's malaya. Malaya, I'm sorry, thank you.
It's malaya. Malaya, I'm sorry, thank you. Take a seat, baby.
Malaya, I'm sorry, thank you.
Take a seat, baby. It means "Freedom."
I'm glad that you reminded me
It means "Freedom." I'm glad
that you reminded me of the pronunciation of your
I'm glad that you reminded me of
the pronunciation of your name, because that name has
Of the pronunciation of your name,
because that name has great potential to be a star, at
Name, because that name has
great potential to be a star, at some point.
Great potential to be a star,
at some point. You're gonna be in the top 15.
Some point. You're gonna be in the top 15. Congratulations.
You're gonna be in the top 15.
Congratulations. We look forward to seeing you
Congratulations. We look forward to seeing you grow.
We look forward to seeing you grow.
Grow.
?
? Like a cat burglar.
? Like a cat burglar. Yeah.
Like a cat burglar. Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah. Thank you. You're welcome.
Thank you. You're welcome. ?
You're welcome. ?
? Let's see what happened up
Let's see what happened up there.
Let's see what happened up there. I'm in the top 15.
There. I'm in the top 15. Ah!
I'm in the top 15. Ah!
Ah! ?
? I am the very first tuba
? I am the very first tuba player on american idol, from
I am the very first tuba player on american idol,
from southfield high school.
Player on american idol, from southfield high school. Whoa.
Southfield high school. Whoa. All right, I'm good.
As malaya dances her way into
As malaya dances her way into the live shows, father of four
As malaya dances her way into the live shows,
father of four maurice townsend anxiously
The live shows, father of four
maurice townsend anxiously takes his seat to face the
Maurice townsend anxiously takes
his seat to face the judges for what could be his
Takes his seat to face
the judges for what could be his last time.
What's going through your
What's going through your mind right now?
Kind of different, mixed
Kind of different, mixed emotions.
Yeah.
I can't--
I think we feel the same.
I think we feel the same. The thing is, like, some people
I think we feel the same. The thing is,
like, some people can sing really well.
The thing is, like, some people
can sing really well. You can sing really well.
?Don't you ever say
?I just walked away
?I will always want you
?I came in
?I came in ?Like a wrecking ball
?I came in ?Like a wrecking ball ?I never hit so hard in love
?Like a wrecking ball ?I
never hit so hard in love ?All I wanted was
?I never hit so hard in love
?All I wanted was ?To break your walls
?All I wanted was ?To break your walls ?All you ever did was
?To break your walls ?All you ever did was ?Wreck me
?All you ever did was ?Wreck me ?Yeah, you, you wrecked me
?Wreck me ?Yeah, you, you wrecked me ?Yeah
Thank you.
Yeah.
It was like, "Ooh."
You've got to have something in your
voice that comes out and makes a connection, and it's not
In your voice that comes out and makes a connection,
and it's not just about runs and all that
Makes a connection, and it's
not just about runs and all that sort of skill.
Just about runs and all that sort of skill.
It's that other undefinable
Sort of skill. It's that
other undefinable thing that you've just got to
It's that other undefinable thing that you've just got to have.
Hmm.
That's why it's been so hard
That's why it's been so hard for us, you know?
That's why it's been so hard for us,
you know? Man, you're a good singer.
For us, you know? Man,
you're a good singer. You got a good voice.
You're a really good singer.
Really good.
But we need other things as
But we need other things as well on top of that.
Well on top of that. But we'd like to see you in the
But we'd like to see you in the top 30.
Top 30. ?
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
Thanks. Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You bet.
I'm rooting for you, baby.
Yes.
I'm rooting for him.
To be in the top 30 right now
To be in the top 30 right now just feels like I'm dreaming.
To be in the top 30 right now just
feels like I'm dreaming. I'm waiting for somebody to
Just feels like I'm dreaming.
I'm waiting for somebody to pinch me and wake me up.
I'm waiting for somebody to pinch me and wake me up. ?
Pinch me and wake me up. ? Yes.
? Yes. Thank you.
Yes. Thank you.
What's most gratifying about this?
That I get to go home and
That I get to go home and tell my babies and my wife that
That I get to go home and tell
my babies and my wife that I made the top 30, man.
Tell my babies and my wife that I made the top 30, man.
We'll see you soon.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, thank you. Congratulations.
Oh, thank you. Congratulations. All right, maurice.
Congratulations. All right,
maurice. So maurice's solo performance
All right, maurice. So maurice's
solo performance earned him a spot in the top 30,
So maurice's solo performance earned
him a spot in the top 30, and in an otherwise tense day of
Earned him a spot in the top 30, and
in an otherwise tense day of auditions, lightened up for a
And in an otherwise tense day of auditions,
lightened up for a moment with a visit from an old
Auditions, lightened up
for a moment with a visit from an old friend.
Yo, yo, look who it is.
A hand for these judges!
A hand for these judges! A hand for these amazing judges!
A hand for these amazing judges! Amazing judges!
Hey.
Oh, cool, cool.
Oh, you got it, you got it.
Oh, you got it, you got it. Come on, come on.
Qjust for a beat, just for a
Qjust for a beat, just for a beat, randy, just for a beat.
Getting out of shape.
You're in great hands.
Hey, judge us, judge us.
Five, six, seven, eight.
?Big chief
?Big chief ?Got plenty of fire water
?Hoo hoo
?Big chief
?Big chief ?Got plenty of fire water
?Hoo hoo
?Do like the big chief
?Do like the big chief ?Said
?Do like the big chief ?Said ?On the mardi gras day
?Said ?On the mardi gras day ?Big chief
?On the mardi gras day ?Big chief ?Got plenty of fire water
?Ooh ooh
?Big chief
?Big chief ?Got plenty of fire water
No, no.
Oh.
Oh. ?Da da da da da da
?Da da da da da da, da
You will not be going
Through.
If they say no, I'm just
Gonna--I'm just--
I don't even know.
Guess I gotta cross that bridge when I get there.
Next to cross that bridge is
Next to cross that bridge is bria anai johnson.
Oh, this is intense.
Oh, this is intense. It's, like, huge.
Oh, this is intense. It's, like, huge. Oh, my gosh.
It's, like, huge. Oh, my gosh. Let's see what they say.
Oh, my gosh. Let's see what they say. Can I run?
Let's see what they say.
Can I run? Let me speed walk, 'cause this
Can I run? Let me speed walk, 'cause this is kind of intense.
Let me speed walk, 'cause this is kind of intense. Hoo.
Power walking, babe.
Yeah.
That's it, how you doin'?
Hoo, I got a director's
Hoo, I got a director's chair.
Yeah.
Great, it feels so great.
Bria.
Bria. What can I say about you, bria?
Bria. What can I say about you,
bria? You did a great job yesterday.
James Brown's It's a Man's,
?Man made a car
?To help us get around a road
?Man made a train ?To carry a heavy, heavy load
?Man made a train ?To carry a heavy,
heavy load ?See, this is a man's
?To carry a heavy, heavy load ?See,
this is a man's ?This is a man's
?See, this is a man's ?This is a man's ?This is a man's world
?This is a man's ?This is a man's world yeah, yeah.
?This is a man's world yeah, yeah. ?But it wouldn't be nothing
Yeah, yeah. ?But it wouldn't be nothing
?Without a woman or a girl
?But it wouldn't be nothing ?Without a woman or a girl
?Without a woman or a girl whoo!
Whoo! ?Oh, yeah
Whoo! ?Oh, yeah you know, this is a tough
?Oh, yeah you know, this is a tough competition this year.
You know, this is a tough competition this year. You know that.
Competition this year. You know that. Everybody performs
You know that. Everybody performs differently, and...it's crazy.
Everybody performs differently, and...it's crazy.
Differently, and...it's crazy. It is.
It is. You know what's crazy?
It is. You know what's crazy? What?
You know what's crazy? What? You made it into the top 15
What? You made it into the top 15 girls.
You made it into the top 15 girls. Maybe that's not so crazy,
Girls. Maybe that's not so crazy, because we love you.
Maybe that's not so crazy, because we love you. Oh!
Because we love you. Oh! Congratulations.
Oh! Congratulations. Thank you, thank you, thank
Congratulations. Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you. There she goes.
You. There she goes. There she goes.
There she goes. There she goes.
There she goes. Has it been tough this week
Has it been tough this week for you?
Has it been tough this week for you? It's been very tough this
For you? It's been very tough this week.
It's been very tough this week. Well, here she comes.
Week. Well, here she comes. Your little girl's here with...
Well, here she comes. Your little girl's here with...
Your little girl's here with... give us the bulletin.
Give us the bulletin. I made it.
Give us the bulletin. I made it. Yeah!
I made it. Yeah! The drama queen here.
Yeah! The drama queen here.
The drama queen here. Bria is through, which leaves
Bria is through, which leaves one less spot for the ladies.
Bria is through, which leaves one
less spot for the ladies. Up next is jessica meuse, who
One less spot for the ladies. Up
next is jessica meuse, who had a tough time during group
Up next is jessica meuse,
who had a tough time during group round.
Had a tough time during group round. Ground rounds, oh, my gosh.
Round. Ground rounds, oh,
my gosh. I don't even have the words for
Ground rounds, oh, my gosh. I don't even have the words for it.
I don't even have the words for it. ?Up in the club
It. ?Up in the club ?
?Up in the club ? Overall, the group was weak.
? Overall, the group was weak. Stephanie, my love, I'm
Overall, the group was weak. Stephanie,
my love, I'm sorry, this is the end of the
Stephanie, my love, I'm sorry,
this is the end of the road for you.
Sorry, this is the end of the road for you.
She's a superstar all around.
Road for you. She's a superstar all around.
Stephanie's mom flipped.
She's a superstar all around.
Stephanie's mom flipped. You would not do anything.
Stephanie's mom flipped.
You would not do anything. You are so rude.
You would not do anything. You are so rude. We need to stop.
You are so rude. We need to stop. You did, you did, and it's--
We need to stop. You did, you did,
and it's-- honestly, it really hurt,
You did, you did, and it's-- honestly,
it really hurt, 'cause even though I didn't
Honestly, it really hurt,
'cause even though I didn't really know what I was doing, I
'cause even though I didn't really
know what I was doing, I still gave it my all and I
Really know what I was doing,
I still gave it my all and I still did it.
Still gave it my all and I still did it.
After a dismal group round,
Still did it. After a dismal group round,
jessica decides, for her last
After a dismal group round, jessica decides,
for her last performance, she needs to take a
Jessica decides, for her last performance,
she needs to take a risk.
Performance, she needs to take a risk.
I picked an original song for
Risk. I picked an original song for solo day.
I picked an original song for solo day.
I wanted to convey to the judges
Solo day. I wanted to convey to the judges that this is me.
I wanted to convey to the
judges that this is me. I'm a singer/songwriter.
That this is me. I'm a singer/songwriter.
This is the package, this is
I'm a singer/songwriter. This is the package, this is what I do.
This is the package, this is what I do. Gotta redeem myself.
What I do. Gotta redeem myself. This is done.
Gotta redeem myself. This is done. It's about an idiot.
This is done. It's about an idiot.
It's about an idiot. So you wrote it about me.
So you wrote it about me. Thank you so much.
?I'm done
?Being the last to know ?Everything ?I'm done
?Everything ?I'm done ?Being the only one at home
?I'm done ?Being the only one at home ?Yeah, I'm done
?Being the only one at home ?Yeah, I'm done ?Being the only one
?Yeah, I'm done ?Being the only one ?Sleeping alone
?Being the only one ?Sleeping alone ?Yeah, I'm done
?Sleeping alone ?Yeah, I'm done ?Being the only one
?Yeah, I'm done ?Being the only one ?I'm done, done
?Being the only one ?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done
?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done ?Puttin' this sick horse down
?Baby, I'm done ?Puttin' this sick horse down ?I'm done, done
?Puttin' this sick horse down ?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done
?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done ?Bury this love
?Baby, I'm done ?Bury this love ?Deep in the ground
?Bury this love ?Deep in the ground ?I'm done, done
?Deep in the ground ?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done
?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done ?Who you gonna crawl to now?
?Baby, I'm done ?Who you gonna crawl to now? ?I'm done, done
?Who you gonna crawl to now? ?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done
?I'm done, done ?Baby, I'm done ?Don't even turn back around
?Baby, I'm done ?Don't even turn back around
?Don't even turn back around thank you.
Thank you. Today, jessica will not be
Thank you. Today,
jessica will not be making her journey to the judges
Today, jessica will not
be making her journey to the judges alone.
Making her journey to the judges alone. She will be joined by
Alone. She will be joined by jesse roach, who wowed the
She will be joined by jesse roach,
who wowed the judges at the austin auditions.
Jesse roach, who wowed the judges
at the austin auditions. ?Is do you still love me?
Judges at the austin auditions. ?Is do you still love me? ?Do ya?
?Is do you still love me? ?Do ya?
?Do ya? I love you.
I love you. I never thought that I would
I love you. I never thought that I would be where I am now.
I never thought that I would be where I am now.
With singing, I just kind of
Be where I am now. With singing,
I just kind of picked it up on a whim.
With singing, I just kind of picked it up on a whim.
This is one of the biggest days
Picked it up on a whim. This is one
of the biggest days of my life besides my son being
This is one of the biggest
days of my life besides my son being born.
Of my life besides my son being born.
I definitely feel like this is
Born. I definitely feel
like this is something that's legendary to me
I definitely feel like this is
something that's legendary to me in my journey in life.
Something that's legendary to me in my journey in life.
?Wide open spaces
?Room to make a big mistake
?She needs new faces ?She
knows the high stakes ?She knows the high stakes
?She knows the high stakes
?She knows the high stakes ?Wide open spaces
?She knows the high stakes ?Wide open spaces ?She knows
?Wide open spaces ?She knows ?The highest stakes
?She knows ?The highest stakes ?She knows the high stakes
?The highest stakes ?She knows the high stakes sorry.
?She knows the high stakes sorry. Thank you.
Sorry. Thank you.
Thank you.
I think yes.
I think yes. I don't see it working.
I think yes. I don't see it working. Like her better than her.
I don't see it working.
Like her better than her. Yeah, but she's more
Like her better than her. Yeah, but she's more interesting.
Yeah, but she's more interesting. Can we keep her at a maybe
Interesting. Can we keep her at a maybe for now?
Can we keep her at a maybe for now? Yeah.
For now? Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
Yeah. Yeah, I think so. Now, jessica and jesse must
Yeah, I think so. Now,
jessica and jesse must meet their fate together.
Now, jessica and jesse must meet their fate together. Good luck.
Meet their fate together. Good luck. Everyone's calling it "The
Good luck. Everyone's
calling it "The final judgment," And that makes
Everyone's calling it "The final judgment,"
And that makes it kind of scary.
Final judgment," And that makes it kind of scary.
It's, like, apocalyptic almost.
It kind of scary. It's, like, apocalyptic almost.
It means more to me now that
It's, like, apocalyptic almost. It
means more to me now that I've put so much work and effort
It means more to me now that I've put
so much work and effort and energy into it, and it means
I've put so much work and effort and energy into it,
and it means the world to me to be here.
And energy into it, and it
means the world to me to be here. How y'all doin'?
The world to me to be here. How y'all doin'? Pretty good.
How y'all doin'? Pretty good. How are you?
Pretty good. How are you? Tense down in that room, huh?
How are you? Tense down in that room, huh? Yes, it is.
Tense down in that room, huh? Yes, it is. Yeah.
Yes, it is. Yeah. We've run into a little bit of a
Yeah. We've run into a
little bit of a problem with the two of you.
We've run into a little bit of a
problem with the two of you. There's a limited amount of
Problem with the two of you.
There's a limited amount of seats on the bus, and we need to
There's a limited amount of seats on the bus,
and we need to know definitively who gets that
Seats on the bus, and we need to know
definitively who gets that seat, and it was so close that
Know definitively who gets that seat,
and it was so close that we're gonna need to hear you
Seat, and it was so close
that we're gonna need to hear you guys sing...
We're gonna need to hear you guys sing... right now.
There's a limited amount of
Seats on the bus, and we need to
Know definitively who gets that
Seat, and it was so close that
We're gonna need to hear you
Guys sing...
Right now.
What?
What? That's crazy.
Wow.
So that's why everything
So that's why everything seemed so crazy for the last
seemed so crazy for the last couple of minutes.
All right, I'ma sing
All right, I'ma sing simple man.
All right, I'ma sing simple man. You want to go first?
Simple man. You want to go first? Okay, go.
You want to go first? Okay, go. ?Mama told me
Okay, go. ?Mama told me ?When I was young
?Mama told me ?When I was young ?Said, "Sit beside me
?When I was young ?Said, "Sit beside me ?My only son
?Said, "Sit beside me ?My only son ?And be a simple kind of man
?My only son ?And be a simple kind of man ?Oh, be something
?And be a simple kind of man ?Oh,
be something ?You'll love and understand
?Oh, be something ?You'll love and understand ?Baby, be a simple
?You'll love and understand ?Baby, be a simple ?Kind of man"
?Baby, be a simple ?Kind of man" All right, baby, thank you so
?Kind of man" All right,
baby, thank you so much, you have a seat.
All right, baby, thank you so much,
you have a seat. Thank you, darling.
Much, you have a seat. Thank you,
darling. All right, I'm gonna do
Thank you, darling. All right, I'm gonna do k.T. Oslin, do ya.
All right, I'm gonna do k.T. Oslin, do ya. Just do it.
K.T. Oslin, do ya. Just do it. Okay.
Just do it. Okay. All right.
Okay. All right. ?Do you still get that thrill
All right. ?Do you still get that thrill ?When you see me walkin'
?Do you still get that thrill
?When you see me walkin' ?Up that hill?
?When you see me walkin' ?Up that hill? ?Now, do ya?
?Up that hill? ?Now, do ya? ?Do you still like
?Now, do ya? ?Do you still like ?The feel of my body
?Do you still like ?The feel of my body
?When it's lyin' next to ya?
?The feel of my body ?When it's lyin' next to ya? ?Oh
?When it's lyin' next to ya? ?Oh ?But I guess what I'm askin'
?Oh ?But I guess what I'm askin' ?Is do you still love me
?But I guess what I'm askin' ?Is do you still love me ?Do ya?
?Is do you still love me ?Do ya? All right.
?Do ya? All right. Thank you, guys.
All right. Thank you, guys. If you guys could give us a
Thank you, guys. If you guys could give us a chance to talk...
If you guys could give us a chance to talk...
you talk about stress.
Chance to talk... you talk about stress. My first reaction was--
You talk about stress. My first reaction was-- they can hear.
My first reaction was-- they can hear. But I was still
They can hear. But I was still more interested in some weird
But I was still more interested in some weird way in jessica.
More interested in some weird way in jessica. Yeah.
Way in jessica. Yeah. I disagree.
Yeah. I disagree. I think the other one proved
I disagree. I think the
other one proved that she's better right now.
Oh!
You sounded good. What are your thoughts?
Um...jessica's got a slightly
What are your thoughts?
Um...jessica's got a slightly broader spectrum.
Um...jessica's got a slightly broader spectrum. Diversity, yeah.
Broader spectrum. Diversity, yeah. Agreed.
Diversity, yeah. Agreed. But jesse is compelling.
By just a little bit. It's just so... yeah.
It's just so... yeah. 'cause they're so--
Yeah. 'cause they're so-- infinitesimally small, narrow
'cause they're so-- infinitesimally small, narrow margin.
Guys, you can come back.
We're doing the right thing, yes? I think somehow we have to
Yes? I think somehow we have to make a decision.
I think somehow we have to make a decision.
So...there's so many things.
Make a decision. So...there's so many things.
This is the hardest decision
So...there's so many things. This
is the hardest decision of the competition, just so you
This is the hardest
decision of the competition, just so you know.
Of the competition, just so you know. It--unquestionably.
Know. It--unquestionably. You're extraordinarily
It--unquestionably. You're
extraordinarily compelling, talented, individual
You're extraordinarily compelling,
talented, individual voices, both of you.
Compelling, talented, individual voices,
both of you. But for the purposes of what
Voices, both of you. But for the
purposes of what we're trying to do, the person
But for the purposes of what we're trying to do,
the person that's going through...
We're trying to do,
the person that's going through... is jessica.
That's going through... is jessica.
Is jessica. I'm so sorry, jesse.
I'm so sorry, jesse. It's okay.
I'm so sorry, jesse. It's okay. We'll miss you, jesse.
It's okay. We'll miss you, jesse. Yeah, babe.
We'll miss you, jesse. Yeah, babe. Some great singing.
Yeah, babe. Some great singing. Thank you.
Some great singing. Thank you. Both of you.
Thank you. Both of you. Amazing singer.
Both of you. Amazing singer. Thank you.
Amazing singer. Thank you. Thank you, jesse.
Thank you. Thank you, jesse.
Thank you, jesse. Congratulations.
Congratulations. Thank you, girls.
Congratulations. Thank you, girls. Thank you for singing on the
Thank you, girls. Thank you for singing on the spot too.
Thank you for singing on the spot too.
I've always wanted it equally
Spot too. I've always wanted
it equally and it just hurts a little bit
I've always wanted it
equally and it just hurts a little bit to...
And it just hurts a little bit to...
To... feel defeated.
Feel defeated. I don't know how else we
Feel defeated. I don't know how else we could have decided.
I don't know how else we could have decided.
But you know, it's about
Could have decided. But you know, it's about moments.
But you know, it's about moments. The thing that tipped it,
Moments. The thing that tipped it, jessica.
The thing that tipped it, jessica. All right, I'ma sing
Jessica. All right, I'ma sing simple man.
All right, I'ma sing simple man. You want to go first?
Simple man. You want to go first? Okay.
You want to go first? Okay. All right.
Okay. All right. "I got it, I'll sing first."
All right. "I got it, I'll sing first." Just a different fighter
"I got it, I'll sing first." Just a different fighter spirit.
Just a different fighter spirit. You need a fighter in here.
Spirit. You need a fighter in here. You need a fighter.
You need a fighter in here.
You need a fighter. So jesse roach's long
You need a fighter. So jesse
roach's long american idol journey comes to
So jesse roach's long american idol journey comes to an end.
American idol journey comes to an end.
An end. But jessica meuse's road to
But jessica meuse's road to stardom is just getting on
But jessica meuse's road to stardom is just getting on track.
I'M READY TO STOP SELLING CDs
I'M READY TO STOP SELLING CDs OUT OF MY TRUNK, AND I'M READY
I'M READY TO STOP SELLING CDs OUT OF MY TRUNK,
AND I'M READY TO BE THE SINGER, SONGWRITER,
Out of my trunk, and I'm ready to be the singer,
songwriter, musician, artist that I'm
To be the singer, songwriter,
musician, artist that I'm supposed to be.
Okay.
Okay. Dexter, this is your time.
?When I was
?When I was ?Eight years old
?When I was ?Eight years old ?Knee-high to a concrete door
?Eight years old ?Knee-high
to a concrete door ?Didn't have a worry
?Knee-high to a concrete door ?Didn't have a worry ?In the world
Dexter, what do you think it
Dexter, what do you think it is that you bring to this group
Dexter, what do you think it is
that you bring to this group of singers and artists?
Is that you bring to this group of
singers and artists? What's that--separates you from
Of singers and artists?
What's that--separates you from everybody else?
I'm--you can tell, I'm real
I'm--you can tell, I'm real bad country, and I just--
You're real bad country.
What is it that you do again?
I work on a farm, I'm a--
That's right, you're a
That's right, you're a farmer.
Yes, ma'am.
?We gotta cut up
?All this ground
?Can't leave none behind I don't know,
just--I'm shakin' right now, I'm scared to death.
I don't know, just--I'm shakin' right now, I'm scared to death.
Well, I mean, the thing that
Well, I mean, the thing that we're--we're trying to find
we're--we're trying to find people that are the real deal.
We're--we're trying to find people
that are the real deal. That's the most important thing.
People that are the real deal.
That's the most important thing. You just--you can't be sort of
That's the most important thing.
You just--you can't be sort of phony, you know?
Mm-hmm.
You can't be all hat, no
You can't be all hat, no cattle.
Yes, sir.
I think...
?'cause if you've seen
?'cause if you've seen ?What I've seen
Um--
?And done what I've done
?And done what I've done ?And you've been
?And done what I've done ?And you've been ?Where I've been
?And you've been ?Where I've been
?Where I've been ?And you've farmed
?And you've farmed ?Where I've farmed
?And you've farmed ?Where I've farmed ?There's only one thing
?Where I've farmed ?There's only one thing ?Comes to mind
?There's only one thing ?Comes to mind
?Comes to mind oh, my god.
Oh, my god. Whoo!
Yeah!
Yeah! ?I'm a farmer's grandson
Good job, man.
Phew!
Was there ever a doubt?
Yes, there was much doubts.
I'm scared to death.
I'm scared to death. My legs were about to shake off
I'm scared to death. My
legs were about to shake off out of the chair.
My legs were about to shake off out of the chair.
Out of the chair. Oh, man.
Oh, man. Just think about, I was in my
Oh, man. Just think about,
I was in my hometown just a few months ago,
Just think about, I was in my hometown
just a few months ago, not even thinkin' nothin' about
Hometown just a few months ago,
not even thinkin' nothin' about this.
He's the real deal, that guy.
Yeah.
That's what's special about
That's what's special about this show, right?
That's what's special about this show,
right? Different pace, a different
This show, right? Different pace,
a different world, and now look at you,
Different pace, a different world,
and now look at you, you're on your way.
Yeah, on my way.
Congratulations, dexter.
Thank you.
Thank you. ?He says, "Go fast"
Thank you. ?He says, "Go fast" I'm ready to leave the farm work
?He says, "Go fast" I'm ready to leave the farm work behind.
I'm ready to leave the farm work behind.
?And he smiled and laughed
Behind. ?And he smiled and laughed oh, my gosh, dude.
?And he smiled and laughed oh,
my gosh, dude. I'm on the top 30 of
Oh, my gosh, dude. I'm on the top 30 of american idol.
I'm on the top 30 of american idol. That's crazy.
American idol. That's crazy. ?I'm a farmer's grandson
That's crazy. ?I'm a farmer's grandson
?I'm a farmer's grandson thank you, guys.
Thank you, guys. Emmanuel.
Thank you, guys. Emmanuel. Are you sure?
Emmanuel. Are you sure?
Are you sure? Are you sure you're ready?
Are you sure you're ready? I am as ready as I can be
Are you sure you're ready?
I am as ready as I can be right about now.
Now, do you think you made
Right about now. Now, do you think you made your mark this week?
Now, do you think you made your mark this week?
Yeah, I literally, like, left
Your mark this week? Yeah, I literally,
like, left my blood on the floor.
Yeah, I literally, like, left my blood on the floor.
My blood on the floor. So hopefully, somebody mopped
So hopefully, somebody mopped it up.
?Time on my hand
?Since you been away, baby
?I-I-I ain't got no plans ?No, no, n-n-n-no, no, no, no
?No, no, n-n-n-no, no, no, no
Hey, hey, emmanuel, you know how
Hey, hey, emmanuel, you know how you would pronounce the name of
Hey, hey, emmanuel, you know
how you would pronounce the name of our president?
You would pronounce the
name of our president? Br-r-r-r-ack obama.
Our president? Br-r-r-r-ack obama.
Br-r-r-r-ack obama. Yes.
Yes. Yeah, yeah!
Yes. Yeah, yeah! I want to see you and jen have a
Yeah, yeah! I want to see you and jen have a walk-off in heels.
I want to see you and jen have
a walk-off in heels. Buddy, I am dying for it!
Walk-off in heels. Buddy, I am dying for it! Oh!
Buddy, I am dying for it! Oh! Yeah!
Oh! Yeah! Get your heels on, and we'll
Yeah! Get your heels on, and we'll do it.
Get your heels on, and we'll do it. But you got to buy 'em,
Do it. But you got to buy 'em, though.
But you got to buy 'em, though. Oh!
Though. Oh! Yeah.
Oh! Yeah. I'll get you a pair.
Yeah. I'll get you a pair. All right, right, right.
I'll get you a pair. All right, right, right.
All right, right, right. ?Oh, baby, I'm goin' down
?Oh, baby, I'm goin' down ?I'm goin' down, yeah
?Oh, baby, I'm goin' down ?I'm goin' down, yeah yes.
?I'm goin' down, yeah yes. ?'cause you ain't around
Yes. ?'cause you ain't around I'm right here.
?'cause you ain't around I'm right here. ?My whole world's upsi--
I'm right here. ?My whole world's upsi-- ? Down
?My whole world's upsi-- ? Down
? Down even though emmanuel killed
Even though emmanuel killed it with his solo performance,
Even though emmanuel killed it with
his solo performance, the nightmare of groups still
It with his solo performance,
the nightmare of groups still haunts him.
The nightmare of groups still haunts him. Group day.
Haunts him. Group day. Complication.
Group day. Complication. Will you be singing with us
Complication. Will you be singing with us today?
Will you be singing with us today? Y'all don't have anybody
Today? Y'all don't have anybody else?
Y'all don't have anybody else? I came here to win this.
Else? I came here to win this. I'm going to win.
I CAME HERE TO WIN THIS. I'M GOING TO WIN. All:
I'M GOING TO WIN. All: I DIDN'T HEAR ANY SINGING.
I didn't hear any singing. It's sad, because I wanted to
I didn't hear any singing. It's sad,
because I wanted to hear your voices.
It's sad, because I wanted to hear your voices. Ugh.
Hear your voices. Ugh. This was terrible, but there's
Ugh. This was terrible,
but there's potential, and that potential is
This was terrible, but there's potential,
and that potential is in emmanuel.
Potential, and that potential is in emmanuel.
I just don't want to be a
In emmanuel. I just don't
want to be a singer, I want to be an american
I just don't want to be a singer,
I want to be an american idol, and I'll find out in five,
Singer, I want to be an american idol,
and I'll find out in five, four, three, two, now.
Idol, and I'll find out in five, four, three, two, now.
Emmanuel. Hi, baby. How are you?
Hi, baby. How are you? What's the matter?
How are you? What's the matter? Are you gonna cry?
What's the matter? Are you gonna cry? I am.
Are you gonna cry? I am. Please don't cry.
I am. Please don't cry. Don't cry.
Please don't cry. Don't cry. Why are you crying?
Don't cry. Why are you crying? For so many reasons.
Why are you crying? For so many reasons. I'm from miami.
For so many reasons. I'm from miami. Mm-hmm.
I'm from miami. Mm-hmm. There's a lot of people who I
Mm-hmm. There's a lot of people who I went to school with who are
There's a lot of people who I went
to school with who are talented, and that are so scared
Went to school with who are talented,
and that are so scared to do something like this...
Talented, and that are
so scared to do something like this... yeah.
To do something like this... yeah. And that feel like they don't
Yeah. And that feel like they don't have a outlet, and to show
And that feel like they don't have a outlet,
and to show people back at home that if you
Have a outlet, and to show people
back at home that if you stay--if you stay dedicated, you
People back at home that if you
stay--if you stay dedicated, you can get to your dream.
Stay--if you stay dedicated,
you can get to your dream. It's so hard.
Can get to your dream. It's so hard. Mm.
It's so hard. Mm. It's--I could have been one
Mm. It's--I could have been one of those people.
It's--I could have been one of those people. Mm-hmm.
Of those people. Mm-hmm. And I'm here, right?
Mm-hmm. And I'm here, right? I'm on american idol, and if I
And I'm here, right? I'm on american idol,
and if I go home, I'll be devastated, but
I'm on american idol, and if I go home,
I'll be devastated, but at least I made it this far, and
Go home, I'll be devastated, but at
least I made it this far, and I met you guys, and you guys
At least I made it this far, and I met you guys,
and you guys were so nice to me, and I made
I met you guys, and you guys were so nice to me,
and I made you guys laugh, and you're gonna
Were so nice to me, and I made you guys laugh,
and you're gonna buy my shoes, and--and--
You guys laugh, and you're gonna buy my shoes, and--and--
He's holding you to that,
He's holding you to that, jen.
Baby, that's what makes this
Baby, that's what makes this so hard, you know what I mean,
Baby, that's what makes this so hard,
you know what I mean, it's because there's so many
So hard, you know what I mean, it's
because there's so many people who sing so great and who
It's because there's so many people who
sing so great and who have the same dream that you do.
Mm-hmm.
It's been heartbreaking all
It's been heartbreaking all day for us.
Day for us. ?
?
But I guess next time I see
But I guess next time I see you, I'll just bring you
But I guess next time I see you,
I'll just bring you the pair of shoes then, since
You, I'll just bring you the pair of shoes then,
since you're in the top 15.
Oh, my--
Br-r-r-ra! Yes!
Br-r-r-ra! Yes! Oh.
I was so hoping you'd say
I was so hoping you'd say that.
Group hug.
Group hug. I want a group hug.
I want a group hug. Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! Thank you guys so much for
Oh, my god! Thank you guys so much for believing in me.
Congratulations.
Thank you guys so much.
Congrats, emmanuel.
Br-r-r-ra!
Br-r-r-ra! ?
Br-r-r-ra! ? Yeah!
Emmanuel.
Ah!
I made it! I made it!
Congratulations!
Oh, my god, I'm so happy!
Uh! Uh!
Uh! Uh! I'm happy for you.
Oh!
Oh! Oh, that's--
You made it!
You made it! Congratulations.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm great.
I am in the top 30 of
I am in the top 30 of american idol.
I am in the top 30 of american idol. I'm so happy.
American idol. I'm so happy.
How's the room feeling
How's the room feeling downstairs?
It's sad to see your friends
It's sad to see your friends go.
Yeah.
Made such a family over the
Made such a family over the past couple days.
You know when there's intense
You know when there's intense experiences like that, it's
experiences like that, it's like--it joins everybody
Experiences like that, it's like--it joins everybody together.
Like--it joins everybody together. It's like, "We're in this
Together. It's like, "We're in this together!"
Especially in this business,
Especially in this business, because we're all artists...
both: YEAH.
both: SO WE'RE ALL SO OPENLY
So we're all so openly emotional all the time that it's
So we're all so openly emotional all
the time that it's even more extreme, that bonding,
Emotional all the time that
it's even more extreme, that bonding, I think.
Yeah, definitely.
Yeah, definitely. It's hard to see people who
Yeah, definitely. It's hard
to see people who share the same love interest as
It's hard to see people who share the
same love interest as you do be really sad about it.
And everybody's so talented.
Yeah, totally.
So it's--you know, as
So it's--you know, as difficult as it is for you to be
So it's--you know, as difficult
as it is for you to be like, "Oh, why this person?
Difficult as it is for you to be like,
"Oh, why this person? Why that person?"
Like, "Oh, why this person? Why that person?"
You know, it's just as hard for
Why that person?" You know, it's just as hard for us, you know.
Yeah.
We're, like, down there
We're, like, down there looking at all your pictures and
We're, like, down there looking
at all your pictures and thinking about all the
Looking at all your pictures and
thinking about all the performances, and saying, "Okay,
Thinking about all the performances,
and saying, "Okay, who really fits this mode?"
Yeah.
"Who belongs in here?"
Yeah, totally.
You know?
You know? "Who are the american idols
You know? "Who are the american idols here?"
"Who are the american idols here?" "Who could be?"
Yeah.
And that's what it comes down
And that's what it comes down to.
Like most others, mk had a
Like most others, mk had a tumultuous group round, but
tumultuous group round, but could she overcome her
Tumultuous group round, but could
she overcome her exhaustion and deliver a stellar
Could she overcome her exhaustion
and deliver a stellar performance when it mattered
Exhaustion and deliver a
stellar performance when it mattered most?
Performance when it mattered most?
Most? ?
?Lights gone, days end
?Struggling to pay the rent
?Long nights, strange men ? ?And they say
? ?And they say ?She's in the class "A" Team
?And they say ?She's in the class "A" Team ?Stuck in her daydream
?She's in the class "A" Team
?Stuck in her daydream ?Been this way since 18
?Stuck in her daydream ?Been
this way since 18 ?But lately her face seems
?Been this way since 18 ?But
lately her face seems ?Slowly sinking, wasting
?But lately her face seems ?Slowly sinking,
wasting ?Crumbling like pastries
?Slowly sinking, wasting
?Crumbling like pastries ?And they scream
?Crumbling like pastries
?And they scream ?The worst things in life
?And they scream ?The worst things in life ?Come free to us
?The worst things in life ?Come free to us ?'cause we're all
?Come free to us ?'cause we're all ?Under the upper hand
?'cause we're all ?Under the upper hand
?Go mad for a couple grams
?Under the upper hand ?Go mad
for a couple grams ?She don't want to go outside
I know.
?She flies to
?The motherland
?Goes mad for a couple grams
She's serious too.
Exactly.
Yeah.
?Fly-y-y ?
? I think with you, it was kind of
I think with you, it was kind of of difficult, 'cause we all kind
I think with you, it was kind of of difficult,
'cause we all kind of fell in love with your voice
Of difficult, 'cause we all kind of
fell in love with your voice and your style, but you're not
Of fell in love with your voice and your style,
but you're not the typical american idol.
And your style, but you're
not the typical american idol. No, I'm not.
The typical american idol. No, I'm not. You know?
No, I'm not. You know? And we wonder, is that a good
You know? And we wonder,
is that a good thing, is that a bad thing?
And we wonder, is that a good thing,
is that a bad thing? Do we think it--what will
Thing, is that a bad thing?
Do we think it--what will america--and all of these
Do we think it--what will
america--and all of these questions start coming up.
America--and all of these
questions start coming up. How do you fit in?
Questions start coming up. How do you fit in? Yeah.
How do you fit in? Yeah. Do you not fit in?
Yeah. Do you not fit in? I have my own thoughts on
Do you not fit in? I have my own thoughts on that too, yeah.
I have my own thoughts on that too,
yeah. What's your thoughts on that?
That too, yeah. What's your thoughts on that?
I'm very obviously gay, and
What's your thoughts on that? I'm very obviously gay,
and there are always gonna be people
I'm very obviously gay, and there are
always gonna be people in america and everywhere else
There are always gonna be people in
america and everywhere else who are definitely gonna hate,
In america and everywhere else who
are definitely gonna hate, but I think that in the last
Who are definitely gonna hate, but I
think that in the last two years, there have been a lot
But I think that in the last two years,
there have been a lot of things that have really
Two years, there have been a lot of
things that have really changed that, and have really
Of things that have really changed that,
and have really made it a positive thing.
Changed that, and have
really made it a positive thing. Thank goodness.
Made it a positive thing. Thank goodness. This is a tough day.
The world is changing, I think. Mm-hmm. We think...
Mm-hmm. We think... strongly.
We think... strongly. That you could be an
Strongly. That you could be an american idol.
That you could be an american idol. Really?
American idol. Really? And we'd like you to be in
Really? And we'd like you to be in our top 15 girls.
And we'd like you to be in our top 15 girls.
You have a great voice, mk.
Our top 15 girls. You have a great voice, mk. Thank you so much.
You have a great voice, mk. Thank you so much. You belong here.
Thank you so much. You belong here. Thank you guys so much.
You belong here. Thank you guys so much. You're welcome.
Thank you guys so much. You're welcome. Congratulations, mk.
You're welcome. Congratulations, mk. Can I hug you guys?
Congratulations, mk. Can I hug you guys? Thank you so much.
Can I hug you guys? Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so much. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you so much. Congratulations!
Thank you so much. Congratulations! Congrats.
Congratulations! Congrats. Thank you guys.
Congrats. Thank you guys. The world is changing.
Thank you guys. The world is changing.
The world is changing. Mk's in.
Mk's in. Come on.
Mk's in. Come on. Good job.
Come on. Good job. Top 15 girls right here.
Good job. Top 15 girls right here. Congratulations.
Top 15 girls right here. Congratulations.
Congratulations. This is incredible.
This is incredible. I really didn't think this was
This is incredible. I really didn't think this was gonna happen.
I really didn't think this was gonna happen.
Okay, kristen, you're up.
Gonna happen. Okay, kristen, you're up.
Okay, kristen, you're up. Kristen o'connor.
Kristen o'connor. After graduating from nursing
Kristen o'connor. After
graduating from nursing school, kristen decided to
After graduating from nursing school,
kristen decided to follow her true calling, and
School, kristen decided to follow
her true calling, and wowed the judges with her
Follow her true calling, and
wowed the judges with her powerhouse vocals back in
Wowed the judges with her powerhouse vocals back in atlanta.
Powerhouse vocals back in atlanta.
Atlanta. She was a standout on day one in
She was a standout on day one in hollywood, and that momentum
She was a standout on day one in hollywood,
and that momentum would carry her through to her
Hollywood, and that momentum
would carry her through to her final performance.
Would carry her through to her final performance. ?Oh, no
Final performance. ?Oh, no ?Did I get too close?
?Oh, no ?Did I get too close? ?Oh, did I almost see
?Did I get too close? ?Oh, did I almost see
?What's really on the inside?
?Oh, did I almost see ?What's
really on the inside? ?All your insecurities
?What's really on the inside?
?All your insecurities ?All the dirty laundry
?Never made me blink one time
?All the dirty laundry
?Never made me blink one time ?Unconditional
?Never made me blink one time ?Unconditional ?Unconditionally
?Unconditional ?Unconditionally ?I will love you
?Unconditionally ?I will love you ?Unconditionally
?I will love you ?Unconditionally ?There is no fear now
?Unconditionally ?There is no fear now ?Let go and just be free
?There is no fear now ?Let go and just be free ?I will love you
?Let go and just be free
?I will love you this week has been the most
?I will love you this week has
been the most intense week of my entire life.
This week has been the most intense
week of my entire life. I was up all night, just running
Intense week of my entire life. I was up all night,
just running through all my performances and
I was up all night, just running through
all my performances and thinking, like, "What are they
Through all my performances and thinking,
like, "What are they thinking?"
Thinking, like, "What are they thinking?" Oh, my god.
Thinking?" Oh, my god. I'm freaking out.
Oh, my god. I'm freaking out. ?Open up your heart
I'm freaking out. ?Open up your heart ?There is no fear now
?Open up your heart ?There is no fear now
?Let go and just be free
?There is no fear now ?Let go and just be free ?I will love you
?Let go and just be free ?I will love you ?Unconditionally, yeah
?I will love you ?Unconditionally, yeah how are you?
?Unconditionally, yeah how are you? I'm good.
How are you? I'm good. You good?
I'm good. You good? Anxious.
You good? Anxious. Yeah.
Anxious. Yeah. I understand.
Yeah. I understand. How did you feel your hollywood
I understand. How did you feel your hollywood week went.
How did you feel your hollywood week went.
I felt like I had a couple...
Week went. I felt like I had a couple...
pretty solid performances, and
I felt like I had a couple...
pretty solid performances, and then one that wasn't so solid.
Pretty solid performances,
and then one that wasn't so solid. Yeah.
Then one that wasn't so solid. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, it's funny--
Yeah, it's funny-- was that group week?
Yeah, it's funny-- was that group week? Yes.
Was that group week? Yes.
Yes. Well, the groups are tough
Well, the groups are tough for everybody, but it tells us a
Well, the groups are tough for everybody,
but it tells us a lot about you guys as a
For everybody, but it tells
us a lot about you guys as a performer, you know?
Lot about you guys as a performer, you know? Yeah.
Performer, you know? Yeah. I liked your last performance
Yeah. I liked your last performance a lot,
you know, and and that's
I liked your last performance a lot,
you know, and and that's actually a tough day.
A lot, you know, and and that's
actually a tough day. To regroup after group round is
Actually a tough day. To
regroup after group round is not an easy thing.
To regroup after group round is not an easy thing. Yeah, right.
Not an easy thing. Yeah, right. I didn't get any sleep that
Yeah, right. I didn't get any sleep that night either.
I didn't get any sleep that night either. Yeah, that's what this
Night either. Yeah, that's what this business is all about.
Yeah, that's what this business is all about.
If you don't have that kind of
Business is all about. If you
don't have that kind of drive and that kind of thing
If you don't have that kind of drive
and that kind of thing inside of you that just doesn't
Drive and that kind of thing inside
of you that just doesn't want to be anything but the best
Inside of you that just doesn't want
to be anything but the best you can be, it just really
Want to be anything but the best you can be,
it just really doesn't work.
You can be, it just really doesn't work. You know we have to just
Doesn't work. You know
we have to just choose--you know, there was
You know we have to just choose--you know,
there was amazing singers this year, and
Choose--you know, there was
amazing singers this year, and we've made a decision.
Will kristen join the top 30,
Or is she headed home?
Give us your answer right now at
The hashtags below.
We'll see how you voted after
The break.
Sending kristen o'connor to the
Top 30 or back home.
We'd like you to be in the
Top 15 girls.
Oh, my--
You're welcome, congratulations.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
This is nuts.
This is nuts. ?
This is nuts. ? I can't believe I just made it
? I can't believe I just made it to the top 30 on american idol.
I can't believe I just
made it to the top 30 on american idol. Whoo!
To the top 30 on american idol. Whoo!
Whoo! Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Congratulations. Good job.
Good job. She made it.
Good job. She made it. Top 15 girl right here.
She made it. Top 15 girl right here.
Top 15 girl right here. Good luck.
Good luck. Go tell somebody.
Good luck. Go tell somebody. If you want something bad
Go tell somebody. If you
want something bad enough, if you're willing to
If you want something bad enough,
if you're willing to work for it, you can do it.
So far, 7 girls have claimed
A spot in our top 15, leaving
Only 8 spots left.
And we've already seen 5 boys
Only 10 spaces remaining.
Confident he had a spot
reserved for him in the top 30 was jordan brisbane.
For him in the top 30 was jordan brisbane.
All right, savannah, georgia.
Jordan brisbane. All right, savannah, georgia. Jordan.
All right, savannah, georgia. Jordan.
Jordan. Back in atlanta, this
Back in atlanta, this 15-year-old threw down the
Back in atlanta, this 15-year-old threw down the gauntlet.
15-year-old threw down the gauntlet. Now, you're just a little
Gauntlet. Now, you're just a little baby.
Now, you're just a little baby. What brings you here?
Baby. What brings you here? I believe I have what it
What brings you here? I believe
I have what it takes to shut american idol
I believe I have what it takes to shut american idol series down.
Takes to shut american idol series down. Really?
Series down. Really?
Really? Yes.
Yes. Wow.
Yes. Wow. When you walk out onstage,
Wow. When you walk out onstage, just because of how sweet you
When you walk out onstage, just
because of how sweet you are, people are gonna jump to
Just because of how sweet you are,
people are gonna jump to their feet and start clapping.
Are, people are gonna jump to their
feet and start clapping. But were they on their feet
Their feet and start clapping.
But were they on their feet for his final hollywood
But were they on their feet for his final hollywood performance?
?I ain't never gonna
?Shut you out
?'cause everywhere ?I'm looking now ?I'm surrounded
?I'm looking now ?I'm surrounded ?By your embrace
?I'm surrounded ?By your embrace ?Baby, I can see your halo
?By your embrace ?Baby, I can see your halo
?I pray it won't fade away
?Baby, I can see your halo ?I pray it won't fade away ?Halo
?I pray it won't fade away ?Halo ?Halo
?Halo ?Halo ?I can see your halo
?Halo ?I can see your halo ?Halo
?I can see your halo ?Halo ?I can feel your halo
?Halo ?I can feel your halo ?Halo
?I can feel your halo ?Halo ?I can feel your halo
?I can feel your halo ?Halo ?I can see your
?Halo ?I can see your ?
?I can see your ? What's up, handsome?
? What's up, handsome? Nervous.
What's up, handsome? Nervous. You're nervous?
Nervous. You're nervous? Yes.
You're nervous? Yes. You're 15.
Yes. You're 15. Well, 16 today.
You're 15. Well, 16 today. It's your birthday?
Well, 16 today. It's your birthday? Yes.
It's your birthday? Yes. Today?
Yes. Today? Yes.
Today? Yes. Happy birthday, baby.
Yes. Happy birthday, baby. Thank you.
Happy birthday, baby. Thank you. How long you been singing?
Thank you. How long you been singing? Since I was five years old.
How long you been singing?
Since I was five years old. Since you were five?
Since I was five years old. Since you were five? Yup.
Since you were five? Yup. So you already been singing
Yup. So you already been singing for a decade.
So you already been singing for a decade. Yes.
For a decade. Yes.
Yes. A decade and a day.
A decade and a day. How 'bout that?
A decade and a day. How 'bout that? Yes.
How 'bout that? Yes. You know, the hard part for
Yes. You know, the hard part for us today is having to say no to
You know, the hard part for us today
is having to say no to so many people, and the thing
Us today is having to say no to so many people,
and the thing about being 15--or in your case,
So many people, and the thing about
being 15--or in your case, 16 today--is you haven't had a
About being 15--or in your case,
16 today--is you haven't had a lot of "Noes" Yet, and it's
16 today--is you haven't
had a lot of "Noes" Yet, and it's amazing--
Lot of "Noes" Yet, and it's amazing-- big nose, yeah.
Amazing-- big nose, yeah. Yeah.
Big nose, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. To get through the audition
Yeah. To get through the audition cities, to hollywood, through
To get through the audition cities,
to hollywood, through the group rounds, you've been
Cities, to hollywood, through the group rounds,
you've been able to keep making it, you
The group rounds, you've been able to keep making it,
you know, and it's been, "Yes, yes,
Able to keep making it, you know,
and it's been, "Yes, yes, yes," Um...
And today's another yes. Yo! You're in the top 15.
Yo! You're in the top 15. Thank you.
You're in the top 15. Thank you. Happy birthday.
Thank you. Happy birthday. Yeah, that's a pretty good
Happy birthday. Yeah, that's a pretty good birthday present.
Yeah, that's a pretty
good birthday present. Happy birthday, baby.
Birthday present. Happy birthday, baby. Thank you.
Happy birthday, baby. Thank you. Congratulations.
Thank you. Congratulations. Thank you.
Congratulations. Thank you. Nice work, man.
Thank you. Nice work, man. Congratulations and happy
Nice work, man. Congratulations and happy birthday.
Congratulations and happy birthday. Thank you.
Birthday. Thank you. Go celebrate.
Thank you. Go celebrate. Thank you, guys.
Go celebrate. Thank you, guys. That's a 16th birthday right
Thank you, guys. That's a 16th birthday right there.
That's a 16th birthday right there. Yeah.
There. Yeah. Sweet 16 and never heard
Yeah. Sweet 16 and never heard "No."
Sweet 16 and never heard "No." He's goin'.
"No." He's goin'.
He's goin'.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday. Thank you, thank you, man.
Happy birthday. Thank you, thank you,
man. This is the best gift you can
Thank you, thank you, man. This is the best gift you can get.
This is the best gift you can get. Yes.
Get. Yes. Go celebrate, all right?
Yes. Go celebrate, all right? Thank you.
Go celebrate, all right? Thank you. See you monday.
Thank you. See you monday. All right.
See you monday. All right. Bye, buddy.
All right. Bye, buddy. Sending up, sending up.
Bye, buddy. Sending up, sending up. Right now, omaha contestant
Sending up, sending up. Right now,
omaha contestant casey mcquillen is ready to take
Right now, omaha contestant casey
mcquillen is ready to take her chance in the chair
Casey mcquillen is ready
to take her chance in the chair upstairs.
Her chance in the chair upstairs. I've always wanted the big
Upstairs. I've always wanted the big stage, the big auditorium.
I've always wanted the big stage,
the big auditorium. I feel like that's what I was
Stage, the big auditorium.
I feel like that's what I was born to do.
I feel like that's what I was born to do. I'm ready.
Born to do. I'm ready. We voted today.
I'm ready. We voted today. No.
We're looking for specific
Things...
?You call me suga-a-ar
But hear it from me, I'm very
Proud of you for perfecting your craft,
and that is ultimately what's gonna take you far in the
Craft, and that is ultimately what's
gonna take you far in the world of entertainment.
What's gonna take you far in the
world of entertainment. The idol journey is also over
World of entertainment. The
idol journey is also over for atlanta contestant,
The idol journey is also
over for atlanta contestant, nica nashae.
I'm a big fan of yours.
I'm a big fan of yours. Unfortunately, this year is not
I'm a big fan of yours. Unfortunately,
this year is not your year, sweetie pie.
?And baby, baby, baby
I think people are gonna
Remember who you are...
Because I feel like you made a mark on me.
I just wanted you to know that I
A mark on me. I just
wanted you to know that I was pulling for you.
I just wanted you to know
that I was pulling for you. I think she was
Was pulling for you. I think she was really good.
Yeah.
She's one of the best singers. It's hard.
And as if these decisions
And as if these decisions weren't difficult enough, an
And as if these decisions weren't difficult enough,
an even tougher one was heading
Weren't difficult enough,
an even tougher one was heading into the elevator.
Okay, leah.
Yup.
Now it's time.
Now it's time. Now it's time.
Now it's time. Now it's time. Andrina as well.
Now it's time. Andrina as well. Both of you have been asked to
Andrina as well. Both of you have been asked to go up together.
Both of you have been asked to go up together.
So we'll put you in here, you'll
Go up together. So we'll put you in here,
you'll hang tight, then ride up the
So we'll put you in here, you'll hang tight,
then ride up the elevator together, and get the
Hang tight, then ride up the elevator together,
and get the verdict, all right?
Elevator together, and get the verdict, all right? Good luck.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh.
Hi, how are you?
Hey.
Pretty good, nervous.
Hanging in there?
Hanging in there? Yes, of course.
Yeah.
This is one of the most
This is one of the most nerve-wracking processes I've
nerve-wracking processes I've ever been through.
Nerve-wracking processes I've
ever been through. This is such a tough day.
Ever been through. This is such a tough day.
It's a tough day for the judges,
This is such a tough day. It's a
tough day for the judges, it's a tough day for you guys.
It's a tough day for the judges,
it's a tough day for you guys. You've been through a crazy,
It's a tough day for you guys.
You've been through a crazy, long week.
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH A CRAZY, LONG WEEK. Etta James'
Long week.
?Something told me
?It was over
?Yeah ?When I saw you and her ?Talkin'
?When I saw you and her ?Talkin' ?Something deep down
?Talkin' ?Something deep down ?In my soul
?Something deep down ?In my soul ?Said, "Cry, baby, cry, now"
?In my soul ?Said, "Cry, baby,
cry, now" ?When I saw you and that girl
?Said, "Cry, baby, cry, now"
?When I saw you and that girl ?Walking out
So I'm just gonna cut to the chase for you guys, okay? Okay.
Chase for you guys, okay? Okay. One of you are going through
Okay. One of you are going through and one of you are not.
One of you are going through and one of you are not.
And one of you are not.
?We, we don't have to
?Worry 'bout nothing
?'cause we got the fire
?And we're burning
?One hell of a something
Yes.
?Light it up
?Like we're the stars ?Of the human race ?Human race
?Of the human race ?Human race ?We got the fire, fire, fire
?Human race ?We got the fire,
fire, fire ?Huh, yeah, we got the fire
?We got the fire, fire, fire ?Huh,
yeah, we got the fire ?Fire, fire
?Huh, yeah, we got the fire ?Fire, fire ?And we gonna let it burn
?Fire, fire ?And we gonna let it burn ?Burn, burn, burn
?And we gonna let it burn ?Burn, burn, burn ?We gonna let it burn
?Burn, burn, burn ?We gonna let it burn ?Burn, burn
?We gonna let it burn ?Burn, burn ?We gonna let it burn
?Burn, burn ?We gonna let it burn ?Burn, burn, burn
?We gonna let it burn ?Burn,
burn, burn ?We gonna let it burn, burn
The end of the day, we have to pick only 15 girls.
It was brutal, and it was almost
To pick only 15 girls. It was brutal,
and it was almost interchangeable, and that's how
It was brutal, and it was almost interchangeable,
and that's how it went the whole time.
Interchangeable, and that's how it
went the whole time. Leah, you're not going through.
It went the whole time. Leah,
you're not going through. Andrina, you're in the top 15.
Leah, you're not going through.
Andrina, you're in the top 15. Thank you, guys.
Andrina, you're in the top 15. Thank you, guys. Thank you.
Thank you, guys. Thank you. I'm very sorry.
Thank you. I'm very sorry. Thank you, guys.
I'm very sorry. Thank you, guys. It's all right.
Thank you, guys. It's all right. Oh, my god.
It's all right. Oh, my god. Thanks.
Oh, my god. Thanks. You nailed that.
Thank you.
You're extremely talented.
Congratulations.
Listen to me.
You're extremely talented.
There were so many decisions that went into this.
There were so many decisions
that went into this. Please come back.
That went into this. Please come back. Okay.
Please come back. Okay. Don't quit the fight.
Okay. Don't quit the fight. You hear me?
Don't quit the fight. You hear me? I hear you.
You hear me? I hear you. Okay.
I hear you. Okay. Thank you so much.
Okay. Thank you so much. You guys, I'm here to stay.
Thank you so much. You guys, I'm here to stay. Congratulations.
You guys, I'm here to stay. Congratulations. Thank you.
Congratulations. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. Leah and andrina.
Leah and andrina. Thumbs up.
Leah and andrina. Thumbs up. Not for both of you?
Thumbs up. Not for both of you? I didn't make it.
Not for both of you? I didn't make it. You didn't make it?
I didn't make it. You didn't make it? Oh, my gosh.
You didn't make it? Oh, my gosh. This...is terrible and amazing
Oh, my gosh. This...is terrible and amazing all at the same time.
This...is terrible and amazing all at the same time.
Through this whole episode, my nose is just gonna be red.
My nose is just gonna be red. I can't smile.
I can't smile. Seriously.
?I am ready for love
?I'd quickly give my freedom
?I'd quickly give my freedom ?To be held
?To be held ?In your captivity-y-y
?In your captivity-y-y ?And if you ask me tomorrow
?And if you ask me tomorrow ?I'll say the same thing
Thank you.
Thank you. Thanks, man.
Appreciate it.
Thank you, malcolm.
This is that moment.
This is that moment. That moment, that moment.
This is that moment. That moment,
that moment. ?Very superstitious
I'm gonna say yes, yes, and
I'm gonna say yes, yes, and double--you're my triple yes
I'm gonna say yes, yes, and double--you're my triple yes today.
?I really wanna love
?I really wanna love ?Somebody
It was terrible
I understand.
It's hard in the groups, but
It's hard in the groups, but you guys could have done a lot
It's hard in the groups,
but you guys could have done a lot better than that.
There's always that little
There's always that little voice in the back of your head,
There's always that little voice
in the back of your head, like, "Well, you didn't do
Voice in the back of your head, like,
"Well, you didn't do good," Or, "You could've done
Like, "Well, you didn't do good," Or,
"You could've done better," 'cause we're always our
Good," Or, "You could've done better,"
'cause we're always our worst critic, you know?
Better," 'cause we're always our worst critic,
you know? It's time to do this.
Worst critic, you know? It's time to do this. No holding back.
It's time to do this. No holding back. Gotta give them judges
No holding back. Gotta
give them judges everything you got, and make
Gotta give them judges everything you got,
and make sure they know that I'm the next
Everything you got, and make
sure they know that I'm the next american idol.
Sure they know that I'm the next american idol.
American idol. ?
?Time on my hands
?Since you been away, baby
?I ain't got no plans ?No, no, no, no ?And the sound of the rain
?No, no, no, no ?And the sound of the rain ?Against my windowpane
?And the sound of the rain ?Against my windowpane ?Is slowly
?Against my windowpane ?Is slowly ?Is slowly drivin' me insane
?Is slowly ?Is slowly drivin' me insane ?Hey, baby
?Is slowly drivin' me insane ?Hey, baby ?I'm goin' down
?Hey, baby ?I'm goin' down ?I'm goin' down
Yeah.
?Whole world's upside down
?Sleep don't come easy ?Ooh, please believe me
?Sleep don't come easy ?Ooh,
please believe me ?Since you been gone
?Ooh, please believe me
?Since you been gone ?Everything's goin' wrong
?Since you been gone
?Everything's goin' wrong ?Why'd you have to say
?Everything's goin' wrong ?Why'd you have to say ?Goodbye?
?Why'd you have to say ?Goodbye?
?Goodbye? ?Look what you've done to me
?Look what you've done to me ?I can't stop these tears
?Look what you've done to me ?I
can't stop these tears ?From fallin' from my eyes
?I can't stop these tears ?From fallin' from my eyes ?Hey, baby
?From fallin' from my eyes ?Hey, baby
?Hey, baby ?I'm goin' down
?I'm goin' down ?I'm goin' down
?I'm goin' down ?I'm goin' down ?Down
?I'm goin' down ?Down ?Cause you ain't around
?Down ?Cause you ain't around ?Baby
?Cause you ain't around ?Baby ?My whole world's upside down
?Baby ?My whole world's upside down all right.
?My whole world's upside down all right. Yeah, great voice.
All right. Yeah, great voice. ?Down, down
Yeah, great voice. ?Down, down ?No, no
?Down, down ?No, no oh, yeah.
?No, no oh, yeah. ?No, no, no, no, no
Oh, yeah. ?No, no, no, no, no
So malcolm, we remember you from the austin auditions. Uh-huh.
From the austin auditions. Uh-huh. You remember that day pretty
Uh-huh. You remember that day pretty well?
You remember that day pretty well? Quite well.
Well? Quite well. It's been quite a journey
Quite well. It's been quite a journey since then.
It's been quite a journey since then. Mm-hmm.
Since then. Mm-hmm. We think you're a talented
Mm-hmm. We think you're a talented guy, and there's all different
We think you're a talented guy,
and there's all different types of talent in this
Guy, and there's all
different types of talent in this competition.
Types of talent in this competition. Mm-hmm.
Competition. Mm-hmm. But we're trying to find--
Mm-hmm. But we're trying to find-- but ultimately, we have to
But we're trying to find-- but ultimately,
we have to decide who's gonna make the
But ultimately, we have to decide
who's gonna make the top 30, 15 boys, 15 girls.
Decide who's gonna make the top 30, 15 boys, 15 girls. Um...
Top 30, 15 boys, 15 girls. Um... on behalf of the panel, I'd like
Um... on behalf of the panel,
I'd like to say that you made it through
On behalf of the panel, I'd
like to say that you made it through to the top 30.
To say that you made it through to the top 30.
To the top 30. ?
? All right.
? All right. Congratulations, malcolm.
All right. Congratulations, malcolm. You and your yellow sweater!
Congratulations, malcolm.
You and your yellow sweater! Congratulations, baby.
You and your yellow sweater! Congratulations,
baby. Thank you so much, you guys.
Congratulations, baby. Thank you so much,
you guys. Thank you so--thank you so much.
Thank you so much, you guys.
Thank you so--thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so--thank you so much.
Thank you. You made it to the top 15
Thank you. You made it to the top 15 guys.
You made it to the top 15 guys. Thank you.
Guys. Thank you. We're really proud.
Thank you. We're really proud. Thank you so much.
We're really proud. Thank you so much. Whoo!
Thank you so much. Whoo! Yeah, you did it!
Whoo! Yeah, you did it! Yes!
Yeah, you did it! Yes!
Yes! I love the yeses.
I love the yeses. I can't even explain this
I love the yeses. I can't even explain this feeling, man.
I can't even explain this feeling, man. It's amazing.
Feeling, man. It's amazing. So all the hard work paid off
It's amazing. So all the hard work paid off for you, malcolm.
So all the hard work paid off for you, malcolm. Congratulations.
For you, malcolm. Congratulations.
Congratulations. Welcome to the next round.
Welcome to the next round. You go celebrate.
Welcome to the next round. You go celebrate. Enjoy.
You go celebrate. Enjoy. I'm absolutely the next
Enjoy. I'm absolutely the next american idol.
I'm absolutely the next american idol. There's no doubt about it.
American idol. There's no doubt about it.
America, I hope you're ready for
There's no doubt about it. America,
I hope you're ready for me, 'cause I'm coming.
America, I hope you're ready for me,
'cause I'm coming. Like, this is my time to shine,
Me, 'cause I'm coming. Like,
this is my time to shine, and it's gonna happen.
Like, this is my time to shine,
and it's gonna happen. Up next is salt lake city
And it's gonna happen. Up next
is salt lake city contestant alex preston, who's
Up next is salt lake city
contestant alex preston, who's gotten far with his
Contestant alex preston,
who's gotten far with his unconventional song choices.
Gotten far with his unconventional song choices.
?We saying, "Oh wee
?Oh wee, wee, oh"
?This is who ?You're working with ?Will.I.Am and britney
?You're working with ?Will.I.Am and britney whoo!
?Will.I.Am and britney whoo! And yesterday, alex pushed
Whoo! And yesterday, alex pushed the envelope one last time with
And yesterday, alex pushed the
envelope one last time with an original song.
The envelope one last time with an original song.
?The kick drum starts playing
?
?And it matches
?My beating heart
?Nowhere to go ?No one to see ?Is it the finish line
?No one to see ?Is it the finish line ?Or the start?
?Is it the finish line ?Or the start? ?And I look into
?Or the start? ?And I look into ?Your soft, green field
?And I look into ?Your soft, green field ?And I see only sunlight
?Your soft, green field ?And I see only sunlight ?And trees
?And I see only sunlight ?And trees ?Oh, it makes me wonder
?And trees ?Oh, it makes me wonder ?Oh, lord, it makes me wonder
?Oh, it makes me wonder ?Oh,
lord, it makes me wonder ?Can you even see me?
?Oh, lord, it makes me wonder ?Can you even see me? ?Yeah, oh
?Can you even see me? ?Yeah, oh ?So take my hand
?Yeah, oh ?So take my hand ?And jump over this mess
?So take my hand ?And jump over this mess ?This is a fairy tale
?And jump over this mess
?This is a fairy tale ?And you're the damsel
?This is a fairy tale ?And you're the damsel ?In distre-e-ess
?And you're the damsel ?In distre-e-ess ?Across the river
?In distre-e-ess ?Across the river ?To the other side
?Across the river ?To the other side ?
?To the other side ? ?I promise you
? ?I promise you ?That it's nicer here
?I promise you ?That it's nicer here ?
?That it's nicer here ? ?Take your hands
? ?Take your hands ?From your face
?Take your hands ?From your face ?All right
?From your face ?All right ?There is no reason
?All right ?There is no reason ?For your fear
?There is no reason ?For your fear ?No reason for your fear
?For your fear ?No reason for your fear
?No reason for your fear
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thanks, alex.
Thank you very much. Thanks, alex. I like that song.
Thanks, alex. I like that song. His song may have impressed
I like that song. His song may
have impressed the judges, but with the spots
His song may have impressed the judges,
but with the spots dwindling, the question remains,
The judges, but with the spots dwindling,
the question remains, is there room for alex preston?
Dwindling, the question remains, is
there room for alex preston? Personally, I think there's a
Is there room for alex preston? Personally,
I think there's a place for me on the show.
Personally, I think there's a
place for me on the show. I think that I'll bring
Place for me on the show. I think
that I'll bring something new, hopefully inspire
I think that I'll bring something new,
hopefully inspire people to start writing their
Something new, hopefully inspire people
to start writing their own music, start pursuing their
People to start writing their own music,
start pursuing their own dreams.
Own music, start pursuing their own dreams. How's it going?
Own dreams. How's it going? Take a seat.
How's it going? Take a seat. You're like linus with his
Take a seat. You're like linus with his security blanket.
You're like linus with his security blanket. Mm-hmm.
Security blanket. Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. I can relate.
Yeah. I can relate. Let me ask you, did you think
I can relate. Let me ask you,
did you think you would make it this far?
Let me ask you, did you think you
would make it this far? Honestly, I didn't really
You would make it this far? Honestly,
I didn't really think I would make it this far,
Honestly, I didn't really think I
would make it this far, because my style is so much
Think I would make it this far,
because my style is so much different, and I didn't know if
Because my style is so much different,
and I didn't know if it would be taken to in this
Different, and I didn't know if
it would be taken to in this positive way, and--
It would be taken to in this positive way,
and-- you have an unusual thing.
Positive way, and-- you have an unusual thing.
It's not something that comes
You have an unusual thing. It's not
something that comes through idol all the time, your
It's not something that comes through
idol all the time, your particular style, your way of
Through idol all the time, your particular style,
your way of playing and singing.
Particular style, your way of playing and singing.
That's why it's been so hard for
Playing and singing.
That's why it's been so hard for us, you know?
Mm-hmm.
Hey, we need to decide on
Hey, we need to decide on this before board goes away.
I--for some reason, I lean
I--for some reason, I lean into a "Yes."
This is what I say.
Okay.
We're gonna go back over all
We're gonna go back over all these later, right?
We will, and we'll have our
We will, and we'll have our notes on them.
Yeah, right, okay.
Wherever there's a question
Wherever there's a question mark, we'll discuss it a little
Wherever there's a question mark,
we'll discuss it a little bit more.
I'm glad that you've made it
I'm glad that you've made it this far, but we just can't take
I'm glad that you've made it this far,
but we just can't take everybody.
This far, but we just can't take everybody.
Everybody. But we'd like to see you in the
But we'd like to see you in the top 30.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh. Really?
Yes, sir.
Really.
You're going through, alex.
Oh, my gosh.
Good work, alex.
All right, man.
Thank you so much.
Absolutely.
Good work, man.
I can't even believe it, you
I can't even believe it, you guys, this means so much.
I can't even believe it, you guys,
this means so much. Thank you so much.
You know that thing comes
You know that thing comes off.
You know that thing comes off. The strap comes off, and
Off. The strap comes off, and you can--yeah.
Does it really?
Does it really? I thought it was just growing on
Does it really? I thought it was just growing on me.
Yeah, no, yeah.
All right, well, have a good
All right, well, have a good one, guys.
You too.
He can't believe it.
Whoo!
We got it.
We got it. All smiles comin' down.
I'm happy for him.
I'm happy for him. I'm so happy that he made it.
This opportunity means
This opportunity means everything to me.
I would always watch the show
I would always watch the show and be like, "Oh, I could never
I would always watch the show and be like,
"Oh, I could never be up there," But then I decided
And be like, "Oh, I could never be up there,"
But then I decided to audition, and here I am, so
Be up there," But then I decided to audition,
and here I am, so it's--I'm still in shock, to be
To audition, and here I am, so it's--I'm still in shock,
to be honest, like--it feels like a
It's--I'm still in shock,
to be honest, like--it feels like a dream.
Where is cj? There he is.
There he is. What's up, buddy?
How you doin', man?
The judges have sent word
The judges have sent word down, they want to see you and
The judges have sent word down,
they want to see you and they want to see casey at the
Down, they want to see you and they
want to see casey at the same time, together, so casey,
They want to see casey at the same time,
together, so casey, come on up.
Same time, together, so casey,
come on up. You guys know each other well
Come on up. You guys know each other well after that group round.
How you doin'?
Good.
Good. So they're gonna take you both
Good. So they're gonna take you both at the same time, all right?
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Casey and cj met and became
Friends during the competition,
And they soon realized how
Similar their journeys have
Been.
Living not 40 miles from each other in alabama,
these two country singers auditioned for
Other in alabama, these two country
singers auditioned for the idol bus tour in tuscaloosa
Country singers auditioned for the idol
bus tour in tuscaloosa and received their golden ticket
The idol bus tour in tuscaloosa and
received their golden ticket to hollywood in salt lake city.
And received their golden ticket to
hollywood in salt lake city. As the guys inch closer to their
To hollywood in salt lake city. As the
guys inch closer to their fate, they can only hope their
As the guys inch closer to their fate,
they can only hope their final performances earned them a
Fate, they can only hope their
final performances earned them a spot in the top 30.
Final performances earned them a spot in the top 30.
?I don't know how you do
?What you do
?I'm so in love with you
?It just keeps getting better ?I wanna spend ?The rest of my life
?I wanna spend ?The rest of my life ?With you by my side
?The rest of my life ?With you by my side ?Forever and ever
?If you ever ?Change your mind ?About leaving
?Change your mind ?About leaving ?Leaving me behind
?About leaving ?Leaving me behind oh.
?Leaving me behind oh. ?Oh-oh, bring it to me
Oh. ?Oh-oh, bring it to me ?Bring me your sweet loving
?Oh-oh, bring it to me ?Bring
me your sweet loving ?Bring it on home to me
?Bring me your sweet loving ?Bring it on home to me ?Yeah
?Bring it on home to me ?Yeah hi, guys.
?Yeah hi, guys. Hey, boys.
Hi, guys. Hey, boys. Hello.
Hey, boys. Hello. Can't believe this right now,
Hello. Can't believe this right now, man, this is unreal, man.
Can't believe this right now, man, this is unreal, man. What?
Man, this is unreal, man. What? What's unreal, cj?
What? What's unreal, cj? Unreal, man.
What's unreal, cj? Unreal, man. How you guys doin'?
Unreal, man. How you guys doin'? You guys get any sleep last
How you guys doin'? You guys get any sleep last night?
You guys get any sleep last night? Yes, I got a bit.
Night? Yes, I got a bit. I actually got some for the
Yes, I got a bit. I actually
got some for the first time all week, not much.
I actually got some for the first time all week,
not much. Did you? That's good.
First time all week, not much.
Did you? That's good. No, that's good.
Did you? That's good. No, that's good. It's a really interesting
No, that's good. It's a really interesting situation.
It's a really interesting situation.
Both you guys are from alabama?
Situation. Both you guys are from alabama? We are.
Both you guys are from alabama? We are. You're both dads, right?
We are. You're both dads, right? Yeah, we're, like, probably
You're both dads, right? Yeah, we're,
like, probably 45 minutes from each other.
Yeah, we're, like,
probably 45 minutes from each other. Is that right?
45 minutes from each other. Is that right? Crazy.
Is that right? Crazy. Yeah, it's crazy.
Crazy. Yeah, it's crazy. I mean, you have so many
Yeah, it's crazy. I mean,
you have so many things in common, which is one
I mean, you have so many things in common,
which is one of the reasons that this
Things in common, which is one
of the reasons that this particular point for us is
Of the reasons that this
particular point for us is exceedingly difficult.
Particular point for us is exceedingly difficult.
This is very, very, very hard.
Exceedingly difficult. This is very,
very, very hard. There's only so many spaces
This is very, very, very hard.
There's only so many spaces available.
There's only so many spaces available. Right.
Available. Right. We're gonna ask you guys to
Right. We're gonna ask
you guys to fight for it right now with your
We're gonna ask you guys
to fight for it right now with your voices.
Fight for it right now with your voices. Okay.
Voices. Okay. We'd like you to sing
Okay. We'd like you to sing something for us right now.
We'd like you to sing something for us right now. Okay.
Something for us right now. Okay. We're gonna talk about it,
Okay. We're gonna talk about it, and we're gonna have to make a
We're gonna talk about it,
and we're gonna have to make a decision on the spot.
And we're gonna have to make a decision on the spot. Mm-hmm.
Decision on the spot. Mm-hmm. Yes, sir.
Mm-hmm. Yes, sir. Who wants to go first?
Yes, sir. Who wants to go first? I'll go.
Who wants to go first? I'll go. Okay.
I'll go. Okay. ?I been run down
Okay. ?I been run down ?I been lied to
?I been run down ?I been lied to ?I don't know why
?I been lied to ?I don't know why ?I let that mean woman
?I don't know why ?I let that mean woman ?Make me a fool
?I let that mean woman ?Make me a fool ?She took all my money
?Make me a fool ?She took all my money ?Yes, she did
?She took all my money ?Yes, she did
?Yes, she did ?She wrecked my new car
?She wrecked my new car ?Well, now she's with
?She wrecked my new car ?Well,
now she's with ?One of my good time buddies
?Well, now she's with
?One of my good time buddies ?And drinkin' in
?One of my good time buddies ?And drinkin' in ?Some crosstown bar
?And drinkin' in ?Some crosstown bar ?Sometimes I feel
?Some crosstown bar ?Sometimes I feel ?Yes, I do
?Sometimes I feel ?Yes, I do ?Sometimes I feel
?Yes, I do ?Sometimes I feel ?Like I've been tied
?Sometimes I feel ?Like I've been tied
?To the whipping post, girl
?Like I've been tied ?To the whipping post, girl ?Oh, good lord
?To the whipping post, girl ?Oh, good lord ?I feel like I'm dyin'
?Oh, good lord ?I feel like I'm dyin' ?Whoa-ho
?I feel like I'm dyin' ?Whoa-ho
?WHOA-HO both: THANK YOU, CJ.
both: THANK YOU, CJ. ALL RIGHT, BABE, WHENEVER YOU
both: THANK YOU, CJ. ALL RIGHT, BABE, WHENEVER YOU READY.
All right, babe, whenever you ready. Okay.
Ready. Okay.
Okay. ?Girl, you cut those jeans
?Girl, you cut those jeans ?Just right
?Girl, you cut those jeans ?Just right ?I know you didn't buy 'em
?Just right ?I know you didn't buy 'em ?Like that
?I know you didn't buy 'em
?Like that ?So baby don't even try that
?Like that ?So baby don't even try that ?You dance
?So baby don't even try that ?You dance ?Oh, oh, you move
?You dance ?Oh, oh, you move ?Like there ain't nobody
?Oh, oh, you move ?Like there ain't nobody ?Watchin'
?Like there ain't nobody ?Watchin' ?Well, girl you know
?Watchin' ?Well, girl you know ?I'm watchin'
?Well, girl you know ?I'm watchin' ?Don't lie
?I'm watchin' ?Don't lie ?You've got it all
?Don't lie ?You've got it all ?Figured out
?You've got it all ?Figured out ?That smile
?Figured out ?That smile ?Has got me spinnin' around
?That smile ?Has got me spinnin' around ?Don't even try
?Has got me spinnin' around ?Don't even try ?Actin' like
?Don't even try ?Actin' like ?It ain't no thing
?Actin' like ?It ain't no thing ?Cause I can see you move
?It ain't no thing ?Cause
I can see you move ?A little closer, closer
?Cause I can see you move
?A little closer, closer ?Everything about you
?A little closer, closer
?Everything about you ?Makes me want ya, want ya
?Everything about you ?Makes me want ya,
want ya ?Know what you're doin, baby
?Makes me want ya, want ya
?Know what you're doin, baby ?Don't ya, don't ya?
?Know what you're doin, baby ?Don't ya, don't ya? Ooh, yeah.
?Don't ya, don't ya? Ooh, yeah. Awesome, man.
Ooh, yeah. Awesome, man. Good.
Awesome, man. Good. Cj, you wanted to sing along
Good. Cj, you wanted to sing along there, didn't you?
Cj, you wanted to sing along there,
didn't you? I did, I like that song.
There, didn't you? I did, I like that song.
I wanted to sing with cj too,
I did, I like that song. I wanted to sing with cj too, man.
I wanted to sing with cj too, man. Hey, why don't you guys go
Man. Hey, why don't you guys go stand by the elevator for a
Hey, why don't you guys go stand
by the elevator for a minute, give us a chance to
Stand by the elevator for a minute, give us a chance to talk.
Minute, give us a chance to talk. Just to talk for a second.
Talk. Just to talk for a second. Yeah, let's chat it out here.
Just to talk for a second. Yeah,
let's chat it out here. Well, no matter what, I had
Yeah, let's chat it out here. Well, no matter what, I had fun.
Well, no matter what, I had fun. Alabama strong, baby.
Fun. Alabama strong, baby. It's because we look--we're
Alabama strong, baby. It's because we look--we're so much alike.
It's because we look--we're so much alike.
Hey, guys, come on back.
This competition for us as judges has-- it's been brutal.
Judges has-- it's been brutal. Bizarre.
It's been brutal. Bizarre. I mean, bizarre and difficult
Bizarre. I mean,
bizarre and difficult and stressful and there's an
I mean, bizarre and difficult and
stressful and there's an immense amount of talent.
And stressful and there's an immense
amount of talent. It's just--it's so hard to pick.
Immense amount of talent. It's just--it's so hard to pick. Um...
It's just--it's so hard to pick. Um...
Um... casey, let's start with you.
Casey, let's start with you. We have concluded, through a lot
Casey, let's start with you. We have concluded,
through a lot of deliberation from all the
We have concluded, through a lot of
deliberation from all the people that have made it this
Of deliberation from all the
people that have made it this far, that you...
Tomorrow night... my heart is like...
My heart is like... the dreaded eliminations
The dreaded eliminations continue.
The dreaded eliminations continue. Do you belong in this
Continue. Do you belong in this competition?
Do you belong in this competition? Just really want to make my
Competition? Just really want to make my mom proud.
Just really want to make my mom proud.
For cj and casey, it's down
Mom proud. For cj and casey, it's down to the wire.
For cj and casey, it's down to the wire.
One of you are going through
To the wire. One of you are going through and one of you are not.
One of you are going through and
one of you are not. We're making our way to the
And one of you are not. We're making our way to the idol top 30.
We're making our way to the idol there's so many talented
Idol there's so many talented girls here.
I'm just, like, shaking.
It's crazy.
You're the last girl in the
You're the last girl in the top 15.
You're gonna make me cry.
I can't believe who we're
I can't believe who we're turning away.
I can't handle this.
We're in a real conundrum.