what are you gonna sing first?
I'm gonna sing to make you feel my love by bob dylan.
go ahead.
love that song.
so tell us about yourself.
I'm from magnolia, texas.
it doesn't matter where you
Start...
ankeny, iowa.
taylor, michigan.
las vegas, nevada.
salt lake city, utah.
it doesn't matter who you
Are...
I'm a farmer.
I work in the oil field.
I work at a retail clothing
Store.
it takes a nation to make an
Idol.
they come from all corners of
The country with dreams bigger
Than any of us could ever
Imagine.
America, this is where they come to be heard.
all: Is american idol!
our search for a superstar
Continues in austin, texas.
Thousands have shown up in hopes of receiving a golden ticket and
Moving on to the next round in hollywood.
come on down here, guys. But to find a superstar, it
And we have three: Jennifer
Lopez, keith urban, and harry
Connick, jr.
They're back for their second day together, and they're
Excited to find your next idol. It's really cool.
You're sitting here listening to people sing and, you know, doing
What they love to do. Just, like, I look forward to
Going to work every day.
where'd the princess go? He's here.
oh, okay. Where is everybody?
Oh, my god. Where are these guys?
are you gonna wear the jacket?
Keep it off? Show the guns? I'm gonna hold it over one
Shoulder. What are they doing, you
Think? It's much more effective when
I say you're going to hollywood like this.
when you have a cape on? Yeah.
oh, finally!
you like? This is my new joint.
no, I hate it. This is how the kids are
Wearing it. No.
I'm kidding. Come on. You can't think I'm serious.
I am excited. I'm nervous.
I'm worried a little bit. Let's go.
I just hope I make an impact on them.
look at that black guitar. That's some serious ink.
yeah. Tell me your name.
I'm jesse. Jesse roach. Hey, jesse.
What made you come in today? I actually was in my garage
One day practicing, and a neighbor lady came up that I had
Never seen in my life and sits down in my garage.
you should have saw her face. She's like, "There's a crazy
Woman that's in my garage." Ever since then, we're
Like this. One day, she said, "I signed
You up for american idol." She had booked a hotel, and we
Are going to austin to try out. I had no choice because she paid
For it. What are you gonna sing,
Jesse? I'm gonna sing some k.T.
Oslin, do ya. Sweet.
cool.
I love the black guitar. Mm.
I love you. I love--I love what you're
Wearing. I love the black guitar.
I love your vibe. And more than that, I really do
Love your voice. And I think you could make
Records, I think you could be an artist.
thank you. Yeah, you've got a lot of
Soul. You have a story that's way
Older than you are, and that's what I--what I hear and feel
When you sing. That's what I love about your
Voice. There is an example of a
Voice with rasp that I wasn't distracted by the sound.
no, it was so pure. Yeah.
I'm gonna say yes. I'mon say yes.
yes. Is that the one...
so jesse snags the first golden
Ticket in texas and swaps her garage for our hollywood stage.
Congratulations. She said that I could do it,
And I did. And she's going to hollywood.
I'm going to hollywood. It's a very simple journey.
You come in. You audition in front of three
People. And little by little, they
Emerge. Little by little, you see kind
Of, you know, the cream rising to the top.
I loved her. Yeah, she was great.
who's next?
I believe I'm one step closer to my dream today.
This is a big opportunity that not many people get, and I'm
Really like nothing else. I get to be someone on stage
That I don't normally get to be in real life.
Audition today. It's just gonna be a chance to
Finally get to show what I can do.
I loved it. I loved the tone in your voice.
I love your confidence. I'd be hard-pressed to see
Someone come and stand here and sound as good.
I think that there's a really, really beautiful voice
There. Thank you.
you're going to hollywood. Oh!
thank you. Thank you. I'm gonna bring it on.
bring it on. I'm gonna bring it.
see you in hollywood, man. Yes!
she sounds quite
Disappointed out there. Yeah, she's not happy about
It at all. All the contestants have
Come here for one reason and one reason only--to get one of
These. It would really prove to my
Family that "A," I really am talented and, hey, this is
Something that I take seriously. Just as far as validation of
Talent. I'm auditioning here.
But also one of my close friends, quiandra, she's
Auditioning as well. We're very close.
He's like my little brother. When he came to the school,
Nobody really talked to him. And the kids, they were mean to
Him. She really reached out to me,
And we became great friends. So she's always there for me.
She's like a big sister. If I don't make it and jamiah
Does, then he's gonna have my 100% support.
the first note. That's all that matters.
oh, my god. You gotta have 'em at hello.
yeah. Hello.
tell us a little bit about yourself.
I love music. Music is all I do.
Music is who I am. Quiandra, what are you gonna
Do for us today, baby? I'm gonna show how it's done
Today. Nice!
Love you! I feel confident.
I wanted to try one of my originals on you, actually.
yeah? Okay.
so. What are you saying?
both: Yellow ticket, yellow ticket, yellow ticket...
yellow ticket, yellow ticket, yellow ticket, yellow ticket.
well, I love your voice. I think you've got a great look.
I think you've got great confidence.
I think you have as good a shot of working in this industry
As many of the people out there. See, it wasn't--everything
Wasn't perfect in it. There's so much more to grow for
You. And I feel like this type of
Competition actually might be a really good thing for you.
Shall we vote? Yeah.
I'm gonna say no. It's a no for me this time
Too. That's a no for me too.
sorry. I'll start, and I'll vote
Yes. It's a yes for me.
it's a yes for me. We want you to come to
Hollywood! Whose life is about to
Change? Find out after the break.
welcome back to idol.
The next dramatic step toward
Stardom is about to be taken by
One lucky contestant.
But whose dream is going to be realized?
quiandra snatches that
Coveted golden ticket. She's up!
congratulations. Thank you, thank you.
we'll see you in hollywood. Whoo!
leaving jamiah with only a brave face.
hey, guys. Hey, man. What happened?
what's up, ryan? How you doing, buddy?
good, good. Any luck?
no, not this time. But you know what?
I think I did pretty good considering the circumstances.
good, man. Well, good to meet you.
thank you. Good luck.
Your pal over here wants to give you a hug.
She's waiting for you. Aww.
My little brother, I'm proud of him for doing the best he could,
But he still didn't make it. I don't even know how to feel
About that.
sorry, 64-b is out of place.
64-b. I love it.
hello. Hi, baby.
how are you all doing? Good. How you doing?
I'm good. What's your name?
oh, I can't believe it. I'm megan miller.
hi, megan. She's very excited to meet
Harry, I think. I am very excited because
You're from louisiana also. Where are you from?
I'm from a place called ethel.
It's about an hour north of baton rouge.
do you know ethel? Of course I know ethel.
I went to high school in ethel, and--
they don't have a high school in ethel, we share a zip code.
yeah, I know. I almost tried to get it past
You, but I couldn't. What you got?
I'm gonna sing last name by carrie underwood.
okay.
I like that.
I love the kind of cry and rasp in your voice.
thank you.
the only thing--I loved it too--I was worried about when
it is kind of a--
well, steven tyler power. My boy steven.
yeah, but I think about--I mean, some people are sort of
Immune to that. Like, he's a perfect example of
Somebody who can scream and still be able to scream the next
I have always been a
you didn't find any--that
not at all.
I sing four or five shows a week.
and there's another danger
Too I find sometimes with singers who have that kind of
Impassioned rasp, which, if it sounds like it's a lot of work
To get it out, it can be a lot of work for the audience
Listening. Whatever effort it takes you to
Form it, it takes exactly the same for an audience to listen
mm-hmm.
yeah.
you should be.
you happen to have a great voice, and I like your work
Ethic. So I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say yes too.
oh, I love you guys so much.
you're going to hollywood, baby.
you didn't make it? Don't do that to me!
I'd be shocked if she has a
I think some people can hold
we'll find out.
yeah, for sure.
thank you so much.
good job. We'll see you in hollywood.
my name is grace field.
I am 27 years old, and I am a professional piano player.
I play a lot at restaurants and bars.
I play probably, like, five to seven nights a week.
I trained in music and art in college, and I have a post-grad
Degree in music as well. And then I've been playing ever
Since. Hey, guys.
welcome to austin, texas!
thank you.
I am grace field.
I'm originally from austin, texas, the best city in the
World. I'm a little partial.
yeah.
I do play piano.
that's awesome. Air high five.
oh, absolutely.
okay.
I'm gonna get pitch from my phone, if that's cool with you
Guys. All right.
thank you, grace. I'm not sure this is the right
Type of competition for you. I mean, american idol is looking
For, like, a powerhouse superstar performer.
It was all over the place. It was--it was frenetic.
it was just a little bit
Kinda like you were a little bit nervous because I felt like
The vibrato was a little bit out of control.
I think that might be her
Vibrato, though. I really do.
I'm not sure if you have the
Entire package for what american idol is looking for.
what happened?
I don't know. I don't think they--I don't
Think I was what they were looking for.
that's a good question.
I was thinking about that.
You know, it's really--it's like a great voice or a great look.
that's what we're always waiting for.
the spikes represent the hardness.
The pink kinda represents the softness.
or charisma or just something memorable.
my brothers and my dad, they all work in the oil field just
oil worker?
all three of us are gonna hear something different.
it's more than singing.
I felt like there was real
thank you.
how much do you like working on the oil rigs?
I don't want to do it forever.
I'm looking for people that are serious about being in the
I hope you take this
Seriously, bro, 'cause you're going to hollywood.
thank youo mu.
we're just waiting for
Somebody to come in and go-- where we just go, "Oh, my god!"
Oh, my god. Are your eyes blue, green?
you're a pretty guy.
and a no from me and keith.
there. I said it.
I don't like it. I don't like being upstaged by
it's just not the eyes.
The skin is gorgeous, the hair's not bad.
my name's spencer lloyd.
I'm from bryant, arkansas. And I'm 19 years old. S.
you hate him.
I love him.
your name is really cool, spencer lloyd.
you look like that.
You--even if you suck, you're carrying around a guitar.
I just--I don't like--what's to like?
girls are going for this.
yeah, I know. I know. I'm unhappy.
I'm gonna sing a colton
Dixon song. Is that cool?
this is torture for me.
young lady, you look nervous.
Are you nervous? Why? Is that your brother?
cool.
now, I'm gonna be straight up with you.
You seem like a really sweet guy.
the part that's missing for me is you're an okay singer.
But to follow you--I think about this stuff as a performer.
You're gonna go out, and you're gonna sing.
Whoever's lined up next to you is gonna have to deal with the
Deafening screams of your looks and your sweetness.
There's something to be said for that.
and also the fact that he can sing.
I wouldn't be saying this if
I totally know what harry's
Saying, and I agree. There's so many ways to
Entertain. And for me entertaining is just
Keeping my attention and engaging me in what you're
Doing. And you totally did that.
I agree. I think that there's a really,
Really beautiful voice there. I really enjoyed that.
harry?
you're gonna bring something to american idol that needs to
Be there. It's an image thing.
it's a yes from me too, man.
you're going to hollywood.
god, if you didn't-- it's the--there's not much
Difference between screams of delight and terror.
it really sounds exactle
I can host upside-down.
Come on! Congratulations.
nothing compares to this, really.
This is the top. This is american idol.
so what--have you got any ideas on what you're planning
To audition with?
well, it's kinda top secret. Hello.
hello, how you doing? How's it going?
What is your name? My name is marlon lindsey.
and what brings you here? I'm gonna be the next
American idol. All right.
I've been wanting to try out for about eight or nine years
Now, but by me being in the army for six years, it kinda put a
Hold on it. And this is a dream come true
For me. Good for you, baby. Okay.
So what are you gonna sing? I'm gonna sing a change is
Gonna come get it.
both: Wow.
so what's the plan?
to just have, like, singing good to singing really bad and
Help it put--promote my movie career.
yeah.
Nobody does it, but I'm gonna sing a bad audition.
but it goes against my plan,
we want you to come to
come on, marlon!
now, when the light goes green, just head in there.
all right. You'll see once it's all--comes
Together. It'll be really funny.
hey.
that doesn't sound quite right.
Usually the judges' voices are like, "Yo, dog.
I'm not feeling it, yo. We're in the pound."
Or like, "That bloody--was bloody awful."
Austin is a place where panhandlers are relatively
Honest, and the lawyers and attorneys wear dreads, so...
is this america's got talent?
so let me ask you a question.
What are you gonna sing? Oh, I'm gonna sing never
Gonna give you up by rick astley.
all right.
come on, bro.
You know you can't sing. There's people out there--
you want me to sing a real song?
no. No. Because you've disrespected the
Process. There's people that wait their
Whole life for this. That's not funny to me.
I'll sing one more song. I promise.
okay.
and so the auditions roll
Right along, and a new idol phrase is born.
that's right, you are.
word.
Some of the people that audition do not belong in this
Business. But let's also be real.
Sometimes you gotta stop the bleeding.
all right.
let's get this rally going.
hey, guys. Fantastic.
good, good, good.
doing great.
now people have to tell you who you remind them of.
okay. I hear that every now and then,
it's got to be our president.
oh, goodness. Let me be clear.
well, you have to understand
That live we live in a nation that is completely torn...
and we must stand together as
One nation.
that's phenomenal. That's so great.
yes!
what are you planning on singing?
I'm gonna sing my songs know what you did in the dark by
yeah.
up.
I loved it. Absolutely loved it.
I love that tone in your voice. I love your confidence, all
thank you. I appreciate that.
yeah, there's something about certain people that when they
Come into the room, they change the kind of energy and the
Chemistry that's happening in the room.
thank you, jennifer.
there was something there that made all of us kind of perk
Up and go, "Oh, who is this person?"
you know what I--you know
What I like about you is that american idol really is like a
Checklist. Like, can you sing?
And do you have charisma? And things like that.
And it was a little eerie sometimes 'cause I really
it felt like obama
I went back into president
that's right.
I wouldn't say you're the greatest singer I've ever heard.
But you're so likeable, it's a yes from me.
it's a yes from me.
it's a yes from me too.
you will not be disappointed. I can assure you.
congrats, man. Thank you.
good luck to you. Thank you, guys.
gotcha. Whoo! Yeah!
you did it, t.K. Congratulations, man.
Good job, buddy. I appreciate it.
you've seen who the judges
Are sending to the next round...
I'm gonna say no.
it's a no from me too.
now with a new twist for
Season 13, let's see if you can
Spot the talent too.
Where is this contestant headed?
Hollywood or home?
chime in right now using the
Hashtags below, and we'll see if
You're right after the break.
before the break, we asked if
You were in sync with our
Judges.
so did they put mckenna
Dennis through to the next
Round?
who else is heading to
Hollywood?
The quest continues.
The contestants have been waiting all year for this
Moment. This is just so
Nerve-wracking. I'm telling you.
because everything is on the line.
nervous? Very nervous.
I think I'm more excited than nervous.
so here's what's gonna happen.
I'll put you in there. It's a chamber. Just hold tight.
Stand in there. Finish warming up, deep breath,
Whatever you wanna do. When the green light goes on,
Open the next door. It's all you.
Good luck. I appreciate it.
thank you. I'm not nervous.
maybe I should've rethought
Losing 130 pounds and then wearing sleeveless.
the tip of the tongue and the tongue and the lips.
my heart just hit the floor! Stop!
Give me a minute! It's like a haunted house out
There.
into the chamber you go. I'm getting locked in here.
shh. Whoa.
Whoa. Howdy.
hi. Hi, ho.
Hello. Hi.
hi. My name's tristen langley.
tristen? Yes, ma'am.
who's-- this is my mom.
okay. Well, wait a minute I kinda
Remember you. Wow.
I was on the very first season.
singing always something there to remind me, nicki
my mom was on the first
Season of american idol. She got third.
so it was kelly, justin-- kelly, justin, me.
and you. Yeah.
wow. Well, the first time I made
An appearance, I guess you could say it was when I was four years
Old. I gave my mom a rose when she
Was onstage. Well, what's your little
Boy's name? Tristen.
tristen, thanks for being here, buddy.
hi, baby. Hi, mom.
Her being up there just inspired me to start singing.
I wanted that, to make people happy and just to love what I
Do. Oh, my goodness.
So cute. Okay.
What are you gonna sing? I will be doing santeria by
okay.
there's a second-generation
that's really cool.
that's nuts.
this is something. This is history right here,
yeah.
this is tough because it's a perfect story.
I just think if mom weren't here, and the story weren't
Here, I can guarantee you it wouldn't work for me.
I totally disagree. It wasn't, you know, blow you
Away, but it was definitely a really, really good voice.
yes, I am.
yeah, but isn't that what--
how 'bout that?
tristen, look, you've got a
Great voice, but, man, when you choke it like that, you can do
It for effect once or twice...
Kind of thing. But you can't stay in that
Place or you will have no voice left.
I'm gonna say yes.
I think you're worth another try, but he's right.
If you don't get that under control--
and learn how to open up and
Let those notes out, you're gonna get into trouble.
But it's a yes for me. I'll take a look at you one more
thank you.
man.
15.
whoo!
no?
congratulations, man! Good job, good job. You got it!
dr. No.
it's come full circle, hasn't
oh, I know.
congratulations.
it's hard to do that, you
what he was doing? Yeah.
at 15?
yeah, crazy.
this is a very big day.
This day could change your life forever!
it would mean the world to me
To have this opportunity to show
My family that I really am
Talented.
I'm an artist.
That's what I do.
adam, you lived in your car
For a couple of years?
I did.
I was sleeping in my car out of
Choice.
I no longer wanted to work.
All I wanted to do was play
Music.
ever since I was about three
Or four, I've been watching this
Show.
You know, I've been secretly
Practicing my whole life, yeah.
the green light hits green,
Go on in.
okay.
N I ng in here?
you can sing.
I've been, you know,
Struggling to find what I need
To do like any other
22-year-old.
I just need to work this out for
Me and my son.
hey, guys.
hello.
we all want you to just
so much.
really, really destroy it. We're rooting for you.
this thing has become iconic
In our country.
american idol is about
you're going to hollywood, baby.
there it is.
for me, it's not american idol material.
thank you, man.
all right.
whoo!
it's okay.
welcome back to austin,
Texas, where our search for a
Superstar has led us way off the
Beaten path.
I'm from goliad, texas.
My dream of being a singer is something that's not new.
It's been here since I was four years old.
Growing up, my family supported my dreams, but there was a lot
Of people that didn't, including my ex-fiancee.
She flat out told me I didn't have the talent, the skill, or
The look, or the charisma. I never gave up hoping one day
I could be america's next idol. How y'all doing, guys?
nice to see y'all.
it's an honor to be in front
Of legends like you guys, man. Keith, I used to sing your song
To girls in high school. J-lo, my goodness.
You are an unfathomably good performer.
I loved it when you got blown up in independence day, harry.
which songs of mine did you
Sing to the girls in high school?
making memories of us. That was actually my favorite
One. Cool.
and what scene are you referring to when you talk about
Me getting blown up? Oh, the one I got blown up in.
after the black knight speech, and you know what?
It was awesome. I loved it. Hilarious. It made me laugh.
You were my favorite character. And you got blown up.
I was like, "Oh, my goodness. His buddy's gone."
I like you.
thank you. What's your name?
my name is l.J. Hernandez. What you gonna sing, baby?
well, I'm gonna sing I'll be by edwin mccain.
okay, let's hear it. All right.
When you're 25? Yeah.
that's in two years.
well, I'll be better, you know.
are they glow sticks? Now, what happened there?
oh, now, that is just-- you scared me when you pulled
Those out. I didn't know what they were.
I'm sorry. Props. You know, for like, going above
And beyond, being different. But they're glow sticks that
Don't glow. Well, they were an hour ago,
But not anymore. Good timing on that.
I can relate. I tried to time it just
Right. I could tell that you put a
Lot into it and that you rehearsed it and you took it
Seriously. Yeah.
it was really fun to watch. Yeah, well, my ex-fiancee
Told me I'd never be here. So, you know.
but here you are. That's why she's your ex.
harry, what do you think? That's a no.
I think you know that, voice-wise, for american idol,
It's maybe not the way to go. Well, thank you, guys.
I appreciate that. I really do.
absolutely. Coming from professionals
Like you all that have been in the industry, it means a lot to
Hear that. You know?
But thank y'all a lot. Y'all have a good day, all
Right? You, too.
well, thank you. Thank you, man.
what happened? No? No ticket today?
not today, bud. But, hey, don't give up on your
Dreams, guys. That's right.
well, better luck next year. In this situation, the cowboy
Cowboys up and gets back on that horse.
Good-bye. I'll see y'all next season.
J-lo, call me, all right? That woke me up a little bit.
austin has that effect on people.
The best part of the job is when we give somebody an
Opportunity to get the break they're looking for.
I mean, that's it for me. How are y'all?
we're good. How are you? Good, man.
I'm so good. I'm glad to be here.
glad you're here. We're happy to have you.
What's your name? John fox.
and where are you from? I'm from magnolia, texas,
Which is a small town outside of houston.
I live at home with my mom and dad.
I was at a four-year school. And then I was like, "This
Isn't what I'm supposed to do. I'm supposed to do music."
So I moved back home. Now I'm stuck there for a
Little while, so... and what do you do?
I'm a worship leader, actually.
ah. John wrote a song for church.
He was six years old. I wanna be an artist.
I wanna be a singer. I finally get that opportunity
To just show the world what I have.
what are you gonna sing? I'm gonna sing to make you
Feel my love yeah. Great song.
right on, john.
gosh, nice voice.
thank you so much.
It's good to play in front of y'all.
yeah.
it's always so cool to, like,
Imagine what someone is gonna sound like.
And then, when they sing, be totally surprised.
I love what then that
yeah, it's like--I did not
Expect your voice to sound like that.
I'm not sure what I expected,
yeah, it was so refreshing
Today. We've had so many guitarists
Come in and sing. And they don't have the
Authority in their voice. And they end--the guitar ends up
Being the thing that's the loudest and the most dominating
yeah.
and you didn't have that problem at all.
I loved it.
you're such a great guitarist, by the way, keith.
thank you. Oh, well, that's it.
thank you. Thank you.
are we voting?
yeah. It's a yes from me anyway.
thanks, keith. I appreciate it.
it's a yes for you?
yeah! Thank you so much.
great job, man.
congratulations.
all right. See you all there.
good job, buddy.
you got it, man!
we're so proud of you!
I mean, what's so interesting is that he likes being a worship
Leader. Like, he's the guy who sets the
Tone for where the service is gonna go.
oh, yeah.
that's what he does for a job.
That's really cool. I like that.
go, john!
look at ryan. Ryan's sleeping on the job.
you are so lucky you woke up
hi, guys.
So what do we think of the day here in austin?
I thought it was a pretty good day.
I think jesse roach was good.
there was a guy that was
oh, right.
But the exciting part about this show is that you get to see
that's it.
like, you watch these young people evolve.
so we're in the beginning of the journey.
And we have to wait and see, like, who becomes that because
We might have seen the american idol.
I agree with that.
are there any issues with the family here?
we're good.
I feel like I have total control.
It's great.
and she won't even sit with us on the same seat.
I feel like we're on love
Connection. You're gonna have to choose
Between bachelor number one, bachelor number two, and
Bachelor number three. Where's chuck woolery when we
Need him? We'll be back.
it's the final rose. Here. Good-bye.
you don't want my rose? After the break, we're
Setting up shop in san francisco.
I'm gonna say yes and pray that keith says yes too.
yay! You're going to hollywood!
find out who gets the gold right after this.
I like your voice a lot. Baah!
that was intense.
the hunt
for your next idol takes us west to san francisco.
I'm gonna drive over the golden gate bridge to go into
San francisco. And today's the real audition
Day. I'm really excited.
but who in this crowd will
Get that all-important golden ticket?
are you ready?
At stake is our prestigious trip to hollywood.
I may be working behind this register, but today we have
Some voices out here you guys just need to hear.
ennir, keith, and harry are primed for the task ahead.
I'm excited about san fran.
And we gonna find some great
People here.
there's so many of a
Particular kind of singer that,
When someone ces iwho isn't
Anything like them, that's the
First time I find myself really
Being interested.
we're looking for something
That we've never seen before.
yeah.
let's hope.
ready to go?
so ready. Let's get it.
I'm rachel leery. I'm 17, and I'm a senior at
Monte vista high school in danville, california.
I love singing and playing the guitar.
I'm not putting pressure on
You, but you have to make this next round of idol so I can
you already yelled at him to
Take his shirt off at the first concert we went to.
"I'll take your shirt, keith."
When I'll go in there, I'll probably, like, try and play it
Really cool so I don't, like, wipe the drool off my chin from
Seeing keith.
hi.
I'm rachel.
hi, rachel.
what's your full name?
rachel leigh rolleri.
okay. What are you gonna sing?
stay okay.
I like that.
I like that kind of stuff.
it's a confidence that that takes.
all right, cool.
you said it's been a long day, or it's gonna be a long
it's gonna be both.
also, that chord was meant
To be an a flat 7 when you said, "Begs you not to go."
It's a great chord. It's a good one.
what is he even talking
About? I just go by what I feel.
What is that look that you gave in the middle?
sometimes I, like, get all nervous, and I hear something
That I think maybe you guys did. And I'm just like, "Oh, I'm
you have such a beautiful
Voice, baby. You've got a great voice.
thank you, keith urban.
you know what's great? Is that it's you.
it's really pretty.
you have a little cry in the back of it too.
a little tear in the back of
it's very mature for 17.
thank you.
and you play guitar really well too.
I agree. It's a sort of understated
Confidence that you have, which is extremely important in
American idol. It's important in life.
it's attractive too. It's very attractive.
But I will say this. The first time you thought you
Flubbed, and you kind of gave us those eyes, it was really cute.
And I said, "I love that there." The second time, it's like,
"Okay, she flubbed again." The third time, it's a bad
Habit. Yeah.
don't do that anymore. Don't tip the fact that you
Think you messed up because maybe we did miss it.
But we didn't. But we might have.
they actually say there's no wrong notes, just the look on
Your face. Rachel's first concert was a
Keith urban show? That's right.
was that your influence? Probably--
it was probably mine. Yeah?
it's a yes from me. Yes from me!
yes! Thank you so much!
I must say you are all wonderful.
Thank you very much for your time.
you're gonna do great out there, baby.
thank you so much. You are.
See you in hollywood. Congratulations, rachel.
there it is.
oh, my gosh. Hello, there. She's really good.
yeah.
I like the thickness in her tone.
yeah, it's--that's what it was.
I couldn't think of how to say it, it was--
it was like the cher thickness.
Like, . Yeah, like a little something
Going on in there. I don't know.
I won't do that again. I'm sorry.
please. That'd be great. We'll keep an eye out for
Rachel in hollywood. But it looks like the
Where I'm from, not a lot of people have been able to make it
To where I'm sitting. I feel like I was just born to
I went to the junior olympics twice when I was ski racing.
And then I started really getting into music.
And my passion for music just kind of consumed me.
I'm auditioning today because I have a really unique style.
It's a lot different from a lot of other people.
I don't look like someone who sings like how I sing.
from the way you look to the way you sound, I felt it was
Very authentic. I like your voice a lot.
I think you've got a big voice, a huge voice.
It was like--it wasn't even raw. It was primitive.
yes. In a really good way.
Like, primitive talent. Thank you.
I think you know what the answer's gonna be.
we're all saying the same thing.
You're going to hollywood! Yes!
it's a yes. Going to hollywood.
you're going to hollywood. Nice job, athena.
thank you.
whoo!
oh, my god!
oh, my god. Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
I'm going to hollywood! I'm going to hollywood.
oh, my god. Next?
how you guys doing today? Good.
real good. My name emmanuel zidor.
I'm 24 years old. I'm originally from miami, but I
Live in atlanta, georgia. You have a great voice.
thank you so much. And a great entry.
I mean, the floor thing. A good entrance.
it scared me a little bit. I'm not gonna lie.
A little bit.
sometimes good theater is scary, you know?
that was nice.
how 'bout you sing something else for us?
okay. Just wanna hear your voice.
okay. Okay?
thank you. I'm gonna cry.
don't cry. Don't cry 'cause then I cry.
And then we'll all be crying. And then I have to fix my
Makeup. Or someone will.
they. Oh, I'm not supposed to cry
On camera at all, girl. You know I'm not--
oh! Did you just go like-- yeah, you just flipped--
Man, you ain't got no hair, and you're flinging your hair.
he's flinging a bald head.
and that was really, really beautiful.
thank you. Really, really beautiful.
yeah. I believe in myself.
I've been told by so many people that I can't do this.
I remember I went into my seventh grade class, and I told
My teacher, "I'm gonna be on american idol, I'm gonna win."
And he told me, "You will never be on that show.
you have three music teachers
Up here, and what you do you think all three of these music
yes!
don't hurt your voice. Yes!
I can't believe that I'm going
welcome back to the bay area
Where, after a great start, the
Judges are one big, happy
Family.
they're good.
are they?
whoo-h0o!
me anywhere near this thing because it's really
Scary. I mean, it is really freaking me
Out. It is so creepy it's broken--
are these all piercings?
I'm trying to figure out all this outfit right now.
that's unbelievable. I wouldn't like to be standing
thank you so much.
I'm sorry.
my bracelet!
that just totally stabbed three of my fingers.
does anyone have a tetanus
bye, sadie.
there's a place called sheep ranch?
yeah. It's actually open-range.
no.
would you use a shorn-off shotgun?
yeah.
I'm gonna hit you with a jazzier version of I want you
Back. I love jazzy.
what is your definition of "Jazzy"?
I'm just curious. What I intended to convey is
That I was gonna change up the song a little bit, so I added a
Little bit of stuff. Right.
Don't use the word "Jazzy." That's not a word.
hatchet. We should vote.
it's a no, man. He had you at jazzy, didn't
He? You can't say anything that
Has to do with jazz for harry. He doesn't wanna know about it.
no, but it's one of those words like "Pitchy."
We all know what it means, but it's incorrect.
So it's called singing out of tune.
Which are not gonna do, by the way.
hey, how are you doing? Good. How are you?
good. So who are you?
I'm katelynn johnson. I'm 15 years old, and I'm from
North plains, oregon. You're 15?
that's just crazy. God, you are not 15 years
Old! Enough!
Enough with the practical jokes on american idol.
That's impossible. You're 32 years old.
You're from new york city, and your name is beth goodwin.
that's impo--come on!
I'm 15, and I'm from north
Plains, oregon.
North plains, oregon, is a
Really small town.
And I live on a 46-acre horse ranch.
We raise horses, get on the atv.
I just run around and feed them. It's really fun living there.
It's a dream. Even though I love the country
Life, I still like to sing blues and keep it pop.
And hopefully I'll surprise the judges and come out with a
Golden ticket. So what are you gonna sing
Today? Something's got a hold on me
By etta james, but the christina aguilera version.
okay. Okay.
all right, katelynn. So, you know, you're not ready.
You need time to work on who you--who you are.
It's a no. I feel like you're talented.
It's not perfect. But I feel like we could maybe--
I'm hoping for something.
I'm still thinking. Look, I really liked it.
I like your voice a lot. I think you've got a big voice.
I think at 15, you're like, you're gonna figure it out
Really quick. But I think it's extraordinary.
And I loved it. Thank you.
I'm gonna say yes. Thank you.
I'm gonna give you one more chance.
yeah. Yeah.
I think you're talented, girl. Come here.
congrats, katelynn. Come on, katelynn.
You're going to hollywood. You gotta get those nerves
Under control. Thank you so much.
it was rocking out there. She'll be good.
she was all over the place. What?
she was all over the place, but she's talented.
she's gonna be good. It'll be good. You'll see.
katelynn's been given the
Chance of a lifetime and is lost
For words.
me?
Oh, I don't know. But back in the holding
Room, it's a very different story.
it's not like I just jumped into this.
Everything has been happening to me like it's supposed to.
When I let this out, it's gonna be amazing, you guys.
I have something that the world honestly needs to hear.
Hi, america. I'm ronald james reed.
I feel like I embody the spirit of being the next american idol.
That's just goal number one. I have a bunch of goals through
World disease, hunger, and famine, and war are gonna be
Ended. And I'm gonna play a part in
That. I know that.
what do you envision? What do you see?
I see the world in a place where all of this happens
Everywhere every day. And that can happen.
We're gonna do it, you know? Well, you've got the right
Spirit. You've got the right attitude.
You got the right energy. It's contagious, your
Enthusiasm. Baah!
hello. Hi.
oh, my god.
describe that moment, right then, when you first laid eyes
On jen. I have been waiting for this,
Jennifer lopez, for more years than I can even put into words
Right now. Aww.
What are you gonna sing? For you.
It's one of my favorite songs. Okay.
do you have a stool somewhere?
Can I-- right there.
just grab that one right there.
you're a sweetheart.
The vocals, you know, are not strong enough.
dude, so sweet.
I really wanted your vocals to be where your personality is.
yes, they are!
on rare occasions can you
Split art up into subjective and objective, the subjective being
Opion,he objective being right or wrong.
And this is very easy to say. Your singing just wasn't there.
it's okay.
I have to say no, ronald. I'm sorry.
it's a no. Thank you for coming, man.
oh, my god.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
he keeps saying, "J-lo," It's
I didn't make it,
oh, no.
you made it here.
That's what it's all about, isn't it?
be strong. Let's go. Let's do it.
It took candice glover three
Years. I can do it in two, maybe.
Hey, whatever. I'll do it. But until then, I'm gonna keep
that's it. That's right.
walk outta here proud.
see you later, all right?
okay.
that's character-building.
my voice will resound.
It's gonna be monumental. It's gonna change things.
oh, yeah, he gonna be all
Right. Wait till next year.
well, look out.
okay, thank you.
see you later. Buh-bye.
welcome back to our san francisco auditions.
What do you think we will find while we're here?
well, I think you're gonna find the best talent.
you know, san francisco,
Everybody flocks to here. It's like the summer of love.
sure.
yes.
thank you.
and tell my girl I said I love her.
oh, what's her name?
The singer. What's her name? Oh, ro--uh, randy.
it's a sign.
I'm telling you, you're gonna
all right, I hope so.
and they're waiting in that room right now, waiting for you
To hear 'em. "Hey, come and look for me."
hello.
hey.
good. How are you guys?
what's your name?
and where are you from?
I am from forestville, california.
I am 26 years old.
and what are you gonna sing, sweetie?
okay. Go ahead.
I love it.
okay, baby. Interesting.
It's interesting. For idol, it's interesting
Because I can hear you on a record.
I can hear you on some great tune like that and think, you
Know, "Wow. I love the sound of this guy's
Voice. And it's super cool.
I'm generally a pretty darn
yeah, it feels like that, and
Then the music took me someplace else.
do you do a lot of writing? Do you write a lot of your own
yes, I do.
that's what you strike me as, a good singer/songwriter,
Storytelling guy. This is the truth.
Half of me sort of thinks you'd get to hollywood week, and you
Would just be crushed by all the singers out there because of
That environment. The other half of me goes, "But
Your staunch originality wouldn't have competition in
That lane." No one's doing what you do.
I agree.
For being such a happy guy, man, that's about as
Misanthropic as you can get. I mean, that's very down.
Like, really down. And idol is not that.
Everybody else is happy. And so you have a--you have your
Own spot in the sadness. You know what I'm saying?
So it's interesting. I'm not sure if it's--if it's
Idol interesting. But it is very interesting.
let's take a vote.
you're interesting enough for
Me to see you one more time. I'm gonna say yes to hollywood
For this guy. It's up to these guys now.
what are they doing with him in there?
coaching. Giving opinion and advice.
what up?
oh, uh-oh.
he has a really, really beautiful tone.
Okay. Can he go up? Can he go down?
Does it get melodic at some point?
well, that's-- if he doesn't do--
how are you doing?
yeah, I'm--it hasn't sunk
it's beginning to sink in.
I've been working really hard at the singer/songwriter
Career for a long time. And to be able to do this and
Move up to the next part is unbelievable and really, really
we'll see you in hollywood,
David. Congratulations.
thank you very much.
nice to meet you.
I'd be interested to see if
He gets kicked out of his lane and starts getting tempted--
yeah, but in a bad way.
Like, I--he's like, "Man, that ain't working."
Like, whoo!
I'm leaving. I am leaving.
really--it was really good.
hi.
how are you doing? Good timing.
twins?
yes!
Special place in my heart for twinnies.
and I'm sierra moreno.
We're a dynamic duo. That's what we call ourselves.
Singing is our lives, and we aren't really good at anything
Else. So...
we're not. We are ready to get this thing
Together, get further than hollywood week.
let's just say someone needs to call the ambulance because
who's gonna go first?
me?
okay. All right.
this is selena, and that's sierra.
I'm gonna be singing try by
okay, go.
okay.
Let's have you sing, and then we'll come back and do it all
come on up, sierra.
it's so hard to do this in front of you.
gosh dang it.
okay. Come on over. Come on up, selena.
nervous?
Good face. Can you tell? I mean...
When you first went, selena,
You have kind of the feel for
Being onstage.
But that felt a little forced. It didn't feel free.
When you sang I felt, "Oh, wow." I actually liked it a little bit
Better. But again the nerves were so in
Control that you guys did a good job.
I would say a good job, a decent job, but it just didn't flow.
selena, when you sang, I thought your voice was rlly
Good. I think you're a really good
Singer. But then, sierra, when you sang,
I thought your voice was good. It didn't hit me in the same way
That selena's voice hit me, but you have more of a kind of
Outgoing star power about you. You know, and there's so many
Things that make up grabbing someone's attention.
Yours does it--did it vocally, and your does it
Performance-wise for me. People ask me sometimes, "Is
It hard being a judge on american idol?"
And the answer is, "No," Because every contestant that walks
Through the door is prepared for a judgment.
yeah. I also probably--even more
Than I know music, understand the dynamics of sisters in a
Household 'cause of my three daughters, which is why I'm
Gonna say this like this. One of you is clearly the better
Singer. As a set, you won't make it.
Individually, there's a decision that's gonna have to be made,
And I have no problem making that decision.
But it's probably gonna be harder on you.
I think you did yourselves a
Disservice by coming in
Together, which is why I'm gonna
Put this like this.
One of you has a better chance than the other.
yeah, so we're gonna separate you first.
let's start with selena,
yeah.
I'm gonna say yes to selena.
I'm gonna say yes to selena too.
I'm gonna say yes to sierra too.
I gotta say no to sierra.
this is what makes the job
mm-hmm.
they are twins.
I'm looking at you as two young women who came in and made a
Very distinctive decision. I think it was the wrong
okay.
this is for you, sweetie.
sierra.
you're welcome.
I know it was probably a hard decision for you.
thank you for coming.
you don't like me.
ah, that's not true. That's not true.
no, baby. I like you.
thank you.
Thank you for coming, both of you.
she started crying for her sister before--
she knew that she was--she
did you see the way they were
uh-huh.
selena, when she was singing, sierra was looking at her like,
mm-hmm.
when selena was watching sierra, she was ice.
She knows. They know.
you always gotta be prepared for it.
There's two of us, so there's always a chance of one going on
I wasn't--
I'm just so happy for you. You rocked it.
I can't--I don't think I'm gonna stop crying for a while.
so sierra will have to wait and watch from the wings.
And many of the contestants are sharing the same pain.
is there any way I can just
I appreciate that, brother.
aww, baby.
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
they entered the chamber with such promise.
oh, I'm gonna do this. Yes.
but not every dream can come true.
you're just not quite ready. So it's gonna be a no.
it's okay.
aw, not the face we wanted to see.
The chamber can become a gateway to heartbreak.
but it can also serve as a
Portal to superstardom.
my name is briana oakley. I am 17 years old, and I am a
I auditioned last year, season
12.
your light, your cool hair, it was just--it all works for
I made it to hollywood week,
But I got sent home. And I was crushed.
But I made the decision to come back this year the minute that I
Got cut last year. I'm not gonna give up.
I'm relentless.
hi.
I know you.
yes. I was here last season.
you said I have...
I said you had cool hair. Can you tell those two your
my name is briana oakley.
what did you take away from last season?
when I didn't make it last year, I was--
I was pretty devastated. I'm not gonna lie.
But, I mean, I learned from that experience that I want this even
More. So it's why I'm back.
I'm gonna sing stay by sara
okay.
17.
jordin sparks.
mm-hmm.
I could keep you singing, but it would just be for my own
but why? Right.
simple as that. Beautiful, baby.
you remind me of jordin
Sparks a little bit, so young and so powerful.
really great.
you know what I really liked
About that? You are proud to sing, because
yeah.
there's nothing wrong with the other styles.
It's just nice to hear somebody say--
yeah, and I gotta say, I
thank you.
oh, my god, thank you!
nice job.
absolutely.
it's so nice to meet you all.
great, briana.
thank you so much! Aah!
oh, my gosh, thank you so
Much. Oh, my god, aah!
I can't wait!
"Oh, my god, oh, my god,
she sang well.
really well.
yeah, I remember her.
I'm going to hollywood! Whoo!
okay, stop. You're a good singer.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'm gonna say you're going to
you're going to hollywood,
Baby!
and he comes out with a ticket.
I'm going to hollywood!
let's get it.
so the dreams of these two music makers have come true.
But would this california gold rush continue?
I love entertaining. I love being in front of people.
I am highly confident that I will walk out with a golden
Ticket today.
My nickname is "Daddy guns," By the way.
whoa.
you wanna attack me?
I mean, you wanna throw down? I'll throw down with you, man.
Seriously, I'll throw down with you.
yay, he's a lover!
that timing was amazing.
the skin on this guy is like--
wow, look at that.
I look like that.
I just didn't wear that shirt. I coulda done it.
I'm amazing.
yeah, you're so freaking
very firm.
I work on it. I do my best.
yeah. What do you do? You swing the kettle bells?
think he swings the liberty
shouli gi all my secrets
Out on tv? I eat right for the most part.
I do a lot of low-weight, high reps, and then I mix it up
do you sing?
I sing, yeah, I do.
let's go?
all right.
sorry, gaddy.
um, you're a really sweet
I can do it some more.
no, no, no.
I-I-it's--
It's--
it's a no for me, baby.
me too.
Thank you for coming in, though, man.
thank you so much.
oh, my god.
I was a little bit too nervous.
you think that's what it was?
yeah, I think that's what it was.
I was just like, looking at the two of you just to see your
I've never heard a sound like
That, much less a voice. Just a sound that when--
yeah, it was even--
My name is adam roth. I'm from sacramento, california.
I'm 28 years old, and I am a sound healer.
I do sound healing for a living. Well, music is the universal
Language of love and light and of everything.
It's the most powerful thing there is.
It's actually healing us from the inside out.
what does that mean, sound? Like, music therapy kinda, or--
you know about the chakra systems?
a little bit, not too much.
well, energy systems in our body that correlate with how
Our--we feel emotionally and our drive and whatnot, there's ways
To send frequencies to those individually to line them up and
To get us feeling balanced and feeling peaceful.
he's doing it right now.
doing it--I believe that music is intentional.
oh, that was the wrong
oh, sorry.
dude, you just put me to
Sleep. I just felt so at peace for--
I felt like I died or something. Really, I went to heaven up in
my man.
yeah. I saw my family and stuff.
whoo!
okay.
My dear, my love, what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing hallelujah by cohen or buckley, however you
okay.
thank you.
I feel guilty and unclean. Like I need to go to confession
you do.
it was a strange performance
'cause you've got an interesting voice, but, like, your usage of
It was, like, so schizophrenic that I'm baffled.
yeah, I know what he meant,
That your voice is really beautiful, and you use it really
Well, but it--there was something to me that felt like,
"Is he forcing this? Is this fake?"
I feel ya.
I think what I'm doing is I'm trying really hard 'cause this
right. We should vote.
I am going to say... Yes.
he just called you "My man."
just to crank it up.
again, the power of god.
just lay the sound therapy
Trip on him. You'll break him down.
yes!
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
whoo!
I--you're welcome.
I love you.
"Of course I'm going to hollywood.
do not listen to one word he
Says. He's a--
good luck. Thanks, man.
thank you very much. Thank you, guys.
you're welcome.
Oh, my god. That was hilarious.
I think I know what you mean by something that was a bit
what's that?
my man.
how are you?
congratulations.
I'm stoked. I've been--I've been calm all
Day, and now it's time to let it out.
whoo, I'm going to hollywood.
there's another side of you.
keith, just give me a beat, and give me the yes.
Please. I will do anything I can.
Thank you so much. Oh, my god.
that was an intense--that was
all: Hey!
yeah.
was it?
yeah, it was a good day.
we don't have a lot of these
Left, so that's always a good sign.
did we find some stars here
absolutely, man.
I mean, the people that were good, they were great.
we got on a run where there was a lot of great people.
It was jt,ike, one after the other.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
and those golden tickets
Rained in from not only california, but also oregon,
Arkansas, across the country to florida, and up the east coast
To north carolina, totaling 19 from our san francisco
Auditions. And with 14 from earlier in
Austin, we have 33 new hollywood contestants to add to the 46
giving us a total of 79
Remarkable singers who are on their way to hollywood so far
If you wanna catch up with any
Of 'em, head to americanidol.Com
To catch their exclusive
Interviews.
it is.
really, really good. It's very promising.
Bye-bye. Next week, our road trip makes
the best of the best represent for motown.
I don't need to hear anything else.
thank you!
as the nation's top
Contenders pick up speed towards hollywood.
I can hear you recording records.
I'm so proud that I come from detroit.
I love that spirit.
okay!
I'm so
Nervous. I'm so sorry.
it's just you're so
Beautiful.