Meerut.
Tell me, Nand from Meerut.
What's so special about that place?
Dude, I myself am special.
Really?
Have you done anything special
in Meerut?
No, I haven't.
But something special
happened to me over there.
Care to know
what happened in Meerut?
This story is about
Meerut and me.
So, let me begin the story
from my house.
Mother of Nand...
...your superstition has no limits.
Doing this every morning...
...has not prevented any
untoward events from happening.
We live in a dangerous city.
You sell lingerie for a living.
What if a school girl
or a college-going bombshell...
...or any other lady
bewitch you with her beauty?
We've been married
for 17 years now.
If I could have been bewitched,
I would have by now.
You've no idea
what sort of a city this is.
It's Meerut.
Meerut.
Like every other small city...
...Meerut too, is very laid-back.
Guruji, greetings.
How was your journey?
Son, may you live long.
Guruji, did you find a solution?
Did I find a solution?
Of course I did!
I picked a black crow
from a burial ground...
...and rubbed the hair from
a black dog's tail on its beak...
...to prepare this powder.
Take it.
Mix this in a cold drink and offer
it to the woman of your choice.
Then within three days...
...that woman will...
...completely surrender herself
to you.
Guruji, I feel blessed!
But the men from Meerut...
...get a kick
out of only one thing.
Scoundrels!
The Delhi intercity train
isn't a girl from your class...
That you can ride on
whenever you want
Hold on, sir.
This is my ear,
not your wife's skirt...
...that you can tug it
whenever you want
You...
Their minds and eyes can be
distracted by only one thing.
And only one thing
can blow their minds away.
Now that thing
had arrived in Meerut.
the women of Meerut are cursed...
...that their house will be ruined
by another woman.
- You shouldn't have done that.
- Shut up.
When Vipul said
"I love you" to you...
- ...you ran off!
- Yes, but Nand is a good boy.
Tell me, why would someone
wear a designer panty...
...if they didn't intend
to show it?
I swear, my pen was on the floor.
When I went under the table
to pick it up...
...I spotted it.
- And then?
- Then what?
After taking a good look at Mickey,
I got up...
...only to find her staring at me.
I was too shy to look at her.
We don't get to see that every day!
But Priyanka saw the whole thing...
...and she ran to the Principal
to complain.
I told the Principal
that Nand has crossed the line.
Priyanka, you're so mean.
He took admission in our school
for your sake.
Nonsense!
He was in an all-boys school
before.
Since he was desperate for girls,
he joined ours.
I'm sure he must have hit on
a thousand girls before me.
You don't have
a girlfriend, Nand
I don't believe that.
Your dad owns a lingerie shop.
A lot of beautiful, young girls
must be visiting it every day.
Yes, but that doesn't mean...
...I get to take
their measurements.
Forget it. Priyanka
is like your sister, right?
Yes, she was.
To get close
to her friend, Rupali...
...I let her tie rakhi on my wrist,
three years in a row.
And also gifted her
a "Dear Sister" card.
That too bought from Archies.
But Rupali fell for
a 12th grade student...
...and I got stuck
as Priyanka's brother
Stop laughing!
Look at him, must be bragging
about the skirt episode.
What's so funny?
All the love stories
at high school...
...begins by tying a rakhi,
followed by a fight, and then...
I know he's a pervert.
Vipul, mark my words.
If I fail to have sex
before I complete my 12th grade...
...I'll stay a virgin forever.
If you fail to do it...
...get "Loser" tattooed
on your forehead
When you can't help me get laid...
...at least stop f*****g with me.
Get lost!
Let's go from here.
'Okay.'
Hey, why did you do that for?
Nand, is it true?
Of course not, I didn't peep
into her skirt deliberately.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the fact
that you want to do it.
Do you really want to get laid?
Yes, I'm quite serious about it...
...but I've run out of ideas
and hope.
- What if I help you out?
- Ask me anything you want.
- One thousand rupees.
- What!
Don't take it so seriously.
I can do it for 100 rupees
in Delhi.
What if you contract a disease
or something?
I'll pay you Rs. 300.
Arrange for it.
You will be in heaven!
If you turn right
after the old market...
...you'll find a house.
A woman lives there.
She's extremely gorgeous.
But I've heard
that she doesn't speak much.
'Hello. Yes.'
Don't you know, I can't answer
my phone when I'm working?
She is he!
- I told you not to call me...
- 'B*******d!'
Tell me what is it quickly.
H*******e... Ram Khilawan!
Why didn't you tell me that the path
to heaven goes through the legs of hell?
I can't wait to see you tomorrow.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Here.
Give it here.
Take it.
Uh-oh, I'm folding my cards.
Well, as you all know,
we are done with Navratri.
Now let's plan for Karva Chauth
for our husbands.
There is no scope
for Karva Chauth in Meerut.
Even Mandodari performed this ritual
for her husband King Ravan...
...but he went after Sita.
It was Mandodari's mistake!
She failed to satisfy King Ravan.
Really, Pushpa?
When the husband is a monster...
...how can the wife satisfy him?
Four or five years
into the marriage...
...we wives cease to be attractive.
That's why husbands go hunting...
...for a new partner.
What say, Sushma?
You seem lost in thoughts.
Your husband is not
sleeping with you or what?
- Sushma!
- Coming.
My limbs are cramped
because of the daily chores!
Come on, massage my body.
What about you, Sneh?
Does your husband
'massage' you in the morning?
- Dear, get the cold drinks.
- 'I'm on my way.'
I have made a cold drink for her.
A special drink!
Keep an eye on your husband.
Now you eat only bland, tasteless food
while fasting for your husbands.
Next year, you won't even
get to eat that.
What do you advise us to do?
Put some make-up on your face.
Leave one of your
blouse buttons open.
You won't die of pneumonia
Go to Pinky Parlour
and get a facial, you fools.
If you can't take good care
of yourselves...
...some other woman
will take your husband...
- Are you crazy?
- Listen! Calm down!
Calm down, students.
Ma'am, you can come in now.
As the saying goes...
"The clouds won't shower down..."
"...until the land goes bone dry."
My adolescence
was in a similar condition.
But it showered
before the famine could hit me.
She's Mrs. Shanu Bansal.
I know how good is your English.
It's quite poor.
Therefore, from now on...
...she will teach you
English grammar.
Greet her!
Hello, ma'am.
Ma'am, they are all yours.
Hello, 11-C.
Now you know my name.
But let me introduce myself,
properly.
'I'm not like your other teachers.'
One instance of stupidity...
...and you'll fail in this class.
And the most important thing...
As long as we are in school,
we'll talk to each other only in...
...English.
Understood?
Are you deaf?
Is that clear?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Good.
'Chapter one.'
Though it's not mandatory...
...for a breeze
to accompany showers...
...but the rainfall will definitely
make you wet.
Why are you staring at her?
You've to talk to her first,
in that case.
Unfortunately,
she speaks only English.
I don't want her to tie me a rakhi.
I want her to be the mother
of my children.
Just wait and watch.
Yes, I was hitting on Shanu Ma'am.
But...
Nand,
what brings you here?
I came here casually.
How are you doing?
I'm doing great. Shall I make
a sweet paan for you?
If you promise
that you won't tell my dad...
...I'll buy a cigarette.
Nand...
...no good has ever come out of
ratting on people.
Take it.
- Pandit ji.
- 'Yes?'
- Who is...
- They are new to the city.
'A married couple
from Hapur.'
You know the
brick factory owner, right?
They are renting his place.
- And what about her...
- Her husband?
Her husband
is a mobile phone salesman.
He's usually out of town
for about three days a week.
Nand, you can't see much from here.
- Pandit ji...
- Yes?
Whom should I see,
and from where...
Leave that to me.
Hi, I'm the cable guy.
'My name's Pappu Tiwari.'
Here, take my card.
Call me if there's a problem
with the connection.
Is it fine now?
- Or should I check?
- Yes, please.
And I'm thinking...
"Pappu, take care".
Shanu ma'am will outsmart you
with her English.
I managed to get inside the house,
but what next?
Oh, she's as cold as ice!
I'll hang up now.
I think she's coming.
Well... The connection... should
be set up in h-half an hour.
A-And thank you very much...
...for the glass of water.
Ma'am.
Call your mother ma'am,
I'm Rasbhari!
I swear on God.
I have developed a new weakness.
It pains a lot, over here.
So far, I have slept
with around 82 girls.
But the kind of workout
this teacher gave me...
...was out of this world!
Pappu bro, I'm not following you.
Are you complaining or bragging...
...or should I be worried for you?
Hey, cut it out.
And listen to this carefully.
Do you know Sirohi's house?
- The one opposite Pandit's shop?
- Exactly.
A beautiful, hot woman
has moved into that house.
She really made me
work my ass off.
Don't ask me, man.
Why? Did she take you
for a ride or something?
You're wrong.
You're absolutely wrong.
I walked right into her bedroom.
She agreed instantly!
And then I ended up doing
what I do best.
Pappu bro, tell me
how do I impress her.
Don't forget to smile at her
when she looks at you...
...everything will be smooth
sailing from there.
Do you understand?
What were you staring at yesterday?
You know it.
So, shall I show it
to you myself, today?
What is happening here?
What is happening?
- Ma'am, well...
- English.
- Just 'Esehi'.
- I said, 'English, please.'
If you cannot talk in English,
please leave the class.
What was happening?
Sex.
No.
That will happen now.
Nand, listen.
Nand.
Couldn't you wait for 30 seconds?
You're beating your meat here!
We're getting late for the class.
- Damn you.
- Don't touch me.
Whoever comes late to the class
will be sent out.
Nonsense. Why are you sleeping?
Whose skirt did you
peep into this time?
- Why are you not in the classroom?
- I had been to the loo.
- Are you done?
- Why? You wanted to come along?
Priyanka, I'm sorry.
There's no sense left in you.
I thought you were
my Rakhi brother.
But you turned out
to be a pervert.
Priyanka, to be honest
I did not peek...
...under the table on purpose.
My pen actually fell down.
I swear on God.
You made her your sister again
by shelling out 15 bucks.
Dude, I'm her friend now.
I'm not going to be
anyone's brother anymore.
So, you want to sleep with Priyanka
before your 12th grade.
He is the one who pulls
the strings.
I'm just here doing his bidding!
Dude, even you know about
Shanu ma'am, don't you?
What do you mean?
Who else knows about her?
- Well...
- Guys, come with me. Right now.
Tomar, what's the matter?
- Ms. Shanu is giving Jitu an earful.
- S**********r. Let's go.
How dare!
He misbehaved with me
in the staff room.
Shanu ma'am, please keep it low.
It's lunch hour.
Children are around...
...please try to understand.
Sir, what do you mean,
keep it low?
I'm going to the police
and filing a complaint against him.
This is unacceptable.
He doesn't deserve to be a teacher.
What will his students learn!
Well, at least tell me
what did he do.
Sir, I was checking the test papers
in the staff room.
He was staring at me
but I ignored him.
And then he walked
up to me and said...
Will you tell him...
...or shall I say it
and wash my mouth later?
Sir, he said, "I think your blouse
is tight, if you don't mind..."
"...I'll take the measurement
and get a new one stitched for you."
- Let me take your measurement!
- Mr. Jitender, what's all this?
S-Sir, I didn't say any such thing.
What? You didn't say anything?
Sir, I'm going to report this
to the police.
Please don't go to the police.
It will cause
unnecessary embarrassment...
...to him, to me
and to you as well.
You take him to my room
and reprimand him.
Look, he's ashamed.
Sir, he said this to me
in front of everybody.
S**********r!
No one will dare to mess
with Shanu ma'am now.
She defiled Mr. Jitu's face.
I can't believe Mr. Jitu
said that to her.
I thought that s**********r
is a coward.
Pappu was cooking up stories
and Jitu bought it, you know.
It's not that easy, man.
Oh, man.
Where did you shoplift this from?
I stole 200 bucks from
my dad's pocket...
...let's drink Haywards 5000 today.
You're a bloody b*****d.
God damn it. Who's calling me now?
- I'm f****d.
- What happened?
I have to take mom somewhere.
I need to go home now.
No problem.
I'll have both the bottles.
Really?
- Go ahead. Drink now.
- Hey...
Get out of here. You think
I'm not going to drink it?
- Enjoy.
- I will. Get lost.
D******k.
Mom, I'm getting late
for my tuition.
Don't worry, you will be on time.
Let me give your dad his medicine.
He's inside.
What are you doing here?
Hi.
I was just...
Don't you think you're obsessed
with female undergarments?
- No, I came here with my mom.
- Mom?
You brought your mom
with you to shop for this?
No, my mom's not shopping.
She came here to meet my dad.
So your dad is shopping with her
for undergarments?
Priyanka, my dad owns this store.
Really?
- Why didn't you tell me before?
- Well, you know...
Next time, I want a discount.
Let's go. Hurry up.
The Guruji is here for only two days.
Don't make me slap you now.
You don't like
taking me around, do you?
- I am late.
- I'm leaving.
Five minutes. Just five minutes.
Okay? Come on.
- Am I late, Sushma?
- No, not at all.
I have picked a number for you.
He will be here any minute now.
Well, I went to give
my husband his medicines.
- Well, did you hear about her?
- Who?
- Sirohi's new tenant.
- What about her?
A married couple have moved
into that house.
No surprise there.
Ms. Sirohi always
rents it out to a family.
- Hear me out.
- Go ahead.
A married couple has moved in...
...and the wife is quite sexy.
So what? What's the big deal?
There are so many sexy
women out there.
Have you seen my niece?
She looks just like Katrina
that too without make-up.
Stop interrupting me now!
Come on, let her talk.
Go ahead.
Tell us what happened.
She's utterly sexy.
All the men in the town
are going...
...around her house
as if it's a shrine.
Sneh's husband
is in the police force...
...and the police station
is near to her place.
Do you still think
it's not a big deal?
What do you know
about her husband?
I heard that her husband...
- Long live the Lord...
Hail the sage...
All hail...
- The Lord...
Hello. Tell me.
Mom, what should I get?
Six Lachha Parathas
- Four Lachha Parathas...
- It's six.
- Go on.
- And...
Two Dal Fry.
- One Dal Fry.
- No, two.
What are you doing?
Let me talk. I'm on the phone.
Mom, tell me the full list.
The guy here is getting mad at me.
There's an order
from Sirohi Villa.
Four Lachha Parathasand one Dal Fry.
Sir, I'll deliver it.
Sir, he had gone yesterday.
Today's my turn.
- Sir, let me go.
- Sir, I'll go. - Shut up!
Where is this enthusiasm...
..when I ask you guys
to do the dishes!
- Yeah. Tell me.
- Hey, Manoj.
I'm taking my order home...
...Sirohi Villa is on the way.
I'll deliver it,
if you don't mind.
Pack both the orders now.
I was waiting for a chance to see
what Shanu ma'am's husband was about.
I didn't know that opportunity
would come knocking at my door.
Yes.
Sir, you had placed an order
for food, at Do Bhai.
Yes.
Naveen, who's at the door?
Shanu, a delivery boy
from the dhaba.
How much is the bill?
Well, it's 320 rupees...
...but I'm not a delivery boy.
- Who are you then?
- I'm Shanu ma'am's student.
Listen, it's your student.
- Hi, ma'am.
- Hello.
Were you saying something?
Actually, I was going home
with my order...
...I thought of dropping off
yours as well.
Okay. I think
something's missing.
Perhaps, it's in my takeaway.
Why don't you check?
Give me a minute. Darling...
Here's 320 rupees.
- Thanks, sir.
- Good night.
Hi, Vipul.
Pappu was making
d*******s out of us.
Shanu ma'am and her husband
love each other very much.
I just saw it.
I'll see you tomorrow
and will explain it in detail.
S**********r!
Aunty, is that you?
Sorry, I shouldn't
have said that.
No problem, dear.
I have heard that word before.
But, aunty, what are you doing
here at this hour?
Stop questioning me
and turn around.
- Aunty, I have to go this way.
- What did I tell you, dear?
Turn around and go.
On one side Shanu ma'am and
her husband's love was brewing.
But women in Meerut...
...were resorting to black magic
to ward her off.
Although a lemon looks cute...
...once the juice is swallowed
it hits the stomach like acid.
I was under the impression...
...that Shanu ma'am and her
husband are in deep love.
But there were rumours
spreading in Meerut.
Mr. Sharma who works
in Meerut Bank.
Rahul, a B.Tech student
and Snehlata aunty's husband.
She has slept with
these three men.
What are you talking about?
Ma'am, your account
has been opened.
Is there anything else
I can do for you?
Mr. Sharma who works in Meerut Bank
scored a homerun last night.
- Really?
- Yes.
Who told you?
Mr. Sharma himself said
this to Bhatia.
Rahul, a B.Tech student
takes tuitions from my husband.
I have fixed the mixer, ma'am.
He told me that he went
to fix the mixer.
"These pretty eyes of yours"
"Set my heart racing"
"It's black magic"
- And?
- What else?
My husband went to pandit's shop.
Normally he doesn't smoke...
...but I sent him forcibly to spy.
He said...
"The inspector
assigned me this job."
Officer, there's no need
to take off your uniform.
The uniform turns me on!
Ms. Snehlata was nearby...
...when her husband stepped
out of Ms. Shanu's home.
And he was not in the uniform.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I went with your lunchbox...
What happened to your uniform?
- They took it.
- Who took it?
The laundry guy.
My shirt was stained with tea.
He'll return after washing it clean.
Why are you still standing here?
Come on, go.
I have to go to the station.
Did she catch him in the act?
Dude, if she had caught
him red-handed...
...she would have spread the news
in the entire neighbourhood.
And she would have kicked
the shit out of her husband.
- Looks are really deceptive.
- You're right.
Ma'am...
...you can ask me if you want
to know anything about me.
Dude, I don't believe this.
Rumours about Shanu ma'am
were in the air...
...and I was getting mind f****d.
[Theme Music Playing]