Really, ma'am.
We are so lucky.
Your daughter came into the family
as our daughter-in-law.
Stop it, ma'am.
She has inculcated the ethics
of both the families.
Let's see how our daughter-in-law
turns out to be.
Hey! Why, Mom?
Shardul selected the girl, right?
You even met her.
Yes. I've met her
and I also know her.
Thank you.
Mom.
Why were you talking about your
daughter-in-law in front of everyone?
She works in a call centre.
- She goes to work
wearing short dresses. - So?
Who knows what she does
after leaving the house!
Shardul keeps going to Bangkok
due to his work.
Who knows what he does there?
He is a boy.
He is allowed to do anything.
Well, that's how men are.
Unless they get to relish
the outside food...
...they can't digest
the homemade food(!)
Even your Naveen stays out
due to work.
Doesn't he do anything?
Keep it in the fridge.
[Title Montage]
Yes. Everybody does it.
What, Ms. Pushpa?
It's so hot and you
are serving us tea.
Order for a cold drink.
Manju, you are bothered
about the cold drink.
And here the men are having fun
with that whore.
Sister, are you trying to say...
...that men don't do anything
after leaving the house?
Yes... They do
but when they are out of town.
Whenever my husband
goes to Delhi...
...he gets a massage done.
As if I don't know where the girl
touches him while giving the massage!
That's fine.
But over here, in our town,
under our noses...
...someone else is giving
pleasure to our husbands!
I can't tolerate that.
What is the use?
We even tried spying on her.
- But we couldn't catch hold
of anyone. - Just once...
Once we catch hold of someone...
...I swear on Goddess Chandi...
...I will drag that teacher
out of her house by her hair.
Why, Ms. Pushpa?
Is your husband on the list too?
[Manju] 'Oh, okay...'
Nand is taking tuitions
from her, right?
Why?
Did she teach him something too?
Nand you've already apologised
a hundred times.
There is no need for all this.
Yes, ma'am I know.
But this is not a sorry.
This is a thank you.
-What is this?
-Soan papdi.
Well, thank you.
-Can I give you a tip?
-Hmm?
The next time you gift someone,
know their tastes and likes.
Don't you like Soan papdi?
Who doesn't like it?
That's called assumption, Nand.
And assumptions do no good.
So, d********r. What
are you learning these days?
Tell me.
What should I say, d*****d?
Did you measure?
You dumbfuck,
I go there to study.
Yes. Hero Nand
has turned back to brother Nand.
Idiot, you were saying...
...that you'll make Shanu ma'am
the mother of your future children.
What happened?
Did you make her your sister?
Listen to me.
Let me do her if you're
not getting any.
Rupali is taken anyway.
And nobody else cares about me.
Buddy, I am fine with anything.
And when the girl is elder to me...
...I love it.
Bhalla.
You don't need Nand's recommendation.
The rate at which Shanu ma'am
is getting laid...
...you just have to spread
your legs and stand...
...and your number will
automatically come.
You dickhead!
Do you have an asshole
instead of a mouth...
...that you shit every time
you use it?
Dumbfuck, she is your teacher.
And above anything,
she is a woman.
Does anyone have something
more to say about a girl?
Start buying food
from your own money.
Okay. Now, a clause is the most
basic unit of grammar...
...containing a subject and
a predicate that is a verb.
So, for example...
..."Nand studied" is a clause.
There are two types of clauses.
Independent and depen...
Nand.
- Nand.
- Yes, ma'am.
- What happened?
- No, ma'am. Nothing. Just...
You had fight with Vipul.
You know, ma'am?
You know, students think...
...that we teachers don't know
what's happening in the school.
[Shanu] 'But that's not the truth.'
I know you fought with Vipul
regarding something.
Is that why you look troubled?
Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am, I'm not able to understand
what's happening in my life.
I don't like what Vipul says.
I'm not able to concentrate
on studies.
And now, even Priyanka
is not talking to me.
Hmm...
Well, Nand, I think you
are ready for a lesson.
Mister, stop.
Okay. I'll see you in
school tomorrow.
Okay, listen. Get those tops.
Bye.
Mister,
is any other system available?
Priyanka, talk to me for just
five minutes and then I'll leave.
Tell me.
Look, I'm an asshole.
Yes. I'm a stupid.
And I don't think before I speak.
But I know one thing very well.
Honesty.
Honesty is very important
in life and in relations.
Do you know there is nothing
more sexy than the truth?
Huh?
What happened?
Can't a teacher use the word "sexy"?
Look, Priyanka.
I like you a lot.
And I do have a little feeling
that you too like me a lot.
You can use the word little.
Okay. You do like me a little.
And I know
that I've hurt you a lot.
I also ignored you.
And I'm so sorry for that.
You have already apologised
to me before.
I am the one who's mad
to forgive you every time.
Don't forgive me this time.
Don't forgive me at all.
But I just want to
tell you one thing.
Tell me.
Everyone at this age thinks...
...to have an affair
is the most important thing.
But two people having
respect for each other...
...is more important
than having an affair.
If you respect,
I don't know about the affair...
...but there will be
a genuine friendship.
You'll get a lifelong friend.
No matter how much we fight...
...one thing is for sure.
That is,
I have always respected you...
...and I'll keep respecting you.
Friends?
Anyway, you carry on.
[Nand whistling]
Mom, why are behaving
like a Ninja in the house?
I haven't seen you whistle like this.
Why? Can only your cooker
blow a whistle? Can't I do it?
- Okay!
- Hmm.
What are you sniffing?
I don't drink beer.
Hmm.
Come, sit.
Sit down. Sit.
Tell me.
Where were you?
- Tuitions.
- Which one?
- English.
- At Shanu ma'am's?
No...
There is a tea seller in front
of her house, right?
Today I had been to him
for tuitions, Mom!
Stop this nonsense.
Are you trying to joke around?
Mom, you know everything.
Then why are you enquiring?
- Enough.
- What?
Enough of your tuitions.
You don't need to go for
English tuitions anymore.
- Huh?
- What huh?
Did you forget Hindi
while learning English?
Don't you get what I am saying?
- But, Mom.
- Nothing doing.
Mark my words.
No more tuitions from tomorrow.
- What happened at Nand's house?
- Not at his house, but in the class.
- Yes.
- You don't hear anything I say.
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm alright.
What will happen to me?
No. I mean...
Does Meerut seem fine to you?
Yes.
- And class?
- Classes are going good.
I enjoy. The students are good.
They are smart.
But you know, my husband
doesn't stay at home much.
He has a travelling job,
you see.
Yes.
-'Don't do this, dear.'
- Stay there...
Stay there. Okay. Now speak.
Why don't you say something?
Are you dumb?
Hey, Nand.
Listen to your mother at once.
Okay!
Here you go.
No...
Your dad will get
whatever you ask for.
- Do you want a motorcycle?
- What are you saying?
- Stay quiet! Motorcycle?
- Mom, you know what I want.
- Tell me if you are ready
to agree or else... - No...
Okay, fine.
- Go to tuitions.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
- Put the knife away.
- Back...
Put the knife away.
Put it away.
[phone ringing]
What happened to him
at this hour?
- Yes, tell me.
- Were you sleeping?
No, you d****d.
I was playing cricket.
[Nand] 'Do you want to play?'
- Listen, that...
- Are you drinking beer?
Yes, buddy.
I went way too far talking shit.
[Vipul] 'You know that there
is no filter in my mouth.'
Whenever I open it, I speak shit.
So, sorry.
Even I hit you for no reason.
[Nand] 'I am sorry too.'
And listen.'Apologise to ma'am.'
Sure, buddy. Sure.
Anything for you.
[Vipul] 'I'll apologise to ma'am
first thing in the morning.'
There are two more beers.
Will you come?
No... Dumb-fuck.
I created a ruckus at home today.
My parents will bury me
if I irritate them more.
Don't get drunk.
- Okay.-[Nand] 'Good night.'
- Mom.
-[Pushpa] 'Yes.'
Aren't you sleepy?
Yes, that...
You are asking me to sleep
after creating a ruckus.
What's the matter now?
Why do you want to go to
Shanu ma'am for tuitions?
Mom, Shanu ma'am is a good teacher.
And I'll become something
if I learn from her.
That is what I'm tensed about.
Mom.
I am your son.
And I won't do anything wrong.
I promise.
- Really?
- Yes, I promise.
Okay. Go to sleep.
- You too go to sleep.
- You sleep.
[Nand] 'Ma'am,
check these clauses once.'
- Hmm?
- 'Clauses.'
Here you go.
Ma'am, this...
Usually it's given while apologising
or thanking someone, right?
And you'll scold me
when you check my homework.
Actually, even I
wanted to thank you.
Vipul had come today.
He kept apologising profusely
for a long time.
- I'll take one more.
- Hmm.
Can I get a glass of water?
What is it, kid?
Are you lost?
M-Ma'am?
What is this ma'am?
I am not a ma'am, dear.
I am Rasbhari.
Kiddo.
- Dear. - Ma'am.
- My precious.
It is time for you to be a man,
kiddo.
Ma'am, today is Tuesday.
We'll do it tomorrow for sure.
Tomorrow. Okay?
No matter if it's a Tuesday
or a Monday, kid...
...one cannot refuse
rain from falling!
And I haven't even done
anything yet.
Ma'am, I can't do this.
Do you know whom
you are saying no to, kid?
I make royals forget their royalty.
They call me Rasbhari.
I will leave you perplexed
once I touch your lips.
My intoxication is like
that of jimsonweed.
Victory to Hanuman who is the
ocean of wisdom and virtues.
Victory to the king of Monkeys
who is illuminating three worlds.
Victory to Hanuman who is the
ocean of wisdom and virtues.
- Victory to the king of monkeys...
- You're the messenger of Rama.
You are also called by the names ofAnjani Putra and Pavana Sut.
Oh mighty valorous one,
of terrific deeds.
Cure my bad mind, oh companion
of those with pure mind.
What, kiddo?
Will you scare me
with Hanuman Chalisa?
No...
- You think I'm a ghost?
- No...
- Come on, kiddo.
Enough of this hide and seek.
Come.
Ma'am, I will be a sinner
and you too.
"Why couldn't I do it?
I got to know this later on."
"I was still thinking..."
"Why couldn't I do anything..."
"...when Rasbhari came in front of me
who I was waiting for so long?"
"Was I shit scared?"
"Or was it my respect for ma'am?"
"Or was it the teachings inculcated
in me by my parents?"
"What was the reason that I lost
the chance of losing my virginity?"
"I was soon going to
get the answer."
[door knocking]
Who is it?
[Pushpa] 'Open the door.
It's me.'
What is happening?
Nothing. What?
What's supposed to happen?
Where had you been?
I had been for tuitions.
Tuitions?
Where are the books?
Books. They're outside.
No, there are no books.
There is the bag and also
the key of the scooter.
But I couldn't find the books.
Yes... They're there.
[Theme Music Playing]