- Then?
- Not now.
It wasn't easy for me
to get admission here.
So, I'm not going to
miss my first class.
Your story sounds way more
interesting than the class.
Please tell me, what happened next?
Please tell me. Please.
Then I asked madam to run!
[Title Montage]
Wait a minute, Nand.
I'm confused. Calm down.
- Ma'am...
- Sit down, what has happened?
The ladies of this town
have decided to target you.
I mean... they want to humiliate you
and kick you out of town.
How can they do that?
- I'm calling the police.
- Ma'am, don't be crazy.
Why would you call the police?
Those b*****s...
Sorry... They will gang up with them.
This is Meerut. People will shoot
your video instead of helping you.
How can I go now?
Even Naveen isn't home.
Call Naveen sir right now.
- And leave once he's back.
- He'll be back at 6 in the morning.
6 o'clock?
Vipul? I need help.
Find Bhalle and get to work.
It's urgent. Okay?
Ma'am, if it's ok with
you may I make a request?
May I stay here tonight?
Ma'am, I'm your student.
And you have taught me that
there is nothing above 'respect'.
You don't have to stress.
You are my responsibility now.
[vehicle honking]
Bhalle, M*********r.
Who eats at this hour?
I jerked off before sleeping so,
I'm starving.
- What?
- Sit.
- Where to?
- To chant prayers.
Okay, let's go. Want some?
[phone ringing]
Nand.
There's water,
if you need something else...
Ma'am, be comfortable. Don't worry.
Thanks, Nand.
Okay, go ahead with your call.
- Good night.
- Good night, ma'am.
[phone ringing]
- Why didn't you pick up the phone?
- I was a little busy, tell me.
- Did you see the picture?
- Picture?
[Nand] 'No.'
- Didn't you see the picture?
- Why?
What were you so busy with?
Where are you?
S****k, s**t, c**t, B***h.
No...
There's no feel in b****h.
What shall I say?
Yes!
W***e.
Take a look.
- How is it?
- Awesome.
Switch off the light.
Where are my sports shoes?
What is the occasion where you need
to deck up as well as run?
Tomorrow is a very important day
for the ladies of Meerut.
[hymn playing]
You go there.
Okay?
Then what are you wearing?
Show me.
What?
Where?
What are you doing here?
At least open the door. Dogs?
I have told my parents
that I'm going to study at Rupali's.
There are all night prayers
at her place.
Yes. I'll put on some vermillion
before I go home.
Come inside.
[hymn playing]
Uncle, put only Twenty.
Save some money.
Tomorrow will be Shanu madam's
extra class. Yes.
- Morning, 10 o'clock. Old Market.
- Okay.
[Nand] 'Bro...'
'It was a treat to watch the
dedication and devotion of the men.'
'There was an idol
of a lady being worshiped...'
'...while other ladies were
having their dignity stripped.'
'After all, they were looking forward
for the blessings of Rasbhari...'
'...how could they focus
on this prayer?'
Yes, it's done.
- Say something.
- Hmm?
- What are you looking for in the phone?
- Shhh. Talk softly.
Ma'am is sleeping.
Is she alone?
Shut up.
Really?
You are taking her side.
That's why I'm here.
I'm well aware of her reputation.
Are you crazy?
- Me and ma'am?
- Why?
She didn't spare Rahul from B- tech.
- And you're...
- Hot? Hmm?
Listen to me first.
Look, whatever you are saying is true.
But that's not Shanu ma'am.
- Huh?
- Hmm.
What do you mean?
I mean...
How do I put this?
She is Shanu ma'am...
...but she is not Shanu ma'am.
- Huh?
- Yes.
What are you saying?
She is Shanu madam
but not Shanu madam.
So...
What are you trying to say?
That's exactly what I'm
trying to explain.
So, kid...
Who's this beauty?
- Madam...
- Okay!
So, this is the fairy whose love
stops you from getting close to me.
A teenage beauty.
Innocent face.
Hmm.
You have good taste, kid.
Let me see...
...what's so special about her.
Come here.
Let me change the flavour.
Excellent, kid.
Along with English,
you've learnt this too.
Come.
Let's see how much
you have really learnt.
I have done a night shift
after a long time, Pappu bhaiya.
I am very sleepy.
Yeah, I could see that.
Hey, Doe-Kay.
Look at this.
What are these men whispering
to each other?
[phone ringing]
Yes, Pushpa ji.
Of course, I remember.
Don't you worry.
Trust me.
We will take out such a procession...
...that it will be only you
and Arnab on tonight's primetime.
Hail goddess Durga.
I'm all set. You leave.
Even I am leaving.
Yes.
Listen. There are three quesadillas
in the casserole.
There's curd too. Please have it.
I'm leaving.
I'll be back in the evening.
Where are you off to
on a Sunday all decked up?
I have some work.
Stop this inquiry.
The inquiry will start when I'm back.
Sir, hello, sir.
Naveen, things are happening here
just like Hapur.
History is repeating itself.
Why didn't you tell me
that Rasbhari is back, Naveen?
- Shhh... Shanu.
- You...
Everything will be alright.
- Sir...
- How will it be alright, Naveen? How?
Sir. Sir, let's go.
They will be here anytime now.
- Come on.
- Come on. - Come on...
Dear sisters.
Today, we're going to save
our husbands from that...
...b***h, s**t, w***e, s***k.
Come on, let's march on her.
March!
Naveen, did you check everything?
There is some cash lying
below the idols... So sorry.
- Will be back.
- Yes, Vipul.
Come here quickly.
Okay.
Nand.
What happened last night?
You know what happened.
Not what happened between us.
That...
Who was she?
That's what I was trying to explain.
She was not Shanu madam.
- Nand. Yes.
- Shall we leave?
Let Pappu come.
Then we will attack.
-[vehicle honking]
- Move... -[Pappu] 'I am here.'
- I am here...
- He is here.
- Where have you been?
- Come on.
Doe-kay, get the camera.
- Come...
- Let's go.
- Are you all ready? Huh?
- Let's go. Yes.
Come on, one, two, three...
Forward march!
- Doe-kay, come here.
- Come in front. Yes. Come on.
What now?
- Huh?
- I think they're not home.
-[knocks the door]
- No.
Something's fishy.
- Let's break the lock and get in.
- And do what?
What I will do at home,
I don't know.
My husband left early in the morning.
- Even my husband went out.
- And mine was wearing perfume.
Nand's father has gone out too.
- What's going on?
- I have no idea.
Wait a minute.
I know what's happening.
Do you all want to catch
that w***e red-handed?
- Of course.
- Come with me.
Your husbands will be found there too.
Old market. Let's go.
Doe-kay, get the camera.
Come on. Hurry up...
It's 10 o'clock already.
Make it fast.
Old Market. Okay?
Yes, Bhalle. Come on...
Hurry up.
Madam, let's go.
Sir, ma'am, please come.
I'm coming with you.
Vipul, take Priyanka with you.
Bhalle, come here, you rogue.
Snacks on me for the whole year.
Got it? Let's go. To the bus station.
Class?
Everybody was told...
...that Shanu ma'am class
will be held at the Old Market.
But no one thought about...
...where exactly this class will be.
Lust took over your brain.
- Huh?
- Yes.
Tyagi bhai, when the brain
in our pants starts thinking...
...the brain in the head
stops working.
Hey, there she is.
[Pushpa] 'Today,
I'm going to finish her.'
Doe-Kay, get the camera
and set the mic.
-[Pappu] 'Come on, let's go.'
-[Pushpa] 'Today...'
Where did she go?
She must be here.
- She must be here.
- Knock the door.
Come on.
[knock on the door]
Madam?
- You'll find everyone here.
- Where are they?
Switch it on.
I'm Pappu Tiwari, from Meerut.
- Look at how the women of this city...
- Move.
...are going to kick a
characterless woman... Move...
- ...are going to kick her out.
- You men can't control your lust?
- Look, how aggressive...
- Whose door are you knocking?
...these women are.
Look, let's get in.
Yeah. What is it?
- Come on, record now.
- Hey, cut it.
[Pappu] 'Cut it.'
I wanted to thank you.
For what, madam?
For saving me.
For saving us actually.
Shanu...
- Come.
- Yes.
- Ma'am, take this.
- Okay, bye, Nand.
I'm very happy that I met you.
Me too, ma'am.
Take care.
Take care of yourself and
your English too.
Sure.
Best of luck.
Bye.
- Give it here.
- Sir, excuse me.
Seat number seven.
Come on, sit there.
- Study well.
- Okay.
Yeah, okay.
Take care.
Take care of yourself and
your English too.
Excellent, kid.
Along with English,
you've learnt this too.
The next day, Shanu was normal.
Like what happened
last night was a dream.
- Did Rasbhari return?
- Yes, once or twice.
But when she came,
Shanu didn't have a clue at all.
Shanu madam mentioned English.
Even Rasbhari mentioned it.
So, if Shanu madam doesn't know
what Rasbhari does...
...then how does Rasbhari know
what Shanu madam does?
[Shanu] 'Take care.'
'And take care of your English too.'
[Rasbhari] 'Excellent, kid.'
'Along with English,
you've learnt this too.'
F**k!
- That means...
...Shanu madam and Rasbhari
were the same.
I don't know, man.
But I know for sure that this was
the most exciting chapter of my life.
- Oh, man.
-[Niharika] 'Hello students.'
I'm Niharika Sharma, your
communication strategy instructor.
Now, by the way of introduction...
...you might find that I'm the most
important person in your life...
...this semester.
And that is because...
...this class is going to decide...
...which one of you is going
to get a job in an MNC.
And which one of you are going
to work in a local factory.
There are three parts
of this course...
...spoken English, written English
and the most important one...
...group discussion.
I have some rules for this class.
-[Niharika] 'First rule...'
- F**k. She's so hot.
I am sure you will forget Shanu madam.
Save both our time and get out
of this class as soon as I enter.
[Niharika] 'The second rule
is more important.'
'I don't care what you're saying...'
...whether you understand it or not
but as long as you're in this class...
...we're going to speak
to each other only in English.
- Understood?
- Yes, ma'am...
Good. Any questions?
Yes.
Ma'am, I just want to know if
you're familiar with a Shanu ma'am...
[Theme Music Playing]