-[Lady 1] You b***h! W***e.
- [Savita] Leave me, sister.
- Leave...
- Sister, leave me...
- Leave you? Huh? B***h...
- Please, sister.
Why is she beating Savita?
Savita had an affair with her husband.
- She caught them.
- Leave you?
- Sister...
- I won't leave you. You, b***h.
- I love Naresh...
- Love?
- Shut up!
- Naresh ji, please tell her.
- What can he say?
- Naresh ji, please say something.
Please tell her, Naresh ji!
- Sister, leave me!
- I won't spare you!
Your husband is fed up of you.
So, you trapped my husband.
- Don't you have any shame?
- Please Sister...
Why doesn't Naresh ji speak up?
An affair is never one sided.
There are two people involved.
That doesn't matter...
... it is the woman who is shamed.
- I'll clean the bedroom.
- Hmm.
[Title Montage]
Bhalle,
what will you have for lunch now?
This is not mine.
It's someone else's. Want some?
- No.
- Have it.
No man.
Let's go. Time for assembly.
- Oh, no.
- Hey...
Let me at least finish.
I won't invite you home
after my marriage.
Who knows what all you will eat up.
- Your wife..?
- What! What?
- Food! Cooked by your wife, man.
- Really!
- Hey, Nand.
- Good morning, madam...
G-Good morning.
Tuck your shirt.
You forgot this yesterday.
Thanks, madam.
But, why you left?
By the time I returned from the
kitchen you had gone. What happened?
I got an urgent phone call from home.
So, I left.
Hey, same time today?
Okay, madam.
[Priyanka] 'What are you doing here?'
- Hi.
- Hurry, it's time for assembly.
- Let's go.
So, what else? How are you?
Everything's great, "Sir".
You tell me?
What do you expect if you ask
such a boring question?
"So, what else! How are you!"
You are definitely funny.
And... also sweet.
- Don't lie...
- No, really!
For real!
Tell me, how are things with Priyanka?
Much better, ma'am.
See...
I told you.
Truth and respect.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Let us revise direct
and indirect speech.
Because sometimes examiners
expect answers to be in...
Nand, what happened?
Is something troubling you?
No... nothing.
Okay, so...
...direct and indirect speech.
Ma'am, I wanted to ask you something.
Go on.
How long did it take you yesterday?
For what?
From here till there.
and then bring the glass
of water back.
I...
That...
Why?
What happened?
Nothing, ma'am.
I just asked.
Okay, so what were you teaching?
Something about indirect speech.
[Nand] 'So I was reading about
multiple personality disorder.'
'What the f**k is it?'
'Really, what the f**k is it?'
'Is it a ghost, witch or
split personality? What is it?'
'I was so clueless.'
I knew I would find you here.
Will you do me a favour?
What? Do you have a form to be filled?
No... Wait.
I have a friend request from this guy.
Really?
So what am I supposed to do?
I want to see his photos.
As long as I don't accept his request,
I won't be able to see his photos.
Do something about it.
I want to see if
this boy is hot or not.
Only then will I make him my friend.
Is that so?
So, are you my friend
because I am hot.
Mental...
Since the day you talked
about 'respect'...
...you have become my best friend.
And it doesn't matter how
a best friend looks...
...he is always a best friend.
Now do something.
His hair style is like a pig.
It's not like that.
- This is the current fashion.
- Yeah, right.
What a fashion(!)
Check out your hair first.
Show.
[Shanu] 'Correct.'
Perfect.
Very good, Nand.
Thank you, ma'am.
So, now syllabus is complete.
Now all you have to do is...
...top that English exam.
Sure, I will.
That's yours.
Actually ma'am,
it is all because of you.
You are a great teacher.
You taught me English...
...as well as that thing
about respect.
So...
All is well between you and Priyanka?
I'll leave, ma'am.
No tuitions from tomorrow.
So, I'll see you at school.
-[Nand] Bye, ma'am.
- Good night.
[Nand whistling]
M-Madam?
Y-You?
Why, kid?
When you don't like me at all...
...why do you keep arriving
at my door?
Madam, I just...
...came to take my k-keys.
And I'm leaving.
No, kid.
I won't let you go anywhere today.
M-Madam...
I have some w-work, madam.
M-Madam, today...
L-Let me go, madam.
- Ma'am...
- Kid.
You will have to do something
for me today.
W-What?
[moaning]
Slow down!
Slowly... you'll kill me!
Is this ok?
Ma'am... I mean...
Rasbhari ji.
Deadly.
There's magic in your hands, kid.
If you are so good
at massaging legs...
...then the rest would be...
Feeling shy, kid?
Huh?
Tell me something, kid.
Is there something wrong with me?
Do I lack something?
No.
Then why am I unable to allure you?
If I tell you...
...will you stop or...
I love someone else.
Oh ho...
So my prince is a lovebird.
Can I tell you something, kid?
Love is nothing.
Two bodies need a reason to unite.
Love is an excuse of that.
From centuries, men and women...
...use this as a reason
to sleep with each other.
"I love you..."
That's it. Isn't it?
Now, kid...
The fire that burns
between out thighs...
...is the reality of our world.
The rest is a lie.
Okay tell me...
...did anything happen
between you and that girl?
No!?
Our dear prince seems
good for nothing!
Why? What did happen?
I didn't have the guts.
Tell me the truth, kid.
You lack guts...
...or you don't know
what is to be done?
And then...
... he sent a message...
...at 2 in the night.
I told him rudely...
...don't message so late at night.
But to be honest...
...I enjoyed it.
Are you listening to me or not?
Hmm, I'm listening.
Then say something.
Kid...
...a woman would rather peek into
a man's heart than his manhood.
Whatever you feel...
...express it.
If you are sad then express it.
If you are angry then show your anger.
If you are upset then show
that you are upset.
This affects a woman's heart.
What should I say?
Tell me, what should I say?
That I enjoy hearing
about your new affairs?
Or should I say that I can't sleep
because you are texting someone at night?
Thinking that you are awake
for someone else.
I don't want to say anything.
And listen...
I'm not like your girlfriends.
Share this story with someone
who will be happy to hear it.
Tell me... why did you call me?
Sit for two minutes.
I don't want to sit.
What's the matter?
Apologise for what you
said this afternoon.
Forget it. I won't.
Why are you driving me crazy, Nand?
I am driving you crazy?
Yes, you are...
Really?
How am I driving you crazy?
When I showed feelings for you,
you never reacted.
Look at me. I am speaking to you.
When I treated you as a loser...
...you talked about 'respect'
and made me a friend.
[Nand] 'I was looking at Priyanka.'
'And then slowly I understood...'
'...why I couldn't do anything
with Rasbhari.'
'Actually...'
'...the reason was Priyanka.'
'When you are this close
to each other...'
'...and your breath
becomes heavy...'
'...then there's only
one thing to do.'
Sure?
Hmm.
Nandu!
-[Nand] Yes, Mom?
- Come here, son.
Hey, let it be.
Avoid these gymnastics.
Get down.
- Give me your hand.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Come.
I have fed you a lot to make you
into this strapping lad.
So, you should come
to my help on your own.
Got it.
Listen...
Yes.
How was your day?
As usual.
Listen, that...
Where all did you go?
Where will I go, Mom?
School, tuition and home.
Tuition.
Sushma.
I was cooking Khichdi.
And she suddenly called.
F**k!
Sushma, you have even kept a maid
to prepare dinner.
Hey, listen.
What's so urgent?
I have decided.
- What?
- About...
...what is to be done
with that w***e teacher.
- What is to be done?
- We have to throw her out.
In broad daylight.
We will go to her house
tomorrow morning...
...drag her by her hair and throw her
out...
... throw her out of the city.
Now you are talking.
We have been waiting for this avatar
of you to awaken.
It has awakened.
And I think...
...we should call Pappu,
the cable guy as well.
- Huh?
- He will make a video.
And who knows, this might be
tomorrow's breaking news.
And yeah...
...inform Manju and Prem also.
Sharp at 10 o'clock.
- Don't be late.
- [Lady 2] Okay. - [Sushma] Yes.
- Okay then, see you tomorrow.
- [Lady 2] Okay.
Come, let's go.
- Go on.
- Pick up, idiot.
[Nand] 'Shall I say something?'
I love your lower lips.
Pick up! M***********r,
what are you doing?
[call waiting]
It is beeping because Vipul
is calling.
Yes.
Hey, then leave it.
Pick it up, f****r!
Pick it!
You tell me. What happened?
Crazy girl.
Okay, I will call you later.
Bye.
Mummy, food!
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
32 missed calls?
Yes, Pushpa ji?
I am here.
And I will come again later.
Don't worry.
I'm keeping a watchful eye
on the house.
Yes... Sure...
M*********r!
You had to choose tonight
to show your dedication?
[door opening]
Ma'am.
Ma'am...
Nand?
What the hell?
What are you doing here?
Ma'am, I'll explain everything.
How much time do you need to pack?
- What?
- How long will you take to pack?
- Why?
- Ma'am, they are all coming.
- Who?
- Ma'am, all of them.
What are you saying?
Wait. You calm down first.
Tell me. What has happened?
[Theme Music Playing]