This is the girl, Bhabhi.
Looks pretty!
What happened?
I said no.
I am too young to get stuck in a marriage
Really? Are you saying your brother's
life is ruined because he got married!
Naveen is lucky.
Let me know if there
is someone like you.
- Really!
- And I'll get married right away.
What time is my brother Naveen
arriving tomorrow?
I think in the evening.
Here you go.
Eat this pudding.
I have had enough. Not anymore.
I’ll sleep now.
- Come on, just try it.
- Not even a bit.
[Title Montage]
But, what happened that night?
- Huh?
- What happened that night?
That...
As usual, I reached home
after work.
Shanu had made carrot pudding.
I have a cousin, Anup.
He visited us two days ago.
She had cooked it for him.
I went to the bathroom
to take a shower.
And when I came out...
Shanu...
Darling, the food is burnt.
Shanu.
Hey, the food is burnt.
Shanu? Where is she?
Darling.
Shanu. Darling.
Shanu?
- Welcome, my Master. Welcome.
- Shanu?
Shanu who?
I'm your dear Rasbhari.
Come.
Come here.
Is this a joke?
The joke is on me.
Destiny has played a game
with my life.
And given me this avatar...
Now there is a queue of suitors
waiting for me in Lucknow.
What are you
talking about, Shanu?
Sounding rustic?
Am I not?
Mom made me drop out of school
And I remained illiterate
But I know everything about life.
Give me a chance.
And I won't disappoint you.
- Shanu.
- What is it, prince?
Is this your wife’s name you keep repeating?
She isn't here.
The woman in your
arms is, Rasbhari.
♪Rasbhari♪
♪Take my heart
Take my life ♪
♪Take me wherever you want...♪
[Naveen] Shanu was absolutely normal
the next day.
As if, whatever happened
last night was my illusion...
...a dream.
Did you see Rasbhari after that?
Yes, a couple of times.
But Shanu has no memory
of this at all.
What are you thinking?
You think she's lying
to me, don't you?
That she's taking me
for a ride...
...and making a fool out of me,
right?
Yes, sir!
I have seen this in movies.
They call it role play.
To make one’s sex...
…personal life spiced up
The man plays the role of a
policeman or a plumber.
And the woman becomes a nurse
or a teacher.
And then you get going… and going!
You get what I’m trying to say.
- Sir. Sir.
- Hmm.
Didn't you ever try to find out?
Try? I left no stone unturned.
[Shanu] Naveen.
Naveen.
- How did this shirt tear?
- Huh?
How did this shirt tear?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
- But I do.
- What?
I had cooked that night,
And you had gone for a shower.
I had kept
this shirt for you.
[Shanu] Then how did it tear
overnight?
- That...
- That!!
You just don't care.
I buy things for you with love
and you ruin them.
Sunday will pass getting this fixed.
Listen.
Can I get you some flowers
on my way back home?
No. You know I'm allergic
to flowers, don't you?
You will get flowers...
...and I'll be sneezing all night.
Remember, what happened
during the festival?
Yes, I thought you're going...
...to extinguish the holy fire
with your sneezing.
- I won't get flowers.
- Don't.
Go.
- Do you really want me to go?
- No.
- Shouldn't I?
- Shall I?
- Yes.
Bye.
[Naveen] 'And then Rasbhari
didn't show up for a long time.'
'I spent sleepless nights
waiting for Rasbhari.'
And then one night.
What's up, mister?
Have you fallen in love
with Rasbhari?
Today you have landed straight on my bed.
Now that you are here...
...why don't you have
a good time...
...with me?
I have brought something for you.
[Naveen] 'Shanu is allergic
to flowers...'
'...but Rasbhari...'
Oh my prince. I’m impressed.
Aren't you going to sneeze?
It's jasmine, my dear.
It doesn't make you sneeze,
it gets you in the mood.
Naveen, what's this?
Why did you bring flowers?
Look at me.
Get rid of them.
Yes...
Sorry...
What?
Well done. Great.
A*****e.
Bloody f****r.
Sir, you were saying something.
No not me, it was Shanu.
She used to tell me,
despite sleeping all night...
...she felt quite tired.
And if she dozes off
during the day...
...she wakes up
with an aching body.
Even I feel this
when I'm alone.
Well, you know...
Did you take her to an exorcist?
Yes, I did that too.
Who else did you take her to?
We are next.
Shanu, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I'm losing my mind.
I'm going mad, right, Naveen?
What's happening to me?
Shanu...
We are going to consult a doctor.
You're going to be all right.
I don't know, Naveen.
I sleep somewhere
and wake up somewhere else.
And I can't recall a thing.
Shanu...
...I'm there for you.
Don't worry.
Dissociative Identity Disorder.
Split personality.
Huh?
It means more than one personality
living in a body.
Sir, this is called being
possessed by an evil spirit
I did not believe it.
But when medicines did not help...
...I had to believe it.
Hello, Mom.
Everything is fine.
Shanu? Shanu is asleep.
Well, Mom, where is that tantric baba
nowadays?
No, everything's fine at home.
It's for one of my friends.
He's in trouble.
Please send the address on Whatsapp
- You mean, that tantric who chases away ghosts?
- Hmm...
Huh?
Have you ever seen a ghost?
Yes, I've seen them in movies.
- They stand like this.
- I've seen a real one.
- What happened to the street lights?
- Just a second, sir.
Sir.
- Hmm.
Can we discuss this under those lights?
But let’s get the tickets.
- We’ll buy them later.
- What has happened?
Greetings, Baba.
Baba, we've come here
for help.
I have got a solution
for every problem.
Tell me. What's your problem?
Baba, this is my wife, Shanu.
Hmm… She's beautiful.
- Naveen, let's go.
- Wait. Let me finish.
Baba, there seems to be
an evil spirit on her.
No. It's impossible.
Why? Baba...
Because, the moment
an evil spirit enters this place...
...it will be burnt to ashes.
- Naveen, let's go, please.
- Have patience.
Baba, I beg you.
You're our last hope.
Help us.
Whom do I save you from?
There are just three people
in this cottage and all three...
What's up, Baba?
Did you forget about me?
I’m here too.
[chanting mantra]
Baba, I know this mantra, too.
- Shanu.
- Right?
Who is this Shanu?
I'm your Rasbhari, prince.
- Come closer...
- Baba.
You witch, leave him alone.
Come on Baba. I'm not an evil witch
hanging from a tree…
…whom you get rid of by
waving a broom.
I was famous from Garhi to Kolkata...
...even before the revolt of 1857.
I wasn't scared of the Nawabs
or the British not even of my mother
So who the heck are you?
- Lets get rid of your ghosts…
- Baba, mantra. Mantra.
- Let me show you how.
- She's insane.
- Come, let me chase away the ghost.
Baba gave up too.
He said even he couldn’t
help me.
Then...
Then what happened?
Only I knew about Shanu’s condition
Then, gradually...
...the entire town came to know.
- Let’s get Bournvita.
No…
you want to drink Bournvita?
What's a big deal?
How much is it, mister?
No problem, sir.
Ma’am will settle it for you.
Huh?
Shanu...
- Have you decided yet?
- Mm-hmm.
What do you want to have?
Well, it's your treat,
your choice.
Really? How is it my treat?
You always bring me to such
expensive restaurants...
- ...I don't understand the menu.
- It's a punishment...
...for forgetting our anniversary.
How can I ever forget
our anniversary, darling?
- Okay, listen.
- Hmm.
Well, the eggplant
that you cook is my favourite.
Of course, it is.
Because you don't have to cook.
Tell me. What do you want to eat?
Tyagi, tell me.
What does ma'am want to eat?
Ma'am, we are four of us.
You can pick anyone you like.
Naveen, let's get out of here.
- Ma'am is leaving.
- Let's go.
You bloody w***e.
After ruining the men of this town…
how dare you enter this temple?
This is God's home,
and not your brothel.
Get the hell out of here.
[Naveen] 'And then one night.'
Sh... Shanu?
What are you doing?
Shanu?
I'm leaving.
To your parents' ?
Yeah, you'll feel better.
I'll drop you.
I'm not going there, Naveen.
Where are you going then?
I don't know.
But I can't stay here.
What are you talking about?
Are you leaving me?
This is the only way
to get Rasbhari out of our life.
No Shanu, no Rasbhari.
No,no... Shanu...
I don't want Rasbhari here either.
But if you leave me,
I'll die.
Everything will be all right.
I am with you.
Then we decided...
...to face it together.
Sir, honestly...
...your love is exemplary.
.
I think there should be a movie
based on your story.
I mean it.
And I'm sorry, sir,
for all that nonsense.
It wasn't your mistake.
Well, I will go now.
Sir, if you don't mind...
...can I talk to ma'am
for a minute?
Okay. I'll call her.
[Nand] 'I realised that though this is a
tragic tale…'
'...I won't be at peace…'
'until I don’t uncover
the suspense surrounding Rasbhari.’
What is it?
Ma'am, can I talk
to you for a minute?
Go on.
[Theme Music Playing]