Mom, hurry up.
I'm getting late for tuitions.
Are you getting late for the tuition
or to meet that w***e(?)
It was not my mistake, Dad.
Manju asked me to stay back
in the school, that day.
I didn't know what she was up to.
Yes. As if you were born
only yesterday(!)
And your milk teeth are
yet to fall, right! (?)
Stop accusing my boy.
He's so handsome.
No wonder girls hit on him.
Straighten up, my dear.
Oh, Mother India(!)
Have you prepared
breakfast for me...
...or should I go out
and eat some junk(?)
Go, ask your daughter Shanu
to cook some breakfast.
She's weeping in her room
for no reason.
Weird family.
["Tum Aaye To Aaya Mujhe Yaad"
Playing]
You know that...
...the manager of Ashoka Talkies
is my friend, don't you?
Look, dear.
No one will be bothered
that there were seven girls.
They will only gossip that the girls
were with three boys.
This town would have made it
impossible for us to live here.
You are a good girl, aren't you?
This is for your own good.
Come on, get up...
...and make your dad
tasty breakfast.
Come on, get up.
[Title Montage]
[alarm ringing]
[moaning]
[door bell ringing]
The maid is extremely punctual.
Tell her that your husband
is going out of station.
And he needs the dosage
for three days(!)
You can get your dosage
anytime you want.
But I won't find another
good maid like her.
Thank God I found her
as soon as we shifted here.
Do you remember we had a problem
finding a maid in Hapur?
I don't want to think about Hapur.
Listen.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm not late, right?
[Pushpa coughing]
You're home.
- Should I get water?
- I'm not thirsty.
Did you hear this?
Guruji told her...
...that her husband shouldn't touch
even a drop of water for a month.
I'm not omnipresent
like your Guruji.
Whom did he say this to,
who shouldn't touch, whose drop?
Well...
Snehlata...
Guruji told Snehlata...
...to keep her husband away
from water for one month.
That means he shouldn't touch
even a drop of water for a month.
Only then he will be saved
from that w***e.
You women are unbelievable.
You buy everything
that the Guruji sells. Snehlata!
Pushpa...
...deduct Rs. 50 from
Nand's pocket money.
He's giving discounts
to his girlfriends(!)
What's wrong?
Are you hungry?
Two rotis are left.
Shall I serve it with butter?
Feed him and make him
as strong as a bull.
- He neither studies nor works.
- Shall I get it?
Dad...
...I'll do it.
What? Are you going
to work at the store?
No, studies.
You were absolutely right.
If I study well,
I don't have to work in your store.
Very good.
- Dad, I need a small favour.
- What is it?
Arrange a tuition for me
and I'll top the class.
Nice. But you already
go to private tuitions.
Well, you better do it.
He's in 11th grade now.
It might affect his 12th scores.
- I'm not going to waste my money.
- Get it done.
If he fails to score well,
he will blame us for that.
Think a bit about your old age.
Do you want some milk?
All right. I'll talk
to the teacher in person.
Let's go then.
- You mean now?
- Yes.
Physics, chemistry, bio.
- Does this teacher teach
all three? - No, Dad.
- Then?
- English.
You b*****d,
you want English tuitions.
You sing that despacatito
the whole day anyway. Let's go back.
Dad, without English, I won't be
able to do well in any of the exam.
Ma'am is quite good
in teaching English.
Learn English from your phone.
I'm not giving you the tuition fee.
Let's go.
Who learns from the phone, Dad?
You. Who else?
Will your father do it?
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hello.
I'm here to talk about
my son's tuition.
- Tuition?
- Yes.
He needs good English
to do well in his exams.
It's very important, you know.
Yes, Dad.
Pushpa.
Stop saying my name.
- Tell me what it is.
- What do you want me to say?
Why don't you tell me...
...what you discussed
with that w***e?
She's not a w***e.
She's Nand's teacher.
You were the one
who asked me to talk.
Now, I'm telling you
there's no need for any tuition.
He's in the 11th grade.
He needs tuition.
Otherwise,
it might affect his 12th scores.
[Pushpa] 'Really?'
How come you have money
all of a sudden?
If he fails to score good marks...
...he's going to blame us
for that.
Are we not going to think
about our old age?
Stop repeating my dialogues.
Guruji was absolutely right.
This dangerous w***e...
...is going to ruin the whole city.
Stop talking nonsense.
- Have food.
- I'm not at all hungry.
Pretty soon my thirst
will be quenched(!)
From tomorrow, I'll be visiting
her for tuitions.
You will be jealous daily.
Soon there will be fire(!)
Trust me.
If I see you around her house...
...I promise...
...I will move back to Khatauli.
Listen, dear...
...I swear on you.
I won't go there...
...not even in my dreams.
My husband went to meet her
regarding Nand's tuition.
Yes.
That's what I'm scared of.
I'm too confused.
[door opening]
Ma'am.
Ma'am?
- Nand?
- Veera?
Dad!
Stop right there.
I can't let you in.
- They placed an order.
- Ladies have asked...
- ...not to send men inside.
- What do I do with this?
I'll take one...
...distribute the rest
in the kitchen.
HUNTING DOWN SHANU
PAPPU TIWARI
RAHUL BTECH
SHARMA OF THE BANK
PROFESSOR KALIYA
CONTRACTOR BATRA
Six victims in three months.
Six names are confirmed
who have done it with that teacher.
Six or seven?
Have you not included
Snehlata's husband?
You better worry about
your husband, Sushma.
In every wedding,
your husband goes around...
...misbehaving with other women,
grabbing other women by their waist.
Really? All right.
You are not stopping
your husband...
...who has such a roving
eye on women.
Instead you're pointing fingers
at mine.
I'm just pointing fingers.
Your husband always
points something else(!)
- Look, what she's saying!
- That's it.
This is the reason
why we women are doomed.
No unity. Everybody's lost
in their own world.
Ms. Pushpa,
please tell us what to do.
- You must agree to what I say.
- Sure..
-[Pushpa] 'Spying.'
-[Sushma] 'Spying?'
Yes, spying.
Everyday one among us...
...will monitor Shanu's house.
We'll keep an eye on who enters her
house and at what time they leave.
And the most important thing...
??
If you see any one
of our husbands...
...entering Shanu's house...
...you have to inform
us immediately.
So that we can catch
that w***e red-handed...
...and put an end to her act.
You turned out to be very smart.
Everybody gets smart when
it's a question of survival.
Please get something to drink.
My throat is drying up.
Waiter, what happened
to the refreshments?
Oh, Lord Ram...
- What happened?
Add another name to that list.
- Whose name? - Veera.
- Veera?
- Are you sure?
- Even women?
This witch won't spare anyone.
[Nand] That was the first day
of my tuition.
'And I was imagining...'
...make out sessions with ma'am.
Please sit down.
Hello, ma'am.
So, tell me, Nand?
- Yes, ma'am. Nand.
Why do you want to learn English?
Because...
You don't have reason?
No, ma'am. That...
Ma'am, because this...
Ma'am, I want to speak
English like you. That's all.
You mean you want
to talk in English like I do.
Yes, ma'am.
That's my reason.
Good reason. Let's start.
This is a diphthong.
- Diphthong is a...
- 'Dipthong.'
- Diphthong.
- 'Thong' I can pronounce.
I know what a 'Thong' is.
Ma'am, actually my father
owns an undergarment shop.
So, thong I know.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello, 'Do Bhai'.
I'm going to take a shower.
Let's eat after that.
Continue...
'Shanu ma'am's husband made
me realise one thing...'
'...that any young man
with determination...'
'...can woo any hot girl
in the world.'
Sir, can I have some more sherbet?
A*****e, you've already refilled
it ten times for 10 rupees.
I'll let you put your stall
in the school next month.
While you're sucking on this,
Jogi took away Rupali.
I don't care, s**********r
I can talk to Rupali
tomorrow in the school...
...but this ice pop
will melt away.
- Look there.
- Don't disturb me.
Come on, take a look.
What is Shanu ma'am teaching you?
You have completely transformed
in four days.
Thanks, bro. Appreciate it.
So what's the plan?
Idiot! He's our friend Nand, right,
s**********r!
Baby, say hello to Nand
version 2.0.
If I was a girl,
I would have given you some(!)
I know.
Were you able to impress
Shanu ma'am?
I'm going to impress everyone.
I'm going to kill it,
just watch me.
[Priyanka] 'Hi, Nand.'
One minute.
- Hi, Priyanka.
- Hi.
- You look good.
- Thanks.
So any work you have?
No, I was...
I was...
I wanted to fill a form online.
I am not able to do it.
I was thinking, tomorrow,
if possible after tuition hours...
...if you can come
to the internet cafe. - Yeah.
- I'll do it.
- Thanks.
It's okay.
- Nand, let me touch your feet.
- Get away from me.
Dude, any guy who goes
to the cyber cafe with a girl...
- ...doesn't come back without a kiss.
- All right...
- Come on, give me a hug, dear.
- Careful.
What are you doing here?
Well, what are you doing here?
You're too old to play
hide and seek.
You will get a tight slap from me.
Why are you going there?
- Tuition.
- Tuition? - Yes.
- Oh...
- Can I go now?
- Or do you want me to stay?
- Get lost.
So tell me Nand...
...have you understood active
and passive voice now?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay. Let's see.
The monkey is climbing the tree.
Is this an active voice
or a passive voice?
A-Active voice?
Correct, but speak
with confidence.
- Confidence. Done.
- Okay. Now...
...tell me what will the passive
voice of the same sentence be?
A tree is climbing
on a monkey.
- No.
- I know, ma'am. I know.
You know you're very funny
and very smart.
If you put a little effort
you can top in every subject.
Thank you, ma'am.
Tell me,
what's your favourite subject?
Now? English.
- No. Tell seriously.
- Computer.
Well, enter your Aadhar number.
That's it.
We are done with your form.
It's done.
- Press the enter key.
- Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Well, you're quite smart.
Shall we go now?
We've still got five more minutes.
What do we do?
Whatever you want.
Priyanka, tell me something.
How can a boy know that a girl
is interested in him?
She will give him small
hints, you know.
Like...
...a girl complimenting you.
Or laughing at your jokes.
Or touching you like this
every now and then.
- What's wrong?
- This is a hint, too.
I'm a girl.
I can't kiss you first.
So, the love is expressed
through anger.
[Nand] We guys are d*******s.
With so much of courage the girl
shared her true feelings.
But we...
We are lost in our dreams
instead of living the truth.
[Theme Music Playing]