She must be innocent too.
Did you watch Raveena's new song?
Tip tip barsa paani?
I don't watch
such songs at home.
It will have a bad influence
on kids.
He has been a spoilsport
all his life. Come on.
My little one.
He troubles me all day.
Yesterday he walked
up to me and said...
..."Mom, I want to marry."
- He is six years old right?
- Yeah.
- Did he say who he wants to marry?
- Yes, he did.
Listen, dear.
What was the name of the girl
Munna wanted to marry?
- Ayesha Jhulka.
- Yes, Ayesha Jhulka.
Ayesha Jhulka?
Oh, yeah. She did a song
with Akshay, right?
Wearing a wet sari?
In the movie Khiladi.
- Yes, Khiladi.
- Yes, she's the one.
And when I asked him
why he wants to marry...
...he said, "Mom, I can't
control my urges."
He has taken after his father.
- Mom, listen.
- Tell me, dear.
I'm done with my homework.
Can I dance now?
Sure. Show everybody
how good a dancer you are.
She has been practicing
for a week now.
She wants to perform
in front of you all.
It's a good thing, you know.
Girls should learn a bit
of dancing and singing.
She's going to make
a pleasing wife, you see.
Look, she's dancing.
Your daughter is something.
She will not just please
her husband...
...she will please
the whole neighbourhood.
I told you, Dinesh...
...such things will spoil the kids.
'Naveen, this is not fair.'
It's a new city.
How do you expect me to stay
alone for a week?
- Darling, I'll call you.
- Nonsense.
Listen. I love you.
I know.
- I can't go.
- Don't go.
- I'm leaving.
- No.
- Bye.
Take care.
Past participle form
of the verb...
...and this can be
regular or irregular.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, ma'am.
Okay, now who can give
an example...
...of a sentence
in past perfect tense?
Any... Yes, Pooja.
Nand had made all the girls...
...his sisters before he finished
first term.
Okay. Calm down.
Akash, you want to stand
in the dustbin?
Quiet. Okay, quiet.
Quiet!
Yes. Thank you, Pooja.
That is a correct example.
And by the way, there's nothing
wrong in what Nand has done.
It only means that he cares
for the girls in the class.
Yes, Nand?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Now the future
perfect tense...
Ma'am took your side.
You're going to get lucky, too.
Perfect continuous denotes
an action that has started...
...at some point in the past...
...but is continuing to
the present. For example...
'What else
should have I asked?'
- Nand, my brother.
- 'Brother?'
Of course. I tied him a rakhi
two months ago.
But you are friends with him now,
ask him out.
No, I'm not going to ask.
If he wants me to go
with him to Mc Mavana...
...he should ask me out.
Priyanka, you're really innocent.
You have no idea
that the boys of this city...
...are hanging out
somewhere else these days.
What do you mean?
I mean...
...the boys have found a place
to satisfy their lust.
I should be getting paid
for sitting in this class.
He farts all the time
in his class.
Forget it.
Nand.
Dude, you're too lucky.
Listen.
- Catch a rickshaw today.
- But why?
- I have to go somewhere.
- With Priyanka?
I don't mind giving you my scooter as
it is going to be your special day.
Here you go.
Let's go.
Although I was roaming around
with Priyanka...
...I was consumed by
the thought of Shanu ma'am.
Priyanka, it's too crowded.
Shall we go elsewhere?
Go get a veg meal.
let's eat outside.
Priyanka, I'm short
of 50 rupees.
But a meal costs only 90.
Yes, you're right.
No. I'm done.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- It's okay.
- Can I tell you something?
- Yes.
Do you know why I came out
with you today?
Why?
When Shanu ma'am
said that you are...
You are...
Caring for people.
I realised Shanu ma'am has a point.
- That's not true.
- What?
Don't you care for people?
I mean, I do care
but not the way she said.
Look, who you are
and what you are...
...can only be known by a person
who spends time with you.
For example, if you pick me up...
...in the mornings and evenings
to tuition...
...I'll get to know
what sort of a person you are.
I hope you got my point.
I got it.
- Really?
- Yes.
Then?
Then... Done.
Where?
Hurry up. Come on.
Pull over here.
Mom might see us.
Okay. Give me the number now.
Give me yours.
I'll give you a missed call.
I'm not asking for your number.
- Give me your maid Veera's number.
- What?
Are you going to take
Veera to tuitions?
Why would I take her
to tuitions?
M-Mom wants her number.
That's why I'm asking.
Come on.
Please give me, sis... That...
We're friends after all.
Write it down.
'I fed you
when you were a baby, Nand.'
You used to latch
on to me...
...while I used to clean
your house.
That's why I'm telling you,
Veera.
Please agree to it.
Give me the money first
and tell me what's the job.
I don't have money to eat
at Mc Mavana.
Veera, let me tell you
the job first.
Let's talk about
the payment later.
Get me the turmeric.
You know, there's a new
tenant at Sirohi's house.
I want you to visit them
and put up an act.
Like, you need a job.
That you're a poor woman.
I'm not a poor woman. I've saved
more money than your dad.
Then why are you
demanding money from me?
Get the hell out of here.
Well, listen to me.
After you start working there...
...you have to report to me every
evening about who visits her, okay?
It will cost you Rs. 500.
All right.
Now tell me the truth.
Why?
I can't tell you why.
I'll charge you Rs. 1000 then.
Okay. I'll pay you Rs. 1000.
All right?
You have to pay me as soon as
I get the job.
Well, I got the seed of this idea
from Priyanka.
But now I'd to wait and see...
...if it would work on Shanu ma'am
Why does mom have to setup
her kitty here?
Come on, stop crying.
Must be a mosquito bite.
No mosquito will pick a spot
to bite, will it?
I used to bite him there before...
...but he didn't like it.
He used to say that his colleagues
will make fun of him.
He has become
a shameless hypocrite now.
Your husband loves you so much.
Everyone knows it very well.
'He bought you a sari
recently, didn't he?'
I lied to you all about it,
Sushma.
It was my sister-in-law's sari
from Khatauli.
Okay... Stop crying.
I just don't believe this.
What sort of a spell that witch
must have cast on him?
There's a solution
for such a problem, you know.
Didn't you use the sorcerous act
suggested by Guruji?
I did it, Sushma.
- I did that too.
- Then?
But still he's in total control
of that witch.
Tell me! She is a teacher.
She's going to be a bad influence
on students.
'Pushpa.'
Gradually, she's going to get the
whole of Meerut in her petticoat.
What do we do about this?
What can we do?
- Nand.
- Yes, Mom.
Why are you standing over there?
I'm coming.
Why are you eavesdropping
on us ladies?
Keep the tea here
and go to your tuitions.
- Dear Nand.
- Yes, Aunty.
There's a teacher named
Shanu Bansal in your school, right?
- Yes...
- Is she good?
She's a great teacher, Aunty.
She teaches from heart.
Listen, dear.
Stay away from her.
What? Are you out of your mind?
What are you saying to him?
He is still a kid.
Why are you still here?
Go to your tuitions.
Come on, have some tea.
Tell me.
I'm on my way.
Attending first period will not make
you a topper, S**********r.
I'll be there soon. Bye.
And she doesn't like spicy food.
She's not into fried food.
Why don't you tell me
also the colour of her shit
Give me some useful information,
Veera.
By the way, the husband
and the wife are deeply in love.
When I reached there today,
her nightie was unbuttoned.
And her husband didn't come out
of the room for a long time.
- And?
- Nothing. I told you everything.
- There must be something.
- And...
Well, the husband is going
out of town for three days.
This is what I'm talking about.
You have to keep an eye on who
visits her, for how long and why.
Do you understand?
Come on, take it.
- Remaining money?
- Remaining?
You will get it when you give me
some useful information.
Hey.
I won't be able to sit
behind Rupali today.
Nothing will happen by sitting
behind her...
...sit next to her, if you really
want to score with her.
You talk as if you sit
on Priyanka's lap.
Eyes on the road.
S**********r.
Nand, way to go.
Look at this.
Who did this?
A*****e, you are acting innocent
after doing the stunt
I swear on you, Vipul.
I didn't do it.
You both have been declared
as a couple in the school.
You must have done something.
Look around. Everyone's showing
their respects to you.
'Wonderful, dear.'
- Congratulations.
'Vikas. What are you doing!'
'Go, stand at the back.'
Do you want to have?
Here you go.
25 girls have questioned me so far
if this is true.
- So, tell me.
- What?
Is this true?
Are you crazy?
Writing names
in a heart symbol...
...doesn't start an affair.
Ashima and Pranav's love story
began the same way.
Everybody thought
they were a couple...
...and gradually they became one.
That rascal must have written.
Let go of me, b***h.
You b***h.
I'm your classmate
since second grade...
...and your best friend, too.
That doesn't mean you can
pull my hair.
I know that's your handwriting.
Don't tell anyone...
...it looks good, right?
Dad, don't send me to school
as I'll be managing the shop.
I send you to school
because I don't want you...
...to run this store for a living.
Got it?
Stop staring at me.
Just sit here for 30 minutes.
Phool will manage the rest.
Come on!
Idiot.
♪Oh, your slim waist...♪
Darling, pick it up.
Whom are you calling darling?
Is she your girlfriend?
She?
No... Just like that.
Well, Priyanka...
- ...I didn't draw the heart.
- I know.
You are not that kind of a boy.
So, you didn't come here
to yell at me!
I'm here to shop.
What?
Do we get vegetables here
You are right.
Go ahead. Phool!
Show it to ma'am.
What do you want me to show?
How much for this?
- Phool.
- 'Yes, sir.'
How much does this one cost?
It's a honeymoon item.
Sir got it from Delhi.
I didn't ask its history.
What's its price?
250.
You can pay 200.
Sir, it's less than
the breakeven price.
So, which one do you want?
Whichever you like.
- How about this one?
- It's good.
Phool, pack this.
Day after tomorrow there's
a festival in Model School.
So, I was thinking...
- ...we both might...
- One second.
Yes.
Now?
All right.
I'm coming right away.
Okay.
Priyanka, there's an emergency.
You can... Phool,
collect 200 rupees from ma'am.
See you tomorrow. Bye.
Ma'am, money.
- What's this?
- I'm returning your money.
Are you crazy, Veera?
No, I'm not.
But the entire city has gone crazy.
They all have cooked up
stories about her.
She does that,
this and she goes after men.
That's what I wanted to find out.
I've found out. It's all lies.
I haven't seen such a good woman
in my life before.
I quit working at four houses...
...now I work for her full-time.
Are you blind, S*********r!
Come on, stop crying.
It must be a mosquito bite.
Mosquitoes don't pick places
to bite.