Is everyone here? Get closer.
Here you go. Have a look.
- It's amazing. - Very nice.
- Wow.
- We can click as many pictures.
- Yes.
- We don't need anyone's help.
Well, what's your
daughter's education?
Our son is a graduate.
As you know, girls study
for the sake of a degree.
Therefore, I asked her
to take up...
...cooking classes after her MPhil.
She made these fritters.
Why don't you have some?
He's very choosy
about what he eats.
He doesn't like fried snacks.
- You please have it.
- Yes.
Well, I'll ask my daughter...
- ...to get some salad
for you all. Okay? - Okay.
You look so beautiful.
Mom, does he look anything like
how he looked in that photo?
He looks much better than that.
He's very tall
and well-dressed too.
He's a perfect match
for you, Shanu.
Mom, stop exaggerating.
Now don't say Shah Rukh Khan
himself is sitting in the hall.
What does he do
for a living?
Well, I just started working.
No problem. What matters
is that you're working.
- Having a job is very important.
- You're absolutely right.
Well, here comes my princess.
[Title Montage]
[Shanu] 'You're very funny
and very smart.'
'If you put little effort
you can top in every subject.'
'By the way, there is nothing
wrong in what Nand has done.'
It only means that he cares
for the girls in the class.
Yes, Nand?
[Shanu] 'So, what do
you want to do today?'
Ma'am, you say.
What do you want to do?
Sit properly first.
Okay, so...
Give me an example of your own...
...of a sentence in active voice...
...and then the same sentence
in passive voice.
Girls are loving me.
And I'm being loved by the girls.
Wow.
Well, that's correct.
And I'm impressed.
How dare you!
Get up.
Get up and get out!
Get out right now.
- Ma'am, I thought that we...
- Thought what?
What did you think?
That you can do anything
as I am being friendly!
Get out of here.
Bloody fool.
Ma'am, why don't you
want to do it with me?
What?
I mean, why don't
you want to...
You're doing it
with the entire city...
Aren't you ashamed, Nand?
Aren't you ashamed? You get
out of here right now. Get out!
I mean, Pappu, the cable guy
when you shifted here.
Manoj,
Rahul the engineering student.
- Professor Kaliya and many...
- Who are they, Nand?
Who are they?
Okay!
Don't you know them?
I am hearing these names
for the first time.
Get out of here. I don't
have time for this nonsense.
I don't want to see you again.
[Shanu] 'Don't you dare come back.'
'Who are they, Nand?
Who are they?'
'I am hearing these names
for the first time.'
'Get out of here. I don't
have time for this nonsense.'
'I don't want to see you again.'
'Don't you dare come back.'
As they say,
when time doesn't favour you...
...everything goes wrong.
Even Priyanka blocked my number.
I was done for.
Subject is acted upon.
Chirag, Akash.
Get up.
Akash, you go back to
your favourite place.
Get out.
[Shanu] 'Give that phone.
Put that phone here.'
Anybody else would
like to join him?
No, ma'am...
- Is this clear?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Any doubt?
- No, ma'am.
Okay, now. Who can tell me...
...what happens to the subject...
...when we change from active voice
to passive voice?
Anyone?
- Anyone?
- Put your hands down.
Put your hands down.
Don't try to be a hero!
Sleeping in class, everyone?
Priyanka.
What happens to the subject...
...when we change from active voice
to passive voice?
The subject...
...changes to the object.
Say it with confidence.
The subject changes to the object.
That's correct.
Sit down.
Okay, now the verb.
Please look at the verb
in the active voice.
The verb is...
[bell ringing]
Don't repeat it.
Stupid.
Ma'am.
Sorry, ma'am.
- Ma'am. Sorry, ma'am.
- Shut up.
Just shut up.
Fortunately for yourself you have
committed this stupidity in my house.
If you would have done
this same thing in class...
...I would have got you expelled.
Please count yourself very lucky
that you are still in this school...
...and not in jail.
Shameless.
[Nand] 'Why did you block
my number, Priyanka?'
Mister, hurry up please.
[Man] Yes, I'm getting.
Priyanka,
won't you talk to me now?
What has happened?
[Man] 'Nand, what do I give you?'
Give me anything worth 50 rupees.
So, Priyanka.
What have I done?
- Do you ever do anything?
- What do you mean?
What! Don't act innocent.
I know everything.
What is it that you know?
You have become so busy
since the time...
...you started taking tuitions
from Shanu ma'am.
I know what she is teaching you.
There is nothing as such,
Priyanka.
Is it? So, when are
you going to kiss me?
Do you want me to write an email(?)
Or should I ask my father
to come with a marriage proposal(?)
- Priyanka, listen to me.
- Move!
Don't touch me.
Am I an idiot to talk to you
after getting humiliated?
I don't want to see you hereafter.
S**********r,
you are my true friend.
He is just after my possessions(!)
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
What do you mean?
What will be fine?
This keeps happening...
...in Bollywood, Hollywood
and everywhere else.
Bro!
What I am going through
right now...
...doesn't happen in any film.
What, d******k!
That's what is called awkwardness.
Huh?
- The meeting after sex.
- Really?
Yes.
Didn’t you see that Priyanka
left without informing?
People smoke cigarettes
after sex...
...so that they can avoid
the 'awkward talk'
That's not true.
Forget it.
Touch his feet.
- Nand lost his virginity.
- The great Nand(!)
Enough...
Enough, Pushpa.
Happy anniversary, dear.
Happy wedding anniversary
to you too.
I just pray to Lord Ram...
...to keep us together forever.
May the Lord fulfil all your desires.
Don't you desire anything?
You are my desire.
Are you recording our video?
Tell us.
It would be a great deal if I could
click a photo in this useless phone.
Don't talk nonsense.
Click a good photo.
I want to post it
in the family group.
How can I click the photo...
...while you are standing 10 feet
away from each other?
Okay, we will get closer.
Mom, stand a bit closer.
Don't be shy.
- Come on, Pushpa.
- Yes.
Come.
- This is good.
- Is it any good?
- So, now...
- Shall we go?
- Yes, let's go.
- Give me two minutes.
- I'll spray some perfume and come.
- Pushpa.
How long are you going to see?
Give it to me.
We will do the same old thing,
Sushma.
First, we will go to Kanha Shyam...
...and have a dish
made of cottage cheese.
And we will have a paan
on our way back home.
He will buy me flowers.
That's all on our anniversary.
How is your studies going on?
Very good.
Are you going for tuitions?
How is that coming along?
Will you speak up?
Dad, that... Chemistry tuitions
are going great, Dad.
- What about English tuitions?
- Yes.
The one you take from Shanu ma'am.
How is it going?
You have lost it, Sushma.
A man gets flatulence,
not sexually aroused...
...after eating flatbread.
What?
Where is your father?
At Shanu ma'am's house.
Shanu ma'am's house.
Shanu ma'am.
Shanu ma'am?
Sushma, who is on duty
at that w***e's place?
Everybody took a day off!
You should have
at least informed me.
- Nand.
- Yes.
Go and check if your father
took the scooter or not.
- Yes.
- Get up, go and check.
Mom, I heard the sound of
the scooter when dad left.
So, it's quite obvious.
To hell with that w****e!
Whose family is she
going to ruin today!
[Pushpa] 'I am not
a woman of my words...'
'...if I don't catch her
red-handed today.'
What has happened?
- Get a glass of water.
- Water.
No need. It's okay.
What has happened?
Tell me.
- Do one thing, dear.
- Yes.
Go. Go to Shanu ma'am's house.
- Shanu ma'am?
- Yes.
And if you...
If you find your father's scooter
there, just barge inside the house.
Why is there a question mark
on your face?
Just go!
Hurry up.
Ma'am, Nand is an idiot.
As I got to know that he
misbehaved with you...
...I rushed here.
Ma'am, it's a request.
Give tuitions to my Nand.
I will even come and sit next to him
if you say so.
Finger on my lip.
You will have
to keep your lips open, sir.
If you won't,
then I will have to do it.
- Dad.
- What are you doing here?
Mom sent me here.
Yes, I am just going home.
- Okay, listen.
- Yes.
I spoke to your Shanu ma'am.
She said that she won't
start the tuitions...
...unless you go and apologise.
Let me go and
apologise right away.
No.
She is not keeping well.
Come in the morning tomorrow
to apologise.
Come on.
Come.
- Dad, it is automatic.
- I know.
- I said, I know.
Do you want me to whack you?
Hop on!
I am going to my maternal home.
Handle everything on your own.
Nothing has happened.
- Nothing has happened?
- Yes. Nothing has happened.
Nothing has happened!
This is what I wanted to hear!
Now, start defending that w***e.
What do I do?
Nothing has happened!
[Tyagi] 'Nothing has happened.'
That was a slap on my feelings
and not my face.
I decided that I have to turn
Shanu ma'am's life a living hell.
Yes, Bhalla.
Tell me.
Where are you?
No. Don't ring the bell.
Go back.
Get on the scooter
and go to school.
I am going to Delhi
to get some notes.
D******d, how will I pack
an ice pop?
Hang up!
Mom, I won't be able to come now.
Are you blind, S**********r?
Sorry, ma'am.
Sorry.
Yes, ticket.
One minute, Mom.
Hold on.
- Where do you want to go?
- Give me a ticket for Moradabad.
Ticket.
I will throw you out of the bus
in the middle of the highway.
Where do you want to go?
I want to go where
that man is going.
Why are you after that gentleman?
No... He isn't a gentleman.
Come closer.
- His wife...
- Yes.
- She is my sis...
She is my distant relative. - Okay.
She has asked me to do this.
The thing is that this gentleman...
...is going to meet his girlfriend
making an excuse of work.
- What?
- Yes.
Now, I need to find out
where he is going.
And then I will inform his wife.
Okay.
Give me 50 rupees.
He is going to Moradabad.
[phone ringing]
Yes.
Yes, Priyanka.
Nand.
Where are you?
You didn't come for tuitions.
I had come to Delhi
for some work.
Delhi?
Okay.
Are you done with your work?
No. No, that...
- I was thinking that...
- You will keep thinking forever.
Do something if you want to
or else forget it.
[Priyanka] 'Nand.
Are you listening to me?'
Okay, Priyanka. Thanks.
[Nand] 'Okay, bye.
I'll see you tomorrow.'
Hey, you are...
Yes, sir.
I'm Shanu ma'am's student.
Yes.
- How is your tuition going on?
- Very good, sir.
So, sir... Is everything alright?
Yes. Everything is good.
How is Shanu ma'am?
Shanu ma'am.
How is she?
You should be knowing that.
I mean, I stay out
for work mostly.
And Shanu ma'am spends
most of the time in school.
So, you should be knowing.
Sir, as you stay out most
of the times for work.
So, Shanu ma'am might get bored
staying alone?
No. She has a hobby
of reading.
So she keeps herself busy
by reading.
What happened?
- You are so naive, sir.
- Why?
Sir, while you are busy
selling mobile phones
your wife is inserting
new sim cards daily(!)
Yes, sir.
I'm telling you the truth.
Men are going to your house...
...and women are spying
outside your house.
Sir, it's not too late.
You should control your wife or else...
I spoke too much.
Now, I am going to get beaten up.
B***h!
She has come here too!
She?
Who is she, sir?
She made us leave one city.
- But she didn't leave my Shanu.
- Who, sir?
The woman who you saw
with men is not my Shanu.
- Who is she then, sir?
- She's a ghost.
A witch.
She is a prostitute from Lucknow.
Her name is Rasbhari.
Her spirit.
My Shanu is not at fault.
That b***h Rasbhari keeps doing
what she wants to.
My Shanu doesn't even know.
F**k!
I was jerking off
to a witch till now!
[Theme Music Playing]