NARRATOR 1: In the future,
a computer program called Skynet...
...will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time,
taking human form...
...to terminate John Connor,
the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor,
John's mother, teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogrammed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle and a
commanding officer with the Resistance.
Together, they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow starts today.
NARRATOR 2: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
Come with me if you wanna live.
So you've been sitting in the same
exact spot since you bailed out on English.
- And your name is?
- It's Riley.
Never brought a girl home before?
- No.
- We can move in today.
Soon as I figure out what to do
with all this.
- We'll take all of it.
JOHN: Cromartie killed 20 FBI guys.
He's here for me.
- I'm looking for the Connors.
- Sarah Connor?
Mr. Dixon wanted to marry
Sarah Connor before you.
So take your wife.
Get as far away from here as you can.
- Forget me, forget John, just go.
- It's not safe here anymore.
CHARLIE: We always thought
we'd raise kids in this house.
- You just can't plan for anything now.
ELLISON: For the road.
[ENGINE TURNS OFF]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[DOG BARKING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[EXHALES]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Did you get me that soda, babe?
Charlie!
- Michelle!
MICHELLE: Charlie!
Michelle! Michelle!
Michelle!
MICHELLE:
Charlie!
CHARLIE:
Michelle!
[PANTING]
Michelle.
I've only been wanting a TV in here
for like a hundred years.
Maybe two hundred.
- That long, huh?
- Well, a while.
The ex-baby daddy
wouldn't have one in the bedroom.
Lookit where that got me. Well, that,
six beers and the rhythm method.
Ow, heh.
- Too much information?
- Yeah, a bit.
Do I need to call the cable guy?
I feel like I'm not even wired in here.
[TV CLICKS ON]
You are now.
But I wouldn't mention it to anybody,
especially the cable guy.
Clever boy.
[WHIMPERS]
ACTOR [ON TV]: Beast Wizard,
the kingdom of Thule will never be yours.
Now, now, Seth,
that's no way to treat your brother.
Beast Wizard 7,
the low-budget film...
...nobody saw when it was released
direct to video two years ago...
...has earned $ 6 million
and newfound star status...
...when its star, George Laszlo...
...inexplicably killed 20 members
of an FBI hostage rescue team...
...in a shootout at his Reseda apartment.
The massacre, you may recall,
also took the actor's life.
A friend of mine from culinary school
did craft services on that movie.
She liked the guy. He ate with the crew.
[KAC Y SIGHS]
This town can screw you up.
What are you doing?
This is the absolute center of the house.
Excellent. Good work.
The house is moving.
- What?
- Moving.
The east-by-southeast
section of the house is moving.
- Really, where's it going?
- Down.
At a rate of 0.93 millimeters per year.
And what?
Does that affect the security system?
Or sightlines for the night scope?
How does this affect the safety
of one John Connor?
It doesn't. But next summer
we're going to have to repaint.
- You get Kacy's TV set up?
- Yep.
I hope you didn't steal cable for her.
Nobody pregnant should watch
network television. It's bad for the baby.
- You don't know anything about babies.
- I know they grow up.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hi.
Eighteen November? Johnny?
That's the code, right? John?
Yeah, where are you?
We... We're on our way out of town.
We're leaving.
- Why?
- I just...
Can you? Can you hang on a second,
please, John?
[SNIFFLES]
[SIGHS]
[CRIES]
Okay, I'm, ahem... I'm back. Just...
Just listen, okay?
CHARLIE:
I just need to say goodbye to your mom.
I didn't get a chance to say goodbye, and
she wouldn't give me her phone number.
I was just hoping maybe you could...
You know, maybe you could
have her give me a call?
Hang on.
It's for you.
- Hello?
- Sarah?
He took my wife.
What do you want me to say, Charlie?
Help. Help me, Sarah, please.
We were just leaving town,
and he just... He just took her.
I mean, with John standing right here,
what am I supposed to say?
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't... I didn't know who else to call.
Please. Please just help me, Sarah.
You shouldn't have called here, Charlie.
You were right to leave.
I don't wanna know where you are
in case I need you.
I'm not gonna need you.
It's better for you if I can't find you.
You understand?
Wait, hold on a second. Are you?
Are you asking me where I am?
Yes, I am.
I'm just at some fruit stand.
It's somewhere off the 14...
...just south of the California City turnoff.
I think.
Please, I really need your help, Sarah.
Stay safe, Charlie.
I told you not to give him your number.
CAMERON:
There's something alive up there.
Is it something that can hurt us?
It's a bird. I'll kill it before it flies away.
No.
- Maybe later?
- Maybe never.
John's gonna buy computers today.
Go with him.
Do not let him out of your sight.
Is there anything I need to know?
You need to know
not to let him out of your sight.
And don't touch that bird.
Cromartie's got Charlie Dixon's wife.
Where's John?
I sent him to get the new computers.
He's with Cameron. They don't know.
Well, where are you going?
You know where I'm going.
Come if you want.
- You can't go.
- And yet I am.
It's a ploy to get John. It's a trap.
I know that.
You don't see John here, do you?
- It's the absolute wrong thing to do.
- It wouldn't be the first time.
[ENGINE STARTS]
- Just wait, all right? Just wait.
SARAH: Hurry up.
[STRETCHING]
[RIPPING]
MICHELLE:
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa, Cameron.
Cameron, let me help you with that.
- I didn't need any help.
- Yeah, you did.
Right.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Hi.
- I'm bored. Wanna hang out?
Oh, I forgot. Eighteen November.
Heh. Where are you?
Promenade. The magazine stand
in front of the coffee bar.
Captivated by the Lohan.
I could be there in like 15 minutes,
you know?
The world could end in 15 minutes.
- I'm gonna vote "I doubt it."
- You never know. Lot of Lohan.
Just stay there, okay?
Hey. Can you drop me off?
Was that Riley?
That's none of your business.
Your mother told me
to keep an eye on you.
That doesn't mean
you have to go everywhere I do.
Yes, it does.
Just because my mother said it
doesn't make it so.
I'm not a child. I can go to the store,
or see a friend...
...or do whatever else people like me do.
There are no other people like you.
Just drop me off.
[SIGHS]
I had heard the trees in this forest
grew lovely fruit.
Yet truly I had no idea.
[LAUGHS]
[TIGER GROWLS]
I must warn you, my lady,
my striped friend is an excellent climber.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Long have I journeyed through forest...
Hello.
WEAVER: Agent James Ellison, please.
- Speaking.
My name is Catherine Weaver,
Mr. Ellison.
I'd like to talk to you
about an opportunity.
- I'm not interested in any opportunities.
- A job opportunity, Agent Ellison.
I presume you won't be returning to the
FBI once your leave of absence is over.
- How'd you get my number?
- I'll tell you about it at lunch.
Shall we say 1:00? My assistant
will give you the information.
No. I don't know who you are.
- And I'm very busy.
- You're not busy.
Come to lunch. We'll talk about who,
or what, actually killed your colleagues.
[THUD]
[PANTING]
[WHISPERING]
Come on, come on.
- Where would he take her?
- I don't know.
- Then how are we gonna find her?
- You don't know?
- No.
That thing could be watching us
right now. We need to go.
- What we need to do is find my wife.
- She won't tell you the truth, but I will.
That thing took your wife to get to John.
You think it gives a damn about her?
Your wife's dead.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
It's her. Hmm?
Make sure it's really her.
They can imitate our voices.
You need to be sure.
Baby?
Charlie. Charlie.
- Honey, are you okay? Are you hurt?
- No.
Is he there with you?
MICHELLE:
Yeah. He's in the next room.
I can hear him.
- Where are you?
- Outside Mojave.
In an abandoned building about
four, five miles off the highway.
- The 14?
- Yeah.
There's a billboard for...
...I don't know, a law firm.
A dirt road runs in front of it. It goes...
- Make sure it's her.
- It's her.
You think I don't know my own wife?
[MICHELLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
O VER PHONE]
Charlie.
Make sure.
- Charlie?
- Baby, I need you to pay attention, okay?
The first time you and I
ever made love, where was it?
- What?
- Just answer the question, please.
First time that we made love,
where was it?
The beach?
Which beach?
[CRYING]
Charlie, I don't know what and where...
[STAMMERING]
Malibu, Paradise Cove.
Okay, and what happened
at dinner that night?
What do you mean, Charlie?
What do you mean? I don't know.
Answer the question.
What happened at dinner?
Oh, God, the magician took my watch?
[SIGHS]
I love you, baby, all right? Just...
We're gonna come get you, just please...
Please hang tight.
[THUD]
CHARLIE:
Michelle?
[SIGHS]
Please.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you? No, don't tape
my mouth. I won't scream.
I swear I won't scream. I won't scream.
[MUFFLED SOBBING]
In 1897, James Atkinson
invented the mousetrap.
The spring slammed shut
in 38 thousandths of a second.
It is a record that has never been beaten.
It is hard to build a better one.
You know what really creeps me out
about these magazines?
They all just want to convert you
into their cult.
It's, like, all in the titles.
It's Us and People and OK!
You know, some of us people
aren't okay.
Yeah, some of us are...
...Popular Mechanics.
Exactly. And some of us
are Guns & Ammo.
Yeah, you're more Yarn Collector.
[CHUCKLES]
You're the Yarn Collector, yarn collector.
So you coming back to school?
No. No, I don't think so.
My mom wants to home-school me
for a while.
Hmm. Sounds like a good time
will be had by all.
What, you'll miss me?
[CHUCKLES]
Ease up, Cat Fancy.
I don't even know your top-10 brands
of scratching post.
Cat Fancy.
Dude, your sister.
MAN: Ha-ha-ha.
- We should go. Now.
Wait, how do we get inside here?
Getting inside is not the problem.
Try to hit something metal.
Wait.
[MICHELLE WHIMPERING]
CHARLIE: Hey.
SARAH: Don't touch her.
CHARLIE:
Hey.
Derek.
[SCOFFS]
They never let you have a good day,
do they?
I'm gonna take the tape off.
Don't move.
Do not move.
Do you understand? Not one inch.
- Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
CHARLIE: Shh.
SARAH:
Hey, Michelle. Listen to me.
You're sitting on a bomb.
If you move, it will go off.
Baby, hey. We're gonna get you
out of this chair, okay?
And then we're all gonna get out of here.
But just, please,
you have to listen to her. Please.
Where is he?
If I'm not back in 15 minutes,
leave without me.
[SOBBING]
Just get me out. Get me out of here.
- Charlie.
- Michelle. Michelle, please.
MICHELLE:
Just get me out. Get me out of here.
Michelle, baby. Hey, baby. Shh.
I'm trying, Charlie. I'm trying.
But the more I sit here,
the more I wanna stand up.
- My legs are on fire.
- It's the adrenaline.
I know it's the adrenaline.
[SOBBING]
I just have to get up. They're on fire.
- It's like they're full of ants.
- Lf you move, you will die.
We all will.
[SIGHS]
Baby, look at me. Hey.
It's all gonna be all right, I promise.
No, Charlie.
It's never gonna be okay. Never.
[SIGHS]
There's a bag in the truck.
Red handles. I'm gonna need it, Charlie.
Charlie.
[DOOR OPENS]
What are you doing here?
I know he brought you,
but you didn't have to come.
- Yes, I did.
- For Charlie?
I just did.
Frankly, I thought it'd be easier.
I thought you'd be dead.
CHARLIE:
Hey.
He killed the car.
We're gonna have to walk out of here.
What?
That doesn't make any sense.
He messes with the car and not us.
We're human. We're not that hard to kill.
Wait, wait, wait. Sarah.
[GASPS]
- Molding clay. Son of a bitch.
- Oh!
Cut her free.
It was a fake?
This whole thing was a fake?
He wants John. He doesn't have to kill us
if we're stuck here with no way back.
I should've known
when you weren't dead.
[EXHALES]
[LINE RINGING]
John. Eighteen November.
Where are you?
JOHN [O VER PHONE]:
Twenty-0-7. The Promenade.
SARAH: Is Cameron with you?
- Uh... Yeah, why?
I need you to stay out.
Don't go home. Don't go to Kacy's.
SARAH [DISTORTED VOICE]:
And don't go to Riley's.
JOHN [DISTORTED VOICE]:
Mind telling me what's going on?
SARAH:
Stay out until you hear from me.
JOHN:
Why? What's happening?
SARAH:
I mean it, John.
Don't go any place familiar.
[VOICE NORMALIZES]
Find a place to hide until I call you.
JOHN:
Yeah, okay.
Just promise me, John.
So, what do you think?
- John.
- Yeah, all right, I promise.
You can do better than that,
Cat Fancy.
Stay with Cameron.
Don't call me. I'll call you.
Okay, fine.
Well?
That's... Yeah, it's awesome.
- That was your weird sister, right?
- No. It was my weird mother.
[BEEPING]
[LINE RINGING]
[RINGING]
Run! It's a bomb! Get out! Go, go, go!
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[COUGHING]
SARAH:
Is everyone good? Everyone good?
DEREK: Sarah?
- I'm good.
- Everyone good?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm okay.
[DEREK COUGHS]
The cell tower out back, he blew it.
After he tapped your call to John.
He has John's number and the code.
That won't work now.
- Ow!
CHARLIE: Oh, baby, baby. Hey, hey.
Charlie, move.
CHARLIE: You okay? Good?
- Yeah.
- I gotcha. Okay?
MICHELLE:
Oh.
[DIALING]
[LINE RINGING]
- Mom.
SARAH'S VOICE: Eighteen November.
Twenty-0-7.
[IN SARAH'S VOICE]
Change of plans, John.
- How far are you from the pier?
- The pier? A few blocks. I don't know.
Wait for me there.
And turn off your phone.
- What is going on? Where are you?
- Don't worry about me, John.
Just get to the pier.
[PHONE BEEPS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
JOHN:
I'm sorry. I have to go.
- I thought we were going to the movies.
- I have to meet my mom at the pier.
- Seriously?
- Riley, I...
Look, John, I'm not afraid of your mother.
Not like you are.
I have to go. I'll call you.
Don't forget the secret code.
DEREK:
Come on.
SARAH: I figure it's five miles to the
highway if we head due west.
Across the desert.
We need a car.
We need to get to John.
Oh, God.
SARAH:
Charlie?
- How bad is it?
- I can't tell.
I can't tell.
If the shrapnel nicked an artery...
...she could be bleeding out inside.
I don't know.
SARAH: We have to go.
- Go? Go how?
On foot.
No way, Sarah. Uh-uh.
I'm not moving her,
and I'm not making her walk.
I'll send someone back for you
as soon as I can.
Huh?
I can walk.
No one has to wait on me.
So...
...you know who I am.
You know what happened.
George Laszlo was the shooter.
George Laszlo is dead.
It's all in the report.
And yet here you are.
Five years ago, a small commuter jet
went down in the eastern Sierras...
...on its way from Sacramento
to Portland.
My brother was on the NTSB team
that investigated the accident.
He found these and brought them to me.
My late husband and I have spent
three years and $20 million...
...trying to reverse-engineer
this technology.
We've not been successful yet.
Red Valley, New Mexico.
Eight years ago.
Twenty-two witnesses report seeing
a man with some kind of robot leg...
...try to kill a boy
later identified as John Connor.
- John Connor?
- Son of Sarah Connor.
It was your case.
She believed robots were after her son.
I know what she believed,
Ms. Weaver.
You know what really killed those agents.
You did not even pretend to ask me...
...what those were.
What do you want from me?
I want what you want, Mr. Ellison.
I want answers.
But more than that...
...I want you to help me find another one.
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Where's John?
SARAH:
Hey!
[GRO ANING]
Get out.
Out.
[SIGHS]
Man.
[MICHELLE SOBBING]
MICHELLE:
Charlie.
[MICHELLE CONTINUES GRO ANING]
[YELLING]
Sarah, slow down.
She's bleeding out here.
I need to get pressure on this. Sarah.
Damn you, Charlie,
I told you to stay away.
Oh, God.
Sarah, you've gotta stop now. Please.
You should have stayed away.
I'm here now. She's here now.
You've got to stop now.
[PANTING]
[GASPING, SOBBING]
It's gonna be okay. It's okay.
[CAPTAIN AHAB'S
"MUSIC MAKES ME" PLAYING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
Little help?
- I don't swim.
- Yeah, I just figured that out.
John?
Mom, I'm good. Let's go.
[CRYING]
[CHARLIE EXHALES]
[SNIFFLING]
PASTOR:
Do not lose heart.
Though outwardly we are wasting away...
...inwardly we are being renewed
day by day.
For our light and momentary troubles...
...are achieving for us an eternal glory
that far outweighs them all.
We know that if the earthly tent
we live in is destroyed...
...we have a building from God...
...a house not made with hands,
eternal in the heavens.
For God has given us the spirit
as a guarantee.
And as long as we are at home
in the body...
...we are away from the Lord.
We walk by faith, not by sight.
And so fix our eyes not on what is seen...
...but what is unseen.
For what is seen is temporary...
...what is unseen...
...eternal.
[ENGLISH SDH]