Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles...
Been drinking?
So what are you in for? I'm Jody.
What did you do-- did you hurt me?
Is there a problem?
No, I'm her brother,
John Baum.
Whatever you say in here is confidential.
The only exception is if you were planning
to harm someone, I would have to report that.
-Jesse.
-Hi, baby.
Are you AWOL?
Jess, did you run?
I need a place to rest.
James Ellison?
Why?
Aren't you on the same side?
Skynet does not believe in you like I do.
Believe?
What do you believe?
You will lead me to the Connors.
Stay there.
There's no one here.
Where the hell are you?
Where the hell am I supposed to be?
We just got robbed.
You were what?
Diamonds, cash, credit cards, IDs.
They cleaned us out.
Machine?
My leather jacket's gone.
So is most of the food.
Human.
If those IDs fall into the wrong hands...
Listen, head downtown.
I'll call you with an exact
location in half an hour.
Who was that?
Real life calling.
You don't always have to answer.
I tried it ignoring it all last time around
and the whole freaking town blew up.
You're a funny man.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the first thing
people say who know me.
Funny Derek.
What's wrong with the system?
Why didn't it beep
or do whatever the hell you set it up to do?
John.
Riley climbed out John's window.
The alarm would
had to have been turned off for her to do that.
Thanks.
You gave her the code?
We were up late watching TV.
She was supposed to reset it.
And somehow your master plan went awry.
Mom-- John, our IDs are out there.
Our names, our faces.
Fake addresses, fake names.
Nothing can be traced to this house.
No? What if the police find who did this?
Where do you think that trail leads to?
If our IDs made it into the system
linked to this address--
Canada.
We should move to Canada.
Saw your door was open.
I thought I'd bring you guys some--
Oh, my god, what happened?
I'll go call Trevor.
No, John's been having some trouble
with some kids at school.
Seriously? Yeah.
You know how stupid kids can be.
Anyway, you'll know soon enough.
We're just on our way to see their parents.
All right, well, if you change your mind--
I'll call you.
What am I supposed to do?
I'd start with a broom.
Come on, Rita.
Look, I got the county breathing down my neck.
We can't have a backlog like this.
I'll get it done.
Today.
I needed it two weeks ago.
It's my son.
He took off this morning with the neighbor's car
and my credit cards.
We'll call you right away
if he attempts a charge, Miss Baum.
Is this a good number to reach you?
Yes, thank you.
If you knew what was going on with the girl,
why didn't you say something?
To you?
To me, to him, to somebody.
I've always made my position
on security very clear.
No one likes a nag.
I'm looking for this girl.
You see these people, sir?
These people are real.
These are the real people,
and they were all here before you.
I'm her uncle.
And I'm Angelina Jolie.
Get to the back of the line.
I know that chick.
So what do you want her for?
She owe you money?
I'm her uncle.
You're not her uncle. You're a cop.
I'm not a cop.
You gonna hurt her?
Yes.
What about her brother, you gonna hurt him too?
Her brother?
Yeah.
John Baum or whatever.
John Baum?
Another prize.
Is that him?
Yeah, that's him.
Let's take a ride.
Who is it?
Los Angeles police department.
Hold on.
I'm just trying to catch up
on last night's game.
You know who won?
Steelers, Mr. Ellison.
Could you open the door please?
Yeah.
You James Ellison?
Mr. Ellison, I'm placing you under arrest
for the murder of Peter Meyers.
What?
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
one will be appointed to you.
Do you understand these rights
as I've read them to you, sir?
Yeah, I know my rights.
I just don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
Please put your hands against the wall, sir.
Now, Mr. Ellison.
Come on, Moishe, open up.
Who are they?
New customers.
Everything we do, without exception,
can be seen many ways in the eyes of god,
or nature, or whatever you want to call it.
Someone came into your home.
Someone took things that were rightfully yours.
The Torah says, "lo tikom ve'lo titor."
No revenge,
no retribution.
On the other hand,
it also says, "ayan tachat ayn."
An eye for an eye.
And then, of course, we have the story
of the brothers of Nablus--
We came here looking for our diamonds.
Can you help us or not?
I wish I could.
But lately,
business is dry as a bone.
I called four other fences.
They said you were the busiest
man on the block this week.
Well, nothing you'd be interested in.
Show us.
Okay.
These...
I bought in the last two days.
All from legitimate sources.
This one's ours.
Young lady, even if those were your diamonds--
And they're not--
There's no way you could tell
that with the naked eye.
We have machines for that.
So are these.
We don't want any trouble.
Tell us where you got 'em and we're gone.
You think I can put a face
to every diamond in this stack?
Just a face from the last 24 hours.
Moishe,
please.
All right.
It's so early in the week for trouble.
But it's not for you. It's for Jesse.
His name's Ostrowski. Walter Ostrowski.
Where do we find him?
He works out of Toluca Lake,
or so he says.
I just buy the stones.
And this Ostrowski,
you're sure he's the guy who sold you these?
I shall not lie.
If you're so into god, what are you doing here?
Hashem has a plan for us all.
For me, diamonds.
Who's Jesse?
He came back with me.
He handled the diamonds.
One of them killed him.
Do you want some gum?
No.
You sure?
It's cinnamon.
Would it kill you to try and make
a little conversation?
No, it wouldn't kill me.
Funny.
You're funny.
In your own sort of cop way.
I'm not a cop.
You're not a cop.
You're not an uncle.
You're just some guy who wants to kick the crap
out of little miss bitch and her brother.
Just some guy.
But why?
She try to kill you too?
Yes.
Well, this is gonna be fun.
I can't believe they stole your food.
Freaking amateurs, man.
I know, right?
What do you think they're gonna do
with two-week old maple turkey?
Bet your mom freaked out, huh?
Yeah, on me.
On you? Why on you?
The alarm code.
Did I forget?
Yeah, you did.
I didn't actually see it happen.
Like, I wasn't here, but I'm pretty sure this--
Yeah, I'm positive.
This is where they busted her.
I heard the cops talking about it
when they brought her in.
You are so buying me these pink and whites,
and that is all there is to it.
Have you seen this girl?
I'm looking for this girl.
I'm so sorry, John.
I can't believe I did that.
Don't worry about it.
It wouldn't have stopped a break-in.
Might have stopped the picnic, but--
So I know you want to find them and everything,
but this is getting a little shady.
Does she hate me now?
Don't sweat it. It's a long list.
You're not gonna get what you want this way.
You should try being warmer to people.
They might be more open,
you know, to talk to you.
I love this stuff.
That's my bad.
That's the guy.
That's definitely the guy.
What am I doing here, detective?
You've been on my side of the table.
You know how this works.
I ask a question, you answer it.
Why am I being questioned?
You tell me.
Who's Peter Meyers?
I don't know Peter Meyers.
You killed him.
Killed him?
No.
Yes. I've got a witness.
Saw the murder.
Recognized you from the news a few weeks ago.
Recognized me?
From the news?
The news? 20 of your guys dead...
You the sole survivor.
By now you're drowning in guilt, I'm guessing.
Throw yourself an anchor.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm talking about surviving, Mr. Ellison.
I'm talking about the everyday,
walk around pain of surviving
when others have not.
I wanna talk to my lawyer.
Okay.
Sure.
Oh.
I meant to ask you.
Why did you steal his clothes?
What?
Meyers' clothes.
You were naked when you killed him.
I told you, it wasn't me.
Smart.
Your alibi isn't exactly iron-clad, Jim.
Unless, of course, you got a twin brother
I don't know about.
You got a twin brother I don't know about?
Dr. Ostrowski's in with patients all afternoon.
Would you like to make an appointment?
We'll just take a second.
Excuse me!
Walter Ostrowski?
Uh, yes.
I think you have something that belongs to us.
Uh, do I know you?
No, but we have a friend in common,
someone in the diamond district.
Moishe.
Mm-hmm.
Um, why don't we, um,
talk in my office.
It's...
just across the hall.
Please, please, don't kill me.
-Where's our stuff?
-What stuff?
Passports, IDs, credit cards.
Leather jacket.
Everything you stole from our house.
Your house? I don't--
Okay, okay, okay.
Tell Moishe I'll pay him.
I'll give you the money today.
It's upstairs in my office.
Pay Moishe for what?
Everything I owe him.
Please.
Just don't kill me.
-Let him go.
-Why?
He's not the guy who robbed us.
And go get Moishe's money.
That's why we're here,
running a collections agency for your fence?
Why we're here is because
our security system didn't work.
that boy behaves less like John Connor
and more like John Baum every day.
That boy, my son,
has been through more than you'll ever know.
Right back at you.
My friends.
Is this what you're looking for?
You do something for me, I do something for you.
It's business.
This is business.
Please, I just buy the stones.
Who sold you our diamonds?
Okay, okay, his name is Tristan Dewitt.
He lives in Reseda.
Not good enough.
It's true. I swear!
He's a friend of my cousin's, a punk.
That's all I know.
You killed Iiko.
Not yet.
You're never gonna find them like this.
Do you even know how many people
live in L.A. county?
An employee at the grocery store
saw them shopping there on
more than one occasion.
It's highly likely they live
within a one-mile radius.
I'm looking for this girl.
This is stupid.
Just take me back to the halfway house.
Did you hear me?
I am done hanging out with a creepy stalker.
I don't even know your name.
I just came with you because I wanted
to get back at that bitch.
And I thought you were kind of cute.
But you know what? You're not cute.
You're freakin' silence of the lambs.
This is kidnapping. You know that, right?
I could have you arrested.
What are you doing? Why are we stopping?
Freak!
You're blocking the sun.
Had an interesting morning
with our friend Moishe.
He's dropping your name
pretty freely in front of people
who don't need to be hearing your name.
Well, he's your fence.
He likes you better.
I'll have a talk with him.
Help me out, will you?
How long are you planning on keeping this up?
What?
You know what, all this.
Well, I'm certainly gonna try
to get through today without
you spoiling it for me.
The sun sets at 5:47.
I'm not missing that sucker.
I'm not missing one of those again.
I'm looking for this girl.
Why are you looking for her?
Has she done something?
She's my niece.
You--you look really familiar.
Common face.
Have you seen my niece?
I haven't. I'm sorry.
The house next door, it's on the market.
You're listed as the contact.
That house has been rented.
Thank you for your time.
Wow, you guy really know how to party.
My mom's not much of a cook.
Uh, what about Cameron?
She's not really into food.
You gonna get that?
No, if they need me, they'll call my cell.
Oh, right, because you're so important.
Hello, Baum residence.
Yeah, just a sec.
Here's John.
It's your neighbor.
Thanks.
Yeah, hey, Kacy. What's up?
Hey, John.
I don't mean to bother you,
but there was a guy here
looking for your sister.
When?
Just now.
And I did not get a good vibe from him at all.
Something was just off, you know?
What's the matter, John?
What's wrong?
Out. We gotta get out now.
Why? Who's there?
No, it's okay, I'll get rid of him.
No, now. I'll get rid of him.
Riley.
I'm looking for this girl.
She's my niece.
Um, sorry, I don't know her.
Wish I could be more help.
Good luck finding her.
How do you like your new house?
It's really nice, I love it.
Excuse me, what do you think you're doing?
Hello, you can't just come into people's homes.
Hello, are you listening to me?
What is wrong with you?
You're not in these photographs.
Maybe because I was the one taking them.
Look, if you don't leave,
I'm calling the police.
Thank you for your time.
We were too supportive.
That was the problem in a nutshell.
Your son says he wants to be a filmmaker.
You tell him, "son, movies are great.
"I love going to see them.
"but that's pie in the sky.
You need a salary job."
Thank you for not going to
the police about this.
We just want our things back.
"come live at home,"
I told him.
"until you can get on your feet."
And every time I bring up the idea
of him getting a salary job,
he's got this project to work on,
or that short film he's producing.
He's had his troubles,
but he's a good boy.
He's not a boy, donna.
He's a 34-year-old man.
He lives with us, working in a video store,
robbing people's homes.
Video store?
Saturn Video on, uh, La Brea.
And who knows if that's true
when every other word out of his mouth is a lie.
Does your son have any friends
who might know where he is?
Anyone at the video store?
Dave.
Another boy wonder.
This is a very curious turn
of events, Mr. Ellison.
I'm innocent.
There's an eyewitness.
It wasn't me.
The witness is quite sure.
As I would be
if I had seen what he'd seen.
Is there something you want to tell me, James?
Something only I would believe?
Not here.
I'll be in touch.
Miss Weaver.
Thank you for believing me.
What good is faith if we don't use it?
Where are we going?
Nowhere.
Anywhere.
That guy isn't really Cameron's uncle, is he?
Because then he'd be your uncle.
He's nobody's uncle.
Then why is he after Cameron?
Is she a criminal or something?
No, he is, all right?
Well, what if he comes back?
That's not how-- that's not how he works.
John, I don't understand.
Look, that guy is really dangerous.
That's all you need to know. Really dangerous.
Well, I got rid of him, didn't I?
I stared him down, and off he went.
You got lucky.
Oh, ease up, squinchie.
"Lucky" is my middle name.
Lucky Riley Dawson.
In that sentence, "lucky" was your first name.
Whatever. stickler.
Admit it,
I was a brave, spooky ninja.
It was totally badass.
Say it! Just say it.
It was badass.
I know!
Fool's errands
and fathers of Nablus.
It's been a great day.
Brothers. What?
Brothers of Nablus.
Genesis. Chapter 34.
You memorized the bible?
Jacob's daughter Dinah
is raped by Shechem, prince of Nablus.
He falls in love with her.
Shechem's father comes to Jacob
and strikes a bargain to allow
his son to marry Dinah.
That's brave of him.
Jacob says yes, on the condition
that all the men in Shechem's town
be circumcised.
And everybody gets what they want.
Three days later, while Shechem's men
were still in pain from the circumcision,
Dinah's brothers rode into
the city and killed them all.
That's your kind of story.
Yes.
My kind of story.
Hello.
-Miss Baum?
-Yeah.
This is Dan Deffenbaugh calling to let you know
somebody just attempted a charge with your card.
Where?
At a bowling alley in Van Nuys.
Alien Lanes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I just have a few more questions,
then we'll get you out of here.
So you say Mr. Ellison
was completely nude when he killed Meyers.
I already told you that.
And that he killed him with his bare hands?
Didn't use a weapon?
He strangled him.
Did Meyers fight back?
A little, but the other guy was too strong.
How so?
Snapped his neck like it was nothing.
A toothpick.
Where was Mr. Ellison before
he killed Mr. Meyers?
Out on the road.
The road.
The road, the street, asphalt.
Anything unusual about the street?
Who cares about the street?
Are you lying about the street?
It was like, uh--
it was like a crater.
A pothole.
No.
It was like a complete dent in the road.
So Mr. Ellison just appeared
out of thin air?
There was a light.
What kind of a light?
Bluish purple.
It made, like, a cracking sound.
Like lightning.
So Mr. Ellison
emerged from this... energy bubble.
I never said anything about a bubble.
But there s a bubble, correct?
So to be clear,
you saw Mr. Ellison...
materialize out of this energy bubble,
completely nude,
walk to Peter Meyers, snap his neck,
steal his clothes, and then disappear.
I know what I saw.
Thank you for your assistance.
Nice.
Okay, so it's 1863
and Abraham Lincoln is on
the train to Gettysburg.
Then the train breaks down.
Some small Pennsylvania town.
So he's got to stay there overnight.
The only problem...
Town's overrun with zombies.
Shew!
Ha ha.
We shoot it on location in Gettysburg,
35 millimeter.
Dude, with what money?
What money?
Do you know how much we made
just off these right here?
Put it down.
That bag you're holding, it's mine.
Uh, not anymore it isn't.
This place is closed, ladies.
Unless you want to get arrested for trespassing,
I suggest you get the hell out.
My jacket, give it to me.
Come and get it.
Come and give it to me.
And the bag.
There's a credit card missing.
We used it on the arcades. We'll pay you back.
Where's the other guy?
What other guy?
Stay here.
They knew where we live.
No!
You know those guys out there?
Were you with them when they robbed the house?
You were never there.
You were never here. You never saw me.
You don't know what happened here.
Understand?
If you say anything to anybody
about what happened here,
I'll hunt you down.
I'll kill you.
Now you wait five minutes, then you run.
Understood?
Clear?
Yeah, clear.
You're free to go.
What?
The witness is a nutjob.
The judge kicked his statement in five minutes.
We'll have you out of here in an hour.
Sorry you had to go through all this.
That's it?
You're a smart guy, Jim.
Take "yes" for an answer.
Good luck out there.
You said you were gonna have a talk with him.
I did.
It was short.
What were you gonna say to him?
Well, you know me.
Funny Derek.
How was the sunset?
Never better.
You never really struck me
as the type to stalk your ex-wife.
I'm sorry.
I just, um...
I had an urge to see the house.
See something familiar.
Weird, I know.
You do realize you don't live here anymore.
Yeah.
Fancy ride.
No wonder we keep losing
people to civilian life.
Company car.
They lease it for me.
I have to tell you,
You don't look so well.
Yeah, I'm not.
I just, um...
I don't know, I...
I miss it.
I miss my old life.
James, this is a really weird
time to start into all that.
No, no, I don't mean that.
Things have changed.
And I just...
I didn't.
You're not making sense.
Come on, come inside.
Paul can make coffee. We’ll talk about it.
Thanks, but I didn't come over for that.
Yes, you did.
This was the wrong thing for me to do.
I don't live here anymore.
It was the right thing to do.
Just five years too late.
Call me the next time you wanna
see something familiar.
I'll send you a picture.
Who was it?
They won't be back.
Place looks good.
Yeah, well,
I think we pretty much
got everything back to how it was.
We?
Riley helped.
So how'd you find 'em?
Was it Derek's fence, or what?
You can't bring people here anymore, John.
What?
She had nothing to do with this.
No, you did.
She just made it worse.
She's a security risk.
Really?
She's never tried to kill me.
And you know that this has
nothing to do with Riley.
Or the rules.
Or the security of this house.
You're pissed off because I found someone
I actually like spending time with
and it's not you.
You think I don't want you
to have a normal life?
No, I don't.
Hey, we didn't choose this, John.
It chose us.
And there's nothing either
of us can do about it.
My job is to protect you.
And you can hate me as much as you want,
but I will keep doing that as long as I'm here.
Then why didn't you protect me
when I was killing Sarkissian?
Why didn't you protect me
when I had my hands around his throat?
Why didn't you protect me from that?
It's a Moray.
They're nocturnal predators.
Does it have a name?
No, it doesn't.
Please, sit.
I read the witness report.
So did I.
He comes across as crazy, doesn't he?
Who wouldn't?
You, if you'd tell me the truth.
There was another one of you, wasn't there?
A twin?
Yes.
Where is it now?
I don't know.
Why did it come?
I think I'm being tested.
Like job?
You know the story?
He suffered worse than any man before him.
Everything he loved was taken away.
Everything but his life.
But he didn't renounce god.
And god spared him.
So who spared you?
Where did you get those credit cards?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
She said...
She would find me.
She said she would kill me.
I promise you,
She won't.