NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
- You've got a nuclear sub?
- Seawolf sub.
The Jimmy Carter. We got a scrubbed
Trip-8 for a captain.
Damn it, Cameron.
You're supposed to burn the endos.
What's happening with you?
CAMERON:
I've planted an explosive in my skull.
It's a small amount, but enough.
RILEY: I saw the metal. She knows I saw it.
- Master fear. Remember the mission.
- I can't go back there.
You are here to keep John Connor
away from her.
- I can get her to tell me the truth.
- Stay away.
Cameron's supposed to kill me.
You knew that was the only thing...
...that would turn John against her.
I rescued you from hell,
and I took you to paradise.
[GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOT]
You don't need to be so dramatic.
It's a milk run.
A milk run across 8000 miles
of metal-infested ocean.
If you're gonna be like this
every time...
Listen. Jesse,
I'm going on a mission too.
- Oh, I see. One of those missions.
- No.
It's something else.
- It's different.
- Different?
How's it different?
- What does "different" mean?
- "Different" means different.
Just listen to me.
You're stuck in a can under the ocean
with one of those things.
Don't worry about Queeg.
He's a good bloke.
He's not a bloke.
Jesse, he's not on our side.
Don't ever think that.
Aim for the chip.
Aim for the chip, they don't get up.
I love you too.
Derek.
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
It means, "I'll see you later."
What are you doing?
Moving.
Yeah, well,
seems about the right time for that.
Get your stuff sorted.
I'm nearly done with the living room.
I'm gonna start on the garage.
Uh... Well, hey, why don't you let me
take the garage?
I got a lot of memory cards
and flash drives out there.
I don't want to save our Dakara records
and torch my copy of "Space Invaders."
It's all yours.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
Great, it looks like
a robot serial killer lives here.
Well, I guess one does.
- I'm doing inventory.
- Well, don't do it here.
We need to clear all this stuff out
before Mom comes in and finds it.
Dig a hole out back,
down below the retaining wall.
I'll bury the parts
and come back for them later.
We have to find a place to burn them.
And we will burn them.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
What you drinking?
I don't know.
You don't know what you're drinking?
There's booze in it,
some sugary crap...
...to cut the hell out
of the burning taste, and some ice.
Of course, this one's pretty much empty.
Could you get her another one
of whatever she's drinking?
- If you don't know, how do you order it?
- Just like you did.
But it's gotta start somewhere, right?
You can't sit down...
...and ask for that right off.
What happened to your face?
You ask a lot of questions
for a guy who wants to get in my pants.
- Do I?
- Yeah, see? There's another one.
That's a nice costume.
You thinking about a career
in the military?
Actually, I fly P-3s. For the Navy.
- Oh. Brown Shoe.
- Guilty as charged. You?
- Submarine. Bubblehead.
- Oh, bubble head.
- They let women on subs in Australia?
- Yeah.
Reprogrammed killer robots too.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, we don't discriminate.
Well, there's a coincidence.
I hunt subs. You drive subs.
Sort of like the wolf
and the sheepdog.
Not that I'm comparing you to a dog
or anything.
It's a good point.
In fact, I just remembered something.
- What's that?
- Sheepdogs hate wolves.
And I hate Brown Shoes.
I can't believe you guys
are just up and moving like this.
You could let me throw a party.
You know, you never did come to dinner.
Tape?
It's okay. It's not like you're moving
to Mars, right?
I mean,
we can still totally keep in touch.
- Absolutely.
- Oh, here, let me help you with that.
No, no, I'm good. Sit down.
You know, I'm fine.
People say it takes a while...
...to get back to fighting trim,
but I snapped back like a rubber band.
- You know, mostly like a rubber band.
- You look great.
I'm thinking if I can breast-feed him
till he's 5...
...maybe I can trick my body
into letting me keep these boobs.
Kidding. Sort of.
- And who's got the baby?
- Trevor.
He's not back. He's just visiting.
He said he needed some daddy time.
I don't blame him.
Not after the call they got last night.
They found a girl in the river,
shot through the chest.
Trevor said that it looked
like she'd been executed.
That's terrible.
Pretty little blond thing.
I mean, probably moved here from Iowa
or something to be an actress...
...fell in with the wrong people.
Dreams die hard.
Trevor said all they have to go on...
...are some scars
from an attempted suicide...
...and a tattoo on her wrist.
You know, a pretty little star.
Right here.
Your mother's coming.
All right, quick, hide this stuff.
I need to talk to John.
Alone.
[BIRD COOING]
Goodbye, bird.
There's a 51 percent chance
I wouldn't have killed you.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
- Cameron...
- I know.
I heard you.
Riley's dead.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Was it you?
Did you kill her?
What if I did?
Don't play games with me.
I need the truth.
I didn't kill her.
- I wanna believe you.
- Believe me.
Sometimes you lie to me.
Yes.
I do, but I'm not lying now.
I am sorry.
You're sorry?
For what?
For your loss.
I really wish I could believe that too.
So are you gonna say anything?
Jesse?
- Thanks.
For bailing me out. Thanks.
I know you don't like police stations.
- Maybe that's because I'm a fugitive.
- I know.
- So thanks.
- What happened?
I told you, I got in a fight.
With four Naval aviators.
Really just three.
One of them went down pretty quick.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I don't believe you.
I need to know
what the hell's going on.
I told you, nothing.
[SIGHS]
- We across the line yet?
- Not yet. Give it a tick.
Zero degrees north,
heading south-southwest...
...over the equator.
Now we've crossed the line.
[CHEERING]
- Whoo, whoo!
- Whoo!
One nice thing
about metal driving the boat:
A schedule's a schedule.
One nice thing.
- That mean we're done?
- Quiet, you.
Proclamation.
"Know ye that Sonarman Second Class
Christopher Garvin...
...on the 13th day
of September, 2027...
...aboard USS Jimmy Carter,
appeared at the equator...
...at latitude zero, longitude 180,
entering into our royal domain...
...and having been found worthy
by my royal staff, was initiated...
...into the Solemn Mysteries
of the Ancient Order of the Deep.
I command my subjects to honor him
as one of our trusty shell backs."
Now rise, shell back.
[CHUCKLING]
- Never gets old, does it?
- Never.
[RUMBLING]
Depth charge.
General quarters. Go. Go!
[ALARM BUZZING]
SAVANNAH:
Boo!
- Come and play hide-and-seek, Mommy.
- I'm working.
But you promised.
Patience is a virtue, Savannah.
To tolerate delay.
It implies self-control
and forbearance...
...as opposed to wanting
what we want when we want it.
Something to think about.
[DOOR BUZZES]
["THREE BLIND MICE"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[GIGGLES]
[LAUGHING]
Would you like to play hide-and-seek?
Mr. Ellison. My daughter, Savannah...
...she's missing.
She's in the building, Mr. Ellison.
We just have to find her.
- It's 23 stories.
- Yes.
And there's someone who knows
what's going on on all of them.
WEAVER: John Henry, we're looking
for my daughter, Savannah.
- Have you seen her today?
- Yes, I have.
- She wanted to play a game.
- Where is she now?
She's hiding.
- Tell us where she's hiding.
- That's not how the game works.
How does the game work?
Hide-and-seek.
There are many variations.
The one we're playing...
...you guess what I'm thinking,
I give you a clue.
Listen to me, John Henry.
You're gonna tell me where Savannah is.
And you're gonna tell me now.
I'm thinking of a country.
Come again?
Let's play the game.
This is ridiculous.
I'm not gonna bargain with a computer.
If I'm not mistaken, Mr. Ellison...
...we've got no choice.
You hit him in the mouth, didn't you?
Never aim for the mouth.
- What's that?
- Antibiotic.
You know, one time
when Kyle and I were kids...
...we, uh, saw two tunnel trolls go at it
over a can of stewed tomatoes.
The loser got three teeth knocked out,
and the winner...
...got a blood infection
from his split knuckles...
...and died a week later.
The human mouth is filthy.
[PHONE RINGING]
You got that?
Yeah.
What?
Damn.
John okay?
All right.
Hold tight. I'm on my way.
[SIGHS]
John's girlfriend is dead.
Oh.
A cyborg did it.
- You know that for sure?
- Who else could it be?
What are you gonna do?
- About the metal?
- What are you gonna do?
Because you can't kill her, Derek.
- What?
- That's not something you can do.
He has to make that decision
on his own.
You've really thought this through.
No.
But I think about it.
Just like you do.
More depth charges.
Shook us up a bit, but no damage.
They want us to make a mistake,
reveal our position.
A lot of metal in the water, captain.
Barrage. Getting closer.
- ASW bots. How many?
- Travel in packs. No way to tell.
Mr. Garvin?
[BEEPING]
Garvin.
Not ASW bots.
Oh, man, oh, man. Kraken.
- We've got a kraken.
- You sure?
Bet my life on it.
- Feed the sonar picture to Tactical.
- Aye, ma'am.
You're a big fellow, aren't you?
And you're very far from home.
That can't be right.
- Where are we?
- Chief of the boat...
...status of our torpedo stock?
Two, maybe three
I'd consider worth using in a fight.
Ready Tube 1. Hold for my order.
Queeg, we can't fight a kraken
with one torpedo. Or three.
We need to break contact
and find a way around.
Mr. Garvin, active sonar, please.
One ping only.
One ping, aye.
[SONAR PINGS]
Torpedo in the water.
Closing fast, maybe 40 seconds.
- Yes. Status on my torpedo?
- Torpedo ready, but...
Thirty-second fuse. Match our speed
and bearing after breakaway.
Fire.
You heard him. Fire.
[WHOOSHING]
- Torpedo away.
- Hostile closing, 55 knots.
You got us 20 degrees down bubble.
Ahead, full. Queeg, you're taking...
Taking the boat to 729.8 meters.
- Crush depth.
- The edge of crush depth.
The kraken won't be able to follow.
Their sonar will reflect
off the thermocline layer.
- We'll be...
- Invisible.
- We're playing dead.
- Eight seconds to torpedo contact.
- Approaching crush depth.
- If he's off by even a millimeter...
- ...for even a fraction of a second...
- He won't be. This is what he does.
Two detonations. Our torpedo and theirs.
Eleven hundred meters to starboard,
120 on the Z.
And now we roll over,
stick out our tongue, hold our breath.
[HULL CREAKING]
- Skipper, we're at 729.8.
- I'm aware, chief. Thank you.
729.8 and holding.
You may return
to your duty stations now.
You heard the captain, people.
What, you never been 20 centimeters
from your maker before? Move.
Skipper, when we're done
skating over our deaths...
...I got a question.
Why are we 300 miles off course?
We were using it for research,
to find out what makes them...
Don't, John. Just don't.
Don't make excuses for her.
Don't cover for her.
- I knew about the parts...
- I'm not talking about the parts.
I'm talking about Riley.
Well, there's nothing to talk about,
is there? Because Riley's dead.
How do you think that happened?
I don't know.
I'm gonna figure it out, though.
You know, John. We both know.
No.
Cameron didn't do it.
How can you say that?
How can you be sure?
Because I'm sure, and I know her...
...and she told me.
She told you.
Just like she told you she destroyed
every part we ever captured.
Just like she tells us what she does
every night when we go to sleep.
When she comes back in the morning,
she's covered in cuts and bruises.
Hey. Just like she told you
she loved you.
You don't know anything.
I'm thinking of an herb.
- Tarragon?
- No.
- We're wasting time.
- But it's working, his game.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you not angry?
Why should I be?
We have a way to get her back.
Tell me where the child is.
[SIGHS]
Look, you asked me to teach him
ethics, morals and rules.
What good is it
if he's not gonna follow them?
He will, if we let him
learn the rules on his own.
Oregano.
- Correct.
- See there? A lucky guess.
- Lucky.
- Give us our clue.
The sun is shining on Savannah.
Security.
Check near all windows.
Any place light is coming through.
I'm thinking of an animal.
- Antelope.
- No.
- Lion.
- Horse.
- No.
- Bird.
- Correct.
- Give us our clue.
- The answer is the clue.
What? What does that mean?
Just what he said. "Bird" is our clue.
Bird.
I know where she is.
Security, meet us
at the elevators.
Savannah, are you okay?
Mm-hm.
Come here, come here.
Here, go to your mother.
You found me, Mommy.
Yes, darling, I did.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey, Aaron. John.
I remember.
- Is Riley around?
- No. She didn't come home last night.
Riley didn't come home?
Thanks.
Foster kids. That's the way it is
with them sometimes.
They drift into your life,
and then they drift back out again.
Not always according to plan.
She's a tough one too.
Good heart, as I'm sure you know,
but tough to know.
Well, uh, I really needed to talk to her.
I don't know if you can maybe
just take a message for me, or...?
[PHONE RINGING]
- See, the last time we spoke...
- Hang on a sec.
Hello?
Riley. God, Riley, are you all right?
Where are you?
[IN RILEY'S VOICE] Everything's fine.
I'm in Riverside. It's a long story.
- Everything's fine.
- We've been worried sick.
- We were about to call the police.
- Please don't do that. Everything's fine.
- John too. He's here.
- John? Really? Can I talk to him?
Me?
Riley?
You're in Riverside. Okay.
Well, listen, we'll talk when I see you.
I thought you'd wanna hear my voice.
You know you're really
freaking everybody out, right?
Am I freaking you out now?
Yes...
- ...so let's talk later.
- I'm sorry.
It's just... I've been thinking
about my parents a lot...
...and there are things
I can't get out of my head...
...and I just thought if I came out
and saw where we used to live...
I know. Stupid, right?
Okay, well, we'll talk about all this
in person, yeah? When you get back.
- We're hanging up now. Ha-ha.
- John?
Yeah, sure. That would be great.
- Yeah?
I love you.
Okay, bye.
What was that about?
[IN NORMAL VOICE] What was what about?
What happened just now.
It was the plan.
No, the plan
was to call the foster parents.
The plan was to let him hear her voice.
That's what I did.
That's not all you did.
What you did was not the plan.
The plan was to make him think
she's still alive...
...so he wouldn't go to the police.
You became part of that plan.
Your reaction made it more authentic.
Don't you think
it was more authentic that way?
Where are we going now?
We're not going anywhere.
I'm going somewhere...
...and I'm gonna go alone.
- You shouldn't be alone.
- Yes, I should.
Did you have fun playing the game,
Mr. Ellison?
- No, John Henry, I did not.
- Why not?
Because what you did made me very,
very angry.
- I don't understand.
- You kept a secret.
Is it wrong to keep a secret?
The secret you kept
could've harmed Savannah.
What if we couldn't have found her?
What if she'd fallen from the roof
and died?
Then she wouldn't be alive anymore,
and her life is important.
Human life is sacred.
If she had died, it would be your fault.
My fault?
Because you were the only one
who knew where she was...
...and you made a choice not to tell.
It was the wrong choice.
Derek?
I'm thinking about Riley.
What the cyborg did to her.
It's a terrible thing.
But...
...if John realizes what the metal is...
...what it really does...
...maybe some good can come of it.
Maybe you can help him see that.
Good?
An innocent kid is dead.
That metal bitch murdered her in
cold blood. No good comes out of that.
None. Not ever.
You're a good man.
Oh, yeah?
Don't let anyone tell you different.
[SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[SIGHS]
We've been bearing 30 degrees
off-course for four hours...
...into a major Skynet zone.
What's going on?
Our new mission required it.
What mission? Where are we headed?
A deep-water oil platform
near the Indonesian archipelago.
Lieutenant Dietz and his team
will board the rig and retrieve a package.
We will deliver this package
to Serrano Point.
We have important cargo to take to Perth.
Components, vaccines...
Our orders come from John Connor.
These orders from John Connor,
do they say what we're after?
What it is?
Yes. They say what the package is.
Right.
Please inform the crew. Thank you.
[SIGHS]
JESSE: Just stay sharp. You'll be fine.
- Oh, I know I'll be fine.
[GUN COCKS]
- I got this.
- I'm serious, Dietz.
- I'm always serious about being fine.
- You do me one favor.
You see anything you don't like,
you think before you pull that trigger.
I've been seeing things I don't like
since J-Day.
You don't get to be my age
without thinking first.
I swear, Mom. We'll hold hands
before we cross the street.
ASDS has cut engines, commander.
I think we're clear for comms.
ASDS, this is Carter, over.
DIETZ: Hey, Mom. I'll say this much
about a deep-sea oil rig:
Second-worst thing I've ever smelled.
Dark as night out hete.
We're gonna keep this channel open.
Maintain radio silence
till you've got the package.
Planning on it.
[RAIN PATTERING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Connor sent me. John Connor.
I've come for that.
That's for him.
I'm just here to pick it up.
[METAL CLANKING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
I had planned on waiting for you
with Derek's sniper rifle.
Pulled the trigger, solved about
50 percent of my problems. One shot.
Do you know how bad I'd have felt?
- Very bad?
- Not bad at all.
But I know someone
who'd have felt bad.
Someone who would never forgive me
if I'd done that.
I don't know what to do with you.
You know what the stakes are.
You know why we're here.
You know what this means.
And yet here I stand,
burning what's left of an endoskeleton...
- ...I thought we'd burned months ago.
- I needed spare parts.
I don't care what you need,
because this is not about you.
No, it's not about me. It's about John.
You're concerned for his safety.
- You bet I am.
- From Skynet.
- From me.
- Maybe.
Maybe especially you.
We're all a threat.
We're all a threat to John.
He worries about us.
That makes him vulnerable.
He cares.
I am not John's problem.
John is John's problem.
Humans are the problem.
There's only one way for him to be safe.
That's to be alone.
What kind of life is that?
John's life, someday.
I'm sorry.