Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles...
I'm here because Sarah Connor is a diluted,
dangerous, grade A whack-a-mole
who killed a man because she
believed that in the future
he'll invent a computer system
that declares war on the world.
I'm looking for this girl.
Have you seen my niece?
There was a guy here looking for your sister.
Get rid of him! Riley!
If you don't leave, I'm calling the police.
That guy is really dangerous.
That's all you need to know.
Really dangerous.
This has nothing to do with Riley.
You're pissed off
Because I found someone I actually like
spending time with, and it's not you.
Riley, look at me.
Show me that.
That's horrifying.
Yeah, well, it's supposed to
stop cars from playing
ping-pong with your head.
Hey, I think your mom's out here.
Hi, Mrs. Baum!
Thank you so much for having me over.
I didn't even know if you were busy
tonight when I texted you.
I'm never busy.
So I should do it again sometime.
Or maybe you could call.
You know, with your voice.
Maybe I could try that.
Maybe you should.
See you soon.
Okay, be safe.
I bought her a helmet.
Responsible.
You think it'll stop a bullet?
Why, you gonna take a shot at her?
A lot of bullets fly around here.
Someone will.
You care about this girl?
Yeah.
Then leave her alone.
I'll talk to John.
John's not listening.
He's always listening.
I was going to suggest a safe.
Well, you might have suggested
it before we got robbed.
Where are you going?
I need to restock the supply drop.
We've been using a lot of ammunition.
Business has been booming.
Where's John?
Still in his room.
He hasn't gotten up yet?
He needs more sleep than you do.
It's because the circadian rhythm
of teenagers is abnormal.
How late were you up talking to him?
Not late.
He won't be seeing Riley anymore.
Is that so?
John's not stupid.
I don't like the way he responds to you.
You got what you wanted.
Where is he?
Check under the bed.
You don't know.
I didn't even know if you were busy
when I texted you tonight.
I'm never busy.
So then I guess I should do it again sometime.
Or maybe you could even call.
You know, with your voice.
Maybe I could try that.
Maybe you should.
See you soon.
Go, be safe.
I'll talk to John.
John's not listening.
He's always listening.
Are you busy?
No.
Did you change?
It's hot out.
Since when do you feel heat?
I feel heat.
Are you hoping that Riley's gonna
see us in bed together,
and be totally scarred for the
rest of her life or something?
No.
I watched Riley leave till I couldn't
see her anymore.
And then you and mom high-fived.
You bring danger into Riley's life.
I know that.
I'm not stupid.
But sometimes you do stupid things.
It would help me to understand why.
Humans do stupid things.
So don't worry about it,
and be happy you're a machine.
I'm a machine.
I can't be happy.
But I understand more than you think.
So you understand that I'm
going to keep seeing Riley,
even if everyone thinks it's a bad idea.
I understand that it's a bad idea.
And I understand that being
John Connor can be lonely.
Oh, yeah?
How do you understand that?
You and I talk about it a lot.
We do?
We do.
We will.
I need-- I need to get some sleep.
And Riley?
I know.
He won't be seeing Riley anymore.
I don't like the way he responds to you.
You got what you wanted.
It's just you.
You been stealing my supplies?
We needed to make a small bomb.
I set this drop up with my people for my people.
And everything's in here for a reason.
John was supposed to ask.
John needs to get his head in the game.
Maybe he couldn't find you.
You don't spend much time at the house.
I don't have a bed, remember?
You didn't have a bed in the old house.
I had a gunshot wound at the old house.
Yes. You almost died.
It's not the first time.
Who's that?
Alarm code from John. He's in trouble.
I need to get some sleep.
And Riley?
I know.
Yeah, right.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Ew, please stop doing that.
Look, I got this from my foster parents.
And it's a rape whistle.
It's totally for moments like this.
Moments like this? Yeah, all right.
When I was a kid, I--
I lived in Mexico for a year and a half.
In this, uh, little village called Dejalo.
And, uh...
That's where we're going.
Thought I'd show you around.
Um, well, did you run this idea by your mom?
Because sometimes I get the impression
That she doesn't really like surprises.
I don't care.
Did you guys get in a fight last night?
No.
So this is definitely a field trip,
and not some revenge fantasy?
All right, if you don't wanna go, that's cool.
But do not make me feel like I'm
kidnapping you or something.
Oh, no, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You just caught me off guard.
I'm really, really happy that you want
to show me where you grew up.
Good.
'cause I booked the honeymoon suite.
Wait, what?
It's good, right?
It's nice to get some space.
You and space.
You know, the first time we talked,
you were sitting by yourself in the grass.
That was space too.
So it was.
You know I used to watch you at school?
When the bell would ring
and those narrow hallways would fill up,
it got so loud, and people would bump into you.
You looked like you could just
jump out the window and run away.
God, you're such a little stalker.
All right, so I get that...
we ran away to get some space.
The only shame is...
we ran all this way, and there's
skulls everywhere.
What, you don't like skulls?
I like other things better.
It's for Dia de los Muertos.
The festival's tonight.
Nice.
Skulls and darkness, how charming.
Doing the best I can.
I never want to leave this room.
Wait, I think I see the problem.
Would you just get in here?
We don't need bubbles.
Well, there's bubbles to be had,
and I'm going to have bubbles.
Ah, not bad, huh?
You're a total pro.
Wait, you didn't live here
with your mom, did you?
No.
We, uh--
we actually had a cabana on the beach.
I think we had very different childhoods.
It wasn't always good.
Sometimes I wish we just stayed here.
Away from everybody.
People suck.
Not just people.
No, I mean--
when you meet someone, you don't
really expect to give a damn about them, right?
Who's got the time?
Life's too short, and people suck.
I don't like getting attached to people.
So...
Why were you living in Mexico?
Oh, you're thinking of a lie or a joke.
-No, I'm not.
-Yes, you are.
-You have a tell.
-I just don't want to sit around
and talk about my messed up childhood.
Can't we just enjoy ourselves?
Yeah, fine.
Enjoy yourself, John.
I'm sure we're not the only couple
that's found themselves in a honeymoon suite,
and not known the first thing about each other.
You're right.
People suck.
Podemos tener picante, por favor?
El verde?
Es muy picante como fuego.
Si, exactamente.
What was that about?
Hot sauce.
You know, uh, they do this killer
thanksgiving buffet here.
I bet.
See?
I'm telling you all sorts of good stuff.
I'm not trying to be your stalker, I just--
I think this is what we should be doing.
You know, getting to know each other.
Well, I have a question for you.
You said, uh, that I have a tell.
What is it?
Okay, you promise not to obsess
over it or anything?
What a handsome couple.
And for only $5,
-a photo memory.
-No, thanks.
See, a beautiful shot.
And it's all digital.
Which means I can email it to you.
I--I think I have something in my teeth.
Oh, well, let me take another.
No, no, really, that's okay.
Hey, I said that's okay.
Look, man, why don't I, uh--
Why don't I just give you five bucks,
and you'll delete it.
Can you do that?
Gracias, joven.
The young boy and mother
who stayed in Vivian's cabana.
Thanks a lot.
John Connor.
No se de quien estas hablando.
You're Sarah Connor's son.
I'll be right back.
I remember when the Connors left Dejalo.
And I remember the stories that
were told after you were gone.
Man, you really--
you really mixed me up with somebody else.
I'm just--
These are pictures you wouldn't
want the authorities to see.
-How much?
-Everything you've got.
Hey, back off, man.
We gotta get out of here, now.
-Run!
-No!
No se puede salir sin pagar!
Puedo pagar la camara.
Stick to English, kid.
The American accent is killing me.
This is a misunderstanding, that's all.
I'll pay for the camera, okay?
What the hell were you doing down here anyway?
We're just tourists.
Cancun's not good for you?
This is the guy?
Yes, sir.
I was about to take his statement.
A man took a picture of me and my girlfriend,
and he wanted us to buy it.
It was crowded, someone bumped into him,
he dropped his camera.
I was afraid a fight was going to start,
so we tried to leave, that's all.
-How old are you?
-16.
-You were drinking?
-No.
You have parents.
My mother and an uncle.
They know where you are?
No.
I'll make you a deal.
If they come pick you up,
I'll let you go with a warning.
Leave a message.
What the hell was that?
It's my uncle's voice mail.
Call your mother.
Hello?
John, thank god. Where are you?
I've been going out of my mind.
Did you get through?
John, are you there? Are you in trouble?
She didn't answer.
Put him in holding.
In a few hours, give him another phone call.
And run his name through Interpol.
Yes, sir.
So which name should I run?
The one on your passport?
Or the real one?
Sir, sir, hello?
Hi, can you come here, please?
Hi, I need your help, please.
This guy in here is a complete psycho.
He's been trying to make moves on me.
You two came in together.
Sir, do you have children?
Do you have a daughter?
My dad told me to stay away from this guy,
and he was totally right.
This guy's a complete freak.
And I don't even care how much trouble I'm in.
All I want to do is call home
And tell them where I am.
Please?
Take a step back.
-I'm going to open the door.
-Thank you.
Lo siento, senor. Lo siento.
Riley, you need to listen to me.
No matter what happens,
if you see daylight, you run.
Okay, don't wait for me. Just run.
What? What are you do--
If you see daylight, you run.
Your strategy has changed from last time.
Has it?
The first time we met,
you tried to kill yourself.
You're right.
This time I'm going to kill you.
She hasn't been careful.
She's made mistakes.
Not as many as you, but enough.
Does she have damage to her chip?
She has damage to her chip.
How did you find the house?
The boy told me.
The one from the bowling alley.
You should have killed him.
Just like you should have killed yourself.
I'm not a murderer.
Who is?
Hello?
Sarah Connor? James Ellison.
I need you to come with me.
James Ellison.
Agent Crossman, how you doing?
It's good to hear from you.
What's on your mind?
Mexico.
You don't say.
I suppose
that they don't have anyone looking into it
over at the bureau.
I know.
Connor's case has been cold since '99.
I was just curious.
Sure, email it over and I'll take a look.
Hold on.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
It does look a little bit like him.
John Connor.
God rest his soul.
You're with the American FBI?
Yes, that's right.
You have a boy in your custody.
His arrest report lists an alias of John Connor,
which matches a fugitive of mine.
The domestic terrorism case.
You're familiar with the Connors?
It was flagged during processing.
But we dismissed it as a coincidence.
Your fugitive would be 24 years old by now,
if he was not already dead.
Look,
I'd be grateful for just a visual identification
to help bring me some closure.
You have traveled an awful long way for closure.
If he is who I think he is,
then I have reason to believe
that your prison is in danger.
And yes,
I've come a long way.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for John Connor.
Daylight, run!
John! I'm here to help you.
Oh, my god!
The car, Riley!
Riley, get in the car, now!
Now! Get in!
-You okay?
-Yeah.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Are there any rounds in this thing?
Look for ammunition. Look for more ammunition.
We need more!
What, are you okay?
I just felt something back here!
Stop the car. Stop the car.
Sarah Connor. James Ellison.
I need you to come with me.
Mom.
We need to move.
It's a clear shot all the way of the alley
back to the jail.
No, that's where it will be waiting.
Let me do that.
I need to be able to use it.
I should hope so.
Why are you here?
John was flagged in the FBI computer.
Couldn't you just have buried it?
It's been watching me.
It?
Out there.
It.
And you still came to Mexico?
You could have led it right to John.
It wasn't me in the trunk.
So what were you going to do,
just pop him out of jail?
Set him free, no questions asked?
Yes, actually.
That's exactly what I was going to do.
Hm, I have a hard time believing that.
I owed you one.
The fire. Silberman's cabin?
Wasn't much.
It was my life.
How you feel about that now?
You have to go.
I promise I'll call you as soon
as we get back to L.A.
But you have to go.
John. Riley, don't.
Go home.
I swear I'll explain everything
when we get there.
Go out the back.
Run due east. There's a bus route.
You know what else there is?
A man with a gun who's killing people.
He won't follow you if you run away from me.
I don't wanna run away from you.
Get her out of here.
I need your phone.
Have a plan?
I've got a weapon.
Cameron.
The girl from the bank vault?
John and I are in trouble.
I need you and Cameron.
John's with you? Well, we're here already.
-We're at the jail.
-What?
Cromartie's here.
Then we should stay undercover.
I'm looking for John Baum. Where is he?
Yo no se.
We gotta get out of here.
We gotta find John.
We're no good to him dead.
I can't let anything happen to him.
Escaped or dead?
Escaped!
A little help, por favor?
Don't worry, it won't be back.
Senor!
Please!
John and I are in trouble.
I need you and Cameron.
John's with you?
Well, we're here already. We're at the jail.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, Sarah.
Then where the hell's Cromartie?
I am sorry, senor,
but I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
I'm gonna need to see John Connor.
Help. Help me!
Ayudame!
I'm looking for John Connor.
He's gone.
Are there any other exits?
No.
Have you come to repent?
I'm looking for John Connor.
All things are possible
to him who believes.
We'll attract less attention if
we don't travel together.
You want me to leave?
What's next?
We'll come back down here.
And bring something with us to destroy it.
His name's gonna be on an alert.
He's got other names.
Then what?
There is no "then what."
Pretend I died again.
I lost a lot when you died the first time.
My marriage, my career.
That's a lot to you?
I suppose many people lost those things.
You want answers.
I just want to know my role
in all of this.
What happens after this?
This is it.
There's nothing else behind the curtain.
This is what I do. It's all I do.
You already know why I do it.
I'm sorry for what you lost.
But I can't help you get any of it back.
Can I have the chip?