NARRATOR: In the future,
a computer program called Skynet...
...will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time
taking human form...
...to terminate John Connor,
the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor, John's mother,
teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogrammed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle...
...and a commanding officer
with the Resistance.
Together they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow
starts today.
NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
Ugh!
SARAH:
He's from the future.
Sent here by John.
Stop Greenway. Serrano Point.
He's concerned about
a censor board in the control room.
- The reactor could melt down.
- Skynet wins.
The reactor's overheating.
My name is Catherine Weaver.
I'd like to talk to you...
...about a job opportunity,
Agent Ellison.
This is Riley.
Now is not the time for this.
Well, when is the time to live my life?
Martin Bedell?
DEREK:
His name was Martin Bedell.
He was in Century Work Camp
with you...
...right up until the escape.
- So I knew him.
- You knew him.
Everybody knew him.
But he doesn't know this one.
Not this Martin Bedell.
No. Another Martin Bedell.
Maybe it's just coincidence.
How many coincidences
named Sarah Connor got killed...
...before Skynet finally locked in
on you?
- So why would they want to kill him?
- He had experience...
...and knowledge John needed.
Military prep school, then West Point.
Bedell had real training.
He helped John
put the Resistance together.
Okay. There were three Martin Bedells
in L.A., now there are two.
- How do we know which is the target?
- They both are.
Machines are thorough.
Only good thing about them.
So it took you, what, 30 seconds
to find those names?
If there is a Triple-8 out there,
he's found them too.
SARAH: Where are you going?
- Martin Bedell Number 1.
Closest address.
- Without a plan?
- Yeah, I've got a plan.
It involves guns.
- Wait.
- You're not going with him.
No, everybody wait.
P Alto. We thought it was a person.
It's not. It's a place.
It's a military prep school in Carlsbad.
Here's the directory.
SARAH:
Martin Bedell Number 2.
Maybe we got a head start.
I'll load the truck. We'll go.
We will, will we?
It's a boys' school.
I can do this. I am doing this.
Nothing complicated.
Find the kid,
throw him in a hole, babysit.
It's safe as anything we do.
Go.
Two.
Two Sarah Connors were murdered
before they found me.
Cameron and I will find
the other Martin Bedell.
Maybe we can stop the Triple-8
before he gets to you.
He's not a soldier.
No.
Not yet.
You haven't said a word
since Anaheim.
That's 40 miles of quiet.
You...
You thinking or worrying?
Thinking.
About Bedell. After we grab him,
where are we supposed to hide him?
Who said we're gonna hide him?
Martin Bedell hiding
in a cave somewhere...
...might as well be
Martin Bedell dead somewhere.
No use to John Connor.
Besides, it's a military school...
...with soldiers, guns.
Can't do much better than that.
ELLISON: So you own this nuclear plant,
Serrano Point?
I have an interest in it.
Is this the same company
you were referring to the other day?
- The one you wanted me to look into?
- It is.
The near-meltdown a few weeks back.
The news said an employee
caused the accident.
Mr. Ellison, there are no accidents.
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING DRILLS]
MAN 1: Come on!
MAN 2: Sir, yes, sir!
MARTIN: Kansas, this is Hammerhead,
do you copy?
- Kansas, respond.
DEREK: He's back. It's Kyle.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Tin cans just hit Kansas' bunker.
MARTIN:
Survivors?
Prisoners now.
One Ogre tank, three monkey wagons.
The convoy'll roll down Wilshire
to Century...
...in an hour. I'm thinking...
- No. We got orders.
Connor wants
this corridor controlled...
...so we sit tight,
we observe Skynet movement...
...and report back at regular intervals.
What's that report gonna say?
That we observed Skynet move these
people into a death camp while we sat?
I know. I know it sucks.
But if we lose eyes on this road...
...we could lose a lot more
than one bunker, Kyle.
- Lf Connor were here...
MARTIN: Connor isn't here.
Corporal, get below.
Round up every tunnel rat
you can find.
Martin, you know what he'd say.
- You know what Connor would say.
- Yes, I know.
Connor wants to shoot me
for disobeying...
...he can get in line
behind the tin cans.
We're doing this.
JOHN:
Hey.
You all right?
We see a lot of boys
like your nephew, lieutenant.
Single mother, socially withdrawn,
move around a lot.
Tend to cling to male authority figures.
- Lost his dad, you said, in the war?
- Killed. On a mission.
- Can't tell you any more than that.
- Don't know?
- Can't.
- I understand.
Well...
Good grades, good test scores.
Good kid. Here's what I'll do:
Three weeks as a plebe.
If he likes it, he can stay.
Then we'll talk tuition.
Thank you.
I'll give him the news.
Lieutenant.
I lost one of my TACs
a couple weeks ago.
Reservist. Had to go.
TAC, teacher-advisor...
...they keep the cadets from going all
Lord of The Flies on us.
Hired a replacement,
but he's not due for a week.
- I'm short-handed.
- Sir.
Respectfully, I'm probably
the last guy you're looking for.
Guys like you get dropped into
the ass-end of nowhere.
You can handle 30 adolescents
for a week.
Good news. You're in.
What's the bad news?
I'm in.
Man up, newb.
You don't wanna get owned.
Stop crying about your
Internet connection and learn to play.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
I gotta AFK a minute.
[DOORBELL RINGING]
Martin Bedell?
Yes?
[GUNFIRE]
SARAH:
Come on, let's go.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Go. Go.
Drive.
SARAH:
You good? You okay?
- Seat belt.
- Who is that man?
He should be dead.
How come he's not dead?
And where's my mom?
No more questions.
Your mother's location is unknown.
That man is a cyborg sent to kill you.
Cameron.
Put your seat belt on.
ELLISON: I'm familiar with the incident
reports, Mr. Nelson. I know what they say.
But what I don't know
is what really happened.
NELSON: The people who wrote those reports
are bureaucrats.
You know what bureaucrats do
when the facts don't fit their boxes?
They ignore them.
Or change them.
So this valve supposedly blew open
because of metal fatigue.
Sure. Okay.
Not likely,
but let's grant Mother Nature that one.
So how in the hell did it
force itself closed?
Okay.
How strong would you have to be
to force this open, then push it back?
Scale of 1 to 10?
Superman.
NELSON: Report says this damage was
caused by a transformer explosion.
- Wanna see what the security tapes say?
- There are no tapes. They're gone.
That they are.
And who took those?
Carl Greenway on the way
to hanging himself?
Those mystery employees
who shut the reactor down?
You ask the same questions I would.
I'm putting together a report
for the NRC.
They're gonna crawl up this place's ass
with a wire brush.
Gonna play hell with the schedule.
Schedule? What schedule is that?
August 2009
new automated system comes online...
...and we're back in business.
That's what they say.
Of course, it ain't gonna happen
if the feds are on a warpath.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUNSHOTS]
- Hey, you jammed?
- Yeah.
You know sports?
Like wrestling?
No. It's a mnemonic.
Sports. S-P-O-R-T-S. May I?
All right. So you wanna slap.
Pull.
Observe.
Release.
Tap.
Shoot.
All right, thanks, plebe.
You're welcome, I think.
GUY:
Baum.
I'm Cadet Captain Martin Bedell.
Commandant asked me
to keep an eye on you.
Prep you for OCC.
- What's this?
- It's a merit for squaring away Pyle.
And that's a demerit.
Next time you have a problem,
flag down a senior cadet or instructor.
You run, Baum?
I love to run.
MARTIN: You look ate up.
- Oh, no. This is great.
MARTIN: Yeah, imagine how it's gonna be
with a Marine DI screaming at you.
Like everything is life and death.
I can imagine.
MARTIN:
That the new TAC?
DEREK: It's a good ambush point,
in case you were looking for one.
In case you choose to jog
in the woods by yourself.
You should be careful.
Of that too.
It's tar. La Brea.
- It's everywhere.
JOHN: Stuff smells terrible.
- Smells like...
- Jet fuel.
So.
You're out here jogging in the open,
exposed with...
...Bedell.
- I've heard a lot about you.
- A lot of good, I hope, sir.
Lot of good.
- So when do I get to call my mom?
- When it's safe.
- When's that?
- Soon.
WOMAN [ON TV]:
Soft, smooth, clear, beautiful skin.
- Do you do this every night?
- Yeah.
Well, what happens
when you go to sleep?
She happens.
[COCKS GUN]
Let's find you
something to wear for bed.
Something in here should fit you.
Try these.
This is too small.
- How do you know? Just try them.
- They're for a 5-year-old.
How about this?
That's for playing soccer.
This isn't your stuff, is it?
No, it's not our stuff.
I wanna call my mom.
She was supposed to get me a book
for my book report.
If you call your mother,
that man will use her to find you.
Then he'll kill her. He'll kill you.
Ahem. Cameron.
Would you like a bedtime story?
CAMERON:
We made a tactical error.
We should've engaged the Triple-8.
With a little boy in the crossfire?
The boy is not important.
- He's not our mission.
- He is now.
MARTIN:
It's just a meet and greet, sir.
Say hi, ask them how they're holding up,
then "Company, dismissed." It's easy.
Oh, and they're probably gonna wanna
ask you about OCC prep weekend.
We take the juniors
through field exercises...
...obstacle courses, simulated missions,
running around in the woods.
It'll be fun.
Fun.
Hi.
I'm Lieutenant Baum.
I'm your new TAC.
So I've been told that my job is to
make sure that you're all doing okay.
Well, you all look okay to me.
So any questions?
All right then.
PYLE:
Sir.
We heard you were in the war.
Heard you've seen action.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've seen action in the war.
Got a lot of kills?
- Say again?
- Kills, sir.
I wanna go infantry soon as I get out
of here. Maybe Rangers, maybe Delta.
Best of the best.
Counting kills, like it's a game.
Like it's just a game.
I remember one particularly fun day.
Guy in my squad got his stomach
blasted open in a firefight.
He spent six hours
holding his own guts in.
His buddy carried him on his back
to the nearest aid station.
Just praying that someone could put
the dumb son of a bitch together again.
The game, Pyle...
...the game is played
with your buddy's life.
With the life of your squad.
Your platoon.
The game is played by you...
...on behalf
of the whole damn human race.
MARTIN:
Meet my friend the EFP.
He sits in the middle of the road
and blows up metal.
This is his life's ambition.
I intend to help him achieve it.
We've seeded the street
with these things.
We gotta make sure
that Ogre cooperates.
MARTIN: Corporal Reese will take you
and set up.
When the convoy rolls to your position,
open fire on this bunker.
Ogre will think it's metal on skin
and move to assist. When it does:
Boom.
Questions?
Move out.
Hey. They're kids.
They key off of you.
I know.
Kids.
Your uncle, he's an intense guy.
Yeah, I know.
He's a good guy, though.
He's just...
He's a lot to take sometimes.
All he's been through, well...
What are you supposed to say to that?
You mean, how do you measure up?
Every man in my family
going back five generations...
...has been a general, or statesman,
CEO, something amazing.
They all went here.
But you know what the best part
about Presidio Alto is?
The cross-country course.
Man, sometimes when I'm out there...
...I'm all alone, I'm going flat out,
everything just sort of...
...falls away.
But sometimes I wish it...
l...
That you could just keep on running
and never look back.
I met this girl over the summer.
Her name's Alicia.
She's amazing, dude.
She started at Dartmouth this year.
She's a runner like me.
She's coming home in a couple weeks,
and when she goes back...
...I think I wanna go with her.
And never look back.
That's a secret, Baum.
You treat it as such.
I always do.
I was just on the roof.
It's flat terrain all around,
but the woods are a problem.
When it comes,
that's where it'll come from.
You're alone and exposed here.
It's not good.
And you're gonna tell me,
"I know better."
Bedell is quitting.
Leaving school.
No, he isn't.
- He won't.
- Well, he is.
He doesn't. He graduates.
Goes to West Point.
Why?
Because the future already happened,
and he's just going through the motions?
- He doesn't have a choice.
- Oh, he's got a choice.
We just gotta help him
make the right one.
Like everybody does with me.
There are three exits within 20 meters,
two lead to a parking lot.
There's a black hatchback three cars in,
unlocked, with the keys above the visor.
I do know better.
MRS. BEDELL [ON TV]: We're begging you,
be merciful and keep our son safe.
Marty, if you can hear this...
...we're gonna get you back.
- Your dad and I love you, and we're...
- Turn that off.
What the hell were you thinking?
He wanted to see his mother.
You all right?
I told you people.
I told you I had to get it done
by Monday...
...and it's Friday already,
and I haven't even started.
I'm in trouble,
and when you don't do it...
...the teacher makes you stand up
in front of the whole class.
Marty, slow down.
[MARTIN PANTING]
You're hyperventilating.
There.
Take a breath.
[INHALES & EXHALES]
Tell me what this is about.
I told you.
- My book report.
- Book report.
Yeah, it's due by Monday...
...and I haven't even picked out
a book yet. Don't you listen?
Let's find you one.
There's gotta be
something for you somewhere.
It was John's favorite.
Who's John?
The machine won't stop.
It'll go back to that kid's house...
...find his parents, find his mom.
- I would.
The police will be there by now.
- The police won't matter.
- I know.
You don't need to be here.
There are other places to be.
You want me to protect his parents.
I want you to keep this contained.
Something you need, officer?
- Good eye.
- Job requirement.
Right. Private sector.
I'm looking into the plant accident.
When Carl Greenway went nuts?
Yeah. When Carl Greenway went nuts.
- I understand he used to come in here.
- They all do.
Including Carl.
Used to sit right where you're sitting,
drink alone.
Drink a lot?
Tonic water.
Like you, I bet.
Was he alone like me?
Pretty much every night.
I don't know why the guy
came in here at all.
Still, I do remember some hottie
chatting him up...
...the night before everything went down
at the power plant.
Probably one of Sandy's friends.
Sandra runs HR at the plant.
A birthday party that night.
Got pictures.
May I?
BARTENDER:
Find who you're looking for?
Actually, quite the opposite.
JOHN:
These gonna kill it?
DEREK:
No. Speed bump, that's all.
This...
Raufoss. Mk211 round.
Tungsten core, armor piercing,
high explosive incendiary.
Hits with the force
of a 20 mm cannon.
I saw your dad take down
an H-K with one.
He liked it better than his plasma rifle.
So this is gonna kill it.
It'll make it stop,
reconsider its life choices.
JOHN: That soldier, the one
you talked about in your story...
...my dad carried him
to the aid station, didn't he?
DEREK:
Yeah.
Spent a whole night in the bunker trying
to get the blood out of his fatigues.
You know, it's funny...
...I saw a deer the other day,
made me think of him.
We were together
the last time I saw one.
- Before Judgement Day?
- No, after.
We were up in Griffith Park
hunting for food.
It was a big bastard too.
Your dad had never seen one before.
I mean, not like that.
After I killed it, and we got close...
...your dad started crying.
But more than I'd ever heard
or seen him.
I didn't know how to make him stop.
I buried the deer.
We went hungry.
He was just a boy.
- So were you.
- Yeah.
I guess I was.
ELLISON:
You see how the metal is twisted?
You can have the Steelers' entire
offensive line tugging on that valve...
...and not generate enough force
to do that.
So you agree it was a machine
as I thought?
Two machines.
One machine ripped the valve open,
and I'm guessing the other closed it.
And I'm pretty sure
there was a fight between them.
Two machines.
This is new.
Where did they come from?
Why did they fight?
I wish I knew.
I wish any of this made sense.
I do know I'm not
the only one asking questions.
The plant manager, Nelson.
He wants the NRC to investigate.
It'll be a nightmare.
That will complicate
our respective goals, won't it, James?
What would those respective goals be?
I'd like my company to lead the world
into the next century.
And I'm fairly sure
you're an avenging angel.
So let's keep looking.
Before the nightmare begins.
Last one.
It's for my heart.
What, you never heard
of the French paradox?
Those frogs eat foie gras and gargle
red wine, they live till they're 90.
Yeah, but it's the chemicals
in the grape skins that do it.
Well, bonjour.
Resvera-something.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
I saw it on 60 Minutes.
You don't say.
NELSON:
You're so beautiful.
Sorry, this...
This never happened to me before.
Don't worry, sweetie.
[GRUNTING]
I bet that never happened
before either.
The FBI has moved Marty's parents.
And the Triple-8?
He's made no attempt
to acquire them.
So, what would you do now,
in your professional robot opinion?
Marty's trail has gone cold.
- I'd switch to the other Martin Bedell.
- So go to the other Martin Bedell.
Wait for the Triple-8.
When it shows up, blow its head off.
He can put it back on.
Marty likes the crusts cut off.
Here you go.
My teacher doesn't like books
that have been made into movies.
She thinks we'll cheat
and watch the movie.
You'd be in big trouble if you did.
The movie's pretty different
than the book.
Really?
How?
Well, the slippers aren't ruby,
they're silver.
And there are two good witches,
not one.
And Dorothy's not 16.
She's near your age.
Smart and brave.
If that guy finds me,
he's really gonna kill me.
He won't touch you.
I promise.
Baum, how you holding up?
Shouldn't you be digging a tunnel
out of here or something?
I'm not gonna skip out on my buddies.
I owe them this much.
Not everybody
gets to run away, you know.
Pick up the pace, Baum.
I'm not gonna carry you up this hill.
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE BLEEPING]
The Triple-8 has been to that kid's
house. It knows about the school.
How long?
Cameron says two, maybe three hours.
She's on her way.
You told me you'd throw that kid
in a hole. Babysit. Nothing complicated.
It won't touch him. I won't let it.
You better not.
Because if you do,
pray the Triple-8 gets to you before I do.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Look, I'm sorry, I didn't...
I didn't mean this.
This was never the plan. Ever.
What was the plan?
I don't know.
You can't always have one.
Not all the time. Sometimes you just do.
And I did, to you.
Well, you saved my life, right?
So good plan.
Thank you.
I said thank you.
I know, I just...
I haven't heard that in...
I haven't heard that.
"You're welcome." Say it.
You're welcome.
Now say, "Marty, let me help you
with your book report."
I can't call my mom...
...and you're not doing anything, so...
Thank you, Marty.
You're welcome.
Tonight's exercise
is a rescue extraction.
Meet Old Fred.
He weighs about 75 pounds and needs
to be carried from place to place.
This is his life's ambition.
- And I intend to help him...
DEREK: Forget that. All eyes on me.
Seniors, get your people on-line.
Ten-meter spacing. Eyes up.
- What about the obstacle course?
- New exercise.
Guy with a gun is gonna come.
Do not initiate contact.
Not even for laughs.
Are we clear?
You see him, send a signal.
If I see that hand signal
before I see our infiltrator, you win.
Exercise over.
Where will you be?
Looking for that hand signal.
You're with me.
You too.
Those are detonators.
Claymore simulators.
Here, here and here.
Wait for the signal. Watch for me to lead
the infiltrator past this line.
When he enters the kill zone,
hit the detonator...
...the simulators go off.
End of story. We go home.
Wait, sir.
The last-minute change in mission...
...pre-positioned equipment,
Claymore simulators?
What, we're not having fun?
[EXPLOSIONS & GUNFIRE]
Son of a bitch. No, no, no.
Gotta be a little more specific.
DEREK:
Stray shot from one of the kids.
Must have hit one of the EFPs.
It set them all off.
We're swinging in the wind.
- Where's the Ogre?
- Coming to kill us.
- Where do you think it is?
- Where is the tank?
About a block away.
Moving towards us.
No way
we've got enough powder to kill it.
I'm gonna lay some covering fire,
drop a couple Endos.
- That'll give Kyle time to get back.
- Reese. We can kill that Ogre.
We got one more magic bullet.
We just gotta get it out there.
MARTIN: "The Emerald City
was soon left far behind.
As they advanced, the ground
became rougher and hillier...
...for there were no farms nor houses
in this country of the West.
MARTIN: Before night,
Dorothy and Toto and the Lion...
...lay down upon the grass
and fell asleep...
...with the Woodman
and the Scarecrow keeping watch.
Now, the wicked Witch had but one eye,
yet she could see everywhere.
She saw Dorothy lying asleep,
with her friends all about her.
The Witch looked out
with her one eye.
She said to the King Crow,
'Fly at once to the strangers.
Peck out their eyes.
Tear them to pieces.'
The wild crows flew in one great flock
toward Dorothy and her companions.
When the little girl saw them coming,
she was afraid."
Come here.
"But the Scarecrow said,
'This is my battle.
Lie down beside me,
and you will not be harmed.'"
Hey! Look over here!
It's me, Connor. John Connor.
MARTIN:
"The Witch got into a terrible rage.
She couldn't understand how all her
plans to destroy the strangers had failed.
There was only one way left
to destroy Dorothy and her friends."
You want me to read for a while?
"The sky darkened, and a low
rumbling sound was heard in the air.
There was a rushing of many wings,
a great chattering and laughing...
...and the sun came
out of the dark sky...
...to show the Witch
surrounded by a crowd of monkeys.
'Go to the strangers and destroy
them all,' said the wicked Witch.
SARAH:
But Dorothy they did not harm at all.
Carefully and gently, they lifted Dorothy
in their arms and carried her to the Witch.
The Witch looked into
the child's eyes...
...and saw how simple the soul
behind them was...
...and that she did not know
of her power.
The witch said to Dorothy,
'Come with me.
For if you do not
I will make an end of you.'
The little girl grew angry.
'You are a wicked creature! ' she cried.
In her anger, she picked up
a bucket of water...
...and dashed it over the Witch,
wetting her from head to foot.
The Witch gave a cry of fear.
As Dorothy looked in wonder,
the Witch began to shrink away.
'See what you have done!'
The Witch screamed, 'I shall melt away.'
With these words,
she fell into a melted, shapeless mass.
The wicked Witch
had come to an end.
Being at last free to do as she chose,
Dorothy ran...
...no longer a prisoner
in a strange land."
Six stops down there's a pay phone
to call your mom.
You got your money?
If you get into trouble, you call me.
Say, "Book report."
Whatever it is, I'll come.
Are you a spy?
No. I'm not a spy.
Are you a mom?
Yeah, I'm a mom.
You kind of suck at it.
I know. I'm working on it.
Let's catch your bus.
MARTIN: So this...
This is what I'm supposed to do?
Stay here. Graduate.
Go to West Point like I don't know...
...the end of the world is coming?
Like any of this, any of it, really matters.
It does matter.
It all matters.
You believe that?
I've got to.
I'll see you around, Connor.
Yeah. I guess you will.
Sometimes I wish I could
just wake up from all this.
Like from a dream.
But I can't, can I?
You wanna know what happened
to Bedell? What really happened?
I don't know. Do I?
I guess it depends
on who I'm talking to.
John Baum or John Connor.
Baum is just a name.
I'll go.
- You'll never make it.
- He's my brother.
You wanna save Kyle, or die trying?
Give me the damn EFP.
Please.
I wanna take this one.
You run like hell, okay?
Bedell, you run like hell.
When this thing goes off, you pop
those wagons, you get those people out.
Don't be a hero.
Go.
DEREK:
And he ran.
He ran so fast.
Fast enough to get to that tank
before it got to Kyle's position.
Fast enough to blow it sky high.
We rescued 40 prisoners that day.
One of them was John Connor.
Martin was always a great runner.
But no one...
No one could outrun
a blast like that.
He died, John.
He died for you.
We all die for you.
[ENGLISH SDH]