NARRATOR: In the future,
a computer program called Skynet...
...will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time...
...taking human form
to terminate John Connor...
...the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor: John's mother,
teacher and protector.
Cameron: a terminator reprogrammed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese: John's uncle...
...and a commanding officer
with the Resistance.
Together, they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow
starts today.
[GRUNTING]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[PANTING]
[SCREAMS]
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
[GRUNTING AND SCREAMING]
Earth to Cameron.
What?
Are you okay?
If you're gonna try and kill me,
I wouldn't mind a head start.
If I was going to try to kill you again...
...we wouldn't
be having this conversation.
Listen, I'm gonna get some stuff
from Radio World.
I'll meet you back here in a half-hour.
Thirty minutes, I swear.
Oh, hey.
Get me some of those cheese things,
all right?
The crunchy ones, not the puffy ones.
[GRUNTING]
Okay. Hey. Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
- I just... I'm having these weird pains.
- What kind of pains?
I don't...
Just like a spicy-taco kind of pain.
But I haven't eaten any spicy tacos.
Oh, and I'm bleeding.
We need to take you to the hospital.
Thanks.
[SCANNER BEEPING]
[GRUNTING THEN SCREAMS]
Miss?
Are you all right?
Someone get the manager.
MAN:
You been drinking?
Taking drugs?
You got a wallet
or some kind of ID on you?
What's your name?
My name?
Why should I tell you?
WOMAN:
If you don't, we'll give you one.
Go ahead. I'm dying to hear it.
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
[SCREAMING]
Alison. Alison Young.
So, what are you in for?
I was in a store...
...and I couldn't remember anything.
Blackouts. Been there, done them.
Can tattoos disappear?
Sure. I got two of my exes
lasered off.
Ryan was right here...
...and Jose, ha, was here.
- Next time, I'm thinking henna.
- Henna?
[CHUCKLES]
I'm Jody.
I'm...
...Alison.
Hmm. Placenta's still attached.
There's no previa...
...no evidence of major abruption.
So everything's fine?
I wanna run a Kleihauer-Betke
to rule out fetal blood cells.
What does that mean?
We wanna make sure the blood
is yours.
Well, what if it is the baby's?
Then we do an emergency C-section.
But let's not get ahead of ourselves.
That didn't sound good.
No, it didn't.
Hey, look, I know you're busy,
so if you need to go...
- Can I call someone?
- You mean, like the father?
I'll be fine.
Go.
- What happened here?
- Some girl totally wigged out.
What do you mean "wigged out"?
She's on drugs or something.
She couldn't even remember
her own name.
What'd she look like?
I'm gonna guess, like, 16, 17.
Brown hair. Maybe like 5'8" or...
Where is she now?
Cops took her.
Store owner's not pressing charges.
I don't wanna see you back here.
And you. I'm sick of you.
This is your last "get out of jail free."
Hey, where you headed?
- I don't know.
- Good.
Why good?
Because you're coming with me.
OFFICER 1:
All right.
OFFICER 2:
That's fine.
Hey, uh, I'm looking for my sister.
She was picked up at the Food Mart
on Van Nuys.
Yeah, that one.
We released her about an hour ago.
Did she say where she was going?
I'm sorry,
but I really need to find her, okay?
She's on medication.
My mom's gonna kill me.
She might kill her, actually.
She left with
one of the street kids. Jody.
Do you know where Jody hangs out?
Usually gets popped
along the boulevard.
All right, thanks.
It's a boy, you know.
A boy is good.
I hate being trapped in bed...
...feeling like there's nothing I can do.
If you can't protect them
when they're inside you...
...how can you ever protect them?
What was yours like?
When John was born?
I was, um, living in Central America
at the time.
We were hiking in the jungle
when my water broke.
Tried to get to town,
but there wasn't time.
- Did you have anything for the pain?
- Bottle of dark rum.
[CHUCKLES]
And John's father?
He was right there with me.
I remember holding his hand
really tight.
Gosh. How did you finally
get out of there?
Hitched a ride on a chicken bus.
Tobacco farmer handed out cigars.
We smoked
and then sang this birthday song.
Oh, sing a little bit for me.
My Spanish is rusty,
and I've never been able to sing, so...
So?
[SINGING IN SPANISH]
[CHUCKLING THEN
KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Kacy?
I heard you were here.
I was worried.
- Is everything, uh...?
- We're waiting on some test results.
- I'm Trevor.
- Sarah.
I should go.
KACY:
Um...
Unless you need something else?
Maybe some magazines?
Jody? Don't know Jody?
MAN: No.
- Hey, do you know a girl named Jody?
- Sorry, no, no.
Do you know a Jody?
Do you know Jody?
WOMAN 1:
No, I don't.
Hey, do you know a girl named Jody?
Do you know someone named Jody?
WOMAN 2: No.
WOMAN 3: We don't.
[BABIES CRYING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
JOHN: Hey.
- Hey.
- Just checking in. What are you doing?
- Uh, nothing. Cameron and I are shopping.
- What are you doing?
- I took Kacy to the hospital.
Is she okay?
SARAH [OVER PHONE]: They're running tests.
- I'm gonna be a while.
- Well, how long?
I don't know. Why?
Delicious.
- Who was that?
- Nobody. I gotta go.
ELLISON: Thank you for taking the time
to see me.
I understand your reluctance
to discuss these things over the phone.
But I'm pleased
you're still considering my job offer.
I am. Thank you.
I appreciate a man who's calm
and careful in his decision-making.
The last time I went hunting
for these things you want me to hunt...
...20 good people died.
I won't let that happen again.
- Nor should you.
- These things...
...they're evil.
We have to be careful
not to anthropomorphize a machine.
These are more than machines,
Ms. Weaver.
But I never make the mistake
of thinking they're human.
Two years ago, my husband and I
were in a helicopter accident.
- He was killed.
- I'm sorry.
He was flying us to Barstow.
There was a microchip plant there
doing some amazing things.
So your husband was a pilot?
He had over 700 hours
on that particular helicopter.
It was his passion.
If this is difficult for you...
The Kuleshov A-85
is a beautiful flying machine.
Like the most perfect bird.
It's almost flawless in its design.
Almost flawless?
It needs a human to fly it.
Are you saying that machines
make better decisions than humans?
What I think...
...is that
in certain extreme conditions...
...even the most calm
and careful of men panic.
Help me find this machine, agent.
You and I will take it apart
piece by piece.
I'm not sure what we'll find.
But I doubt we'll find evil.
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS IN DISTANCE]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
So much food.
I know. We're totally puking later,
but whatever. It's an occasion.
- I like your necklace.
- It's cool, huh?
I got it from this awesome thrift store
in Echo Park.
So...
...two years ago,
when I moved here from Michigan...
...I had this internship
at a storefront in Chinatown.
But the designer
was this total druggie.
When I finally called him out on what
a stuck-up and talentless bitch he was...
...I got "fired" from my unpaid job.
That's when I started crashing
with people...
...and doing, you know, whatever
for money...
...which got sketchy real quick...
...especially in L.A.
This city is like a freak magnet.
You'd look really pretty in this.
MAN:
Hey, Jody.
- We should bounce.
- How much did you get?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- My laptop?
I didn't take your laptop.
Oh, weird. It just disappeared
the same day you left.
Okay, look...
[GRUNTING]
Who are you, huh?
You a little thief too?
Huh?
Just take it. Go.
Please, just go.
And next time I see you,
you better have me something.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
All I'm saying is,
you gotta take a punch once in a while...
...in order to keep the cash.
That was a lot of cash.
I'm sorry.
Fill it out so we can
crash here for a couple nights.
- I don't know what to write.
- It doesn't matter. Lie.
The other catch is, you have to have
this interview with a counselor.
Just B.S. your way through it.
Don't tell them anything real.
Nice.
Where'd you learn how to do that?
I don't know.
You weren't, like...
...getting beaten up or anything,
were you?
Sorry about that thing I said earlier
about taking the punch.
If you've gotten your fill,
I shouldn't have said it.
But don't worry.
From now on...
...I got your back.
Wasn't easy getting that shot.
Where was it?
Tanzania.
Paul and I just got back
a couple of weeks ago.
But you didn't come here
to talk about zebras.
I was hoping you could run a check
on someone for me.
- Off the record.
- Who is it?
Catherine Weaver. Zeira Corp.
- What's your interest in her?
- Actually, she's interested in me.
She offered me a job.
- You're leaving the bureau?
- It's just an offer, Lila.
You're not wearing your cross.
- How do you know?
- The way you're carrying yourself.
What happened in North Hollywood...
...that wasn't your fault.
WOMAN:
Agent Ellison?
- Got those updated 302s for you.
- Thank you, Liz.
Glad you kept the name.
It's a good name.
WOMAN:
Where are you from, Alison?
I don't remember.
COUNSELOR:
Where are you from, Alison?
I don't remember.
Don't remember
what town you're from?
Why does it matter?
It's not there anymore.
COUNSELOR:
You know...
...sometimes when people forget,
it's because they need to forget.
Because something painful
has happened.
I'm wondering
if something has happened to you.
[ROARS]
WOMAN:
Tell me about your life.
I live in a tunnel.
I eat garbage for dinner.
COUNSELOR: Anything you say in here
is confidential.
The only exception is
if you were planning to harm someone.
- I would have to report that.
- I would never hurt anyone.
WOMAN:
Tell me about your family.
COUNSELOR:
Memory is a very associative thing.
Sometimes sights, sounds...
...even a smell could take us back.
My father was an architect.
He taught me how to draw.
My mother was a music teacher.
She'd sit for hours
and listen to Chopin.
WOMAN:
What's that bracelet on your arm?
My sister gave it to me
for my birthday.
July 22nd.
I had a party in Griffith Park.
All my friends were there.
I saw a boy ride by
on his silver mountain bike.
And I told my dad...
...that's what I want.
And he said, "Next year."
But I didn't have a party the next year.
No one did.
WOMAN:
Why not?
Everyone was dead.
[CRYING]
COUNSELOR:
Why not?
It's a Balinese tiger.
Have you ever seen a real one?
Unfortunately, they were hunted
to extinction in the '30s.
Do you ever think
that could happen to us?
To humans?
COUNSELOR:
Is that something you worry about?
I wanna go home.
WOMAN:
Where is home?
Palmdale.
COUNSELOR: Palmdale?
- That's where I'm from.
Hey, do you know a Jody,
by any chance? Jody?
Do you know a Jody?
- Anybody know a Jody?
- Yeah, I know her.
- Yeah, she was here earlier.
- Do you know where she went?
No. Oh, but she hangs out at this
halfway house sometimes on Yucca.
Yucca. Thanks.
KACY:
Hungry?
- Split my Jell-O with you.
- Where's Trevor?
He went to go get me some real food.
He's the baby daddy,
in case you didn't figure that out.
- You never mentioned him.
- We've been on and off.
He freaked when I got pregnant, but...
...now he's here. I don't know.
I just want life to be perfect for him.
You know?
Didn't you feel that way?
Don't get me wrong. I'm not an idiot.
I know it'll never be perfect.
It's just...
Right now...
...in there...
...no one's ever made fun of him...
...turned him down for a date.
How long does he have, really...
...until he figures out
how hard it can all be?
[RINGING]
- Hello?
- Mom?
It's me...
...Alison.
I'm sorry.
You must have the wrong number.
- Mrs. Young?
- Yes.
- This is Claire Young.
- I'm here with your daughter.
There must be some mistake.
I don't have a daughter.
Not yet.
Very pretty name, though. Alison.
She didn't even know who I was.
Parents suck.
Especially mothers.
Why would she do that to me?
Who knows
why anyone does anything?
Come on.
Let's go have some fun.
Hey.
KACY: Hey.
Ah-ah. Sit.
Eat. I insist.
Thank you.
You like tri-tip?
I grill a mean tri-tip.
We could do a barbecue
with you and your kids. Uh...
John and...
What's the girl's name again?
Cameron.
TREVOR: I can't wait to meet them.
If you want, I can take John
to the range with me sometime.
He's not much of a golfer.
TREVOR: Me neither.
Guns.
Trevor's a cop.
TREVOR:
Detective.
L.A.P.D.
We got the results.
Cells were all maternal.
The baby's fine.
We need to keep you overnight,
but you can go home tomorrow.
I knew it. He's a fighter, this kid.
Just like his mama.
No criminal history.
No pending SEC investigations,
nothing from FinCEN.
Her CTRs all check out.
Not even a civil suit.
- That's good to know.
- James.
Before you make a huge change, don't
you think you should talk to someone?
Marshall Weaver's helicopter crash
was due to mechanical failure?
You're not listening to me.
I talked to a couple of people.
- It's possible you're suffering from...
- What people?
- Paul?
- He served in the Persian Gulf.
He's got experience
with this kind of thing.
- I came to you in confidence.
- I'm worried about you, James.
I've never seen you in so much pain.
Now, we both know that's not true.
Thank you for the report.
CAMERON:
Jody, no.
[CAMERON GRUNTING AND
JODY LAUGHING]
JODY: Oh!
CAMERON: Okay, okay.
JODY:
No, no, no.
Yes. I'm gonna go get a soda.
JOHN:
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
- Playing foosball.
- We've gotta go.
Go where?
- Home.
- Home?
Who are you?
Cameron.
My name's Alison.
No. It's not. It's Cameron.
I can't explain this to you right now.
- We have to go before Mom gets home.
- You're freaking me out.
I'm freaking you out?
- Do you really not know who you are?
- I'm Alison.
- From Palmdale.
- You're not Alison.
You're not from Palmdale.
You're from the future.
- You're a machine.
- A what?
Your chip is messed up. I can fix you.
I fixed you once, remember?
Fix me?
Why would you fix me?
[ALARM BLARING]
[GRUNTING]
MAN 1:
Get out.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
WOMAN 1: What do you want here?
Get away from here.
WOMAN 2:
Please, get out.
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN 2:
Out.
Go.
WOMAN 3:
Get out. Get out.
[GRUNTING]
[SHRIEKING]
[ROARS]
[ROARING]
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
[GRUNTING]
- We have to get out.
- What did you do? Did you hurt me?
JODY:
Is there a problem?
No, I'm her brother, John Baum.
I don't have a brother.
Look, dude, I don't know who you are,
but I really think...
[GRUNTING]
MAN:
Sir, you need to leave.
[GRUNTING]
[CRYING]
You shouldn't have run.
You're just making things worse
for yourself.
CAMERON:
Your hair.
It's so pretty.
We work very hard on the hair.
To get it right.
I'm not your enemy.
- Right.
- I want to get to know you.
You're very brave.
That must be why
John Connor chose you.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- I admire him.
His determination. His spirit.
His fearlessness.
- I'd like to meet him.
- He wouldn't wanna meet you.
They're going to kill you.
They're going to kill every one of you.
They'll hunt you down
until every human is gone...
...and you're extinct.
Then why are we having
this conversation?
Because some of us don't want that.
Some of us want peace.
You were chosen, Alison.
Not just by John Connor.
By us.
Tell me where his camp is.
I think...
...I'm a machine.
COUNSELOR: A machine?
What kind of machine?
From the future.
What do you do in the future?
- I'm an infiltrator.
- What do you infiltrate?
The Human Resistance.
I see.
Why?
- It's what I was programmed for.
- Programmed?
To find John Connor.
Why is he so important?
- He's the one who saves mankind.
- Saves them?
- From what?
- Extinction.
And what are you gonna do
when you find John Connor?
I'm going to kill him...
...and hang his head on a pike
for all to see.
Your hair.
It's so pretty.
Thanks.
Tell me about your life.
Why?
- I want to get to know you.
- I don't really like talking about my past.
I came to L.A. to start over.
Did you?
Yeah.
Burned a lot of bridges here, though.
I keep thinking I'm gonna go
someplace more authentic.
Like Portland.
I could come with you.
We could reinvent ourselves.
We could.
So who are you, really?
I've never heard of you.
Suddenly, your Kacy's best friend?
- I'm just a neighbor.
- Huh.
Sorry. Cop brain.
Stresses her, you know? My job.
You'd think having a cop around
would make her feel safe.
- She's afraid it'll follow me back home.
- Does it?
I can protect them.
It's your family, right?
You do what it takes.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Sorry.
Yep.
Right. Damn.
That was a robbery-homicide downtown.
I'm gonna have to take off.
What about tomorrow?
She's gonna need a ride.
I'll be here.
I just... I hate for her
to spend the night alone.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Agent Ellison. Come in.
This is my daughter, Savannah.
ELLISON:
Savannah.
Sudoku. I used to love these.
You have children, Agent Ellison?
Um, no.
- Do you want them?
- I did. Once.
Very much.
But my wife, um...
Well, my ex-wife...
It wasn't meant to be.
Bye, Savannah.
Your husband's helicopter crash.
I read the official report.
The NTSB concluded
that mechanical failure was to blame.
Mechanical failure.
Correct.
That's not what you led me to believe
the other day.
Correct.
Which is it?
What's the truth?
You tell me.
I think...
...what people write in reports...
...what is official, isn't always true.
I think if I had a child...
...one that I knew would grow up
asking what happened to her daddy...
...I think I would make sure
that answer...
...the official answer...
...was the one
I would want her to hear.
And I think you saw what you saw.
Just as you saw what you saw.
When can I start?
I used to baby-sit for this family
five years ago. They're loaded.
You said you moved here
two years ago from Michigan.
They usually
hide a key here somewhere.
Sweet. You are jacked, girl.
CAMERON:
Look for cash and jewelry.
JODY:
Check this out.
I saw the lady open it.
And I memorized the combination.
Just put it all in the bag.
What are these?
Whatever. Just put them in the bag.
They're the same
as the necklace you gave me.
Because I stole it when I worked here.
You said:
"I got it at this awesome thrift store
in Echo Park."
[SCOFFS]
Tell me about the necklace.
Why are you making such a big deal
out of this?
Tell me about the necklace.
I didn't buy it or steal it, okay?
It's mine.
This is my parents' house.
CAMERON:
You lied to me.
I told you where the camp was.
You told me
your sister gave you that bracelet.
What does that have to do
with anything?
We found these
on some of your friends.
Why are you all wearing them?
It has something to do
with the Connor camp.
No.
It's a pass.
To get into the camp.
You were going to send me without it.
They would have known what I was.
You lied to me.
[GRUNTING]
I'll never help you get to John Connor.
[BONES SNAP]
You already did.
- You lied to me.
- I'm from L.A., okay?
Let's go.
Tell me who you are.
I went to CalArts for two years...
...and got kicked out,
which was for the best...
...because that place is a factory.
And my parents cut me off, like yours.
And just pretend I don't exist.
We have to go. Now.
CAMERON:
Why?
Because there's a silent alarm,
and we tripped it when we walked in.
You weren't going to tell me.
- Police are gonna be here any second.
- We were never going to Portland.
You were gonna run and leave me here
to take the blame.
No.
You lied to me.
[GRUNTING]
I'll never help you get to John Connor.
[BONES SNAP]
No, no, no. What did you do?
What did you do?
We have to go. John.
We have to go.
Did you kill her?
[GASPING]
Apparently not.
KACY: Hey.
- Hey.
- Where's Trevor?
- He was called in to work.
He'll be back tomorrow
to take you home.
What's wrong?
It wasn't him that freaked out.
It was me.
When I found out I was pregnant.
- The cop thing. He told me.
- Yeah.
The cop thing.
It's kind of cool and sexy...
...when you're a 25-year-old pastry chef
making gourmet doughnuts...
...at this hip cop hangout
in Silver Lake.
When you think
about breast-feeding your baby boy...
...next to the walkie and the 9 mm...
Still.
He's a good man.
He'll be a good dad.
Kacy, I have to tell you something.
That story about John's birth,
it wasn't true.
- The jungle?
- Well, that part was true.
The part about his father wasn't.
He wasn't there with me.
He died before John was born.
Before I even knew I was pregnant.
Why did you tell me that story?
Because I wished
it's the way it could've been.
That's the saddest thing
I've ever heard.
The thing is, I got through it. All of it.
By myself. And so can you.
Besides, you won't be alone.
I'll be right next door.
That was my last "get out of jail free."
Damn right.
Where'd you get that?
I got it at this awesome thrift store
in Echo Park.