DEREK:
217, yeah, I'm here.
Where are you?
You're hunting it?
How do you know it's not hunting you?
Hello?
Hello? Sarah?
You're breaking up. Hello?
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[WOMAN GROANING]
[WHEEZING]
Whoa, hey, easy, easy, easy.
Sarah Connor sent me, okay?
I'm here to help.
Sorry. I thought...
I know what you thought.
You'd be dead already.
All right.
- How far along?
- Thirty-four weeks.
DEREK:
Okay.
[WHIMPERING]
All right. Looks like a through-and-through.
Caught her lung.
LAUREN:
I know, I need to put the tube in.
Look, you... Just hold her still.
You stay still also.
I'm fine, okay? I'm fine.
Okay, ready?
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
There you go.
- You wanna tell me what happened?
- That thing. The cyborg.
It's been tracking us for six months.
How'd it find you?
How do you know Sarah?
Hey.
Lauren, we don't live in a barn.
We close the door and we wipe our feet.
- They're alive.
- Are you the Fields?
Lauren, go to your room
and lock the door.
- What do you want?
- I'm here to help. Are you the Fields?
- Anne, call 911.
- No, no police.
Go get the girl back.
I need to get you out.
Someone is coming.
- I'm not here to rob you.
- Then put down the gun.
You don't understand. You're in danger.
We need to go.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Just stand there.
We had a hit of a name on the list.
Alpine Fields, it's a family.
Everything's under control.
We might be late. Can you handle dinner?
John, just put the alarm on.
Teenagers, huh?
LAUREN: Don't move.
Put the gun down.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
Tell me the truth.
The truth?
In the near future, a computer system
called Skynet takes over the world.
It sends humanoid machines back in time
to eliminate anyone who's a threat.
I have a target list. Your name is on it.
A machine is coming to kill you.
It found your house in the city,
now it's coming here.
- Your house sitter's dead.
- Call the police.
Tell them there's a crazy woman
in the house with a gun.
You. Stand over here with her.
Hey, we're going, now.
Now.
[DOG BARKING]
- What about Charles Barkley?
- No.
- Why would you keep a gun in the house?
- Maybe for a situation like this. Or a bear.
This wouldn't work
in a situation like this.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Or a bear.
I knew you'd react like this.
This is not helping.
- Does your son know you kidnap people?
- Yes.
- You know he'll be prone to delinquency.
- Mom, it's obvious she's beyond Dr. Phil.
- You know, this is none of your business.
- Sarah.
[ANNE & DAVID SCREAM]
LAUREN: Come on. Come on, Dad. Let's go.
SARAH: Out.
Get back to the cabin, now.
DAVID: Let's go.
SARAH:
Run!
DAVID:
I'm coming, I'm behind you.
[GUNSHOTS]
[GUN CLICKING]
[WHIMPERING]
DEREK:
I'm sorry.
You should keep that covered.
It's a Saint Jude's medal.
It's my grandmother's.
It's a target.
Where'd you get it?
One of them.
Oh.
- Do I wanna know?
- Not really.
You sound so used to all this.
You don't get used to it.
You live through it.
You sound like David.
We were outside a motel in Elko
when it found us.
Dad emptied the Mossberg
into that thing.
And then he went after it
with a table lamp and a curtain rod.
Just long enough for us to get out.
She told us to call if it came back.
Do you think David could be all right?
Anything's possible.
What?
Nothing.
I just know that look.
DEREK: Your plan sucks.
You can't use metal for this.
PERRY: Look, they hit Eagle Rock Bunker with
a bio weapon that killed everybody inside.
Only one person survived out of 200.
Now, we need her back here alive.
Metal's immune to disease, so we're...
Tin cans are immune to disease,
but not immune to going bad...
...and putting a bullet in the person
who could save us from this plague.
I'll find the survivor. I'll bring her back.
Just hope like hell she can help us.
Once exposed, there's no way to know
how long you've got.
Could be four hours till the symptoms hit,
20 before the bug kills you.
- This could be a one-way trip.
- We're all one-way trips.
He's not out there, you know.
Your brother Kyle. He's gone, Reese.
Now, either you learn
to live with that...
...or die from it.
She's sleeping now.
So you wanna tell me how it found you?
It's best if I know.
It was my fault.
I used the phone.
I called a friend. Roger.
I guess...
...I needed to feel normal, you know?
Like a person.
- So you broke the rules.
- Yeah.
And rule number one is
there is no normal.
Down, down, down.
I think I messed up my ankle.
DAVID:
What the hell was that?
The thing from the future.
We need to get him to a hospital.
We need to call the police.
No. You call the police, police come,
that thing kills them. I need tape.
We have to get out. Your car's outside.
We can just take your car.
The road's blocked. It's out there.
We won't be going that way.
- Is there another road out of here?
- No. Schafer's got a road...
...but it's a mile through the woods,
and I don't think he's there.
[GAGGING AND GROANING]
ANNE:
Oh, God.
Can you stand?
[GRUNTING]
Barely.
Leave me. Head for Schafer's place.
See if you can get down that way.
ANNE: David, we're a mess.
- We can't run a mile through the woods.
- No one gets left behind.
- What about your daughter?
- She's not my daughter.
She's one of them from the future.
No freaking way.
SARAH: She's on our side.
I need to know which one of you
that thing is after.
Which one?
That thing wants one of you dead.
I need to know why.
Either of you deal with computers,
technology, the military, anything?
I'm a banker. She's a housewife.
She's nothing.
LAUREN: Hey.
DAVID:
You know what I mean.
ANNE:
It's a mistake. We're normal people.
Here, do you want your Oxy, honey?
I have a bulging disc.
L4. Look...
...we don't know what we did, all right?
We can't help you. I'm sorry.
- What's this door handle made of?
- It's oil-rubbed copper.
Why?
[DOOR CLICKS]
I wanted to see if I could help.
You can look for flashlights.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna set a trap.
Do you have any hole-saw bits?
A metal cylinder with teeth?
Like for making holes for birdhouses?
I don't know. I don't make birdhouses.
Me and my dad have made a million.
Still waiting for
our first bird family to move in.
- That sounds so lame, right?
- Why would that sound lame?
Because you're running around
with guns, fighting robots.
Cybernetic organisms.
The outside is very real.
You're fighting cyborgs,
and we're building birdhouses.
I'd trade for birdhouses any time.
What's it like? I mean...
...doing what you do. It must be...
Why'd you come out here?
You stand there like you're gonna
tell me a secret, but you don't.
My son does that.
You really do this? With a kid?
He's why I do this.
Is that it?
It's my dad.
There's something he's not telling you.
SARAH:
Syndyne. Tell me about it.
Syndyne Cybernetics, the company
you've been working with.
Cybernetics? What are you
talking about? David?
Computers, cyborgs, the future.
Your husband's been holding out.
Okay, yeah, the tech company
is one of my clients.
LAUREN:
These are the e-mails.
This is what I asked for.
Why didn't you tell me?
It's just business. It doesn't have
anything to do with robots.
Cyborgs.
- What were you doing?
- Business.
Banking. Why do you need to know?
Because I'm not here just to be nice
and help your nice family.
I'm trying to stop the end of the world
from happening and save my family.
So I need to know what Skynet's doing
and why they'd want you dead.
Why don't you just tell her, David?
Because it's not exactly legal, okay?
ANNE:
Why didn't you tell me, David?
DAVID: What part of "secret" and "illegal"
do you not understand?
So this was an actual crime?
And what are you doing
on my computer?
Looking at lesbian porn.
What's the difference?
You're gay?
ANNE: Lauren?
God, people, no. Thanks for knowing me.
ANNE: Well, I'm sorry, but apparently your
father is some sort of criminal mastermind.
[CREAKING]
DAVID: Anne, you have no idea what it...
ANNE: Is any of this real?
Quiet!
This is very real.
What is it?
- Is something happening?
- They're hunting.
Hunting what?
Each other.
So are we safe?
No one is ever safe.
I'm sorry. I need some air.
You know how to use this?
If you do, take it. If you don't, leave it.
You don't go outside without it.
DEREK:
Hello?
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Oh, jeez.
WOMAN:
Excuse me.
Your fly's open.
Sorry. This keeps reopening.
You need to lie still.
Where is she? Where is Lauren?
She went out for some air.
And you let her?
With that thing out there?
Your kid will be fine.
Lauren? She hasn't been
a kid for months.
It's easy to think, and it's easy to say.
It's not always so.
What do you know about it?
I know she's protecting you.
I know that story she told me
about calling that Roger guy was crap.
She's too smart to call anybody.
But somebody called Roger.
And I'm guessing it was you.
Kids can adapt to all this.
It's harder for adults.
DAVID: Is it necessary to destroy
the entire house?
David, you got us into this.
Let her do her job.
- What can I do?
- In the bag, give me the black tape.
You never asked
where the money came from.
I assumed you were earning it.
- Now what?
- I'm going to the bathroom. Is that okay?
- What'll that do?
- There's a chip in their head.
The shock will trigger a reboot.
If one of them touches this door handle,
we have two minutes to get the chip out.
Does that work?
SARAH: I've only tried it on the girl.
And, no, it doesn't always work.
So, what guarantees
he comes through the front door?
They always come through
the front door.
I didn't know the lights worked.
I switched the breakers back.
Who you calling?
No one. Sorry.
I'm just checking the phone line.
I'm scared.
- Hawaii?
- Yes.
- Are you married to your son's...?
- No. Barely knew him.
Lucky you. You think you're getting this,
then you realize you got that.
- Don't worry about the past.
- It's easy for you to say.
I'm not like you. I'm just normal.
I was normal. All this I had to learn.
I thought crisis was supposed
to bring a family closer.
Don't confuse close with happy.
LAUREN:
Hey, I see something.
I saw something.
I think someone's coming.
It's not her. It's a man.
- I think it's Mr. Schafer.
- Who?
- It's Roger from the next property over.
- It's okay. We know him.
These things can look like anyone.
- Friends, neighbors.
- I told Roger we were camping this weekend.
[DOG BARKING]
LAUREN:
Charles!
- Dogs can smell these things.
- It's him.
- What would he be doing?
- That's him.
- How could you know?
- The shock will kill him.
SARAH: Wait.
DAVID: Anne, you don't know...
- Hey, Annie.
- Roger, get inside!
[BARKING]
He's coming to see me, okay?
She never goes camping.
She keeps the home fires going.
With Roger?
Don't confuse close with happy.
I know it was stupid...
...but I needed...
...to let him know...
...and now he's dead.
And David is dead. I know he is.
I had no idea what happy was.
It's funny, the things you say to yourself.
"Oh, I've seen worse." "It'll be fine."
"Can't happen to me."
But the worst is always out there,
isn't it?
And it can happen to you,
and it isn't fun.
[CRYING]
Even after everything,
she's still trying to cover for me.
Protect my dignity, I guess.
She needs it to be normal.
She needs it to be good...
...or seem that way.
All right. I'm done.
No more talking, okay?
It's gonna get your heart rate up.
It's not good.
Doesn't matter. Lauren matters
and this baby matters.
They're all that's gonna be left of me
after this is over.
[WHEEZING]
A mother knows.
You the one? Who sent the signal?
No.
My shore party picked up a coded SOS
about 45 ticks back.
Sent me to fossick around.
What's that in English?
Means someone's still alive inside.
Probably a civilian. Probably hiding.
Radio room, I'm guessing.
I didn't go in that far.
What'd you say about a shore party?
Been making troop and supply runs back
and forth from Perth for months.
Seawolf sub. The Jimmy Carter.
You've got a nuclear sub? Who drives it?
Not who. What.
We got a scrubbed Trip-8 for a captain.
You've got metal running a sub. Huh.
Well, you find me a sub commander
who survived J-day, I'll switch him in.
Have a little faith, mate. She'll be apples.
Means we'll be all right.
You believe that?
- Sure as my mother loves me.
- My mother's dead.
Here.
- Gas?
- Bugs.
This gonna work?
Probably not.
DEREK:
Come on, come on.
[BANGING ON METAL]
[SCREAMING]
We need to get her to a hospital.
ANNE: This isn't like last time.
It's not gonna happen.
- She needs a doctor. A real doctor.
- She needs you to keep it together.
- Oh, yeah? Who put you in charge?
- You did, just now.
Until Sarah comes through that door,
the safest place in the world is here.
They can't kill it. They couldn't
kill it before, they can't now.
Baby. Baby, I'm sorry.
- When did this affair start?
- You wanna talk about this now?
- Last summer when I couldn't travel?
- You have a bulging disc from sleeping.
- I slipped and fell...
- You have a weak core.
- Well, at least my core isn't a slut.
- Hophead.
- Whore!
- Hey. That is your wife.
Hey, don't you...
- Hey.
- Hey. Damn it.
Fuses are fried.
Not sure I can get the power rerouted.
And who is this, again?
Sarah. She saved our lives.
From the guy who looks like a guy
but is a robot?
- It's real, Roger.
- A real man, maybe.
- But, Anne, robots?
- The correct term is "cyborg."
SARAH:
Roger?
Did you drive here?
No, but I got the 540 at my place.
A mile away, and we're out of here.
With that thing out there,
we'll never make it.
Fine, David. I'll carry you.
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
Right, right. Cyborgs. Anne, look at me.
She's a crazy woman.
The guy in the woods is probably
her meth-head boyfriend or something.
This is what we're gonna do.
Come to my place. We'll head into town,
get everyone fixed up...
[BARKING]
...and then we'll talk all this through
like adults.
- What the hell is that?
- It's one of those things.
- Is it dead?
- I hope not.
This is a good one. Is she?
- I don't think so.
- Can you turn her back on?
[DOG WHIMPERS]
It's coming!
ANNE:
Roger.
Roger!
- What are you doing?
- I'm the one it wants.
- Somebody's gotta do something.
- Can't let you do that.
Lady, I don't give a damn about Skynet,
or whatever the hell it is you're selling.
I'm trying to save my family.
So let me go out there and do it,
or I'll do it right here.
Daddy.
I'm sorry.
For everything.
[GRUNTING]
Hey. I'm David Fields, the one you want.
Take me. Leave my family.
That's right.
Do me a favor.
It's not him. It's after one of you.
Someone's not telling me something.
I can't help you both run.
Anne?
David doesn't know. It's not his.
You're pregnant?
Go. Stay in here.
Don't make a sound. I'm gonna
help your mom get to Roger's car.
Wait. No, you can't.
It's after you. She'll be safe here.
Mom, I get it. I'll be okay.
- You sure?
- I mean, I'd rather be making birdhouses.
Me too.
Okay, Anne. Let's go.
[ANNE SCREAMS]
I did this to you. I'm sorry.
- What is this about?
- You wanna know what this is about?
This is about your mother
and your baby sister...
...and they need you right now.
My baby sister? What...? How do you...?
Oh, God. You're from the future.
Your sister's name is Sydney...
...and I knew her.
Those gas masks, they won't help.
You're already infected.
Sun's up.
We can't move out till night.
That's when the tin cans
switch to infrared.
Guess we'll just have to
sit it out and wait.
When we get to Serrano Point,
they can cure this thing?
DEREK:
Let's just get to Serrano first.
What is this?
JESSE: Plumpy'nut.
Peanut butter mixed with baby formula
and vitamin powder.
Slept on top of a pallet of it
on the trip over from Perth.
- You guys are growing food again?
- Yeah. Beats chasing rabbits.
Rabbits?
Thought Australia was all wombats
and wallabies and stuff.
No.
Some whacker brought them over
in the 1800s.
We've been overrun with them ever since.
Tried everything to kill the things.
Trapped them, shot them, poisoned them.
Built a fence across half the country
to keep them out.
In the 1950s, they even introduced
a virus to wipe them out forever.
Killed most of them,
but a couple were immune...
...so 10 years later, Oz was up
to its eyeballs in rabbits again.
Tough little bastards.
That's why you have to
cook them longer.
Can you pass me your water?
I'm parched.
Let's go.
In broad daylight?
Just because you're death-crazy
doesn't mean we've enlisted.
SYDNEY:
It starts with a dry mouth.
And then the sweats.
Then the fever and shaking starts.
And then your lungs fill up with fluid,
and then you die.
You don't have much time.
It's coming.
Let's go.
ANNE:
So you're...
...from the future, like them?
Like those machines?
Yeah. Yeah, like them.
And in the future, you know my baby.
So does that mean she makes it?
Your daughter Sydney
has an immunity in her blood.
She helps us cure a deadly disease.
She saves a lot of lives.
Sydney.
[CHUCKLING]
And Lauren? Does she save her too?
[GASPS THEN SCREAMS]
[FOOTSTEPS THEN DOORKNOB RATTLES]
[GRUNTING]
- He's human?
- Yes, of course.
My mistake.
Come on. Come on, get in.
Go around, go around.
[SCREAMS]
She's fully dilated.
You have to do this, baby.
You have to do this.
My sister's coming.
[CRYING]
You know what Oscar Wilde's
last words were?
"Either the wallpaper goes, or I do."
I thought it'd be over by now.
You're ready for it.
No.
No, I'm not.
Then what were you doing
when I found you outside Eagle Rock?
I think...
...I was waiting for you.
[COUGHING]
Thank you for saving my sister.
I've been where you are.
There are days when you don't think
you can go on, but you will...
...because she needs you to.
We all do.
But even if they kill that thing,
there's more, aren't there?
Does it ever end?
I don't know.
We're trying.
Come stay with us.
- I don't know.
- Think about it.
I have to do this.
[CRYING]
Did you get it? I mean,
when this happened to you...
...how long until you knew
everything was gonna be different?
Right away.
I don't know if they get it.
They'll need your help.
They always have.
Sarah. Hey. Yeah, I'm still here.
Did you get the Triple-8? Are you sure?
Yeah, that does sound pretty sure.
Um...
Baby's fine.
Girl's a tough kid.
I told her she could come stay with us.
Well, it can't get much worse, can it?
Yeah. Yeah, call me when you get back.
Lauren, I...