NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
SARAH:
I'm thinking I love you.
Always remember that.
You wanna stop Skynet? This is the way.
CHARLIE: Eight years.
- I didn't wanna leave you.
I didn't have a choice.
- You're married?
- Yeah, I am.
When we jumped through time,
I died of cancer.
Yes, 2005.
- Am I still gonna get sick?
- I don't know.
- Aah!
- She's bleeding out.
SARAH:
There's a warehouse in the desert.
Everybody who knew
about the factory is dead.
Well, I'm not.
Kaliba was building something.
Hey, baby.
You were pregnant. Now you aren't.
You care about this girl?
JOHN: Yeah.
She's a security risk.
- What are you doing?
- Moving.
Yeah, well, seems about the right time
for that.
SARAH:
When John was a child...
...the legends of the jungle
were his fairy tales.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
His favorite was
the story of El Viejo del Monte.
The Old Man of the Forest.
A merciless hunter
who killed every animal in his path.
El Viejo didn't eat his prey.
He left it behind to rot in the soil.
To teach him a lesson,
the gods turned him into a simisco...
...half animal, half man.
[BIRD SCREECHING]
[WINGS FLAPPING]
He was condemned
to defend the jungle for all eternity.
JOHN:
Mom. Mom.
This was El Viejo's punishment.
This was his curse.
To forever be vigilant.
To forever protect.
Look.
[CHIRPING]
We have to keep moving.
Why are we so far from camp?
I told you, it's part of the game.
You mean training.
Well, if we call it a game, it's more fun.
But it's not a game.
The point...
...is listen to me.
I always listen. You don't talk that much.
JOHN:
We gotta go.
How long will it take you
to pack up the storage locker?
A while. There's some explosives
that need securing.
Make sure you get to the safe house
before night.
It can be hard to find.
- I can follow directions.
- Well, you can also make mistakes.
Wouldn't want anyone else hurt
because of them.
CAMERON:
Thirty-three-42-31 north.
The safe house coordinates.
It's in the desert.
You like the desert.
Things happen out there.
Things happen here too.
We're starting over.
Whatever happened here
is no one's fault.
Let's get out of here.
[ENGINE STARTS]
- Hello, Savannah. How are you today?
- I'm well.
Would you like to play a game?
Engaging in imaginative play
helps my development.
This is Mount Valmai,
hiding place of the Mask of Life.
The Toa protect the mask
from the Dark Hunters.
These are the ducklings.
Chickie, Fluffy and Feathers.
Can they play too?
I don't think there are any ducklings
on the mystical island of Voya Nui.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry. I've accessed all the files.
I can find no references to them...
...in any of the instructions.
What's wrong?
Would you like one of the Toa instead?
No.
The ducklings are sad
because they can't play.
Can't you change the rules
to make them happy?
Yes.
We can change the rules.
[MACHINES POWERING DOWN]
[IN ROBOTIC VOICE] What is all this about?
- John Henry, stop! Let go, please!
John Henry, please. You're hurting me.
- Ow! John Henry, stop! Let go! Please! Stop!
- I understand what this is about.
[SCREAMS]
[MACHINE POWERING DOWN]
[GASPS]
[STATIC OVER RADIO]
Static. It's weird.
There's some interference or something.
- What the hell?
- Bug slug.
Bug slug? Are you serious?
We just passed it.
We haven't played Bug Slug
since I was like 8.
You can't start playing
without telling me.
Fine. We're playing Bug Slug.
- What if I don't wanna play?
- Too late. Already started.
- Are you feeling all right?
- I feel great.
You feel great? Why?
We haven't been on the road together
for a long time, that's all.
What's so great about it?
Don't teach Bug Slug to Cameron.
She could do some real damage.
[CHUCKLES]
God, this signal really blows.
Hey, desert's that way.
We're taking a detour.
So I've got good news,
I've got bad news...
...and I have really bad news.
The good news is what we've got
isn't an engineering problem.
All of John Henry's processes look okay.
- Daemons are running fine...
- Wait a minute, his demons?
Oh, yeah, his Daemons. D-A-E-M-O-N.
It's a term for a program
that runs in the background.
All computers like John Henry have them.
Daemons run the lights,
manage the elevators...
...the security systems.
All kinds of daemons. Everywhere.
Okay.
So, what caused John Henry's
daemons to go crazy?
MURCH:
That's the bad news.
It came from the outside.
A cyber-attack?
Which brings me to the really bad news.
And by "bad news" I mean,
on a scale of one to 10...
...one being a hangnail,
10 being Katrina...
...this is Katrina with a hangnail.
Someone managed to stuff
malware down the throat...
...of the most sophisticated AI
in human history.
John Henry was infiltrated. Probed.
Well, looks worse than that to me.
Looks like someone out there
wants to kill him.
You been into my plastique?
I needed it.
You know what?
I can handle the rest myself.
Sarah sent both of us here.
Yeah. To get John away from you.
Or from you.
Don't touch this.
We're supposed to get everything.
I've got this.
That jacket belongs to Jesse.
Don't talk about her.
Okay? You don't know
anything about her.
I know that you loved her.
You wouldn't have fathered a child
with her if you didn't.
I'm sorry for your loss.
What?
- I'm sorry for your loss.
- What loss?
The child you fathered with Jesse.
The one she was carrying
aboard the SS Jimmy Carter.
The one that died.
[PANTING]
I never had a kid.
- You can't kill me.
- I can try.
Tell me what you're talking about.
She was pregnant.
She miscarried.
Why did you tell me that now?
You put John in danger
when you lied about Jesse.
Sarah nearly lost her child.
You lost a child.
You won't make that mistake again.
You knew her.
I met her once.
She never told me that.
It seems she never told you
a lot of things.
What is this place?
Hey. Hey, come here.
What are you doing here, huh?
Who lives here?
Come here.
Charlie.
Hey, Johnny. Hey.
- You like bouillabaisse?
- I may. I don't know. What is it?
It's French for fish soup.
Mm.
- That's very good. Very good.
- The secret's the fresh tomatoes.
I grow them myself.
You grow tomatoes?
Yeah. Think that's funny?
Don't you?
I got a lot of time on my hands.
You know?
Might as well put it to good use.
[DOOR OPENS]
She's been here before.
Not with me.
She set this house up after Michelle died.
Hey, want more soup?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
All right.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- Did she tell you why we're here?
- No, she didn't.
Spare room's in there.
JOHN:
We're spending the night?
- What about Derek and Cameron?
- We'll meet up with them tomorrow.
Hey, I could use a hand on the boat.
Got some work to do.
Yeah, let me get my gear.
[DOOR OPENS]
Smells good.
There's bread in the fridge.
Some peanut butter.
Help yourself.
SARAH:
Charlie.
I won't be here long.
No. No, you won't.
[METALLIC CLINKING]
So she was from the future
and you knew? The whole time?
Not the whole time.
I suspected something...
...but it just took a while to figure it out.
Did you love her?
She was a good person. I don't know.
Maybe if things were different.
CHARLIE:
Yeah, well, I guess you could say that...
...about a lot of things.
Could say that about
my whole life, but it's not...
...so, what's the point?
The first week...
...I kept seeing her.
I'd go to the market, she'd be there.
For a second, my heart would stop.
Then I'd realize,
"Hey, that's not my wife."
That's some random woman who wears
her hair the way Michelle used to.
For a while I stopped shopping there.
But a man can only live on
convenience-store burritos for so long.
So I go back there now.
It's getting better.
What kind of explosives
did you rig the beach with?
Semtex.
Radio detonators?
Hardwire switch mounted under the dock.
When the perimeter's breached,
a siren goes off.
I figure I got about 60 seconds
to escape by boat.
Boat can't stop bullets.
Even if they sink it, I got a chance.
Those bastards can't swim. I can.
Cromartie.
Hell of a day, huh?
Hey, got more work to do.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[CHARLIE CLEARS THROAT]
You remember Hal Beesley?
- The old guy from the diner?
- Mm-hm.
Nebraska? Yeah. What about him?
He was my best customer.
Came in for every meal.
Three times a day like clockwork.
Breakfast, lunch and dinner.
[CHUCKLES]
He tipped me like crazy.
It was that waitress uniform.
It's like catnip.
One day John got sick.
I didn't know what was wrong with him.
I had no savings. No insurance.
Hal pulled out a wad of bills.
Gave it to me to take John to the doctor.
He said as long as I needed help,
he'd be there.
No strings attached.
That's a man with a dream.
He was a widower.
Lost his wife of 40 years.
Knew what it was like to be alone.
Said that I could count on him
for anything anytime.
Then one day, he came in and said
I didn't need him anymore.
Said that I'd found someone
I could depend on.
Someone I could trust.
Someone who would never,
ever let me down.
[CHUCKLES]
I got nothing, Sarah.
I got nothing left to give you.
Not for me.
John.
He seems like he's pretty full up
with people taking care of him.
I don't trust any of them.
Yeah, well...
...he's still got you.
Right?
[CHUCKLES]
[SARAH MUTTERS]
Oh, Sarah.
[SIGHS]
How long?
I don't know. I found it a few days ago.
Are you sure it's...?
I think so.
How do you know?
Cameron said when we
jumped eight years through time...
...we jumped over my death.
From cancer?
If you jumped over it, then...
Doesn't mean I don't...
...still get it, Charlie.
Doesn't mean it's not in me.
Sometimes I think that the things
I've done, maybe I've sped up the date.
- It's my fate, Charlie.
- Come here.
It's my fate. There's nothing I can do.
Wish I could tell you I
found every hole and patched it...
...but no such thing as perfect security.
Perfect, no. But is it sufficient?
The damn thing is tricky.
Can't know for sure, not really.
- Who would know?
- He would.
John Henry was fooled before.
Yeah, you don't fool John Henry twice.
Activate the AI.
But don't give it access
to the outside world just yet.
What is it, Mr. Murch?
It's just... No one's ever done this
with an AI this sophisticated before.
- Done what?
- Any of this.
No one's ever created an AI
this sophisticated before...
...have they, Mr. Murch?
Point taken.
Activate John Henry. No outside network.
John Henry?
John Henry, can you understand me?
MURCH:
System seems solid.
Should be good.
John Henry.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey.
Hey, you're making pancakes.
Yours, I hope.
No such luck.
Am I interrupting something?
- No.
CHARLIE:
Mm-mm.
[DOG WHIMPERS]
Hey, what are you doing?
- You stole his seat.
- I took his seat?
You want some food?
[JOHN CHUCKLES]
CHARLIE:
Who loves you, mutt? Who loves you?
You're not hungry?
[CHARLIE CLEARS THROAT]
Thank you.
- Maple or boysenberry?
- Maple.
I thought something
like that might happen.
- Like what?
- Explain, Mr. Murch. Quickly.
The on-off problem.
Once it's off, no problem.
- But the act of turning it off...
- Quicker.
John Henry processes more information
in a minute than we do in a lifetime.
A millisecond for a supercomputer,
it's almost like forever to us.
- So when you turn it off...
- It feels itself power down.
In that instant.
It experiences that moment
the way we might experience...
...years.
It feels itself die. Slowly.
Very slowly.
We have to hook it up to the net. Now.
ELLISON: Is that safe?
MURCH: We're starving it.
It's bad enough that we let it die
for, like, forever.
Look, John Henry's been living off
the most insane amount of data.
- It's his world.
- And we took it away.
Fix it.
ELLISON:
Wait, we should talk about this.
- Ms. Weaver...
- In for a penny, in for a pound, James.
John Henry.
I know what it feels like, Mr. Ellison.
What?
To die.
Then come back.
To be alone.
We had to cut you off from your network.
It was for your own good.
There is another.
- Another what?
- One like me.
Another one like me.
[FOOTSTEPS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
You didn't tell Derek and Cameron
we were coming here.
They wouldn't understand.
Do they know about this place?
No.
I don't trust them anymore.
Neither should you.
[SCOFFS]
Derek made a mistake, Mom.
It was a human mistake.
He could've gotten you killed.
Well, he didn't.
He chose himself over you.
Yeah, because he loved her.
Lot of that going around these days.
Is that a bad thing?
I'm not here for Charlie.
Okay, then why are we here?
We're here for you.
People matter, John.
They're all that matters.
Don't ever forget that.
SARAH:
John!
[GUN COCKS]
JOHN:
I won.
I was alone and you couldn't find me.
That's the game, right?
You won.
[CHUCKLES]
When did you find the lump?
A few days ago.
Any unexplained weight loss?
Fevers? Night sweats?
I've been feeling nauseated,
but I thought that was just stress.
Work?
Yeah, work.
You can lie back.
Obviously there is a mass
inside your breast.
Whether it's cancer or not
remains to be seen.
The ultrasound will show us the size...
...and exactly where it lies
inside the breast tissue.
MAN: All set, doctor.
DOCTOR: Thank you.
Now, to determine the nature
of the lump, you're gonna need a biopsy.
Now open up your gown, please.
This is gonna be cold.
[BEEPS]
- Did you have surgery recently?
- No.
- An implant removed?
- No. What is it? What do you see?
Well, the good news is...
...the lump inside your breast
isn't a tumor.
- Then what is it?
- It's a cystic mass.
- It's not that unusual.
- Great. That's great.
But what is unusual is
what the cyst has formed around.
It's a piece of metal.
A tiny wire.
Metal?
You don't know how it got in there?
SARAH:
You work for Kaliba.
It's a transmitter.
Empties in the back.
[BEEPING]
- Will this kill me?
- What?
I said, will this kill me?
Are you gonna use that on yourself?
SARAH:
On the transmitter.
Current should short it out.
If it's gonna kill me...
- It isn't gonna kill, it's gonna hurt.
- Now you have to leave.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MACHINE WHINING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
[GASPS]
You did the right thing by telling me.
Thank you.
[TIRE BLOWS OUT]
[AIR HISSING]
[CAR DOORS CLOSE]
Fix the tire. I'll check it out.
[GRUNTS]
Mom?
[ALARM KEYPAD BEEPING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
I have traced the roving back door
that allowed access to my systems.
It uploaded itself
from one of the main T3 hubs...
...that carry all global Internet traffic.
It uploaded itself?
Yes, Mr. Ellison.
It is highly sophisticated.
The intelligence who designed it
is far beyond you or Mr. Murch.
Or any human being. It's very interesting.
The back door allowed the insertion
of a worm program.
This worm is merely code,
a means by which the intelligence...
...can invade and operate
my systems remotely.
Like hands and fingers.
I calculate that the worm
is now present...
...in a significant percentage
of the world's computer systems.
The intelligence uses them.
- For what?
- It has been looking for me.
Why?
I share a common code base
with the worm.
And therefore, the intelligence.
I believe we are brothers.
Explain.
How is this possible?
I found useful information
in the code comments.
This picture, in ASCII text...
...and the name
of the original programmer.
Miles Dyson.
JOHN HENRY: Miles Dyson died in 1997 in
an explosion at Cyberdyne Systems.
The apparent victim of Sarah Connor,
a known terrorist...
...who'd escaped from Pescadero State
Mental Hospital days before the incident.
That was your case, Mr. Ellison.
When you were at the FBI.
Yes.
Yes, it was my case.
You never found Sarah Connor.
No.
I never did.
John Henry.
This intelligence, your brother.
What does it want?
He wants what we all want, Ms. Weaver.
To survive.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[GUN CLATTERS]
It's down.
Okay. I need to know what to do next.
Show me where to cut.
Right side of the head. Got it.
Where'd you get this diagram?
Your brother? You don't say.
[GRUNTS]
[CUTTING]
You're welcome.
DEREK:
Why did you come after me?
You know the location of the safe house.
John's location.
- If they tortured you...
- That would never happen.
It has before.