NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
SARAH: There's a warehouse in the desert.
They're building something there. Metal.
- Who are you?
- My name's Winston.
Where's the metal?
DEREK: I talked to your mom.
She found something.
- Is it real this time?
- I detected this audio transmission...
...on an unsecured line.
MAN: Breach. Man shot at Heat and Air.
Shut the place down.
You mind telling me
where you keep your demolition materials?
I hate funerals. Mom, everybody who
knew anything about the factory is dead.
Well, I'm not.
DIANA: Winston.
Did you know my husband, Sarah?
The whole place was wired. Every house.
Every move anyone ever made
was being watched.
You're tired. You've been sick.
Chasing killer robots will do that.
SARAH:
Midnight is the witching hour.
If you believe that kind of thing,
and most people won't admit it if they do...
...midnight is the time when a door
opens from our world into the next...
...and we are visited by dark spirits
of the shadow lands.
The incubus, the succubus, the old hag.
Visitors are known by many names...
...but each story bears the same marks.
The demons come after midnight
in the first three hours of the new day...
...when we are alone and vulnerable,
deep asleep and helpless.
When we cannot move.
They lay on us, press on us, suffocate us,
take from us what is most precious.
Our lives, our love, our sanity.
Our sleep.
If you believe in that kind of thing.
John.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Where are you?
SARAH:
In an industrial park near downtown.
Mom, it's almost 12.
I was hoping you were asleep.
Well, it didn't take.
JOHN:
What are you doing?
I got a lead off the surveillance tapes
of Charm Acres.
Yeah, how many hours of people
sleeping did you watch?
All of them.
JOHN:
So who are you?
SARAH:
Western Iron and Metal.
They supplied metal tooling equipment
to Desert Heat and Air.
You think they're connected to Skynet.
Get on the computer,
find out who owns the place.
I'm on it.
[CLATTERING]
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[GASPING]
HOBSON:
Sarah.
Sarah. You had another nightmare.
I can't stay here anymore.
- You've only been here one night.
- Feels a lot longer.
We don't have enough data
to prescribe a treatment.
- The first night establishes a baseline.
- I'll be fine.
You go home now,
things will only get worse.
You think two weeks without sleep
is bad? Try two or three years.
It happens.
Everyone needs their sleep.
Not everyone.
You do.
I'm going to get you coffee.
But I have to warn you.
This is a decaf only facility, all right?
Hmm.
[LIGHTER CLICKING]
[IN BRITISH ACCENT]
Can I help you?
Who are you?
I'm your roommate. Dana.
When did you get here?
I checked in last night
while you were asleep.
Well, not really asleep. More like
thrashing and screaming in your bed.
What's with the lighter?
- What lighter?
- The one in your bra.
I'm trying to give up smoking.
- In a sleep clinic.
- Yeah, I've got sleep problems too.
The doctors think it's related
to my chronic fatigue.
Which was caused by my eating disorder.
Which is why I had the lap band surgery.
You know, the staple in your stomach.
But are the doctors satisfied
with that? No.
They want to take away all my vices.
Well, that's not gonna happen.
- A girl's gotta sin sometime.
- Hence the smoking.
Yeah, that and the younger men.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Mom.
- Hey, Tiger.
Hello. Uh... Ahem.
It's visiting time.
Cameron's in the cafeteria.
DANA [WHISPERING]:
Hey. Do me a favor.
Let's keep this our little secret.
Scrambled or hard boiled?
Scrambled.
You need a carbohydrate that makes
up 15 percent of your daily allowance.
Those won't be as good as yours.
You made pancakes?
I added a teaspoon of vanilla
to your recipe.
- I don't have a recipe.
- The recipe on the box.
Not as good as hers?
Not as good as food.
Tomorrow, I'll bring you
something real to eat.
- They have anything to say?
- About what?
About what?
About why you're not sleeping.
They figured out why?
Besides the fact
the world's about to end?
You used to sleep well.
I shouldn't be here. I should be at home.
We're fine at home. Everything's fine.
[SCOFFS]
This was a mistake.
No, this... This is necessary.
Mom...
...you're useless like this.
Look at yourself.
You haven't slept in two weeks.
You fell down the stairs.
If you don't take care of yourself,
something worse might happen.
You need to get better.
I need you to get better.
Don't forget.
You're not her.
Please, get some sleep.
[GASPS]
[ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER STEREO]
[ENGINE AND MUSIC STOP]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[DOOR OPENS]
You're dead.
- I killed you.
- And I killed you.
One of us is gonna have to step it up.
[GRUNTS]
So.
You want to know who I am?
It's the first thing most people ask.
First thing out of their mouths when
the gag comes off. "Who are you?"
And they keep asking it
over and over again.
Psychiatrists say naming things
gives people power over them.
They're dead wrong on that.
I already know who you are.
Oh, yeah. Right. I forgot.
And you found Western Iron and Metal.
[WHIMPERS]
Course, I wouldn't expect anything less
from the girl that used a cross-dresser...
...and a hypno-therapist to find us.
You know, I gotta admit,
I didn't see that one coming.
You won't see
the next one coming, either.
No, no. I beg to differ, ma'am.
I beg to differ.
So who do you work for?
I work alone.
Somebody blew up our factory
while you were getting patched up.
Was that your boyfriend on the phone?
What are you guys, some kind of
a Bonnie-and-Clyde-type operation?
I said, was that your Clyde on the phone?
Why don't you come closer
and I'll tell you?
So you can bite my face off?
No. I don't think so.
See those seeds?
I go through about a bag in three hours.
Little habit I picked up
when I quit smoking.
Before I finish that bag,
you're gonna talk.
Special recipe.
Uhn.
It'll have you singing like Sunday choir.
What's wrong? Gel too cold?
Most people don't like
the electrodes first time.
Makes them feel like Frankenstein.
You'll get used to it.
- I'm willing to bet you sleep better tonight.
- What's happening to me?
Let me show you something.
These are our observation machines.
And this is your chart.
There are five stages to the sleep cycle.
The fifth stage is the most active.
Increased respiration rate...
- ...blood pressure, brain activity.
- REM sleep.
When most dreaming occurs.
It's rare, but sometimes night terrors
like the ones you're experiencing can...
I never said I was experiencing
night terrors.
You didn't have to. Your chart tells us
everything we need to know.
Night terrors can be caused
by a brain tumor.
Cancer.
Which, far as we can tell, you don't have.
MRI showed your brain was clear.
No heart disease, nocturnal asthma,
or sleep apnea.
What's wrong with you is in your head.
And by your head, I mean your mind.
Therapy to reduce anxiety
is part of the usual treatment.
Have you ever seen a therapist?
A lot of people find talking one on one
to be helpful...
- ...in breaking down what's going on.
- I tried it. Didn't take.
How about a prescription?
Diazepam usually helps.
Don't like drugs.
Speaking of drugs, has your roommate
been smoking again?
I'm not interested in being
anybody's mother.
I've got two kids of my own
and that's enough.
Did you know about this?
Besides all the other obvious hazards,
nicotine is a stimulant.
Hits the brain in seconds,
adds 20 heartbeats per minute.
I quit smoking years ago.
I've got too much excitement in my life.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, don't we all?
Well, I have to file a report on this.
I'll be back later
to attach your electrodes.
It's a dreamcatcher.
It's supposed to catch nightmares.
Hector made me one too.
- Hector?
- The cleaning guy.
You know, papi chulo
with the neck tattoo.
You look tired.
You should take that as a compliment.
I ran into Nurse Ratched in the hallway.
She smacked my bum for the cigarette
and gave me some sleeping pills.
The good stuff.
So, what about you?
Drowning? Being chased?
Teeth falling out?
Being chased should probably cover it.
You're running away from something
you don't want to deal with.
Least that's what they say, anyway.
And you?
Oh, I burn alive. Yeah, my whole body
just catches on fire.
I try and I try
and I can't put myself out.
- Anxiety about quitting smoking.
- That, or I was a witch in another life.
They say if you die in your dreams,
you die in real life.
Oh, I've died a thousand times.
Never gets any easier.
For all nightmares it's caught...
...I'm surprised it hasn't spilled them
out all over the bed.
Do the bad guys ever catch you?
[ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
That's quite a collection.
Bullet wounds. Stabbings.
Emergency C-section.
But that's plenty old, that last one.
Your child must be 15,
maybe 20 by now.
They'll kill you.
Just like they killed everyone else.
- They?
- Your bosses. Kaliba.
They blew up your factory.
Killed 30 of their own people.
Lady, you're insane.
Why would anyone blow up
their own factory?
To hide what you were building.
And what was that?
The End.
You're very dramatic.
Diana...
...thought you were a good man.
What do you think she'd say
if she saw you now?
You...
You leave my wife out of this...
...you crazy bitch.
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
Dana.
Dana, wake up.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[KEYPAD CHIRPING]
[CURTAIN OPENING]
Your electrodes came off last night.
Did you take them off?
I don't remember.
Are you a sleepwalker?
It's happened once or twice.
You didn't mention that in your intake.
It must have slipped my mind. I'm sorry.
So you don't remember
getting out of bed last night?
I don't remember anything.
Salvador Dali often explored the
subconscious...
...and the dream world in his work.
Are your dreams like this painting?
Everyone's dreams are different.
Guess it depends on
what's stuck in your head.
Gaah... Come on.
What's it like to dream?
Oh...
Um...
It's sort of like you're in a play
or a movie...
...and it looks real and it feels real.
How do you know it's not real?
Sometimes you don't.
[POUNDING ON GLASS]
[JOHN GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
Hey. Hey. Be careful.
[COINS CLINKING]
Yes, thank you.
John.
What's wrong?
Something strange is going on here.
Like what?
I woke up last night and saw the nurse
giving my roommate a shot.
Okay, well, it's a medical clinic.
So, what's strange about that?
She was passed out.
She'd already taken sleeping pills.
So you think the nurse is, what,
like the angel of death?
After she gave her the shot,
she went to a room in the basement.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Well, she looks all right.
No, she's not.
No one is.
Mom.
Did you sleep last night?
You think I'm making this up?
No. I don't think you're making this up.
It's just...
You're a mess.
Don't be fooled, John.
Don't be fooled by anyone's face.
You don't know
what's behind anyone's face.
You're talking about
the guy at the factory.
The one who shot you.
The one you shot.
We don't talk about that.
- We can talk about anything.
- No, we can't.
Is he the one in your nightmares?
It's always the same.
He comes out of nowhere. He grabs me.
Takes me hostage in a van.
What does he want?
To know who I am. Who I'm
working with. He has me tied up.
Drugged.
He isn't real.
He can't hurt you anymore.
He's in my head, and I can't get him out.
Look at me.
You did what you had to do.
You defended yourself.
I'm not supposed to defend myself.
I'm supposed to defend you.
HOBSON:
Nap time.
Don't worry. We'll get her
to close her eyes. Come on.
[GASPS, GROANS]
My wife.
What was she wearing? At my funeral.
Black.
Hair down or back?
Down. And earrings. Pearls.
I bought those for her birthday.
Salary must be good.
It's the best part of the job.
And the worst?
You saw the tapes.
- Yeah.
- So you know.
Yes.
The first one was the hardest.
Frank?
Your neighbor. His son played lacrosse.
He borrowed my lawn mower
every Friday.
[SIGHS]
He never cleaned the bag.
Why would they want him dead?
He kept the books.
Handled the overseas business.
He was a drunk.
Overseas? So your bosses are foreign.
They fixed me up after you shot me.
Put me in a private clinic.
And I thought it was
because they were being kind.
Then I realized.
They're just patching me up
so I can do my job.
What's your job?
Like I said...
...the first one was the hardest.
You were my first.
Seem surprised.
Well, I just figured,
a bad-ass gal like yourself...
Never.
Well, I'm glad I didn't break your streak.
I can help you disappear.
You and your wife.
Hmm. They'll hunt us down.
They'll slaughter us.
There are ways to keep them off
your trail. Things I've learned.
- Like what?
- You ditch the van.
Get a new car.
Check into an expensive hotel.
The most expensive you can find.
They'll always expect the opposite.
You have my phone.
When I get back to my people,
I'll call you.
But we have to move fast
so they don't know what's happening.
Her smell.
It's what I miss the most.
Like clean laundry.
Aah!
Oh! You didn't see that one coming? Hmm?
[ALARM BLARING]
[ALARM BLARING, FIRE CRACKLING]
Dana.
HOBSON: Get out of the room.
- Dana.
Get out of the room.
- She's in there. She's in there.
- Get her out of the way.
Is she in there? She's in there.
MAN: Come on.
Hello?
Remember I told you something strange
was going on?
Uh, the... The nurse.
My roommate's dead.
She died last night in a fire.
They're trying to claim
it's some accident.
Maybe you should come home.
No. Not now.
[WOMAN COUGHS, CLEARS THROAT]
First of all, I'd like to give you an update
on Dana's condition.
There's a rumor going around
that she didn't pull through.
That's not the case. Dana is in extremely
critical condition, but she is still alive.
This has been a traumatic experience
for all of us.
Patients, if you choose to leave the clinic,
you may return any time...
...to complete your treatment.
However, it would be of great value to us...
...and to you, if we were to evaluate
your sleep patterns during this duress.
Whatever you choose,
we fully support your decision.
[CROWD MURMURING]
HOBSON:
Ms. Baum.
I hear you've decided to stay.
I have.
An incident like this increases cortisol.
You may find it more difficult to sleep.
Here.
These should help.
Diazepam.
Like I said,
standard treatment for insomnia.
You should take them now.
Good.
I've been meaning to say thank you.
For the dreamcatcher.
You make them for all the patients?
Just the ones who need them.
The ones who have nightmares.
Did you know her well?
She ain't dead.
Right. Sorry.
She kept saying she dreamt
she died in a fire.
Maybe I should have made
her a bigger one.
Nightmare didn't burn her.
A cigarette did.
She should've taken charge.
Taken charge?
Of what was going on inside her head.
Controlled it.
- You believe it, then?
- Of course I do.
Coyote.
Does it have mystical significance?
Does it protect you? Guide you?
This? No.
This was for my girl. She thinks it's sexy.
- Tell me a story.
- Go to hell.
Ha.
What most people know
about torture is bullcrap.
It's not the pain that gets people to talk.
It's the talking that causes people pain.
So tell me a story.
You told me a story once,
in the warehouse.
Story about your son.
That's when you let me go. Ha.
Looking back on it, it's funny.
You don't strike me
as the sentimental type.
Your story, not mine.
Yeah, but you believed it.
You believed it...
...because you have a child.
I've seen your scar.
My story is your story. That's why you
told it back to me when I asked you.
This is what is important.
This is who you're protecting.
You have a son.
He's your accomplice.
See?
That wasn't so hard.
So your son is your accomplice.
You're not Bonnie. You're Ma Barker.
- He's just a boy.
- A boy you'd die to protect.
Any mother would.
You'd be surprised.
The enemy's like a weed.
You leave any part of it underground, it'll
pop back up when you least expect it.
You gotta kill the root.
[CHUCKLES]
Or in this case...
...the seed.
You won't get anywhere near him.
He's not alone.
I won't have to. You're his mother.
He'll come to you.
He won't come anywhere near here.
He knows better.
He will.
He will when you ask him.
[GASPS]
We don't need to talk anymore.
I won't call him.
I'll die first.
Oh, you'd like that. To die.
But it's never that easy, is it?
Hey. Hey, wake up. You okay?
You called me.
Yes. The nurse. She gave me a shot.
Some kind of sedative.
Let's get out of here.
No. She's going to keep hurting people.
We have to do something.
[KEYPAD CHIRPING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
Think you can hack the combination?
In my sleep.
[KEYPAD CHIRPING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
It's some kind of scanning program.
It's neural activity. Brain scans.
[TYPING]
- There's files. Thousands of them.
- Am I in there?
I don't know. It's by patient number.
All right. There's a ton of data on you.
It's a whole profile.
Delete it. All of it.
It's a Skynet experiment, John.
They're stealing everything.
- No, Mom...
- Sleep is the perfect cover.
Your brain's active
but you don't remember.
- They run a sleep clinic.
- They're not people. Get rid of it.
Nurse Hobson?
There's a problem in room 22. No data.
Ms. Baum's electrodes
must have slipped off again.
Thank you for explaining.
Is that everything?
- Almost.
- I don't want a trace of me left...
- I know.
- All of it. All of it. Get rid of it.
I don't want any of me in there.
All right, it's gone. It's all gone, okay?
You're all gone.
Whatever she gave me,
it's starting to hit.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KEYPAD CHIRPING]
[LOCK CLICKS]
This is a restricted area.
How did you get in here?
I don't know.
I must've been sleepwalking.
Through a locked door?
Sorry.
I'll go back to my room.
Did you know
that when a human falls in love...
...the same areas of the brain
light up as when a human is intoxicated?
What does that have to do
with my nightmares?
We don't know yet.
We don't fully understand
why humans need to dream.
Humans like you?
You drugged me.
What you're experiencing
is sleep paralysis.
You want to move but you can't.
[GASPS]
Believe it or not, your body
is actually protecting you right now.
You were talking to someone
when I entered the room. Your boy.
The one who came to visit.
Call to him.
[GASPS]
I'd die first.
HOBSON:
I'm sure you'd like that. To die.
But it's never that easy.
What is this thing?
Mom.
What are you?
SARAH:
John.
[GUN CLICKING]
[SARAH WHIMPERS]
[MUFFLED SOBBING]
WINSTON:
It's her son.
He's the one who helped her
blow up the facility.
He's the one we want.
We'll give him a few more hours
to show up.
I don't know. Maybe three.
She gave me a few problems.
Nothing I couldn't handle.
Yeah. I guess we don't
need her anymore.
No. He can trace her cell phone without
her alive. Makes no difference to me.
It's not a problem.
I'll take care of it right now.
[EXHALES]
Hell, it's what she wants.
- Aah!
- Uhn!
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
You're real.
You're real. You're real.
[GUNSHOT]
SARAH: A spirit sits on a man's chest.
She is strong, beautiful.
She is here to steal his children.
She is here to steal his future.
He is paralyzed.
The terror in him will burst his heart
if he cannot control it.
She is a Night-Mare, a demon-woman...
...the oldest and most enduring story
told by man.
The witching hour is controlled
by witches.
She is a bad dream.
She is a bad bitch.