NARRATOR: In the future,
a computer program called Skynet...
...will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time,
taking human form...
...to terminate John Connor,
the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor,
John's mother, teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogrammed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle, and a
commanding officer with the Resistance.
Together, they fight to stop
Skynet from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow starts today.
ANNOUNCER: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
Do we have a John Reese?
[GRUNTING]
Come with me if you wanna live.
I'm not who they think I am,
some messiah.
- You've gotta stop it. Please.
SARAH: I'll stop it.
You wanna stop Skynet? This is the way.
CAMERON:
He came through. He knows we're here.
We're programmed to repair ourselves.
We're programmed to blend in.
[GRUNTS]
SARAH: There are other people he sent back.
CAMERON: Resistance fighters.
- You don't even know who he is.
- He's your uncle.
The machines gotta go.
DEREK: Don't think you can train them like
a pet. It'll be the last thing you think.
ELLISON: Your fiancée, Sarah Connor,
killed a man. She believes, in the future...
...he'll invent a computer system
that declares war on the world.
AND Y: My Turk plays chess at a level
that could defeat every human player...
...that has lived or ever will live.
- I might just blow up the world.
Sarkissian called me.
He'll meet about selling The Turk.
- Guy that Derek killed.
- Sarkissian.
I don't think that was Sarkissian.
If you die, they win.
[SIREN WAILING]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
O VER RADIO]
Agent Ellison? Can I borrow you?
Pulled him from the apartment.
That's your guy, right? The shooter?
Yeah, that's him.
NORGAARD: How does a mope like that
take out 20 of our HRT?
SAC wants you back home
for a full incident report.
Need a ride?
I can get a junior agent
to drive your car. Come on.
They're gonna believe a mope like this
took out 20 of your HRT?
They gonna believe a machine
from the future stole his identity and did it?
They gotta believe. This has to end here.
Sorry you gotta take the blame for it.
It's not your fault.
Just bad luck.
Are you all right?
John, are you all right?
You answer me!
Mom!
[CAR HORN HONKING]
Can you move? Are you hurt?
You're bleeding.
- I'm fine. Are you all right?
- It's just my shoulder.
[PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
We gotta go.
[JOHN GRUNTING]
- Can you walk?
- Yeah.
Good, because we gotta run.
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey!
MAN:
Come back here!
WOMAN [O VER RADIO]: Fire and EMT
personnel, advised to stand by.
Fire has destroyed a home
at 204 Laurel Avenue.
Number of dead or injured is unknown.
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN 1: The gas line is behind
that bearing wall through there.
Go ahead, pull it.
MAN 2: Bring it up.
MAN 1: He's working on the left side.
- Hey. These the only two DO A?
- That's it.
- You check the whole house?
- House is clear.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCLTY]
What the hell is going on here?
Where is she?
Hell if I know.
Long gone, if I know her.
- Who's out there under those sheets?
- We were doing a deal.
It went bad. We stole this.
Guess they came back for it.
- What's on it?
- Oh, records, names, transactions.
I don't know.
We thought we could use it
to find something.
- What are you looking for?
- It's a piece of tech. It's called The Turk.
- It's another computer. It's a program.
- What's it do?
Right now? Plays a mean game of chess.
Couple years?
It's gonna get really pissed off.
Blow up the world.
WOMAN [O VER RADIO]:
Units requested.
Possible stolen vehicle
involved in accident.
Suspect fled scene, injuries unknown.
- She could be anywhere.
- That's right, she could be anywhere.
Or she could be right there.
Maybe with your chess program.
The identification of these two victims
hasn't yet been released...
...and it's unclear how they're connected
to this or the car explosion nearby.
WOMAN:
Mr. Walsh?
- Ma'am.
- Do you have it?
I do, ma'am.
It's a modest little mouse, if I may say.
It's not much to look at for 300,000.
Better be able to checkmate
Bobby Fischer.
Not for you to judge, Mr. Walsh.
- The last you'll hear of it from me.
- When will I see you?
I thought I'd tour the sights
with it for a bit.
- Make sure I was clean.
WOMAN: That seems prudent.
- An hour, then?
- An hour.
And, Mr. Walsh? Bobby Fischer's dead.
[PHONE BEEPS]
WOMAN [O VER SPEAKERPHONE]:
Ma'am?
Call a meeting
of the department heads for tonight.
Tonight? But, Miss Weaver, Justin Tuck
is in Palm Springs for a long weekend.
- I'll get him back.
- Thank you.
[STAPLE GUN CLICKING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Witness saw a woman and a boy
get out of the car...
...and move off to the south.
- Are they hurt?
- Either way, they're moving.
[GRUNTS]
I'm okay. I'm okay.
It's just bruised. Let's go.
- It could be broken.
- How's your leg?
Is your head still bleeding?
Gotta get off the street.
We need to find a safe place.
[PRIEST SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Has there been an accident?
[BOTH SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
We need sanctuary.
Can I ask for that? Please?
We need somewhere to hide. Now.
Yes. Of course. Come with me.
And they should leave.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Come on.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
- So, what are you gonna do?
- Do?
Join the team? Think she's gonna
go with you or let you take care of her?
Because that's not gonna happen.
She left you at the altar for a reason.
- That's not what I want.
- Really?
- Yeah, I'm married.
- So you say.
- I love my wife.
Look, I just wanna know they're okay.
Got it?
- What if they're not?
- Then I'll make them okay.
Like I did for you.
[CHATTERING]
Your money will be deposited
in the account within 30 minutes.
Please, take all the precautions
we discussed.
Of course, ma'am. So much for so little.
Again, don't mind me saying.
They flow from street to street...
...at a particular speed
and in a particular direction.
Walk the block. Wait for the signal.
Cross at the light. Over and over.
So orderly. All day, I can watch them...
...and know with a great deal of certainty
what they'll do at any given moment.
But they're not orderly, are they?
Up close. Any individual.
Who knows what they're gonna do?
Any one of them might
dash across the street...
...at the wrong time
and get hit by a car.
When you get up close,
we never follow the rules.
You give a computer a series of rules,
and it will follow them...
...till those rules
are superseded by other rules...
...or that computer simply
wears down and quits.
Computers are obedient to a fault.
Do you know what's extremely rare
in the world of computers?
Finding one that'll cross against the light.
Thank you, Mr. Walsh.
Be careful out there.
[MAN SPEAKING IN SPANISH
O VER RADIO]
Are you all right?
- You already asked me that.
- I'm asking you again.
I'm fine.
We need to talk about
what happened back at the house.
- No, we don't.
- Maybe I need to talk about it.
Maybe you do, but I don't,
so let's not. Please.
Then we need to talk about her.
Whatever happened with the explosion,
it's flipped a switch.
She's reverted or something.
- She knows everything.
- I know.
Bank accounts. Contingency plans.
Weapons stash.
- I know.
- How we run, where we'll go.
Who we've been, who we'll be.
She's stronger and faster.
- We have to kill her, John.
- I know!
I know.
FEDERICl:
I just read your incident report.
I wanna thank you
for filling everything out so quickly.
- It's a big help.
- Of course.
So Laszlo.
Did you ever think that he had it in him?
- Out-of-work-actor, a civilian?
- I did not, no.
But he was here before.
Suspect in multiple murders.
- We cleared him.
- You had a change of heart, obviously.
I discovered he was
impersonating an FBI agent.
Yeah. Yeah, I had a change of heart.
Do you have any idea whose bullet
was ultimately responsible...
...for taking his life?
No, I don't.
Do you know who threw
the tear gas into the residence?
- No.
- Do you know who fired...
...into the apartment,
igniting the canisters?
No, I do not.
It's amazing you survived.
- Do you know how you survived?
- No.
You wanna talk to somebody?
You need help?
You want a counselor,
you want a pastor?
- You're divorced. Do you have anybody?
- I'll be all right.
We want you to take six weeks'
paid leave. Special circumstances.
- I don't think that'll be necessary.
- We insist on it.
So...
Under possible penalty of perjury,
as relates to Case File B1987004...
...do you, Agent James Ellison,
today attest that all you've recorded...
...in said case file is accurate and factual
as far as your recollection can warrant?
Yes. I do.
Good luck, agent.
Yes? May I help you?
- I'm looking for my family.
- Your family?
My mother and my brother.
We were in an accident.
I think they're hurt.
There is no one here.
I need to find them. It's life or death.
- Like I said, there is no one here.
- I'm going to look around.
It's life or death.
Now.
- Two minutes.
- I know.
PRIEST: What are you doing?
- Stay away. Please.
I told you to go away.
You have to stay away.
Go!
Seventy seconds.
- I know. The knife isn't sharp enough.
- Well, push harder.
- How much time?
- Fifty-five.
Oh, wait, I see it, I see it, I see it.
Screwdriver, screwdriver.
- Thirty-five.
- It's not the right size.
- Twenty seconds.
- Okay, okay. The knife, the knife.
- Unh. Damn it!
- We can't do this. Come on, John.
She's waking up. She's waking up.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
SARAH:
Keys.
[TRUCK HORN HONKING]
[MAN GRUNTS THEN
SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[JOHN COUGHING]
Mom.
You have to go, John.
- John.
- What?
Go. Go.
Go.
Go!
[GRUNTING]
- Call to him.
- No.
Call to him.
[SCREAMS]
- You're making this difficult.
- He won't come back!
No, he won't.
[GRUNTING]
[CLATTERING]
[ENGINE RATTLING THEN CLICKS]
[ENGINE SPLUTTERING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
John. John. You can't do this.
- You don't know what you're about to do.
- Yes, I do. You're gonna kill me.
No. John, you can't do this.
You're not doing the right thing.
This is not the right thing, John.
Things are good now.
Things are fine now. I ran a test.
Things are good now. I'm fixed now.
You can trust me now.
- Everything's good now.
- What are you waiting for?
She doesn't know. She doesn't.
I'm good now.
I'm good. I ran a test.
Everything's perfect. I'm perfect.
- John!
- I'm sorry for what I did. I'm sorry.
It wasn't me.
You have to understand. It wasn't me.
That wasn't me. You can't
let this happen, John. You can't.
Please, listen to me. Listen to me.
I don't wanna go. Please, John, please.
John, listen to me. I don't wanna go.
Please, John. Please? I'm good now.
Listen to me. I don't wanna go. I'm sorry.
That wasn't me.
I'm fixed now. I ran a test.
- Everything's perfect. You can trust me.
- John Connor.
I love you. I love you. Please.
I love you, John, and you love me.
We should get going soon.
You cut a pretty serious
path of destruction across the city.
Wasn't us.
[GRUNTS]
- Sorry.
- Should've called earlier.
- Maybe we could've helped you avoid those.
- I doubt it.
- How's this?
DEREK: Looks trashed.
So Sarkissian didn't tell you where
he sold The Turk before you killed him.
Wasn't that kind of conversation.
DEREK:
Did he see it all?
He saw it all.
Damn.
Charlie told me that Cromartie
killed about 20 FBI guys today.
He's still out there.
He's here for me.
They're dead because of me.
They're dead because some people
refuse to accept the reality of the situation.
Which is what?
Which is that they carry death with them.
- She was different.
- No.
I made her.
I sent her back.
- She's different.
- She's not different.
There's physical damage to her chip...
...which means she can be repaired...
- John.
I need her.
She saved my life.
She saves my life.
I know what you saw today.
I know what you did,
and I'm so proud of you.
Maybe you could fix her.
I know you wanna try...
...but I can't let you. I just... I can't.
So burn her.
Let's get the hell out of here.
What she said back there...
...everything she said was a trick.
You know that, right?
They don't feel anything.
They don't have feelings.
They don't know love.
I know that, Mom.
Yeah, I saw her do this with the last one.
DEREK:
Only way to be sure.
Especially this one.
John, chip.
Flare. Where is it?
- Sarah?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
DEREK:
John.
John. Don't do this.
- John, don't do this.
- Back off. John, she'll kill you.
There's only one way to find out.
Are you here to kill me, John?
Are you here to kill me?
No.
Promise?
Promise.
I'll never lead you to her.
If that's why you left me alive,
you might as well kill me right now.
I'll never do the devil's work.
We'll see.
Thank you for joining me tonight.
I'm pleased to announce...
...the formation of a new division.
It'll cross disciplines,
draw from many areas of expertise...
...and require the highest level of work
from your groups.
Each of our groups?
How's that? Won't you be hiring?
I'll take team members
from each division and create a new team.
TUCK:
With all due respect...
...and I can only speak on behalf
of the Al Division when I tell you...
...that I haven't a man to spare.
- Your division will be hard hit.
The list of new team members will be on
your desks after you leave this meeting.
The name of the new group is Babylon.
It's from the Bible.
And what does Babylon do?
I mean, besides steal our team members.
Mr. Tuck, it's going to change the world.
I got what I could.
Some smoke and water damage,
but you don't have to start over.
Wouldn't be the first time.
- Thanks.
- There's one too many.
Charlie took off. Said to say bye.
I guess he really does have a wife.
Have you seen John?
I think he's using the shower.
Do you believe in the Resurrection?
What?
The story of Jesus Christ.
The Resurrection.
Do you believe in it?
Would you, if you'd seen what I've seen?
Faith isn't part of my programming.
Yeah, well, I'm not sure
it's part of mine either.
Don't let him do that again.
If I ever go bad again,
don't let him bring me back.
JOHN:
Yeah.
I made you a sandwich
and brought you some clothes.
I'll be out soon.
John, I need you to know
everything that happened today...
...everything we did...
...it was all...
It just happened the way it did...
...and there's nothing we can do
to change it.
And whatever happened, we're alive.
Okay? We're alive.
I know you need more from me today...
...but it's gonna have to be enough.
Can you hear me?
Are you listening?
JOHN:
Yeah, I'm listening.
Happy birthday.
Well, that was something, wasn't it?
Wonder what she's got planned.
Who knows what goes on
in that brain of hers.
I don't understand what the hell
she's talking about half the time.
Zen koans and Bible quotes.
It's all a bunch of bull.
Our options have tripled
since she took over...
...so I wouldn't bite the hand
if I were you.
Well, that's easy for you to say.
She's not cannibalizing your division
for some top-secret Torah study.
Okay.
God, that bitch pisses me off.
Sorry I piss you off, Mr. Tuck.
The feeling's mutual.
[ENGLISH SDH]