NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
COP: Been drinking?
- So, what are you in for?
I'm Jody.
What did you do? Did you hurt me?
JODY:
Is there a problem?
No, I'm her brother. John Baum.
RITA:
Anything you say is confidential.
The exception is if you plan
to harm someone.
I would have to report that.
- Jesse.
- Hi, baby.
Are you AWOL? Jesse, did you run?
I need a place to rest.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Oh!
James Ellison?
[GUN COCKS]
[BUZZING]
Why? Aren't you on the same side?
Skynet does not believe in you
like I do.
Believe? What do you believe?
You will lead me to the Connors.
Stay there.
[THUMPING]
[THUMPING CONTINUES]
[FLOOR CREAKS]
There's no one here.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[ONE BEEP THEN TWO BEEPS]
[PHONE BEEPS]
Where the hell are you?
Where the hell am I supposed to be?
We just got robbed.
DEREK [OVER PHONE]: You were what?
Diamonds, cash, credit cards, IDs.
They cleaned us out.
Machine?
My leather jacket's gone.
- So is most of the food.
- Human.
If those IDs
fall into the wrong hands...
Then head downtown.
I'll call you with a location
in half an hour.
[PHONE BEEPS OFF]
Who was that?
Real life calling.
You don't always have to answer.
I tried ignoring it all last time around...
- ...and the whole freaking town blew up.
- Heh.
You're a funny man.
Yeah. Yeah, that's the first thing people
say who know me: "Funny Derek."
[BEEP]
What's wrong with the system? Why
didn't it beep or whatever you set it to?
John?
Riley climbed out John's window.
The alarm would have been turned off
for her to do that.
Thanks.
You gave her the code?
We were up late watching TV.
She was supposed to reset it.
And somehow your master plan
went awry.
- Mom...
- John, our IDs are out there.
Our names. Our faces.
Fake addresses, fake names.
Nothing to be traced to this house.
If police find who did this,
where do you think that trail leads?
If our IDs made it into the system,
linked to this address?
Canada.
We should move to Canada.
I saw your door was open,
I thought I'd bring you guys some...
Oh, my God. What happened?
I'll go call Trevor.
SARAH: No.
Uh... John's been having trouble
with kids at school.
KACY: Seriously?
[CHUCKLES] Yeah.
You know how stupid kids can be.
I'll know soon enough.
We're on our way to see their parents.
All right. If you change your mind...
SARAH:
I'll call you.
What am I supposed to do?
I'd start with a broom.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Here you go.
Come on, Rita. I got the county
breathing down my neck.
We can't have a backlog like this.
I'll get it done.
- Today.
- I needed it two weeks ago.
It's my son. He took off this morning with
the neighbor's car and my credit cards.
MAN [OVER PHONE]: We'll call you right
away if he attempts a charge, Ms. Baum.
- Is this a good number to reach you?
- Yes. Thank you.
If you knew what was going on,
why didn't you say something?
- To you?
- To me. To him. To somebody.
I've always made my position
on security very clear.
No one likes a nag.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
I'm looking for this girl.
You see these people, sir?
These people are real.
These are the real people.
And they were all here before you.
I'm her uncle.
And I'm Angelina Jolie.
Get to the back of the line.
Hey. I know that chick.
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
So, what do you want her for?
She owe you money?
I'm her uncle.
You're not her uncle. You're a cop.
I'm not a cop.
- You gonna hurt her?
- Yes.
What about her brother?
Hurt him too?
- Her brother?
- Yeah. John Baum or whatever.
John Baum?
Another prize.
Is that him?
Yeah, heh, that's him.
Let's take a ride.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
[FOOTSTEPS]
ELLISON: Who is it?
MAN: Los Angeles Police Department.
ELLISON: Hold on. I'm just trying
to catch up on last night's game.
You know who won?
Steelers, Mr. Ellison.
Could you open the door, please?
[UNFOLDS PAPER]
Yeah.
- You're James Ellison?
- Yeah.
I'm placing you under arrest
for the murder of Peter Meyers.
What?
You have the right to remain silent,
the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
one will be appointed.
Do you understand these rights
as I've read them to you?
I know my rights. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Please put your hands
against the wall, sir. Now, Mr. Ellison.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
DEREK:
Come on, Moishe. Open up.
MOISHE [OVER INTERCOM]: Who are they?
- New customers.
MOISHE: Everything wee do,
without exception...
...can be seen many ways
in the eyes of God.
Or nature.
Or whatever you wanna call it.
Someone came into your home.
Someone took things
that were rightfully yours.
The Torah says:
[SPEAKS IN HEBREW]
No revenge. No retribution.
On the other hand, it also says:
[SPEAKS IN HEBREW]
An eye for an eye.
We've the story
of the brothers of Nablus...
We came here looking for our diamonds.
Can you help us or not?
I wish I could.
But lately, business is dry as a bone.
DEREK:
I called four other fences.
They said you were the busiest man
on the block this week.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, nothing you'd be interested in.
Show us.
MOISHE:
Okay.
These I bought in the last two days.
All from legitimate sources.
This one's ours.
[CHUCKLES]
Young lady, even if those were
your diamonds... And they're not.
...There's no way you could tell with
the eye. We have machines for that.
So are these.
We don't want any trouble.
Tell us where you got them,
and we're gone.
You think I can put a face
to every diamond in the stack?
Just a face from the last 24 hours.
Moishe.
Please.
All right.
So early in the week for trouble.
But it's not for you. It's for Jesse.
His name's Ostrowski.
Walter Ostrowski.
Where do we find him?
He works out of Toluca Lake,
or so he says. I just buy the stones.
And this Ostrowski...
...you're sure he's the guy
who sold you these?
I shall not lie.
If you're so into God,
what are you doing here?
Tsk. Hashem has a plan for us all.
For me, diamonds.
Who's Jesse?
He came back with me.
He handled the diamonds.
One of them killed him.
Do you want some gum?
No.
You sure? It's cinnamon.
Would it kill you
to try and make a little conversation?
No, it wouldn't kill me.
Funny.
You're funny
in your own sort of cop way.
I'm not a cop.
You're not a cop. You're not an uncle.
You're just some guy
who wants to kick the crap...
...out of Little Miss Bitch
and her brother.
Just some guy.
But why?
She try to kill you too?
Yes.
Oh.
Wow.
This is gonna be fun.
I can't believe they stole your food.
Fricking amateurs, man.
Yeah, I know, right?
What do they think they're gonna do
with two-week-old maple turkey?
I bet your mom freaked out, huh?
- Yeah, on me.
- On you? Why on you?
The alarm code.
- Did I forget?
- Yeah, you did.
JODY: I didn't actually see it happen.
I wasn't here, but I'm pretty sure...
Yeah, I'm positive.
This is where they busted her.
I heard the cops talking about it
when they brought her in.
You are so buying me
these pink-and-whites...
...and that is all there is to it.
Have you seen this girl?
WOMAN: No, sorry.
I'm looking for this girl.
I'm so sorry, John.
I can't believe I did that.
Don't worry about it.
Wouldn't have stopped the break-in.
Might've stopped the picnic, but...
[CHUCKLES]
I know you wanna find them
and everything...
...but this is getting a little shady.
Does she hate me now?
Don't sweat it. It's a long list.
JODY: You're not gonna get what you want.
Try being warmer to people.
They might be more open, you know,
to talk to you.
I love this stuff.
That's my bad.
That's the guy.
That's definitely the guy.
What am I doing here, detective?
You've been on my side of the table.
You know how this works.
I ask a question, you answer it.
Why am I being questioned?
You tell me. Who's Peter Meyers?
- I don't know Peter Meyers.
- You killed him.
Killed him?
- No.
- Yes. I got a witness.
Saw the murder, recognized you
from the news a few weeks ago.
Recognized me?
- From the news?
- The news.
Twenty of your guys dead,
you the sole survivor.
By now you're drowning in guilt,
I'm guessing.
- Throw yourself an anchor...
- I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm talking about surviving, Mr. Ellison.
I'm talking about the everyday,
walk-around pain of surviving...
...when others have not.
I wanna talk to my lawyer.
Okay, sure.
Oh.
I meant to ask you:
Why did you steal his clothes?
- What?
- Meyers' clothes.
- You were naked when you killed him.
- I told you. It wasn't me.
Smart.
Your alibi isn't exactly ironclad, Jim...
...unless, of course, you got
a twin brother I don't know about.
You got a twin brother
I don't know about?
CLERK:
Dr. Ostrowski's in with patients.
- Would you like to make an appointment?
- It'll take a second.
Excuse me.
Walter Ostrowski?
- Uh... Yes.
- You have something...
...that belongs to us.
Uh... D...
Do I know you?
No, but we have a friend in common.
Someone in the diamond district.
[SIGHS]
- Moishe?
- Mm-hm.
Mm.
Um...
Why don't we talk in my office?
It's just across the hall.
[CAR APPROACHING, TIRES SQUEALING]
Please, please, don't kill me.
- Where's our stuff?
- What stuff?
- Passports, IDs, credit cards.
- Leather jacket.
- Everything you stole from our house.
- Your house? I don't...
Okay, okay, okay.
Tell Moishe I'll pay him.
I'll give you the money today.
It's in my office.
- Pay Moishe for what?
- Everything I owe him.
Please.
Just don't kill me.
- Let him go.
- Why?
He's not the guy who robbed us.
And go get Moishe's money.
That's why we're here?
Running a collections agency
for your fence?
Why we're here is because
our security system didn't work.
We're here because that boy
behaves less like John Connor...
...and more like John Baum every day.
"That boy," my son...
...has been through
more than you'll ever know.
Right back at you.
[DOOR SLAMS]
MOISHE:
My friends...
Is this what you're looking for?
Something for me, something for you.
It's business.
This is business.
- Please, I just buy the stones.
- Who sold you our diamonds?
Okay, okay. His name is Tristan Dewitt.
He lives in Reseda.
- Not good enough.
- It's true, I swear.
He's a friend of my cousin's.
A punk. That's all I know.
You killed Liko.
[LIKO GROANING]
Not yet.
[DOG BARKING]
JODY:
Never gonna find them like this.
Do you even know
how many people live in L.A. County?
An employee at the grocery store
saw them there...
...on more than one occasion.
It's highly likely they live
within a one-mile radius.
[ENGINE STARTS]
- I'm looking for this girl.
- No, sorry.
This is stupid.
Just take me back
to the halfway house.
Did you hear me?
I am done hanging out
with the creepy stalker.
I don't even know your name.
I came because I wanted
to get back at that bitch...
...and I thought you were kind of cute,
but you know what? You're not cute.
You're fricking Silence of the Lambs.
This is kidnapping, you know that, right?
I could have you arrested.
What are you doing?
Why are we stopping?
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Freak!
[LAUGHTER AND CHATTERING]
You're blocking the sun.
Had an interesting morning
with our friend Moishe.
He's dropping your name in front of people
who don't need to hear your name.
- Well, he's your fence.
- Well, he likes you better.
I'll have a talk with him.
Help me out, will you?
WOMAN:
Oh!
[CHATTERING AND LAUGHING]
How long are you planning on
keeping this up?
- What?
- You know what. All this.
Well, I'm certainly gonna try...
...to get through today
without you spoiling it for me.
Sun sets at 5:47.
I'm not missing that sucker.
[GIGGLES]
I'm not missing one of those again.
Mm.
I'm looking for this girl.
Why are you looking for her?
Has she done something?
She's my niece.
You know, you look really familiar.
Common face?
Have you seen my niece?
[SIGHS]
I haven't. I'm sorry.
The house next door,
it's on the market.
- You're listed as the contact.
- That house has been rented.
Thank you for your time.
Wow, you guys really know
how to party.
[CHUCKLES]
My mom's not much of a cook.
Oh. What about Cameron?
She's not really into food.
[PHONE RINGING]
You gonna get that?
No. If they need me,
they'll call my cell.
Oh, right,
because you're so important.
Hello? Baum residence.
Yeah, just a sec. Here's John.
[WHISPERS]
It's your neighbor.
Thanks.
- Yeah, hey, Kacy. What's up?
- John, I don't mean to bother you...
...but there was a guy here
looking for your sister.
When?
KACY: Just now.
I did not get a good vibe from him.
Something was just off, you know?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[GASPS]
What's the matter, John?
What's wrong?
- Out. We gotta get out.
- Why? Who's there?
- It's okay, I'll get rid of him.
- No. Now.
- I'll get rid of him!
- Riley.
[KNOCKING]
I'm looking for this girl.
She's my niece.
Sorry, I don't know her.
[CLICKS]
- Wish I could be more help. Good luck.
- How do you like your new house?
Oh, um...
It's really nice. I love it.
Excuse me,
what do you think you're doing?
Hello, you can't just
come into people's homes.
Hello? Are you listening to me?
What is wrong with you?
You're not in these photographs.
Maybe because
I was the one taking them.
Look, if you don't leave,
I'm calling the police.
Thank you for your time.
We were too supportive.
That was the problem in a nutshell.
Your son says
he wants to be a filmmaker.
You tell him, "Son, movies are great.
I love going to see them,
but that's pie in the sky.
You need a salaried job."
Thank you for not going
to the police about this.
We just want our things back.
"Come live at home," I told him,
"until you can get on your feet."
And every time I bring up the idea
of him getting a salaried job...
...he's got this project to work on,
or that short film he's producing.
He's had his troubles,
but he's a good boy.
He's not a boy, Donna.
He's a 34-year-old man.
He lives with us, working in
a video store, robbing people's homes.
Video store?
- Saturn Video, on La Brea.
- Who knows if that's true.
Every other word
out of his mouth was a lie.
Does your son have any friends
who might know where he is?
Anyone at the video store?
Dave.
Dave. Another boy wonder.
[TALKING IN SPANISH]
[DOOR BUZZES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
This is a very curious turn of events,
Mr. Ellison.
I'm innocent.
There's an eyewitness.
It wasn't me.
The witness is quite sure.
As I would be...
...if I had seen what he's seen.
Is there something
you want to tell me, James?
Something only I would believe?
Not here.
I'll be in touch.
Ms. Weaver...
...thank you for believing me.
What good is faith if we don't use it?
[DOOR BUZZES]
RILEY: Where are we going?
- Nowhere.
Anywhere.
That guy isn't really Cameron's uncle,
is he? Because then he'd be your uncle.
He's nobody's uncle.
Why is he after Cameron?
Is she a criminal or something?
No.
He is, all right?
Well, what if he comes back?
It's not how he works.
- I don't understand...
- He won't.
That guy is dangerous. That's all
you need to know. Really dangerous.
Well, I got rid of him, didn't I?
I stared him down and off he went.
- You got lucky.
- Oh, ease up, squinchie.
Lucky is my middle name.
Lucky Riley Dawson.
In that, Lucky was your first name.
Whatever. Stickler.
Admit it. I was a brave, spooky ninja.
It was totally badass.
Say it. Just say it.
It was badass.
I know.
Fools' errands and the fathers of Nablus.
- It's been a great day.
- Brothers.
- What?
- Brothers of Nablus.
Genesis, Chapter 34.
You've memorized the Bible?
Jacob's daughter, Dinah,
is raped by Shechem, prince of Nablus.
He falls in love with her.
Shechem's father comes to Jacob
and strikes a bargain...
...to allow his son to marry Dinah.
- That's brave of him.
- Jacob says yes...
...on the condition that all the men
in Shechem's town be circumcised.
Everybody gets what they want.
Three days later, while Shechem's men
were still in pain from the circumcision...
...Dinah's brothers rode into the city
and killed them all.
It's your kind of story.
Yes. My kind of story.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
MAN [OVER PHONE]: Ms. Baum?
- Yeah.
- This is Dan calling back...
...to let you know that somebody
just attempted a charge.
Where?
At a bowling alley in Van Nuys.
Alien Lanes.
[COMPUTER CHIRPS]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
KAPLAN:
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Just have a few more questions,
then we'll get you out of here.
So you say Mr. Ellison
was completely nude...
...when he killed Meyers.
I already told you that.
And that he killed him
with his bare hands?
- Didn't use a weapon?
- He strangled him.
Did Meyers fight back?
A little,
but the other guy was too strong.
How so?
Snapped his neck like it was nothing.
A toothpick.
Where was Mr. Ellison
before he killed Mr. Meyers?
- Out on the road.
- The road?
The road, the street, asphalt.
Anything unusual about the street?
Who cares about the street?
Are you lying about the street?
[SIGHS]
It was like a...
It was like a crater.
- A pothole?
- No.
It was like a complete dent
in the road.
[SIGHS]
So Mr. Ellison just appeared
out of thin air?
- There was a light.
- What kind of a light?
Bluish-purple.
It made, like, a crackling sound.
Like lightning?
So Mr. Ellison...
...emerged from this energy bubble?
I never said anything about a bubble.
But there was a bubble, correct?
So to be clear, you saw Mr. Ellison...
...materialize out of
this energy bubble...
...completely nude...
...walk to Peter Meyers, snap his neck,
steal his clothes, and then disappear?
I know what I saw.
Thank you for your assistance.
[EXHALES]
Oh!
Nice.
Okay, so...
...it's 1863 and Abraham Lincoln
is on the train to Gettysburg.
But then his train breaks down,
some small Pennsylvania town.
So he's gotta stay there overnight.
The only problem?
The town's overrun with zombies. Zhoo!
Ha-ha.
TRISTAN: Huh?
We shoot it on location in Gettysburg,
35 millimeter.
Dude, with what money?
What money?
Do you know how much we made
just off these right here?
SARAH:
Put it down.
That bag you're holding, it's mine.
Not anymore it isn't.
This place is closed, ladies.
Unless you want to get arrested,
I suggest you get out.
My jacket. Give it to me.
Come and get it.
- Come and give it to me.
- And the bag.
Oh.
[ZIPPER OPENS]
There's a credit card missing.
Hey. Just give it.
We used it on the arcades.
We'll pay you back.
Where's the other guy?
What other guy?
Stay here.
[GROANING]
[TRISTAN GRUNTS]
They knew where we live.
Don't. Please.
You know those guys out there?
Were you with them
when they robbed the house?
[INHALES DEEPLY, EXHALES]
You were never there. You were
never here. You never saw me.
You don't know
what happened here. Understand?
If you say anything to anybody
about what happened here...
...I'll hunt you down.
I'll kill you.
You wait five minutes and you run.
Understood?
- Clear?
- Yeah. Clear.
You're free to go.
What?
The witness is a nut job.
The judge kicked his statement.
We'll have you out of here in an hour.
Sorry you had to go through all this.
That's it?
You're a smart guy, Jim.
Take yes for an answer.
Good luck out there.
[INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[CLATTERING]
You said you were gonna have
a talk with him.
I did. It was short.
- What were you gonna say to him?
- Oh, you know me.
Funny Derek.
- How was the sunset?
- Never better.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
You never really struck me as the type
to stalk your ex-wife.
I'm sorry, I just...
I had an urge to see the house.
See something familiar.
Weird, I know.
You do realize
you don't live here anymore?
Yeah.
Fancy ride. No wonder we keep
losing people to civilian life.
Company car.
They lease it for me.
I have to tell you,
you don't look so well.
Yeah, I'm not.
I just...
I don't know, all that, I...
I miss it.
I miss my wife.
James, this is a really weird time
to start into all that.
No. No, I don't mean that.
Things have changed.
And I just...
- I didn't...
- You're not making sense.
Come on. Come inside. Paul can
make coffee. We'll talk about it.
Thanks, lamb.
I didn't come over for that.
Yes, you did.
This was the wrong thing for me to do.
I don't live here anymore.
It was the right thing to do.
Just five years too late.
Call me the next time you wanna
see something familiar.
I'll send you a picture.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[DRILL WHIRRING]
[DOOR UNLOCKS]
Who was it?
They won't be back.
Place looks good.
Yeah, well, I think we pretty much got
everything back to how it was.
We?
Riley helped.
So how'd you find them?
- Was it Derek's fence or what?
- You can't bring people here anymore.
What? She had nothing to do with this.
No, you did.
She just made it worse.
She's a security risk.
Really?
She's never tried to kill me.
You know that this has nothing
to do with Riley. Or the rules.
Or the security of this house.
You're pissed because I found someone
I actually like spending time with...
...and it's not you.
You think I don't want you
to have a normal life?
No. I don't.
Hey. We didn't choose this, John.
It chose us.
And there's nothing either of us can
do about it. My job is to protect you.
And you can hate me
as much as you want...
...but I will keep doing that
as long as I'm here.
Then why didn't you protect me
when I was killing Sarkissian?
Why didn't you protect me
when I had my hands around his throat?
Why didn't you protect me from that?
WEAVER:
It's a moray.
They're nocturnal predators.
Does it have a name?
No. It doesn't.
Please. Sit.
I read the witness report.
So did I.
He comes across as crazy,
doesn't he?
Who wouldn't?
You, if you'd tell me the truth.
There was another one of you,
wasn't there? A twin?
Yes.
Where is it now?
I don't know.
Why did it come?
I think I'm being tested.
Like Job?
You know the story?
He suffered worse
than any man before him.
Everything he loved was taken away.
Everything but his life.
But he didn't renounce God.
And God spared him.
So who spared you?
[CRYING]
Where did you get those credit cards?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
She said...
...she would find me.
She said she would kill me.
I promise you...
...she won't.