NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
SARAH: Kaliba was building something.
WEAVER: John Henry was infiltrated.
MURCH: Someone out there wants to kill him.
- Who's John Henry?
He's my friend.
Savannah's survival may
someday depend upon John Henry.
What were you doing at the house?
Why'd you take the girl?
Protect her. Girl's in danger.
When we jumped,
you told me I died of cancer.
- She's lost weight.
- What?
Let me talk to Weaver.
I'll meet with Connor.
Make it happen.
MAN [OVER PA]: Put your hands
behind your head. Kneel on the ground.
[DOOR OPENS]
I know you've been told this...
...but as I am a "measure twice,
cut once" kind of carpenter...
...I wanna reiterate
that you have the right to an attorney...
...if you are so inclined,
and if you are not...
...anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
Not inclined.
Fair enough and noted.
Here's where we come down
on all this.
Ten years ago,
you murdered one Miles Dyson...
...employee of Cyberdyne.
Long time gone, but the man's still dead,
so we've got that.
Eight years ago, you and your son
and a high school friend of his...
...blow up a bank vault
and die in the explosion.
Now, of course, you're still alive,
which is inconvenient for many...
...but the bank's still blown,
so we've got that.
More recently,
and by that I mean Monday...
...you participated in a firefight,
leaving five dead...
...and kidnapping
one Savannah Weaver...
...daughter of Catherine Weaver
and citizen of Scotland...
...making this an incident
both federal and international.
Two of the dead were
law-enforcement officers...
...and that usually gets you the needle,
but in that I do digress.
- Agent Aldridge?
- Yeah?
You're a funny boy.
That's what Mom says.
I never liked funny boys.
I doubt they like you either,
Ms. Connor.
There's two ways I can bring your son
into custody: with your help or dead.
- Which do you think it should be?
- My son?
Your son. John Connor.
- John is dead.
- I don't think so.
He died in the bank.
Oh, I don't think so.
I don't think anyone died in the bank.
- Well, you're wrong.
- Sometimes, but not today.
Not yet.
Think about it.
WOMAN [ON TV]: She was arrested
and is now in custody...
...facing a series of new charges
as well as a host of old ones.
Authorities are also on the lookout
for Connor's son...
...as well as a female accomplice.
Here are photos dating back eight years.
Both fugitives would now
be in their mid-'20s.
- We should move.
- This motel is out of the way.
The desk clerk could have clocked us.
Relocating within 24 hours
of the incident has high risk factors.
This room provides sightlines
down the highway.
This is not an incident.
This is my mother.
I need a computer.
I need to do research.
You want the blueprints
for the Los Angeles Jail.
Do I?
So you can plan
how to get your mother out.
I'm not going to let you.
You should know that.
- I do know that by now.
- Then what is there to research?
Power sources.
Shielded nuclear-power sources.
- Like mine?
- Just like yours.
Why?
I wanna know if being around them
all the time can give you cancer.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON TV]
MAN [ON TV]: Also in the news,
authorities have arrested Sarah Connor...
...a known domestic terrorist.
She's seen here being escorted to...
Okay, it's a large room...
...it's dark, it's quiet,
it's impossible to see.
- You may wanna roll a scan.
- I'll roll a scan.
- I rolled a one.
- One. Oh, okay. Tough luck.
You don't see the umber hulk
as it crawls from its nest in the stone...
...and attacks you.
You take three hit points of damage
from a bite to the shoulder.
I attack the umber hulk.
Twenty.
Wow.
Okay, that's a crit with the
vorpal longsword to the umber hulk.
Unbelievable.
Lucky roll.
Hello, Ms. Weaver. I just delivered
a crit hit to the umber hulk.
Congratulations. Mr. Murch?
Who's winning, Mr. Murch?
MURCH:
Oh, it's not really that kind of game.
But I'm a little bummed
that he killed the umber hulk so fast.
You've considered he can roll
whatever number he desires?
Mr. Murch...
...how long will it take
to disassemble everything for transport?
Uh, everything?
You mean, like, everything?
Is that something
you're planning on doing?
No. But John Henry's
been attacked once.
We should be prepared.
John Henry was hacked.
And we fixed that.
Besides, I think we're past the point
where moving the hardware's a good idea.
In fact, I think it's potentially
a really bad idea.
Oh? How's that so?
For example...
...the other day, one of the fan wires
on a server was glitchy.
So we switched it out.
Same wire. Same length. Identical.
Like, uh, changing a spark plug.
- And...?
- Sort of tweaked him.
WEAVER:
I'm not sure what you're getting at.
What I'm getting at is I think
what we know to be John Henry...
...only exists as this specific collection
of hardware and software.
Body and soul.
We change a wire,
we change John Henry.
Yes.
Mr. Murch?
I'm ready to confront
the mind flayer now.
Twenty.
They followed me to the movie theater.
I didn't know. I swear.
I spent the last four hours convincing
them we weren't in this together.
Maybe I should tell them we were.
Maybe we were in this together.
- I just wanted the girl to be safe.
- So did I.
- From whom?
- I don't know.
Don't know or you can't say?
I don't know. If I did,
I probably couldn't say.
They wanna know
what you've been doing for 10 years.
What did you tell them?
I told them I have no idea
what you've been doing.
What else could I tell them?
You could tell them.
Tell them everything
you've been doing.
You could draw them a picture...
...of everything they know
and everything you know.
If you're innocent, you could do that.
The last time I drew a picture...
...I ended up in a psych ward.
Maybe things would be different now.
Maybe you got nothing to lose.
There's always something to lose.
I am sorry for this.
Yeah, sure you are.
Where's the girl?
Back with her mother.
Where else would a child be?
She's not safe.
Agent?
Mr. Ellison, come in.
It's open.
This is where they stick us now.
Pretty sure I know what the subtext is,
but I refuse to read that deep.
- She's not budging on the son.
- Maybe she's telling the truth.
Maybe she's a liar lacking
the proper motivation to tell the truth.
But she's got a guilty conscience.
- What makes you think that?
- Well...
...for starters,
she's requested a priest.
- What?
- Yep. A man of the cloth in the flesh.
Black and white and God all over.
- Father Armando Bonilla ring a bell?
- No.
Can't imagine what the connection is.
It ever occur to you
she just might wanna pray?
Not for a second.
Other than a lawyer,
a priest is the only other person...
...she could ask to speak with
that we can't listen to.
[DOOR OPENS]
Buenos días, Father.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Do you remember me?
You and your son hid in my church.
There was a problem
with your daughter.
At least that is what you told me.
Yeah. She's better now.
Where is she?
She's in hiding.
With my son. I don't know where.
And they are wanted?
You have included them
in your crimes.
Do you believe in the devil, Father?
The devil?
Do you believe in the actual devil?
Something opposes God.
Something tempts man into sin.
I don't know about God or heaven.
But I do believe that someone or something
wants this world to burn.
The devil. Demons.
I believe.
And that day in the church?
My daughter?
You saw things, didn't you?
I pray...
...every day to understand...
...what happened that day.
I can explain it to you.
I don't know if you'll believe me,
but I can explain it to you.
And after I'm done, I'm gonna ask you
to do something for me.
Will you do something for me?
WEAVER:
Mr. Ellison. Welcome back.
How are your friends
in law enforcement?
in law enforcement, Mr. Ellison?
Very determined.
What is this?
WEAVER:
Sarah Connor is talking with a priest.
Father Armando Bonilla.
I can see that.
Why is it here?
Why are you watching it?
WEAVER: John Henry monitors
all law-enforcement channels.
It seems prudent.
It seems illegal.
So is lying to the FBI.
Don't think now is the time to be
parsing which laws we'll obey.
- And which we will not.
- Now's not the time.
I heard it when she said it.
- Those cameras should be off.
- I want to meet him.
The priest?
No. The boy.
You wanna meet John Connor?
Someone's attacked my family.
They may attack again.
I think he knows something.
And besides, he saved my daughter.
- And I want to thank him.
- Thank you.
Can we talk outside?
It's a bad idea.
I don't know
what you think John knows.
I know he was at my house
when the attacker showed up.
I want to know why.
His mother thinks he's the messiah.
And despite your reluctance
to tell me...
...I surmise that he
and his cyborg companion...
...are connected
to the John Henry body.
And I want to know why.
Yes, she's a cyborg.
Don't pretend you didn't know.
She's dangerous.
And you think I need protecting.
That's sweet.
But don't ever lie to me again.
Now, about John Connor...
I don't know how to find him.
Well, I do.
Twenty.
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
How?
- Ammo?
- Silencers.
You know we can't sell
that kind of stuff.
Ask to speak to Manny.
I want to speak to Manny.
Call the number first. Then ask.
You know, I always thought the best
thing about those guns was the sound.
No, it's not.
How much weight has she lost?
You think she has cancer because she's
lost weight. How much has she lost?
Eleven percent of her mass
in the last six weeks.
She was healthy
before you showed up.
That's all I know. She was healthy.
If my power source
was leaking radiation, I would know.
I have sensors for that.
- Where are they?
- You can't see them.
Of course not.
I just have to trust you on it.
But stuff does go wrong with you,
doesn't it?
Stuff breaks.
You kill birds, you twitch.
You try to murder me.
You're not perfect.
You're a machine.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Mom?
Uh, yes, I remember you.
Buenos días to you too, Father.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Underneath the bench
there is an envelope.
I hope it is enough.
It's all I could find.
I have a message for you as well.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
What's wrong?
The IDs are flawless.
They're flawless.
There's nothing else there.
There's nothing hidden there.
No secret message there
for her escape.
I am to tell you this...
...from your mother:
Leave this place.
As soon as it is safe...
...leave this place.
Do not think of her.
Do not come for her.
Leave.
You are to make sure that he does.
We lose everybody we love.
She said that?
No.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
That's interesting.
[GUN COCKS]
Let me repeat, I had nothing
to do with your mother's arrest.
If I had, there'd be a SWAT team
outside your door right now.
Same thing would happen to this SWAT
team as happened to your last one.
Catherine Weaver
would like to meet you.
Why?
She wants to thank you
for saving Savannah.
Well, she just did.
Your mother wanted to meet her.
Well, when my mother gets out,
trust me, she will.
I told Miss Weaver you'd never
come without your mom.
She said if that was the case,
I'm supposed to ask one question.
She says I'm supposed to ask you:
"Will you join us?"
She says she hopes
you'll know what that means.
Do you know what that means?
No, I don't.
Please leave now, Mr. Ellison.
I think you've said enough.
- John...
- You've said enough, Mr. Ellison.
I won't ask you again.
He upset you.
Me?
I think he upset you.
You know that's impossible.
Is it?
You said it yourself, John.
I'm just a machine.
I believe you.
You believe me what?
I believe there are machines.
I believe they've come back from the
future to first kill you and then your son.
I believe in time travel,
I believe in cyborgs.
I believe there's a world
that I've not yet seen...
...but you have, and John.
In the last eight hours,
I've received 37 calls...
...from people who have met
a young man named John Baum...
...or his sister Cameron,
or Sarah Baum, the mother.
They now know her
to be Sarah Connor.
By all accounts your son looks
16 and not 24...
...just as you look 35 and not 43.
I believe you have participated
in the miraculous and the terrible...
...and through it all, you have maintained
a moral and good soul.
I want to help you.
I wanna help your son.
Help me do that.
My son is dead.
- Do you know who Danny Dyson is?
- Danny?
Miles Dyson's son.
Do you know where he is?
No.
Why?
He's been missing three months.
Hey.
You the guy
who smashed through my gate?
Yes.
Hey. I liked that gate.
Catherine Weaver?
Sure.
[WOUNDS SLITHERING]
The chip has been treated
with a phosphorus compound.
- When exposed to oxygen...
- It burns up.
I know what happened.
I saw it happen.
Can any data be recovered?
I can try, but it's highly doubtful.
We need to know what it knows.
Who sent it?
It is safe to assume
my brother sent it.
Mr. Ellison, where have you been?
Where have I been?
It's 7 in the morning. I've been asleep.
- Didn't you get my message?
- It was very disappointing.
Did you give the message
exactly as I said it?
Of course. Look, I told you before...
...she'll never leave his side,
and he'll never leave his mother's.
[IN UNISON]
We'll see.
Don't do that.
My mom used to do that.
I really hate that.
What's going on?
You need to understand how it works.
- What?
- This chip.
This body.
The software is designed
to terminate humans.
The hardware is designed
That's our sole function.
- Not you.
- No.
Not anymore.
But what was there is still there.
It'll always be there.
So down deep...
...you wanna kill me.
Yes.
I do.
Then why don't you?
I might some day.
I need to show you something.
This body.
Get on top of me.
Put your knee here.
Right here.
If I'm damaged, we should know.
Reach down under the breastplate.
There.
What does it feel like?
Cold.
That's good, right?
That's good.
That's perfect.
John.
It's time to go.
[PHONE RINGING]
CAMERON [OVER PHONE]:
Buenos días, Father Bonilla.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
It's okay.
GUARD:
Door.
[LOCK CLICKS]
You did what I asked?
I did.
And? Why are you here?
They have a message for you.
She's coming.
[ALARM WAILING]
I don't know what to do.
You're a priest.
Pray.
[GUN COCKS]
[MURMURING INDISTINCTLY]
What's that Bible story?
The one where the locks fall off?
- Peter.
- Yeah. That's a good one.
Gird thyself.
[MEN CHATTERING]
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
INMATE:
Go, go, go!
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[SCREAMS]
There's been a bit of an incident.
At the jail?
JOHN HENRY:
Yes.
- Any idea how it started?
- Yes.
Look there.
And there.
You look like hell.
Can you keep up?
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PA]
I sent you a message. I told you...
Yeah, bad John Connor. Ground me.
Are you okay?
I'm not 100 percent.
How far from 100 percent are you?
Why?
I need to meet Catherine Weaver.
And she needs to destroy whatever's
in that basement.
God, I really wish
we weren't here right now.
Savannah could tell them
we know about Cromartie.
John Henry now.
Metal.
If she tells them, they'll move it.
Maybe they already have.
Well, we'll know soon enough.
Mom, are you sick?
Cameron thinks you're sick.
She does?
You've lost weight.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
I love you.
Where's Cameron?
In the car.
Expecting trouble?
No change for the meter.
You're not armed, are you?
Expecting trouble?
No reason for that.
No reason at all.
[GRUNTING]
Hello.
I know you.
And I know you.
Will you join us?
So. Why are we here?
- We need...
- Let me restate.
We are here, first and foremost,
so that I can thank you...
...for your heroism
regarding my daughter Savannah.
She's the light of my life,
and I'd be lost without her.
And where is she?
Let's assume school.
We have a common enemy.
One we cannot fight
with conventional weapons or means.
Kaliba?
Don't presume to know Kaliba.
I'm sorry, I wasn't speaking to you.
I was speaking to you.
About Skynet.
Savannah's told you about John Henry,
I assume?
Which is why your cyborg
is skulking around my basement.
What the hell?
Get down.
Run.
WEAVER:
The basement.
Mr. Ellison.
- John Henry.
- We need to get out.
They're trying to kill my son.
No, they're trying to kill my son.
Just like you are.
- I'm sure she's done it.
- You better hope not.
Your John may save the world,
but he can't do it without mine.
Her chip, it's gone.
Well, where is he? The... John Henry?
He took her chip. Where did he go?
WEAVER:
He didn't take the chip.
- She gave it to him.
- John.
Where is he?
Not where.
When.
What? What do you mean, when?
I know that. I've seen it before.
Is that the Turk?
That's Andy Goode's Turk.
Three dots.
You lying Terminator bitch.
You're building Skynet.
No.
I was building something to fight it.
And I'd watch
who's calling who a bitch.
- Coming, James?
- Coming?
After John Henry.
- Our boy.
- He's not my boy.
- And you, you...
- Mind picking up Savannah, then?
Gymnastics ends at 5:30.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
John, we can't.
He's got her chip.
He's got her.
Mom.
I'll stop it.
Where's Cameron?
- Where's her body?
- It doesn't go through.
[DOGS BARKING]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Got one.
- Got one.
- One what? What?
- Please, I'm not metal.
- Don't move. Don't move.
I swear I haven't got anything.
I'm... I'm human.
Because I will blast you.
MAN: Stand down.
Look in his eyes.
He's got about as much metal in him
as you do.
Derek?
Yeah?
John.
John Connor.
I know a lot of people, kid.
I don't know you.
Anybody heard the name
John Connor?
Well, you know what?
I think you're gonna be famous.
My brother's back,
and you're wearing his coat.
SARAH:
I love you too.