NARRATOR: Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
Where's the metal?
- Who are you?
- My name's Winston.
DEREK: I talked to your mom.
She found something in the desert.
- It has something to do with those dots.
- Is it real this time?
Well, the bullet in her leg sounds real.
You stay, I'll go. You made your call.
This is what living with it means.
I detected this audio transmission
on an unsecured line.
MAN 1 [ON RECORDING]: Got a breach,
man shot out at Heat and Air.
MAN 2: Well, you know the drill.
Shut the place down.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
MAN [ON RADIO]: Authorities are trying
to determine the cause of the blast...
...which killed 32 employees of
the Desert Canyon Heat and Air plant...
...earlier this week. A vigil is scheduled
for today in Charm Acres...
...the desert enclave
that served as a town...
...for the workers and their families.
Area schools and many of the town's
local businesses will be closed in obser...
CAMERON: Native Americans believe
that when their pictures are taken...
...their souls are stolen
and locked in the photograph forever.
I think you're safe.
God, I hate funerals.
I hate Skynet.
This sounded easy when we talked
about it on the way up...
- ...but now that I see all these people...
- Just find somebody to talk to, John.
Everybody who knew anything
about the factory is dead.
- Well, I'm not.
- Yeah, well, I guess you're lucky.
I'd feel luckier
if we could find somebody...
...who knew what was going on
out there.
You'd never guess he had it in him.
No. I see it.
That seat taken?
Are you gonna say annoying things?
- Annoying things?
- "I can't believe it's happening."
"It comes in waves."
"I just feel numb."
No, I will try not to say those things.
I'm John.
Zoe.
So you know somebody
in Charm Acres, John?
Or are you just a sucker
for a small-town, homey vigil?
My mom worked at the factory...
...so she, uh, you know,
came to pay her respects.
So you got dragged along.
Little drag, also some push.
Seemed like the right thing to do.
Stupid thing to do.
If you had a choice.
Did you have a choice?
Funeral crasher.
Stupid funeral crasher.
Am I crazy or is that girl
creepily staring at us?
That would be my sister.
I don't like that.
No. No reason to.
That's my mom.
My dad worked at the factory.
- Sorry.
- I picked out his suit this morning.
You know, to bury him in?
I picked a gray one. Henry said
I should've picked black.
He looked better in gray, though.
Speak of the Henry devil.
They're about to do the candle lighting.
Hi, I'm John.
Is that your boyfriend?
You know, he keeps applying for the job.
I'm just not hiring.
It was nice to meet you, John.
MAN:
Do not stand at my grave and weep
I am not there; I do not sleep.
I am a thousand winds that blow
I am the diamond glint on snow
I am the sunlight on ripened grain
I am the gentle autumn rain.
When you awaken
in the morning's hush...
Excuse me.
He hated having his picture taken.
You wouldn't know it by looking
at him there, but he did.
- Excuse me, I'll leave you to...
- No, no, no. It's okay.
It's actually refreshing
to see an unfamiliar face.
Everybody here,
all I see are the people that they've lost.
All I see is what's missing.
I'm Sarah.
Diana. Winston.
So did you know my husband, Sarah?
[GUNSHOT]
[ORGAN PLAYING MUSIC]
Gene used to project old movies
on his garage door.
Every Saturday night
during the summer...
...there'd be couples out in the driveway
with their beers and popcorn...
...watching Casablanca
or Out of the Past or His Girl Friday.
I just went for the free beer.
I've been to a lot of places for that.
I can't remember the last movie
that Ed and I saw together.
Or when.
I used to just leave his dinner in
the fridge for whenever he came home.
It wasn't the easiest place to work.
I was only there for a few months,
but long enough to figure that out.
I can't tell you how many times
I wanted to make a call...
...or write a letter and ask them
what kind of security...
...they had Ed doing that kept him
out of the house seven days a week.
- But you never do that.
- No one does that.
Not here.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Do you have him, Mr. Walsh?
No, ma'am. He's proven a bit harder
to locate than I had anticipated.
You assured me it'd be
a very simple job.
I know, ma'am. Everyone I've spoken to
thinks that he's dead.
Died in the explosion at the factory.
WEAVER: I can tell you he isn't.
He didn't.
WALSH: I've got a good lead on him, ma'am.
I hope so, Mr. Walsh.
ELLISON: I must have missed the memo
about wearing plaid today.
Oh, yeah.
Don't worry, it's not a company policy.
It's just something a few of us do.
Paying homage, you know?
To whom?
Weaver. Lachlan Weaver.
Today's the anniversary of his death.
- Did you know him?
- Yeah, he was... He was a great guy.
You know, he was a genius.
He was funny as hell.
They both were, you know, back then.
Good morning, Mr. Ellison.
Mr. Murch.
Ms. Weaver.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
I'm going to say a few words
about my friend Gene Miller...
...but before I do, I wanna take
this opportunity to thank everyone...
...at Desert Heat and Air's
parent company, The Kaliba Group...
...for their generous donations
to this service.
And not just for the beautiful flowers
you see around our chapel...
...but also
for the generosity and kindness...
...they've extended to the families
in this very difficult time.
Is this all it costs to buy us?
Flowers and a few kind words?
Where is anybody from the company?
Have any of you seen anybody
from the company?
Has anybody ever seen anybody
No. You have not.
- Diana.
- Stop it.
Let us pray.
[CRYING]
The first six years of our marriage
we lived in nine states.
Ed was in the military...
...so when he got the chance
to settle down...
...you know, the nice company car,
the big house, the even bigger salary...
...I pushed him to take that job.
Head of security
for Desert Canyon Heat and Air.
Come on, what kind of heat-and-air
factory needs that kind of security?
- What did you do there?
- Me?
Um...
Coffee and sandwich cart.
Waitress on wheels.
- I never knew what went on there.
- No one does.
Ed never said a thing about it, and
every time I'd ask, he'd shut me down.
So I stopped asking.
We all did.
None of this is your fault.
Ed was a decent man.
Whatever went on there,
he was a decent man.
Decent people
can get caught up in things.
I found these
when I was going through Ed's things.
I've never seen them before in my life.
This one goes to a storage locker.
You don't have a storage locker,
do you?
No.
I've been meaning to go.
But then I get scared.
So I tell myself,
some doors are better left unopened.
Not this one.
- Looks like you could use a lift.
- What's that?
- A lift. You want one?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
- Yeah?
- Uh, great, thanks.
Appreciate it.
Condolences.
It's not my funeral, but thanks.
I'm an OSHA investigator.
Looking into the explosion.
Hmm.
Big change from being a cop.
Yeah. Twenty-three years, Baltimore.
Fourth Precinct. Pikesville.
You a local?
My wife worked up at the plant.
She, uh... She knew a lot of these people.
My condolences.
- So, what do you think?
- About what?
What happened.
I think it's too early to tell.
- Would you, even if you knew?
- Tell?
- Yeah.
- No.
- People say it wasn't an accident.
- Is that right?
They say something was going on there
other than heating and air conditioning.
- Something as in what, exactly?
- That's what I'm asking you.
Suppose you knew something
was going on up there...
...what would you do?
- Absolutely nothing.
That's what I said.
- Thanks for the ride.
- No problem.
- I'm gonna walk the rest of the way.
Good luck with your investigation.
DIANA:
Empty.
I did not know that man.
I loved him, but I didn't know him.
Sometimes that's for the best.
He called me. Ed did.
Three days ago, for the last time.
He must have dialed by accident.
WINSTON [ON RECORDING]: My name's
Winston. I install air conditioning, all right?
Please don't hurt me.
I have a wife.
[GRUNTING]
[CRYING]
What happened to him, Sarah?
I can't die here.
Somebody tell me
I'm not gonna die here.
You won't die here.
I hate these people.
I don't relate to any of them.
Great. Thanks, Zoe.
Hey, what if we just kept driving?
Got on the highway and didn't stop
till we hit somewhere amazing.
The Grand Canyon.
I went there when I was a kid.
My mom and I took mules
down into the canyon.
Sounds cool.
It would have been if my mule wasn't
completely schizo. He ate my spare shirt.
I've never been.
Got a postcard from there once.
Seriously, if you start talking about Mike
Thompson, I'm getting out of the car.
- Boyfriend?
- Ex. And he was a good guy.
- Until he ditched me.
- What happened?
He was just like the rest of us.
His mom worked at the plant.
Mike was just a normal, funny guy.
He liked watching Monty Python movies
and playing lacrosse.
What happened to him?
Apparently, his mom had violated
some confidentiality agreement...
...or something at the plant.
They just up and left
in the middle of the night.
Mike never said a word about it.
I woke up one morning
and he was just gone.
A few months later, I got a postcard
from the Grand Canyon.
- He was a real prize.
- Shut up, Henry.
Why don't you think about somebody
besides yourself for once, huh?
You're not the only person
who's lost someone.
- Zoe's not in love with you.
- What?
She doesn't love you
the way you love her.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
- Get out of the car.
- What?
I want them out.
ZOE:
Henry, just go. Go.
- Are you gonna go?
- No.
- Hey, what...? What are you doing?
- Get out.
- Make a right up here.
- What the hell is going on?
Look, I can't deal with another funeral,
Henry. Not right now.
Hey, do you wanna see something
really messed up?
One day you'll be out here,
and they're lying there like that, dead.
And the next day, they're gone.
Like Mike.
- Yeah, like Mike.
- What's killing them?
Idiots with guns.
No bullet wounds.
What are you,
Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman?
Maybe it's the water.
You'd think people
would've picked up on that.
ZOE:
They always did wanna be rich.
That's what Henry said.
His mom wanted the good things.
Be careful what you wish for, huh?
What do you mean?
Insurance money.
The company's agreed to pay.
We're all rich.
Woo-hoo.
What did Henry's father do
at the plant anyway?
He went to work in the morning,
came home at night...
...didn't talk about it.
Same as everybody else
that worked there.
What's so secret
about heating and air conditioning?
The secret is it wasn't
heating and air conditioning.
- What was it?
- Some kind of government project.
That's what I think.
There's some smart people around here.
Real smart.
So you think, what,
that somebody sabotaged the plant...
...and killed all these people?
Your father?
It wasn't an accident, John.
Moo.
[SINGING "IN THE SWEET BY AND BY"]
The guy who shot me was either
a serial killer or a true believer.
His wife thinks he was murdered.
She's right.
But nothing about the, uh, thing
you think you saw?
The drone or whatever?
I don't think I saw it. I saw it.
Who's he?
Looking for something.
I figure the best way to find out
what it is, is to let him find it.
He made you.
He'll try and lose you,
but he doesn't know me. I'll handle it.
Always do.
Skynet's here, Reese. I can feel it.
Hm.
What?
You called me Reese again.
That's what you used to call him,
isn't it?
Kyle?
Maybe you should try to let him go.
Maybe you should.
Is Henry gonna be okay?
Henry smokes a lot of weed.
You know,
my father died before I was born.
Yeah, well, my father's a pile of ashes
somewhere, so I guess we're screwed.
I thought you picked out a gray suit
to bury him in.
Why am I even talking to you?
You don't know me.
You don't know
what I'm going through.
Stop trying to make it seem like
you're some kind of sensitivity expert.
You don't know anything.
She's not crying.
She's not doing a lot of things.
Mr. Ellison. Come in.
You've changed your tie.
Is that plaid?
Yes, um. I went home at lunch.
I hope you don't mind.
I spoke to Mr. Murch and he spoke of...
- Lachlan's death.
- My sympathies.
Yes. Thank you.
I remember when my father died.
He was a...
He was a tough man.
We didn't get along.
Even so, it took me a long time
to come to terms with his passing.
I threw myself into work
so I wouldn't have to.
- Was this recent?
- Recent enough.
- Then you understand.
- I do.
So how does Savannah do with this?
- "Do"?
- How is she dealing...
...with her father's death?
Dr. Sherman was very helpful
in that regard.
Now he's gone too.
Children are nothing if not resilient.
I'm surprised she's not here.
- Why?
- Being the anniversary, I mean.
Yes, I guess that is surprising.
Dr. Sherman felt it was important
for a child to maintain a regular routine.
Today's not the day for excitement.
Would you excuse me, Mr. Ellison?
I'm feeling emotional.
Yes. Of course.
Victoria?
VICTORIA [OVER INTERCOM]: Ms. Weaver?
Find my daughter and bring her to me.
[CHATTERING]
JOHN: You know, there are times, and
I'd have to say that this is one of them...
...where it seems every logical step
we take leads to the most bizarre place.
You mean crashing that poor guy's wake
and eating his widow's shrimp skewers?
Yeah, Derek. I mean that.
- What's the point?
- You know what the point is.
Your mom thinks that factory
was linked to Skynet.
Yeah. And you think she's nuts.
Doesn't mean I think she's wrong.
She hasn't looked at her father's picture
since we've been here.
Not once.
- Neither has her mother.
- Yeah. And?
If you had a photo of Kyle Reese,
you'd look at it, wouldn't you?
Maybe there's something
I don't understand.
He's not dead.
That's a big leap.
Let me repeat. If you had a photo of
your brother, would you not look at it?
He's not dead.
We should find him before he is.
What are you doing
in my parents' room?
Your father's alive, isn't he?
Get out.
Let me go.
I know you're scared.
You wanna protect him.
- You don't know what's been going on.
- Get away.
- Let me help you.
- You can't.
Yes, I can.
No.
Derek?
DEREK:
Hey. Where are you?
- In a garage.
- Garage? Where?
It's a long story. Where are you?
We're at a wake.
A fake wake.
The whole place was wired.
Every house in the neighborhood.
Every move anyone ever made
was being watched.
Skynet work camp.
This is how they were set up.
People working for the machines
monitored by other people...
...working for the machines.
Who are you people?
I need to know
what they were building.
I need to know who owned it,
and I need to know right now.
I don't... How would I know?
- Because the tunnel led to your garage.
- My husband's garage.
Look, we don't know you people.
You could be responsible for this.
You could be some terrorist organization.
We're some kind of terrorist
organization. Believe me...
...if someone hadn't blown up that plant,
I would. Now, where is your husband?
He's dead.
No. He's not dead. Yet.
Wait. Wait, please. He's innocent.
- He is. John, you have to believe me.
- No, I don't have to.
I was with him when he got news
everyone was dead. He freaked.
He was trying to figure out what to do.
He didn't know. He was scared.
- Like we all are.
- What were they building at the plant?
- Nobody knows.
- How can you not?
How can any of you not know? How
can you sleepwalk through your lives?
- Tell us what they were building.
- Just stop it.
He told us he was gonna play dead.
He told us everybody died,
that he should've died...
...and it would be better if that's what
everybody thought. That's what he said.
You think I'm sad, that I am pathetic.
That I sleepwalked through all of this.
Well, maybe you're right. Maybe I looked
the other way. We all did.
Every one of us.
Maybe that's not what you think
you would do...
- ...but that's what most do.
- You don't owe them...
There's no plant now. No plant.
No Charm Acres.
But it is a lot of insurance money.
Enough for my family to get lost
and start over.
So I didn't ask any questions.
Why would I start now,
when we are so close?
Look at this.
I pulled this from the archives.
Mike?
Daddy?
You may not like asking questions...
...but me, once I get started,
I can't stop.
JOHN:
Mom.
I think I know where he might be.
Hey.
Excuse me.
I've been watching you.
You wanna know what I see?
What do you see, Diana?
Ed would say, you don't smell right.
Well, I guess Ed would know.
Look, I deserve the truth.
I opened up to you.
Sometimes it's better not to ask
too many questions.
- You're crying.
- No.
Yes, you are.
Come here.
I want to tell you something.
I remember when my father died.
He was a tough man.
We didn't get along.
Even so, it took me a long time
to come to terms with his passing.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I miss Daddy.
What do you miss about him?
He used to read me stories.
- I can read you a story.
- He did it better.
You know, any time you want
to see your father, we have videos.
It's not the same.
Why?
I can't sit on his lap.
Come, sit on my lap.
Your lap is cold.
I know.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[CAR DOORS SLAMMING]
Where are we, John?
What is this place?
I don't know.
[WATER BURBLING]