NARRATOR: In the future, a computer
program called Skynet...
...will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time...
...taking human form
to terminate John Connor...
...the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor, John's mother,
teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogrammed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle and a
commanding officer with the Resistance.
Together, they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow
starts today.
NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
SARAH: What happened in the explosion
flipped a switch.
- You don't know what you're doing.
- You'll kill me.
I love you, please.
I love you, John, and you love me.
SARAH: You can fix her, but I can't let you.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm looking for the Connors.
- Sarah?
Mr. Dixon wanted to marry Sarah
before you.
- Maybe he's hiding her.
- If one of them follows you here...
- ...you'll have killed us.
- You died two years ago.
It was cancer. You died.
Ugh!
Hey.
[GRUNTS]
DEREK:
Did you sleep?
What do you do with a guard dog
you can't trust?
What, that one?
I'd have spent the night talking to him.
Yeah, I think she's outside
his jurisdiction.
Just a wire knocked loose
or something.
- So he says.
- But she's nothing but wire.
It's only a matter of time.
- That's healing quickly.
- Quicker than yours.
What about the rest of you?
You're back to normal?
Things have changed, John.
- What things?
- You can't be trusted anymore.
- Me? I can't be trusted anymore?
- You risked your life to fix me.
That was a very dangerous thing to do.
That could upset people.
They'll have to deal with it.
Not them.
What did she say?
Nothing.
You should go to school.
Start on a new place.
School. Really?
You always talk about how
English is so boring.
I think we could all use boring today.
Especially you.
- What about her?
- Last thing she is, is boring.
I'll keep her with us.
[CLASS BELL RINGING]
So you've been sitting in the same spot
since you bailed out on English.
I figure it must have
some kind of redeeming value.
You're in Mr. Hendrick son's class, right?
It's Mr. Amadon's class, weirdo.
And, yeah, I'm third row,
second from the left.
Right.
- And your name is?
- It's Riley.
Way to flatter a girl.
Look, Riley, I really...
- I don't mean to be rude...
- Let me guess...
...you are just way too busy
for company right now?
Obviously.
[CLASS BELL RINGING]
- Don't you have somewhere to be?
- Don't you?
Hey, you got 20 bucks?
- Yeah, why?
- I'm still hungry.
There's three bedrooms...
Four, if you count the nursery...
...and why wouldn't you?
This one here's the master suite.
DEREK:
I'll check the electric.
- So you live next door?
- Mm-hm.
- Where did the owners go?
- In Tokyo for a year.
Bob's the last-minute fill-in for his boss.
Guy stroked out three days
before he was supposed to leave.
Don't feel bad. I met the guy once...
...and he grabbed my ass,
with his wife five feet away.
Not this ass, of course.
- Car accident.
- Oh.
The whole family.
- Teaching that one to drive.
- You're kidding me.
I don't kid about teenagers.
I can't even imagine.
- How many months are you?
- Seven.
- I feel like a whale.
- You look great.
I'm an orca with boobs.
There are worse things to be.
Do you wanna feel it? It's cool.
Everyone does.
It's crazy, right?
Once upon a time, you were inside her.
We can move in today.
Once I figure out
what to do with this stuff.
We'll take it. All of it.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Mrs. Dixon, I'm James Ellison, FBI.
May I come in?
I'm not here as an FBI agent.
I'm here to help you.
MICHELLE: I found it in a drawer
this morning after he went to work.
Charlie hates guns.
CHARLIE:
Mich, I'm home.
What's going on here?
We need to talk.
SARAH:
Hey, help!
Check the perimeter.
- Greenway.
- What?
DEREK: What? What are you trying to say?
Who?
- Stop Greenway.
- Who's Greenway?
- Who's Greenway? Hey.
- At Serrano Point.
- The power plant, Serrano Point?
- Two days.
"Two days" what?
Wait. Hey. No, no, no.
SARAH: Ah!
Hey.
He's from the future.
Sent here by John, I assume.
That's how he found us.
- You sure that's not broken?
- I'm sure I don't care.
You heard the guy: Serrano Point,
two days, stop Greenway.
- I'll handle it.
- I've seen how you handle it.
I send you and the land mine
to do this...
...I guarantee someone's
ending up dead.
Maybe somebody's supposed to.
And the other part of that equation is,
maybe not.
You coming?
It looks a lot different
than I remember.
SARAH: In the future, the Resistance
controls this plant?
Battle of Avala Beach,
December 8th, 2026.
Humans regain control of Serrano Point
from Skynet.
It's a key strategic hold.
One of our main sources of power.
The guy who died said something
about two days.
- What's happening in two days?
- Maybe Greenway will tell us.
Maybe Greenway's trying
to sabotage the plant.
- Think he'll tell us that?
- I think he will.
SECURITY:
Go ahead.
Okay.
Nuclear power plants supply 20 percent
of the nation's electricity.
But how do they work?
These lovely ladies are uranium
fuel rods, and they are hot.
WOMEN [ON TV]:
We're gonna start a chain reaction.
SQUIRREL:
Nuts.
Hot rods make the water boil.
The steam spins turbines.
Abracadabra. Energy.
We can't forget to cool the steam back
to water so the process can be repeated.
Or else we'll have a massive compromise
of the containment system.
I don't like taking on new temps,
I will tell you.
Still, perfect score
on your placement exam...
...security clearance...
...and I did have two janitors call in
some personal emergencies, so...
Come on.
Is there a reason why you two
are so rough around the edges?
- Car accident.
I can't have problems in my plant.
Stay out of the fuel building
without your protective gear on...
- ...or you could get crapped up.
- That doesn't sound very pleasant.
WOMAN: That's plant talk for getting
exposed to radiation.
Then you'd need a scrub down.
You don't want a scrub down.
MICHELLE:
Sarah's alive?
In L.A.?
And these things, they're not human?
They're...?
I can't... I can...
I don't love her anymore, babe.
Not like that.
Of all the things you just told me...
...she seems to be
the least of our problems.
ELLISON:
You two need to leave this place.
It's not safe here anymore.
Where is?
MAN:
Here you go.
Saint Bibiana.
- Saint who?
- Saint Bibiana.
It's the school that I went to
until 9th grade.
Well, 9th and a half, technically.
Because I got the boot for this.
Can you believe it?
So, what's your story?
You look a little...
Oh, it's just a car accident.
- I was teaching my sister how to drive.
- Did everyone check out?
- Check out?
- Is everyone okay?
Oh, yeah, we're fine. We're good.
We're alive...
...for now.
You're full of carrots and apples.
- Carrots and apples?
- Yeah. Carrots and apples.
You know, happy thoughts.
- I don't think that's really an expression.
- It's not?
I don't know.
Maybe if you're on a farm.
We're moving.
My mom found us
a new place this morning.
Is it nice?
I don't know. I haven't seen it.
Are you serious? She hasn't
shown you any pictures or anything?
She's not really the picture type.
Yeah, I totally know that type.
So you wanna come see it?
What? The mystery house?
Yeah, the mystery house.
You wanna come with me and see it?
GREENWAY: Check the cooling-pump
calibration on the PWR board.
It was fine yesterday.
We're less than 36 hours
from going online. Check it again.
I'd have a headache too if I had to
figure out those buttons.
They're just vitamins.
I'm Karen, by the way.
Carl. You're new?
Brand spanking.
Just moved here from Texas.
Really? Whereabouts?
- Little town called Elgin.
- Near Corpus Christi.
I was stationed
at Ingleside Naval Base.
Imagine that.
Neighbors and never even knew it.
I hear there's a big test tomorrow.
The reactor's going back online?
Exactly how's that work?
Hopefully, perfectly.
NELSON:
Greenway.
A word.
- Nice meeting you, Karen.
- Likewise.
NELSON: There's cautious,
and there's just plain paranoid, okay?
We're going online.
I'm sure as hell
not gonna let you stall us.
[SPEAKING INAUDIBLY]
JOHN:
Well, I guess this is it.
RILEY:
Sweet.
What's the matter?
Never brought a girl home before?
No.
- Well, I wonder where your room is.
- I don't know.
Well, let's go look for it.
She can't be serious.
WOMAN:
Hey, there you are.
Thanks, you guys.
Sir, one more please.
BARTENDER: You got it.
I'll have what he's having.
I'm drinking tonic water.
I won't have what he's having.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON JUKEBOX]
I waitressed for years.
On our break,
the other girls would smoke. I would...
Play with matches?
Study for my computer classes.
See how far it got me?
So, what's your story, Carl?
How do you end up at Serrano Point?
Started off in the Navy.
Served 12 years on a nuclear sub.
- Every girl loves a uniform.
- My ex didn't.
At least, not the one
with my name stitched to it.
- Bitch.
- Affirmative.
That's a good scar.
Got a good story to go with it?
I don't know about good,
but it's a story.
CAMERON:
Hi.
I'm Cindy. I'm new in town.
This looks like fun.
Well, Cindy, this may look like fun,
but Bob here's got 50 bucks...
...says he can beat anyone in this bar.
Ain't that right, Bob?
I'll play you, Bob.
- You ever played this game before?
- How hard could it be?
Oh, it's plenty hard, girl.
Let me show you.
Now, what you're gonna do is
take this stick and lean over the table.
Now slide it through your fingers.
Relax. And get a real good feel.
That's right.
Nice and easy.
Still my shot. Right, Bob?
So the first surgery, they went in,
took out most of the lymph nodes.
They went back in four months ago
and cleaned out the rest.
Luckily, they were able to go
through the same incision.
You don't hear many people
with cancer use the word "luckily."
Well, you'd be surprised.
After four rounds of chemo...
...you say a lot of things
you never thought you would.
Most of them I won't repeat.
Well, I've gone and spooked you.
No.
Yeah.
It's okay.
You wouldn't be the only one.
In a nuke plant, a guy with cancer
is sort of a black cat.
Funny thing is, 20 years around
nuclear reactors...
...I haven't been crapped up.
- Not once.
- Lucky.
See? Lucky.
There you go.
You seem like a good guy, Carl.
If no one will drink with you
because you're sick, then it's their loss.
That isn't why they won't drink with me.
Somebody just smashed
Greenway's windshield.
- Big guy with a crew cut.
- Greenway's got a lot of enemies.
He stopped the last reactor test
because of safety concerns.
If he stops the test tomorrow,
people fear the plant...
...will get shut down
and they'll lose their jobs.
He's concerned about a sensor board.
It's showing slight irregularities
in the coolant pumps.
I hacked into the computer
and read his notes.
Anyway, his boss is pressuring him
to ignore it. Says it's nothing major.
But if Greenway's right
and there is a problem...
The reactor could melt down.
Half the state would be contaminated.
Skynet wins.
But if Greenway stops the test
and they close down the plant...
The Resistance can't use it
in the future.
Skynet wins.
Wow, they didn't even leave
any pickles.
Check the freezer.
Oh, my God. You're a genius.
How did you know?
[CAR APPROACHING]
What's wrong?
- It's my mom.
- Is that a problem?
SARAH:
John?
Who are you?
This is Riley.
- From school.
- Hi, Mom.
Let's talk, you and I.
Riley? From school?
You never mentioned her before.
- That's because I just met her today.
- Really?
JOHN:
Mm-hm.
Now is not the time for this.
Now is not the time?
Well, when is the time?
For me, I mean.
To live my life.
Hey, if you guys are gonna keep
fighting about me, I can leave.
No.
Everything's fine.
Do you think about the future much?
JOHN:
Hm?
RILEY:
Future.
When you're out of your house,
away from your family?
You know...
...freedom?
Yeah. I think about the future a lot.
I don't know about freedom, though.
Parents are freaks.
Yours too?
Hey.
Look at the stars.
[PHONE BEEPING]
[BEEPING]
What are you doing in here?
This is a restricted area.
I'm looking for the supply room.
One of the lifts in the waste-barrel area
leaked hydraulic fluid.
You might as well take care of it
since you're here.
Suit up. Could get nasty in there.
[CRACKLING]
What is that? What does it mean?
Means you just got crapped up.
- Morning.
- Hey.
- What, did you sleep on the floor?
- Early riser.
- What's that?
- What's it look like?
Looks like a robot.
It's a robot, big scary man...
...whatever. He's for you.
To protect you while you sleep.
- Do I look like I need protection?
- If you don't want it...
No, no.
It's very cool. Thank you.
You're very welcome.
So guess I'm gonna try
to make it to English.
What about you?
Maybe not today.
Can I call you sometime?
This is gonna sound really weird,
but whenever you call me...
...the first words out of your mouth
need to be the date.
Day first, then the month, okay?
And I'm doing this because...?
Because you wanna call me,
and that's just the way it is.
See you later, then.
These are my same clothes.
Aren't they crapped up?
It turns out they're not.
Positive radium must have been
a hiccup.
- A hiccup?
- Yeah.
Sometimes these scanners
have a mind of their own.
Agent Ellison.
Wanted to make sure
you got off all right.
All right's pretty relative, isn't it?
How's she doing?
Well, you know, we always thought
we'd raise kids in this house...
...but you just can't plan
for anything now, can you?
For the road.
So, what about you?
Are you gonna leave?
Or does God have a plan for you?
We'll see.
Yeah, we'll see.
Thank you.
Good luck.
T-minus-2 minutes.
Coolant-system numbers
are within tolerances.
Of course they are. Everything is fine.
- But yesterday you said...
- Everything is fine.
Sixteen November.
DEREK: Twenty-0-7.
Something's wrong with Greenway.
Are you at his house?
I'm searching now.
Sarah, is Greenway there?
Are you telling me that he's there?
He's here.
Four, three, two, one.
[BEEP]
And we're online.
Greenway. He's been replaced
by a machine.
Did you hear me? Greenway has control
of the plant, and he's a machine.
Hey.
You alive in there?
I'm thinking about what to do.
Since when do you do that?
[ALARM SOUNDS]
What's going on?
MAN: Turbine building.
One valve sprung a leak.
Go fix it.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
Where did you go?
Something's wrong.
We need to turn on the water pumps.
Cool it down.
Everything is fine.
Carl, the reactor is overheating.
It's going to melt down.
Please remain calm.
You need to talk to Greenway.
He's lost his mind.
NELSON:
What the...?
WOMAN:
Clear this side. Clear out.
MAN 1 [ ON PA]: Code red. All employees
must evacuate immediately.
- Code red.
- He's unconscious.
The reactor's overheating.
Emergency manual.
- There's no way.
- Code Red.
SARAH:
Water-tank leak.
- There's no time. We gotta go.
- Found it. Instructions.
- Sarah, come on. Now.
- No.
There's some kind of schematic.
MAN 2 [ON PHONE]: NRC Emergency.
Security code, please.
I'm in the control room. We need help.
MAN 2:
Sir, I need a security code.
This is an emergency.
We don't know what we're doing.
- Sir, I'm sorry. I understand.
- Sarah!
But I need a code to help you.
Sir, hello?
SECURITY:
Hold it. Stop right there.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You're clean.
When we jumped through time,
you said I died of cancer.
Yes, 2005.
Am I still gonna get sick?
I don't know.
Is today how it happens?
What am I supposed to do, just wait?
Like a time bomb,
am I just gonna go off someday?
I don't know.
Am I?
You have a new friend.
Her name is Riley.
And you probably creeped her out.
When you talk, don't stand so close.
I was assessing her threat level.
Well?
Am I safe?
I don't know. Girls are complicated.
About what you said before...
...about not being able to trust me.
Yes?
I don't have to prove
anything to anyone.
Anyone.
Including you.
[PHONE RINGING]
RILEY:
Sixteen November.
Hey, you got it right. What's up?
Just practicing.
[PHONE HANGS UP]
Because of this tragic incident,
the owners of Serrano Point...
...and six other power plants
across the nation...
...are entering into a partnership
with my corporation, Automite Systems.
New automated technology
we have developed...
...will be implemented
in all control rooms.
These sophisticated machines will
eliminate the possibility of human error...
...and prevent a major disaster.