NARRATOR: Previously on Terminator:
The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
You like me? The loner weirdo?
That's why I came up to you that day.
I thought, since you're a weirdo...
- ...you'd get me.
- She's a security risk.
You understand
I'm gonna keep seeing Riley...
- ...even if it's a bad idea?
- You're all crazy.
It's all gonna burn and you're gonna
be nothing but bleached skulls.
[SCREAMS]
You wanted to talk?
RILEY: I don't think I can do this anymore.
- What if I want out?
- There is no out.
WEAVER: We're developing
a human-interactive AI.
Hello, Mr. Ellison.
My name's John Henry.
WEAVER:
The AI needs to be trained.
You taught it rules,
but it's got no ethics.
I keep seeing it in my dreams, John.
It means something.
It was written in blood on my wall.
JOHN: Mom, you're tired. You've been sick.
Chasing killer robots
will do that to you.
SARAH:
Tell me about the three dots.
SARAH: In 1490
the Spanish explorer Cabeza de Vaca...
...landed on shores of the New World...
...seeking power and fortune.
He was immediately attacked
and captured...
...almost all of his
traveling companions murdeted.
Enslaved, de Vaca chose to embrace his
captor's beliefs and learned their ways.
He became a healer.
Over time, he was freed...
...and de Vaca attracted
his own following...
...who believed he had the power
over life and death.
The desert had transformed him.
He was not the first,
and he would not be the last.
EILEEN: It's like the world's been
pulled out from under my feet.
I don't know what's real
and what's not.
Eileen, what you're describing...
...is common among experiencers
such as yourself.
When a person lives through something
beyond human understanding...
...we experience fear, a loss of control,
a sense of isolation...
...and a deep, almost existential,
loneliness.
And you, Ms. Fly-on-the-Wall?
What brings you here today?
I'm Sarah.
Hello, Sarah. Welcome.
I came here today because
there have been reports...
...of people seeing UFOs
with this mark.
I need to find out what it means.
It's important to you.
I've been dreaming about it.
I'm having nightmares.
Are they nightmares
or are they memories?
My son thinks I'm crazy.
Maybe not crazy.
Maybe that's the wrong word.
But he doubts me.
- He's never doubted me before.
- Oh.
If there's one thing
we understand here...
...it's doubt.
I have additional photos on my website.
Here's my card.
And these are actual photos
of the California drones.
These alien spacecraft have been spotted
in various locations around the state.
Alien. Not military?
Oh, definitely not military.
The drones' loitering capability is beyond
anything our military has in its fleet.
No, the Predator, Reaper,
none of them...
...has anywhere near
the presence the drones do.
And the symbol...?
Now, some witnesses have reported
seeing the three dots...
...on the hull of the spacecraft.
The mark is also referred to
in the Abraham blogs.
Abraham claims to be a scientist...
...working on a top-secret
alien-centric project...
...being covered up by the authorities.
The metal hyper-alloy
that he was working with...
...exhibited a tensile strength
far beyond our existing technology.
Fire, explosions, extreme pressure,
this metal could survive it all.
It was basically indestructible.
Abraham. Where do I find him?
That's the million-dollar question.
I don't know. No one knows.
Abraham blogged a few times,
then he disappeared six months ago.
You think someone killed him?
I know your type.
Come out, watch the kooks,
have a good laugh at our expense.
- I'm not laughing at anyone.
- Enjoy the rest of the freak show.
EILEEN:
You're interested in Abraham?
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
JOHN: Hello?
SARAH: Hey, John.
Hey. You coming home?
No, I've got a lead. I'll be home late.
From the flying-saucer convention.
The UFO experiencers, yes.
There's a blogger named Abraham.
He may have worked with
endoskeleton metal.
Oh, well, we all know how reliable
bloggers are.
- Why do you have to be so sarcastic?
- Mom...
...just be careful out there, okay?
Wow.
- And I thought my room was a disaster.
- Your room is a disaster.
Berry Bonanza or Peachy Keen?
- This is a work in progress, all right?
- It sure is something.
You okay?
I'm peachy keen.
Why? Do I not look peachy keen?
You're smiling with your mouth
but not your eyes.
See? You're doing it right now.
I flipped out at my foster mom.
What do you mean "flipped out"?
Two of the kids were fighting
and it kind of got to me.
So I went on this little rant.
About what?
They're just so naive, you know?
They have no idea
how good they have it.
All they do is complain
about every little thing...
...and everyone at school's
the exact same way.
It's like one big whine-a-thon.
You're so lucky
your mom's homeschooling you.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, it's been awesome.
- You didn't buy me a smoothie.
- I'm sorry, I didn't know you were here.
I'm always here.
Cameron, I'm not sure
we're gonna have enough paint.
Would you do me a favor
and go out and get some?
You have 420 square feet to paint.
- What you have should be sufficient.
- Two coats.
It's a bigger job than it looks.
I have a job too.
Well, could you do it
in the other room? Please?
Peachy Keen is my favorite.
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIOS]
[CHATTERING]
Come here.
You're a pretty girl.
What's your name?
Does Abraham know we're coming?
EILEEN:
Abraham doesn't live here, I do.
- You said...
- Interested in Abraham?
You'll want to see this.
[KETTLE WHISTLING]
Abraham is a pseudonym?
Alan Park is his real name.
Has a master's from MIT,
specialized in something called "lidar."
- Light detection and ranging.
- You know what it stands for...
...then you know lidar
is an optical remote-sensing technology.
Like radar, except with light.
- Its main application is...
- Robots.
You say that like it's a bad thing.
All I can offer you is tea.
You seem more like a coffee type.
So I've been told.
Type A.
Focused. Goal-orientated.
And yet here I stand
with a cup of chamomile tea.
- Can I ask you a personal question?
- Could I stop you?
What are you doing out here...
...in the desert?
- Looking for answers.
- About Abraham?
Abraham. Life.
Whether the government is hiding
little green men in fallout shelters.
How to make the perfect cup of tea.
You?
I haven't figured out
all my questions yet.
A doubting Thomas
in the house can't help.
How about you? You got family?
Or is this a one-gal operation?
Just me, myself and the coyotes.
Solitude. I remember it fondly.
Most of the time, I love it.
Most of the time.
These are drone sightings.
And these are sightings of Abraham.
This one's the most recent.
Then that's where we'll start.
This room is so adorable.
How could you not like it?
Because I'm not 8.
It's my mom's subconscious way...
...of trying to keep me a kid.
The minute she took off,
out came the paintbrush.
Where'd she go?
- You don't wanna know.
- Yeah, I do actually.
- Why?
- Because she's your mom...
...and I care about you.
Hey, you got something.
- What happened to you?
- Nothing.
- It's a bruise.
- John, it's nothing.
Who did that to you?
- John, please.
- Was it your foster dad?
- No. It was no one, okay?
- I swear I'll kick his ass.
John. It wasn't him, okay?
I swear. Just drop it, please.
The answer's still no.
- I can't do what you're asking.
- Shame.
I thought a night's sleep
would change your mind.
I didn't sleep.
John Henry needs someone to talk to
now that Dr. Sherman is gone.
Dr. Sherman is gone because he...
It killed him.
It wasn't murder, Mr. Ellison.
You said so yourself.
You said I was remiss
in creating John Henry...
...without teaching him
right from wrong.
This is our opportunity
to correct that oversight.
Our opportunity?
Your religious faith and paternal instinct
make you the ideal candidate...
...to foster his moral development.
ELLISON:
That thing killed 20 FBI agents.
It needs a whole lot more
than just a talking to.
The program responsible
for those murders is gone.
The John Henry program
is no more responsible...
...for the deaths of those FBI agents
than you or I.
Many believe tactile experience...
...is integral to AI development.
This body is merely a puppet.
An interface.
We control him.
You control him.
And when John Henry
completes his development?
When he realizes what
his puppet is capable of...
...do you know how powerful he'll be?
Cows are more powerful than man,
Mr. Ellison.
But I'd still rather be
the farmer with the rifle.
Talk to John Henry.
Teach him right from wrong.
You know, Abraham was spotted here
a week ago.
- By who?
- I don't know.
It was an anonymous posting
in a UFO chat room.
- Do you belong to many newsgroups?
- I'm not much for computers.
Usually they go hand in hand.
Computers, technology, visitations.
Not for me.
I'm only interested in the drones...
...and the markings,
the ones that Abraham saw.
- Everything comes back to Abraham.
- I guess so.
What are we doing here?
Well...
...right now, I'm gonna go pee.
Abraham.
Where is he? If you know, tell me now.
I am Abraham.
I'm the one you're looking for.
My real name is Alan Park.
What else is real?
- All of it.
The research, the blogs. It's all true.
Except the woman part.
- My life was in danger. I needed to hide.
- From who?
- I don't know.
- Not good enough.
A few years after MIT,
I went to work for an aerospace firm.
It was there that I was approached
by a company...
...that needed my expertise with lidar.
The money was good.
More than good, it was incredible.
They gave us cars, company housing.
What was the project?
That's the thing. I never knew.
No one knew.
We all signed NDAs.
Everybody worked in isolation.
But we had access to technology
and materials I'd never seen.
Was it military?
I started blogging...
...asking if anyone recognized
what I was working with.
Strange things started to happen.
My apartment was broken into.
And then one day
I was driving home from work...
...and my brakes went out.
Next morning, I went to the bank...
...and withdrew all my savings,
went into hiding.
Some disguise.
I couldn't take any risks.
You took a risk with me.
You know something about all of this
that I don't. I can tell.
You have proof?
Can you prove anything
you just told me?
I have a piece.
The metal I worked with.
I stole a piece before I left.
- Where is it?
- In a storage facility.
I rented it the day I disappeared.
I'll drive.
It's not safe.
It never is.
JESSE:
You all right?
It's okay if you're not.
I want you to tell me if you're not.
I'm all right.
Maybe this color red is too bright.
Maybe the brown was better.
The red's perfect.
You're just not used to it.
The lady in the store
said I was an autumn.
I've never even seen autumn.
[DOG BARKING]
Why did you pick me?
I've always wanted to ask.
But you never have.
I thought you'd tell me
when the time was right.
I think the time is right.
No, sweetie.
The time's past.
What happened to your face?
Nothing.
How did you get hurt?
It was nothing.
Smacked into a door.
- What part?
- What?
Of the door.
I don't know. Just the door.
I like your star.
- Excuse me?
- Your tattoo. It's tight.
Thank you.
I'm thinking of getting one.
Can I look at yours?
- Did it hurt?
- Not too much.
They stuck needles into your skin.
Needles can be painful.
Hey. What's going on?
I'm looking at her star.
She's thinking about getting one.
A tattoo. Of what?
A tiger or a wolf.
I haven't decided yet.
We need to talk.
I'm cool. Really.
Talk.
We missed you at choir practice.
Don't think my wife doesn't notice...
...when our best baritone is gone.
- I'm sorry. Things have been crazy.
- You've been through a difficult time.
We need to see more of you not less.
Do you remember I come
from a big family?
Seven kids?
Before Lila and I got married,
we used to talk into the night...
- ...about how many kids we'd have.
- Family is a blessing.
Yeah, she wanted three, maybe four.
I was more in the four to five range.
Sounds like there was room
for compromise.
She wanted to wait until she
made it through Quantico. I agreed.
She graduated September 1st, 2001.
We started trying in earnest
that very night.
- Ten days later...
- September 11th.
She decided she didn't want
to get pregnant anymore.
Understandable reaction.
But she already was.
I didn't find out
until after she had terminated it.
I always wondered what happened
between you two.
Yeah, that's what happened.
When you called today
you said you wanted guidance.
Yeah, that's true.
Does this have to do with Lila?
No.
Does it have something to do
with the child?
- The child?
- Yes.
Does this have something to do
with the child?
I don't know.
[GATE OPENS]
It's gone.
I swear it was here.
Sarah, they must've broken in.
[ENGINE REWING]
[AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE]
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
- The truth.
- I told you I don't know.
The name led to a shell corporation.
It's all a dead end.
- You're lying.
- No.
- You're a liar and a fake.
- You're the fake.
You're a mother. You're a seeker.
You're a soldier.
You're everything but you're nothing.
You don't know anything about me.
Oh, really?
I'm a man who lives as a woman,
and you're a woman who lives as...
Stop.
- What made you so hard?
- Who were you working for?
- You almost got me killed.
- Tell me.
Tell me about the metal,
about the symbols.
The bullets, I could feel them.
They were close.
So close.
We nearly died.
You don't feel it.
Why don't you feel it?
I don't hate them, you know?
- They tried to kill you. Twice.
- They did kill me.
They killed Alan Park.
And I thank them for it.
They gave me a gift.
The life I was scared to lead.
Before this happened, I was a cog
in the machine. Ordinary, repressed.
How many people dare
to live the life they dream of?
Face their real fears
about who they really are...
...not their houses, or their jobs,
or their habits...
...but their deepest, truest selves?
Do you have any idea
what I'm talking about?
I used to be a waitress.
They killed her too.
Tell me about your lab. Where is it?
They made sure we never knew.
The company came,
picked us up every morning.
Drove us in a van
with blacked-out windows to the facility.
What is it?
There may be a way
to help you remember.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, Jesse.
No one's following me.
I double backed like you taught me.
Jesse, I'm really sorry.
- Don't get mad at me, please.
- Phones.
- That's why we have phones.
- I just didn't know where else to go.
Yeah, well...
...not here, sweetie.
Any place but here.
I got kicked out of my foster home.
- You did what?
- I got kicked out.
They threw me out because I hit Kay,
my foster mom.
I was just freaking out.
You know, I started thinking
about everything.
What's coming for all of us. For them.
I just... I needed someone to talk to.
I need you.
I was thinking that instead
of just getting another foster home...
...that maybe we could find
someplace close together.
Like an apartment or something.
I'll just tell John that I quit school...
...and we can be together.
I'm not here to babysit.
And you're not here
to feel sorry for yourself.
I'm not your friend.
I am not your mother.
And you are here to keep John Connor
away from her.
Go finish your job.
Go.
She's lying.
About what?
I don't know, but her pulse was
elevated, and her hand was perspiring.
She's lying.
Yeah, her pulse was elevated
because you were freaking her out.
As usual.
- What happened to her face?
- I don't know.
She didn't say.
I can get her to tell me the truth.
Stay away from her.
Riley.
Riley, answer me.
Open it.
Now.
MORRIS:
New memories can be confusing.
The question Sally poses
is very important.
How soon do we tell a new person in our
lives we've experienced an abduction?
[DOOR OPENS]
Dr. Morris? Sarah.
We met at the UFO convention.
I'm busy at the moment, but if you'd like
to make an appointment...
No appointment. It's an emergency.
No matter what happens,
I'm never going back to what I was.
Good luck.
Have a seat, please.
Who taught you how to play chess?
I did.
ELLISON:
Did you play with Dr. Sherman?
No. We played other games.
Talking games.
Do you miss Dr. Sherman?
I'm designed to learn.
He helped me learn.
His absence slows my growth.
His absence is more important
than that.
His value was more
than just his function for you.
Human beings aren't like chess pieces.
It matters if we live or die.
Why does it matter?
All humans die eventually.
ELLISON:
Yes. That's true.
But their lives are sacred.
Do you know what sacred means?
Holy. Worthy of respect. Venerable.
Do you know why human life
is sacred?
Because so few humans are alive
compared to the number that are dead?
No.
Because we're God's creation.
God made everything.
The stars, the Earth,
everything on this planet.
We are all God's children.
Am I God's child?
That's one of the things we're here
to talk about.
Checkmate. I win.
Would you like to play again?
Your body is completely relaxed.
Your mind is clear and open.
I'm gonna count down from five.
When I reach one,
you'll be in the park...
...waiting for your ride to work.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Where are you? What do you see?
I'm waiting at the bench.
There are five other people.
We all live in town.
[OVER DEVICE]
We all climb inside the van.
After a few miles, we come to a stop.
There's a sound.
At the end of the dirt road
is a warehouse.
There's an office in front. No windows.
No way to see in or out.
MORRIS:
Does that bother you?
EILEEN:
No. I like not being seen.
The van parks outside.
The driver unlocks the door.
We head inside.
[DOOR OPENS]
Can I help you?
I said, can I help you?
[GUNSHOTS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
MORRIS:
Your body is completely relaxed.
Your mind clear and open.
I'm gonna count down from five.
When I reach one,
you'll be in the park...
...waiting for your ride to work.
Are you ready?
EILEEN:
I'm ready.
MORRIS:
Five, four, three...
...two, one.
Where are you? What do you see?
EILEEN:
I'm waiting at the bench.
There are five other people.
We all live in town.
Here it comes now.
MORRIS: The van?
EILEEN:
It approaches from the left.
We climb inside the van.
It heads north out of town.
It's dim inside. I can barely see.
MORRIS:
Does the darkness disturb you?
EILEEN:
No. Secrecy doesn't bother me.
Because I have a secret too.
MORRIS:
And what's your secret?
EILEEN:
I'm not who they think I am.
After a few miles, we come to a stop.
There's a sound.
MORRIS:
What is it?
Eileen?
EILEEN:
I don't know. The sound. It doesn't...
MORRIS:
Trust yourself.
The truth is inside you.
What do you hear?
EILEEN: It's rain.
Every day.
But the heat. We're in the desert.
It doesn't make sense.
Nothing makes sense.
We're on a dirt road.
Now a bump.
A clacking under the tires.
[BOARDS CLACKING]
At the end of the dirt road
is a warehouse.
There's an office in front.
No windows. No way to see in or out.
MORRIS:
Does that bother you?
EILEEN:
No. I like not being seen.
I don't know who they are,
but that's okay...
...because they don't know
who I really am either.
MORRIS:
And who are you?
[EILEEN CHUCKLES]
EILEEN:
I'm a waitress.
Will do. First thing in the morning.
- I'm sorry, ma'am. We're closed.
- Where's the metal?
Please. Don't shoot.
Please don't shoot me.
- The metal. Where is it?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Who are you?
- My name's Winston.
I install air conditioning, all right?
Please don't hurt me.
I have a wife. I have a son.
I'm his coach.
I'm his Little League coach.
Put your hands on your head.
- What's in the warehouse?
- I don't know.
My boss rents it out to another
company. Look, I'm just an installer.
I know where you live.
Don't call the police.
[GUNSHOT]