NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
- Get to the safe house before night.
- The safe house in the desert?
Hey, desert's that way.
SARAH: Taking a detour.
Who lives here? Charlie?
WEAVER: John Henry was infiltrated.
MURCH: Someone out there wants to kill him.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[TASER CLICKING]
[GRUNTING]
I don't know which one is his.
DEREK:
Doesn't matter.
Grass, trees. Could do worse.
Could.
It's been 25 years.
DEREK:
Desert.
You said meet us in the desert.
- I did.
- Funny thing about the desert...
...you don't find many lighthouses there.
We stopped to see Charlie.
So you did.
- Charlie's dead.
- So I heard.
- From who?
- John.
- He called you too?
- Good thing.
Might not have found you.
My brother buried out there, I thought...
...that counted for something
between us.
Well, John counts for more.
And you keep too many secrets
for my tastes.
I'm sorry about Charlie.
- Well, everybody dies for me, right?
- John.
I found this on the body
at the lighthouse.
Who is it?
I don't know, but I've seen her.
- Where?
- Dr. Sherman's office.
The shrink from the list?
I think she was a patient there.
Probably the one we were looking for.
They tried to kill us. They have a picture
of this girl. It means something.
We all know we're going, so let's just go.
All right, everyone,
go to your Learn-a-Word program.
I'm gonna give you 10 new words.
You'll put them in the search box,
and then...
[GIGGLES]
Savannah?
Maybe you'd like to tell the class
what's so funny?
Um...
Nothing.
- That doesn't look like Learn-a-Word.
- I'm just chatting.
- With whom?
- My friend.
Who's your friend?
TEACHER:
She said his name was John Henry.
John Henry?
I'm sure it's made up.
These types of predators
often use pseudonyms.
I see.
A grown man
contacting a girl this age...
I don't have to tell you, Ms. Weaver...
...there are some troubled people
out there.
- Yes, there are.
- Some of them look perfectly normal.
Yes, they do.
Well, I hate to think what can happen
if he finds out where she lives.
I appreciate you bringing this
to my attention.
I'll talk to her.
WEAVER: Why were you talking
to John Henry during class?
I was teaching him the words to a song.
- What song?
- The one Daddy used to sing.
I want John Henry to sing it with me.
- Maybe I could sing it with you.
- You're not a boy, and you can't sing.
Fine. We won't sing.
But what you do have to do,
is pay attention to the teacher.
She said bad things about John Henry.
What did she say?
She said if you talk to somebody
on the computer...
...they could come to your house
and hurt you.
John Henry would never hurt you...
...but there are people
who wouldn't understand him.
People are afraid of things
they don't understand.
If they knew him, they'd like him.
That may be. For now, I don't want you
to talk to anyone about him.
- Is that clear?
- Okay, I won't.
I'll see you tonight.
What are you looking at?
- Myself.
- Why?
Do you have a brother, Mr. Ellison?
- Yes. In Atlanta.
- Does he look like you?
People seem to think so.
Do you think my brother looks like me?
John Henry,
wherever your brother might be...
...he's a computer.
He doesn't look like anyone.
He certainly doesn't have your face.
I know that, Mr. Ellison.
I simply meant, I wonder how similar
his data is to my data.
I wonder if we share the same thoughts.
I have no idea.
But I imagine you're unique.
Yes, I am unique.
We may still reach
many of the same conclusions...
- ...given similar data sets.
- You may think alike.
I'd like to know if we do.
The human brain is an amazing computer.
Its raw clock speed
is 20 billion calculations per second.
Its storage is functionally infinite.
- But it's flawed.
- How's that?
There's nowhere to download it
when you die.
Not exactly, no.
Your Bible solves this problem
by introducing the concept of heaven.
- Yes.
- Billions of souls with no bodies.
Okay.
JOHN HENRY:
Yet all this is required...
...simply to process the unique entity
you call John Henry.
Yes.
It's possible heaven
has a hardware problem.
It's not that simple.
I need to know
what my brother is thinking, Mr. Ellison.
I need to know what he plans to do.
I don't wanna die again.
Do you think you can be a little angel
while I do turbo body crunches?
- I still have math. I'm adding.
- Okay.
[RINGING]
Hello? I can't talk right now.
JOHN HENRY: Why not?
SAVANNAH [OVER SPEAKERS]:
I'm doing my homework. But I have an idea.
You can come over and do math with me.
I have to go. I can't hold the phone
and write my numbers.
JOHN HENRY [OVER PHONE]:
Use the headset.
You can talk and work simultaneously.
Si...
- Simul...
- Simultaneously.
It means, "to occur at the same time."
Coterminous.
Oh.
- John Henry?
- Hello, Savannah.
What does "coterminous" mean?
Hello?
[EQUIPMENT BEEPING]
John Henry?
Hello?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
DEBBIE:
Hi.
JOHN HENRY: Savannah, listen to my voice.
- I'm scared.
Do as I say, and you will not be harmed.
But you'll have to finish
your homework later.
[PHONE RINGS]
[ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS]
MAN [OVER ANSWERING MACHINE]:
Hello, Mrs. Weaver? This is RNE Security.
We detected an unauthorized entrance
at your front gate.
Do you require assistance?
Mrs. Weaver, we're sending a unit
to your home.
Now come out of there.
SAVANNAH: I don't want to.
Don't worry. I can tell you where to go.
Who's that man?
JOHN HENRY [OVER HEADSET]:
The water delivery man.
- Where's Debbie?
- Debbie's in the foyer.
We're not going that way.
Go to the garage.
SAVANNAH:
Where do I go now?
John Henry?
[STATIC HISSING OVER SPEAKERS]
[BEEPING]
John Henry.
[DOOR CLICKS]
JOHN:
Hey. Shh. Shh. Shh.
Shh. Shh. No, no. It's okay. It's okay.
[SAVANNAH SCREAMS]
Come on.
[GLASS CRASHING]
Okay, go, go, go.
[GRUNTING]
JOHN:
Come here, come here.
It's okay.
Come on.
Keep moving.
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Detective Crayton, L.A.P.D.
James Ellison. Head of Security.
CRAYTON: I know who you are, Mr. Ellison.
ELLISON:
What happened?
There was an attack on the residence.
Alarm went off.
Security arrived, found the nanny dead.
There was a pretty ugly firefight.
Four security guards killed,
plus one of the gunmen.
- Daughter missing.
- Any ID on the gunman?
No ID. We're waiting for ballistics,
coroner's report.
Anyone call with demands?
CRAYTON: No.
There's an Amber Alert out.
We've set up a command post
in the lobby.
Officers posted throughout the building.
I'm putting 24-hour protection
on Ms. Weaver.
How are you holding up?
The detective wants to speak
with Savannah's friends.
I made a list. But I'm concerned
I may have left someone off.
If you can think of anyone else
Savannah spends time with.
I'll take a look.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Mr. Ellison.
When I said I knew who you were,
I didn't mean anything bad by that.
ELLISON: You know things are rough when
"I know you" can be taken as an insult.
Anyway, no offense.
None taken.
So how do you like the private sector?
- I get a better car.
- Nice.
Anything you can tell me about Weaver?
Not much to tell.
Husband died a couple years ago.
She didn't talk about that much?
She doesn't talk about much much.
What's her relationship
with her daughter like?
They seem close.
- Have any enemies?
- Not that I know of.
I hate these cases.
We'll find her.
Why did you stop looking
for Sarah Connor?
- Well, she, um, died eight years ago.
- No, that's not true.
So you accept she's alive?
- Sarah Connor was at the house?
- Alive.
Obviously, yes. Did she take Savannah?
So it doesn't surprise you she's alive.
No, it doesn't surprise me.
You lied about what you know.
Did she take Savannah?
- I tried to help but could not.
- Did Sarah Connor kill those guards?
- No.
- Then who was she shooting at?
Him.
We should tell Ms. Weaver.
No. I don't think we should tell anyone.
Mr. Ellison...
...you're asking me...
...to keep a secret.
You tell me it's wrong to lie,
yet you keep doing it.
I know what I said, John Henry.
But in this case,
a lie might save someone.
How?
Our best chance to get Savannah back
is for me to handle this.
Quietly.
You understand?
Is Sarah Connor going to hurt Savannah?
No.
Would she harm me?
- Why do you ask that?
- She blew up Cyberdyne.
She killed Miles Dyson.
His work is in my code.
Right now, the most important thing
is to find Savannah.
Who is she?
She's like me, isn't she?
Yes.
If I keep your secret,
will you bring Savannah back?
- I'll do everything in my power.
- So will I.
[GUN CLICKS]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
ELLISON:
Sarah Connor? This is James Ellison.
How'd you get this number?
A friend found it for me.
Do you have her?
Just tell me if she's safe.
I need her back.
Weaver's house is wired.
I've seen the surveillance tapes.
Right now, I'm the only one that has.
Let's keep it that way.
I can't, not yet. It's a long story.
Tell it to me.
Downtown, 3rd Street tunnel, one hour.
- What are you doing?
- Taking you to Sarah Connor.
The plan was to meet at the tunnel.
The plan changed. We'll take a left.
- I'm going to need your gun.
- I don't carry one anymore.
You lied to me once before.
I should have killed you then.
Drive.
[CAR DOORS SLAM]
ELLISON:
Where's Savannah?
- What's your deal with Zeira Corp?
- I work there.
- Why'd you take the girl?
- To protect her.
- From who?
- One of them.
A machine was there at the house.
ELLISON: What would they want...
- ...with a 6-year-old girl?
- Who knows with these things.
- They may want her mother.
- Why?
The girl was seeing Dr. Boyd Sherman.
He worked at Zeira Corp,
died at Zeira Corp.
- That was an accident.
- The girl's in danger.
Her mother's in danger. You're in danger.
Give me the girl back. I'll handle it.
Listen to me. Derek's dead.
Charlie's dead.
Charlie?
Eight years ago,
you would have thought I was crazy.
You'd have thrown me back in Pescadero.
But you've seen them.
You know it's true.
They're very good at what they do,
and they're not going to stop.
Let me talk to Weaver.
- Let me have Savannah.
- She's not safe with you.
I'm gonna have a hard time
explaining that.
Then let me explain it. To her.
- I told you to stay out of this.
- I tried.
Everywhere I turn, there you are.
The security footage from the house.
I need to see it.
I can't access it right now.
- Why not?
- The files were corrupted.
A faulty sector on one of the drives.
I'm working to repair it.
[DOOR OPENS]
Savannah's safe.
- You didn't bring her back.
- Not yet. I'm working on it.
We need to talk.
JOHN:
Hey, you remember me, right?
Squirrel runs around the tree?
Dives in the hole,
scurries out the other side.
That's right.
- You taught me how to tie my shoe.
- I did.
At Dr. Sherman's.
He died.
I know.
I liked him.
Me too.
He was my friend.
The man that got hurt at my house.
Was he your friend?
Yeah, he was.
I'm sorry.
Me too.
It's all my fault.
That is not true.
The teacher told me.
Mommy told me too.
Not to talk to John Henry.
That if I did, bad people would come
to our house and hurt us.
Who's John Henry?
He's my friend. At my mommy's work.
What does he do there?
He lives in the basement.
He lives there?
My mommy
says people won't understand.
Oh.
Well, I understand.
I had an imaginary friend too
when I was your age.
He's real. He talks.
I'm teaching him how to sing.
Well, why does he live
in the basement, then?
He can't leave.
There's a cord in the back of his head.
- A cord?
- In the back of his head.
Do other people talk to John Henry?
Mr. Ellison.
- Mr. Ellison?
- He works for my mommy.
He teaches John Henry stuff.
What kind of stuff?
Sarah Connor's alive?
- Yeah, she wants to meet you.
- She took my daughter.
To protect her. From a machine.
It might be after you.
- How do you know?
- I saw the security tapes.
You did?
- John Henry, I suppose.
- I asked John Henry to hide them.
- From me.
- From everyone.
Including you.
I can't say that pleases me.
I think you should do what she asks.
You should go meet her.
- I'm staying here.
- Why?
- Someone needs to protect John Henry.
- John Henry? This is your daughter.
There's a machine out there looking
for her. You need to protect her.
- I'm sorry.
- You should be.
What you need to understand,
Mr. Ellison...
...what I believe you're beginning
to understand...
...is when my behavior implies
I value John Henry's survival...
...more than that of my own daughter...
...it is not because I love John Henry
more than Savannah.
It's because I believe
Savannah's survival...
...may someday depend
upon John Henry's survival.
And because I believe that your survival...
...may someday depend
upon John Henry's survival.
I'll meet with Sarah Connor.
Make it happen.
[ELEVATOR OPENS]
[CHATTERING]
CRAYTON:
Ballistics came in on the John Doe.
Funny thing is, the bullet that killed him
didn't come from the security guards.
Strange.
Turns out he's a fugitive. Ex-con.
Escaped custody
on a felony murder charge.
That's the other funny thing.
It was your case.
Andrew Goode murder.
- You interrogated him?
- Yes, I did.
Hours before he escaped?
That's right.
Guilty?
- I never had a chance to prove it.
- Because he escaped?
Only to turn up months later
at the home of your employer.
I know what you think.
I know why you're thinking it.
I would think the same thing
if I were in your shoes.
I'm not thinking anything yet, Mr. Ellison.
I'm just collecting information.
[CHATTERING]
SARAH:
How's the girl?
She's fine. She was, uh, just telling me
about her friend John Henry.
The man with the cord in his head
in the basement of her mother's work.
Plugged into a big computer.
And this is him.
Oh, it gets better.
She says that Mr. Ellison
has been teaching it things.
I destroyed that chip.
You destroyed a chip.
I don't think it's Cromartie.
I think it's something else.
Something bigger. Something worse.
It's Cyberdyne all over again.
Why do they need the body?
The technology can be reverse
engineered and used as a platform.
Yeah, I know all that,
but they're not using it for the parts.
They're playing with it.
I should've killed him.
- I'm going to kill him.
- You're not going to kill him.
- He can't be trusted.
- No one can be trusted.
- But I only want to kill him.
- No one's going to be killed.
No one's going to be killed.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Yes?
ELLISON: Catherine Weaver's agreed to meet.
Great. When? Where?
You give me the girl.
The police go home.
When it's clear, I'll bring you in.
- The girl can't stay there. It's not safe.
- That's for her mother to decide.
Done.
We don't kill just to kill.
I never have.
Looks vicious.
They stay in hiding mostly.
And only attack when provoked.
What does it eat?
Cuttlefish, crustaceans, other eels.
Please don't tap the glass.
How long has Mr. Ellison worked for you?
A few months.
Do you ever ask yourself
why he didn't stay with the FBI?
No, I don't.
Are you aware he was arrested?
- Murder.
- He was cleared of those charges.
Did the two of you argue lately?
Have any tension?
Any reason he might wanna harm
you and your family?
Detective, are you suggesting
Mr. Ellison...
...may be complicit
in the disappearance of my daughter?
Well, it wouldn't be the first time
we've seen an employee...
...try to blackmail their boss.
Well, it would be the first time I had.
This thing, it eats other eels, huh?
It's interesting.
When you told me the security tapes
were corrupted...
...you were lying to me for Mr. Ellison.
And I'm lying to him for you.
What would happen if he knew?
Knew what?
That you aren't Savannah's mother.
That you aren't anyone's mother.
Are you threatening me, John Henry?
I could tell Mr. Ellison.
You could,
but that would be unfortunate.
Mostly for Mr. Ellison.
I find him useful but not efficient.
What if he fails?
Then we won't see Savannah again.
Mr. Ellison taught me
that human life is sacred.
"Sacred."
That's an interesting word.
It comes from the Latin, sacrum.
Much like another word, "sacrifice."
Sacrifice.
Perhaps it's necessary to sacrifice
Savannah for the greater good.
The greater good is keeping you safe.
In the elevator, you told Mr. Ellison...
...that Savannah's survival
depended upon my survival.
Yes, I did.
But you didn't say that my survival
depended upon hers.
It doesn't.
Ms. Weaver?
Yes?
There is a Bible story of two brothers,
Cain and Abel.
God favored Abel. Cain killed him.
God cursed Cain and ordered him
to wander the world alone.
I'm familiar with the story.
Which brother am I?
I don't know, John Henry.
Perhaps you are neither.
Perhaps in this story you are God.
I wanna tell you something.
Yes?
It was not my idea
to ditch you and Derek.
I thought we were gonna meet you...
...and then my mom took
this detour off to Charlie's.
I thought you knew.
She had her reasons.
Yeah, she was pretty damn pissed
at Derek about the whole Jesse thing.
Who wasn't?
I guess none of that matters now.
You'll miss him.
Well...
...there's no use crying about it, is there?
I'm sure future-me would beat my ass
if I did.
Future-you knows what it means
to lose people you love.
It happens to him too.
Your mother ditched us
because she was going to ditch you.
She was going to leave you with Charlie.
No.
No, that's insane.
She found a lump in her breast.
- Yeah, the transmitter. I know.
- She thought it was cancer.
- Well, she had a lump. It makes sense.
- She's lost weight.
What?
[FOOTSTEPS]
SARAH:
Get her up.
We gotta go.
MAN [ON SCREEN]:
I can't shoot a lady.
Give me the gun. Give me that gun.
[WOMAN SCREAMING ON SCREEN]
CAMERON:
Think he'll come?
He'll come.
He could be deceiving us.
He's done it before.
He wants the girl. He'll be here.
And what if he doesn't come through?
With the meeting with Weaver?
We're going into Zeira Corp.
with or without him.
And when we're done, it'll be ashes.
MAN 1 [ON SCREEN]:
She's wrecking the town looking for you.
Come on, I gotta get you out of here.
MAN 2: if she sees me out there,
she'll kill me! She's crazy.
MAN 1: Come on, Mr. Archer, we gotta
get out of here!
- You alone?
- Yes. Where's Savannah?
Row J.
I'll be in touch about the meeting.
CRAYTON: Put your hands behind your head.
Kneel on the ground.
[GRUNTING]
ELLISON:
John, I swear I didn't know.
JOHN:
I'll kill you. Let go of me. I'll kill you.
I'll kill you.
[SINGING
"DONALD, WHERE'S YOUR TROUSERS"]
[BOTH SINGING]