NARRATOR: Previously on
Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles:
Well, when is the time
for me to live my life?
WEAVER: You know what's rare
in the world of computers?
Finding one that'll cross
against the light.
I'd like to talk to you
about an opportunity.
I'd like my company to lead the world
into the next century.
And I'm fairly sure
you're an avenging angel.
SARAH: My father slept with a gun
under his pillow.
There was no pill for his sickness.
No medicine to ease his mind.
He left blood and sweat
and part of his soul in a foreign land.
My father never talked to me
about the war he fought.
He never talked to anyone.
Ever vigilant. Ever silent.
Anyone here?
I never thought I'd follow
in his footsteps.
SARAH: Dr. Boyd Sherman.
Child psychologist. Family therapist.
What's his link to Skynet?
Friend or foe?
- Don't know.
- Skynet doesn't have friends.
Well, it's got foes. And whatever
the opposite of foes are, okay?
- Friends.
- We don't know anything here.
All we know is his name's on the list.
Everyone we found on the list was
a Skynet target and needed protecting.
Not everyone needs protecting.
Some need...
We don't know anything yet.
[CAMERA CLICKING]
PHOTOGRAPHER:
Turn your head a quarter inch.
Perfect.
Another half inch.
And a smile now.
Warmer, if you can.
Warmer. Warmer.
Never mind.
Quarter inch to the left.
Perfect.
Can we get the child in for a few?
Very good.
You want to be in the pictures
with mommy?
PHOTOGRAPHER:
How we doing on time?
No.
- Looks like fun.
- No, it doesn't.
MAN: Whatever. Keep me updated.
- Savannah. Sit here with me.
Savannah.
Sit here with me.
No.
- Savannah.
- Ma'am?
Sit here with me.
Ma'am, maybe we shouldn't force it.
- Thank you.
You have a child.
Yes.
What do you do with it?
It?
He. Leo.
He had some issues
during my divorce.
Some days I wanted to kill him.
But we went to someone.
A real miracle worker.
I can get you the number.
BOYD:
Who wants to start?
I'm not sure therapy is for us.
No offense.
None taken.
Maybe if you tell us
a little about yourself.
Well, I've been a family counselor
for 20 years.
I started my work
up in northern California.
Up north? Silicon Valley?
BOYD:
Livermore VA Med Center.
Military?
Since I've moved down here
I've treated civilians almost exclusively.
Iraq's changing that, however.
Do you have family in the military?
Your dad?
He passed away.
BOYD:
I'm sorry.
Is that something you'd all
like to discuss?
It was a long time ago.
We've been on our own for some time.
That must be difficult.
SARAH:
You can get used to it.
- Do you?
- I'm used to it.
It's fine.
Is there anything else I should know?
Anything else we should know?
If we choose to go forward...
...I'd like to meet
with each of you individually.
Is that something you'd be open to?
I could do tomorrow,
if you're up for it.
Tomorrow's good.
[DOOR BUZZES]
Can you hold that, please?
Sir, you're gonna have to take
another one. That elevator's full.
MAN:
Show me a tree.
Happy.
Funny.
Get the lights, please.
It's an unanticipated response
in the symbolistic software.
The AI keeps giving us random,
unsolicited images.
We don't know what they mean
or why it continues to respond this way.
What we do know is that when we run
performance tests on the Al...
...its computational time is increasing.
The optimality of
its outputs is decreasing.
It's taking more time to do less.
Yeah. I mean, you could say that, yes.
I just did.
Right. Yeah.
A lot of children come to see me.
They all have something
that's bothering them.
Sometimes they know what it is,
sometimes they don't.
It helps if we talk about those things.
Hey.
Your shoes are untied.
You know how to tie them?
Would you like me to show you?
So...
...let's see what we have here, okay?
Have dolls.
Coloring books.
Look, and we have a set of cards
with faces.
Happy.
Sad.
Scared.
Play with anything you want.
I'm gonna talk to your mommy
for a second.
This will take some time.
I can wait outside if it will
make things go faster.
More time than just today.
I'll wait outside.
Where you been?
On a run.
You've been gone six hours.
I guess I'm slow.
I doubled back on Sherman's house.
I got nothing. How was he?
Curious. Smart. Annoying.
- So he was good at his job.
- Better than we were at ours.
We bugged the office.
We still need the patient files.
- You're going back?
- Not my first choice.
[GUNSHOT]
I'm fine, okay? I'm fine.
Just cleaning it,
I thought I'd cleared it.
It's just a burn. Shell casing.
BOYD [ON BUG]: You wanna be the girl?
SAVANNAH: Where's her mommy?
BOYD: I don't know.
Where do you think her mommy is?
SAVANNAH:
She's working.
BOYD:
Okay.
She doesn't like the way
her mommy looks at her.
No? How does she look at her?
She wants to tell you a secret.
Okay.
I want my old mommy back.
Your daughter is beautiful.
Thank you.
She looks just like her mommy.
Yes.
She does.
I just need a minute
with your mom, okay?
Wait here.
What are your strongest memories
from childhood?
My strongest memories?
Yeah. What do you remember most?
What's vivid to you?
Why do you ask?
Well, the death of Savannah's father
is the most vivid memory she has.
Hearing the news, the funeral.
She's so young,
she has no distance from it.
Well, we can't make her grow faster,
can we?
Look, I'm sure you're in a lot of pain.
But you need to reassure Savannah
that she hasn't lost her mother...
...as well as her father.
Hey.
You know the squirrel and the tree?
See...
...you make a loop for the tree.
The squirrel runs around the tree.
And he dives in the hole...
...and scurries out the other side.
WEAVER:
Savannah.
John.
- The usual?
- Yeah. Thanks.
MAN: Hey, baby.
WOMAN 1: Hey.
WOMAN 2:
All right. Run to your sister.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[WINGS FLUTTERING]
- Jesse?
- Hey, baby.
DEREK:
What are you doing here?
Connor sent you back.
What for?
Why'd Connor send you back?
You're here. You must know.
No one told me.
And you left without saying goodbye.
My orders were to set up a safe house
and wait.
For what? I don't know.
I wait.
At the park.
Eating hot dogs.
What about you?
What's Connor got you doing?
Connor didn't send me back, Derek.
He didn't? What do you mean?
That's new.
Not to me.
There's metal everywhere these days.
Looking for us.
Working for us.
Connor's got at least one
in every major base.
A big one flipped on us
and took out half a bunker.
Bird.
Cullie.
That's from the same shrapnel
that killed Cullie.
How'd you get back here?
Cullie's brother. He's a bubble tech.
- He's the same one...
- Who sent you back.
I know.
Are you AWOL?
Jesse, did you run?
From the war?
I need a place to rest.
You're a soldier.
You fight.
Not anymore.
When everything ends...
...I wanna be here with you.
Derek, please.
I don't want everything to end,
Jesse. Not again.
When I showed you in,
you assessed the exits.
You're talking to a VA doc.
Every vet does it. Every day.
Well, I don't know what to tell you,
I'm not a vet.
No. Of course not.
Your dad was, though, right?
Vets are the ones
who come back, right?
My dad never came back, so...
My mistake. I'm sorry.
You didn't have that yesterday.
What happened?
Oh, it's a burn.
Just an accident. I was cooking.
What were you cooking?
What? What does that matter?
Just curious.
I was boiling water for pasta.
Why do you think your mother
brought you here?
I don't know.
She doesn't tell me everything.
Why do you think you're here?
I couldn't tell you.
Do you cook for the family much?
Is that a role you take on?
What?
What is your role in the family?
What do you do?
Do?
I go to school. I hang out. I'm...
I'm a kid.
Are you?
You think I'm lying?
Why don't you check my passport?
I simply meant that...
...some children who have
lost a parent feel pressure...
...to take the place
of the absent parent.
They...
Well, they grow up quickly.
Interesting, you say passport when a lot
of kids would say driver's license.
You ever feel like running? Escaping?
All the time.
Why? Why do you want to escape?
Look, I want you to know,
everything you say is between us.
This is a safe place.
No, it's not.
Nowhere is.
Did you know that 60 percent of all
teen suicides are committed with a gun?
He thought it was clear.
It was an accident.
Some first attempts
may appear to be an accident.
What's taking so long in there?
BOYD:
Can we talk?
I'd like to see John again.
Alone.
John? Why?
Well, actually I'd like
to see all of you again.
I think your daughter has
some sort of social disorder.
It's too early to diagnose, but she does
exhibit possible Asperger's symptoms.
And John?
Yeah, this might sound
strange to you...
...but he reminds me of
veterans I used to treat.
War veterans.
Yeah, Vietnam, especially.
The way he evaluates a room,
his guardedness.
The way he carries himself.
Do you know of any violence
in his past?
He's never been abused,
if that's what you're suggesting.
Oh, no, no.
I'm not suggesting anything like that.
Thank you, doctor.
It may not be me,
but that boy needs to talk.
To somebody.
We talk.
That's not enough.
The strangest thing about her?
Well...
...for one of the best minds in the tech
world, she's practically a Luddite.
[LACHLAN LAUGHS]
REAL WEAVER:
You liar.
Bicycle or car?
- Bicycle.
- Mm-hm. Electric or acoustic?
- He thinks he's so smart.
- No, no, no.
I just know you, that's all.
Tell them how you work at home.
Come on. Come on. Tell them.
My father was a butcher.
One of the oldest shops in Edinburgh.
We didn't have money
for school supplies.
LACHLAN: She writes on butcher's paper.
Like, big rolls of it.
With grease pencils.
I like the way it smells.
WOMAN [ON INTERCOM]:
Ms. Weaver, you're needed down in the lab.
It won't run any tests or diagnostics.
It just keeps playing these twisted
pictures and doing equations.
I don't know.
Maybe we should consider...
...you know, scrapping it
and starting over with a clean platform.
Should I consider scrapping my team,
as well?
Or does that seem equally
as intemperate?
LACHLAN [ON VIDEO]:
Strangest thing about her?
Well, for one of the best minds in the
tech world, she's practically a Luddite.
[LACHLAN LAUGHS]
REAL WEAVER: Liar.
LACHLAN: Bicycle or car?
Daddy keeps touching your tummy.
Does he?
Is he trying to hug me?
LACHLAN:
Come on. Come on. Tell them.
- I don't know.
- I think he's trying to hug me.
LACHLAN: She writes on butcher's paper.
Like, big rolls of it.
With grease pencils.
- When are we going back to Sherman?
- We're not going back. Not now.
Patients list was a bust.
He's got the names encoded for privacy.
Tapes have been useless so far.
- But we'll keep listening.
- Well, I can push him more.
- Get something.
- Like what?
I don't know.
He's on that wall for a reason, though.
He could have
a Triple-8 on his ass.
Or it could be six months from now.
There's no timetable on the list.
So you just wanna give up?
We don't know what Skynet
wants from him. We can't trust him.
Maybe his name's on the list
because he helps John.
Helps John?
What makes you think
John needs help?
What makes you think I don't?
Do you?
Because you can talk to me, John.
You always have.
No. I'm fine.
MAN:
Ugh!
Had this friend once.
We dug tunnels together.
Roughest son of a bitch I ever knew.
One day, he went out to take a leak...
...and when he was out there,
he just decided to blow his head off.
Just like that.
He fought and fought and fought
for his life. Then...
...he just couldn't anymore.
John is not suicidal.
No.
But what is he?
He's not a boy. He's not a man.
He's not a soldier.
He has changed.
He saw his mother kill a man.
[CAR ALARM CHIRPS]
I won't scream.
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
[CRUNCH]
[SCREAMING STOPS]
Getting off?
I'm going down.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to get off on this floor.
Of course.
[BEEPING]
WEAVER: We're developing
a human interactive AI.
It's like a child.
Its neural network needs
to be trained to recognize images.
Well, I guess I'm still a little fuzzy
as to why you called me here.
We were in the process of training the Al
when it stopped running all its tests.
Now...
...all it plays is this.
[LAUGHING]
Is something funny?
It is if you get the joke.
It's asking a question. Look.
A question mark equals "Why."
Equations. That's math.
Books, well, they're books.
And these images here,
they all represent sadness.
If you put it all together,
"Why is a math book so sad?"
It's a riddle. A joke.
A third-grader told it to me.
Around 3 to 4 years old
a child starts asking questions.
But your AI appears
to be even more advanced. It...
It recognizes humor.
That doesn't happen until...
Well, actually, some people
never get a sense of humor.
If this were one of my patients...
...I would say it was
a gifted child who's grown bored.
It's amusing itself.
But of course, that's impossible.
It's just a machine.
Yes. Impossible.
Why is a math book so sad?
Because it has so many problems.
[LAUGHING]
BOYD [ON RECORDING]:
Why? Why do you want to escape?
Look, I want you to know,
everything you say is between us.
This is a safe place.
JOHN:
No, it's not.
Nowhere is.
BOYD: Don't you feel safe
around your family?
JOHN:
My family? Safe?
BOYD: Well, your mother seems like
a strong woman.
Doesn't that make you feel safe?
JOHN:
Might if that was what she wanted.
Safe is the last thing
she wants me to feel.
BOYD:
I find that hard to believe.
JOHN:
I'm sure she's right.
She's always right.
Fear can be a good thing.
On a bad day it'll keep you alive.
BOYD:
Do you have bad days like that?
John?
I was...
[CLEARS THROAT]
...thinking about that time we met.
You found me outside the bunker.
When you went to take a leak
and almost talked yourself...
...into eating your gun?
I don't think I've ever thanked you
for what you said that day.
I think the exact words were:
"Your fly is open."
- Yeah.
- It was.
Is there a word for what we just did?
A word?
For what we just did.
I can think of a few, yeah.
- Can you?
- You wanna hear them?
No.
I want a new one.
Is this your way of getting rid of me?
You'll be gone soon enough.
What do we need a new word for?
I'm pretty sure if I use one of
the old ones, you'll still do it with me.
I might choose to misunderstand.
The old words.
I have a new life, Derek.
I want new words.
Think of one and I might let you stay.
I'm thirsty.
Can you get me a drink, please?
I don't think I've ever seen
anything like it.
It's for my daughter.
I'm sure she'll love it.
You think so?
I don't know what she loves.
How goes the robot hunt, Mr. Ellison?
Absurd, when you put it like that.
If you need any resources,
you let me know.
I do have a question,
if that's all right.
The basement.
What's happening down there?
It seems that there's high security.
And for good reason, Mr. Ellison.
We're building something.
Good luck on your hunt.
Sorry about the confusion.
My assistant's out today.
The temp agency is sending someone.
Are you all right?
You said this was a safe place, right?
- That I could say anything?
- That's right.
[STATIC ON BUG]
You have to understand,
my mom doesn't want me coming here.
She worries.
About you?
About everybody.
What about your sister?
She worried about her too?
My sister's...
...stronger than I am.
[DING]
Someone broke into your house.
She forgot my birthday.
I thought she did.
She sent my sister out for a cake.
We were alone and a man broke in.
He wanted computer equipment.
JOHN:
He tied us up.
BOYD:
What happened next?
Nothing.
Nothing happened.
The guy got what he wanted,
and he let us go.
You know...
...John, sometimes children feel
like they need to...
...protect their parents.
But that's not your job.
You're not one of my vets.
Your not a...
You're not a soldier.
You get to be a kid.
No.
[DING]
WOMAN:
I know the records are in there.
MAN: No, you don't. It's a waste of time.
WOMAN: It's not a waste of time.
[DING]
It was here for Dr. Sherman.
- It was there to kill him.
- Or protect him.
Whatever Sherman is or isn't supposed
to do, he's gonna live to do it.
For now.
I guess we're not gonna get any
answers from this. What'd you do to it?
CAMERON:
Nothing.
Once I accessed the CPU,
the chip destroyed itself.
- This model has been redesigned.
- With a self-destruct feature?
Skynet must not want me
reprogramming in the future.
This is one way to stop you.
JOHN: I guess they're getting smarter.
We should too.
Time's up, Savannah.
See you next week.
Could you play for a minute, Savannah?
I'd like to speak with the doctor.
I'm very impressed with your work.
Oh, well, you've done
some good work too, Ms. Weaver.
Savannah seems happier.
I gather you've worked hard to show her
the mother she knew...
...before her father's death.
I have, yes. But I wasn't speaking
of your work with Savannah.
I meant the insight you had
into my project.
I could use someone with your instincts
on my team.
I'm... I'm flattered, but I do have
a responsibility to my patients.
As a consultant, then.
You compared the AI to a child.
Help me raise it.
Well, you realize you're talking to a man
who doesn't even know...
...how to run his own lawn mower.
Just treat it like one of your patients.
You'll do quite well.
When I was a child, I did my sums
on rolls of butcher paper.
My father would bring them home
from work.
I liked the way the paper smelled.
That's my most vivid memory
from childhood.
What did the paper smell like?
Cow's blood.
SARAH: In 1678, doctors diagnosed the
mental affliction soldiers suffered from...
...as nostalgia.
Homesickness.
A longing to return to the past.
The cruel reality of war is
that there is no return home.
No return to innocence.
What is lost, is lost forever.
Like my father,
war's wounds have bled me dry.
No words of comfort.
No words of forgiveness.
No words at all.
I have to say, I was surprised
when you called.
Why don't you start by telling me
why you're here?
[GRUNTING]
[CRUNCH]