In the future,
a computer program called Skynet
will declare war on the human race.
Machines have traveled back in time
taking human form
to terminate John Connor,
the future leader of the Resistance.
Sarah Connor, John's mother,
teacher and protector.
Cameron, a Terminator reprogramed
to defend them at all costs.
Derek Reese, John's uncle
and a commanding officer
with the Resistance.
Together, they fight to stop Skynet
from ever being created.
The battle for our tomorrow
starts today.
Episode 204: Allison from Palmdale
v 1.00
http://Projet-SG.net
Earth to Cameron.
What?
Are you okay?
'Cause if you're gonna try and kill me
again, I wouldn't mind a head start.
If I was going to try
to kill you again,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
Fair enough. Listen, I'm gonna go
get some stuff from Radio World.
I'll meet you in a half hour.
30 minutes, I swear.
Get me some of those cheese things,
all right?
The crunchy ones,
not the puffy ones.
I'm sorry to bother you. It's just...
I'm having these weird pains.
What kind of pains?
Just like a spicy taco
kind of pain,
but I haven't eaten
any spicy tacos.
And I'm bleeding!
We need to take you
to the hospital.
Thanks.
Miss?
Are you all right?
Someone get the manager.
You been drinkin'?
Taking drugs?
You got a wallet
or some kind of ID on you?
What's your name?
My name?
Why should I tell you?
If you don't, we'll give you one.
Go ahead.
I'm dying to hear it.
Alison!
Alison Young!
So, what are you in for?
I was in a store...
and I couldn't remember anything.
Blackouts.
Been there, done that.
- Can tattoos disappear?
- Sure.
Got two of my ex's lasered off.
Ryan was... right here.
And Jose... was here.
- Next time I'm thinking henna.
- Henna?
- I'm Jody.
- I'm...
Placenta's still attached.
There's no previa.
No evidence of major abruption.
So everything's fine.
I wanna run a Kleihauer-Betke
to rule out fetal blood cells.
What does that mean?
We wanna make sure
the blood is yours and not the baby's.
What if it is the baby's?
Then we do an emergency C-section.
But let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
That didn't sound good.
No, it didn't.
Hey, look,
I know you're busy, so...
if you need to go...
- Can I call someone?
- You mean like the father?
I'll be fine. Go.
What happened here?
Some girl totally wigged out.
What do you mean, wigged out?
She's on drugs or something.
She couldn't even remember
her own name.
What'd she look like?
Wanna guess like 16, 17,
- brown hair, maybe like 5'8"...
- Where is she now?
Cops took her.
Store owner's not pressing charges.
I don't wanna see you back here.
And you... I'm sick of you.
This is your last
get out of jail free.
- Where you headed?
- I don't know.
- Good.
- Why good?
'Cause you're comin' with me.
I'm looking for my sister.
She was picked up
at the food mart on Van Nuys.
Yeah, that one.
We released her about an hour ago.
Did she say where she was going?
I'm sorry,
but I really need to find her, okay?
She's on medication.
My mom's gonna kill me.
She might kill her, actually.
She left with one of the street kids,
Jody.
Do you know
where Jody hangs out?
Usually gets popped
along the boulevard.
All right, thanks.
It's a boy, you know.
Boy's good.
I hate being trapped in bed...
feeling like
there's nothing I can do.
If you can't protect them
when they're still inside you,
how can you ever protect them?
What was yours like?
When John was born.
I was living in Central America
at the time.
We were hiking in the jungle
when my water broke.
Tried to get to the nearest town,
but there wasn't time.
- Did you have anything for the pain?
- Bottle of dark rum.
And John's father?
He was right there with me.
I remember holding his hand
really tight.
Gosh, how did you
finally get out of there?
Hitched a ride on a chicken bus.
Tobacco farmer handed out cigars.
We smoked and then sang
this birthday song.
Oh, sing a little bit for me.
My spanish is rusty
and I've never been able to sing.
So?
I heard you were here.
I was worried.
- Is everything...
- We're waiting on some test results.
- I'm Trevor.
- Sarah.
I should go.
Unless you need something else.
Maybe some magazines?
You know Jody?
A girl named Jody?
Hey, you know a girl named Jody?
You know a Jody?
You know Jody?
Hey, do you know a girl named Jody?
Hey, you know someone named Jody?
- Just checking in. What are you doing?
- Nothing. Cameron and I are shopping.
- What are you doing?
- I took Kacy to the hospital.
Is she okay?
They're running a few tests.
I'm gonna be a while.
- How long?
- I don't know. Why?
Delicious!
- Who was that?
- Nobody. I gotta go.
Thank you for taking the time
to see me.
I understand your reluctance
to discuss these things over the phone.
But I'm pleased you're still
considering my job offer.
I am. Thank you.
I appreciate a man who's calm
and careful in his decision making.
The last time I went hunting
for these things you want me to hunt,
20 other people died.
I won't let that happen again.
Nor should you.
These things...
They're evil.
We have to be careful, Agent,
not to anthropomorphize a machine.
These are more
than machines, Miss Weaver.
But I'll never make the mistake
of thinking they're human.
Two years ago, my husband and I were
in a helicopter accident.
- He was killed.
- I'm sorry.
He was flying us to Barstow.
There was a microchip plant there
doing some amazing things.
So your husband was a pilot.
He had over 700 hours
on that particular helicopter.
It was his passion.
This is difficult for you.
The Kulishov A-85
is a beautiful flying machine.
Like the most perfect bird.
It's almost flawless in its design.
Almost flawless?
It needs a human to fly it.
Are you saying that...
machines make better decisions
than humans?
What I think...
is that in certain
extreme conditions,
even the most calm
and careful of men
panic.
Help me find this machine, Agent.
You and I'll take it apart
piece by piece.
I'm not sure what we'll find,
but I doubt we'll find evil.
So much food.
I know.
We're totally puking later.
But whatever.
It's an occasion.
- I like your necklace.
- It's cool, huh?
I got it from this awesome
thrift store in Echo Park.
So...
Two years ago,
when I moved here from Michigan,
I had this internship
at a storefront in Chinatown.
The designer was this total druggie.
And when I finally called him out
on what stuck up
and talentless bitch he was,
I got fired from my unpaid job.
That's when I started
crashing with people
and doing, you know,
whatever... for money...
Which got sketchy real quick.
Especially in LA.
The city is like a freak magnet.
You'd look really pretty in this.
- We should bounce.
- How much you get for it, bitch?
- Don't know what you're talking about.
- My laptop, with all the stuff?
- I didn't take your laptop, dude.
- It just disappeared the day you left.
Okay, look...
Who are you, huh?
You a little thief too?
Just take it.
Go!
Please just go!
The next time I see you,
you better have me something.
All I'm saying is sometimes
you gotta take a punch once in a while
in order to keep the cash...
That was a lot of cash.
I'm sorry.
Fill it out so we can crash here
for a couple of nights.
- I don't know what to write.
- Doesn't matter. Lie.
The other catch is you have to have
this interview with a counselor.
Just BS your way through it.
Don't tell them anything real.
Nice.
Where'd you learn how to do that?
I don't know.
You weren't, like...
getting beaten up
or anything, were you?
Sorry about that thing
I said earlier about taking a punch.
If you've gotten your fill,
I shouldn't have said it.
But don't worry.
From now on...
I got your back.
Wasn't easy getting that shot.
Where was it?
Tanzania.
Paul and I just got back
a couple weeks ago.
But you didn't come here
to talk about zebras.
I was hoping you could run a check
on someone for me... Off the record.
Who is it?
Catherine Weaver.
Zeira Corp.
- What's your interest in her?
- Actually, she's interested in me.
She offered me a job.
- You're leaving the bureau?
- It's just an offer, Lila.
You're not wearing your cross.
How do you know?
The way you're carrying yourself.
What happened in North Hollywood...
That wasn't your fault.
Agent Ellison?
Got those updated 302s for you.
Thank you, Liz.
Glad you kept the name.
It's a good name.
Where are you from, Alison?
I don't remember.
Where are you from,
Alison?
I don't remember...
You don't remember
what town you're from?
Why does it matter?
It's not there anymore.
You know, sometimes
when people forget,
it's because they need to forget...
because something
painful has happened.
I'm wondering if something
has happened to you.
Tell me about your life.
I live in a tunnel.
I eat garbage for dinner.
Anything you say in here
is confidential.
The only exception is
if you were planning to harm someone...
- I would have to report that.
- I would never hurt anyone.
Tell me about your family.
Memory is a very associative thing.
Sometimes sights,
sounds,
even a smell can take us back.
My father was an architect.
He taught me how to draw.
My mother was a music teacher.
She'd sit for hours
and listen to Chopin.
What's that bracelet on your arm?
My sister gave it to me
for my birthday.
July 22nd...
I had a party in Griffith Park.
All my friends were there.
I saw a boy ride by
on his silver mountain bike,
and I told my dad...
That's what I want.
And he said next year.
But I didn't have a party
the next year. No one did.
Why not?
Everyone was dead.
It's a Balinese tiger.
Have you ever seen a real one?
Unfortately, they were hunted
to extinction in the '30s.
Do you ever think
that could happen to us?
To humans?
Is that something you worry about?
I wanna go home.
Where is home?
Palmdale.
- Palmdale?
- That's where I'm from.
Hey, do you know a Jody,
by any chance?
Jody?
Do you know a Jody?
- Anybody here know a Jody?
- Yeah, yeah, I know her.
She was here with some other chick.
Do you know where she went?
But she hangs out at this halfway house
sometimes on Yucca.
Yucca. Thanks.
Hungry?
Split my jell-o with you.
Where's Trevor?
He went to go get me some real food.
He's the baby daddy.
In case you didn't figure that out.
- You never mentioned him.
- We've been on and off.
He freaked when I got pregnant.
But... Now he's here.
I don't know.
Just... I just want life
to be perfect for him,
you know?
Didn't you feel that way?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not an idiot.
I know it'll never be perfect.
It's just...
Right now... in there...
no one's ever made fun of him,
turned him down for a date.
How long does he have, really,
until he figures out
how hard it can all be?
- Hello?
- Mom?
It's me, Alison.
I'm sorry.
You must have the wrong number.
- Mrs. Young?
- Yes. This is Claire Young.
I'm here with your daughter.
There must be some mistake.
I don't have a daughter.
Not yet.
Very pretty name, though, Alison.
She didn't even know who I was.
Parents suck.
Especially mothers.
Why would she do that to me?
Who knows why anyone does anything?
Come on.
Let's go have some fun.
Ah, ah. Sit.
Eat. I insist.
Thank you.
You like tri-tip?
I grill a mean tri-tip.
We could do a barbecue.
With you and the kids.
- John and... What's the girl's name?
- Cameron.
I can't wait to meet 'em.
If you want, I can take John
to the range with me sometime.
- He's not much of a golfer.
- Me neither. Guns.
Trevor's a cop.
Detective.
LAPD.
We got the results.
Cells were all maternal.
The baby's fine.
We need to keep you overnight,
but you can go home tomorrow.
I knew it.
He's a fighter, this kid.
Just like his mama.
No criminal history.
No pending SCC investigations.
Nothing from FINCEN.
Her CTRs all check out.
- Not even a civil suit.
- That's good to know.
James, before you make
such a huge change,
don't you think
you should talk to someone?
Marshal Weaver's helicopter crash
was due to mechanical failure?
You're not listening to me.
I talked to a couple of people.
- It's possible you're suffering from...
- What people?
- Paul?
- He served in the Persian Gulf.
He's got experience
with this kind of thing.
I came to you in confidence.
I'm worried about you, James.
I've never seen you in so much pain.
Yeah, we both know that's not true.
Thank you for the report.
Yes!
I'm gonna go get a soda.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Playing foosball.
- We've gotta go.
- Go? Where?
- Home.
- Home?
Who are you?
Cameron...
My name's Alison.
No, it's not. It's Cameron.
I can't explain this to you right now.
We have to go before mom gets home.
- You're freaking me out.
- I'm freaking you out?
- You really not know who you are?
- I'm Alison.
From Palmdale.
You're not Alison.
You're not from Palmdale.
You're from the future.
You're a machine.
A what?
The chip is messed up again,
but I can fix you.
- I fixed you once, remember?
- Fixed me?
Why would you fix me?
- Come on, we have to get out of here.
- What did you do? Did you hurt me?
Is there a problem?
No. I'm her brother.
John Baum.
I don't have a brother.
Look, dude,
I don't know who you are,
but I really think...
Sir, you need to leave.
You shouldn't have run.
You're just making things
worse for yourself.
Your hair.
It's so pretty.
We work very hard on the hair
to get it right.
- I'm not your enemy.
- Right.
I want to get to know you.
You're very brave.
That must be
why John Connor chose you.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I admire him,
his determination.
His spirit, his fearlessness.
- I'd like to meet him.
- He wouldn't want to meet you.
They're going to kill you.
They're going to kill
every one of you.
They'll hunt you down
until every human is gone,
and you're extinct.
Then...
Why are we having this conversation?
Because some of us don't want that.
Some of us want peace.
You were chosen, Alison,
not just by John Connor,
by us.
Tell me where his camp is.
I think...
I'm a machine.
A machine.
What kind of machine?
From the future.
What do you do in the future?
I'm an infiltrator.
What do you infiltrate?
The human resistance.
I see.
Why?
- It's what I was programmed for.
- Programmed.
To find John Connor.
Why's he so important?
He's the one who saves mankind.
Saves them. From... What?
Extinction.
And what are you gonna do
when you find John Connor?
I'm going to kill him
and hang his head on a pike
for all to see.
Your hair.
It's so pretty.
Thanks.
Tell me about your life.
Why?
I want to get to know you.
I don't really like
talking about my past.
I came to LA to start over.
Did you?
Yeah. Burned a lot
of bridges here, though.
Keep thinking I'm gonna go someplace
more authentic, you know, like Portland.
I could come with you.
We could reinvent ourselves.
We could.
So... Who are you, really?
I've never heard of you.
Suddenly you're Kacy's best friend.
I'm just a neighbor.
Sorry. Cop brain.
Stresses her, you know.
My job.
You'd think having a cop around
would make her feel safe.
She's afraid
it'll follow me back home.
Does it?
I can protect her.
It's your family, right?
You do what it takes.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Right.
There was a robbery/homicide downtown.
I'm gonna have to take off.
What about tomorrow?
She's gonna need a ride.
I'll be here.
I just... I hate for her
to spend the night alone.
Agent Ellison.
Come in.
This is my daughter Savannah.
Sudoku.
I used to love these.
You have children, Agent Ellison?
No.
- Do you want them?
- I did... once.
Very much.
But my wife...
Well, my ex-wife...
wasn't meant to be.
Bye, Savannah.
Your husband's helicopter crash.
I read the official report.
The NTSB concluded
that mechanical failure
was to blame.
Mechanical failure.
Correct.
That's not what you led me
to believe the other day.
Correct.
Which is it?
What's the truth?
You tell me.
I think...
what people write in reports...
when it's official
isn't always true.
I think if I had a child,
one that I knew would grow up asking
what happened to her daddy...
I think I would make sure
that answer,
the official answer,
was the one
I would want her to hear.
I think you saw what you saw.
Just as you saw what you saw.
When can I start?
I used to babysit for this family
five years ago.
They were loaded.
You said you moved here
two years ago from Michigan.
They usually hide a key
here somewhere.
Sweet! You are jacked, girl.
Look for cash and jewelry.
Check this out.
Saw the lady open it.
And I memorized...
the combination.
Just put it all in the bag.
What are these?
Whatever. Just put 'em back.
They're the same
as the necklace you gave me.
Because I stole it
when I worked here.
You said, "I got it at this awesome
thrift store in Echo Park."
Tell me about the necklace.
Why are you making
such a big deal out of this?
Tell me about the necklace.
I didn't buy it or steal it, okay?
It's mine.
This is... my parents' house.
You lied to me.
I told you where the camp was.
You told me your sister
gave you that bracelet.
What does that
have to do with anything?
We found these
on some of your friends.
Why are you all wearing them?
It has something to do
with the Connor camp.
No.
It's a pass.
To get into the camp.
You were going to send me without it.
They would have known what I was.
You lied to me.
I'll never help you
get to John Connor.
You already did.
You lied to me.
I'm from LA, okay?
Let's go.
Tell me who you are.
I went to Cal Arts for two years,
and I got kicked out,
which was for the best,
because that place is a... factory.
And my parents cut me off
like yours,
and just pretend I don't exist.
We have to go. Now.
Why?
Because there's a silent alarm,
and we tripped it when we walked in.
You weren't going to tell me.
The police are gonna
be here any second.
You were never going to Portland.
You were gonna run
and leave me here to take the blame.
No.
You lied to me.
I'll never help you
get to John Connor.
No, no, no. What did you do?
What did you do?
We have to go.
John.
Did you kill her?
Apparently not.
- Where's Trevor?
- He was called into work.
Be back tomorrow to take you home.
What's wrong?
It wasn't him that freaked out.
It was me.
- When I found out I was pregnant.
- Cop thing. He told me.
Yeah. Cop thing.
It's kinda cool and sexy
when you're a 25-year-old pastry chef
making gourmet doughnuts
at this hip cop hangout
in Silverlake.
When you think about
breast-feeding your baby boy
next to the walkie
and the.9 millimeter...
Still...
He's a good man.
He'll be a good dad.
Kacy, I have to tell you something.
That story about John's birth,
it wasn't true.
- The jungle?
- No, that part was true.
The part about his father wasn't.
He wasn't there with me.
He died before John was born.
Before I even knew I was pregnant.
Why did you tell me that story?
'Cause I wished
it's the way it could have been.
That's the saddest thing
I've ever heard.
The thing is, I got through it.
All of it.
By myself. And so can you.
Besides, you won't be alone.
I'll be right next door.
That was my last
get out of jail free.
Damn right.
Where'd you get that?
I got it at this awesome
thrift store in Echo Park.