Legend of Tennessee Moltisanti
In the Czech Republic too,
we love pork.
Ever had our sausages?
In the Czech Republic too,
we love pork.
You ever had our sausages?
Adriana?
In the Czech Republic too,
we love pork. Ever had our sausages?
Emil Kolar?
- Help you?
- Salami sub, hold the mayo.
We're out of mayo.
Change my meat to black forest.
You killed me.
What do you want me to do?
I want to tell you.
What?
You come here every night.
You fucked up.
What do you mean?
Here's these.
Where'd you find them?
One in the table. Three in my skull.
You will have our sausages.
Get rid of these.
Let go of me! Let go!
- I would've wrapped it...
- That's okay. A computer!
This one got such a good write-up,
I got one for myself.
- Let's move on, okay?
- Congratulations. God bless.
You look gorgeous.
Who's your date?
What do you mean, Who's your date?
- Good to see you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Melissa was beautiful up there.
Oh, Mama Livia, come stai, darling?
Listen to him,
with that my darling.
I am nobody's darling.
She never disappoints you.
Are you still seeing your
other women, Lorenzo?
Come on, Ma, let's mingle.
Sorry, the older she gets,
the worse she gets.
I heard disturbing shit last night.
I wanted to talk to you.
But with the rehearsal dinner
and everything, you know...
There's the priest.
I'll be right back.
Federal indictments?
Where the fuck did you get this?
I got a guy, his goomar works at FBI
headquarters as a word processor.
When's it coming down?
I don't know. When she knows,
she'll tell me.
- Indictments? What the fuck?
- You sure?
It ain't just my source in Jersey. Half
of New York moved to Fort Lauderdale.
Fuck! They're gonna want my ass.
Why?
What do you mean, why? I'm O.C.
When'd you get your wings?
I didn't. Not yet, anyway.
Uncle Junior, you got anything to say?
You guys see indictments
under your bed at night.
You're ready to lam it. As far as
I'm concerned, it's speculation.
It's rumor.
Better be safe than sorry.
I say we duck for a while.
What're we gonna do, close shop?
We can't do that.
Tony, what do you think?
What the fuck are you asking him for?
I just gave you the answer.
He's right, we go, it's open season.
Albanians will be living in our houses.
I just gave a G-note
to Larry Boy's kid for the boost.
If I have to lam in a hurry,
I'd have duped her another time.
I gotta go. It's an emergency.
Say goodbye to your father for me.
I agree with my uncle.
He calls the shots, we do it.
Well, maybe for today,
for right now...
...you were thinking that everybody
should do spring cleaning?
That was my next comment.
Think they'll come over the weekend?
They're coming someday.
- Where's the rest of the money?
- Everywhere.
Get it.
- What else?
- How about your phone numbers?
Anybody who's anybody's in my head.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing. Just, here we go.
Here.
Why now? Why the fuck now,
just when things were going good?
- Boot your computer, cops are coming.
- So?
You want them to see
that porno you downloaded?
Better give me your jewelry.
Oh, Jesus!
We can't produce receipts.
You want them stealing it?
Come on.
Not my engagement ring.
This isn't stolen.
Is it?
No.
What do you think I am?
Come on, give me that!
Adriana!
It ate my whole script now!
You're still on the file.
You deleted the text.
The fuck... Whatever.
You fucking asshole!
Stop with the hysteria,
would you please?
If you're gonna keep behaving
like a baby, I'm not gonna help you.
I mean it.
At least you work that
squirrel program in the restaurant.
There, the text came back.
- You put it in buffer memory.
- What do you think?
Of the script?
Babe, I can't give an opinion
every time you add a sentence.
I gotta have the whole story flow.
I'm starting with the dialogue.
I manuged to get the drop on him?
Do you mean, I managed
to get the drop on him?
Or is he saying manuge,
like mannuggia I'americano?
My Tennessee William.
Where you going?
Get over here.
I have never seen you
apply yourself like this.
I love movies. You know that.
That smell in Blockbuster...
...that candy and carpet smell,
I get high off it.
Gonna let all this love
and knowledge go to waste?
My cousin Gregory's girlfriend, Amy,
who works for Tarantino, said:
Mob stories are always hot.
I can make my mark.
With these indictments, shouldn't
you put the script away for a while...
...and get rid of evidence?
Travel light. Free bird.
You stole this computer, plus
the one you just gave Melissa.
I'm writing.
Turn on channel 6.
New Jersey Attorney General,
James Ricci, stated at a fundraiser...
... that a grand jury has been
empaneled to investigate...
... possible Mob activities in the
Garden State with indictments to follow.
With us is syndicated columnist
and author of Mafia:
America's Longest-Running
Soap Opera, Jeffrey Wernick.
- Welcome.
- Pleasure to be here.
For years, FBI has been telling us
that the Mafia is all but dead.
Let me interject.
While it is true that the Mob is
getting a standing eight-count...
... I wouldn 't call the fight.
The government knows this best.
Murder, truck hijacking and money
laundering are expected inquiries.
Do we know names of those
who 'll be indicted?
The indictments are sealed,
but with the recent death...
... of acting Di Meo family boss,
Jackie Aprile...
... my sources tell me that
Corrado Junior Soprano...
... was made new boss
after the death of Aprile.
The Sopranos have long, historic
ties to the New York families.
What about possible
murder charges?
They will undoubtedly be focused
on the as yet unsolved...
... execution-style slaying of Soprano
family associate, Brendan Filone.
- Was it part of a power struggle?
- Interesting.
No one would have ranked him
as associate!
- A loyal soldier,
and he winds up dead...
Soldier?
Brendan Filone? Associate?
Soldier? Fuck you!
Jesus!
Did you see it from the beginning?
Did they mention my name?
Stop the fucking chitchat, all right?
I gotta go.
Nobody makes guinso gravy
like you, Nana.
You know, I'm up at Bard
waiting for my care package.
I don't like that word, Jason.
What, guinso?
- The word is offensive!
- She's right, Jason.
Sorry, Nana. What's it mean?
- It's from guinea.
- What's that?
It's a derogation.
I have a patient.
You wouldn't say guinea to him.
Italian male seeing a shrink.
Let me guess: Mother issues.
- Why wouldn't you?
- Just wouldn't.
You'd be scared?
Is he in the Mafia?
No, I shouldn't have mentioned it!
Can we change the subject?
No way. Mom, is he
in the Mob, or what?
He's not a mobster, is he?
Nobody knows better than you, Richard.
I can't discuss my patients.
I just hope he's not one of those
crumbs on the news.
Just refer him to another doctor.
You can do that, couldn't you?
Grate the cheese, Dad.
Sure she can.
That might be what
you would do, Richard.
Now I remember why we got divorced.
Why refer him to another doctor?
He's my patient.
You can't treat sociopaths. You
shouldn't help scum with bed-wetting.
You have no idea who this man is,
and yet you call him scum.
People like him are the reason
Italian-Americans have a bad image.
I agree.
Ask any American to describe an
Italian-American in this country...
...invariably he's gonna reference
The Godfather, Goodfellas...
Good movies.
...and the rest will mention pizza.
- Good movies to eat pizza by.
Stop it, Jason!
I never said he was in the Mafia.
We'll never see an Italian president.
And that's my patient's fault?
I realize that you're involved
in the Anti-Defamation lobby.
So go after Hollywood if you feel
you must. But leave my patient alone.
It's a synergy.
News items and the portrayal
of Italian-Americans as gangsters!
Wasn't the Italian Anti-Def deal
started by Joe Colombo? A mobster?
Italians Against Discrimination
did a study.
In its height, the Mafia in the U.S.
Had less than 5000 members.
And yet, that tiny,
insignificant fraction...
...casts such a dark shadow over
20 million hard-working Americans.
At this point in our cultural history,
Mob movies are classic American cinema.
Like Westerns.
I have to agree there, Rich.
You never saw the Scotch-Irish
pissing and moaning...
...about being portrayed
as rustlers and gunslingers.
That's absurd!
See what you started
with your gravy, Nana?
To we, the 20 million.
- Salute!
- Cent'anni.
- Salute.
What?
Come here.
We're exterminating.
I'm busy now.
Get some sfogliatelle for the guys.
Yeah.
Twenty-nine.
Here you go, big guy.
Hey, Gino. What can I get you?
- Get me some...
- Number 34, right here!
He just went out
to get gas in his car.
I go out, fuck your sister, come
back Saturday, I go to the front?
I said he could.
Poppin' Fresh, I'm in no mood!
I'm next, now get
a fucking pastry box.
Gino, what can I get you?
Dougie, let him go first.
He don't make the rules here!
All right, two Neapolitan loaves...
You touch a single crust, you'll
wish you took that job at McDonalds!
Fuck you!
Okay, take a walk.
- What about my bread?
- You come back in 10 minutes.
What do you think you're doing?
Come on.
Get up, I'm not gonna hurt you.
What is it?
Do I look like a pussy to you?
- No.
- Seriously, be honest, I won't get mad.
So why give me a hard time
and talk to me like I'm nothing?
I'm sorry.
Get a pastry box.
Move it!
That's better.
Now fill it with cannoli,
sfogliatelle and napoleons.
Move.
Good.
Give me the box. Come on.
Next time you see my face,
show some respect.
I will.
You motherfucker!
You shot my foot!
- It happens.
- You fucking asshole!
If I'm getting an invitation to the
dance, I wish the feds would hurry up.
You heard what the news said.
The way things are working,
it's Junior's party.
That was a far-thinking plan
you had there, Tone.
I called you last Christmas.
Fuck this!
The sfogliatelle!
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
You brought up in a barn, or what?
What's the matter with you?
This is no time to go on the rag.
Not with the indictment coming down.
Take Georgie, go in the bathroom,
sweep for bugs.
Come on.
Well, I hope they'll be all right.
Who?
- The guys.
- What about me?
They didn't even
mention your name on TV.
Amazing, huh? That news guy,
he said the words Brendan Filone ...
...the hairs on the back of my neck,
they fucking stood up.
I knew the guy.
They made him look like
John-fucking-Gotti.
I brought him around here.
Tony wouldn't have never known him
if it wasn't for me.
I had no idea.
Who is it? I'm sleeping.
- Carmela.
- Oh, come on in.
I just said that in case
you were...
...that snooty-assed Mrs. Ryan
down the hall.
She is so shanty Irish,
and with all her airs.
- Come on, I'm taking you to brunch.
- What?
Get dressed.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Why does something have to be wrong?
Meadow? She eats like a bird.
Everything is fine, Ma, relax!
Nothing is wrong.
You come here unannounced. I shouldn't
wonder if something's wrong?
Jeez, I'm sorry. It's a nice day,
I thought I would take you out.
I don't want to go out!
Is it Anthony? Those indictments?
His father could take it in stride,
but he can't.
I don't believe you.
Ma, will you get dressed?
- We just went to a wedding!
- That was a big to-do.
This way we get to spend
some quality time.
The Manor will stop serving
brunch any minute.
Did he cheat on you again?
I try to do something nice.
I come here to take you out.
You think I have some other agenda
that I have to talk to you about?
Don't flatter yourself.
I'II...
I'll throw something on.
Buckle your seat belt, Ma.
I can't find it! Where is it?
It's not definite.
I just thought I'd tell you.
In case I don't show up
for an appointment.
You're telling me you're planning
a vacation, but you're not sure when?
Right.
I may never go.
Let's put it this way:
There's a strong possibility
that it could happen.
Does this have anything to do
with what's been on the news lately?
If you suddenly stop coming
to your appointments...
...I will assume that you are
on vacation?
And I should wait to be contacted?
That would be a good assumption.
- Who is it?
- Paulie. Open the door.
I thought we were stepping out.
I got two broads in the car.
You said Ad went to stay
at her mother's.
No wonder. The place looks
like a fucking sty.
What's wrong?
Talk to me. This ain't like you, kid.
I ran into Billy Cracciolo.
The meter maid?
What about him?
Told me the cops in Nutley
are looking for a guy.
Blew off a kid's toe for
no good reason in Russo's Bakery.
Drove a Lexus?
Does Tony know about this?
What's going on, Chrissy?
Been working my ass off on this script.
You know how many pages I got?
Nineteen.
That a lot or a little?
Books say a movie's supposed to be
about 120 pages.
I thought the computer would
do a lot of it.
You're being frank
about the business...
I would never do that.
It's only suggested by.
That writer, with the bullfights?
Blew his own fucking head off.
I bought a scriptwriting program.
My advice?
Put that thing down awhile.
We get our joints copped.
Tomorrow, the words will come
blowing out your ass.
You ever feel like nothing
good would ever happen?
Yeah. And nothing did. So what?
I'm alive, I'm surviving.
That's it.
I don't want to just survive.
It says in movie-writing books that
every character has an arc, understand?
Everybody starts out somewheres
and then they do something...
...it changes their life.
That's their arc.
Where's my arc?
All right, take Richard Kimble, right?
No, that's no good. His arc is
run, run, jump off the dam...
Keanu Reeves, Devil's Advocate.
- AI.
- Right.
Keanu's a lawyer, gets all turned on
by money, power and the Devil.
Then his wife says, You're not
the man I married, leaves him.
You see the arc?
He starts down here, he ends up here.
Where's my arc, Paulie?
Kid...
...Richard Kimble, the Devil's
whatever, those are all make-believe.
I got no arc either.
I was born, grew up, spent a few years
in the Army, a few more in the can.
And here I am. A half a wiseguy.
So what?
I got no identity.
Even Brendan Filone's got
an identity. He's dead.
I killed that fucking Emil Kolar,
and nothing.
I don't even move up a notch.
All I got is nightmares.
That Polish, Czech,
whatever he is...
...is haunting me in my dreams
every night.
That happens. The more of them
you do, the better you'll sleep.
I had one prick for months
in my dreams.
I feel like he's trying to tell me
we fucked up the night we buried him.
- We didn't.
- I'm in danger.
Can I ask a question?
Why would he tell you
you're in danger...
...considering you put
a moonroof in his head?
What did we do wrong that night?
The gun was hot, so the slugs
couldn't be traced to me.
You know who had an ark?
Noah.
Is that him?
That would be some fucking
coincidence if it wasn't, wouldn't it?
- Holy shit! Look.
- What?
He was clean-shaven.
He's got a beard now.
You know what?
I read that. That happens.
I always thought it was bullshit.
Look at his fingernails!
They're like a woman's.
I'm gonna fucking puke.
Help me lift him and take him to Pine
Barrens before they build a condo here.
Georgie!
I don't know about
selling this property.
I don't know about you,
but I sure could use an infusion...
...if we're supporting Jase
after he graduates.
It's funny how even during our
marriage, we saw things differently.
I never saw this place
as an investment.
I always thought
that we'd build a house.
So are we gonna sell, or what?
For Jason.
I don't want to hear that you took
one of your Colleens on a cruise.
What's that supposed to mean,
Colleens?
We all know you're a sucker
for those Irish girls.
Every Italian boy
bows down to the freckles.
- I married you!
- Yeah, I was a mother figure.
Don't bust my balls
with Freud-by-numbers.
Don't bust my balls?
Richard, your calabrese is showing.
Are you implying by all this
I'm ashamed to be an Italian-American?
With all the poverty, starvation,
ethnic cleansing...
...and horrible shit in this world...
...you devote your energy to protecting
the dignity of Connie Francis!
You're worked up about my patient...
...a man who has no bearing on
who or where you are in this world.
Call him a patient.
The man's a criminal, Jennifer.
And after a while, you're gonna
get beyond psychotherapy...
...with its cheesy moral relativism.
Finally, you're gonna get
to good and evil. And he's evil.
Sorry I'm late. The alarm...
What is wrong with you?
I ain't been feeling good.
- I wipe my ass with your feelings.
- Thanks.
Drive the fucking car!
We're under a microscope. I hear you
shot some kid because he made you wait!
- Fucking Paulie!
- Don't blame Paulie!
Nutley PD's got a description
and a make on the car!
Why don't you leave a urine sample?
- Lf I could...
- Shut up!
Georgie comes in with vomit all over.
I ask, What the fuck?
He said you're digging up some body!
- I was worried...
- Shut up!
- You want to get caught.
- I want to?
Yeah. I seen it before.
That's fucking cowboy-itis.
You want to be a bad guy?
- I was worried that I didn't...
- Shut up!
Can I try and explain here?
I don't know, Tony.
It's like the regular-ness of life
is too fucking hard for me.
I don't know.
Look at you.
I'll bet you're sleeping all the time.
It's the only thing I still enjoy.
You know what I think?
Maybe I have cancer.
Remember how Jackie got?
Cancer?
Something fucking horrible
is going on inside my body.
Does this word cancer
pop into your mind a lot...
...a little bit, what?
Well, I'm just thinking,
maybe you're...
...depressed.
- Me?
I'm no fucking mental midget.
Right.
- Watch the...
- What?
- Filter.
- Oh, fuck!
Maybe you got...
...a serotonin problem,
or whatever the fuck they call it.
You know about that shit?
I saw it last night on a program.
What, take fucking Prozac?
Not this skinny guinea.
Let me ask a question.
You ever think about...
...you know...
Fuck no!
Good.
Bunch of losers blowing
their skulls all over the bathroom?
It's fucking pathetic.
- Did you hear the doorbell?
- I'm in the middle of a game.
You'll be in the middle of
the street, you don't wise up.
Anthony Soprano?
Why are you in my yard?
The gate was open.
I'm Agent Harris, this is
Agent Driscol. May we come in?
If I say no?
If we were local, we wouldn't knock.
What's your point?
We have a search warrant.
We know you have children.
Our other team's out front. We don't
traumatize kids by kicking in doors.
So why don't you take a minute
and tell them you have visitors.
Any quarters, you can keep.
You trying to bribe me?
Tell me what you're looking for,
I can save you time.
Any incriminating evidence
would be nice.
Dad!
- I have an English paper!
- You gotta be shitting me.
I better have all my programs
when it comes back.
Anthony!
What the hell are they doing
in my kitchen?
What are you doing?
Forgot your lunch, just ask.
I'm very sorry.
How much would you say
that bowl cost?
- I'm not cleaning that up.
- Grasso, clean that.
Grasso, ti faccio un culo così.
Your ass!
Take it easy.
Grasso, take it easy.
We'll be gone in a few minutes.
Let's wait in the living room.
Clean up the bowl.
Come on.
I know they're doing their job,
but I'm pissed.
Harris wasn't so bad.
He was the biggest sneak out of
all of them. It's part of his act.
That guy broke the bowl on purpose.
He was just a klutz.
What was his last name?
- Rizzo, Razzo, what?
- Grasso.
Grasso. You think it's a coincidence
they sent him?
If he wasn't Italian, he'd be
at the office sweeping up. Jerk.
Bet they frisk him
before he goes home.
- Why?
Because he has a vowel
at the end of his name: Grasso.
Does he think he'll make it to the top
by arresting his own people?
Pass the moo shu.
He'll see. He'll learn.
- We have a vowel.
- And you be proud of it!
You'd think there was no Michelangelo,
the way they treat people.
An Italian invented the telephone.
- Alexander Graham Bell was Italian?
- You see? You see what...?
Antonio Meucci invented it,
and he got robbed!
Everybody knows that!
Who invented the Mafia?
What?
- La Cosa Nostra. Who invented that?
- Who cares.
Wasn't it Salvatore Lucania,
known as Charlie Lucky Luciano...
...who organized the five families:
Lucchese, Gambino, Bonanno, Profaci.
Is there something
you want to say to me?
I just like history, like you, Dad.
Can you shut the fuck up about it?
A.J., did you know
John Cabot was Italian?
- Whoa.
- Like he knows who that is.
The famous discoverer of Canada.
The Bank of America.
One of the biggest banks in the world,
started by an Italian.
The first American saint
was Italian. Mother Cabrini.
Is it true the Chinese
invented spaghetti?
Now think. Why would people
who eat with sticks...
...invent something
you need a fork to eat?
Here's more I bet you don't know.
More Italians fought for the U.S.
In WWII than any other ethnic group.
They won't tell you
about Sacco and Vanzetti.
The anti-Christs
that got the electric chair?
- Anarchists.
- Isn't it anti-Christs?
They were innocent and got
the chair because they were Italian.
How are there two anti-Christs
and only one Christ?
So?
And of course, Francis Albert.
Will I see you next week?
If you know something I don't.
You understand, I have to charge you
for the missed session.
What do you mean?
We agreed on that
on our first meeting.
But I just explained my situation.
I understand, but it's important
that we respect the agreement.
- What if I got hit by a car?
- But you weren't.
- I know, but what if?
I know that, but what if?
- You weren't.
- Answer my fucking question!
I will not.
You won't?
All right, fine.
Fine, here. Here you go.
This is what it's all about.
Motherfucking, cocksucking money!
Here!
I don't understand that, and I don't
appreciate being made to feel afraid.
I don't appreciate feeling like
I pour my heart to a call girl!
- Is that how you see me?
- Not until now.
But it's obvious you don't give a shit
about my situation.
Otherwise, you wouldn't shake me down.
It'll show as paid
on your next bill.
Fine.
Stick it up your ass.
And how about Dr. Goldman here?
He was gonna be a tree surgeon,
but he fainted at the sight of sap!
Sap, ladies and gentlemen.
Pace yourselves.
Don't spend it all in one place.
Movie night, right? Last week they
showed the Polish version of Rashomon.
Everybody remembers the rape
exactly the same!
What's the matter with you, Corrado?
Headaches, that's all.
Not the kind you take aspirin for.
Now, tonight on our show, we have
Mitzi Gaynor, Sergio Franchi...
...and a woman from France will pull
light bulbs from her husband's throat.
This woman can relate.
We may have a bad apple.
Does Tony know about this?
What will you do?
There's not much to do.
We sit back and wait.
Don't let Tony know you know.
He's under enough pressure.
Yeah.
I'm sure he's telling his psychiatrist
it's all his mother's fault.
What, a psychiatrist?
Yeah, a psychiatrist.
He's been seeing one for a while now.
God only knows what he says.
- Tony?
- Yes, Tony.
Tony, who had such a terrible mother.
A psychiatrist?
Yes, Junior. For chrissake!
Show of hands, how many people think
J.F. K is still alive? Come on.
They should take a Zapruder film of
your salad bar. Hello? Help me out!
Who? The psychiatrist, I mean.
Do you think I know?
- What did you say to Tony about this?
- Me?
Nothing.
I wouldn't give him the satisfaction.
And, Junior, I don't want
there to be any repercussions.
A psychiatrist?
You're a broken record.
Yes, yes!
Do I have to...?
Do I have to say it again?
Picture yourself at Ellis Island.
All right? How does that sound?
It's me. Leave a message.
Christopher? It's Mommy.
I know you're there. Pick it up.
Are you all right?
I'm worried about you.
My God, they mentioned your name
in the newspaper. The Star-Ledger.
Mrs. Jones told me.
With all those scumbags!
It's been a while
since we met for therapy.
Jason, how's Bard?
I'm moving into a smoke-free dorm.
And how do we feel about that?
I'm interested
in discussing what we mentioned.
Jason, are you concerned that your
mother is treating this patient X?
I don't care.
As a colleague, Jen,
I suggest you drop the patient.
After her last encounter...
...she finally acknowledged...
...that she saw the different side
of him, the subhuman.
I take it you were frightened.
Frightened, revolted.
At last, appropriate emotions.
Oh, for chrissake, Richard.
You too, Sam.
When did we become afraid
to get our hands dirty?
It's what she gets paid for.
Jason, how would you like
to see your mother...?
Never mind, I'm not gonna paint
any graphic images.
See? He always does that.
What?
Follow that up, Jase. Dad does what?
His issue is that I should
distance myself from this man...
...on the grounds of the stigma
that he brings us.
I say refer this patient
to a therapist...
...that specializes
in Mafia depression.
This isn't funny.
No, of course not.
Jen has a real honest to goodness
personal and professional dilemma.
You know, on my mother's side,
we have a few dark sheep.
Excuse me?
Lepke.
Who's Lepke?
Louis Lepke Buchalter.
You know. Murder, Incorporated.
My mother's uncle
was Lepke's wheelman.
His driver.
Those were some tough Jews.
English Sub Sync by VeNOm