1
00:00:11,920 --> 00:00:15,799
Looking down from two miles above
the surface of the Earth,

2
00:00:15,880 --> 00:00:18,159
it's impossible not to be impressed

3
00:00:18,240 --> 00:00:22,439
by the sheer grandeur,
and splendour and power

4
00:00:22,520 --> 00:00:24,039
of the natural world.

5
00:00:27,560 --> 00:00:30,999
Ten years ago, in a television series
called Planet Earth,

6
00:00:31,080 --> 00:00:33,799
we revealed many of those wonders,

7
00:00:33,880 --> 00:00:36,519
but today, much has changed.

8
00:00:38,720 --> 00:00:40,839
DAVID ATTENBOROUGH:
We can now show life on our planet

9
00:00:40,920 --> 00:00:42,879
in entirely new ways,

10
00:00:45,320 --> 00:00:48,839
bring you closer to animals
than ever before,

11
00:00:51,880 --> 00:00:56,879
and reveal new wildlife dramas
for the very first time.

12
00:00:58,960 --> 00:01:00,519
(GROWLING)

13
00:01:00,600 --> 00:01:01,879
But that's not all.

14
00:01:02,840 --> 00:01:05,119
Our planet has changed, too.

15
00:01:05,760 --> 00:01:09,079
Never have those wildernesses
been as fragile

16
00:01:09,160 --> 00:01:11,479
and as precious as they are today.

17
00:01:15,080 --> 00:01:17,919
At this crucial time
for the natural world,

18
00:01:18,000 --> 00:01:20,879
we will journey to every corner
of the globe

19
00:01:22,720 --> 00:01:26,239
to explore the greatest treasures
of our living planet,

20
00:01:32,520 --> 00:01:37,519
and reveal the extreme lengths
animals go to to survive.

21
00:01:52,440 --> 00:01:56,359
Finally, we will explore our cities

22
00:01:56,440 --> 00:02:01,319
to see how life is adapting
to the newest habitat on Earth.

23
00:02:03,680 --> 00:02:06,159
This is  Planet Earth II.

24
00:02:06,600 --> 00:02:08,719
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)

25
00:02:46,480 --> 00:02:50,439
ATTENBOROUGH: There are hundreds
of thousands of islands,

26
00:02:50,520 --> 00:02:52,879
each one a world in miniature.

27
00:02:54,120 --> 00:02:57,159
A microcosm of our living planet.

28
00:02:59,000 --> 00:03:01,959
The struggles to survive
on these remote lands

29
00:03:02,040 --> 00:03:06,159
reflect the challenges
faced by all life on Earth.

30
00:03:17,000 --> 00:03:21,119
The tiny island of Escudo
off the coast of Panama,

31
00:03:23,280 --> 00:03:27,159
home to the pygmy three-toed sloth.

32
00:03:30,800 --> 00:03:34,399
This is a male,
and life here suits him well.

33
00:03:37,640 --> 00:03:41,759
Mangroves provide all the leaves
he can eat

34
00:03:41,840 --> 00:03:44,399
and there are no predators to worry him.

35
00:03:46,360 --> 00:03:49,119
Island life may seem idyllic,

36
00:03:49,200 --> 00:03:51,319
but it comes at a price.

37
00:03:53,000 --> 00:03:56,639
There are only a few hundred
pygmy sloths in existence,

38
00:03:58,040 --> 00:04:00,599
and he needs a mate.

39
00:04:02,040 --> 00:04:03,839
(SHRILL CALL)

40
00:04:04,840 --> 00:04:06,839
That's an enticing call...

41
00:04:07,400 --> 00:04:08,879
(CALL CONTINUES)

42
00:04:08,960 --> 00:04:10,319
...from a female

43
00:04:12,840 --> 00:04:14,919
somewhere out there.

44
00:04:18,000 --> 00:04:22,839
And this, for a sloth,
is a quick reaction.

45
00:04:41,920 --> 00:04:43,279
(CALL CONTINUES)

46
00:04:45,040 --> 00:04:48,959
The problem is there's deep water
between them.

47
00:04:50,480 --> 00:04:53,639
So what should any red-blooded sloth do?

48
00:04:59,000 --> 00:05:00,519
Swim, of course.

49
00:05:31,160 --> 00:05:32,839
Could this be her?

50
00:05:39,880 --> 00:05:43,479
He does his best to put on
a turn of speed.

51
00:05:53,880 --> 00:05:55,919
But she's not the one.

52
00:05:56,000 --> 00:05:57,799
She already has a baby

53
00:05:57,880 --> 00:06:00,839
and she won't mate again
until it leaves her

54
00:06:00,920 --> 00:06:02,639
in about six months' time.

55
00:06:09,880 --> 00:06:14,399
Even life on a paradise island
can have its limitations.

56
00:06:17,760 --> 00:06:19,039
(CALL CONTINUES)

57
00:06:20,080 --> 00:06:23,119
But at least she can't be far away.

58
00:06:28,000 --> 00:06:31,319
The world's entire population
of pygmy sloths

59
00:06:31,400 --> 00:06:36,799
is isolated on a speck of land no bigger
than New York's Central Park.

60
00:06:39,920 --> 00:06:43,079
The size of an island
has a huge influence

61
00:06:43,160 --> 00:06:46,119
on the fate of those cast away there.

62
00:06:51,000 --> 00:06:54,799
The island of Komodo in Indonesia.

63
00:07:05,320 --> 00:07:07,519
Home to dragons.

64
00:07:24,880 --> 00:07:29,159
Ten feet long and weighing
an impressive 150 pounds,

65
00:07:29,880 --> 00:07:34,159
these are the largest living lizards
on the planet.

66
00:07:45,880 --> 00:07:49,199
It's unusual to find large predators
on islands.

67
00:07:52,880 --> 00:07:57,599
Yet, for four million years,
the Komodo dragon has dominated here.

68
00:08:07,760 --> 00:08:09,759
It might seem there wouldn't be
enough food

69
00:08:09,840 --> 00:08:13,319
to support such giants
on this relatively small island,

70
00:08:15,720 --> 00:08:18,199
but reptiles, being cold-blooded,

71
00:08:18,280 --> 00:08:22,519
need only about a tenth of the food
a carnivorous mammal would.

72
00:08:26,840 --> 00:08:30,359
A single meal
will last a dragon a month.

73
00:08:33,560 --> 00:08:37,239
They're so successful,
that their only serious competition

74
00:08:37,320 --> 00:08:39,759
comes from others of their own kind,

75
00:08:40,800 --> 00:08:43,679
and there are some 2,000 of them here.

76
00:09:07,000 --> 00:09:09,839
This giant, however,
isn't looking for food.

77
00:09:10,400 --> 00:09:12,319
He's looking for a mate.

78
00:09:16,360 --> 00:09:19,799
Female dragons come into season
only once a year.

79
00:09:30,320 --> 00:09:31,719
She is receptive.

80
00:09:39,880 --> 00:09:42,079
So far, so good.

81
00:09:46,360 --> 00:09:49,119
But he strayed
into someone else's patch.

82
00:09:54,880 --> 00:09:59,519
Another huge male
thinks he is the king here.

83
00:10:04,040 --> 00:10:08,759
Space being limited on islands,
dragon territories overlap,

84
00:10:09,640 --> 00:10:11,719
and that creates continual conflict.

85
00:10:19,440 --> 00:10:22,759
In dragon society, size is everything.

86
00:10:37,960 --> 00:10:42,719
But if rivals are closely matched,
the outcome can be uncertain.

87
00:10:49,960 --> 00:10:53,399
Muscular tails strike the power
of sledgehammers.

88
00:11:03,480 --> 00:11:07,199
And their serrated teeth
are as sharp as steak knives.

89
00:11:19,080 --> 00:11:21,639
Each tries to topple his opponent.

90
00:11:43,240 --> 00:11:44,239
Defeated.

91
00:11:45,320 --> 00:11:49,359
Only the most powerful dragons
win the right to mate.

92
00:11:49,480 --> 00:11:50,479
(FLY BUZZZZING)

93
00:11:53,080 --> 00:11:54,079
(SNORTING)

94
00:11:58,520 --> 00:12:01,919
The limited food and space
on the small islands

95
00:12:02,000 --> 00:12:04,599
can often lead to intense competition.

96
00:12:06,160 --> 00:12:08,919
But some islands are immense.

97
00:12:10,000 --> 00:12:11,999
More like miniature continents.

98
00:12:13,360 --> 00:12:18,279
And these provide opportunities
for life to experiment and evolve.

99
00:12:23,280 --> 00:12:26,399
Madagascar is one of
the biggest islands

100
00:12:26,480 --> 00:12:28,679
and also one of the oldest,

101
00:12:28,760 --> 00:12:33,319
having split away from Africa over
120 million years ago.

102
00:12:44,560 --> 00:12:47,799
With time and isolation,
its animals have adapted

103
00:12:47,880 --> 00:12:50,919
to take advantage
of every available niche.

104
00:12:57,480 --> 00:13:02,759
The island now has some
250,000 different species,

105
00:13:02,840 --> 00:13:05,439
most found nowhere else on Earth.

106
00:13:17,640 --> 00:13:20,519
These are not monkeys, but lemurs.

107
00:13:26,720 --> 00:13:30,879
From a single ancestor, about a hundred
different types have evolved.

108
00:13:35,920 --> 00:13:40,159
The largest, the Indri,
seldom comes down from the branches.

109
00:13:47,200 --> 00:13:51,639
The much smaller ring-tails
wander in troops across the forest floor

110
00:13:51,720 --> 00:13:52,919
searching for fruit.

111
00:13:54,560 --> 00:13:58,919
And tiny bamboo lemurs eat nothing
except bamboo.

112
00:14:06,600 --> 00:14:08,159
With few competitors,

113
00:14:08,240 --> 00:14:13,039
lemurs have been free to colonise almost
every environment on the island,

114
00:14:15,640 --> 00:14:18,279
even the most extreme.

115
00:14:25,640 --> 00:14:29,879
This baby sifaka
has a hard life ahead of it.

116
00:14:34,640 --> 00:14:37,719
He's been born in the most arid
and hostile corner

117
00:14:37,800 --> 00:14:39,839
of Madagascar's vast landscape.

118
00:14:43,040 --> 00:14:46,399
If he is to survive here,
he has much to learn.

119
00:14:53,760 --> 00:14:56,119
The spiny forest is like a desert.

120
00:14:57,560 --> 00:15:02,439
It rarely rains, so water and food
is very hard to find.

121
00:15:10,560 --> 00:15:13,759
Moving from tree to tree
is a perilous business.

122
00:15:15,760 --> 00:15:19,719
Here, nearly all the plants
are covered with ferocious spines.

123
00:15:21,960 --> 00:15:25,239
His mother searches the treetops
for the youngest leaves.

124
00:15:27,640 --> 00:15:31,359
They provide the only food and water
to sustain the family.

125
00:15:37,800 --> 00:15:41,799
At three months old,
the youngster is starting to explore.

126
00:15:47,400 --> 00:15:50,959
All too soon, he will have to fend
for himself up here.

127
00:15:56,600 --> 00:16:00,919
But it's altogether easier
to stay on Mother's back.

128
00:16:08,680 --> 00:16:12,719
If he can master the strange ways
of this forest,

129
00:16:12,800 --> 00:16:15,999
he will have a little corner
of Madagascar to himself.

130
00:16:22,480 --> 00:16:26,439
Island life encourages animals
to do things differently,

131
00:16:27,520 --> 00:16:30,639
and on some islands, that is essential.

132
00:16:31,560 --> 00:16:32,559
(VIOLENT RUMBLING)

133
00:16:45,360 --> 00:16:47,719
There are islands still forming today

134
00:16:48,640 --> 00:16:50,599
built by volcanoes.

135
00:16:54,280 --> 00:16:56,519
Some erupt explosively,

136
00:17:03,040 --> 00:17:06,039
others pour out rivers of molten rock,

137
00:17:07,160 --> 00:17:08,159
lava.

138
00:17:14,400 --> 00:17:15,919
In the last 50 years,

139
00:17:16,000 --> 00:17:19,119
10 new volcanic islands
have been formed.

140
00:17:46,120 --> 00:17:51,319
Newly created and often remote,
they're hard for colonists to reach.

141
00:17:54,920 --> 00:17:59,119
Even those that do, find these
are tough places to survive.

142
00:18:04,840 --> 00:18:06,959
This is Fernandina,

143
00:18:07,040 --> 00:18:09,479
one of the Galapagos Islands
in the Pacific.

144
00:18:11,880 --> 00:18:16,799
Young and still volcanically active,
it's a desolate place.

145
00:18:30,720 --> 00:18:34,959
The surrounding sea, however,
is particularly rich with life,

146
00:18:39,120 --> 00:18:42,679
and the frontier between these
two very different worlds

147
00:18:42,760 --> 00:18:46,079
is the home of one of the strangest
of reptiles,

148
00:18:50,800 --> 00:18:52,559
sea-going iguanas.

149
00:18:55,480 --> 00:18:57,279
They are vegetarians,

150
00:18:57,360 --> 00:18:59,839
but since there's little food for them
on the land,

151
00:18:59,920 --> 00:19:02,999
marine iguanas graze on the sea floor.

152
00:19:07,160 --> 00:19:10,439
A big male like this one
can dive to 30 metres

153
00:19:10,520 --> 00:19:12,719
and hold his breath for half an hour.

154
00:19:38,680 --> 00:19:43,479
There are more than 7,000 individuals
on Fernandina alone.

155
00:19:51,480 --> 00:19:54,359
And by bringing nutrients from the sea
to the land,

156
00:19:54,440 --> 00:19:57,759
the iguanas help other animals
to survive here, too.

157
00:20:01,680 --> 00:20:04,959
Crabs feed on dead skin
on the iguanas' back

158
00:20:05,040 --> 00:20:09,119
and, in turn, provide
a welcome exfoliation service.

159
00:20:15,920 --> 00:20:16,959
(FLIES BUZZZZING)

160
00:20:17,040 --> 00:20:20,799
While smaller lizards prey on
the flies that pester the colony.

161
00:20:43,200 --> 00:20:47,719
But not all the relationships
on this island are so harmonious.

162
00:20:54,280 --> 00:20:57,159
Marine iguanas lay their eggs in sand.

163
00:20:59,480 --> 00:21:03,439
In June, when the hatchlings emerge,
they're vulnerable.

164
00:21:07,520 --> 00:21:10,839
They must join the adults
at the edge of the sea.

165
00:21:10,920 --> 00:21:13,319
But the journey will be a dangerous one.

166
00:21:38,520 --> 00:21:40,039
Racer snakes.

167
00:22:09,640 --> 00:22:11,839
The snakes missed their chance.

168
00:22:20,040 --> 00:22:22,199
But more babies are hatching.

169
00:22:27,720 --> 00:22:31,519
And now the snakes are on the alert.

170
00:22:31,600 --> 00:22:35,999
This is the best feeding opportunity
they will get all year.

171
00:22:51,480 --> 00:22:56,159
On flat ground a baby iguana
can outrun a racer snake.

172
00:22:57,680 --> 00:22:59,879
But others are waiting in ambush.

173
00:23:27,640 --> 00:23:32,519
Another hatchling has its first glimpse
of a dangerous world.

174
00:24:29,960 --> 00:24:34,959
A snake's eyes aren't very good,
but they can detect movement.

175
00:24:37,000 --> 00:24:41,199
So if the hatchling keeps its nerve,
it may just avoid detection.

176
00:26:13,280 --> 00:26:15,559
A near miraculous escape.

177
00:26:22,360 --> 00:26:23,599
The lucky survivors

178
00:26:23,680 --> 00:26:26,519
can begin learning
the unique way of life

179
00:26:26,600 --> 00:26:29,159
demanded by this hostile island.

180
00:26:37,560 --> 00:26:41,079
Although marine iguanas
are expert swimmers,

181
00:26:41,160 --> 00:26:43,359
they can't cross open oceans.

182
00:26:51,960 --> 00:26:53,959
But even the stormiest waters

183
00:26:54,080 --> 00:26:56,599
are no barrier for birds.

184
00:27:06,080 --> 00:27:09,039
Gale force winds and cold temperatures

185
00:27:09,120 --> 00:27:12,279
make the subantarctic islands
off New Zealand

186
00:27:12,360 --> 00:27:15,239
particularly unwelcoming in winter.

187
00:27:27,840 --> 00:27:33,639
But when the brief summer comes,
temperatures rise and winds slacken.

188
00:27:48,800 --> 00:27:52,039
It's now that visitors arrive.

189
00:27:54,760 --> 00:27:58,479
All here to breed before winter returns.

190
00:28:00,880 --> 00:28:02,679
There's the Snares penguins.

191
00:28:11,120 --> 00:28:12,999
Shearwaters come, too.

192
00:28:15,920 --> 00:28:19,719
This is an excellent place for them
to dig their nesting burrows,

193
00:28:19,800 --> 00:28:22,399
for no predators
have managed to get here.

194
00:28:28,440 --> 00:28:31,879
Soon the island is crowded with birds.

195
00:28:33,400 --> 00:28:37,359
Every one of them eager to make
the most of the short breeding season.

196
00:28:41,440 --> 00:28:44,199
But not everyone has a partner.

197
00:28:50,480 --> 00:28:53,999
A male Buller's albatross
waits for his mate.

198
00:28:57,040 --> 00:29:01,719
Each year they spend six months apart,
travelling the ocean.

199
00:29:06,680 --> 00:29:09,319
They reunite here to breed.

200
00:29:12,240 --> 00:29:14,599
But this year, she's late.

201
00:29:18,200 --> 00:29:20,199
No, that's not her.

202
00:29:24,560 --> 00:29:26,839
The other birds come and go.

203
00:29:36,800 --> 00:29:38,519
The clock is ticking.

204
00:29:39,800 --> 00:29:44,639
If she doesn't appear soon, it will be
too late for them to breed successfully.

205
00:29:47,360 --> 00:29:51,599
Every morning the shearwaters fly off
to collect food for their young.

206
00:29:52,040 --> 00:29:53,039
(HOOTING)

207
00:29:54,360 --> 00:29:55,839
(CHIRPING)

208
00:30:09,480 --> 00:30:12,599
Everybody else seems
to be getting on with it.

209
00:30:25,040 --> 00:30:29,559
The shearwaters' return
marks another lost day.

210
00:30:31,600 --> 00:30:34,479
There are three million birds
on the island,

211
00:30:34,560 --> 00:30:36,919
but only one matters to him.

212
00:30:44,920 --> 00:30:46,079
Could this be her?

213
00:30:52,280 --> 00:30:53,399
At last.

214
00:31:04,440 --> 00:31:05,799
(SQUAWKING)

215
00:31:07,960 --> 00:31:10,319
At first, he's a little coy.

216
00:31:11,480 --> 00:31:13,639
(SQUAWKING)

217
00:31:24,520 --> 00:31:26,159
But not for long.

218
00:31:33,200 --> 00:31:35,759
They greet each other
with the special dance

219
00:31:35,840 --> 00:31:38,559
they've perfected over many years.

220
00:31:49,680 --> 00:31:55,239
There is much to do, if they're to raise
a chick before winter returns.

221
00:31:59,880 --> 00:32:02,599
But when you've been apart
for six months,

222
00:32:02,680 --> 00:32:04,999
some things can't be rushed.

223
00:32:23,680 --> 00:32:29,879
Islands in warm tropical waters
don't experience seasonal extremes.

224
00:32:32,840 --> 00:32:35,959
The Seychelles, lying off
the coast of East Africa,

225
00:32:36,040 --> 00:32:39,119
provide a sanctuary
for seabirds all the year round.

226
00:32:40,880 --> 00:32:42,839
(BIRDS CHIRPING AND SCREECHING)

227
00:32:55,720 --> 00:32:58,279
Fairy terns are permanent residents.

228
00:32:59,800 --> 00:33:04,919
They take a fairly relaxed view
about what constitutes a nest.

229
00:33:06,280 --> 00:33:08,599
A bare branch is quite enough.

230
00:33:17,320 --> 00:33:22,199
Climbing onto it to incubate
has to be done with care.

231
00:33:30,560 --> 00:33:33,239
Once a year, the noddies arrive.

232
00:33:34,800 --> 00:33:37,839
They do make nests, and Pisonia trees

233
00:33:37,920 --> 00:33:41,959
provide their young with a rather
less precarious start in life.

234
00:33:48,880 --> 00:33:51,479
Nesting on this island looks idyllic,

235
00:33:52,840 --> 00:33:56,999
but behind the beauty
there's a sinister side.

236
00:34:01,320 --> 00:34:06,399
The Seychelles fody makes quick work
of an unattended egg.

237
00:34:21,480 --> 00:34:23,359
She knows something's not quite right,

238
00:34:23,440 --> 00:34:26,879
but her drive to incubate is strong.

239
00:34:41,440 --> 00:34:43,639
The noddies, too, have a problem.

240
00:34:47,560 --> 00:34:49,359
As their chicks grow,

241
00:34:49,440 --> 00:34:53,439
so the Pisonia tree
develops seeds that are sticky

242
00:34:53,520 --> 00:34:55,159
and equipped with hooks.

243
00:35:00,560 --> 00:35:02,719
By the time the young noddies leave

244
00:35:02,800 --> 00:35:06,879
they carry these hitchhiking seeds
away to other islands.

245
00:35:13,440 --> 00:35:17,679
But sometimes the Pisonia trees
are too successful.

246
00:35:23,240 --> 00:35:27,039
If a fledgling testing out its wings
drops to the ground,

247
00:35:27,120 --> 00:35:29,799
it can get covered with the seeds.

248
00:35:38,200 --> 00:35:40,479
Entangled and weighed down,

249
00:35:41,120 --> 00:35:44,759
if it can't free itself,
the youngster will starve.

250
00:35:58,200 --> 00:36:03,079
The Pisonia may have failed
to disperse these seeds,

251
00:36:03,520 --> 00:36:07,919
but it will soon have fertiliser
for its roots.

252
00:36:13,720 --> 00:36:19,559
This is why some people call
the Pisonia the "bird catcher tree".

253
00:36:22,320 --> 00:36:23,959
(SQUAWKING)

254
00:36:52,600 --> 00:36:55,559
The Fairy tern laid another egg,

255
00:36:55,640 --> 00:36:58,559
and now she has a tiny chick to feed.

256
00:37:05,200 --> 00:37:06,679
This chick is lucky.

257
00:37:09,480 --> 00:37:13,439
By the time it fledges,
the Pisonia seeds will have dispersed

258
00:37:13,520 --> 00:37:15,919
and the danger
they brought will be gone.

259
00:37:27,120 --> 00:37:30,239
Even the most idyllic looking of islands

260
00:37:30,320 --> 00:37:33,999
presents challenges
for the animals living there.

261
00:37:34,080 --> 00:37:38,159
But the greatest threat they face
is change.

262
00:37:54,440 --> 00:37:57,159
Christmas Island in the Indian Ocean.

263
00:37:58,600 --> 00:38:04,399
For millions of years this remote
spec of land has been ruled by crabs.

264
00:38:10,480 --> 00:38:13,439
Their ancestors came from the sea,

265
00:38:13,520 --> 00:38:17,599
but most have now adopted
a land-based existence.

266
00:38:26,680 --> 00:38:30,999
Given there are so many of them,
they get along relatively harmoniously.

267
00:38:33,560 --> 00:38:39,359
They're the gardeners and caretakers
of a tiny crab utopia.

268
00:38:43,040 --> 00:38:46,679
Once a year, they must all return
to the sea to breed,

269
00:38:46,760 --> 00:38:48,959
and the march of the red crabs

270
00:38:49,040 --> 00:38:52,919
is one of the greatest
natural spectacles on Earth.

271
00:39:04,440 --> 00:39:06,799
There are 50 million of them.

272
00:39:13,640 --> 00:39:18,119
It's an event that has brought
the island worldwide fame.

273
00:39:28,720 --> 00:39:30,399
But in recent years,

274
00:39:30,480 --> 00:39:34,519
millions of red crabs
haven't managed to reach the sea.

275
00:39:40,440 --> 00:39:43,439
An invader has occupied this island.

276
00:39:46,440 --> 00:39:48,559
Yellow crazy ants.

277
00:39:49,640 --> 00:39:52,839
They escape from visiting ships,
and with no predators

278
00:39:52,920 --> 00:39:55,559
to control them,
they have now created vast

279
00:39:55,640 --> 00:39:58,039
super colonies in the forest.

280
00:40:03,960 --> 00:40:06,999
When migrating
red crabs march into their territory,

281
00:40:07,080 --> 00:40:08,599
the ants attack,

282
00:40:10,240 --> 00:40:13,999
squirting acid
into the crabs' eyes and mouths.

283
00:40:23,880 --> 00:40:26,079
The crabs have no defence.

284
00:40:29,920 --> 00:40:33,999
Blinded and confused, they're doomed.

285
00:40:45,320 --> 00:40:48,719
Humans brought these ant invaders here

286
00:40:48,800 --> 00:40:51,679
and now humans are having
to control them.

287
00:40:55,200 --> 00:41:00,799
Isolated communities may evolve
for millions of years in relative peace,

288
00:41:02,240 --> 00:41:06,599
but when new challenges arrive,
they can struggle to cope.

289
00:41:09,000 --> 00:41:13,519
Of all the species that have become
extinct in recent years,

290
00:41:13,600 --> 00:41:16,999
around 80% have been islanders.

291
00:41:20,600 --> 00:41:25,399
Our impact on the Earth is greater today
than ever before.

292
00:41:26,440 --> 00:41:28,759
Yet some islands are so remote,

293
00:41:28,840 --> 00:41:31,879
that few humans have even set foot
on them.

294
00:41:35,200 --> 00:41:37,919
Zavodovski Island is one.

295
00:41:41,520 --> 00:41:44,279
It lies in the great Southern Ocean.

296
00:41:44,360 --> 00:41:47,639
It's not only surrounded
by the stormiest of seas,

297
00:41:47,720 --> 00:41:50,599
it is itself an active volcano.

298
00:41:53,200 --> 00:41:56,639
It's the last place on Earth
you'd choose to live.

299
00:42:05,680 --> 00:42:08,639
Unless, you're a chinstrap penguin.

300
00:42:11,160 --> 00:42:14,479
There's plenty of food in these waters,
but to exploit it,

301
00:42:14,560 --> 00:42:17,159
the penguins have to risk their lives.

302
00:43:05,880 --> 00:43:09,639
Life here is dangerous in the extreme.

303
00:43:22,800 --> 00:43:23,839
(PENGUINS CHATTERING)

304
00:43:26,720 --> 00:43:30,239
But there are some benefits from living
on a volcano.

305
00:43:32,720 --> 00:43:36,079
Its warmth melts the snow
early in the year

306
00:43:36,960 --> 00:43:40,319
and byJanuary,
the Antarctic's mid-summer,

307
00:43:40,400 --> 00:43:42,839
the island is covered in chicks.

308
00:43:42,920 --> 00:43:43,919
(CHIRPING)

309
00:43:47,160 --> 00:43:50,239
Parents take turns at guarding them

310
00:43:50,320 --> 00:43:52,599
until they're large enough
to be left alone.

311
00:43:57,480 --> 00:44:02,439
This mother's chicks are hungry,
but she has no food left to give them.

312
00:44:04,320 --> 00:44:08,439
Their survival depends on their father
returning with their next meal.

313
00:44:12,800 --> 00:44:14,519
But some don't make it.

314
00:44:28,640 --> 00:44:32,559
Skuas harass the colony
hoping to snatch a chick.

315
00:44:32,640 --> 00:44:33,719
(SKUA HONKING)

316
00:44:40,440 --> 00:44:42,319
She can't risk leaving them.

317
00:44:47,160 --> 00:44:51,079
Everything will be fine
as long as their father comes back soon.

318
00:45:20,440 --> 00:45:23,599
He's been fishing 50 miles offshore,

319
00:45:23,680 --> 00:45:25,679
but now, he's not far away.

320
00:45:28,400 --> 00:45:31,799
For him, however,
and for all the other parents here,

321
00:45:31,880 --> 00:45:34,519
the worst of the journey
is still to come.

322
00:46:06,400 --> 00:46:10,879
Tiny claws help him to get
whatever grip he can on the rough lava.

323
00:46:38,640 --> 00:46:41,599
For these commuters, it's rush hour.

324
00:46:43,160 --> 00:46:45,919
Some have had a really bad day.

325
00:46:50,160 --> 00:46:54,279
The father now has
a two mile walk to the nest,

326
00:46:54,360 --> 00:46:56,879
and a stomach loaded with food
doesn't help.

327
00:47:03,960 --> 00:47:07,839
This is the largest penguin colony
in the world.

328
00:47:07,920 --> 00:47:09,879
(PENGUINS CHATTERING)

329
00:47:14,640 --> 00:47:17,999
But as he makes the same journey
every other day,

330
00:47:18,080 --> 00:47:21,079
he should be able to do it
with his eyes closed.

331
00:47:29,640 --> 00:47:32,759
It's true that there can be safety
in numbers,

332
00:47:32,840 --> 00:47:35,439
but numbers can also be something
of a problem

333
00:47:35,520 --> 00:47:37,679
when you're trying to find
your own nest.

334
00:47:44,240 --> 00:47:46,119
The mother is still waiting.

335
00:47:48,240 --> 00:47:50,319
Her chicks are now desperate.

336
00:47:50,400 --> 00:47:51,399
(CHICKS CHIRPING)

337
00:47:56,160 --> 00:47:58,759
In the midst of all this
deafening chorus,

338
00:47:58,840 --> 00:48:01,319
he can recognise her particular cry.

339
00:48:01,400 --> 00:48:02,399
(CRYING OUT)

340
00:48:20,920 --> 00:48:22,039
At last.

341
00:48:37,520 --> 00:48:39,599
Both chicks will get a meal.

342
00:48:46,840 --> 00:48:51,479
With a head bob of acknowledgement,
their mother now leaves.

343
00:48:51,560 --> 00:48:54,759
It's her turn to do the feeding run.

344
00:49:01,160 --> 00:49:07,359
This formidable commute is the price
these penguins pay for sanctuary.

345
00:49:13,680 --> 00:49:17,119
A strange vision of paradise to us,
perhaps,

346
00:49:17,200 --> 00:49:20,599
but for one and a half million penguins,

347
00:49:20,680 --> 00:49:22,799
this island has it all.

348
00:49:33,560 --> 00:49:37,479
Islands may seem remote
and insignificant,

349
00:49:37,560 --> 00:49:41,719
but they are home to some of the most
precious wildlife on Earth.

350
00:50:05,120 --> 00:50:08,119
The expedition to film on the island
of Zavodovski

351
00:50:08,200 --> 00:50:10,799
was the most intrepid shoot
of the series.

352
00:50:11,760 --> 00:50:13,399
To ensure its success,

353
00:50:13,480 --> 00:50:17,479
the team have called in
Antarctic expert Jerome Poncet,

354
00:50:17,560 --> 00:50:20,559
one of the few people to have set foot
on the island.

355
00:50:23,080 --> 00:50:26,559
This whole region of Antarctica
is rarely visited.

356
00:50:30,720 --> 00:50:33,399
And this is the planet's roughest ocean.

357
00:50:42,480 --> 00:50:45,039
After seven long days and nights at sea,

358
00:50:45,120 --> 00:50:48,119
they get their first glimpse
of their final destination.

359
00:50:48,800 --> 00:50:50,959
It's actually quite surreal
after a whole year

360
00:50:51,040 --> 00:50:52,519
of trying to
put the expedition together,

361
00:50:52,600 --> 00:50:55,039
and then today we wake up
and there's the volcano.

362
00:50:55,120 --> 00:50:56,239
That's Zavodovski.

363
00:50:57,960 --> 00:51:00,639
ATTENBOROUGH:
The explorers who discovered this place

364
00:51:00,720 --> 00:51:04,799
spoke of the stench of sulphurous gases,

365
00:51:04,880 --> 00:51:09,559
treacherous waters
and astonishing numbers of penguins.

366
00:51:13,000 --> 00:51:15,319
It seems not much has changed.

367
00:51:16,680 --> 00:51:18,199
The drone's been around the whole place

368
00:51:18,280 --> 00:51:21,599
and there, literally, is only
one safe area to get on,

369
00:51:21,680 --> 00:51:24,359
and he's telling us
it's that rock face over there.

370
00:51:27,200 --> 00:51:30,279
ATTENBOROUGH: The team must take
everything they need to survive.

371
00:51:31,200 --> 00:51:32,199
MAN: Here are penguins.

372
00:51:35,040 --> 00:51:36,719
ATTENBOROUGH:
Though the boat will stay nearby,

373
00:51:36,800 --> 00:51:38,559
they will need to be self-sufficient.

374
00:51:39,880 --> 00:51:43,519
But that means taking a ton
of equipment up this cliff.

375
00:51:44,520 --> 00:51:46,279
MAN: Just get that lot to help.

376
00:51:46,360 --> 00:51:47,999
Many flippers make light work.

377
00:51:50,680 --> 00:51:53,439
ATTENBOROUGH: They work all day
getting the gear ashore,

378
00:51:56,120 --> 00:51:59,079
but the fact that there are
so many penguins on the island

379
00:51:59,160 --> 00:52:00,399
doesn't make it easy.

380
00:52:01,760 --> 00:52:04,839
Yeah, the hardest thing for us
has been finding a pathway through,

381
00:52:04,920 --> 00:52:07,719
as there's absolutely penguins
everywhere you look.

382
00:52:15,080 --> 00:52:17,319
ATTENBOROUGH:
Finally, it's time to make camp.

383
00:52:22,320 --> 00:52:25,999
They choose a sheltered place
that won't disturb the locals.

384
00:52:27,480 --> 00:52:31,239
But since most of the penguins
won't have seen a human being before,

385
00:52:31,320 --> 00:52:33,519
they seem keen to pop over and visit.

386
00:52:33,600 --> 00:52:34,599
(PENGUINS CHATTERING)

387
00:52:36,040 --> 00:52:37,239
ELIZABETH WHITE: Nosy neighbours.

388
00:52:39,720 --> 00:52:41,399
ATTENBOROUGH:
The team set off to start documenting

389
00:52:41,480 --> 00:52:43,759
the daily lives of the penguins,

390
00:52:43,840 --> 00:52:46,199
and what they find is astonishing.

391
00:52:47,200 --> 00:52:49,079
As soon as you walk over that ridge,

392
00:52:49,160 --> 00:52:52,479
you so get the tingly feeling
because I've never seen

393
00:52:52,560 --> 00:52:54,479
that many animals in one spot.

394
00:52:55,160 --> 00:52:56,239
It's just mind-blowing.

395
00:52:59,040 --> 00:53:01,919
Just like Glastonbury Festival,

396
00:53:02,000 --> 00:53:03,479
the whole landscape was full of

397
00:53:03,560 --> 00:53:06,319
little black and white penguins
waddling around.

398
00:53:10,920 --> 00:53:14,079
This is penguin paradise
and that's what we've got to show.

399
00:53:18,800 --> 00:53:20,119
ATTENBOROUGH: A promising start,

400
00:53:21,720 --> 00:53:25,079
but, here, fortunes can change quickly.

401
00:53:29,000 --> 00:53:30,479
MAN: # Summertime... #

402
00:53:34,000 --> 00:53:36,519
- Every season within 1 0 minutes.
- WHITE: Mmm.

403
00:53:39,960 --> 00:53:43,799
ATTENBOROUGH: As the snowmelts
it creates an unforeseen problem.

404
00:53:46,000 --> 00:53:48,839
We've purposely changed the campsite
because it was a place

405
00:53:48,920 --> 00:53:50,959
where the penguins didn't seem to go.

406
00:53:51,040 --> 00:53:53,599
I think we've realised why the penguins
don't nest here,

407
00:53:53,680 --> 00:53:56,519
it's because of the spray
and because of some run-off,

408
00:53:56,600 --> 00:53:58,559
so we are literally in a bit of a bog.

409
00:54:00,680 --> 00:54:02,999
ATTENBOROUGH: And it's not just mud.

410
00:54:04,760 --> 00:54:06,879
MAN: Couple of these guys,
as they wander down

411
00:54:06,960 --> 00:54:08,599
to do a spot of fishing,

412
00:54:08,680 --> 00:54:11,919
they tend to use my tent as
a little, uh, poop spot.

413
00:54:13,160 --> 00:54:15,839
You kinda get used to it at night
just hearing a constant

414
00:54:15,920 --> 00:54:17,519
splat on top of the tent.

415
00:54:18,160 --> 00:54:20,399
But, as you can see, all of the kit,

416
00:54:20,480 --> 00:54:24,519
I'm afraid that's, uh,
getting splat on as well. (CHUCKLES)

417
00:54:24,920 --> 00:54:28,719
ATTENBOROUGH: And when the wind changes,
it brings a noxious reminder

418
00:54:28,800 --> 00:54:31,319
that they are camping on
an active volcano.

419
00:54:33,720 --> 00:54:36,119
It's the first time
we've smelt sulphur which is

420
00:54:36,200 --> 00:54:38,599
a welcome relief from smelling penguins.

421
00:54:39,520 --> 00:54:40,879
It's smoking away.

422
00:54:42,480 --> 00:54:45,439
(CHUCKLES) And I think if they
start running for the sea

423
00:54:45,520 --> 00:54:47,759
we're gonna be calling Jerome
pretty quick with the boat.

424
00:54:50,960 --> 00:54:53,079
ATTENBOROUGH:
Each day filming on Zavodovski

425
00:54:53,160 --> 00:54:55,239
seems to present a new challenge.

426
00:54:59,520 --> 00:55:02,519
Next, a huge storm hits the island.

427
00:55:05,320 --> 00:55:10,519
Only now do the team realise just
how tough life can be for the penguins.

428
00:55:14,240 --> 00:55:19,039
It's hard not to be moved by the effort
they go to to feed their chicks.

429
00:55:21,360 --> 00:55:23,639
These huge waves are coming in.

430
00:55:23,720 --> 00:55:27,719
The penguins are surfing it,
getting battered on these big boulders,

431
00:55:27,800 --> 00:55:30,919
and now and again you just get a penguin
that gets catapulted

432
00:55:31,000 --> 00:55:33,719
15 metres in the air,
it's totally ludicrous.

433
00:55:35,960 --> 00:55:39,239
I really think there are, uh,
quite few penguins getting killed in it.

434
00:55:44,960 --> 00:55:49,279
The beach in the afternoon was just
a scene of death and destruction.

435
00:55:51,120 --> 00:55:52,879
It was absolute carnage.

436
00:55:55,160 --> 00:55:56,399
It's kind of heartbreaking,

437
00:55:56,480 --> 00:55:58,079
I mean, they're trying so hard
to get up the beach

438
00:55:58,160 --> 00:56:00,599
with broken legs and bleeding and...

439
00:56:01,600 --> 00:56:04,159
Very, you know, sobering, really.

440
00:56:07,600 --> 00:56:11,239
ATTENBOROUGH: After witnessing
the struggles the penguins must endure,

441
00:56:11,320 --> 00:56:13,399
the team now face the same problem,

442
00:56:14,720 --> 00:56:16,199
getting off the island.

443
00:56:17,440 --> 00:56:19,279
With another storm coming in,

444
00:56:19,760 --> 00:56:21,599
they decide to take their chance.

445
00:56:23,480 --> 00:56:27,359
Jerome has seconds to get in and out
between the waves.

446
00:56:28,480 --> 00:56:30,039
Or the Zodiac could tip,

447
00:56:31,200 --> 00:56:32,679
leaving them all stranded.

448
00:56:33,880 --> 00:56:36,279
WHITE: Hey, that's the first box
off the island.

449
00:56:42,000 --> 00:56:43,559
ATTENBOROUGH:
What took a day to get ashore

450
00:56:43,640 --> 00:56:47,479
must be off in minutes.
And the swell is getting bigger.

451
00:56:49,360 --> 00:56:51,999
Their window of opportunity is closing.

452
00:56:53,400 --> 00:56:55,399
MAN: Hey, look at the swell.
Now watch out, watch out.

453
00:57:02,080 --> 00:57:05,439
ATTENBOROUGH: The equipment's off,
but now the team has to follow.

454
00:57:10,360 --> 00:57:12,239
MAN: So she's just leaving us now,
is she?

455
00:57:12,480 --> 00:57:15,119
That's the producer, she's gone.
We have to swim now.

456
00:57:20,200 --> 00:57:22,319
ATTENBOROUGH:
Luckily, it didn't come to that.

457
00:57:27,120 --> 00:57:31,519
Safely aboard, they leave with
an unforgettable experience

458
00:57:31,600 --> 00:57:34,119
of how hard life is

459
00:57:34,200 --> 00:57:36,719
on an island at the edge of the world.

460
00:57:36,800 --> 00:57:38,319
(PENGUINS CHATTERING)

461
00:57:41,240 --> 00:57:42,439
Next time,

462
00:57:42,520 --> 00:57:44,479
we ascend
into the planet's highest peaks

463
00:57:46,160 --> 00:57:49,279
to discover a spectacular
but hostile world

464
00:57:49,960 --> 00:57:52,799
where only the toughest animals
can endure.

465
00:57:53,840 --> 00:57:55,199
(GROWLING AND SNARLING)

466
00:57:55,480 --> 00:57:57,999
This is life on the roof of the world,

467
00:57:58,080 --> 00:57:59,839
mountains.

