(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
DAVID ATTENBOROUGH:
One quarter of all the land on Earth
is covered by a single,
remarkable type of plant.
Almost indestructible,
it can grow two feet in a day...
And be tall enough to hide a giant.
(GRUNTING)
That plant is grass,
and the world it creates
is truly unique.
The grass in northern India
is the tallest on the planet,
home to some of the most
impressive creatures to tread the Earth.
(GRUNTS)
(TRUMPETS)
These are the good times,
but in just a few months,
all this fresh growth will be gone,
and the animals
will be forced to move on.
That is the way things are
on grasslands across the planet.
A cycle of abundance,
destruction and rebirth
that affects every creature
that lives here.
(ELEPHANTS GRUNTING)
The largest grassland on Earth,
the vast Eurasian Steppe,
stretches one third of the way
around our planet.
Spring rain has brought fresh grass,
and with it, new life.
A relic from the Ice Age,
a baby Saiga antelope,
just three hours old.
His only company, his twin.
Until they can stand, their mother
has left them hidden in the grass.
They should be safe,
as long as they remain quiet.
(CALLS)
For these calves,
the clock is already ticking.
Their herd will soon be moving on,
seeking the freshest new grass.
(CALLS)
Their lanky legs are a sure sign that
they're built for a life on the move.
Saiga always give birth to twins,
so their numbers grow rapidly
just when grass is plentiful.
Their bizarrely shaped nose
can detect fresh growth
from hundreds of miles away.
(SAIGAS BAWLING)
The young twins will now
begin the nomadic life
they share with most animals
on the world's open plains.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Grasslands occur where rain is
too sporadic for forests to exist.
The rain that a grassland
needs to survive for a year
might arrive all at once.
(LIGHTNING CRACKS)
Storms like these can release
12 inches of rain in 24 hours.
(HEAVY RAINFALL)
Not much fun if you're out in it.
Eventually the earth
can't soak up any more,
(THUNDER CRACKING)
and the grassland undergoes
a radical change.
(WATER FLOWING)
Many plants would drown here,
but grasses thrive.
They grow so fast,
their leaves quickly rise above
the water and into the sunlight.
Here in southern Africa,
water transforms one of the most
remarkable grasslands on Earth,
the Okavango.
Every year, 5,000 square miles
of grassland are flooded.
For one pride of lions,
this poses a major problem.
There may be plenty of prey around,
but lions struggle
to run it down in water.
The pride has three-month-old cubs.
They've never seen water before.
(CUBS MEOWING)
If their mothers
don't make a kill soon,
the cubs might not survive the week.
(YOWLS)
But fuelled by the flood, the eruption
of grass attracts new possible prey.
Buffalo arrive in herds 2,000 strong.
(GRUNTS)
Powerful, aggressive and united,
they're the most dangerous animal
a lion can face.
(BUFFALO GRUNTS)
The biggest bulls don't run.
They're simply too huge
to be scared of lions.
At 900 kilos, he weighs more
than all five lionesses combined.
The pride do have numbers on their side,
but one sweep of his horns
could be deadly.
One distracts the bull up front,
while her sisters attack from behind.
The cats must somehow
topple the buffalo,
but with swamp under foot,
they can't get any traction.
The bull is weakening,
but the lions are tiring, too.
It's now a battle of will
as much as strength.
To live, the bull must somehow
shake off the lioness.
(DRAMATIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
The bull is wounded,
but thanks to his two-inch-thick hide,
he will recover.
For the pride, these are hungry times.
(CUB WHIMPERS)
But, ultimately, once the water recedes,
there will be new life,
and new food to benefit all.
In the right conditions,
grasses have the extraordinary ability
to grow from first shoots to flower
in a matter of only days.
Grasses become the miniature equivalents
of fruiting trees.
(CRICKET CHIRPS)
And for creatures living
within the grass,
this is a landscape as vast
and towering as any rainforest.
And excellent place
to build a tiny tree house
for a harvest mouse.
(SQUEAKS)
During summer,
European meadowlands are full of food,
but only for those that can reach it.
(STEM CRACKS)
Climbing grass is harder
than climbing trees,
not least because their stems
just won't stay still.
Her prehensile tail
acts like a fifth limb,
so she's as agile as a monkey
clambering around in a tree.
(STEM CREAKS)
And just as well,
for the best food in this tiny forest
is at the very top of its canopy.
Feeding up here, she's exposed.
A barn owl.
Not her finest move...
But it did the trick.
Harvest mice seldom go
all the way down to the ground.
It's a tangled and
dangerous world down here.
(INSECTS CHITTERING)
But she can read the pattern
of the stems overhead like a map,
and so find her way home.
And not a minute too soon.
There are mouths to feed.
(SNIFFS)
Her babies must fatten up quickly.
They need to harvest the summer grasses
while they're still rich with food.
On the African savannah, too,
seasonal grasses are filled with life,
but it won't last long.
Carmine bee-eaters
are superb aerial hunters,
experts at catching insects in midair.
But they have no way of
flushing their prey out of the grass.
(INSECTS CHITTERING)
Once alarmed, most insects stay put.
The bee-eaters need someone
to stir things up a bit.
(CALLS)
A kori bustard.
It's the world's heaviest flying bird,
so it should be bulky enough
to kick up some insects.
(INSECT BUZZING)
Bingo!
Until someone else comes along
and cramps your style.
(CHIRPS)
Never mind, perhaps there are
bigger opportunities ahead.
What about an ostrich?
The heaviest bird of all.
This time there's more than enough
transport to go around.
(SQUAWKING)
Soon, almost every ostrich
has its own passenger.
But free riders are only
tolerated for so long.
What the bee-eaters really need
is a creature so big
it won't even notice them.
(GRUNTING)
Nothing cuts a swathe through grass
like an African bull elephant.
The trick is to fly as close to
the front of the giant as possible.
They only have a split second
to grab the prize.
As more insects are stirred up,
the competition intensifies.
(FRENZIED CHIRPING)
With summer drawing to a close,
the race to stock up is on.
Soon, the grass will wither,
and this opportunity will have gone.
As the dry season takes hold,
food becomes increasingly thin
on the ground.
Now, only the most specialised predators
on the plains can make a living.
She may be spotted like a cheetah,
but this cat is no sprinter.
Instead, she has extra-long legs
which give her a high vantage point.
But a serval cat's main weapon
are enormous radar ears.
(GRASS RUSTLING)
They help her pinpoint prey
hiding in the grass.
But the prey she seeks are canny.
Southern vlei rats.
They know that any sustained movement
can give them away.
So they move in short bursts.
(RUSTLING)
But even the slightest rustle
will give her a clue.
(RUSTLING)
Warm.
(RUSTLES)
Warmer.
Missed.
(RUSTLING)
(ANIMAL CALLS)
(SQUEAKS)
In better times,
she could catch 10 a day,
but now, with so few rodents around,
she will have to go hungry.
As drought intensifies,
life gets tougher for all.
Predators with permanent territories
must tough it out,
while most of their prey
disappear over the horizon.
(GRUNTING)
To avoid starvation, many grassland
animals follow a nomadic way of life.
Over 2,000,000 wildebeests wander
the East African savannahs
chasing the rains.
And they are not alone.
Arriving on the wing,
Jackson's Widowbirds
also seek fresh grass.
(CHIRPING)
Although, it's not just
food that they're after.
(CHIRPS)
This male wants a mate.
He's grown elaborate breeding plumage
for this moment,
but he needs a stage
on which to show it off.
By carefully selecting grass blades,
each trimmed to the correct length,
he's creating something very special.
He needs an even surface,
and a centre-piece.
The stage is set.
His bachelor pad is sufficiently
neat and tidy to attract a female.
The problem is,
can she see it?
(CHIRPS)
He has competition.
(CHIRPING LOUDER)
It might take more than a little
gardening to impress the ladies.
Jumping is the right idea,
but he's misjudged
the height of the grass.
His rival makes it look easy.
Time to raise his game.
(BOTH CHIRPING)
It's not only who jumps the highest,
but who can keep doing so the longest.
Unable to go the distance,
his rivals drop out one by one.
Stamina has won him admirers,
now he can show off
his courtship arena...
And engage in a little
romantic hide-and-seek.
Finally, he's done enough.
The East African savannahs
support millions of grazers.
(GRUNTING)
Each year they devour
millions of tons of grass,
and yet there's one creature here
whose impact is far greater
than all these animals combined.
They're found wherever
grass grows on the planet,
yet their labours go
almost entirely unnoticed.
One of the most remarkable is found here
on the grasslands of South America.
These blades are so tough that virtually
no large grass eaters can stomach them.
Yet they're harvested
on an industrial scale...
(CRACKING)
...by tiny grass cutter ants.
But they themselves
can't digest one bit of it.
So, why bother?
The answer is underground,
and it's very ingenious.
Each blade is cut to length
and placed into a garden of fungus.
The rotting grass feeds the fungus,
and in turn the fungus feeds the ants.
But feeding 5,000,000 workers
requires intensive agriculture.
Luckily, they are an industrious lot.
This colony alone will collect
over half a ton of grass every year.
With billions of ant colonies
across the world's grasslands
all doing exactly the same thing,
that's a mind-boggling amount of grass.
It's estimated that over one third
of the grass that grows on Earth
will be harvested by an insect.
In northern Australia, termites
memorialise their industry in sculpture.
These astonishing mounds
are 10 feet tall.
They're always built
on a north-south axis,
which is why their builders
are called compass termites.
These castles of clay
protect their builders
from extremes of heat
and seasonal floods
experienced on many grasslands.
Termites manage to do
what most grass eaters can't,
break down dead grass
and extract the nutrients.
But they themselves can be food
for those that can reach them.
(SUCKING NOISE)
A two-foot-long tongue
covered in microscopic hooks,
followed by claws longer
than those of a velociraptor.
(SNIFFING)
A giant anteater
on the plains of South America.
(SLURPING)
It can devour 20,000 insects a day.
Powerful forelegs enable it to rip apart
a termite hill with ease.
And as the sun bakes the grass,
the termites face new danger.
(FIRE CRACKLES)
In minutes, fire turns grassland to ash.
But the grasses are not dead.
Their underground stems are unharmed.
Weeks, months may pass,
but eventually the rains will return
and the grass will sprout again.
Some grasslands must endure
not only fire, but ice.
As winter approaches, the prairies
of North America begin to freeze.
(CRACKING)
(LOW GROWLING)
In summer, bison roamed freely,
almost continuously cropping
the abundant green grass.
Now, that grass is not only withered
and frozen, it's about to be buried.
Sixty million tons of snow
now blanket this herd's territory.
(SNORTING)
Pushing through deep snow
is exhausting work,
and the bison are now slowly starving.
Just keeping warm
saps huge amounts of energy.
(GROWLS)
Their thick coats can insulate them
down to minus 20 Fahrenheit.
It's now minus 40.
The only thing that will keep them alive
is buried beneath three feet of snow.
And that's a problem shared
with a surprising neighbour.
The food the fox seeks
is also deep beneath the snow.
(GRUNTING)
The survival of both creatures depends
on getting through to the ground.
For the bison, it will be
a matter of brute strength.
Massive neck muscles enable them
to shovel five tonnes of snow a day.
Their light-weight neighbour
needs more precision.
(CHEWING)
The bison have reached their goal,
a mouthful of withered grass.
And where the bison have dug,
the fox now spots an opportunity.
Every footstep counts,
but he mustn't break through...
Yet.
He listens carefully
to pinpoint his target.
(PATTERING)
It's moving.
(SQUEAKS)
A vole.
Small, but 100 times more nutritious
than a mouthful of dried grass.
To get through the winter on these
prairies, sometimes brain beats brawn.
Ultimately, life on all grasslands
depends on the turn of the seasons.
(CRACKING)
Five hundred miles further north
than any tree can survive,
grass returns to life.
(CALLS)
Caribou females have
journeyed to the far north
to calve.
(CALLS)
Over 70,000 caribou babies
will be born in the next few days.
As the calves appear, so too do the
leaves of the newly sprouting grass.
And the calves must strengthen quickly.
Within days they will have to
keep up with their parents
on a never-ending march.
At one day old, they're already faster
than an Olympic sprinter.
They're testing the legs that will
carry them thousands of miles,
better to learn their limitations now.
(CALLS)
(CARIBOU GRUNTING)
It may look playful, but there's
no harder life on the grasslands
than that facing these infants.
The caribou mothers now join together,
each with an infant
exactly the same age.
They're setting off on the greatest
overland trek made by any animal.
But wherever grass eaters travel,
predators lie in wait.
(CARIBOU CALLING)
Here they are, Arctic wolves.
They must seize their chance
while the caribou
pass through their territory.
(PANTING)
The wolf runs at the herd, trying to
flush out the weak or the slow.
A calf is separated.
At full tilt, 40 miles an hour,
the wolf is just faster.
But the calf has stamina.
Only a few weeks old, and this
calf's will to survive is remarkable.
And it needs to be,
for these young caribou
have now started a journey
that will last a lifetime.
Forever chasing the seasonal growth
of the grass on which they depend.
Like all grassland creatures,
they are at the mercy
of these unpredictable
but ultimately bountiful lands.
Grass can survive some of
the harshest conditions on Earth,
flood, fire and frost,
and still flourish.
So it is that grasslands
provide a stage
for the greatest gatherings of wildlife
on planet Earth.
For the grasslands team,
no location would prove as challenging
as that dominated by elephant grass
in northeast India.
The aim, to capture intimate images of
some the world's most elusive creatures
using the latest technology.
But they will need to be careful.
(COCKS GUN)
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETS)
More people are killed by wildlife
here in Kaziranga
than in any other
national park on the planet.
Every time we go into these tunnels,
we have to take an armed guard,
'cause there are so many animals
in here that are dangerous.
Tigers are probably
the least of our worries,
but rhinos and buffalo,
elephants, sloth bear,
all of them can injure you.
And we gotta keep up
with our armed guard.
ATTENBOROUGH: The team have bumped
into their first obstacle.
SANDESH: There's a rhino right there.
Let's go back because it's too risky
going through this heavy grass.
Let's get in the open.
- (SPEAKING LOCAL LANGUAGE)
- There's another rhino.
- Now we have two rhinos.
- Let's get in here.
Okay.
ATTENBOROUGH: The guard throws
a ball of mud to one side of the rhinos,
moving the animals on
without harming them.
(SHOUTS)
- We're okay. It's gone.
- Okay.
What about the other one?
Let's go, quick.
ATTENBOROUGH: With the rhinos
now a safe distance away,
the crew focus on the best spots
to position their camera traps.
I love that tunnel, the effect.
ATTENBOROUGH: Over 100 scaffold poles
provide the anchor points
for these secret cameras.
When an animal triggers
an infrared beam,
the cameras will switch on automatically
and start recording.
If it works, the remote-control cameras
should capture close-up footage
without disturbing the animals
or putting the crew at risk.
Basically, that's about as much
like grass as we can make it look.
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
ATTENBOROUGH: As night falls,
the crew head back to base for safety.
It's time for the new technology
to prove its worth.
At dawn, the crew have
a whodunnit mystery on their hands.
CHADDEN: Oh, wow.
That's carnage!
This looks like elephant, we think?
This is scaffold pole
they have bent.
Look at that. (CHUCKLES)
It's a sad day.
You win some, you lose some.
And this time,
the animals have outsmarted us.
In fact, check this out.
(CHUCKLES)
Whoo-hoo.
So this is our little army of guards,
protecting our trigger box.
Do they bite? These ones, they bite?
Sting?
Whoa! Argh! Ow!
The little (BLEEP).
ATTENBOROUGH: While Chadden
irons out the bugs,
Sandesh has met some grumpy locals.
Wild Asian water buffalo
have extraordinary senses.
Mothers will charge
if they feel threatened.
The guard carries a gun,
in case a warning shot is needed,
and with good reason.
More people are killed by buffalo
than by any other animal in Kaziranga.
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTS)
That'll wake you up in the morning.
ATTENBOROUGH: Many of the park staff
have cautionary tales about buffalo.
(SPEAKING HINDI)
The buffalo caught him here,
through his throat
and the horn came out through his mouth
and flung him before running away.
It's a miracle that he's still alive.
ATTENBOROUGH: If the wildlife
is unfriendly to humans,
it's proving downright hostile
to camera traps.
CHADDEN: Completely ripped out
the scaffold poles,
they've torn the triggers.
ATTENBOROUGH: While Chadden
is convinced it's elephants,
the rest of the crew are not so sure.
SANDESH: This is huge!
It's almost like a human footprint.
You can see the front paw, the rear paw.
CHADDEN: We are now two weeks in
and it's very frustrating.
I've never actually been anywhere
where the animals
go after your equipment and destroy it,
more than here.
ATTENBOROUGH: It's time for the team
to do some detective work.
Here is our little security camera.
If any animals are coming through
and vandalising our main cameras,
we hope that they're being caught
on these little things.
ATTENBOROUGH: As the crew
up their spying efforts,
the guards take them
to a promising lead.
Nothing attracts tigers
like a rhino carcass.
It's very fresh.
It's like from the morning.
And it looks like there's a tiger cub,
so it should be a tigress with cubs,
coming to feed on this rhino carcass.
It's pretty cool.
ATTENBOROUGH: Chadden decides to give
the camera traps one last chance.
If there are tigers around, they might
scare away the mystery vandals.
Elsewhere in the park,
the security cameras are
turning up some unexpected results.
At nighttime, survived another... Ooh!
It's a bear.
Wow, that's a very rare sighting.
SANDESH: I've never seen a bear
in Kaziranga.
In all my years, never.
- Oh, his fingernails...
- Look at his claws, right on the lens.
CHADDEN: So I thought
this was elephant damage.
I never thought we'd see
a sloth bear doing that.
That's amazing.
ATTENBOROUGH: A return to
the rhino carcass and the plot thickens.
SANDESH: Our transmitter's gone.
CHADDEN: That's what tigers
think of camera traps.
CREW MEMBER: Do you think
there's a bit over there?
Pieces.
ATTENBOROUGH: The security cameras
have caught a new culprit.
CHADDEN: Oh, my goodness,
there they are.
SANDESH: Ooh!
There it's a tigress, see that.
It's a tigress.
It snarled at the camera trap,
look at that.
Sure don't like camera traps.
Okay.
ATTENBOROUGH:
With the technology struggling,
Sandesh decides
to put himself on the frontline.
CHADDEN: It's on.
SANDESH: And now we're ready.
Time to get the tiger.
ATTENBOROUGH: He'll have no protection
apart from a thin wall of grass,
and must hope he's as well-hidden
as the local wildlife.
Over the next five days,
Sandesh plays the role
of human camera trap.
(BIRDS CAWING)
Eventually, the more
hands-on approach pays off.
Traditional filming methods
and a little bit of patience,
have helped reveal the
hidden creatures of Kaziranga.
(GRUNTS)
But it's good to know
there are still wild places
where animals like to keep
their secrets.
(CREAKING)
CHADDEN: I knew it was elephants.
ATTENBOROUGH: Next time,
we venture to
the newest habitat on Earth,
our cities.
To reveal the extraordinary ways
that animals survive
in this man-made world.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
OCR and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com