Previously on Dexter...
We have to catch them
in the act at the shipyard.
He's gonna find out,
and then he's gonna kill me.
Harry knew my mother.
Why would Rita print out
narcotics anonymous literature
If Paul's dead?
Because recently
I entered the program.
How many fucking times
do I have to tell you that I'm fine, Maria?
This is my department.
I need to know that you are fit for
duty. That's my job as a Liutenant!
I always stop and eat lunch at 1:00.
You'll learn that about me.
Why don't you sit down?
You're very fidgety.
Anyone ever tell you that?
My father.
You applying for the job?
Well, you said you'd call.
Where are you,
and when are you coming back?
Tomorrow morning.
Promise me to stop by the house
first thing.
See you.
- Is she OK with you doing this?
- I didn't tell her.
I don't care what you did.
I'm no longer sure
who made me what I am.
Funny thing is I've met someone
who doesn't care.
- We need to talk about Coral Cove.
- What about coral cove?
The algae on the rocks
sent us there.
If I were you,
I'd consider moving your boat.
- Security out there sucks.
- When I'm back, I'll hit the marina
and make sure there's
no blood traces on my boat.
This isn't a commercial marina.
But I can see the upkeep
on this place is dismal.
That's why I'm gonna order 24h surveillance
on this marina and the two others.
There's another shipment
coming in tomorrow.
Cocaine.
How much?
300 bricks, give or take.
Can you get your hands on some?
That wasn't part of our agreement.
We need hard evidence. Otherwise,
it's just your word against Estrada's.
I'll protect you.
I promise.
You better.
Do you meet me later?
Laura, the tape's still rolling.
Very convincing.
What was that?
Laura, the tape's still rolling.
Damn it.
My mother...
Confidential informant...
and mumbler.
Whatever sweet nothings
she had to whisper
I probably don't want to hear.
It seems that my foster father and my
biological mother were having an affair.
It's bad enough I can't shake
the visual. But the questions...
Did he blame himself for her death?
Is that why he took me in?
Did he love her,
or was he just using her?
Was he using me?
I always thought Harry's code was
on-The-Spot creative problem-Solving,
But maybe he planned for me
to settle the score all along.
It's times like this I wish
I really were a drug addict.
I had emotional problems as a kid
because of what happened to my mom.
Harry said he was trying to help me,
mut we only talked about his rules.
I spent so much time
trying to live up to his expectations
because I thought he had
my best interests in mind.
If you come over this late, the least
you could do is bring me a coffee.
- Sorry.
- Cappuccino...
Make a note of it.
Truth is, Dex,
It doesn't really matter
why Harry did what he did.
The result's the same.
You have an addiction.
Do you think Harry
made me what I am?
Plenty of people go through trauma
without turning to addiction.
Whatever Harry taught you
led you down the wrong path.
But I've built everything
in my life
on what Harry said
I was supposed to be.
My job, my girlfriend...
It's all what Harry
told me I needed.
What do you think you need?
I have no idea.
Whatever's inside you
is splattered all over
that paper I took from your lab.
Looks messy.
It probably is.
Look, Dexter.
Everyone has a moment
when they realize their value system
is different from their parents'.
Mine was in college, but...
maybe you're a late bloomer.
- Lucky me.
- Damn right, lucky you.
You get to have a fresh start.
Whatever you thought or did
doesn't matter.
Now you get to figure out who you are.
I went to Lila for answers,
but now all I have is more questions.
Who am I? What do I need?
What do I want?
Coffee. I really want
a cup of coffee.
- What up, half-day?
- Is there coffee left?
You're late.
I fell asleep before you got home
last night. Were you at Rita's?
You're welcome, ass.
- Your brother looks like shit.
- Tell me about it.
I may be out of line with this,
but did he fall off the wagon?
What wagon?
The only wagon he's ever had
is a radio flyer.
Your brother's a junkie.
Isn't he?
Are you high?
He's never even smoked a cigarette.
I'm glad you got
some new material, though,
'cause "freak" and "psycho"
were getting kind of tired.
Agent Lundy?
So, I hear a rumor you're tracking
all our Internet activity.
Is it true?
'Cause I can explain
all that she-male stuff.
I need my team outside in five minutes.
That sounds important.
Got a major break in the investigation.
Patrol found a guy saying he
escaped the Bay Harbor Butcher.
He claimed he was captured
two hours ago.
That's a neat trick,
considering I was asleep.
At least trying to sleep.
This could be good news for me.
- Morgan?
- Yes?
The other Morgan.
I'd like you to join us,
if you can spare him.
That's fine with me.
- Is there blood?
- Not that I'm aware of.
But what about Masuka?
Yeah, I'm the lead forensics
investigator.
Masuka's lab work is more pressing.
I need him to hold down the fort here.
He totally saw the she-male stuff.
So, what do you say?
I'll buy you lunch after.
Pork sandwich, right?
- Yes. Sure.
- Good.
I figured it was time to get
a fresh perspective on the case.
Rumor has it you have a knack
for attracting serial killers.
I hear the same about you.
Dexter also enjoys long walks
on the beach and foreign films.
Then we got a lot to talk about.
He knocked me out.
Then when I woke up, I was tied up
in that train car over there.
- You said he used rope?
- Dumb fuck.
I stretched it out enough
so I can get my legs free
and I got out of there.
Ran across the road, almost got hit
by that guy in the car.
So, that's the alleged victim
of the Bay Harbor Butcher.
But I've never seen him
before in my life.
O'Connor, Singer, make sure
you take pictures of those footprints.
- Hey, Dex.
- Hey.
So, the victim says the Butcher
held him in this train car.
Lundy wants you to search
for trace evidence.
- Your spidey sense tingling yet?
- We'll see when I get inside.
Take your time.
We've never been this close
to this pendejo.
Closer than you think, amigo.
He may have borrowed my pseudonym,
but this guy doesn't know
the first thing about my techniques.
Amateur.
Why do you think it was the Butcher?
He told me the Bay Harbor
Butcher's gonna clean up Miami.
He said, "You're gonna get
what you deserve."
And what do you deserve, Mr. Henry?
Well, look.
The Butcher kills criminals, right?
I just got out of jail, you know.
Six years for aggravated assault
and home invasion, so...
He kills murderers.
You didn't kill anyone, did you?
Alright, I gave this old guy
a heart attack.
It's not like I was doing it
on purpose, alright?
I used to hit retirement homes,
communities.
Snowbirds are easy targets.
And I don't do that anymore.
I did my time.
Your mother must be so proud.
I wanna check out
the train car with your brother.
Why don't you keep an eye
on our friend here
while we confirm his story?
Sure.
Killing tools left behind.
I'd never be this careless.
Whoever did this would
never pass Harry's muster.
Then again, neither would Harry.
He lied about my past,
he cheated on my foster mother
with my biological mother.
Maybe Lila's right.
It's time for a new set of standards.
If you were the Bay Harbor Butcher,
would you use a place like this?
Actually, yes.
Location wise, it's not a bad choice.
It's quiet,
remote.
Could use an upgrade in
the lighting department, but...
You think this is our guy?
Not exactly.
From what I understand,
the conditions in this space
don't support his M.O.
It's filthy, for one thing.
Butcher's clean...
orderly.
And some people would say compulsive.
Really? You think he's compulsive?
That doesn't fit either.
A hatchet is sloppy.
The butcher uses precise
surgical instruments.
He's not that predictable.
Is he? Mixes it up.
Different tools every time.
And never rope.
He uses duct tape and plastic wrap.
- Plastic wrap, how can you tell?
- Depression patterns in the skin.
Maybe the butcher's having
an identity crisis.
- It's entirely possible.
- But not likely.
My guess is we're looking
for a vigilante
inspired by the butcher's principles.
Bet he never thought
he'd be a role model.
I bet you're right.
So,
any new leads on the real guy?
Not yet.
We hope the cameras'll
turn something up.
- Cameras?
- In the marinas.
Put them in a couple of days ago
to monitor for suspicious activities.
Good news for all those cops
who keep boats at Coral Cove.
You've got one, too, right?
We've been needing a security
upgrade for a long time now.
Has Lundy seen me on the tape?
Is that why he invited me
along today? To mess with me?
Sorry if I was short with you
this morning.
I'm lost without my morning coffee.
- Whatever.
How was your playdate
with Lundy? Did you bond?
You didn't tell me they put up
security cameras at the marinas.
It's not like
they're doing us any good.
The station's computers
need an update
so we can synch up with
Lundy's equipment.
- The cameras aren't recording?
- They are, but nobody saw the footage.
Lundy said it should be fixed
by tonight.
That's a relief.
Your mom told me about
your cultural presentation at school.
Did your teacher give you
a country yet?
Saudi Arabia.
No. That's israel.
I won't tell the Saudis
you said that.
Looks like Cody's enjoying himself.
Dexter's very patient with him.
Dexter's a saint.
Where's Astor?
Uh, she's by the water.
I want to say goodbye.
I gotta go.
I was supposed to meet Lila
10 minutes ago.
Who's Lila?
His sponsor.
Really? A woman?
Dexter's sponsor is a woman.
Is that a problem?
Is she attractive?
- Mom...
- I'm just curious.
Is she?
I have an idea.
Why don't you and Lila
have dinner with us?
That's very kind of you,
Gail, but...
I think it'd be really nice
if we got to know the woman
you spend so much time with.
- Mom, they're doing step work.
- But they have to eat, right?
Here. Let me help.
Thank you.
So lovely of you to have me over.
Now I can put names to faces.
Dexter talks about you all the time.
Good things, I hope.
Dexter never says a bad word
about anyone.
Tell me, Lila.
What exactly
are you recovering from?
I'm a meth addict, sober five years.
I don't know much about meth.
- Rita's ex-Husband shot heroin.
- Like Dexter.
Guess we know your type, don't we?
Just can't seem to help myself.
You have nothing to worry about...
with Dexter, I mean.
I'm sitting right here.
- I didn't mean to imply...
- No. I completely understand.
Rita's your little baby.
You have every right to be concerned.
But if I can reassure you,
Dexter's doing incredibly well.
Well, I'm happy to hear that.
And I'm sure it's got everything
to do with the two of you.
He tells me you're very supportive.
Dexter's lucky to have you.
Well... that's very sweet
of you to say.
So, tell us more about yourself.
Dexter tells me you're an artist.
Yeah, she does amazing things
with a...
blowtorch. What's it called?
Talent.
But... I'm not
the only artist at the table.
- Since when?
- It's not really art.
She's talking about a blood-spatter
pattern she took from work.
What kind of career choice
is blood spatter, exactly?
He helps catch criminals, mother.
And it makes perfect sense, what with
Dexter's mother and everything.
You know...
she's...
... dead.
Forgot the bread.
Dinner was fantastic, Rita.
And this dessert...
I never thought I'd say this,
but I kind of like her.
Yeah, me too.
She's really helping me.
I wish she didn't have
to help you tonight.
Why? What are you thinking?
- My mom could watch the kids.
- I have to swing by the office tonight.
I need to take care
of something really important.
I mean, can't it wait till morning?
I promise we'll go straight to bed.
You're very convincing,
but it needs to get done tonight.
Just give me an hour, okay?
Meet you back at my place?
I still think it's funny
you write children's books.
Yeah, a big, tough guy like me
should be do something manly,
like wrangling cattle.
I don't even know any kids' books.
My dad told me cop stories before bed.
It was really the only alone
time I ever got with him.
You okay?
Yeah.
Sorry, just an annoying day at work.
You know the FBI guy
I was talking about?
I was really starting to feel
like I was his go-to girl,
But...
he realized Dexter
is the superior Morgan.
I should be used to it, you know?
It was like that with my dad, work.
I guess I hoped Lundy
would be different.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I respect him.
He's great at his job,
supersmart,
And, like, funny, but in this really
dry way where he doesn't even know it.
You love him.
What?
You totally have a crush on Grundy.
- Lundy.
- Now you're getting touchy about it.
I don't have a crush on him.
He's like my dad.
Except I spent my life trying
to get my dad to notice me,
and he actually pays attention
to what I say.
And grundy loves you.
Oh, fuck off.
Lundy's good - Double-Locked...
and a bit beyond my expertise.
I could try to crack it open,
but in my own station...
too risky.
I can do this more often now
that my mom's in town.
I feel like we're being bad.
Bad...
Bad is good.
Let the machine get it.
Hey, Dex, just calling to check in.
Thought we could do
the debriefing on dinner.
I thought it went well, don't you?
I'd say so.
Rita's sweet, very Martha Stewart.
I love Martha Stewart.
God, her mum, she's got quite
the rod up her ass, doesn't she?
By the way, I am such a twat.
I can't believe I almost
slipped up about your mum.
At least, I didn't spill the beans
about our road trip.
Don't you dare!
Can you imagine Rita's face
if I told her you and I
spent the night together in a hotel?
Anyway...
You and Lila stayed
in a hotel together?
- We had adjoining rooms.
- Adjoining rooms? Right.
God, I am such an idiot.
I can't believe I defended you while
you were sleeping with another woman.
Wait.
I thought you were different than Paul,
but you're the same.
Actually, you're worse.
You made me trust you.
- Please, just let me explain.
- I've had it!
I have been patient and understanding,
but there's only so much I can take.
You're a liar and a cheat,
and I am through.
It's over, Dexter!
Tracy Jenkins was given the liver
of a 9-year-old...
Hi, honey.
I thought you were spending
the night at Dexter's.
We had a fight.
- I think we broke up.
- What?
Mama's here.
Yesterday I was so hopeful.
A new me, a new life.
But a life without Rita
seems strange.
What in the name of fuck
are you doing up so early?
I got to get to the station.
Are you okay?
You seem weird.
Weirder than usual.
Rita broke up with me last night.
Seriously?
What happened?
It's a long story.
I've got time.
Yeah... but I don't.
Cliff Notes.
She thinks I did something bad,
but I didn't.
Did you tell her that?
I tried, but she dumped me
before I had a chance to explain.
She said, "It's over," and left.
- Did you go after her?
- Was I supposed to?
You're such a guy.
When I get pissed, I say stuff
I don't mean all the time. "I hate you,"
"I faked it,"
- "You're hung like a grape."
- You lost me.
When Rita said, "it's over," I'm sure
she didn't actually mean it.
Stop being a douche bag
and go fight for her.
She's fucking perfect.
I know.
Sure, I'll be right there.
Yeah. I'll tell him.
Who's that, Gabriel?
No, Lundy.
He's holding a meeting at the station
about the bay harbor case.
He specifically requested
that you be there.
I missed my window.
He's already seen the footage.
- Me? Why?
- Because you're his new butt buddy.
You gonna be okay?
Check back with me later.
The show has already started, but have
they seen the feature presentation?
Bane of the Bay Harbor Butcher,
starring Dexter Morgan as himself?
It's all synched up?
Yep, you can watch streaming video
of the marina right now if you want to.
Yeah. Maybe you'll get to see
some pontoon poon.
Did you... need something?
That's not my marina...
yet.
I'll be making my on-screen debut
soon enough.
I've got to find a way
to get to those video files.
The media frenzy about the Butcher
has come back to bite us.
Big surprise.
Now we've got a wannabe
vigilante out there
Who liked the Butcher's style
and thought,
"Hey, I should try this at home."
He attacked this man - John Henry,
Ex-convict, preyed on the elderly.
It gets better.
I have already received reports
of ads on Craig's list
and coffee-shop bulletin boards
requesting the services of the Butcher.
People think they've found
their own personal Batman.
This is not good news.
If this kind of thing catches on,
We're looking at an epidemic.
- Kind of like herpes.
- Fuck, Masuka, I'm trying to listen.
One in four, Morgan. One in four.
Vigilante justice is
domestic terrorism.
And terrorism prevention
is the FBI's top priority.
I've done my best to be diplomatic,
but if we lose one life
to a vigilante,
I will pull this case from Miami Metro
and hand it over in full
to the FBI. It's a promise.
That's a disaster.
It'd be raining feds in Miami.
So, if we want to keep
the investigation here,
we need to nip this in the bud,
make an example
of our would-be vigilante.
The last thing we need is
a bunch of weekend warriors...
I think I found a suspect.
Could you?
Ken Olson.
Olson's mother was hurt badly
in a home-invasion robbery.
Guess who hurt her.
Please, tell me John Henry,
our train-Car victim.
I think Olson attacked him
for revenge.
- Any evidence?
- Only circumstantial.
- Can you get him here for questioning?
- Can't find him.
OK. Leak this to some
of your media contacts.
Let's beat this guy out of the bushes.
Nice work, detective. Let's get moving.
I need hard evidence on this
Olson character, and fast.
And if you can find the guy,
even better.
The full force of the FBI -
That's the last thing I need.
I've got to make sure Lundy
gets his man...
after I figure out a way
to erase the marina files
and make up with my girlfriend.
Then maybe I'll tackle world hunger
'cause things can't really get worse.
Another shipment's coming in
tomorrow.
Cocaine.
How much?
300 bricks, give or take.
Turn it off.
That wasn't part
of our agreement, Harry.
I said turn it off.
I heard what you said.
I just don't take orders from you.
Is there a reason you're
in my lab, sergeant Doakes?
Is there a reason you're listening
to tapes as old as you are?
I had a little talk with your sister.
Turns out she didn't know
you were in program.
- Anonymous, sergeant.
- How long did you say you been clean?
Actually, I didn't because it's
none of your goddamn business.
So, if I were to take a hair
from your desk and run it for drugs,
it would come back positive, right?
Because why would someone
pretend to be an addict if he's not...
unless he's got something
a hell of a lot worse to hide?
Back...
the fuck...
off.
You want to hit me? Go for it.
I've been waiting for a chance
to take your ass out.
I know how you feel, sergeant.
I want to file a formal
complaint against Doakes.
Jesus, Dexter, the two of you...
He crossed the line, lieutenant!
He broke into my lab.
He went through my personal things.
He threatened me. He's probably
gonna start tailing me again.
- Sergeant Doakes tailed you?
- For weeks, maybe longer.
OK, you have every right
to file a complaint,
but before you do that, I'd like
the chance to talk to James myself.
He's really not much of a talker.
I'm asking you, as a personal
favor to me, to hold off.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Okay, in the meantime,
I strongly encourage you
to take a break for a couple of hours.
Just go somewhere. Cool off.
No.
- Excuse me?
- I need to be here, lieutenant.
This is really not a good time
for me to leave.
It isn't a suggestion, Dexter.
It's an order.
Clear the station. Clear your head.
I don't want to see you here
until after lunch.
Understood?
Blimey, look at you.
You wanna tell me what's going on?
What's going on?
Being the new me sucks.
I'm about to be found out
at work for what I am.
For what I really am.
And I can't do anything to stop it
because I got kicked
out of the office to cool off.
It seems to be going well for you.
Add to that the fact
that Rita heard your message
and dumped me last night.
I tried to explain to her nothing
happened, but she wouldn't listen to me.
- Nobody fucking listens to me!
- Listen, you need to calm down.
Last time, you came back
covered in blood.
So?
You said I was supposed
to feel my feelings.
Now I tell you to get them
under control.
- You don't understand.
- Why don't you make me?
Which step was that?
The naughty one.
What are you thinking?
Absolutely nothing.
I guess we found a way to quiet
the voices in your head.
I guess so.
How do you feel?
Much better...
actually.
I guess I must be
a good sponsor after all.
Definitely.
And where are you off to?
I still have that thing at work
to deal with.
Well, come back tomorrow.
I promise you some serious recovery.
Hello?
Dexter, hey.
- You at work?
- I will be soon.
I was just taking a break.
What's going on?
I'd really like
to get together and talk.
I don't like how our last
conversation ended.
Me neither.
You said you wanted to explain,
and I owe it to you to hear you out.
I owe it to us.
Okay.
So, can you come over after work?
Sure.
Great.
Apparently my new life
involves a love triangle.
I'm that guy.
The voices are back. Excellent.
You were tailing Dexter?
What the hell were you thinking?
If you wanted to have lunch,
you could have asked.
If Dexter files a complaint, you will be
kicked off the force, end of story.
There's a reason he hasn't
reported me until now.
He's hiding something.
I can feel it.
Is this another one
of your conspiracy theories?
It's instinct and a hell
of a lot of experience.
I've spent years looking
the enemy in the face,
and I'm telling you
Morgan is dangerous.
Your instincts haven't been
that great these days, James.
Two shootings in the last six months,
Stalking a police employee...
Listen to me.
Morgan lied
about the Ice-Truck Killer.
That crack pipe knew
more than he told us.
He was trying to protect his sister.
You of all people should understand.
I followed him to an N.A. meeting.
That asshole lied about that too.
- You're obsessed.
- I'm not.
You are,
and I need you to see it...
as your boss and as your friend.
We've been through this before.
Last time it cost you
our relationship.
This time it's gonna get you
kicked off the force or worse.
I'll take my chances.
Let it go.
I mean it.
Leave Dexter alone.
The Batista suspect come in yet,
the wannabe vigilante?
Olson just came in.
Saw himself on the 3:00 news
and showed up with his lawyer.
I hope we nail his ass to the wall.
I love it when you talk dirty.
- Morgan?
- Right here.
The other Morgan.
I didn't know you were a smoker.
Have you seen Dexter Morgan?
He's on a break. Why?
Detective Batista's got
a suspect in interview room 1.
We think he's the would-be vigilante
who attacked our train-car victim.
I need him to take some scrapings
for evidence.
You want to use Dexter again?
Isn't Masuka on your task force?
Yes, he is.
So, Mr. Olson, the man who assaulted
your mom was attacked yesterday.
- Did you know that?
- Nope.
Can't say I'm upset, though.
Son of a bitch almost killed my mom.
My client's emotional, detective.
- I'm sure he's not trying to say...
- Any idea who might have done it?
I don't know.
Maybe it was the Butcher.
I think a guy like that
should be running the police
force, not hiding from it.
- Is this a lion or a hippo?
- I think it's a lion.
Tastes like a hippo.
- Animal cracker?
- No, thank you.
What do you do for a living,
Mr. Olson?
I just lost my job.
That's too bad.
I see that you have
a minor assault record
and no alibi for yesterday morning.
I'm sure my client didn't
realize he needed one.
You have a girlfriend, Mr. Olson?
She just broke up with me.
Why, you interested?
Just curious.
Now, this is a lion.
Alright, let me keep this all straight.
No job,
no relationship.
You got guns
and a minor assault record.
- And I voted for Bush both times.
- Sorry, were you getting at something?
What he's getting at, Mr. Novik,
is your client fits the 4-point profile
of someone who'd commit a vigilante
offense. You're a ticking time bomb.
You ask me, you just needed a reason
to take the law into your own hands.
And the butcher
was the perfect excuse.
- You don't know me.
- We know you attacked John Henry.
You need proof to make those
kinds of accusations, detective.
You heard the man, detective.
We've got work to do.
Make yourself comfortable, Mr. Olson.
We're just getting started with you.
That's my marina.
And in less than 30 minutes,
I'll be on that screen.
I need to take care of this,
and fast.
I'm out of time.
I need an idea, a sign,
anything.
What would the old Dexter do?
Definitely not that.
No security cameras.
Apparently the new Dexter's stuck
in high school.
Maybe I am a late bloomer.
A fire drill? Are you kidding?
We have work to do.
It's probably one of those kids
in the bullpen.
It's something I would have done.
Well, at least it stopped raining.
All clear. Everybody out.
All clear! Everybody out!
Respect the vest.
Don't make me take out my hose.
Like it never happened.
If only the rest of life
were so easy to figure out.
Where you headed?
I figured you'd be 1st
to ogle the firemen.
I have to arrange protective custody
for that fucking train-car victim.
- Why?
- 'Cause we have nothing on Olson,
not even enough to get a warrant
to search his place.
Is that Olson's file?
If we don't get something soon,
Lundy'll have to let him go,
meaning Olson will kill again,
meaning we lose
the Butcher case to the FBI,
- meaning we're fucked.
- Some more than others.
No shit. Till Lundy showed up,
I felt like the dipshit who
slept with the ice-Truck killer.
If he pulls the plug, I go back
to being the resident retard.
Chin up little sister,
these things have a way
of working themselves out.
I just have to find
a piece of evidence
to make sure Lundy
catches Olson fair and square.
Looks like I have a fan club,
membership of one.
Why you so interested in the Butcher?
Who the fuck are you?
Holy shit, you're him, aren't you?
Stop. Don't kill me. Don't kill me.
I'm like you. I take out criminals.
You mean you try... pitifully.
No, that was just the last one.
He got away.
I should have never made it personal.
- You've killed others?
- That's I'm telling you.
First was a drug dealer -
I ran him down with my car.
It felt... It felt fucking great,
Even better than the free stash
I got off him.
And then, this guy at work
found out I was fucking his wife.
He started to beat on her,
so I pushed him down a stairwell.
The cops thought it was
an accident, but it was me.
See, you can't kill me.
I wasn't going to...
until now.
This is what the kill room
should look like.
the inside of a big plastic bag.
Of course, I spent hours working
in this train car yesterday,
so I'm not too worried
about trace evidence.
To your credit,
your location was well chosen.
It just needed
a little cleaning, a few lights,
proper tools, of course.
- I did it because of you.
- No.
You attacked those people
because you wanted to.
- You inspired me...
- I didn't.
- ... with your principles.
- They're not mine.
- Of course they are!
- Don't tell me who I am.
All my life, I've done what
someone else said I should do,
been who he said I should be. I followed
his rules, I stuck to his plan.
I never stopped to think about
what I wanted and what I needed.
And now I don't know
who I'm supposed to be.
I'll tell you one thing, though.
I'm not the Bay Harbor Butcher.
I'm certainly not
anybody's role model.
What are you talking about then?
Who are you?
I'll let you know
when I figure that out.
Though, I got to tell you,
I am well on my way, because...
as sure as I'm standing here,
I don't need to kill you.
That's a relief.
I mean that need
that comes from within
that always drives me to this table
I don't feel it.
I'm in recovery.
- I knew you weren't gonna kill me.
- No, I will kill you. I have to.
I just don't need to.
It's very empowering.
Anyone in there, make yourself known!
Arm.
Leg.
Head.
It's Olson, gift-wrapped.
It would seem the Butcher
is watching us,
- tracking the investigation.
- That wouldn't be too hard to do.
But why'd he leave the victim's
body for us? It's a 1st.
Probably didn't take too kindly
to the idea of Olson imitating him.
It's a good way to
discourage others, don't you think?
I hate to say it, but he
probably did us a favor.
Take the law into your own hands,
the Bay Harbor boogeyman'll get you.
It's the 1st time
we've set foot in a place
where the Bay Harbor Butcher's
actually been. Let's get busy.
- Anybody seen Lundy?
- Over there on the phone.
He's talking to D.C., I think.
Shit. Is he gonna
pull the case from us?
Sure, have Robinson call me.
He's got my cell.
I came here for privacy,
officer Morgan.
- Sorry.
- Too much background noise over there.
Hearing's the first thing to go.
- Or is it memory? I always forget.
- You gonna pull the case from us?
- You said if anybody died...
- At the hands of a vigilante.
This was our killer.
I'm afraid you're still stuck with me.
Will your brother be here tomorrow?
Yeah, I think so.
I'll tell him you want him
within shouting distance.
What just happened?
No, it's cool. He's always been
the family superstar.
- Who? Dexter, your new go-to guy.
This isn't about Dexter. It's about
Masuka. I can't stand him.
If I hear one more titty joke,
I could punch him in the face.
Really?
Any north unit, request has been made
for 42 escort from Orange belt to J.M.S.
Hey.
Come on in.
Sit down.
I was angry before
when you tried to explain.
This time I'll listen.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about the road trip.
Lila...
came with me to Naples...
as my sponsor.
That's all.
Why would you need her in Naples?
You remember
when I went out of town?
I went to find the man
who killed my mother.
What are you talking about?
A lot of stuff has been
coming up for me in recovery,
things I never thought
I'd deal with.
I watched my mother die
- when I was 3.
- God.
I'm so sorry.
She was murdered
in front of me.
I saw it happen.
I think that has a lot to do
with why I'm...
... why I do the things I do.
Of course.
Of course, it makes sense.
I found the man who killed her
in Naples.
I thought maybe if I talked to him,
I could find some kind...
of closure.
That's why Lila came with me.
For support.
- What?
- This was a huge moment
in your life, Dexter...
and you chose to include Lila
but not me.
- She's my sponsor.
- And I'm your girlfriend.
I was afraid
you wouldn't understand.
So...
let me try to understand now.
You and Lila
went away together
as sponsor and sponsee.
And you really did have
adjoining rooms.
So you didn't have sex that night?
Not that night.
Leave.
Rita...
No, please! Leave now.
There was a time I would have done
anything to protect Rita.
I would have even lied.
But today I told the truth...
even though I knew she'd get hurt.
Maybe I am leaving
the old me behind.
resync by --pano--