-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly presents
Sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Dexter
Season02 Episode03
Previously on dexter...
Two treasure hunters made
a ghastly discovery today
When they stumbled on what appears to be an underwater
graveyard in a crevice off the coast of miami.
Do you know what that means?
Means there might be a new mass murderer out
there,way worse than the ice-truck killer.
The bay harbor butcher?
That's what the press is calling
whoever dumped bodies offshore.
The last thing miami needs
is another serial killer.
13 and counting.
They're so swamped up there,they
had to bring in outside talent.
Frank lundy?*******
The green river
killer,the D.C.Sniper --
If the case was impossible,he broke it.
So,this is the man who stands
between me and death row.
With your help,we'll find
whoever did this awful thing.
So,let's get a jump-start
on the bay harbor butcher.
With doakes tag inme,my life's
been all jekyll and no hyde.
Paul kept insisting to me that
you knocked him over the head,
Dragged him to his motel,and
shot him up with drugs.
I hit paul to protect you and the kids.
Look,if there is
anything left between us,
You will answer me this one question
and you will tell me the truth.
Are you an addict?
Yes,I have an addiction.
'An Inconvenient Lie'
My name is caroline.
I'm an addict.
Hi,c oline.
Um,I started taking pain
pills after my back surgery.
I don't need them for the pain anymore.
Now I...
Now I just need them.
And I need duct tape
-- three or four rolls.
Running low on heavy-duty trash bags.
When's the last time
I sharpened my knives?
And I lost my license.
Tears now?
It's very hard to concentrate in here.
How am I supposed to get any work done?
My husband says he's gonna
leave me if I don't stay sober.
But I have to do this for myself.
No self-control,lost
everything,trying to stop.
Same whiny story over and over for...
10 minutes --
feels like 10 hours.
Taking lortabs and darvocet and percocet
And anything I could get my hands on.
And even now...
I'd kill for a vicodin.
Lightweight.
First I thought,narcotics
anonymous,I don't belong here.
You guys are real addicts.
So,how was the meeting?
Tell me everything.
It was,uh,interesting,hearing the
same story over and over again.
- Knowing you're not alone.
- Exactly.
Did you get fortune cookies?
Only the ones with the good fortunes.
So,did you share or just listen?
I just wanted to take it
all in my first time out.
Think they forgot...
Ah,here they are. Spring rolls.
And what about a
sponsor? Did you find one?
I didn't want to rush into anything.
It's an important relationship.
Absolutely.
Okay,so,let's see your newcomer's chip.
Newcomer's chip. Yeah...
You did stay until the end,didn't you?
Of course I did.
Right to the end.
You're a terrible liar.
I know too much about 12-step
programs to be easily conned,dexter.
I didn't stay till the end
end,if that's what you mean.
I had some important errands to run.
Important? What?
Am I important? Are the kids?
Yeah.
Yes,of course.
Well,you're just gonna have
to figure out how important,
Because if you don't work the program
-- and I mean really work it --
I just... I can't go through this again.
All right,kids. Dinner.
How important are they?
I'm sure someone with a heart
could answer that question.
Tomorrow. I'll go tomorrow.
I'll stay.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Hold the elevator!
Thanks.
Nice dodge last night,flooringit
through that yellow light.
Were you behind me?
See you tonight.
We will get to all of you.
Okay,take their names and keep them out
of the bullpen till we figure this out.
Sue macmillan.
She disappeared four years ago.
Who are they?
Every family member of every
missing person for the last decade.
Including some sad,lonely,and
presumably single women,
Courtesy of lieutenant pascal.
It's not her fault. That
reporter's an asshole.
Sergeant?
Yeah,hold the rest of them
downstairs. We're out of room here.
You seen pascal?
You know,pascal is just
caught in a cycle of reaction.
She's not co-creating her own reality.
You know those words don't
actually mean anything,right?
Look around you,bro.
She's manifesting negativity.
It's on again.
Excuse me,lieutenant?
No comment.
We have reports there were dozens of
bodies found in that underwater grave site.
Not dozens.
The boss' sweater
melons look bigger on tv.
The operative word is boss.
Show some respect.
I thought I was.
One dozen? Two dozen?
18 or so.
Have the families been notified?
We're still trying to identify them.
If viewers have information,they
should contact you?
Yes. Fine.
So,there you have it.
Police are seeking any leads that can help them identify
the 18 faceless victims of the bay harbor butcher.
If you have any
information,please contact...
Pascal is definitely off her game.
Word is,her fianc? Is catching
some strange on the sly.
That'd do it.
The shit stops here. Give it to me.
Most of these people
won't find answers here.
Chances are good their loved
ones weren't among my chosen few.
May I have your attention,please?
First of all,I want to tell you what a great
job you've all been doing on this horrific case.
And with the help of the best man hunter
in the fbi,we should have answers soon.
In the meantime,the daily work of this
precinct must continue to serve the public,
So we'll be dividing up our resources.
Agent lundy has requested the following
officers for his joint task force.
Officer cook...
Lundy made me lfi.
Lfi?
Lead forensics investigator.
Sorry you got
boned,but,hey,no blood spatter.
Sucks to be me.
Actually,it keeps me off lundy's radar.
Sergeant lee.
Detective ramos...
Officer panko...
- detective batista...
- yes!
I saw this happening.
And officer debra morgan.
Those called will report
directly to special agent lundy.
And let's not forget this
is on all of us,folks.
Let's keep our eyes and our ears open.
The ice-truck killer was an
amateur compared to this guy.
I'd also appreciate it if your lieutenant would
consult with me before speaking to the press.
I'll rip her a new one...
If I can find her.
Prints,fiber,trace
evidence --
No,they won't find anything.
I followed all of harry's
painstaking preventative measures.
He knew that nothing
stays buried forever.
His code will protect me.
Still,I wish my own sister weren't hunting
me -- makes for an awkward family dynamic.
So,I'm a fed.
My suit proves it.
The other suits here are feds.
But suit or...
Ugly hawaiian
shirt --
No offense --
we're a team.
And our first play is
I.D.Ing those bodies.
Once we know who they are,we'll
fill in every detail of their lives,
From their huevos ranchos
to their crËme br˚lÈE.
And,uh,get used to food
references 'cause,well,I like food.
Vince masuka and his team are
gathering dna,prints,and dental records.
The rest of us are going to cull through
cold cases and missing-persons files.
Also,I want that crowd
out there interviewed --
Though most of them
will be a waste of time.
Negative thinking.
You four,move them out as quickly
as you can,but be thorough.
If we get even one
hit,it'll be worth it.
Everyone else,work the files.
Remember,I.D.S will lead to a
pattern,which will lead to our man.
When the manhunt is
on,the hunted go shopping.
Not for a
new car --
For my next project.
I won't act on it... Yet.
I'm still laying low.
Harry would insist on that.
Just getting the
research out of the way.
Someone talked his way into the homes of two
women and didn't leave till they were dead.
Ann cohen and,a month
before her,lynn hall.
A certain car dealership ran
credit checks on both women.
Both bought cars elsewhere,so
nobody thought about it twice.
But who requested those credit checks?
Roger hicks.
All I need is
some dna proof --
Cup of coffee should do the trick.
How many kids you got?
Enough.
I hear you.
When my two came along,it
was bye-bye,convertible.
Of course...
They're worth it.
Must take after their mom.
That they do. Thank god.
I tell you,I miss my
convertible,but,uh,truth --
My minivan's got a much nicer ride.
So you own one.
Oh,the same one you're looking at.
I mean,I know
-- whipped,right?
But,uh,my kids love the twin dvds.
They're just crazy about
spongebob,you know what I mean?
Actually,I do.
My wife loves the nav system
and all the safety features.
And when they're happy...
- you're happy.
- That's right.
Except the kids don't
exist,neither does the wife.
And he owns a beemer,not a minivan.
Still,he's seamless.
Impressive.
It's not flashy,but...
What did flash ever get me? It
got me pulled over,that's what.
I'm definitely not into flash.
You got to sit in the
captain's chair,though.
It's like a 747,man.
Manuel,hold up.
Thank you,sir. So,uh...
We should take it out.
Check out the ride.
I'm just doing research.
Okay,you don't want a big
sales pitch. I get that.
Let me at least pull the specs for you.
Because,truthfully,we have a hard
time keeping these on the lot.
You might want to grab the
test-drive while it's still here.
I think I have all the information
I need to make a decision.
Yeah?Well,then,you've seen the,uh,
The stow 'n go seating system,right?
I have had everything in here
From a soccer team to
a freakin' deer carcass.
It was an accident,of course.
But,uh,I sure was glad for the ample cargo
space,not to mention the tinted windows.
I can see how that might come in handy.
I'll just grab the keys.
I go to stalk a killer and
I end up with a new car?
- How'd that happen?
- New car?
Yeah.
You get married?
Not that I know of.
So what's with the mommy mobile?
I'm,uh...
Not sure.
Synthetic.
Even roger's hair is a lie.
I could learn a thing
or two from this guy.
Who's your daddy?
Harry morgan.
Dude,the lead forensics investigator
of the joint task force -- that's who.
Oh,okay.
So,you want in on this bitch or not?
What bitch?
The only bitch in town,baby.
The bay harbor butcher.
I got you temporarily assigned.
Vince,you didn't have to do that.
Nothing sexy,of course,just some
bone-marrow collection for dna I.D.S.
But it'll get you in the tent.
And you got to see the tent. Amazing.
Say it.
You're my daddy.
It sounds weird when you say it.
I haven't been much use
since he disappeared.
I know I'm supposed to move on,but...
Here's the picture of him.
He looks...
Nice.
Not according to my mother...
Or the police.
He was in and out of jail,but my
heart raced whenever I saw him.
I brought his toothbrush.
They say you can get dna off it.
You can find him with this,right?
Special agent lundy?
Look,thanks for choosing me
for the task force and all,
But I'd appreciate you
finding someone else.
You want off?
Just as soon as you can replace me,sir.
This is a chance to solve
a pretty important case.
Most people get into this
line of work to do just that.
Well,i've got cases
of my own backing up,
And the precinct's
shorthanded with all this shit.
So,if you don't mind...
I'll see what I can do.
In the meantime,if you could
continue the interviews...
Yeah. Yeah,of course.
Thank you.
Most of 'em have been
underwater for years.
But some,it's awesome,you
can't even tell.
The temperature on the ocean floor
and the airtight bags kept them intact.
I mean,a little gelatinous
residue,sure. But...
I'd rather remember my old
playmates as they were --
Neat,clean little packages.
You know,vince,I appreciate
you doing me this favor but --
Actually,you're doing me the favor.
I need your help,buddy.
The pressure's fucking ridonkulous.
Glad to be of service.
Field morgue for the overflow,but
it's state-of-the-art.
Fucking fbi,eh?
A good percentage are just bones.
Must have fed the fish
when the bags tore.
Humpty fucking dumpty,right?
Exactly.
They weren't meant to
be put together again.
They were meant to remain in the
silent shadows,keeping their secrets.
Now they're exposed to the glare,reflecting my
darkness like some grotesque carnival mirror.
Harry was right --
nothing stays buried.
Perhaps not even me.
Looking for my taurus,sergeant?
Keep looking.
You don't need to know
where I'm going tonight.
And genius me,not only do I leave
my works in my girlfriend's car,
But also all the dead fish
from the fishing trip,right?
Then I collapse in her
parents' house,scare her kids,
And get myself fired,'cause
guess what -- we work together.
Yeah.
So,now,well,I'm 20-days sober...
Again...
Hoping to make it to 21.
Thanks,gordon.
This meeting recognizes
lengths of sobriety with chips.
So,if there's anyone who
would like a newcomer's chip...
You've got three minutes
to share if you want it.
Oh,really?
Go ahead,man. You among friends.
Well,I,uh...
What's your name?
Bob.
- Hi,bob.
- Hi.
And i'm,um...
An addict.
I use...
Heroin --
shoot it.
It's affecting my job.
My boss found my works. He fired my ass.
But I showed him -- I spent every
penny of my final paycheck on junk.
Doctor said I...
I almost died.
Coffee sucks...
As bad as the doughnuts.
It's better next door. Come on.
It is good coffee. Thank you.
So,tell me...
Exactly how full of shit are you?
I'm not full of anything.
It was a nice performance in there.
Where did you download
it from? Addict.Com?
Look,I have no reason to lie.
Sure you do.
We all do.
You thought I was lying?
I don't know... Bob.
Well,it is anonymous.
Everyone in that room has heard or lived
Far worse than anything
you've ever done.
I doubt it.
Oh,so you're super-junkie.
I don't mean to imply that what you've
been through hasn't been difficult.
But there's no way that I could
know what you've experienced,right?
I couldn't possibly feel that need.
Like a thousand hiding
voices whispering,
This is who you are.
And you fight the pressure,
The growing need rising like a wave,
Prickling and teasing
and prodding to be fed.
But the whispering gets louder
until it's screaming,now!
And it's the only voice you hear...
The only voice you want to hear.
And you belong to it,to this...
Shadow self.
To this...
Dark passenger.
Yes.
The dark passenger.
No.
I'm sorry,but I need to go.
Thanks for the coffee.
She knows.
She recognizes demons...
Dark passengers.
Maybe the others can,too.
This program is too
risky,especially now.
Rita will have to understand.
Hey.
You just missed story time.
I was at a meeting.
Thank you.
It made me realize something important.
Oh,really? What's that?
Those meetings are not
a good place for me.
I know how this sounds,but
I can do this on my own.
Dexter,you need a program.
I've read
studies --
People are 10 times as likely to change on their
own as they are with the help of doctors or programs.
So you're quoting studies?
Look,I lived this.
I watched paul try and fail
with white-knuckle sobriety.
I'm not paul.
I'm not any of those people.
Going to those meetings will do
more harm than good,I swear to you.
I'm better off alone.
I pray you change your mind.
What just happened?
Deb?
Thought you were staying at rita's.
Taking the night off.
I thought you'd be on the treadmill.
With no money down,guaranteed,or
we'll make your first two payments...
A night off is good to
remember what's important.
Two women are dead,the
killer is selling minivans,
And I have an opportunity to
prove it,even if I am laying low.
Having a victim prepped and ready
will take the edge off the wait...
I hope.
Hey,hang on just a second,okay?
- What's going on,dex?
- Hey.
Any problems,the service center can take
care of you,but they're around the corner.
Actually,the minivan's fine.
Well,of course it is. I
never sold a lemon in my life.
I'm just rethinking
the extended warranty.
Great,i'll set you up with
a warranty writer,then.
And I'm thinking roof rack
and premium sound system.
- Going all out.
- Yeah.
That's great,but I'm with a customer.
- And so one of my associates
- - I'd rather deal with you.
- i'll just wait for you in your office.
- Outstanding.
Dna,dna,come out and play.
Uh-oh,roger's got you in the box.
Once you're in the box,you
don't leave without a deal.
Don't worry. You're safe with roger.
He's the best.
I'm just dropping off
this thank-you note.
Well,I was just leaving.
He sent you across the street,didn't he?
Across the street?
It's okay,he told me not
to tell anyone either.
Yeah,I don't know how he makes a living
sending all of his commissions to other dealers.
Maybe he has ulterior motives.
Or maybe he knows I
can't afford his price.
After he ran a credit check?
Trw doesn't lie.
So,you're single?
Y-yeah.
Makes it tougher to afford those
big-ticket items,like cars and houses.
- You rent an apartment?
- A house.
I hate sharing walls.
You can hear everything.
Tell me about it. No pets,though,right?
Yeah. Is this a come-on?
'Cause it's a little weird.
It must be why I'm still single.
Another brunette.
Single,neighbors at a
distance,no guard dog.
The credit check gets roger
all the details he needs.
She's next,and I can't
do anything about it --
Not until this manhunt ends.
Harry would insist on it.
What?
No,i'll take care of it.
I know the card is in his name.
I just want to check the charges.
Well,the supervisor I spoke
with this morning allowed it.
Yes --
no,uh...
Yeah,i'll hold. Yes?
Just a reminder that the biscayne
drive-by warrant needs your approval.
I'll look at it.
And the homicide that came in last
night still needs to be assigned.
Right,thanks.
Look,esmee,
I know that things are rough
with you and your fianc?Right now,
And I'm sorry,really,but we need to
keep clearing that board out there.
Yeah,you're right. I'm sorry.
I seem to have had my
head up my ass lately.
It's called being human.
Okay,who's up?
Samuels and kent are up.
Put them on the liquor-store shooting.
And where is the biscayne warrant?
Oh,right here.
Simms and hoagie want S.W.A.T.For entry.
I think it's a good
measure,given the weapons charge.
Excuse me,I'm -- I'm gonna
need a minute. Just...
Just gonna need a minute.
Esmee?
- Esmee?
- Please,maria.
I'll handle it.
You're not taking my calls,and now you're
checking my credit-card charges,esmee?
Roger's dna matches the semen
found at both crime scenes.
Irrefutable.
If I do nothing,another woman dies.
Is that my long-dormant
conscience talking
Or the dark passenger whispering?
Hi,it's me.
Hi,dexter.
Kids home from school yet?
Colleen's bringing them home now.
I'm A...
Little confused.
I'm sorry you're confused.
I mean,it's pizza night.
Should I pick up the usual?
Did you go back?
To a meeting --
thinking about it.
The kids and i will order in,then.
Uh,okay.
So...
Is this it?
That's up to you,dexter.
I want to know,where is she,mi teresita.
She's so young
-- 7 year old.
You help me.
I know you find her.
We'll do what we can.
Don't cry.
No spanish. No habla.
Only english. Angel?
Just tell her we'll call her.
She thinks you can find the daughter.
There are no kids down there.
Tell her I can't help her.
- She - - I-I
can't help you.
Morgan?
Morgan!
It's been 24 hours since
I asked to be replaced.
Has it?
What's taking so long?
Every cop on the damn
force wants in on this case.
Just take your pick.
I've been wondering about that,actually.
Everyone wants on,but you want off.
I told you,I have cases.
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so.
Jesus,I just don't want to be
on your task force,all right?
Why?
Because I'm the last person in
the world that should be on it.
You want me to find a serial killer?
I was engaged to one,for christ's sake.
What kind of cop
-- what kind of --
That's why I chose
you,you know --
Because of what you went through.
You survived.
I don't know how.
I can't begin to imagine the
strength it took -- continues to take.
More than that,
You got a firsthand look into
the mind and heart of a killer,
And you're still here.
If you can accept that
--really accept it --
You could use it.
Mix that with some of
your strength,and...
You could catch someone even
worse than the ice-truck killer.
But you have to stop running.
Finish today's interviews.
Then,if you still want out,you got it.
Lead fucking investigator.
Translation --
everyone's bitch.
I do have a life,you know.
You do?
Just give me your
bone-marrow dna results.
No matches.
Big surprise.
Do me a favor on your way out,will you?
Drop these dental x-rays
at the field morgue for me?
Tech should still be there.
Fucking bay harbor butcher is
butchering my online social life.
Sorry.
Next.
I figured you'd still be here.
You were a pain in the ass
but always a damn hard worker.
And,of course,you knew
how to handle the press.
Come here a minute.
The public needs to believe that we can
protect them,or all hell breaks loose,
So I need all my people operating
at their very highest levels.
I agree.
Should I be worried about pascal?
Pascal? Why?
You can cut the crap,maria.
I know she's been awol
on personal matters.
The press fuckup is huge,
And now I'm beginning to hear
rumors about erratic behavior.
And you're asking me because...
Because you've done the job.
So if she's out,that
means you're back in.
That makes you her harshest
critic,and I want it straight.
So...
Take your shot,maria.
You know what erratic means?
It's code for non-male,
And it's the same bullshit sexism
I put up with when I was in charge.
I won't dignify rumors,captain.
Pascal's fine.
Minivan's that way.
Field morgue's this way.
I'll wait.
You should take the night off,sergeant.
On pizza night? No way.
What does that girlfriend of yours
see in a freak show like you anyway?
You have to ask her.
Maybe I will.
What exactly is it you think i've done?
I know you're connected
to the ice-truck killer.
Could you be more vague?
I know you're too careful.
You keep your assets in cash.
You don't belong to any
organizations or alumni groups.
You were top of your
class in med school,
But you traded it for
fucking blood spatter.
I know you studied
martial arts in college,
But I don't know what a lab
geek needs with advanced jujitsu.
Do you know what an easy credit is?
I know you're a good liar,too.
Not good enough.
Sergeant doakes thinks
he knows my secrets,
But he only needs to look at this,my
body of work,to know the real me.
Suit up if you're gonna touch them.
No,I'm just,uh...
Dropping off some x-rays.
I'm dexter morgan.
I know who you are.
Right.
Looks like the lab tech's gone
home for the night,so i'll just...
You hoping they'll talk to you?
The ones with heads,anyway.
They always speak... Eventually.
Just got to ask the right question.
Which is?
Why were they chosen?
You looking for a pattern?
One doesn't kill this many people in this
careful,methodical way without a reason --
Some... Twisted set of principles.
Yeah,they would have to
be twisted,wouldn't they?
The worst killers in history are usually the
ones who think their murders were somehow...
Just -- even
deserved.
Leaders have slaughtered whole
populations for the same warped reason.
But there's never any
justification for killing.
No.
Well,one,of course.
To save an innocent life.
How many more bodies would there
be had I not stopped those killers?
Dndi't do it to save lives...
But save lives I did.
Motivation aside,I think harry
and lundy would agree on this one.
- Roger the artful dodger.
- Jesus!
You scared me,bro.
We have some unfinished business.
Oh,yeah,right,the warranty
and stuff. Listen,uh...
I can't write you up right now.
I got the wife waiting for me.
You're not married.
Ex-wife. I got to take the kids.
You don't have kids.
- Stepkids --they're hers.
- Nope.
Okay,how about this one?
I don't give a shit.
Neither do I.
You were right about
the ample cargo space.
Where am I?
Looks different under plastic,but
you spent an evening here...
With ann cohen.
You took her last breath
from her right over there.
- You remember?
- No.
You're -- you're
wrong. I wouldn't.
You would and you did and
you were about to do it again.
That's why we're here.
No,this is crazy.
You got the wrong guy.
I -- I sell
cars,for god's sake.
I've never hurt anyone in my
life -- definitely not a woman.
Why can't I do that?
Do what?
Lie like that.
I mean,I thought I was
good,but you,it's...
I don't lie.
Okay,that one was weak.
Okay,look,any car on the lot,it's yours.
T-bird,town car,you
name it -- yours free.
I'll call it in right now.
Lot's closed.
I'll have them open
it up. I'm the manager.
The manager's name is rick buxton.
Yeah,but i've been
there longer than he has.
You've been there three months.
At the other lot.
It's like watching someone ski moguls.
You just hop from
one lie to the next --
No shame,no embarrassment.
You just don't give a shit.
That's the key,right? Not to
care about anyone or anything.
I care.
I care a lot.
No,it was a compliment.
- I don't care,either.
- Yes,you do.
Like about your wife.
Not married.
Girlfriend,then.
I saw it the minute
you walked on the lot.
What did you see? Tell me.
Look,most guys your age,they beeline...
Right for the horsepower --
you know,something flashy,sexy.
But you -- you're
there all alone,
No one there to nag you,and you
don't even glance at the coupes.
The only thing you
look at is the minivan,
Like you can see her in the passenger's
seat and the kids in the back.
- Leave the kids out.
- See?
You're lying to yourself
if you think you don't care.
She's just a companion,really.
Started that way,anyway.
Someone who.
Looked good,normal.
They worm their way in.
Yeah,they do.
Then they shut you out.
That's what this is about
-- That she shut you out?
Man,okay,I get it.
I-I -- i've been there.
But you can't let her get
to you like this,'cause --
'Cause they're all the
same -- fucking bitches.
You do everything for
them,and then they fuck you.
She's not worth it,all right?
You're better off without that cunt.
Don'T...
Talk that way about my girlfriend.
I'm dexter,and I'm not sure what I am.
Hi,dexter.
I just know there's
something dark in me...
And I hide it.
I certainly don't talk about it...
But it's there... Always.
This dark passenger.
And when he's driving,I feel...
Alive...
Half sick with the thrill
of complete wrongness.
I don't fight him.
I don't want to.
He's all i've got.
Nothing else could love me,not even...
Especially not me.
Or is that just a lie the
dark passenger tells me?
Because lately there are
these moments when I feel...
Connected to something
else -- someone.
It's like...
The mask is slipping...
And things...
People...
Who never mattered before are
suddenly starting to matter.
It scares the hell out of me.
Hello... Dexter.
That's all the time we have for sharing.
Would someone lead us
in the serenity prayer?
Lila.
I knew there was
something wrong with you.
The secrets,the
sneaking around --
Now it all makes sense.
A lot of cops have been where you are.
The booze,the drugs...
Makes the job go down easier.
Stay clean and stay out of my
way,we won't have a problem.
Oh,and you owe me a new
michelin,you motherfucker.
I have all your forms,so we'll do
what we can to bring your dad home.
I'm sorry. You don't understand.
I don't want him home.
Just tell me he's dead.
We need to know he's gone.
Right,you want closure.
I want peace.
He made our lives a living hell.
When he'd go to prison,it
was a blessing,but,uh...
You kept letting him out.
I need to tell my mother,my sister that
they're safe and that he's rotting in hell.
Call me when you can tell me that.
Lundy,wait.
I think -- I mean,it
could be a coincidence --
But there are two of them.
Two...
Missing people with
records -- prison records.
Interesting.
And who typically has a prison record?
I don't know.
Bad guys?
Bad guys.
- Do you think it could
be a - - a pattern?
Maybe.
We'll run all the victims'
dnaagainst the criminal database.
D.C.Lab is still open.
Come on. Let's get to work.
Dexter,what?
You were right.
I'm sorry to wake you up,but I had
to let you know that you were right.
About what?
The program.
It'S...
It's good. It's really good.
I... Am always so in my head.
But this --
it was... Good.
In fact,it's already
helped me a lot. Thank you.
Oh,I do love this car.
Yeah,I thought you might.
So,I will pick you up in an hour.
We'll go someplace nice for lunch.
- Oh,there's my sponsor.
- Really?Where?
The guy in the blue shirt?
No,next to
him -- lila.
- Bye.
I'm back.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly presents
Sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚