Subtitles by DramaFever
[December 1988]
[Seoul, Dobong-gu, Ssangmundong]
Oh!
Mr. Choi!
Where did you get such pretty gloves?
Wow... did a lady friend
get them for you?
I'm not crazy, right?
Those are actually pink, right?
Where did you get those gloves?
Taek gave them to me
as my birthday gift.
Wow... our Taek is so cool.
Wow!
He bought his dad such pretty pink ones!
Here's the weather.
A cold front is taking
over the entire country.
The middle region of Korea will be
around negative ten degrees Celsius
and in the Seoul region, it will go up to
about negative two degrees Celsius.
[Episode 8: One Warm Remark]
Do you two think that I'm an idiot?
No.
This time, it's for real.
Hey.
Isn't it obvious?
He's totally crazy about you!
Of course he is.
Hey.
Why else would he come all the way
to the McDonald's in Apgujung
from Ssangmundong?
He totally likes you!
Congratulations, Duk Seon.
You just got yourself
a boyfriend again.
Shut it!
Pipe down, already.
When I think about how humiliated
I was because of you two, I... geez!
Hey.
Also, what do you guys
even know about men anyway, huh?
If you rush to conclusions
one more time, I'll end you!
All right, already.
Hey, Joey Wang.
Your hair color looks nice.
What did you dye it with?
Oh, this?
Hydrogen peroxide.
What?
You did that to your hair?
Just get it done at the salon!
Hey.
Why don't you stay out of this one,
Ms. Rich Girl?
Us two, broke girls
are in the middle of talking.
Wow, Sung Duk Seon!
You know the English word, "talking?"
Are you kidding me?
Should I dye my hair
during winter break, too?
I have hydrogen peroxide at home.
Don't, don't.
Use something else.
My head hurts so much from the smell.
Really?
What should I use, then?
What else?
Duk Seon.
Where did you go this morning?
To meet the girls.
- What did you eat?
- Ddukbokki.
Why?
Did something happen?
Never mind.
What's with Mom?
Did something happen?
Apparently, 30,000 won
disappeared from her wallet.
So?
It wasn't you?
What does she take me for?
Where's the hair dryer?
Why are you digging through
someone else's wallet?
You call yourself
an older sister?
How could you doubt
your younger sister?
Here!
Happy?
Huh?
If it's not you, whatever.
It wasn't me, Mom!
It really wasn't me!
I didn't take it!
I don't even know
where you keep your wallet!
Why are you doubting me?
I really didn't take it!
Really!
Okay, Duk Seon.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Want a sweet potato?
Oh geez...
Does it taste good?
Yes.
But Mom...
Yes?
It might be No Eul.
He's the only one who
could have done it, right?
Even if he did,
don't say anything to him.
He'll feel hurt by that
and go down a crooked path.
He'll rebel because I suspected him.
Got it?
Okay?
What about me, then?
You're not worried about me
going down a crooked path?
Bo Ra...
Have some sweet potatoes.
What about me?
I'm only a year older than him!
I feel hurt too, you know!
Oh yeah.
Isn't today the day that Jung Bong
gets the test results?
Probably.
I wonder how he did...
We could have misheard.
I'll call them again.
I'm sorry.
You didn't pass.
I apologize.
I have nothing to say.
Geez.
It's fine.
You can just take it again. Right?
Geez, you're going to cause an earthquake
with your tremendous sighs!
What's on your head? Is it Sports Day?
Are you cheering for the white team?
Jung Bong.
Go to your room and rest.
You're being hospitalized tomorrow.
It's no good for you to be stressed.
Hurry!
Go to your room!
It's fine!
Chin up, okay?
Kim Jung Bong!
These things happen!
They call it an exam
because you might fail!
It wouldn't be an exam if everyone
passed every time! It's okay! Okay?
If only he wasn't getting surgery...
Even so, he grew up so well.
I'm thankful, even just for that.
You sure are hard to please.
Did you forget everything already?
No...
Honey, leave the house
for about two hours.
Go to Mr. Choi's
jewelry shop or something.
And what will you be doing?
The lady from Amore is coming.
Just go play outside for two hours.
Are you going to buy makeup again?
Just leave!
Okay, okay.
I'm going.
But why two hours?
Doesn't it usually only last an hour?
The woman from Jutanhak is coming too.
Oh.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I ate.
Where would I go, on a weekend?
No. I told you,
I'm not going.
You're going?
It can't be helped then.
We can just meet up next week.
Don't be disappointed that
I'm not asking you not to go.
I thought you were going because
you had something to take care of.
I told you, go ahead.
I'll be fine.
What?
Hurry it up.
I'm expecting a call.
Yeah.
Okay.
See you next week.
Who would you be expecting a call from?
Dong Ryong! We're going to watch
the Pop Top Ten together today.
When did you guys ever
call before meeting up?
Hello?
Oh, Hwang Hee Soo?
What's up?
Right now?
Hi, Bo Ra.
That's "hello" to you, punk.
Hello.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to see my boyfriend.
Oh, top-of-the-morning to you!
Greet me properly, damn it!
Yes, ma'am.
Sorry, ma'am.
Watch yourself, kid.
I will indeed watch myself, ma'am!
You like her, even when she's like that?
Not that attitude in particular.
Right?
You're human after all, too, huh?
What are you going to do? She says
she's going to see her boyfriend.
No, she isn't.
When she goes to meet her boyfriend,
she always wears a skirt.
But look.
She wore pants.
She just lied on purpose,
for me to hear.
Geez... that freak.
He freaks me out.
She's not human.
What is she then?
A daffodil...
Crazy bastard.
You've moved on
from Joey Wang, then?
Yeah.
Ji Yeon's the best.
She's not really my type.
Yeah, of course not.
What?
This bastard is into aggressive girls.
You know, strong girls and such.
Yeah.
You know, someone like Bo Ra.
What?
Well, that's plausible.
But I'll bet that even she doesn't
act that way in front of her boyfriend.
What do you mean?
Wow... you guys really
don't know anything.
All you know are formulas.
You know nothing about women.
No matter how much girls fool around
and do the crab-leg dance at home
she'll be on her best behavior
in front of the guy she likes.
If a girl fools around or does
the crab-leg dance in front of you...
that means that she doesn't
see you as a man.
If she did, she wouldn't be
act like that, no matter what.
She'd be too embarrassed.
Who is it?
I'm the young lady from Amore!
Sun Young?
This feels so good...
- Wow... thanks to you...
- This is great...
She does it the best.
It feels so nice.
Don't smile.
You'll get wrinkles.
Your skin is so good!
Maybe it's because you're
an affluent woman?
She's always had great skin.
Even so, she took such good care of it.
And it seems that
she never gets stressed out!
Well, figures, since
you live in such a big home.
What concerns could you possibly have?
Does it really seem like that?
Of course!
You look like such an affluent woman
who's never suffered once in her life!
Wow... I'm so jealous!
Does it really seem that way?
She really looks like someone
who's never suffered once in her life?
Yes!
- Wow... you've succeeded!
- I'll say.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing.
Oh yeah.
You're going to give us
a lot of samples today, right?
Of course! You bought all that makeup,
so of course I will!
Just give us 300 or so.
Oh, my!
- Rock, papers, scissors, shoot!
- All right!
I'm not good at making ramen, though.
[La Bamba]
Stop messing around. You make it every
day because of Jung Bong. Hurry up, go!
I'm hungry!
Hurry up!
Damn it...
Hey... it's been a while
since Taek's been home.
Ramyun won't do. Let's just order in.
Okay? How about it?
- I want ramen.
- You little...
Don't turn it on until I get back,
all right? I haven't seen "La Bamba!"
Hurry the hell up and go!
I've never been the same...
because I love my girl...
Oh yeah.
You didn't forget about tomorrow...
right, Taek?
Wow... look at you and
your selective memory.
You forgot, didn't you?
We're all going to see a movie
in Jongro tomorrow, remember?
I bought the tickets
at the theater in Jongro.
I stood in line for an hour!
I remember now.
I have a competition tomorrow though,
and it'll be late when it's over.
Hey, that's why we decided to see it
in the evening, in the first place!
Did you forget?
Oh yeah... you're right.
Yes, that's right, Master Choi Taek.
Do you even know where the theater is?
Yeah. I just have to go to Jongro.
The Dansungsa Theater... right?
Yes, that's right...
but just wait for us at the club.
We'll come pick you up.
It's fine.
You think I can't even find a theater?
- Yep. You can't.
It's on the way to the theater anyway,
so we'll come get you.
Don't take a taxi, get off somewhere
weird, and wander away again.
Got it?
Don't go wandering off,
and wait for me... okay, honey?
Hasn't it been forever
since you went to the movies?
Not since we finished
graduated middle school, right?
He went with me a while ago.
Oh, really? Was it fun?
What did you watch?
As if he'd know.
He slept through the whole thing.
He'd stayed up two nights in a row
before he came.
Who is it?
I'm the lady from Jutanhak!
What the hell is this?
I just tossed in
whatever was in the fridge.
That's how we make it at our place.
My older brother eats like this.
It tastes great!
Thanks.
When is his surgery?
This weekend.
He'll be hospitalized tomorrow.
We all have to go visit him there.
Which hospital is it?
No need for that... he's just
having a one-hour surgery.
You don't need to come.
One hour?
It only takes that long?
Didn't it take about ten hours last year?
He had to get new valves that time.
This time, they're just
changing the batteries in it.
What about his exam?
Did he get into college?
He failed.
Your nose is bleeding.
I guess winter really has come.
What if you're sick, too?
What are you saying?
He got a checkup,
but they said he's fine.
They said it was his immune system.
He and his brother have weak bodies.
Geez... I wonder how many perverted
things he saw for it to be this bad.
It's because of my immune system, okay?
Good for you.
You little...
Even so, I'll bet your mother
feels sad about it.
Even if it's a simple surgery.
Who?
My mom?
We're talking about Ms. Ra here.
- Wow, feels great!
- My face feels so soft.
Sun Young, look at my face!
How does it look?
You look beautiful!
Thanks!
You look pretty, too!
I feel like an affluent woman!
Wow... look at your hands!
Wow... they're so soft!
I'll bet this lady lives like a queen!
Why do you say that?
Your hands are so soft. It looks
like they've never touched cold water.
Isn't that right?
And you have no worry lines
on your face either!
I'm so jealous!
Oh my... even it's just flattery,
it's nice to hear.
What do you mean?
It's as clear as day, here!
But... you're going to give us
a lot of samples, right?
The young lady from Amore left us a ton!
Oh, of course!
I'll leave you a ton!
You bought so much at once, after all!
Just leave us 300 or so.
Let me see your face.
Wow, you're glowing!
No matter how I look at you
you're not the same person
you were three years ago.
Is there anyone who has
suffered as much as you?
Just ask anyone who has suffered
more than you to step forward!
Words can't express
just how much you've suffered.
Geez... yeah.
Strange things happen in life, huh?
I can't believe they'd say such things.
You suffered so much
when Jung Bong got sick.
Wow.
You're really a fighter.
You'd leave Jung Bong at home to go work.
You used to wallpaper
people's walls, right?
Well... yeah, I'd do that,
and I would deliver newspapers.
And I worked at a restaurant.
You're really incredible.
If someone told me my child had
heart disease, I'd pass out right there.
What else was I supposed to do?
He had to get surgery,
but I had no money.
I had to earn money any way I could.
There were times that my husband and I
starved for a day or two, too.
Wow... and you didn't even tell me!
You're really something!
It's not like I was the only poor one.
You two had it worse.
Well, yes.
Oh, yeah. What kind of surgery
is he getting this time?
Didn't he get a new valve
or something last time?
Yeah. He got that surgery last year.
Why does he need surgery again?
Oh, it's a simple one this time around.
There's a battery-like thing inside,
and they need to swap it.
It'll be about... an hour?
Two, if it takes a long time.
It'll be over quickly, then.
Yeah.
Wow... even so, if my child were
getting surgery, simple as it may be...
I'd be so nervous,
I wouldn't able to eat anything!
Why worry?
We have money now, so the best doctor
in Korea is operating on him.
There's nothing to worry about.
Wow... you're such a tough one!
That's how she managed to endure
during those hard times!
Otherwise, you would've
gone mad already, right?
Exactly.
But where's Jung Bong?
Where did he go?
Hey. We've heard all the songs
on the LP already.
Hurry up and spill it.
What is it?
What's so bad that
you can't tell a friend?
Bo Ra.
Yeah?
Um... about Jong Hoon...
Jong Hoon?
Um, no...
I mean, upperclassman Jong Hoon.
What is this?
Why are you referring to
my boyfriend so casually?
There's really nothing between us.
What do you mean?
Did something happen
between you two?
I felt that you should know,
no matter what.
On the day you couldn't go on the
retreat because of family issues...
I had a lot to drink that day.
I drank a lot, and upperclassman
Jong Hoon was really drunk too.
And so?
I went out for a bit
to get some fresh air...
and upperclassman Jong Hoon followed
me out, saying his head hurt too.
Did you two kiss?
I'm sorry, Bo Ra.
It was honestly a mistake!
The two of us were way too drunk.
We weren't in our right minds.
I'm really sorry.
I felt so bad, I couldn't even
look you in the eyes properly.
Even so, you're my friend, so...
you're my best friend, so...
I couldn't just keep quiet
and let it slide.
Bo Ra!
I'm sorry.
Really.
It's fine.
I'm not going to associate
myself with him anymore.
So don't cry.
And I'm not associating myself
with you anymore, either.
Friend?
As if.
Buckwheat jelly for sale!
No Eul, what time is it now?
I bet your dad is having
a drink somewhere again.
Geez... what a wretched fate...
My Il Hwa!
I'm home!
Hey. Your hubby is here!
You're at it again! You drank up a storm,
didn't you?
Geez... is that any way
to talk to your husband?
I really tried to come home early today
but there was something really important
to be done at the bank, so...
it couldn't be helped,
and I just had one drink.
Work, my ass! How is it that you have to
work overtime every single day?
And just what is that, now?
This is a liquid that erases ink!
It's the first time you've seen
such a thing, right?
So, uh...
I was taking the subway
on my way home
and I saw a kid,
about No Eul's age, selling these!
Oh my, oh my...
You know as well as I do that
I usually don't buy this kind of stuff!
But they said that this
really erases ink!
I would've regretted it if I didn't
buy it, so I bought just one.
And then... I bought just one more!
And then, just... three!
Wait a minute.
Where's the ink?
Let's just see.
It's okay!
I can just get it out
with this stuff!
Just watch! Just watch.
You take this here, and
do this, and then... this.
You just sprinkle it on here,
like so. Rub, rub, rub, rub!
And then, you just rub it in!
Like this! Rub, rub, rub, rub.
Rub, rub, rub, rub!
This is weird... it worked so well
during the demo on the subway.
Geez... you half-wit! Half-wit!
How can you call your husband that?
A half-wit? A half-wit?
What else would you be then?
You idiot!
Huh?
What does that mean?
I'm calling you an idiot, stupid!
How dare you call your husband an idiot?
Why I ought to--
Wow, what a saint we have here!
How many years ago
was your last promotion?
Why the hell are you
bringing that up now?
What does that have
to do with this liquid?
If you had performed
your wifely duties better
I would have kept on
being promoted by now--
Promoted, my ass!
My ass? My ass?
How dare you talk to me that way?
Yeah, you heard me!
If only... imagine you didn't
rack up all that debt?
Would we still be living like this,
in a half-basement? Huh?
Why are you bringing up
irrelevant things again?
I dare you to say that again!
I'll kill you!
What did you say?
What did you say you'd do to me?
Go ahead and try to kill me, then!
Go ahead!
- What are you doing?
- Go ahead!
You must be out of your mind!
Just try and kill me!
Are you... okay?
What do we do?
Can you see with that eye?
How many fingers am I holding up?
Try and count them.
I'll kill you...
What's all this, Big Bro?
This is my other half.
These are my Rubik's cubes...
And this is my stamp collection.
And these are my
Campus Music Festival LPs.
And these are all the
movie posters I've collected.
And this is... my journal.
I'll give you all of this.
I don't need any of this anymore.
Geez... quit overreacting!
Why are you making such a big deal
over an hour-long surgery?
Even so, surgery is surgery.
Big Bro.
They say that the chances of the surgery
failing are less than three percent.
I looked into it already.
The chance of getting heart disease when
you're young is less than two percent.
That's why... I'm so scared of
that three percent chance.
Geez...
Stop overreacting!
Big Bro! They say that it's a surgery
that doctors can do with their eyes shut.
Stop saying silly things
and go to sleep already.
Want to sleep with me tonight,
Little Bro?
That's a little...
Yeah.
I'm not too keen on it, either.
I'm home.
Oh, you're home?
Hurry and wash up.
Are you hungry?
I'm fine.
Oh my God, oh my God.
I'm totally hungry!
Want to eat red bean porridge?
Yeah.
Honey.
Do you want a bowl of
red bean porridge, too?
I do, indeed.
You must have been inconvenienced
by other household affairs...
When did you find the time
to make such a thing?
What's with your eye, Dad?
Did you get hit?
It's nothing, child of mine.
Mom threw a rock at him.
Do you want red bean porridge,
No Eul?
I'm good... ma'am.
All right.
Darling.
May I inconvenience you by
asking you for a glass of cold water?
Oh! Of course I'll get it for you!
Is there anything else you might like?
No, my lady.
Ah, yes.
I shall change the
charcoal briquette out tonight.
Oh my, I'm so thankful!
I'll leave it to you, then!
Don't stand the pillow up
like that, bastard.
If you could wait for me, my lady...
What's with them?
They decided to speak formally
to each other, starting today.
What?
Why?
They said they keep fighting because
of the way they speak to each other.
They say it's embarrassing
doing that in front of us.
This is more embarrassing, though.
Exactly, my lady.
Food's ready!
Time to eat!
Why don't any of you ever come out
the first time I call you?
What are you doing? Eat!
There's not much we're packing this year.
I stuffed the entire car
with luggage last year.
What's with this,
first thing in the morning?
Stop saying useless crap,
and eat already.
Bonggie!
Let's eat breakfast!
I don't want to.
Hurry and wake the hell up!
Don't ask me to make you something later!
Just eat with everyone else!
I don't think I can
stomach anything right now.
What the hell are you saying?
Hurry the hell up!
Mom.
We don't have pork cutlets?
We always have the same sides.
Just eat. Don't you complain
about side dishes either.
Honey, hurry over!
The soup will get cold!
Apparently, the two of them decided
to use formal speech with each other.
Isn't it hilarious?
Honey!
You must have waited for me.
You all should have eaten without me.
Even so, we have to wait for the
head of our household to eat first!
How long are you going to keep this up?
It's seriously embarrassing to watch.
Don't spill your food when you eat!
Who do you take after
that you're so sloppy?
Did you say that with the intention to
have me freaking hear that, my lady?
Oh, no!
Of course not!
Let's eat.
Yes, hello?
They're looking for Bo Ra.
Tell them that I'm not here.
Yes, she told me to say
that she's not here.
Yes, I understand.
They said they'll call again.
I wonder who our No Eul took after,
that he's a bit slow in the head?
Did you, by chance, say that to imply
he's stupid because he takes after me?
Now, now... of course not.
Shall we eat?
Yes.
You're done eating already?
Have some more, will you?
No. I'm going to sleep.
Don't wake me up.
Jung Bong.
You've already had two of these difficult
surgeries. Why are you so worried?
Don't you worry one bit, okay?
Yes, Father.
Jung Hwan!
Hurry over.
Thank you for the meal.
You got another nosebleed?
It's not like this is anything new.
It always happens when
I wash up with warm water.
You're going this afternoon, right?
Yeah.
You don't have to come, though.
Yeah. There's no place
for you sleep there, anyway.
Just stay home.
It's not a big surgery. There's no need
for the whole family to be there.
Yeah. Come tomorrow, Jung Hwan.
The surgery is on the day after tomorrow
so you can just come tomorrow.
Okay.
Taek should be done by now, right?
Yeah, he has to be.
Just look at the time.
I wonder if he won.
Isn't the competition today a huge one?
I'm sure he won.
Isn't it because he was confident,
he agreed to see it in the first place?
We're here.
I see the Baduk Club.
What time was the movie, again?
Hey, over here.
Hey, go and get Taek.
You have to hold his hand tight
so you don't lose him, okay?
Want me to come with you?
It's fine.
Master Choi!
You've worked hard.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's an honor, Sir!
Congratulations, Sir!
You've worked hard, Sir.
You've worked hard, Sir!
Hey, what about your bag?
You had it this morning.
Oh yeah.
You did it again!
What the hell do you do
with that brain of yours?
Hurry up and get it.
I'll get it for you, Sir!
No, it's okay!
He needs some exercise.
I'll be at the food cart over there.
Come over there, okay?
Okay.
Don't mope around!
Come straight there, got it?
Okay.
Then... goodbye.
[Korean University Hospital]
Jung Bong!
Let's eat!
There's a pork cutlet place
out front, so I got some to go.
Oh, good.
He won't be allowed to eat starting
tomorrow, so let's feed him a lot today.
I don't want to eat, though.
Stop talking nonsense
and get over here.
Mr. Kim Jung Bong.
- Yes.
His surgery is
the day after tomorrow, yes?
Yes, Doctor.
The surgery we'll be doing will involve
making adjustments to his
artificial heart's pacemaker.
You can just think of this as
a surgery to switch the batteries
on the pacemaker we inserted during
last year's cardiac valve surgery.
They last about five to ten years,
but there are some instances in which
surgery is needed, when they're placed
in less-than-ideal locations.
It's a simple surgery... right, Doctor?
There's no such thing as
a "simple surgery" in this world.
We have to open him up to know for sure.
But, even so... I heard that these types
of surgeries end in about an hour or so.
Even I, a doctor, doesn't know that,
so how would you know?
We'll only know after we do the surgery.
- Goodbye.
He could have spoken
a bit more kindly to us.
How could we ask him anything,
with him being so intimidating?
He's always like that.
He was like that last year, too.
And doctors always talk like that.
It's not exactly a new development.
Jung Bong, let's--
Hello?
Yes, are you looking for Bo Ra?
And who are you?
Oh.
Okay. Just a minute.
Bo Ra, pick up the phone!
They say they're your friend,
Park Jong Hoon!
But, um...
what relationship do you have with my--
Don't pick up his calls, Mom.
He's a crazy bastard.
Geez.
I feel like Bo Ra is irritated
about something lately.
I almost pissed my pants the other day
because of her!
She got into a huge fight
with her boyfriend.
Wow.
She has a boyfriend?
Yeah. But I think they'll break up soon.
Even so, who in their right mind
would like her?
You'd have to be a real piece of work,
that's for sure.
Jung Hwan!
Come sit over here.
No thanks.
We're almost here, anyway.
Where are you going?
To the waiting room.
I'm going to go watch some TV.
You go to sleep first.
Yeah, okay.
My Mi Ran...
You've gotten so strong.
You couldn't even
fall asleep in past years.
Now, you can even watch TV.
I'm not the same as I was back then.
This kind of surgery isn't even surgery.
I'll just watch the Drama Awards
and come right back.
Did Jung Bong get admitted
to the hospital already?
You don't need to go?
They said to come tomorrow.
Thinking about it,
it's been a really long time
since we've played soccer with him.
We used to play soccer with him so much,
up until the night of his first surgery.
Jung Hwan.
Wasn't it your dream in elementary school
to be a professional soccer player?
Because you were crazy about
Diego Maradona?
This punk was good at soccer
back in the day, too...
Geez.
He's sleeping so soundly.
I'm sleeping.
Okay.
Ugh, it smells!
When did you fart?
Damn it!
Ten minutes ago.
Just what the hell do you eat?
Do you smell it?
- Of course!
- I don't smell it, though.
- What the hell are you saying?
I don't smell anything.
Hold on.
- Damn it!
Why?
Just... why?
[Do Not Feed]
Isn't it about time for
Jung Hwan to be here?
I told him to bring my razor.
Big Bro.
- You're here?
- What about my razor?
Oh, here.
Geez... you're fine, right?
What's with you? You were once in surgery
for ten hours, and you were fine.
Where did you get such precious things
like pineapples and bananas?
Did you buy them?
Oh, Taek gave those to me.
He got them as a gift, and he
gave them to me to give to Big Bro.
He's not allowed to eat, already?
They just put that sign up now.
Wait here.
Let me go ask the doctor.
Yes, go ahead.
Um, excuse me...
where is Dr. Choi Hyun Sung?
What is it, ma'am?
Please tell me.
I have something to ask the doctor.
Oh, here he comes now.
Oh, hello, Doctor.
Um, Doctor...
My child's younger brother's friend
is Choi Taek.
He's a really famous Baduk player.
You've heard of him, right?
He sent pineapples and bananas
for my boy.
Couldn't he just have a little bit?
They only put the "Do Not Feed"
sign up a short while ago.
He'll fast as soon as he's done
eating this, I promise. Please?
Do whatever you want.
Excuse me?
I said, do whatever you want.
Did you get a nosebleed this morning?
Huh?
When did this happen?
How strange. I used to get nosebleeds
a lot too, around your age.
That's a really useful trait
you passed down to him, isn't it?
Give this to Jung Bong.
No, no thank you.
Jung Hwan, eat up.
What's this? You're giving up food
to someone else for a change?
You really are scared of getting surgery,
aren't you?
I don't have a good feeling
about this one.
Stop that kind of talk this instant!
They said it's a surgery that
even little kids handle well!
Stop spouting nonsense
and eat this banana, already!
Yes, Sir.
I'm expecting a call.
Hurry it up.
Oh, okay.
You're coming to our neighborhood?
No, I'll just meet you in front of
Sungshin Women's University...
Okay.
I'll wait for you
in front of the bus station.
Okay.
You have a girlfriend?
What school?
What grade?
A student should be studying!
Is this the time for you
to have a girlfriend?
I'm going to tell Mom!
Geez... I've only met her
a couple of times.
She's not my girlfriend.
I'm breaking up with her today.
She's not even your girlfriend,
so why do you need to break up?
She has one-sided feelings for me.
For you?
Why?
What's with this development?
You expect me to believe that?
It's the truth.
Just let me off the hook for today.
I'm going to take care of it.
You better take care of it
by today, got it?
Um... Soo Kyung.
I think we should break--
What the flying f--k!
That f--king scared me!
Hey.
What did you say, just now?
Nothing, I swear.
I thought I just heard you say
that we should break up.
Why?
- You don't like me anymore?
- No, I like you.
You little...
Do you take me for a fool?
Hey.
Even if we started on your terms,
we can't part on your terms, too.
What's with your hair?
I got a pinkle-perm.
This was seriously expensive!
Hey. Who cares if it's expensive?
It doesn't suit you at all.
You two have weirder hair, you know!
What's with you?
You dyed your hair again?
Yeah.
It cost a bit, too.
I knew you'd end up
doing that eventually.
It looks pretty.
- It's pretty, right?
- Yeah.
I used two bottles of
hydrogen peroxide for this color.
Really?
Way to go.
Hey.
Isn't that your younger brother?
Wow, No Eul!
You're hanging out with girls already?
Who are you ladies?
You know my No Eul?
Wow, you're so skilled, No Eul!
Wow...
How pathetic.
Really.
No Eul.
You don't want to come with us?
I'll buy you ddukbokki.
Hey.
No Eul has plans with us.
Please go on ahead.
Hey, No Eul...
are you crying?
Hey, you made my younger brother cry?
- Let go!
- Did you make him cry?
- Huh?
- Are you out of your damn mind?
Oh no!
Hey!
Spread the wings of adventure!
The Boy of the Sun, Esteban!
Open up the dictionary of youth.
There's no such thing
as "impossible!"
Let's follow the path that the horizon
has drawn for us, with the seagulls...
let's run with vigor
toward the faraway horizon!
Look like my daughter
is having a lot of fun!
Where are you going, Mom?
It's raining.
I have to go get the laundry.
It's cold.
I'll do it, Mom.
Just a moment, Jin Joo.
I'll be right back.
I'll do it.
Okay, then.
Oh yeah!
Let's run, let's run!
Good job, good job!
Let's talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
Even so... you can at least
hear me out, can't you?
Wow... they're all frozen solid!
It was a mistake, is all.
I drank way too much,
and I wasn't thinking.
The weird thing is... I only remembered
all of this after I woke up the next day.
It was a mistake.
Okay?
Okay, yes.
Mistake or not, it's my fault.
I know. I'm the crazy bastard here.
I really am...
such a crazy bastard... geez.
I'm really sorry.
Forgive me just this once.
If I ever do that again, I...
I'm sorry.
I really am.
Okay?
Will anything change
just because you're sorry?
A mistake?
You've never done such a thing
under the influence before.
I've never seen you do that.
I don't understand you,
and I can't forgive you.
I just can't rationalize what you did.
You call yourself a human being?
How could you do that
with my best friend?
Just let me go this once, already!
Hey, I said I was sorry!
How many damn times
did I say it already? Geez.
Wait a minute.
What qualifies you to be
so high and mighty, huh?
Are you perfect?
You never make mistakes?
Yes, that's right...
you are perfect.
Yeah.
You're smart.
You always have to be number one,
and you hate receiving help from anyone.
You rush home just because
your boyfriend got a little drunk.
And you act repulsed, like I'm an insect,
when I try to hold your hand.
Look!
Shit.
Do you even have emotions?
Do you?
I've never met a more inconsiderate,
cold bitch than you.
Really, you're the first.
Whatever.
Dating you, I felt so suffocated
that I thought I'd die.
I feel like I'm not dating a girl...
more like a hunk of ice.
If you don't fix that damn temper of
yours, you'll be alone forever.
You know that?
You're really the worst
a woman could ever be.
Whatever.
Wow... that guy really knows
nothing about you.
I don't need your pity.
You're a warm person.
And you're a good person.
[Winter, Two Years Ago]
Oh, Bo Ra's coming.
School's over, Bo Ra?
Hello.
Go inside.
Your mother should be there.
Okay.
Hey, just cry.
Don't hold it in,
and just cry.
At times like this, you're supposed
to just let it out, Sun Woo.
It's okay.
You can cry.
Hey.
Something's falling.
It's raining, Sun Woo.
Let's go inside.
I really hate getting caught in the rain.
Bo Ra.
Why are your hands so cold?
Because my heart is warm.
People with warm hearts have cold hands.
Let's go.
Coffee.
What about yours?
I only had enough money for one.
Um, Sun Woo...
I won't tell anyone else about this.
How did you read my mind?
I'm very interested in you,
that's why.
Hey.
I'm not in the mood for jokes right now.
But... what happened to your hand?
Oh.
I tripped.
Geez. Way to go, you klutz.
Ouch.
Doesn't it hurt?
I'll... go on ahead.
Oh, thank you for your hard work.
Where are my children?
Duk Seon!
Mom!
Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh my... my child.
What happened to you?
Oh my!
It must have hurt so much!
Who did this to you?
Huh?
It was you?
You hit my Duk Seon?
I got hit too, lady!
How dare you look an adult in the eyes?
And what are you doing here?
She's No Eul's girlfriend.
He must be out of his mind.
What did you say?
Sung No Eul!
Geez... just look at this girl's head.
Who, in their right mind,
would take her for a high schooler?
What's it to you, lady?
Wow... and just look at how she talks.
What is the world coming to?
How in the world
did your parents raise you?
Excuse me!
May we go now? I have to feed my kids.
I'm hungry, Mom.
You are, right?
That student's parents have to come too.
Both parents have to come and sign this
for them to be able to leave.
Oh my... look at her mother.
What's with her?
It's probably her stepmother.
I'm sorry.
I just got out of work.
I'm very sorry.
I'm Soo Kyung's guardian.
What's your relationship with her,
exactly?
I'm Soo Kyung's older sister.
What about your parents?
Our parents...
passed away last year in a car accident.
She lives with me now.
Oh... I see.
It was just a fight between kids,
so you don't need to worry too much.
Please sign here and take her home.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Get up.
I'm really sorry.
I should have taught her better.
I'm very sorry.
Oh... no... it's fine.
We're sorry.
She's actually a good kid, but
after our parents passed away last year
she hasn't been able to
deal with it properly, it seems.
I'm sorry.
She really is a good kid.
She's really not like this
on the inside.
What the hell are you saying?
Stop it, already!
Shut your mouth.
You did nothing right!
- Hurry up and apologize!
- I don't want to.
Hey!
Oh... oh, it's okay.
My kid did nothing right, either.
Geez... I didn't even know,
and you have red hair and all...
So I misjudged you.
Oh... my hair?
I'm attending cosmetology school.
I'm practicing right now, so my hair
and makeup are a bit over the top.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
Someone between us
has to earn some money, so...
Oh, I didn't even know that,
and... geez.
I'm sorry.
Oh, geez!
You have such a great personality.
So you two can live on well then,
since you seem so dependable.
Who was it? Huh?
Who laid their hand on
my precious daughter?
Huh?
Duk Seon! Are you okay?
Oh, look here.
Look at your damn hair.
You two did it, didn't you?
You two must have done it.
You two really look like a pair of
disgustingly delinquent punks, too!
How could two girls pick up
such bad mannerisms
and beat up
someone else's precious child?
Are you two gangsters?
Or part of a crime syndicate?
Did your mother and father
teach you to act like that?
Do your parents even know
you're living like this? Huh?
How dare you two...
Huh?
Honey.
When did you get here?
It seems that these two girls' parents
haven't come yet.
I'm curious as to why they're fine with
letting their kids be such thugs.
Shut your mouth already!
You're so annoying!
And that's the end of the
formal speech saga.
Their parents passed away
in a car accident last year.
And the older sister's hair is like that
because she goes to cosmetology school.
And Duk Seon is the one
who started it in the first place!
What the hell are you blabbing on about
when you don't even know their situation?
What do you mean, "blabbing... on"?
What the hell do you think?
You can't think clearly
without cooling your head, all right?
Jesus... how the hell can you
speak like that to your husband?
I guess you really must love to
humiliate your husband in public!
Want to go for round two right here?
Huh? Damn it!
You're so damn loud!
Be quiet, please!
What are you doing,
in front of these kids?
- Yes... Sir.
- I'm sorry.
Um, Sir.
I'm truly sorry.
I'll teach her to be better from now on.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, oh, oh...
no need for that!
I didn't even know anything, and I...
I'm the one who's sorry.
Oh my...
You bastard!
What were you doing while
your sister was getting in trouble?
Hello, there.
Who's the captain here?
Bring them here!
I'm the dean at Ssangmun High
and I heard that Ms. Sung Duk Seon was
badly assaulted by some shady characters.
So I came here to deliver
some divine justice.
What is this?
Who called Dong Ryong's father here?
Um... I felt a bit nervous
on my way here from the bank
and Dong Ryong's dad said he knew
a lot of people in law enforcement
so I made a small request...
Oh my God... what am I going to do?
Offending the other person's appearance,
their hair, and physical violence!
With all these offenses, we have
more than enough to put you behind bars!
Student, consider your life
officially over.
Please, stop it already...
And of course,
your expulsion is a given.
Mr. Sung.
No need for such deep sighs.
I have, with me here, an inspector.
He's my friend,
Detective Kim.
Say hello.
Hello!
Bring the police captain
out here, already!
I'm going to have a nice
one-on-one chat with him.
You two are dead today.
Goddammit... stop it, already!
Please, stop it, already!
I'm so sorry.
I'm extremely sorry
for the inconvenience.
Then, I'll be off now.
Oh, um... Inspector.
Thank you so much for coming
all the way here, in person.
This man isn't an inspector.
Excuse me?
He's the principal of our school.
His name is Kim Gum Sa. (Inspector Kim)
Your younger sibling's name is
Kim Pan Sa, right? (Judge Kim)
And what was your
younger sister's name, again?
Kim Jip Sa. (Deaconess Kim)
Then, we'll be going now.
Geez... he really does have a family
full of law enforcement officers.
I always wondered who Dong Ryong
took after. He's just like his dad.
I'm hungry.
Me too.
You are, right? Let's go home.
I made doenjang soup.
Goodbye.
Um, then... we'll also be leaving.
Come eat at our place.
Our house is right around here.
We can have dinner together.
No, thanks.
Hey, don't act all high and mighty.
Just come.
I'm so hungry, I could die.
All right!
It's not too good, right?
No, it's delicious! It's the first time
in a while we've eaten like this.
We only ever eat ramen.
Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
All right, all right.
Hey.
What did you use to dye your hair?
This?
No way you did that with beer.
Hydrogen peroxide.
Hydrogen peroxide? You can't
get that kind of color with that.
Three times.
You have to do it three times.
And you need to
give it sunlight for one hour.
Oh...
Damn girl...
Fix that hair color of yours first!
If you don't, I'll shave it all off
and ship you off to a monastery.
Why are you only saying that to me?
And you too, Soo Kyung!
What's with that hair of yours?
You have that beautiful hair
your parents left you
so why did you dip-dye it like that?
And take off that
ghoulish-looking makeup!
And wear nice clothes,
suitable for a student! Got it?
I'm going to check on you
once a week!
Got that?
Yes.
We'll have to move.
Um... I'd like more rice.
Oh, sure.
- No, I'll do it.
- No, no.
Hey, you...
why do you like No Eul, anyway?
- Big Sis!
- Shut it!
With a face like yours,
you could do a lot better.
You have really low standards.
He was the first one.
What do you mean?
First what?
The first one who told me
not to smoke.
He's the first one who
ever said that to me.
After my parents passed away last year,
people only said nice things to me.
Things like, "It's okay"
or "Everything's fine."
Or, that anything I did was okay.
But No Eul was the first one to
get mad at me and bitch me out.
And he was doing it earnestly, too.
I was really thankful for that.
Honey.
Go sign the surgery consent form.
Okay.
Let's go together.
We don't both need to go.
Go by yourself.
Okay.
Got it.
Hurry up and go to sleep.
Your surgery is tomorrow.
I can't fall asleep.
And why not?
Huh?
Are you scared?
A little bit.
Jung Bong.
I asked all the nurses here
this afternoon
whether or not there's a chance
that the surgery won't go well.
They said that there's
no chance at all. Really.
Have you ever seen me lie?
Also... I had ribs
with your dad for dinner.
Do you think I'd be able to
eat out if I were worried?
Neither of us are worried at all.
So... don't you worry either.
Hurry and get a good night's rest, okay?
What's wrong, my son?
You handled that other huge surgery
so well, too.
You're a strong person, Mom.
You're a strong person,
but your son has such a weak body...
and such a weak heart.
Why is my child weak?
You have so much strength,
because you take after me.
Do you think just anyone overcomes
such a difficult surgery, like you did?
Jung Bong.
That, in and of itself,
is an amazing feat.
You're a much stronger and greater
person that I am, honey.
Hurry and go to sleep.
I'm going to go watch some TV.
What are you doing over there?
Oh... Doctor.
Why are you still up?
I was watching some TV.
Ma'am.
You don't need to worry.
It's a very simple
surgical procedure.
It's quite easy.
It won't even take an hour, and it has
almost no risk factors whatsoever.
So please don't worry,
and go to sleep.
Thank you.
I... I just...
What's come over you?
You seemed to
bear it all so well up until now.
But, um... it's really nothing
to cry over.
It really won't take that long.
I'll make sure to
finish it within an hour.
Oh my.
You must have been
so worried up until now.
It's almost all over now.
You just have to overcome this one thing.
[Korean University Hospital]
Oh, Doctor.
It ended without a hitch.
- Oh...
- Thank you.
Thankfully, we adjusted the location
and he didn't lose too much blood.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
You've worked so hard!
You won't need to see me for some time.
I'll see you again
in ten years.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you so much!
- You've worked so hard, Sir!
Mr. Kim Jung Bong.
Mr. Kim Jung Bong?
Yes... he's almost completely
conscious now.
Jung Bong.
It's me, Mom.
Your surgery went well!
What a relief...
You've worked hard.
You've worked so hard.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't
give birth to you as a healthy child.
Why are you crying again?
Jung Bong!
They said your surgery went really well!
You don't need to worry!
They said that everything is fine now!
Okay?
Jung Hwan.
Yeah, Big Bro?
Your... nose...
Huh?
Is your nose okay?
Damn it... what the hell?
One's feelings can be put into words.
That's why just one remark
can give off warmth.
In this cold, harsh world,
the thing that allows one
to recognize the warmth that is present
in life, and makes it worth living
is not a wise saying,
or a refined, witty remark.
Rather, it is one warm remark filled
with one's raw, unrefined feelings.
[Brazil Ddukbokki]
Hey. Do you have a hole in your chin?
Why do you keep spilling food
all over the place?
Ew!
But, um... Big Sis.
Who do you think took
Mom's 30,000 won, that time?
How did you know about that?
I heard from Bo Ra.
It wasn't you?
Are you out of your mind?
Dad gives me plenty of allowance.
Really?
Who could it have been, then?
It wasn't Sung Bo Ra, or you.
Or me.
Then...
Just a moment.
[November 2015]
Who is it?
It's me, No Eul.
Okay!
No Eul's here?
Yeah. I told him I'd give him
some red ginseng.
Oh.
What took you so long?
Were you playing baseball again?
Big Sis!
Oh, Brother-in-Law.
Long time, no see.
Yeah.
Come on in.
Hey... how is it that you look
younger by the day?
What are you saying?
It must be tough,
living with my Big Sis.
Oh, please.
Hey... what's with your foot?
Did you get hurt?
Someone must have stepped
on his foot during baseball.
It looks like it hurts.
Oh, I'm fine.
Big Sis, give me my red ginseng already.
I left my car outside
without parking properly.
Big Sis.
Where are you going?
Who was it?
Lead the way!
How could they do this
to your foot?
Come on, Big Sis!
I'm not a little kid!
Do something
about that temper of yours.
How is it that your temper
has gotten worse than Bo Ra's?
Are you really okay?
Yeah.
Shouldn't he see a doctor, or something?
Oh, he definitely should.
Looks like he needs surgery right now.
I'll bet it'll take three whole hours
to recover from this.
Do you still see me as
seventeen years old, and in high school?
I'm turning 48 this year!
To me, you'll always be a high schooler.
Got it?
Okay, Big Sis.
How is it that you never seem
to get any older?
You look exactly the same
as when you were younger!
And how is it that you just
seem to get older and older?
He finally looks his age, is all!
It took me ten years to speak
informally to this punk.
Shut it.
He's still a kid to me.
As if.
He's like... 70.
I said shut it!
The kid will hear.
I already heard it all, though.
Don't listen to evil things, my child.
- Okay.
- Only listen to good things, okay?
Okay.
I won't.
I can't hear anything.
I haven't seen Jung Bong lately.
Did he go somewhere?
He went to a Buddhist temple.
Why, is he sick again?
Whoa!
Oh my.
She really has no fear.
Bo Ra... will be fine, right?
How dare you use
informal speech with me?
Do you know me?
Huh?
Hello?
Who is it?
Bo Ra.
Are... are you okay?
Oh, geez!
There's no set order
when it comes to dying.
Oh my god... what'll we do?
How could this have happened?
Isn't this world
just way too unfair?
They said they'll raise them.
How am I supposed to live now?
Then come eat with us,
at my place.
Okay.
Give that here.
Taek likes Duk Seon.
It has to go well.
What the...
so it's first love, huh?
What would you do without me?
Taek!
Subtitles by DramaFever