Subtitles by DramaFever
["I Bow My Head and Beg for Forgiveness"
- President Chun Doo Hwan]
Duk Seon! Isn't it time for
your father to be home?
- What time is it now?
- It's going to be a while.
- You want me to trim more of these, Mom?
- Yeah!
Duk Seon, I think Dad's going
to be late today.
It's a mess over there in Jongro.
- Abolish the government!
- Abolish it!
Geez!
Geez, really... You can't ever go around
doing things like that... okay, punk?
- Just study hard, okay?
- Okay. Yeah.
Thank you so much, sir.
Um... student. Come over here.
Take this and buy yourself
something delicious.
What are you doing? Hurry up and take it.
Okay... go home. Make sure you wash
up before you go home, though.
Go home.
Duk Seon, set the table!
I'm bringing the food over!
Okay!
Ow!
- Oh no! Mom, are you okay?
- Let me see your foot.
Oh my! Oh God... It's bleeding!
- Ouch!
- Get a band-aid!
I'm fine. It's nothing,
so go ahead and eat.
You're hungry, right, honey?
So why do you always
transfer at Jonggak Station?
Students are always protesting
over there.
What am I supposed to do then?
Other places are even worse off!
Between here and Jongro,
protesters are everywhere!
At any rate, it'll be difficult to
get the tear gas out of my suit...
Even my eyes are stinging.
Oh yeah. Where's Bo Ra?
She's not home yet?
Sung Bo Ra is quite
a busy individual nowadays.
Yes... that's right.
I guess she's really preoccupied
with studying nowadays.
Well, it's only to be expected,
since she's a college student.
You two... get your head in the game
and study hard like her, okay?
- I'm home.
- Bo Ra, you're home?
Come and eat. You haven't
eaten yet, right?
- Come on in!
- What's this smell?
Hey! Are you a protester?
Stop right there! Come over here.
Oh my... This little brat
is going around protesting!
Have you lost your mind?
You want to see me foam at the mouth
and die? Huh?
What's with you?
It's none of your business!
What... what did you say?
Of course it's my business, punk!
How dare an Education major
go around protesting?
Have you completely lost it?
You think I worked my fingers to the bone
so that you could go around protesting?
Bo Ra, hurry up and say you're sorry!
Are you crazy? Why should I?
What did I do wrong?
What? Look at this girl,
mouthing off at me!
Bo Ra... say that you
won't do it again! Now!
Geez! What do you know, Dad?
Bo Ra.... what about dinner?
Eat something before you
go to sleep at least!
I'll make the fried egg
that you like so much.
Fried egg, my ass! Are you crazy?
Crazy bitch. I won't even waste a single
grain of rice on that impudent girl!
How dare an Education major
go around protesting?
Oh my, oh my! Mother, Father!
It seems that this daughter of mine
is going to ruin our entire family!
You've really raised her well! Way to go!
I ought to kill her!
[The Populace's Outcry]
[The History of the Korean People]
[14:00, Garak-dong,
The Democratic Party Headquarters]
What? Bo Ra did? Bo Ra, that girl...
what if she gets taken away?
Geez... I don't know who she takes after
to be doing things like that.
It's fine! There isn't a college
student that doesn't protest nowadays.
All of them do it.
As long as she's not one of the ones
standing in the front, she's good.
She's right. You know, the ones
who go like this at the front.
As long as she's not one of them,
she's fine. Don't worry too much.
She's the type to make me worry.
Even though her father is
getting so worked up over it
she won't even think of apologizing.
Instead, she glared at him and
talked back to him. Geez.
Seeing that, Bo Ra isn't close
with her dad.
Isn't the eldest daughter usually
close to her dad?
No, they are close!
It just seems that way,
but that's not the case.
That girl, Bo Ra, is the problem!
Her father isn't the issue!
It's not like Bo Ra is the gentle type
or has any cute traits about her.
I much prefer Duk Seon, even though
she's often dead last in school.
Bo Ra, that girl... she's scary!
Even so, just watch.
Bo Ra is going to become
really successful one day.
She's not an average kid.
You can say that again.
She's really not a normal kid.
I don't want much. I'll just be satisfied
if she didn't get kicked out of school.
That young man seems to be
quite popular lately.
He's so handsome.
He's tall and has a great body.
- Who is he?
- That guy.
I bet a bunch of kids
are going to try imitating him.
I bet someone's going to
end up breaking something.
Nebok. (Undergarments)
Three... two... one... start!
Hey, Sun Woo. Can you
do it one more time?
Hey, where are you going?
Yes, he just arrived.
Get out of the way!
[Science]
Jin Joo, I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Jin Joo. Give me a kiss.
I think I'll get better soon
if you do that.
Jin Joo, "Run, Honey"
is on TV now.
Oh, yeah!
You leave too, Mom.
I just stretched a ligament. I'm fine.
Go do what you need to do.
Is there anything you want to eat?
Am I a kid? No, there isn't.
- I'm making beef bone soup.
- What?
- Beef bone soup.
- Geez... Mom!
Isn't there anything
else you want to eat?
- I'll buy you anything.
- I'm fine.
I don't need anything.
Can I have 300 won
worth of bean sprouts
and one square of tofu?
[2000 won]
That's 700 won all together.
Why not buy a banana?
I heard that Sun Woo got hurt.
- How much is one?
- 2000 won.
Geez... you should splurge a little
when your child is sick!
When will you ever buy it again?
Jin Joo! Mommy bought some bananas!
Really?
[Banana-flavored milk]
Can I have a sip?
It's that good?
What about your older brother?
Did you give him one?
- Yeah.
- Good girl.
Duk Seon... Go home for today. It's late.
You're worried about me,
even in this state?
He's not worrying about you.
He's worrying about himself.
You need to leave if he's going
to get any sleep.
Aren't you going home?
What are you two going to do
when I leave?
How's that any of your business?
Hey. Stop fighting, and leave...
both of you.
I don't even have any money, though...
Do I need to borrow from
Jung Bong's mom, again?
They say that when it rains, it pours...
When will the day come when I have
a thousand of these in the storage shed?
[Episode 5: Preparing for Winter]
Who ordered the charcoal briquettes?
- Me!
- Yes!
Yes! Me, me! We ordered them!
We're coming!
Yes!
Yes, over here!
Over here!
Closer!
Yes!
Here!
Yes, here!
I'll go get some drinks for you all!
I can't believe that
such a day has come...
Madam! Today's the day of the
charcoal briquette delivery, huh?
Yeah.
- Wow! How many is that?
- A thousand.
Oh my! You really seem
like a rich woman now!
How much did that cost?
I wonder if there will ever come a day
that I can have tons of these stacked up.
What are you saying? Up until
three years ago, I had to use firewood.
That's right.
Wow... you did have a time when
you were once poor, didn't you?
It hasn't been long,
but I forgot already.
- Oh yeah. Don't make dinner tonight.
- Why not?
I made abalone porridge. I heard
that Sun Woo hurt his leg.
Why did you go through the trouble
of making that?
Then, can I just have a little bit?
I'm expecting a guest tonight.
- Who?
- The kids' grandmother.
What? Why is that
nasty bitch coming?
How much is she planning
to upset you this time?
It's not like she's coming to see me.
She's coming to see the kids.
It doesn't even affect me anymore.
She treated you so badly after
her son died!
She said that you devoured
her precious son alive!
She didn't watch any of her words
and said so many crude things to you!
Is she nobility or something?
It's not like you owe her money
or something. Geez.
Geez... when I think of that day,
I get so angry.
Is she the only one
who ever lost her son?
She has no consideration
for her daughter-in-law
who became a widow at a young age!
She's the one who cut ties with you,
calling you an unlucky bitch.
So why the hell is she coming
to see you, now? Pisses me off.
It's fine! Why are you
getting so worked up?
It's frustrating to me as a bystander!
Geez... and you can't even say
a single thing to her, like an idiot.
Geez! So frustrating!
What good would it do
if I did say something?
It will just wear my jaw out.
It doesn't affect me anymore.
I'm going to think of her as a stranger.
But... is this what you're going to wear?
What's wrong with what I'm wearing?
You don't have any new clothes?
It's fine! Appearances
aren't important.
I don't feel embarrassed at all,
even looking like this.
I'm really not going to care anymore.
- Put this on.
- Can I?
Oh, how nice.
- Wait, it doesn't suit you.
- Stop it! I'm wearing it!
All right, then.
Sun Woo. If there's anything
you need, call me right away.
- Okay?
- Yes. Goodbye.
- You're out of rice?
- I'm going to buy some today.
- You should have--
- I'll take care of it.
Why is Sun Woo so skinny?
Compared to last time,
he's skin and bones.
You don't care about your children?
Also, you... you only have
those clothes to wear?
Look at you. So grim. Pathetic.
I'm sure any incoming luck would go
running at the sight of you. Geez.
And why is it so chilly in here? You
don't have any charcoal briquettes?
What if the kids catch a cold?
Geez! What exactly do you
do around the house?
Do you bring any money home,
or go to work?
After swallowing my son whole...
you receive my son's pension
and live in my house
and you can't even raise the kids right?
We're getting along just fine.
And I'm raising my son
just fine, too.
Don't worry about it.
How could I not,
when you're living in this state?
Are you doing this to spite me?
You want to show me just how much
of an unlucky bitch you are?
Huh?
What did he ever see in you?
What a terrible fate.
What crime did I commit in my past life
to be associated with you?
Geez.
Why do you have to say things like that?
You know...
I'm my mother's precious daughter, too.
If my mother knew I was subjected
to this kind of talk from someone
I'm sure she'd cry tears of blood.
At the very least,
for my mother's sake...
I won't sit by and listen to you
talk to me like that anymore.
Mother-in-Law.
Don't ever come here again.
Even if I have to shave my head, I'll do
whatever it takes to raise my kids well.
Even if I can't buy them
brand-name shoes
I won't let them starve
and will buy them pretty clothes
and will live a life that
nobody would consider shameful.
So... Mother-in-Law... Don't
ever come back here again!
Don't ever come back here
so that the three
of us can live in peace!
I won't ever agree to see you again.
Even if you come to see us,
I won't open the door!
You got that?
Buy the kids some clothes with this.
It's fine.
Did anyone say that this is for you?
I'm giving it to my little ones.
How dare she... geez!
I don't need it.
I'll clothe my own kids.
Goodbye.
I feel so much better.
What a load off my chest.
Sun Woo! Eat this before you go to sleep.
Jung Hwan's mother
made abalone porridge for you...
Geez. Stop sweeping
the street, already!
- Is it because you're lonely?
- Hello.
Hello. Oh yeah. Is Taek home?
Did he come back yesterday?
Yes. He came home yesterday.
- Dad, the hot water doesn't work.
- What?
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
Taek. You haven't had
breakfast yet, right?
No.
I made some abalone porridge,
so come and take some.
- I've put some aside for you.
- Thank you.
- You have a microwave at home, right?
- Yes.
Just keep it in the refrigerator.
Put some in a separate container
when you want to eat it and
heat it up with the microwave.
You have small bowls at home, right?
Not glass ones, but ceramic.
Put about two ladle’s worth
in a soup bowl, and...
It's fine. I'll call your dad.
- Go ahead. - Yes. Goodbye.
What brings you here
so early in the morning?
- Did you get home last night?
- Yeah.
- You didn't go to school today?
- Hey, today's Sunday.
- Oh.
- Geez... I'm so jealous of you, bastard.
Jung Hwan. Go buy one square of tofu.
Okay. Let's go.
- Thank you!
- Okay!
- Open your eyes, Special Unit.
- Oh... it's Taek. Hi, Taek.
Oh, hi. Did you not get any sleep?
Yeah.
Duk Seon!
- When did you get back, Taek?
- Last night.
What brings you here,
when you've hurt your leg?
Oh... Duk Seon, can I borrow
your Korean-English dictionary?
Mine? You came to borrow mine?
With that leg?
You don't have
a Korean-English dictionary?
Yeah... I don't.
Is that right? Well, yeah.
Hers is completely new.
It's better to borrow it from her instead
of spending money on a new one.
Shut it.
Is your leg okay?
I just stretched a ligament. I'm fine.
Wait here, Sun Woo. I'll bring it.
No, it's fine. I can walk that much.
- Hey, hey.
- Geez!
I'm fine!
I'm fine.
No, no... other side. Yeah.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine! Hey, watch the stairs.
Um... Mother.
The room is cold...
did the briquettes go out?
Your father put it out
early this morning.
I re-ignited it not too long ago so just
wait a bit. Jung Bong, pass me a dish.
Go back to your room.
Honey. The toilet's
clogged again.
Set the table.
Okay.
- Lower the volume!
- Okay. Mom, did you see the newspaper?
Geez... ow! Mother!
What? I'm bleeding!
Where?
Where? Hmm?
Honey, the steamed egg is overflowing.
Come quickly!
Turn off the flame then!
- Mom, this is yesterday's paper.
- I turned the flame off!
- Ow!
- It's still overflowing!
Hurry over here! Quick!
Ow!
Mom, what about today's paper?
Where's today's paper?
The egg is exploding! Hurry over!
You're not going to die!
Why do you only ever treat me this way?
Geez... I ought to...
Oh my. Did the sun rise
from the west today?
What are you talking about?
It's the first time I've seen
Duk Seon awake early enough to
eat breakfast on a Sunday!
Dad. I go to the
study room nowadays.
I have to head straight there
after breakfast.
Wow. I guess this daughter of
mine is studying now, after all!
How long have you been going there?
You never even told me!
Today's her first day. She
hasn't even gone once yet.
Don't you know that getting started
is half the battle?
Thank you for the meal! I'm
going to hurry over there now.
Dad. You didn't know that Duk Seon
has a chronic illness, right?
A chronic illness? What
do you mean by that?
What kind of chronic illness
does Duk Seon have?
[My Daily Schedule]
["Don't Sleep" Study Room]
A chronic illness?
What are you talking about?
What chronic illness does our
Duk Seon have?
"Falling-asleep-after-eating-itis."
It's been a while since
she's been suffering from it.
Speaking of which... has Bo Ra
been sleeping this whole time?
Where is she?
She went to school. She has finals
starting tomorrow.
She said that she wants to get a good
spot in the library, and left early.
What if she went out early
to go to another protest?
No! Why can't you trust people?
It's true. She took a bunch
of books with her.
Oh my!
That girl is so popular lately!
What's her name, again?
Lee Mi Yeon
(Plays older version of Duk Seon).
Wow.
How great would it be if
Lee Mi Yeon was my older sister?
How is she so different from Duk Seon,
when they're the same age?
Hey. That girl is the
same age as Duk Seon?
Yeah. She's 18, just like Duk Seon.
Someone looks like that
while others... ugh.
Hey, you bastard.
What's wrong with our Duk Seon?
In my eyes, Duk Seon is so much prettier!
Yeah. I agree.
Father, it's time for
the Cosby Show to be on.
I'm flipping back to this channel
when Little House on the Prairie is on.
Kim Jung Bong. Stop spilling
crumbs everywhere! Clean them up!
Honey, take your
feet off the TV!
It'll get dirty! Or put
socks on, at least!
Geez! What a bunch of animals.
I can't believe you lot. Move your foot!
Hello? Hi, Mi Sook.
Why did she go up to the mountains again?
It's not like chestnuts
are even worth much.
Okay. I'll come. Why isn't she going
to the hospital?
Just wait. I'll take her.
Okay... bye.
- Your grandmother sprained her ankle.
- Is she badly hurt?
I don't know. She won't go to the
hospital, so I have to go see her.
Let's go together. It's been a while
since I've seen my in-laws.
Stay here, honey. Are you going
to let the kids starve to death?
Okay. I'm going to be away
for two days.
If you want to live, heed my words.
Got it?
Underwear goes here. Undershirts go here.
Socks go here. Got it?
Here.
- The briquette has gone out.
- What do you do?
- Use a mini-briquette.
- Correct!
Look here.
What do you do when
the briquettes are stuck together?
- Kitchen knife.
- That's right!
This is beef. You just have to
saute this in the frying pan.
These greens are going to go bad,
so have them for lunch and dinner.
As for the salad and the black beans,
put them in smaller bowls.
Got it?
I have a question.
Can't we just order in?
Cook, damn you! I even made all
of the side dishes already!
Make sure you check the gas.
Make sure the water in the toilet
goes down all the way, or it'll clog.
And you have to eat the greens
by today, okay?
Also, Jung Hwan.
Use your hand to figure out how much
water to use when you're making rice.
- Up to here, okay?
- Okay, okay!
Hurry up and go!
I'm sure your mother is waiting!
Have a safe trip, Mother...
Geez. My feet won't move.
Oh yeah, Jung Hwan.
I ironed your uniform and your drill
uniform and put them in your room...
Hurry up and go!
Go! We'll take care of ourselves. Hurry
up and leave this block, already.
- Okay? Okay. Go!
- Oh, also...
Okay! Go!
Go!
Bye!
[Mayonnaise]
[Margarine]
[Sugar]
["Don't Sleep!" Study Room]
Hey. Hey, stop sleeping!
How many hours
have you slept, already?
If you're going to be like this,
go home and sleep.
- What time is it now?
- The sun already set, girl.
It's 7:00 p.m.
- What time is it now?
- The sun already set, girl.
It's 7:00 p.m.
I'm going to stop by at home for a bit.
Why? Did something happen at home?
It's dinnertime.
The protests against
the current ruling party
as well as the previous
president are continuing.
A group of students from Seoul University
consisting of approximately 400 students
protested for four hours
on the roof of the assembly hall.
at Garak-dong, in Songpa-gu
this afternoon around 3 p.m.
The students prepared...
Why are college students
doing this lately?
Geez. Don't they know how much they're
hurting their parents by doing this?
Geez.
Oh yeah, Duk Seon. You studied hard
at the study room today, right?
- Yeah.
- Good.
You know... I don't even wish for
you to do as well as your sister.
If you did even half as well...
just half as well
then I'll be so happy, I'll run around
the neighborhood 200 times.
Just look at your sister.
She worked so hard to get into college,
and yet she still studies so hard.
So make sure you come to your senses too,
and study really hard, okay?
- Okay.
No Eul, you... just have to
stay healthy. Okay?
What's wrong?
There is a warrant for arrest out
for 25 of those students.
The students occupied the rooftop
and shouted...
What do we do? Oh my God...
what will Bo Ra do?
I should go outside.
Maybe she's nearby?
What do we do? Bo Ra...
where could she be?
Oh, thank God. Oh my God...
Oh my... oh my.
Thank God you're safe, Bo Ra.
Thank God.
You little... get over here.
Get the hell over here!
Let me go!
- Stop it!
- Let go!
You crazy bitch. Are you actively
trying to ruin your life? Huh?
Will you finally come to your
senses after I pass out? Huh?
You, if you get arrested while protesting
you're going to be blacklisted forever.
If you get yourself blacklisted
on our family registry
you're going to be taking our entire
family down with you! All right?
It's not only your life you're ruining.
Your mother. What are you going
to do about your mother?
Your mother, who believed
only in you for your entire life...
how will you make it up to your mother?
Huh? Your mother!
You think your mother will be able
to live properly if that happens?
Huh? Do you think so?
And yet... and yet, you
still choose to protest?
No Eul. Get me the scissors.
I'm going to cut off all her hair
so she can't set a single foot outdoors!
Hurry up and get it, bastard!
Bo Ra. Hurry up and say you're sorry.
Tell your father that you're sorry!
Why should I? What
did I do wrong?
What the hell did this bitch
just say to me? I'll kill you!
Honey, please!
She won't do it anymore!
You seriously believe that? Huh?
Forget school. Go to your room
and stay there. Got that?
Until you tell me that you'll never
do it ever again and apologize to me
don't you dare take a single step
out of your room.
Got that? Also... honey!
Until she apologizes don't you dare even
give her a glass of water. Got that?
Hurry up and apologize! Sung Bo Ra!
I didn't do anything wrong.
What the hell did you say?
Get the hell back here!
Honey!
Heed my words. All right?
If anyone even gives her a glass of water
I'm going to flip
the whole house upside down!
Don't you dare give a damn whether
or not she dies. Any of you.
- Got it?
- Okay.
Don't give her anything.
Don't you dare.
That damned girl.
We sacrificed so much for her.
Even though we scrimped and saved
when it came to our own things
we never hesitated to give her the best.
I wanted to treat her
like the smart and precious child
that we told everyone she was!
We poured so much into her...
that ungrateful wench!
She's aware of all that, and yet she has
the gall to do this to her parents?
Huh?
I heard that all of her upperclassmen
were captured already.
What if they take Bo Ra
away, too?
What if she gets a criminal record?
If so, then all of Korea's college
students will have criminal records.
Don't worry.
And even if she
does get arrested
she just has to write a letter of
reflection to be released right away.
What's that?
Geez... it's basically a document
saying that you're sorry.
It's this thing you write
to formally apologize.
If she just writes that,
she'll be released right away.
Damn it! She's done for! My older
sister is Sung Bo Ra, okay?
She'll never say that
what she did was wrong.
- You know how she is.
- All too well.
But you said that she made it home.
Then she'll be fine.
- Oh, you're here?
- Yeah.
What are you two doing
by yourselves?
- What?
- What are you two doing?
What do you mean, bastard?
We're just conversing here.
You know, talking. Talking.
What's with you? I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
- To the study room.
What?
Apparently, she's been
going to the study room lately.
Hey, do you know what time it is?
The sun set already.
I'll be back before 12:00 a.m.
I'm someone who has willpower, too.
Hey, even though your face
can be considered a lethal weapon
walking around past midnight
is dangerous.
Just give up on college.
Like me.
The study room is right there.
I'll be back before 12:00 a.m.
Bye!
Bye, friend!
Yes, this is Master Choi Taek's home.
Yes.
Who was that?
Kyu Won?
Your dad.
Huh?
He says he's hungry, so he wants you
to hurry over and make him dinner.
What the hell is this?
My younger brother.
Grandfather once said,
"All things expand and shrink."
If you have hot water on the bottom
and cold water on the top
the two different temperatures work
together in harmony to do this.
We can make them come apart like this.
My son.
Shall your father lend you a hand?
Dad, this is burning!
Wow.
It's cold over there.
Come over here and sleep.
Don't you worry whether I die or not.
What if she leaves in the
middle of the night while I'm sleeping?
I'm going to guard this door
no matter what
so go ahead and sleep, honey.
Speaking of which,
Duk Seon still isn't home?
It's almost midnight!
She should come home earlier!
Did she fall asleep?
I'm home!
Hi, honey. Come home earlier.
Okay.
- Sun Woo! Breakfast!
- Okay!
Mom, we're eating in here?
It's okay. We can eat in the living room.
It's warmer in here. So nice.
Let's eat in here.
- Mom, why aren't you eating?
- Hmm? I will.
We don't have a lot of side dishes.
I should make you some meat dishes...
Oh... it's fine! I don't even
like meat that much.
It's delicious.
Who is that? It's so early.
Yes?
Mom! What is it?
What?
Is he badly hurt?
He was probably not watching his
step, as usual... which hospital?
You don't need to! I can
take care of him! Geez, Mom.
You have to hurry up
and get Tae Soo married, already!
What?
You're... coming to my house right now?
You're at the terminal?
You're getting off in Seoul now, Mom?
I have some things to give you
and I wanted to see Sun Woo and Jin
Joo so I'll be dropping by for a bit.
It'll only take me 30 minutes
to get there by bus.
You don't need to come and pick me up!
I'll take a taxi and I'll be right there.
I'll just drop by for a bit and just have
a glass of water before I go.
You don't need to worry. Not one bit.
See you soon!
You're not going to work today, Dad?
He's taking the day off.
He's doing it to make sure Bo Ra
doesn't escape.
Even so, we should feed her, at least.
She didn't even have dinner last night.
I told you, no!
Until she gets on her knees
and apologizes, I'm not budging.
I worked so hard to send her to a good
college and this is how she repays me.
She won't come to her senses
unless she starves.
Don't you dare sneak her anything.
Got it?
Dad. The briquettes went out.
No they didn't. I just changed it
early this morning.
It's way too cold.
The fire's fine.
What could be the issue?
Grandfather once said this.
There are two different types of
briquette boilers.
The type that uses the briquette
as a direct source of heat
and the type that uses briquettes to
heat water, which in turn heats rooms.
The type that our home uses
is the latter.
If the briquette is fine
but the room is still cold...
in that instance, the issue lies with...
this.
The possibility that this tank has
run out of water is close to 100 percent.
- Oh.
- Ah.
Jung Hwan. What's for breakfast today?
Oh. It's your favorite.
Is it, perhaps... ramyun?
I need something to put this on!
Hurry!
Aw, yeah! What about Dad?
Dad!
Have breakfast!
Children. The toilet
is clogged again.
Oh geez. I just lost my appetite.
I tried using the plunger,
but it wouldn't work.
Grandfather once said this.
If the floor is full of feces,
you have to lower the pressure.
I have a good feeling about this one.
Stop spouting bullcrap
and do something about this.
Then, I'll leave the rest to you.
Thornton.
Sun Woo! Your grandmother is coming!
It's an emergency!
Change into something else
and clear the table! Don't eat!
Here, this one. Wash your face first!
I have to go to school, though.
Oh... yeah.
I'll use only a little
and give this right back!
These, too!
Jung Bong! Can you help me?
Oh... oh geez.
Oh my God, you scared me!
It is finished.
Jung Bong, thanks so much. I'll
put everything back later.
You can take your time with that.
Wow... I think this is
pretty much perfect now.
I won't be caught at this rate, right?
These are sesame seeds,
and these are senna seeds.
Make it into tea and give it to Sun Woo.
I heard it's good for one's health.
Mom. They sell this stuff in Seoul, too.
Why did you bring it here?
Oh, geez.
- Mom, also...
- Yes?
Eat something before you go.
I called Tae Soo and he seems fine.
Things like that happen
when you're a cab driver.
You can take your time
heading over there.
No. I have to hurry
and go there.
Jin Joo!
Granny's going now!
Already?
Mom, it hasn't even been 10 minutes
since you got here! Stay a bit longer!
Oh, geez... what good would it do
for me to stay here any longer?
Oh my.
I'm just getting more worried about you.
Don't come outside to see me off.
I'm leaving now.
Mom! You should stay a bit longer!
Geez! You really don't listen!
Where's your bathroom? I kept
drinking so much juice, so...
Over there.
I told you, go back inside!
You're in such a hurry!
- Oh, hello, Sun Woo's grandmother!
- Yes! How are you?
- You're doing well, right?
- Yes.
You're already leaving, ma'am?
My son hurt his leg, so I have to
go see him at the hospital.
Then... I'm off!
I'm leaving now!
Have a safe trip home, ma'am!
- Thank you!
- Bye, Mom.
She came here for the first time in a
while, but didn't even stay the night?
She came here because
of your brother's leg injury?
- Is he badly hurt?
- I don't think so.
She probably just came to
see how I was doing.
She was probably curious
about my living situation.
She worries that
I don't eat properly and such.
She thinks that I'm not aware of that.
Is that right?
Madam. Look at me. I've been doing all
sorts of crazy things since this morning!
But I didn't get caught!
- Oh yeah. Is Bo Ra okay?
- No, she's not okay.
Her father didn't even go to work today
because he's watching her like a hawk.
Geez! She didn't even have anything
to eat... I'm so worried about her!
- Eat.
- Oh... put it here.
Oh my. That's all the side
dishes you have for me?
Yep. Just eat.
You should have made me
a fried egg, at least.
We don't have any eggs!
Anyway... what about you?
You're not eating with me?
You think that I could eat at a
time like this? How inhumane.
- Oh!
Bo Ra's mother!
What are you doing outside
on such a chilly day?
Geez... my heart feels so heavy,
so...
Jung Bong's mother hasn't come back yet?
No. She's coming back tomorrow.
I guess it's a vacation
for the guys at your place.
The house is a mess, right?
No, that's not true.
We're getting by so well.
It's just that we don't do housework...
but when we do, we're good at it.
I see.
You should put some socks
on, at least. Geez.
- You made alcohol out of ginseng?
- Yes!
When else could I drink it,
except when my wife is gone?
- My husband is home today, too.
- Oh, really?
- Then we can have a drink together!
- Yes!
There's no use in
getting your kids educated.
Even if you get them to study hard,
they act like they're hot shit
and do whatever they want.
Even so... I wish Jung Bong
could be half of what Bo Ra is.
He's my child, but... this kid...
I'm so worried about him.
Because my wife and I had
a soft spot for him
we just let him do as he wished, but...
I'm really worried about him.
Speaking of which...
is Bo Ra okay?
I'm not eating.
Eat already!
Are you planning to starve to death?
I'm not hungry and I have no appetite.
Just have one spoonful.
Just have one spoonful  and sleep.
I made your favorite. Just have one bite.
I told you, I'm not eating!
Leave me alone!
Just one spoonful, Bo Ra!
Okay? Just one.
Then... I'll leave it here. So eat it
later whenever you want to. Okay?
If you don't want to eat now,
eat later, at least. Got it?
Jin Joo! Oh, geez.
I have to wash that again!
Seriously...
Okay. Your arms.
- Whose daughter is my little Jin Joo?
- Mommy's daughter!
Oh, my child! Jin Joo, what do you want
to eat? What should we eat?
Banana.
Banana? You had that yesterday
too, though.
Banana!
Okay. I'll go buy some later.
Go to your room. Good girl!
To my kind and beautiful daughter
I don't have much money,
so I couldn't put in a lot.
Buy some pretty clothes
for yourself, my daughter.
My daughter, whom I love so much...
don't live life with your head hung low.
You've done nothing wrong!
Make sure to take care of your health!
Geez. Mom... really...
When did she leave that?
I can't believe her.
Honey, your laundry...
Oh geez. Way to go.
Sun Woo's mother. Have you see Bo Ra?
No, I haven't seen her.
Why, she's not home?
Oh geez... where did that girl go?
No, I haven't seen her.
She didn't come by here.
Okay.
Taek's father. Did you see Bo Ra?
Did she pass by here?
No, I didn't see her.
- Oh my... what do I do?
- Ma'am!
- Here.
- Thank you.
Sung Bo Ra. That's you, right?
Freshman, Math Education major
at Seoul University.
You're student Sung Bo Ra, right?
You know Ko Heung, right?
Student body president
at Seoul University.
He's your leader, isn't he?
Did you participate in the protest
at Garak-dong or not?
No, I didn't. I didn't do it.
Look at this bastard.
Cooperate and come with us
while we're still being civil.
Bo Ra!
Bo Ra. My daughter isn't the one
you're looking for.
You can't take her away.
Um... Madam... Do you know
what kind of daughter she is?
She's the smartest kid
in the entire neighborhood.
She's even smarter than
the kids from rich families!
She could have went to Seoul
University's law school
but she wanted to get a scholarship
to she settled for the Education major.
Her dream since she was young
was to be a prosecutor or a judge
but she didn't want to burden
her parents financially, and settled.
You know Seoul University, right?
It's the university that only accepts
the smartest kids in our country!
She was never tutored or went to a cram
school, but she got in on her first try!
That's the type of daughter
that my daughter is.
Do you know how many days
our neighborhood celebrated?
Even her father's company
sent flowers as a congratulatory gift.
Also, when she was graduating
high school...
she got an award from the principal
as the student representative!
She also made the top ten when it
came to her Suneung (Korean SAT) scores!
Her uncle is a provincial governor
and she's close enough with
him to have dinner with him!
and one of her cousins
is going to medical school now!
Also, also... do you know
about her father?
He worked so hard for 20 years
that he received an award
from the president of the bank!
He even had dinner with her, and wow...
he said that there couldn't be a smarter
or kinder daughter in the world.
The president even gave her
some spending money!
And he even drove her all the way home
in his personal car!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry
for what I did.
Bo Ra! Don't say such nonsense!
- What I did was wrong!
- No, no, no!
My child would never do that!
My daughter isn't that kind of child!
I said, what I did was wrong!
I'll go to the police station.
No, Bo Ra! You did nothing wrong!
My child isn't that kind of child!
- Let's go.
- No.
Let's go.
I told you, my daughter
would never do that!
- Please let go, ma'am.
- Let go! Let go!
My child isn't that kind of child!
Sometimes, I felt like my mom
was an embarrassment.
There were time I couldn't understand
why she seemed to have
self-consciousness or a sense of pride
and got angry.
I didn't realize it then, but it was
because there was something precious
that she wanted to protect
more than herself.
And that it was because of me.
When true love manifests it doesn't allow
one to be concerned over one's pride
and causes one to cast it aside.
That's why mothers are strong.
Mom, I'm home!
Oh, my child!
Jin Joo! How are you?
- Did Jung Hwan drop you off?
- Of course.
I didn't come home drenched,
which is a relief.
- I'm going to go wash up first.
- Okay.
Hello?
Tae Seok. Are you okay?
Geez, you... you're so old,
and yet you're still bothering Mom.
How are you going to get by without Mom?
Is Mom awake? Put her on the line.
Hello?
Mom.
Sun Young?
Oh... hello?
Why did you give me the money?
Mom!
They say that God created mothers because
they can't be everywhere at once.
Even when one is at
the age to be a mom
one's mother is always one's guardian
and even saying the word, "Mom"
is something that has the power
to tug at one's heartstrings.
Mothers are always strong.
Is Bo Ra okay?
Well... they're letting her
off with a warning.
What a relief.
That's good, then.
It'll be okay.
Speaking of which,
they should be coming out soon.
Didn't you say that you quit smoking?
It's okay.
Just give her a stiff punishment!
Sit her down and give her a scary look
and strike fear into her heart!
Geez. Why should I do that? It's
not like she committed a crime.
How could I make her
get on her knees and yell at her?
Banana.
Okay. The biggest one is for Jin Joo.
And, this one is for Mom!
No, it's okay.
I'm not going to eat.
You eat it.
Geez... then, I won't eat it either.
Let's throw it out.
Okay, okay! I'll eat it!
Is it yummy, Jin Joo?
I'm home!
What should we do about dinner?
What about Dad?
Yeah. What about dinner?
I'm hungry. Okay. Hurry over.
I used all the leftover side
dishes to make fried rice.
I put dumplings in it, too.
Hello?
Who was it?
Mom.
She said she just arrived
at the terminal.
Did you clean it?
What are you doing?
Hurry up and clean!
When did anyone play badminton?
What about the charcoal briquettes?
You didn't let it go out?
Of course we didn't.
It's nice and warm.
What about laundry? It's raining.
You forgot to get the laundry
from the clothesline, right?
We collected it all. Jung Bong collected
them, folded them, and put them all away.
Honey. See? I told you we'd be fine. We
were totally fine without you here!!
Don't you worry about us! Okay?
Aren't you hungry?
I made the dumpling soup that you like.
I'm fine. You have some.
Since it's raining and all,
want to have some soju?
It's time to go to sleep... what soju?
Drink by yourself.
Should I make some kimchi pancakes
for you, then?
It's fine! Go and watch TV.
Why? Why do I feel uneasy?
I guess something at home is a mess.
No way. We cleaned everything.
We cleaned, did the laundry,
and did the dishes perfectly.
We even changed all the briquettes
and ate all the side dishes
she told us to eat.
I'm sure my mom was shocked, too. She
doesn't even have to lift a finger.
I see.
- Um, Jung Hwan.
- Yeah?
[Happy Ramyun]
What?
Mom, Jung Bong burned his hands!
Geez, I can't believe you!
How old are you that you can't
even make ramyun properly?
Geez! They're stuck again.
A scissor...
Mom! Dad broke the
briquettes again!
Geez... geez! Way to go! You can't do
anything right! I can't believe you!
Geez!
Mom! Have you seen my shorts?
Geez... geez, geez, geez!
Right here! You can't even find this?
I didn't see it.
Geez! What would you
all do without me?
Nobody can do anything properly.
Let's eat together.
What kind of dumplings are those?
Kimchi dumplings. The ones you like.
And soju!
If you really want to, I guess.
I'm forcing myself to eat
for your sake.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's go!
Hey, Jung Hwan.
You don't understand
why your mom's in a bad mood?
No.
It's because the family
is doing way too well.
You all were doing too well without her
for her liking.
- Let's make a toast! Cheers!
- Cheers!
It's been a while!
What do you mean, it's been a while?
It's only been two days.
Wow! Really... without you
around, I realized something.
What?
Us men are garbage without
you, honey. Okay?
When one is at the age when
one can console one's mother
it's when one has matured past being
able to say "Thank you" and "I love you."
If one wishes to make one's mother happy
the words, "Mom, I need you,"
are more than enough.
[Duk Seon's. 3 years of bad luck
to anyone who touches this.]
Damn.
Damn it!
Stop walking around so late.
- Where are you going?
- To get some batteries!
Hi!
Hey, why do you keep coming
back here, with your leg like that?
It's almost done healing.
What brings you here?
Oh... I came to borrow a sewing kit.
- Are you going somewhere?
- To get some batteries.
I have some.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Let's go to my house.
I'll give you some of mine.
Hello!
Oh, hi!
You're here, Jung Hwan?
Hey, I need to use the bathroom.
Go to my room.
Okay.
Wow... look at this guy...
he has everything in alphabetical order.
What a freak.
[Duk Seon's. 3 years of bad luck
to anyone who touches this.]
Look at this. It
looks brand new.
[11665 Sun Woo]
Do you want something to drink?
[Sewing Kit]
Subtitles by DramaFever
I have someone I like.
I think he'll do it soon. I feel it.
Geez... it's about time
that he called already...
Your head's going to roll off
your shoulders while you're waiting!
Duk Seon. Do you want me to
make you another ramyun?
Ugh... bastard.
Sit.
It's fine.
I have no interest in hearing about
other people's love lives. Bye.
I think it's going to be hard
for Taek this time.
I don't think he's in a good state.
Even when it comes to Baduk,
he's wary against strangers.
Want to bet?
He'll come! You'll see!
Duk Seon!
On the day of the first snow.
Confess on the first day
that it snows, okay?