[November 1988]\NDownload HD Videos and English sub from Dramatorrent.net
Duk Seon!
You'll be late for school! Hurry up!
Okay!
I'm off!
[City Bus Ticket]
[Middle and High Schooler's]
I'm off!
Do you want me to drive you?
It's okay.
I have a car too.
A car?
Hi, Air Jordans.
I'm off...
Nobody's home, right?
I know. Yes.
Oh yeah, my backpack.
Mister!
Hurry up and go!
Damn it!
Here! Take it!
What the hell?
- Come through!
- Sorry!
- Come on!
- I'm sorry.
Geez!
Mister, go!
Should I just go back home?
[Episode 4: Can't Help-ing]
I want to go to college.
Crazy girl. You must be out of
your damn mind. As if.
I'm going to study, starting today.
Get me a tutor.
What... what tutor?
Your older sister goes to
Seoul University!
You can just learn from her
instead of wasting my money!
Learn from your sister.
[Three Years Ago]
Transfer it.
Move everything except for "x"
over to the other side!
Oh.
2x equals...
Six minus eight.
Geez.
Are you certain?
Hey, you idiot!
I told you to negate the number when
you move it to the other side, didn't I?
Yes, ma'am.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Are you hollow?
Do you have nothing in there?
This is for first-year middle schooler's!
First-semester first-years, no less!
Even if you're that much of an idiot,
how can you not even solve this?
There's something
fundamentally wrong with you.
Everything is a joke to you.
You have nothing you're serious about.
You always have
a dull look in your eyes too.
Jesus Christ.
What I'm saying is,
focus more on an everyday level.
If you're dumb,
you should at least try hard!
Do you think living life
is that easy?
You know, the thing stuck
to your neck. Your head.
Why do you carry that around?
Don't just use it for styling your hair.
Use it to study for a change!
Use your damn head!
Even if you're an idiot, you can
at least memorize things!
Don't try to understand it...
just memorize it!
Got it?
Geez, you idiot!
Damn it.
My chest hurts.
If learning from her means life or death,
I'll take death.
I'm going to go to the
study room from now on.
Mom. Her issue is
her lack of concentration.
She can't last ten minutes at a desk.
I've never even seen her sit at a desk.
But you know, I've heard...
that there is something that
works wonders for concentration.
What?
Just consider yourself lucky
that you have me as a father.
Also, know what a huge blessing it is
to be living on this block.
You must be busy.
Sorry.
Do you even know how to play Baduk?
Go first.
Do you want to eat ramyun?
Do you want me to make it?
Wow! Why did you go through
all the trouble of making this?
I bought them because they were on sale.
I just bought an entire box.
Hurry up and eat,
Bo Ra's father.
Yes.
My husband never eats this at home.
How should I eat this?
You just take this in
your hand and eat it.
We just started having croaker recently.
Wow... Jung Bong's mother
really is a saint.
How could you be so generous, to share
something so precious and expensive?
I'd feel like there was barely
enough to feed my own family...
Oh my... oh my...
Oh my. It's so chubby.
Just look at how much meat is on here.
Wow.
I could just die right here!
It's delicious!
I heard Duk Seon is
learning Baduk as of late?
I did hear that Baduk is good for
increasing one's concentration.
Baduk must be difficult for her.
She probably won't last too long.
Hey, how can you say that?
What do you mean,
she won't last long?
I bet she already gave up on it
without lasting a full day!
I know I shouldn't talk about
my own daughter like this...
but she really has no talent
for studying.
But, you know, I heard
something else too.
I heard that Baduk really is that good
for increasing one's concentration.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you eating?
Get some more rice for yourself. Geez.
Want to switch?
I'll open it for you.
You do this.
Wow!
Here!
Here.
Work on that.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Dear!
Is Jung Bong studying well nowadays?
There's less than 50 days
before exams, right?
Three... two... one.
Start!
Got to get some
fermented soybean paste...
Oh! Where were you off to,
so early in the morning?
Today is my wife's birthday!
I'm making her seaweed soup.
I'll be heading inside then.
You bastard!
I'll kill you...
Sorry...
I'm off!
You know that we're
eating out tonight, right?
Come home early.
I'm going to be studying
until late though.
But today's Saturday...
You want to die?
I have to be home by 5 p.m., right?
What's with your shoes?
What? Why?
What?
Can't you tell?
They're Air Jordans. Why?
You'll get caught by
the Leadership Team with those.
Don't you know that, idiot?
Sun Woo's been on the Leadership Team
since last week, idiot.
Must be nice, idiot.
Must be nice for you too.
You won't even need to bring lunch today.
You can just have what's stuck
on your chin for lunch. Idiot.
Geez...
Bye.
[Banghak-dong to Toegyero]
Where are we?
Are we here? Do we get off?
We still have a long way...
Do you think I'd leave you behind?
Duk Seon. Where are you?
Can you hear me? Answer me, Duk Seon!
Don't call my name...
Mister! Geez...
What happened?
Are we here?
Do we get off, or what?
Huh? What happened?
Honey!
It's almost time!
You look pretty enough!
Let's go, already!
What time is it now?
4:33 p.m. It's almost time!
Jung Hwan!
Jung Bong!
You two hurry up too!
Geez, you all are getting all dolled up
because we're going out to eat.
What's this?
Is that really my son?
Are you an actor?
I like those colors.
Is it new?
I wore this yesterday too.
Oh!
What about your older brother?
Tell him to come out quickly too.
Older Bro. Let's go.
Today is Mom's birthday.
We're eating out.
I won't take a single step out
until I finish this.
It's my own battle to fight.
We're going to eat pork cutlets.
I might get carsick
if I do this in the car.
Geez... what's taking her so long?
Honey!
Mi Ran!
Ra Mi...
Honey, why did you stuff
your shoulders so much?
Can I just... stay home?
No. Family has to stick together.
Hurry up and get in.
I have some stuff in the front,
so everyone ride in the back.
Let's go, Kit.
[Keum Sung Electronics Dealership]
Honey.
Did... we eat all of
the stuffed blood clams?
Yeah.
Then you should've bought some
before we ran out!
You know how much I love those!
Shut the hell up
and eat already!
Do you know how annoying
it is to make those?
They take so long to bring home and boil
and then I have to put sauce
in every single one!
You think they grow
on trees or something?
Geez, it's not like I asked you to make
me galbi stew or shuck me oysters!
I love stuffed blood clams the most!
You can't even make that one thing!
Also, why are you getting
so mad over it?
Geez. Socrates was really on
the money when he said this:
"A terrible wife is still a wife."
It's my fault that I've dealt with you
for all this time! You know that?
What bullshit...
Be grateful that I put up
with someone like you!
No manners, no charm.
Geez, geez, geez...
Well, I must have had something going
for me for us to have had three kids!
- Hello. We greet all of you.
- Hello, I'm...
Turn that shit off!
I ought to throw that away!
Lower the volume, you bastard!
Now's the time for you to watch TV?
You'll be a high school sophomore soon.
You should be studying, damn it...
He's like this because
he takes after you.
What? Why is that my fault?
Huh? How is that my fault?
If he took after me, he'd be first in the
entire school! He takes after you!
What did you just say?
Say it again.
What's wrong with my brains, huh?
What's wrong with my brains, tell me!
To be frank, you didn't even
graduate high school.
What the hell!
That's low!
You started it!
Our program, "Fun Saturday Night"
is gaining more and more popularity.
Opening our show tonight will be
a rising star among newcomers...
our very Dooly among musicians...
Mr. Byun Jin Sup.
Please, welcome him!
- Get out! I said, get out!
- Why are you treating him like that?
Can I take your order? The best thing
on our menu is the pork cutlet.
Oh...
Four pork cutlets, please.
- Father, I'd like the beef cutlet.
- I'd like the Hamburg steak.
The pork cutlet here is the best.
- Beef.
- Hamburg.
Two pork cutlets, one beef cutlet,
and one Hamburg skake.
One Hambak skate...
One Hamburg steak, please.
- Would you like rice or bread?
- Rice.
- Me too.
- Yes.
It's so nice to eat out
with the family.
I'm sure that there is no family
more harmonious than ours.
Isn't that right, Jung Bong?
Yes, Father.
Enjoy yourself as well.
When I see my kids and my Mi Ran eating
so happily, I feel satisfied enough.
Jung Hwan. Do you want more steak?
Do you want me to order you another?
I already did.
Why are you talking so much?
Your spit is going to
get on the food. Stop it.
Okay.
What happened?
What?
One, two, three!
Here you go.
- I'll take a photo for you.
- Ah, yes. Thank you!
No, it's okay!
Let's take one! Let's take one together!
Please take one.
- I don't want to either.
- Jung Hwan, let's take one.
Jung Bong, just take one and keep eating.
Take it, and then eat.
Come on. Jung Hwan, you can eat
after we take it.
Hurry. Put your fork down.
Honey. You look so pretty. Look there.
He's waiting, come on!
It's a happy occasion!
We should take one.
He's waiting. Look, smile!
Smile!
Smile, okay?
Okay, smile!
Pork cutlet!
One, two, three!
[Don't Sleep Study Room]
Study, you bastard.
[The only thing
I can give you is candy...]
I can give you is love...]
[Candy]
Jung Hwan.
Your dad bought some Italiano!
High-quality ice cream!
Italiano!
Hurry and come out.
Let's eat it together.
Kim Jung Hwan!
I'll put this on the table then.
Come out and eat it!
My older son!
Let's have some ice cream!
Hey, my eldest son.
You don't want ice cream?
I'll leave it in the kitchen then.
Come out and have some.
At the Baduk Championships today,
6-dan Choi Taek
was defeated by newcomer
Park Joon Young.
Park beat 6-dan Choi Taek in 123 moves.
Choi Taek was disadvantaged from the
beginning and seemed to give up halfway.
He has been overcome by a jinx
in the past, and this time
he showed his weakness
to a newcomer.
There are many who wonder
if he has fallen into a slump.
Hey, Dong Ryong.
Today, Taek...
Where are you going, Mom?
I'm going to Taek's to give them
some kimchi pancakes.
I heard he lost today!
Don't say anything about it.
He'll probably feel even worse.
What?
Are you going somewhere?
No... just up there.
Aren't you hungry?
No, I'm fine.
You should do it first.
You want me to do that, at my age?
Yes. You do it!
Why are you talking down to me?
I'm sorry!
Ah, ha. I'm a bit embarrassed.
What time is it now?
You didn't feed the dog,
Haeng Gook, today, right?
Hurry up and feed him.
You want me to do that?
Then you want me to do it,
at my age?
Ah, ha. I'm a bit embarrassed.
Oh, President Kim!
Where are you going?
The bathroom.
Feed Haeng Gook too,
while you're at it.
Okay.
Haeng Gook...
Oh my God, you scared me!
Make a little noise when you
walk around, will you?
Speak for yourself.
Where were you?
The study room.
To study.
Look at you, lying through your teeth.
You sure you didn't just dig up a grave?
Are you a zombie or something?
Geez.
Exactly how old are you?
In the middle of the night, too.
Oh my God!
You scared me!
Why are you so on edge?
Duk Seon.
Do you have any pencil lead?
Yeah.
Follow me.
I'll give you some.
Are you asleep?
I made some kimchi pancakes.
Is Taek sleeping?
Let's just act as if nothing happened.
He's taking this a lot harder
than he usually does.
Don't worry too much about him.
You'll make him feel worse.
Just pretend like nothing happened.
I'll be going now.
Have some of this.
[Italiano]
All you kids, come gather together.
Jin Joo, eat.
As they happily clap their hands...
Mom.
It starts today, right?
Yeah!
Jung Bong's mother
especially included you!
No! I told you, I won't
get tutored by her!
Honey. There's no
stuffed blood clams today?
Shut it.
Don't eat.
Just do it, already!
Do it for your sister's sake,
at least!
I said no!
They're letting you join even though
Jung Hwan is the one getting tutored.
For free.
Shut it.
You really didn't catch onto that?
It's as if Jung Bong's mother
is giving you allowance!
You think that Jung Hwan
really needs tutoring?
You're the only one on the block
that needs any tutoring!
There's Dong Ryong, too.
Dong Ryong's father is a teacher!
So why would he need tutoring?
Either way, we decided to do it starting
today, so don't say a word. Just study.
Don't think of her as your older sister.
Think of her as your teacher!
I'm not doing it.
I'm really not doing it.
And why the hell not?
They said that Jung Hwan and Sun Woo
ranked Number one and two respectively,
are coming.
Why are you being so stubborn?
Huh? Stop being stupidly stubborn!
Just do it!
Just do as your mother tells you--
Sun Woo is coming!
Older Bro.
Ugh, so cold!
Would you like some juice?
Enjoy it yourself.
Hurry up and get dressed too.
The kids will come to get tutored soon.
I don't want to make them
feel awkward, so let's leave.
I said, let's leave!
Go out by yourself.
I'm just going to stay here.
Jung Bong's father loves to stick
by your side... so where is he today?
I don't know!
What's he grumpy about this time?
Geez... it's like raising another kid.
Oh, come here!
Have a beer.
Oh geez... what's this,
drinking in broad daylight?
I'm afraid of what others will think.
We're all friends here on this block,
so whatever.
But... what about Bo Ra's father?
Why didn't you two come out together?
He could've had a drink with us.
I don't know. He left in the morning
saying he was meeting friends.
I wish he'd take No Eul to the public
baths or help around the house today.
He's so selfish.
He doesn't even bother you... how nice.
Geez, lady.
You're so lucky to be able to
say something like that.
If Bo Ra's father was even half
the man that Jung Bong's father was
I'd carry him on my back every day.
I'd treat him like a king.
It's only nice for a day or two...
trust me.
I wish he'd see his friends
or go off somewhere on the weekends.
All he does is
roll around the house... geez!
Wow... you two have no etiquette.
Are you poking fun at me
for being a widow?
Are you bragging about
your husbands in front of me?
Geez.
Your life is the best, honestly.
Geez... it must be nice to be you.
Really.
Then... get together with Taek's dad.
It's pretty much fate that
you live on the same block.
What did you say?
Are you out of your mind?
Why? What's wrong with it?
Oh, my.
It's like fate... it's Taek's father.
Well... then again, living with him
would be like living with a rock.
But he has a lot of money...
Looks like our Sun Young's life
will blossom in her older years!
What good would that be?
I barely hear him say
two words in a single day.
I have to practice abstinence
forever, at this age?
I'm fine with someone with no money, but
I'm not fine with someone who's no fun.
What about my husband, then?
No thanks.
You can keep him.
Oh! I was going to come back for that!
Well, you live right here, so...
How's Taek?
Well.. you know.
Just act as if nothing happened.
That's the best thing to do.
Yes.
It's not like he can win all the time.
He has to lose sometimes.
We won't say a word to him.
But... I know it's Sunday,
but the block is especially quiet.
What about the kids?
Oh... the kids are getting
tutored by Bo Ra today.
What?
They're going to be juniors soon.
That's why they're
getting tutored by Bo Ra.
Our friend over here
treated all our kids!
Isn't tutoring... illegal?
It's among us,
so what does that matter?
Who would report us?
Are you going to report us?
Of course not.
- Here, have one!
- Look, he's going off to report us.
You're here too?
Yes.
Your father is a teacher, though.
What if he reports us
to the Board of Education?
Did you tell your dad about us?
My dad's busy.
My mom registered me for this.
Why is your dad busy?
It's Sunday.
My dad...
tutors.
You all think that
I'm a science teacher, right?
That's a load of bull!
I'm... not a science teacher,
but what?
- A music teacher!
Okay, bingo!
All right... shall I have a listen, then?
We're starting the periodic table.
Ready?
One! Two!
One, two, three, four!
H, He, Li, Be, B, C, N, O, F, Ne, Na, Mg
Al, Si, P, S, Cl, Ar, K, Ca!
One more time!
H, He, Li, Be, B, C, N,
O, F, Ne, Na, Mg...
The dean... no, your father... he's a
chemistry teacher. He teaches math too?
His major in college
was mathematics.
What a plot twist,
am I right?
Wow.
All right.
Quadratic formula.
One! Two!
One, two, three, four!
x equals negative b
plus or minus the square root
of b squared minus 4ac
all over 2a. All done!
You punks.
Did you bring your math textbooks?
What is this?
She only looked at the section on sets.
I do sets better than
anyone in my class!
Geez... good for you.
What's with your book?
It's so wrinkly!
Don't touch that.
That's his drool.
Let's just give up on math.
Physics.
Let's test you two on physics.
A really easy question, too.
A middle school problem.
You know the formula,
F equals ma, right?
Jung Hwan, who is 70 kilograms
hits Sun Woo with a force
of 20 Newtons.
What's the acceleration?
How did you endure that?
It must have hurt.
You endured it well.
If you didn't get hurt,
that's good enough.
Juice.
Enjoy.
Thanks, Jung Bong.
You're welcome.
My pleasure.
Older Bro.
Where are you going?
Huh?
Oh, I want to ask Taek how to solve this.
Taek's not home.
He went to the club.
Even we barely get
to see him these days.
What?
[Korean Baduk Club]
What brings you here on a Sunday, Sir?
Same goes to Taek, 6-dan.
It's Sunday, so you should relax.
For him, this level of play
is relaxing.
How can you win every time?
Losses happen.
They say that losses are all
a part of gaining experience.
Just consider this a good experience
and forget about it already.
Even so, Choi Taek, 6-dan's still the
likely winner of this competition.
It's fine!
Don't worry about it.
Other people lose 20 or 30 times a year.
The fact that you have a
70-percent winning rate...
even that's impressive enough!
Hey!
What brings you here?
You never come out on Sundays.
I came to console our Taek.
You're okay, right?
Of course.
Even if you're the Almighty Choi Taek,
you can't win all the time.
And you still have the the finals.
It's fine.
I'm worried about Taek.
Yeah.
I'm more worried about your lives!
I thought you at least knew some English.
Geez!
You guys.
English is just memorization.
Just memorize it!
Just forget everything else
and memorize it! Okay?
Do you even know any words?
Do you know anything that will
supplement your memorization?
Of course I do!
What do you take me for?
What, then?
I, my, me, my.
You, your, you, yours.
- That's first-year middle school stuff.
- He, his, him, his.
Jesus.
She... her, her, hers!
We, our, us, ours.
I know how to speak German, too.
Der, des, dem, dem,
die, der, der, die
das, des, dem, das,
die, der, dem, die.
Hey, I know Spanish.
Spanish.
Jeez.
When I walk down the street
the bright sunlight flows down
and beckons me.
Chiquilla mia somos
como el temporal
que arrastra todo y no
le importa donde va
nuestro carino es un
barco en alta mar navega libre
sin temor a naufragar.
Carino mio, somos dos
y tu y yo pajaro y la flor
y tu y yo lanzamos el amor
y tu y yo directo al corazon
al corazon eres carino mio.
My lovable dearest,
I want to keep you by my side forever
the one I want to kiss,
who has shaken my heart
my eternal love!
You didn't forget that you're coming to
Duk Seon's school with me tomorrow, yes?
Hey, I don't know when
I'm getting out of work.
You go by yourself.
They asked both of us to come!
It's the first meeting about her future.
How can I go alone?
All right, already!
Give it a rest!
I'll come.
Thank you!
Don't go talking to strangers
on your way home.
Call home as soon as you leave the bank.
Why do you never call?
Look at Jung Bong's dad. He calls
every hour after he leaves his shop.
Other husbands--
All right, already!
Give it a rest!
I'm not your child.
Every time I try to say something,
you're just dying to nag at me!
Really, I...
oh my.
Oh, T...
He probably feels terrible.
Don't say anything to aggravate him.
Be really careful.
Why, I ought to...
Master Choi!
Hi, there.
Oh, yes.
Um... here. Have one of these.
Also, why don't you and your father
come eat dinner at our place tonight?
I'm going to make seaweed soup today.
You like seaweed soup, right?
It's okay.
Um... then...
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
Bye, now!
Bye!
How sad...
Why, I ought to...
Did you feed your common sense
to Haeng Gook?
How could you offer seaweed soup
to someone who lost a match?
Oh my God! It's an allegory for failure.
You're right.
Oh my God, what do I do?
I totally forgot.
Geez... what do I do?
Go and tell him that
you're sorry, already!
Geez...
You're just getting home?
What about dinner?
I ate.
Taek.
Have strength. Okay?
Yes.
What about your dad?
He says he doesn't want any.
Wait.
Dinner, honey.
Your food is going to get cold.
I wonder what he's
grumpy about this time.
Geez.
Where are you going?
You're not eating dinner?
I'm going to Taek's.
I'll eat with the guys.
Don't bother Taek
and come home early!
Okay!
Eat up already.
My mom really likes this!
And this, too!
You're a filial son, Chil Deuk.
But don't just play.
Do some hard work, too.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Earn some money fishing.
- Your mother is worried because of you.
- What do you know about my mom...
Hey. Eat.
Okay.
Hey, that's Kim Hye Soo,
right?
Wow... she's so pretty.
What is she, 22, 23?
She's 19!
She's 19! She's younger than Bo Ra!
Oh my... she's 19?
What kind of 19-year-old
is so good at acting?
Look at her face.
She's a pretty one.
Geez... who doesn't look that good at 19?
I was pretty like that when I was 19.
What utter nonsense.
When I met you, you were 18.
There wasn't a single part of you
that was pretty.
Then did I date Il Hwa or Yi Hwa?
(wordplay of "one" and "two")
Please!
Do you know how you were back then?
You had such terrible dry skin...
you're lucky that you met me.
Geez, you... how could you talk
to your almighty husband like that?
It's so obvious that you're uneducated.
Almighty, my ass.
Don't joke with me.
Don't joke with me?
Look at the way you talk!
I...
And just where the hell
are you going?
To Taek's.
- Don't go!
Taek is still sad about his loss.
Don't hang around there.
Stay the hell at home!
It's too late to be visiting people.
Leave Taek alone.
Mom, I'm off!
It's dinnertime!
Where are you going?
To Taek's!
I'll eat with the others!
Sun Woo!
Don't say anything to Taek!
You'll make him feel worse...
Geez.
Taek.
Taek...
I'm washing up.
Okay.
Mister, is Taek home?
Yeah, he is.
But his condition isn't...
Taek!
The Almighty Me is here!
- Mister!
- Hello!
Is Taek home?
Yeah. But he's...
- No need to explain...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
If you try it yourself...
ah, ah, ah!
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know! Do you know?
- I don't know.
- I don't know, either.
Hello. Is Taek...
Yeah, he's here. Yeah.
He's been here for a while now.
Yes.
Taek!
Geez...
I heard you got beat badly.
Way to go, bastard.
You've humiliated our town.
Hi, Taek!
I heard you lost.
Geez.
I heard they stepped all over you.
Yeah. It's about time you lost once.
It's been a long time coming.
It was a mistake.
Mistake, my ass.
Genius Baduk players
can't afford to make mistakes.
Am I supposed to win every day?
You have to win every day.
You can't lose, be jinxed,
fall into a slump, or even take a...
No, you can take a dump.
But it's not allowed to smell.
Hey. Should you be laughing right now?
Just curse instead.
Look.
Go ahead.
God f--king damn it.
Geez!
Sun Woo.
God f--king damn it!
Hey...
Try it!
Try it, already!
God f--king darn it!
Hey, you have to do it right.
God f--king damn it!
Damn it!
Yeah!
God f--king damn it!
F--k!
Do it!
God f--king damn it!
[Ssangmun Girl's High School]
Duk Seon has a very bright personality.
She tries very hard,
and gets along with her friends well.
She has great social relationships
and her personality is great...
But, um...
her grades this time around are...
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Geez!
Oh no.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and come.
I can't believe him...
he could've at least held the door.
What's with all this rain?
Can we get two orders
of kalguksu here?
I want sujebi!
Why not ask me first
before ordering?
Geez... okay, fine.
Have sujebi. All right?
Can we get one sujebi
and one kalguksu?
I told you beforehand, we have
to worry about Duk Seon's studies.
I said, even if we can't get a tutor
we should at least
send her to a cram school!
Geez... we can just ween
her into her studies now.
She still has two years left.
Also...
do you know how hard
white-collar life is?
The other mothers all take care of
their kids' educations.
If you had done that, Duk Seon
wouldn't have ended up like this.
Oh my God.
So it's my fault?
It's my fault that Duk Seon
is 999th place in the entire school?
Geez... you think it's easy
to raise a kid?
If only we had money...
I wouldn't have let things
get that bad.
Geez.
What a wretched life.
What's so wrong with your life?
Did I lose our house
through gambling or something?
Did I cheat on you?
Am I a drunk who beats you?
Geez... stop it already.
You're so annoying.
Let's just eat kalguksu.
Cheers.
[A ping-pong love]
People are even getting married to
Chinese people nowadays.
Wow.
What's with all this rain? Geez.
[Please ensure that you don't mistake
another person's umbrella as your own.]
Geez... even if I can't swap my husband,
shall I try swapping my umbrella?
Oh my.
Where did my umbrella go?
Geez... why would someone take
someone else's umbrella?
Is anyone the owner of this umbrella?
Whose is this?
Oh dear... I guess the owner of
this umbrella took mine instead.
I guess it can't be helped.
Ah, so cold!
Yeah...
Figures, with my luck.
What's taking you so long?
No matter how much better
others' things may seem
they all have their faults.
What are you doing?
Hold onto my arm.
Let's go.
[Apathy]
Jung Bong! Jung Hwan!
Have some kimchi pancakes!
Okay!
A family that does not communicate...
Father?
Have some kimchi...
They wish for a warm conversation.
Have some interest in your children.
Public Service Announcement.
Hey... Dong Ryong.
My dad hasn't spoken
to us in a few days.
Why do you think that is?
It's because of you, your brother,
or your mom. One of the three.
What should I do about it then?
It's the easiest thing in the world
to make your dad stop being angry.
Just accept it.
Accept what?
Is it Duk Seon?
Duk Seon, I'm in the kitchen!
Oh, President Sung!
Oh, President Kim!
- It's really great to see you!
- Really great to see you!
I came to get some juice.
- I'm having dinner with the others.
- Okay.
Once again, we bring you a
live broadcast of "Fun Saturday Night."
Next up is someone who needs
no introduction.
Here's the famous
Cho Yong Pil!
Geez... lower the volume.
You like the TV that much.
I love these.
- Delicious.
- Really?
There's nothing one is more sick of
and considers more tacky than
something that has belonged
to them for a long time.
It's raining and all...
want some soju?
There's nothing one is more sick of
and considers more tacky than
something that has belonged
to them for a long time.
However, another way
to say "tacky" and "sick of"
is "accustomed to"
and "comfortable."
The feeling of being accustomed
only comes with
having spent a long time with something.
And only the people I'm comfortable with
can truly know me, embrace me,
and console me.
Sometimes, you're so sick of something
and it seems so tacky
that you don't even
want to look at it
but the only people in the world
who can protect me are "my people."
People who I'm used to,
and am comfortable with...
people who have been my people
for a long time...
are people who you
cannot help but love.
"We cannot help loving them."
You can't help but to love them.
Asshole.
Sun Woo.
It's raining outside.
"I am raining."
It's, "it's raining."
Oh.
Hey, Taek.
My older brother has
been on that for a week.
Figure it out, and then
tell me how to do it.
I'll tell him the exact method.
Open the door!
Put something down!
- Hey!
Hey!
Not that...
[High Schoolers' Essential
Basic English Grammar]
Are your studies going well?
You really think
they'd be going well?
She's studying for the
first time in 18 years.
Shut it.
Duk Seon and I decided
to give up on math altogether.
Just use your spoon!
Geez!
But English seems doable enough.
Me too.
I'm confident with idioms.
"Can not help-ing."
It means, "I can't help but to..."
I can not help laughing!
You don't know things like this, right?
Here.
Wow.
Even if he just started studying today
I bet Taek would do
much better than you two.
Hey, Taek.
Tell me how to do it again.
Kids!
Come out for a second!
Can you help me move my things?
Yes, Sir!
Hey, Jung Hwan.
You clean up, okay?
Okay.
Hey... hey!
Hey, hey, hey... cramp!
Cramp, cramp, cramp!
Are you okay?
Ow...
What do we do?
I got a cramp in my leg!
Okay, already!
Ow... ow!
Don't touch. Ow.
Ow!
Do something about it!
Meow!
What the hell are you doing?
No?
Meow!
Hey... stop that.
Fine.
Don't touch it!
What do you want me to do, then?
Okay, then... meow!
I said stop!
Ow!
- Meow!
- Stop it!
- Ow...
- Here, let me see!
Let go! Ow!
It really hurts!
- Meow, meow, meow!
- Stop it!
Meow!
Let me see, already!
Ow, ow, ow!
Roar!
You think roaring is going to work?
I'm off!
Oh yeah, my lunch.
Damn it!
- What are you going?
- Huh?
Are you waiting for me?
No!
I'm waiting for Sun Woo!
Oh.
Sun Woo?
Miss, what about Sun Woo?
He already left!
Damn it!
Hey, Mister!
Geez!
I'm going to be gone for two days or so.
If you want to live,
listen carefully to what I have to say.
Don't you worry.
All right?
Yay!
We did it up yesterday, right?
I'll borrow this and give it right back!
This, too!
They said that they've
arrived at the terminal.
Terminal?
This is an emergency!
Change your clothes and
clean everything!
You're dead today!
- Let go!
- Get over here!
Are you trying to ruin your life?
Do I have to foam at the mouth and
pass out for you to come to your senses?
What if Big Sis gets a criminal record?
Bo Ra is the issue!
She's so scary!
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Aren't you worried about your child?
Sun Woo.
Have you seen my Bo Ra?
Stop coming here, already!
Bo Ra!