All right.
I will now introduce my family,
which is full of harmony and love.
First, I will introduce someone
who is attempting
to get into college
for the sixth year in a row
[Answer Me 1988]
to get into college
for the sixth year in a row
[Answer Me 1988]
a persevering punk.
The eldest son of our family,
Kim Jung Bong!
It seems that he went to a study room.
[Hyper Olympics
50 won for one game]
Next up is my son, who looks
just like me from head to toe...
I introduce to you our second son,
Kim Jung Hwan!
Jung Hwan.
Say something for the camera.
Geez... quit doing stuff
like this, already.
Today's the first time
I've done this, though...
The only one who I can trust
is my wife.
The cornerstone of our home
and my cheetah
and my jaguar!
Honey, say something!
Ow!
You brought this from
your show again, didn't you?
How much is this worth?
980,000 won.
Why? You're such a miser.
Is that any way to talk to your husband?
Here... a word to your miser husband?
Geez! I can't even break this...
It's not that you won't hit me...
it's that you can't!
Shut it, already!
Geez!
Excuse, excuse me!
Please, excuse me!
Looking, looking
very closely...
is this your home?
Yes, yes, yes it is!
How did you know?
Don't reciprocate his stupidity,
Duk Seon. It'll become a habit.
I think it's funny, though.
Mom wanted me to bring this to you.
My grandma brought it.
Wow... tell her that we'll enjoy it.
Duk Seon, you must be happy.
You really love your grandma.
Yes.
But she's leaving tomorrow.
Hey!
Why are you using your hands?
So disgusting...
What's it matter to you?
Ah, this scent... you have such a
nice scent coming from you.
Geez... don't old farts like me
just smell like old farts?
No.
You smell nice.
Dad smells like this, too.
Your belly is so flat, so how did Dad,
my uncle
and my chubby aunts
come out of here?
After giving birth
to four chubby kids
my belly ended up shrinking.
Look at the stupid questions she asks,
even though she's a high schooler.
Granny. Do you know what
Sung Duk Seon's nickname is?
Don't you dare.
It's "IWESS."
It stands for
"Idiots Who Especially Suck at Studying."
As if you're good at studying...
all you do is go to protests!
Did you just call me "you?"
You little...
Hey! I'm warning you!
Argue one more time, and I'll beat you
and kick you both out!
I'll beat you to a pulp!
Mother. You're not uncomfortable
in any way, right?
Then, good night.
Okay, okay.
- Go to sleep.
- Yes, Mother.
I'll kill you both...
Sung Duk Seon...
consider yourself saved by Granny.
Granny.
What?
What was Uncle like?
Did he study better than Dad?
No. Your father was a whole lot smarter
than him when it came to school.
And he graduated from
that prestigious school in Gwangju.
Your uncle...
took it upon himself since he was young
to earn money for his younger siblings.
But even so, Uncle is the
richest among us.
He even lives in the U.S.
You think that running a laundromat
in the States is prestigious?
He's barely managing
to put food on the table nowadays.
Geez. When I think about your uncle...
my heart just hurts.
Then, who's a better son to you?
Dad calls you every morning.
Why are you asking that?
Both of them are good sons.
Your dad and your uncle never fought.
Why can't you two be like that? Geez.
That's because Bo Ra
always picks fights with me first.
Hey!
- Not again...
- What?
You little...
Come on.
[Episode 2:
One Thing You Misunderstood About Me]
[Historic Match Today.]
- Mother, be careful.
- Okay.
At any rate, why are you in
such a rush to leave?
Since you're here, you might as well
spend another night here.
Geez... I have to go home and dry flowers
and a lot of other things.
Granny, I'll come visit
during winter vacation.
Okay, my child.
But... where's Bo Ra?
Where'd she go?
She left early to go to the library.
College students study so much nowadays.
Library, my ass.
She probably went to protest.
Oh dear... hey.
You're throwing this away?
Huh?
Yes.
It's not usable anymore, Mother.
What are you saying?
It looks fine!
Give it here.
Yes, Mother...
Okay. Wow!
I'm going to take this home
and use it.
Geez... you already have
so much stuff to carry back!
Why are you taking that, too?
When I come visit you,
I'll buy you a better one than this!
it's not like you make that much,
so don't be wasting money on me!
I can just use this one.
Hey, you'll be late to work. Go. Quickly!
Geez.
- Good bye!
- Have a safe trip!
I told you, I've got it!
- No!
- Stop it! Sheesh!
- Give me that!
- No, I'm holding it!
- That's mine!
- Stop that!
Stop worrying about me and go!
Give me that!
No! You give me back
my stuff!
- Geez!
- Quit it!
Go, already. Go.
So stubborn.
I'm off!
Okay, see you later.
If you wear that and get caught
by your sister, you're dead!
Bo Ra goes drinking every Saturday.
I'll be home before her.
Hey, Kim Jung Hwan! How do I look?
I'm late. Piss off.
Hey, there's only three minutes left.
This is new. How does it look?
Isn't that your sister's?
Hey, only two minutes left!
Let's hurry!
Hello!
Hello, Mister!
Hey! When did you get back?
Yesterday.
Are you going to school?
Yeah.
Drink a lot of milk and
grow big soon, my little Taek!
You have to hurry and grow up
so you can marry me.
- Ow!
- Hey, there's only one minute left!
You want to die?
You want to die? Hey!
Be on time for a change.
Aren't you tired of getting punished
for being late every morning?
It doesn't matter.
My head is full of rocks, anyway.
Hey, Wang Ja Hyun.
So... what'd you get?
Only 45 percent.
I don't think our love
will work out.
Look.
You idiot... you did it wrong!
What?
You wrote your name first.
That means you only like him 45 percent.
Really?
Let me try it again.
I'll write his name first.
70 percent!
70 percent?
70 percent? Byun likes you 70 percent?
As if.
I'm going to try it, too. Me too.
What is this?
They're not Korean noodles...
It's called spaghetti.
You've never had it, right?
It's the first time I've seen it.
You should have just made
normal noodles.
I have money, so might as well spend it.
I'm going to eat what
rich people eat before I die.
What are you doing?
Are you boiling Korean noodles?
Are these chewy noodles?
I said it's spaghetti!
Okay.
Stop glaring like that.
You look so scary.
At any rate, why are we celebrating
Taek's victory at our place?
It's just the two of them,
so it's not like they'll cook anything.
I told them to just buy chicken.
- Taek is coming, too.
- Oh, really?
I guess I'll see Mr. Choi
for the first time in a while, huh?
Wouldn't it be great if I had a daughter
and got him as a son-in-law?
I claimed Taek first.
He's going to be my son-in-law.
But, Bo Ra isn't coming today?
Everyone else is.
She does something at school
every Saturday and comes home late.
She won't be home after
12:00 a.m. today, either.
Mom! Where are you?
Bo Ra?
What the heck?
Why is she back so early?
Mom!
Eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve,
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen...
How old am I, again?
Eighteen.
Click it two more times.
Seventeen, eighteen.
If it breaks, your love is doomed.
If it breaks, your love won't come true.
Hey. Don't you even dream
of love until you get those braces off.
Shush.
My first love depends on this.
I'm going to a club trip today.
I'm going to go as soon as I pack my bag.
What's this about a club trip,
all of the sudden?
I don't know.
An upperclassman said he got
paid today, so he wants to go Daesungri.
Crazy bastard!
He just does whatever he wants!
Mom.
Did you see my tan pants
that were here?
I washed those this morning
and hung them up.
They should be dry by now.
Let me go get them.
No, it's okay.
I'll just wear these pants.
But Mom...
I don't see that.
You know... my jacket.
Where's my jacket?
The baseball jacket.
I left that at the dry cleaner's...
No, no. My denim jacket.
Huh?
Where's my denim jacket?
It was definitely here.
I even saw it this morning!
Where's my denim jacket?
Huh?
Um... that is...
um... Bo Ra.
It was definitely here
this morning!
Why isn't it here now?
Where's my denim jacket?
Damn it! Hmm... did I wash it?
Wait just a minute.
Where's my denim jacket?
Damn it!
Sung Duk Seon! I'll kill her!
I'm going to kill her!
Damn Sung Duk Seon!
I think watching the fiasco downstairs
would be more entertaining than this.
Ma'am. Lend me your phone.
Oh, and the phone book.
Yes, this is Ssangmundong High School.
Sir! No, no...
Can you put a the dean
on the line?
Yes, this is the dean.
Dong Ryong's father!
Can you put No Eul on the line?
Yes, hello?
Mom?
Duk Seon!
Duk Seon! Jacket!
[Dae Wang Computer Game Cafe]
He's definitely on steroids. For sure.
What the hell am I going to wear?
I'm going to kill Sung Duk Seon!
Damn it!
Where did Sung Duk Seon go?
Geez... where do you think?
School, obviously.
Geez... sometimes, I wonder how
she even got into Seoul University.
She's coming. Over there.
Where are you going?
To go kill Sung Duk Seon.
Here it is!
It was right here.
I totally forgot.
I'm back from school.
Oh, you're home, Duk Seon?
You're early today.
It's Saturday so I got out earlier.
Hey, Sung Duk Seon.
What?
Did you wear your indoor slippers
to school today?
Yeah. Duh.
Duk Seon.
Go get washed up,
and let's go to Jung Hwan's.
We're celebrating Taek's victory today.
So Jung Hwan's mom bought
American noodles and everything.
Damn it!
What are you going to do about this?
- Should I use the hair dryer?
- I don't have time for that!
Why did you wash this
without even asking me?
What am I supposed to wear today?
Hey. Grow up.
What did you just say to me?
I said, grow up instead
of harassing Mom!
You little... hey!
You grow up.
You're always last place.
I'm not last place!
There are other people lower than me!
Is that something to brag about?
And also, what do you need clothes for
when all you do is play all day?
Just wear whatever!
You're ugly, so it's not like
you need to worry about looks anyway.
I held back a lot today.
You're dead today. Hey!
You think you're pretty?
You nose looks like a man's!
Damn it!
I'm back... off to school.
Am I your friend? Huh?
I'm going to kill you!
You drive me crazy!
"You?" I'll kill you!
Crazy bitch!
[A moment's decision influences
the next 10 years of your life.]
If I met Mr. Young Pil,
my life would be complete!
Jo Young Pil is two years younger
than you! No need call him "Mr."
Even so...
Hi! What are you all up to?
- They're still not here?
- Oh, hi, Jin Joo!
Wow, look at everyone!
Honey, you're home early today.
Geez, you...
Mr. Choi's dad said that he's treating us
for the first time in a while
so of course I couldn't be late
on a day like today.
Speaking of which,
what's on the menu for today?
We have spaghetti.
Get... getty?
What's that?
Spaghetti. It's American food.
How are we supposed to eat this, anyway?
How do you think?
The same way you eat anything else.
Why isn't Mr. Choi here yet?
The noodles are getting bloated.
Mr. Choi is like the Jo Young Pil
of our neighborhood.
The superstar always comes last.
Oh, the superstar is here.
The door is open,
so why is he using the bell?
Here you go.
Hello.
"Kantapia."
Go to Jung Bong's room.
Why did you get here so late?
We were waiting for you.
You should have closed shop
on a day like today.
You don't need to work so hard
when your son earns so much money.
That's not my money.
That's Taek's.
Where would Taek even use that money?
Why not use some of it?
Oh yes... here you go.
Wow... you bought two of them?
Honey. Put this in Jung Hwan's room.
Okay.
Is Taek coming, too?
It's been so long since
I've seen him.
He's coming.
He doesn't even attend school
so the only friends he has
are the kids from this block.
But he wants to cool his head first.
Oh, geez.
Mr. Choi.
Say a greeting for me.
- Huh?
- What's that?
Mr. Choi!
Please grant this wish of mine!
No, it's okay.
Geez... then...
Bo Ra's dad,
please say something!
Then, what about the Ugly Sisters
of our town?
- A camera!
- So amazing!
It records our movements!
Geez.
Oh!
There's a missing lady here.
There was a lady who was
the prettiest among you three.
Has anyone seen my cheetah?
Here she is.
I'm giving you until the count of three.
One, two, three!
You thought I was putting it down,
right?
- Geez...
- Ow!
Get rid of it!
My eye almost popped out! What
would I do if that happened?
- I'm back.
- Hello.
Hey there.
- Where's our Sun Woo?
- He's coming.
- Hello! I'm back from school!
- You're here, my son?
Our Sun Woo... you know that
I brag about you, right?
Yes.
I wonder why my friend
isn't coming?
Who?
Oh, President Sung!
Oh, President Kim!
- It's so great to see you!
Oh, Duk Seon!
Thanks for reciprocating.
I got it. I know.
What the hell are you two doing?
How come Taek didn't come with you?
He's coming.
The star of the show
always shows up last!
I told him to go borrow some comic books.
Wow, Duk Seon.
You've got some nerve.
Making the Almighty Taek
do that for you?
Only outsiders care about that stuff.
Do you think the kids
treat him any differently?
They're childhood friends.
Hello.
- Congratulations!
- Yay!
- Come on in!
- Hi!
Thank you for gracing us with
your presence today, sir.
This place is unfit for your presence,
and yet you've come.
What an honor this is.
Oh yeah, I want you all to greet him.
He's our son-in-law.
What are you saying?
He's going to marry my Jin Joo!
We called dibs first! Right, Taek?
Welcome. I'm your new mother.
I'm your new father.
Oh, stop it, already.
Go inside.
All the kids are here.
Enjoy your meal.
Okay.
Look at him.
He's all grown now.
Geez... he's totally like an adult!
Compared to our kids,
he seems so much older!
He's still just a kid.
All he knows how to do
is play Baduk.
He knows nothing about the world.
Geez, you... elements of the real
world are all a part of Baduk.
Do you think Taek doesn't know that?
And he's one of the
best Baduk players ever.
In some ways, he might know more about
the world than we adults do.
Speaking of which, how much was
the prize money this time around?
I heard that he won the largest
competition in all of Korea.
50,000,000 won.
Oh my goodness!
Taek should buy a huge round
for the kids today!
Oh my God...
50,000,000 won...
I'm speechless.
- That's so much money.
- You must be so happy. I'm so jealous.
- 50,000,000 won?
Buy us ddukbokki.
- Ddukbokki!
- Hey, have some chicken.
- That's okay.
Look at how pale your face is. Don't
forget to work out once in a while.
Is this your stomach or your back?
You're so thin.
I'm fine.
Hey, Taek. You're going to China again,
right?
When are you coming back?
Are you coming back before your birthday?
Why?
- You want to throw him a birthday party?
- No. Bring us some liquor.
- Mom!
- What's wrong with you?
Why are you telling Taek to do that?
Buy it yourselves!
He's on a different level.
They always give him expensive
bottles of liquor in China.
Hey, Choi Taek.
Don't give it to your dad this time.
Give it to us. Okay?
- Hey.
- Where are you going?
- To get some juice.
- Don't you dare tell on us.
Fine.
Hey, ugly.
Get only the juice, all right?
Don't eat the sausage in the fridge.
It's Jung Bong's.
I won't!
Land.
Land is the best.
Mr. Choi, buy some land no matter what.
They say that the value of the land
in Ilsan is rising nowadays.
Geez... if you don't know anything,
don't talk.
What's there to see in Ilsan?
It's in the middle of nowhere!
Rather, it's safest to put
your money in a bank.
Geez... bank interest
doesn't even amount to much.
Of course, the interest rates
have decreased a bit
so it'll only be about 15 percent or so
but even so, you'll accrue interest.
There's no place safer than a bank.
You're going to put
all that money in a bank?
Mr. Choi.
Buy an apartment.
A great one, in Gangnam.
Um... what's it called?
Umma (Mom) Apartment, yes.
It's Eunma...
Yeah. Umma. Umma Apartment.
- Eunma. Eunma.
- That's what I just said! Umma. Umma.
I heard they go for 50,000,000 won.
What? How is an apartment
that much money?
Where is it?
- Anyway, congratulations, Mr. Choi!
- Yes. Thank you.
Meanwhile, our daughters
are busy blowing our money...
Mr. Choi is so lucky.
Mr. Kim, come sit down.
It's still not working?
Geez... you paid so much for it
but you don't know how to use it?
If it doesn't work, just give up
and come sit here!
Why are you fussing about putting on
some music in the middle of the day?
Then, let's just toast! Cheers!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Jin Joo.
Does that taste good?
Can you give me just a bite?
Here, here, here!
Here it is!
Who could that be?
I think someone's here.
Mr. Choi.
What did I say before?
Excuse me?
What did I tell you to buy
if you got a lot of money?
An apartment.
Here, get up.
Everyone, get up! Yeah!
All right!
Took you long enough.
They're at it again.
Who's the featured singer today?
The usual.
- My mom...
- And my dad.
Taek.
Do you have anything you want
for your birthday?
Yeah. Tell us before you leave for China.
Do you listen to music?
He only listens to
Deulgukhwa.
Oh, yeah. Jeon In Kwon's
solo album is out. Do you want that?
Kim Jung Hwan, you heard him, right?
- Buy it.
- No, thanks.
Hey.
Brazil Ddukbokki is going to close soon.
They close early on Saturdays.
Where are you going?
To eat ddukbokki!
Goodbye!
After the ceremony last night
at 7:00 p.m. at the Seoul Olympic Stadium
the 1988 Seoul Olympics
has come to a close.
The Seoul Olympics,
in which 159 countries participated
had the Soviet Union get first place,
with 55 gold medals
and East Germany in second place,
with 37 gold medals.
Korea came in fourth place
with 33 gold medals
and performed quite well
during the Olympics.
Hey, get up!
Why does he always shift down
in his sleep?
Get up, Sung No Eul!
You have to go to school!
- What time is it?
- 6:30 a.m. Eat and wash up.
Hello? Mom!
Oh... you're awake?
What about food?
We're eating now. How's Granny?
Is Granny okay?
She's not doing so well. I have to stay
here a couple more days.
Did you pack the lunches?
Yeah.
What about Dad? Is he okay?
He's fine. He's doing well.
Did you wake up your older sister?
She has to go to school
early today.
Whatever.
I'm sure she'll wake up on her own.
Bo Ra. Wake up and eat breakfast.
Damn it...
Why, I ought to... kill you...
She says she's not eating.
I told her she has to eat.
Tell her I said that.
She said, "I told her she has to eat."
Damn it!
Tell Sung Duk Seon
to stuff her own damn face.
Okay.
She told you to stuff her own damn face.
Tell her that, if she doesn't stuff her
damn face, I'll wash up first!
Damn it...
She says, "If you don't stuff your
damn face, I'll wash up first!"
Tell her to do that
if she has a death wish!
Okay.
She said, "Do that
if you have a death wish."
Is this fun for you?
Huh? I ought to kill you!
Damn it! You're all psychopaths!
Ow!
Mommy...
Damn it!
Is there no hierarchy
in this house?
Why are you washing up first?
You didn't wash up when you were
supposed to! I'm going to be late!
I told you last night that
I was washing up first, didn't I?
Then why don't you get up early
and wash up first?
What? "You?"
You think you're a freaking queen
or something?
"You?"
Yeah, "you!"
Hey!
I'm going to go insane!
- Get over here.
- Hey!
I'm telling Mom!
Let go. Let go!
You know what we're doing tonight, right?
- Yeah.
- What?
Look at you,
acting like you don't know.
We promised to go
to the 19 and over movie theater.
Oh... yeah.
I heard that it's a lot better
than the last one.
Ew. Ew!
Just what the hell
did your mother make?
I feel like my tongue
is going to fall off!
It's better than your crappy
instant noodle lunch!
You know about lunchtime, right?
What is it now?
Soccer, bastard!
I'm not playing with Crazy Mutt.
I don't want to break my ankle.
He's always singling me out!
He's a total psycho!
It's fine. He's a nice guy.
And what do you base that on?
He doesn't smoke.
Does that automatically mean
that he's a nice guy?
Yeah.
Geez... you're so simple.
Are you an amoeba?
Anyway, show up. Okay?
Whatever. I'm sleeping
during lunchtime.
Crazy bastard.
Why are you sleeping during lunch
when you don't even have
to do your class rep duties?
Jung Hwan says he'll cover you.
Sun Woo. Sun Woo! Please?
If you're not there,
who's going to score goals for us?
Tell me, who? Please?
No.
Sun Woo. Please?
I'll kill you.
Stop reading romance novels
already, you two.
Aren't you tired of them by now?
What's this?
[An Officer and a Princess]
"An Officer and a Princess?"
"He headed straight,
toward her lips."
"And he desired
her luscious lips deeply."
"However, she grew flustered."
"What flustered her was"
"not his rough lips, but the feeling of
his bare, rock hard chest against..."
Are you living out your fantasies
vicariously through these?
Whatever. Give it here.
Hey, come to your senses, already.
There are no guys like this
in real life.
"Bare, rock hard chest," my ass.
Hey. Ben Johnson.
He has the best body.
Hey, hit them no matter what.
Do it when the referee isn't watching,
okay?
Okay.
If we lose again today,
I'm going to hit you upside the head.
- Yes, sir.
Let's work hard.
Why aren't these bastards coming?
Hurry up and get your asses over here!
You take care of Crazy Mutt.
You know that
I hate guys like him, right?
Geez.
I got that goal in.
Geez... damn it.
Did you see that? He can't get it in.
Over here, over here!
Damn it.
[Audition of Love]
This one is a bit weak.
They don't get further
than just kissing.
Throw it out.
Don't disappoint me.
Give me some raunchy passages, okay?
Duk Seon!
The teacher is looking for you.
Hey... what do I do?
If you get caught,
just say that they're mine.
All you did was bring them to me.
Okay?
Duk Seon.
Yes, Teacher?
Pick up the phone.
It's from your family.
What?
Hello? Who is it?
If it weren't for Crazy Mutt,
we could have won 5-0.
No, 10-0.
Hey, what time is the movie tonight?
We can just skip night class, right?
Three o'clock.
You crazy bastard...
we're going to miss Math class!
No, Crazy Mutt...
the three of them are coming!
What?
Get out of my way.
You guys are real friendly.
Yes, sir. We're friends.
Hey, Student Council President.
You're all right at soccer.
Why don't you be the MVP from now on?
You do it!
Wow, look at his glare.
What are you going to do
by just glaring at me, huh?
You think you're hot shit
because you're the President?
And what's this? Is it a necklace?
Take it off, bastard.
A student can't wear
a necklace to school.
Huh?
You have to set an example
for the rest of the students, right, sir?
I said take it off, bastard.
Take it off.
Take it off!
Are you deaf?
I said, take it off,
bastard!
Hey.
We'll be late to our next class.
Come on.
Let's go.
This son of a bitch...
See you next time.
I'll kill you.
You dropped something.
Damn it... let's go.
We have orchestra.
Can't you just take that off
for a little bit?
My dad gave this to me,
how could I take it off?
Why can't you?
You can just put it back on later.
Geez... you're so frustrating.
Don't cry. Pack your bag and come.
Bo Ra.
Bo Ra!
It's okay. Stop crying.
Granny is in a better place now.
I told your teacher everything
so pack your bag quickly and come.
Bo Ra!
No Eul is coming, too.
There isn't much time. Hurry and come.
Bo Ra!
Hurry and go to sleep.
It'll be a while until we get to Goksung.
You won't be able to sleep there.
[Funeral Condolences]
Okay. I won't cry anymore.
Are you sadder than Dad?
Don't you cry, either.
We have to console Dad.
Let's go.
Is this really a funeral?
It feels more like a party.
This is Granny's house... right?
Bo Ra, you're here? Eat.
Where did Dad go?
I only see our aunts.
What if Dad is sick?
Oh. Hey, Bo Ra!
Dad...
What are you doing? Say hello.
Sir! This is my eldest, Bo Ra.
She goes to Seoul University,
the best college in the nation!
She's a student there!
- Hello.
- Yes, yes!
You're Bo Ra?
When did she grow up to be a lady?
Wow, you're so pretty
and study well to boot!
We couldn't send her to cram school
because we have no money
or get her a tutor.
Even so, she studied up all on her own.
And... this is my second eldest,
Duk Seon.
She's the one who was on TV!
This is Duk Seon! I saw her on TV!
Hey... after this is over,
let's take a photo together!
Yes, yes.
I heard that holding those picket signs
is really competitive.
Since you're seen on
international television and all.
I heard hundreds and thousands
competed for a spot!
That's amazing.
Oh yes, and the one on the end
is my youngest, No Eul.
He's more filial son than he seems.
He looks kind.
Sir. It's me, Jae Young.
You must be so mournful.
Oh my, Jae Young! You punk!
Wow, it's really been a while!
Wow... you look like you're
doing well for yourself nowadays!
No, sir.
Sit down, and let's have a drink.
- Yes, sir.
- Okay.
Bo Ra. Is Dad a cyborg?
How could he not shed
even one tear?
Wow... it's really been a long time
since I've seen you.
- Yes.
-
Are all adults like that?
They don't get sad?
Shush. Just keep frying these.
Our aunts, too.
It's their mother.
Is this the time to be
showing off her ring?
I told you, it's white gold!
White gold? Please.
This is so much better.
Just look at the design.
I feel so bad for Granny.
Geez... take the younger kids
and go to sleep.
I'll take care of this.
Uncle isn't coming?
We gave him a call as soon as
Granny passed out.
He didn't even to be by her side
during her final moments.
I'm sure he'll be here tomorrow.
It's not like the U.S.
is around the corner.
And there's nothing that can be done
if he can't come.
I feel so bad for Granny...
Stop crying.
I won't stand for it anymore.
What? I can't even cry if I want to?
You little...
Stop it. Other people are watching.
But... what if there are cops there?
You know how busy
Korean police officers are?
Why would they waste time
being there?
That's nonsense.
Why are the cops...
was there a thief?
It's probably because today's
the premiere. Tomorrow will be fine.
- You want to come back tomorrow?
- Of course!
- Let's go.
- Where? Back to school?
- Are you crazy? No. Taek's place.
- Why?
An erotic love tale among mulberry trees,
as sweet as honey.
I borrowed a steamy one.
Taxi!
I'm off!
Sun Woo!
You're going to be late
again today, right?
Uh... yeah.
Oh yeah, Mom.
When are you going to Goksong?
Tomorrow. I was going to go
with everyone in town.
Sun Woo. Your lunch will
be cold by dinnertime.
Buy yourself some cup noodles
to eat with it. How much do you need?
I only need 500 won.
Here's your lunch.
Eat it with some cup noodles.
How much is it?
10,000 won.
Want to die?
I'm off.
Oh my God! Geez.
Mother. Please just give me 10 won.
With just 10 won, I can play all day
with an Olympic legend.
Study, damn it.
Mother, please just give me 10 won!
Here he is.
Dong Il, wake up and have breakfast.
Okay? Breakfast.
Let's eat.
Geez... eat up.
Put the rice in the soup.
Oh. Thanks...
You didn't make any seasoned clams?
How come?
You don't need so much food
in the morning.
Eat it while it's still warm.
Okay.
Wow. This soup is great.
Wow. Rich kids are really
on a different level.
Here we go.
It's kimchi.
What the hell?
You only have kimchi?
Let's see what else.
Curry and rice.
Then eat that for dinner.
I think I will. I had curry
for breakfast, too.
All right.
Side dishes? Nope, none.
Do we have any soup?
No, we do not.
Then... kimchi fried rice. Damn.
Hey, have some of mine.
Wow, sausages.
It's hard to make these taste bad.
Shall I try one?
Ugh, it's so salty!
Just what the hell does
your mom make every day?
I think this tastes fine.
Huh?
Oh, it's just an eggshell. It's fine.
At your house, no one could gain
weight no matter how hard they tried.
Ugh, so salty.
Don't forget... round two today.
The cops are probably going to
be there today, too.
That's why I came prepared.
You guys are just nerds
with no street smarts.
What about dinner, though?
My mom packed me extra food.
It's all eggshell-encrusted
sausages, anyway.
I'll buy today.
Hamburgers. You down?
Of course.
We don't have much time. Strip!
Three soldiers.
Hey, wait.
I have to go to the bathroom.
What, already?
You crazy bastard.
Sun Woo.
He wants you to come over here, too.
Look at Uncle.
He's acting like nothing's wrong.
Hey. Even his wife, the daughter,
is acting fine.
So why would he be any different?
Bo Ra. Why are they singing?
Way to go, you little shits.
You're third years with
important exams coming up!
Are you bastards out of your mind?
You think you'll make it into college,
at this rate?
You really must be out of your
goddamned minds.
How dare you come here?
Geez... these bastards.
Oh, look here.
Isn't this my son?
You must be so busy studying, sir.
So how did you make time
to wander down here?
- Hello, Father.
- Yes, yes.
You see, I was just going to have partake
in some cultural education, and then...
What the hell did you say, bastard?
Cultural education, my ass.
- Why I ought to...
- Ow... Father, Father!
Who's your father, huh?
I'm sure your father died
from being worried sick about you!
If you're shit at studying,
don't cause any trouble, at least.
You useless little...
Geez.
Consider yourselves saved
thanks to Sun Woo. Got that?
All right?
Come to the teacher's lounge
after classes tomorrow. Got that?
- Yes, sir.
- Got that?
- Yes sir!
Got that?
- Yes, sir!
I'll see you later at home...
Don't you dare think about
coming home tonight, bastard.
I respect you, Father!
Wow, Mr. President.
Why don't we chat for a sec?
Hey.
Thanks.
How can I ever repay this debt to you?
- Upperclassman, it's not like that...
- Back off.
Hey, Mr. President.
I said thank you.
All right?
Look at this asshole.
His upperclassman
is saying something to him...
What's this?
I told you to take it off.
Take it off, bastard!
This bastard... hey.
That... that was Sun Woo's father's.
He got it as a keepsake
when his father passed away.
So what?
Can you disrespect your elders
because you have no dad?
You proud that you don't
have a dad or something?
You flaunting that, bastard?
Are you out of your mind,
you crazy bastard?
You just say whatever the hell comes
out of that shithole you call your mouth?
Choose your words before
you speak, asshole.
[Funeral Condolences]
I guess Uncle isn't coming.
It's almost 10:00 p.m.
Tomorrow's the wake so if he can't
make it today, he won't come.
Dad. Get some sleep.
Geez... my pretty and kind daughter.
Your Dad is fine.
I'm fine.
Dong Il.
Our poor mother...
Our poor mother!
Why did she have to go so soon?
Why?
Now we can't see her anymore!
I want to see Mom...
- Brother!
- You're here!
Why did you come so late?
We waited for so long!
You couldn't even say goodbye to her...
Mom wanted to see you so much!
It's just that adults keep it bottled up.
They were just busy being adults
and they just acted strong due to
the pressure that came with their age.
Adults feel pain, too.
I can't go on.
I can't go on without my mother!
Mom!
Mother!
Mother...
Sit down.
Give me your hand.
Bye.
Jung Hwan.
Can I sleep over at your place tonight?
I don't want to face my dad.
You think he won't know, you idiot?
What do we do about your necklace?
I'll just not wear it anymore.
What about your face, though?
Worry about yourself.
Bye.
Geez.
Even so, it's fine
to be deluded sometimes.
If you can make your mom happy
by making her think her cooking is good
it's easy enough to eat
disgusting lunches.
I'm home!
Oh, you're home, my son?
- Yes!
- Oh, my son!
I'm going to go wash up. Go to sleep.
Okay.
Wow... my Sun Woo ate all of his lunch.
They were good, huh?
Yeah!
They were delicious!
There's no need to force the harsh truth
onto a small bit of happiness.
Sometimes, you need an illusion
to be happy.
Another victory for Choi Taek,
"6-dan," has been reported in China.
Yesterday at 6:00 p.m.,
at the Tong Yang Cup
taking place at the Shangri-La Hotel
in Beijing.
Choi Taek, "6-dan"
beat Jeo Bi Pyung, "9-dan"
with 343 moves.
Choi Taek, "6-dan," came back to Korea
through Gimpo Airport this morning.
In order to celebrate his
18th birthday...
I'm sure Taek's mother
is so happy up in Heaven.
What a filial son he is.
Oh, please. Death is the end.
What good are filial deeds
after your parent dies?
You have to treat your parents well
while they're around.
Is it a blackout?
I think it's just the bulb.
I'll go buy one. Give me some money.
On your way back, get 200 won's worth
of bean sprouts too
so we can have some soup
tomorrow morning.
Don't drink, honey.
All right, all right.
Oh, Mr. Choi!
Are you heading home?
Hello, sir.
Hey, Taek... today...
can you be my drinking buddy?
Wow... our Taek is an adult now.
When did you become so mature?
You're all grown now.
Mister.
I heard that your mother passed away.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't even visit.
Why are you bringing that up?
I'm going to start crying.
That's right.
Mothers tend to be the one you miss
the most, whether they're alive or dead.
Oh yeah... I even got to see
my older brother.
Taek.
When do you miss
your mother most?
Hmm?
Every day.
I miss my mom every single day.
An adult-like child is just one
without complaints.
It's just that they've acclimated
to the world of adults
and they've grown used to
the illusions around them.
An adult-like child
is just that, a child.
An illusion is short,
but a misunderstanding lasts a long time.
That's why illusions offer freedom while
misunderstandings chain you down.
Happy birthday to you,
happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Taek!
Happy birthday to you!
Yay!
Come home earlier! Sheesh.
Look here.
Hey, change into something else.
Are you a grandpa?
I thought I'd die of starvation
waiting for you.
We even called you!
Hurry up and blow it out.
It's going to blow out.
Hurry.
Hurry! One, two, three!
- Here, your present.
- Yay!
[Jeon In Kwon]
We're done now, right?
Where is it, huh? Hurry it up.
- Where is it?
- Take it out!
Here, here.
Hey, let's do this later.
Where is it?
Let's watch TV.
Hurry up and take it out!
Hey, let me see.
Where is it? Hey, lower the volume!
Taek, you're not going to eat
all this, right? I'm taking it home!
- Okay?
- Where is it?
Hey, it's obviously in his bag!
Geez!
Bag! Give me that.
Let me see. Open it.
All right, all right, all right!
It's a good one! Nice job!
Mom! These kids are drinking!
Stop screaming! Hey!
Ow!
They're drinking!
Taek was the last one to move here.
After his mother passed away,
they left
her hometown which was
full of her scent and came to Seoul.
We don't know why this father and son
chose this block in particular
but what I am sure of
is that the four troublemakers of
this block found a new friend.
Taek was a quiet kid.
So the boisterous kids on this block
may have been too much for him.
Even so, Taek was always with us.
Even when we were
doing mischievous things
or doing pathetic things
he was always by our side.
Of course, he always had
an expressionless face.
But even so, he was with us.
Still, the block creates friendships
just through the power of time.
That is how the taciturn child
and the four noisy kids became friends.
And that's how we became five.
Geez... really.
Just from drinking this?
And here, I thought you guys
could handle your liquor.
Hey.
Just try it, then. You'll die.
Who do you think I am?
Oh... hey!
Hey! You're all dead!
Ugh... ow!
Ugh... what do I do?
She's pretty. Joey Wang.
Yeah.
There's no such girl in real life.
Who do you think is the prettiest?
Um... Joey Wang.
We said there's no such woman
in real life.
I've also fallen for another girl
at Jung Yi Performing Arts High School.
The girl with the short hair
with the pale face?
How did you guys know?
Everyone has a crush on her.
Then... there's another girl
that I've fallen for, in the study room.
She's a Third Year with long hair.
She goes to a performing arts school.
And wears a white cardigan, right?
You little punks...
you don't study but only ogle at girls?
Who else has a pretty face?
Also...
You have another one?
Doesn't it seem like Duk Seon has
gotten just a little bit cuter, lately?
Huh?
Yeah.
Yeah. A little.
Hey, Taek. What about you?
Yeah.
Hey, Jung Hwan.
You all must be crazy!
You're all out of your minds.
Are you all drunk?
Geez.
You've all had too much.
Dammit! You farted!
Ew, it smells!
Stop that, already!
Why did you have to fart on us?
Damn it...
[Sung Duk Seon]
You read it, didn't you?
Read what?
My diary!
No.
Yeah, you did!
I told you, I didn't. Stop being so loud.
It's coming out of my mouth,
so mind your own!
Be quiet!
You read it, didn't you?
I told you, I didn't!
Mom!
You read it, didn't you?
Be quiet.
You did.
I told you, I didn't.
"At the hour when everything
is draped in darkness..."
"and therefore,
becomes a lonelier time..."
"at this time,
when the world is asleep..."
"my feelings for you cannot
seem to become still with the night."
I'm going to kill you! Hey!
"They say that feelings
are for expressing."
"That's why I have to become brave
and let these words escape my lips..."
Hey!
Mom! Duk Seon has someone she likes!
She even gave them chocolate!
Hey!
[2015]
How did I write these words
if I was sane at the time?
I want to throw it away,
but I don't know where I can.
I'm afraid to put it in the trash
in case someone finds it...
Oh my God... what nonsense.
You were a totally
rebellious kid back then.
Why did you spend time
with so many guys?
You read my diary, didn't you?
Wow. I can't believe you.
What the hell.
You read my diary, right?
- No.
- Yeah, you did!
I didn't.
Hey. Be honest with me.
How can you say "hey"
to your husband?
If you can say it,
why can't I?
You did read it, didn't you?
I didn't!
Who did you give the chocolate to?
It wasn't me.
Jesus...
Why did you read someone else's diary?
Huh? Why?
Who did you give it to?
I gave it to you!
You want to die?
It wasn't me!
Yeah, it was.
It wasn't you?
I'll come back after a smoke.
It was you!
I told you, it wasn't me!
Geez... it was him.
It's been almost 30 years,
so I guess he forgot.
He was so smart back then, too.
Jin Joo.
Does it taste good?
Where are you going?
To go eat ddukbokki!
Goodbye!
Your sister is going on
a field trip tomorrow!
I don't know!
Hey!
Duk Seon.
Want to eat ramyun?
Duk Seon! Sung Duk Seon!
Duk Seon!
Sung Duk Seon!
Sun Woo is going to break the door.
Bye.
What are you going to do?
What?
It looks like he likes you.
Let's go, Sun Woo.
Subtitles by DramaFever