-That one.
-That one? Alright.
So when he rocks up,
all you gotta do is say you
wanna see the guns first, ok?
How's that? No, that way?
Yeah? Ok, good.
-Go and annoy your mum, angel.
-Girl: Mum, I want to play!
Doesn't matter
what he wants to do.
-You've gotta see the guns.
-Alright.
Now, guys,
you gotta be aggressive.
Can't be fucking around
with this guy.
We gotta fuck him up.
If we don't,
he's gonna start thinking
he can come back at us
and we don't want that.
-Girl: Daddy!
-Why don't we just knock him?
Why knock him
if we don't need to?
Trust me, if we do this right,
this motherfucker's
not gonna come back at us.
Hey, blood capsules, yeah?
Fake blood.
Whack two in your gob. Put 'em
in the corner of your mouth.
Then when we start
to give you a bit
of a touch-up,
you can bite down on 'em,
make it look like
we've gone to town on you.
Jesus, mate. I don't really like
the sound of that, to be honest.
Don't be a fucking pussy.
We're not gonna fucking hurt ya.
We gotta make it look good
so they don't think
it's a fucking set-up.
(kids shout)
ok.
-Have you got that?
-Yeah.
-Are we good?
(splashing and laughter)
-woman: Good job, honey.
-Child: No!
(insects chirp)
(rubbing)
(engine rumbles in distance)
(brakes squeak, engine stops)
(doors open)
-how youse going?
-Good, mate. How you doing?
Not too bad.
How you wanna do it?
Oh, you show me the toys,
I'll get you the cash.
Alright.
(bag rattles)
(man grunts) have a look.
-Happy?
-Righto.
-Get on the fucking ground, pal!
-Whoa, whoa!
Don't you move!
Don't you fucking move!
-Get the fuck on the ground!
-Alright, mate.
-Get down now! Get down now!
-On the fucking ground, cunt!
-Get the fuck down!
-Get down there, you...
(grunting)
-abracadabra! Get the fuck down!
-Ugh!
-Ohh!
-Get down!
-Oh, fuck!
-Get on the fucking ground!
-(grunting)
-get on the fucking ground, bro!
-Fuck you!
-(groans)
(grunting and shouting)
(imitates groaning)
grab the fucking bag!
You stay the fuck down!
I've got the guns,
I've got the guns. Let's go!
-Huh!
-Hurry up!
Let's get out of here!
Fuck you. Stay down, you fuck!
(moans)
(coughs and gasps)
(car doors thud, engine starts)
oh...
Shit, boys. Fuck!
You right, mate? Mate?
Oh, come on, mate.
We gotta get you
out of here, mate.
Come on. I'll get you up.
I'll get you up.
(grunts) come on, come on.
Come on, mate.
I'll get you back to the car.
(groans)
here. Come on.
There you go.
Get your legs up.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit. Mate, come on.
Hey, mate, we gotta get you up.
Come on. We gotta
get you out of here.
Oh, shit. Come on.
(groans)
(grunting)
oh, come on. Get up. Come on.
Here we go.
(speaks indistinctly)
here we go. Come on.
Get in, get in.
(pants) get in.
(man mumbles)
oh, go on.
(grunts)
(pants)
alright, I gotta
get the fuck out of here.
Ohh... Ok.
(starts engine)
(tyres squeal)
(moans softly)
(birds chirp)
how you feeling?
Not great.
Why'd you run me over?
You know why.
Mate, I had nothing
to do with the rip-off.
-Who else knew?
-Mate, how would I know?!
What, you reckon I told anybody?
Cut the shit, will ya, mate?
Mate, I'm telling ya!
Okey-dokey.
I just want the guns back, mate.
That's all I care about.
Honestly, I swear
on my kid's life...
(motor sputters)
-(motor starts)
-come on, mate.
Please! Come on!
Come on! I swear to god!
Mate!
Come on! Please, mate!
-(motor revs)
-please! Please...
Ok, ok!
Ok, ok! Ok!
-Ok, ok, ok, ok!
-(stops motor)
(pants)
ok.
Ok, what?
Ok, I'll get the guns for ya.
I want names too.
I can't...I can't
give you names.
But I can...I can
get the guns back, ok?
You just...You just
gotta give me my phone.
-Names.
-Mate, I can't give you names.
Why can't you give me names?
Look.
These blokes...
Like, they're my mates,
you know?
Like, I've known these guys
my entire life.
Like, I just can't give 'em up.
Ok? Like, I'm sorry.
I just fucking can't.
Well, you're a loyal bastard,
mate. I'll give you that.
Give your mates a call, huh?
(grunts)
(line rings)
-man: Heya.
-Mate, it's me.
-Fuck, steve, what's going on?
-Look. We, uh...
We gotta give
the guns back. Yeah?
No, look, mate.
They...They know.
-What do you mean, they know?
-Ok, they know.
What? You fucking told them?
Yeah, well, I fucking had to!
He was about to chop me fucking
leg off with a fucking chainsaw!
"everything will be fine,"
you fucking said.
Well, it ain't fucking fine!
Ok, I've been run over
by a fucking car.
I've been chained
to a fucking fence all night.
-Fucking come and get me!
-Calm the fuck down.
No, don't tell me
to fucking calm down!
(man on phone
speaks indistinctly)
shit!
You got a pen there?
Uh... Yeah.
Ok.
Farley's brook, harndorff road.
There's an old, uh, farmhouse
there called belleview.
There's a sign out the front.
You got four hours.
You bring the guns,
30 grand cash
or we got a problem.
(phone beeps)
(handbrake creaks)
(engine stops)
(birds squawk)
how'd you pull up?
Not bad.
So how you wanna do this?
Guns and cash first, please.
You alright?
Yeah.
-The cash?
-(scoffs)
our lad first, hey?
(mutters)
I'll see you 'round, hey?
(engine starts)
-oh, fuck!
-Get out, get out!
Oh, fuck!
(gunfire and shouting)
-ugh!
-Oh!
Jim! Fuck!
(all grunt)
-(gunfire continues)
-oh, fuck!
-(grunts)
-(man shouts)
ugh!
-No!
-No, steve! Wait!
-Arggh!
-Get up, steve!
Get up!
Bastards!
-Steve!
-(groans)
fuck! Fuck, steve! Get up!
Fuck, steve!
Come on, mate. Come on.
I fucking need you
to get up. Come on!
Ohh!
Ugh!
(pants)
oh!
Fuck. (groans)
oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
(grunts and pants)
oh...
(breathes heavily)
(gags)
bit off more than
I could chew, eh?
Just a little.
Sorry about that beating, mate.
It was nothing personal.
Don't worry about it.
Should...Should've just
given you the fucking cash.
Coulda, shoulda.
It don't matter now.
Well, no, but,
you know, my boys...
I got 'em killed, hey?
(gurgles)
what's your name?
Huh...
Graham.
Ray.
(wheezes and gurgles)
(exhales)
eh...
(sighs)
(zipper buzzes)
fucking hell.
What's that?
Yeah, three-way split.
Nah, you guys split it.
-What?
-I don't want it.
You ok, ray?
Easy, tiger.
(low, sombre music)
(exhales)
(sighs)
(machine whirrs)
(light rock music
plays on stereo)
what's your birthdate?
25 March '76.
You're a dragon.
-Is that good?
-Yeah.
You're in my
triangle of affinity.
What's that?
It's where there's three
animal signs in a triangle.
Dragon - you, me -
and then monkey and rat.
Is that what your mum is, a rat?
No, she's a tiger.
Tigers don't get along
with dragons, though.
That's why you got divorced.
So if you want
to get married again,
you need to find someone
who's a dragon, monkey or rat.
Easy-peasy.
People don't
say that anymore, dad.
It's, like, circa 1980.
Ok, word nazi.
Ok, boomer. You can just
drop me here, dad.
-What for?
-Just drop me here.
-Yeah, but why?
-'cause.
What, you too embarrassed to be
seen with your old man now, hey?
Just drop me here.
(kids chatter)
'bye.
-No kiss?
-I'm 12.
(window whirrs)
(shouts) love you, brit!
-(girl laughs)
-girl 2: "love you, brit!"
little shit.
-Girl: 'bye, dad.
-Man: 'bye. See you tonight.
(bell rings)
(men chatter)
man: Hey! Whoa!
Fucking serious?
(mutters) fucking jerk-off.
Man: Good on ya, fucking idiot.
Man: Oh, here we go.
Man 2: What's your
problem, dickhead?
You're slapping the mirror.
What's your problem?
You're supposed
to stop, dipshit.
Why is that, mate?
Because it's
a pedestrian crossing, mate.
So where's the white stripes
painted on the road and the sign
that says it's a pedestrian
crossing, then, buddy?
-Still a crossing, you fuckwit.
-Is it?
-Oh!
-Hey!
Are you for real?
(siren blips)
oh, fuck.
(lock buzzes)
(people chatter lowly)
kelsey?
Back against the wall.
Ok, we're gonna
conduct a search on you.
Listen to the instructions
given to you.
Do exactly what I say.
Do you understand that?
-Yep.
-Ok.
To start off, take the shirt
off and hand it to me.
Underwear off and hand it
to the officer.
Lift your balls.
Right up.
Leg out like that.
And now the other leg.
(lock clicks, gate creaks)
just wait there. Yep.
(gate slams)
(lock rattles and clicks)
(man shouts in distance)
(indistinct chatter on radio)
man: Hey, sweeties, how are ya?!
(prisoners shout and whistle)
(door clangs, lock clicks)
(muffled shouting in distance)
-(footsteps pace outside)
-(door clunks nearby)
(keys jangle)
(prisoners jeer
and shout outside)
(door clangs)
ray: How you going,
mate? Alright?
Sorry.
(door shuts, lock clicks)
(shouting and banging outside)
-first time in, huh?
-Yeah.
You can tell?
Yeah, normally
we don't shit in the cell
'cause it stinks the joint out.
(flushes toilet)
shit, sorry, mate.
That's alright. You didn't know.
Cheers.
If you need to shit,
just use the communal dunnies
down the hallway.
-Right, yep.
-Yeah.
I'm adam.
So what are you in for?
Oh, it's a...Long story.
Got plenty of time.
Uh, I'm...
Well, my wife started
seeing this dude
behind my back for a while.
-Mmm.
-Like... Yeah.
You know, it wasn't
the first time.
Mmm.
But, yeah, she was
seeing this dude
and she took off with him,
and I didn't really
give a shit about that.
Uh, well, like, I did.
The problem was, um,
we have a kid together
and, yeah, so I just...I just
wanted to see my daughter
and make sure she was ok
'cause, yeah, she's only 9.
Yeah, anyway,
to cut a long story short,
she took an avo out on me
and I didn't realise, like,
you can't even text somebody
when they've taken
an avo out on ya.
I texted her a few times
just saying, you know,
I want to see my daughter
and all that,
and, yeah, she told the cops
and so now I'm in here
for breaching the avo.
-Oh, that's fucked.
-Yeah.
What are you in here for?
Rape.
Shit.
Mmm.
I should stop, but I just
fucking love doing it, you know?
-Love raping.
-Yeah?
Oh, yeah, well, you've got...
You're probably... Yeah.
That's... Yeah, it's not
for me to judge, hey?
-You never raped anybody?
-Me? No.
How come?
Um...How come?
I just... Yeah,
don't know really.
Just not really into it.
But, like...
What, do you think
there's something
wrong with it or something?
No, no. Like...
Ray: Yeah.
I mean, it's not like
I rape women and shit.
Oh, ok.
Just blokes.
Huh. Yeah, well...
Oh, you fuck.
(adam laughs) fuck me.
Oh!
I'm ray anyway.
I'm adam.
-Good to meet you.
-Fucking hell.
Almost had
a fucking heart attack.
-Sorry about that, mate.
-(laughs)
couldn't resist. Had to do it.
(laughs)
jacinta on phone:
Hey, it's your dad.
-Brittany: Hello?
-Hey, sweetheart.
-How are ya?
-Good. Where are you?
Ray: Uh, queensland.
Yeah, I know.
But where in queensland?
Um...
Near brisbane.
-How's school?
-Good.
When are you coming back?
Oh, hopefully, you know, like...
Probably two, three weeks maybe.
What do you mean, hopefully?
Oh, not hopefully.
You know what I mean?
Um...
Just, you know,
like, I'll probably
be back in...
You know, probably
two to three weeks.
Why are you being weird?
I'm not being weird.
I'm just, uh...
You know, everything's good.
And, uh, you know,
just look forward
to seeing you when I get back.
-Ok.
-Ok?
Alright, I love you.
Love you.
(line clicks and beeps)
dad's being weird.
Jacinta: Mm, what's new?
('a well respected man'
by the kinks)
♪ 'cause he gets up
in the morning
♪ and he goes to work at nine
♪ and he comes back home at 5:30
♪ gets the same train every time
♪ 'cause his world
is built 'round punctuality
♪ it never fails
♪ and he's, oh, so good
♪ and he's,
oh, so fine