‐Hey. What's going on?
‐Hey.
What you doing?
Prepping.
For what?
For what's coming.
Ooh.
‐What are these?
‐They're silica packs.
They help the food last longer.
How's your porn business going?
Yeah, good, mate.
Business cards are done.
Website went up yesterday.
Pass them around.
Holy shit, mate. Professional.
GARY: Schmicko.
Naughty Boy Productions.
Gary speaking.
Yeah, sure, mate.
Uh, well, it's $1,500
and, for that,
you get two copies
either on DVD or...
‐Dad?
‐What's going on?
Can I go hang out
with my friends?
‐Now?
‐Yeah.
Where?
‐The beach?
‐What beach?
‐Clovelly.
‐Alright. Grab your stuff.
Sorry, who am I speaking with?
OK, Lucas, we'll be in touch.
OK, 'bye for now.
I got a job!
Ray!
‐RAY: Yep. Mm.
Alright, love,
I'll see you at about 4:00.
‐OK.
‐Have fun.
‐See ya, Brit.
‐'Bye.
‐GIRL: Hi.
‐BRITTANY: Hi.
Watch out for sharks!
Nothing.
‐GARY: Doesn't even care.
‐RAY: Nah.
GARY: Couldn't care less.
RAY: Yeah,
but you can't say that.
‐GARY: Why can't you say it?
‐You just can't.
I mean, you can say, "OK,
I don't think there is one,
"but you can't say that
there definitely isn't one."
So, you think there is one?
‐There's gotta be.
‐Why?
Big Bang.
Yeah?
‐Trillions of years ago, right?
‐Yeah.
OK? What they're saying is,
there's nothing.
All of a sudden,
Big Bang, right?
Mm‐hm.
And then you've got a universe,
right?
You've got billions of planets,
‐Yeah.
‐Where'd they come from?
‐Fuck knows.
‐Exactly, right.
Something had to be there,
right, to make the universe.
Right, but if there was nothing
before the Big Bang,
then how can nothing
make something?
It can't, right?
‐Nothing, right...
‐Yeah...
..can't make something.
Yeah. So, you're saying...
What...
What the fuck are you saying?
‐Something, right...
‐Yeah.
..had to be there.
‐A god?
‐God.
‐Right. OK.
‐Right?
You can't get something
out of nothing.
‐Right.
‐Right?
You can't get a bang
and a universe out of nothing.
Right.
So, you gotta have something...
‐Yeah.
‐..to get something.
‐Right, OK.
‐Alright?
Sure. OK. Alright.
Hang on a minute.
Where are they going?
Is he smoking?
GARY: He's fucking smoking!
RAY: Little shithead.
GARY: What a scumbag!
GARY: He's offering her a drag.
She said no.
Good girl, Brit. Good girl!
Is he making a move?
He's making a move.
RAY: If he starts
feeling her up,
I'm gonna go down there
and rip his tiny dick off.
GARY: What's going on?
RAY: Ah, she's giving him
the flick.
GARY: What's she looking at?
I think she's making a call.
'Sup, sweetheart?
BRITTANY OVER PHONE: Hello.
'Sup?
Since you're here, can you buy
me and my friends some chips?
Yeah, OK.
‐Thank you.
‐See ya.
Sprung.
Made by a 12‐year‐old.
Hey.
What's going on?
‐You alright?
‐It's the, uh...
It's the old man.
He's, um...
He topped himself.
Oh, Jesus Christ, mate.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, mate. Shit.
Yeah.
Mate, I was in here, like,
a couple of weeks ago.
He was good as gold, you know?
Yeah.
Is your mum alright?
Don't know what to say, mate.
Sorry. I mean,
I'm fucking speechless.
‐I mean, it's...
‐Yeah.
What about a coffee
or something?
We'll go and have a chat.
What do you reckon?
‐Yeah.
‐Yeah?
‐Yeah, OK.
‐Sound good? Alright, mate.
‐Let's go do that.
‐OK. Yeah.
Jesus, man, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, no, yeah,
so, there was this guy
that started training at the gym
a couple of years ago
and Dad took him under his wing,
as he does...
..and he, um...
He got the old man to invest
in this business,
this tea, this Chinese tea,
a weight‐loss tea.
Mm.
So, he got him
to take out a loan,
put the gym up as collateral.
Anyway, turns out the tea
wasn't a weight‐loss tea.
It was a scam.
‐And he wants the gym?
‐Yeah.
Anything I can do?
Nah, mate. It's fine.
I'm taking care of it.
You gonna whack him?
Not me,
but the wheels are in motion.
‐You gonna pay somebody?
‐Already have.
‐How much?
‐30 K.
You gonna waste 30 grand
on this prick, are you?
Fuckin' oath.
Why should he get off scot‐free?
He should suffer.
‐Dead men don't suffer, mate.
‐Yeah, well...
I'll look into it, alright?
What are you gonna do?
I'll do something.
Who's this guy
you gave the 30 K to?
He's a mate of mine.
Alright.
COMMENTATOR ON RADIO: Here we
are, ladies and gentlemen,
on this beautiful sunny day
at Randwick Racecourse.
Race 6 is about to start.
They're getting them lined up.
There they are.
‐How you doing?
‐You right there?
‐I'm a mate of Killian's.
‐Oh, OK.
Do you mind if I come in and
have a chat to you for a minute?
Uh, look, listen, mate,
I really...
I got a bunch of shit to do,
alright?
Did he give you some money
for a job or something or...?
Uh, what's it...
What's it to you?
I'm a friend of the family's
and Killer wants to cancel
the job, so...
What, Killian?
He...he never said nothing to me
about calling the job off.
Yeah, well, that's why I'm here,
to tell you, so...
Yeah, but, well,
why didn't he say something?
Does it matter?
Well, I...
Yeah, but I just don't see...
Why are you getting involved?
Well, you don't need to know
why I'm getting involved.
OK, alright.
Listen here, champion,
this is none of your business,
alright?
Well, I'm making it
my fucking business.
‐Yeah?
‐Yeah.
‐Where's the dough?
‐What dough?
‐The 30 K, mate.
‐I don't have the dough.
Why not?
Look, I‐I gave it to
a mate of mine, alright?
I'm not gonna...
He's gonna do the job.
Who's this mate of yours, then?
He's...he's just a mate.
Alright, let's go see him,
then, alright?
OK.
‐OK.
‐ Alright.
‐You got your phone?
‐Yeah.
Give him a call.
Um... Look, I don't...
I don't even...
Spit it out.
I‐I didn't give the money
to him yet.
I spent it.
That's no good.
What the fuck do you want
from me, you fucking...
Look, I've got it.
I've got the money.
"CHOPIN'S 'NOCTURNE' Op. 9 No. 2
PLAYS QUIETLY"
COMMENTATOR:
..right down the outside...
..market
and see how we finished
today's trading session,
and, in one word, higher.
But, no, a decent day.
‐About 0.4% for the...
Similar for the XJO,
really powered today by
the materials and energy sector.
FEMALE ANCHOR: But there was
a lot going on under the hood.
Hello if you're watching us
on Twitter.
Here are some of
the market's best today.
Gold doing well.
A lot of the resources names
doing very well.
WorleyParsons came out at the
Macquarie Conference updating,
saying guidance is on track,
improved result...
How's the shares going?
Who the fuck are you?
You have a lovely house, mate.
What the fuck are you doing
in my house?
What sort of car's that you got?
Uh, it's a 911.
Ah. Nice.
You wanna sit down there for me,
mate, please?
1958.
Looks expensive.
What did that set you back?
Four grand.
Jeez, mate.
You must be doing alright.
So, sorry to barge in on you,
but I wanted to have a chat
to you about old Bobby Jenkins.
‐OK. What's up?
‐Do you know he topped himself?
Oh, fuck!
Eugh.
So, what was this business thing
you had going with him?
Well, basically, it was...
I found out about this tea.
Bai Ling tea.
A friend of mine who's Chinese
put me on to it
and, well, apparently...
..apparently it's a big thing
in China with weight loss.
Turns out it's not really
that effective,
so there was some bad press
about the product in the media
and it kind of snowballed
from there.
RAY: Mm. Mm.
You ever done any time?
Uh, no.
No?
No.
OK.
Now, you know why
I did that, right?
'Cause I lied.
Bingo.
So, what did you do time for,
mate?
Fraud.
Fraud. Ah.
So, the whole Chinese tea thing,
that was a load of shit,
wasn't it?
‐Yes.
‐Mm.
But you took old Bob's money
anyway, didn't you?
Yep. I'm sure you're not going
to believe me, but I am sorry.
I never thought...
How was I to...
So, you're sorry.
‐Yes.
‐Yep. OK.
So, now you're gonna do
the right thing.
‐How much did he give you?
220 K.
Alright, well, you're gonna
have to come up with some cash.
Look, I've only got
a few hundred in the house,
but I might have...
I might have five or six K
in the bank.
That's all you got?
Yeah, well, when the business
went bust, I lost the lot.
So, why are you drinking $4,000
bottles of wine, then, mate?
Well...
We can go down to
the bank right now.
There may even be
eight K in there.
Mate, I don't think
eight K's gonna do it.
Now, just make sure, right,
you keep your eyes closed, OK?
'Cause this shit burns
like a motherfucker.
No, hold on. Hold on! Hold on!
I've got cash! I've got money!
Whatever you want!
How much do you want?
‐How much you got?
Huh? How much have you got?
Go on.
Get a bag.
‐Hey.
‐G'day, mate.
‐Lucas.
‐Gary.
‐Nice to meet you, mate.
‐Nice to meet you too.
‐Come in. Come in.
‐Yeah? All good. OK.
‐Oh, you good?
‐Yeah, yeah. That's alright.
As long as
I can get through there.
‐No dramas. Just through there.
‐Thanks, mate.
‐Find the house alright?
‐Yeah, yeah, no problem.
All good. All good.
Wow.
‐This is plush.
‐Thank you.
‐How long you lived here?
‐Uh, about 3, 3.5 years.
OK, yeah, great, great. Yeah.
‐You mind if I set up there?
‐For sure. Go for it.
OK. Can I... Can I get you
a drink or something?
‐Do you want a wine?
‐No, I'm alright, thanks.
He looks more like
a beer drinker to me.
Oh, Gary,
this is my partner, Benjamin.
Hey. G'day, mate. How you going?
Good.
Gary.
‐Nice to meet you.
‐Yeah, you too.
Um, can we get you a beer
or something, Gary?
Oh, no, I'm OK, mate.
‐Gotta stay sharp.
‐Oh, right.
Well, I'm definitely gonna
have a martini. Thank you.
So, is it just the two of you?
What do you mean?
Oh, I charge by numbers,
so, you know,
sometimes people like to squeeze
another one in last minute.
‐Oh, sure.
‐Yeah.
‐Yeah, it's just the two of us.
‐OK, cool.
The fuck?
Where did you find this guy?
I found him online.
Can we give you a hand at all?
No, no.
I'm all good, mate. Thanks.
Um, there's a power point
just there if you need it.
Yeah, that's all good.
Everything's charged.
Everything alright, Gary?
‐Huh?
‐You OK?
OK.
How do you want to do this?
‐Um...
Well, we were kind of hoping
you would tell us that.
Yeah. You're the director.
Oh, yeah, right. OK.
Alright, well...
..why don't we start
on the couch?
‐Yeah, sure.
‐Perfect.
‐Suits me.
‐OK.
So, do we start out standing...
Yeah, like,
sort of foreplay first...
Yeah, and, like, kiss and stuff
and then, um,
maybe we can sort of
rumble our way in to the couch,
into, like,
this sort of a position?
That.
Well,
at Naughty Boy Productions,
we like to customise the shoot
to your needs,
so it just depends on
what it is that you're after.
I mean, what kind of feel
are you after?
Do you want more of
a handheld doco style
or a bit more of
a Hollywood movie style feel?
Oh, God,
I hadn't thought about it.
Yeah, look, I mean, I...
I don't want anything that's
too sort of, you know, raw.
You know, something
a little bit more polished,
I think, would be good.
It's not like
your mum's seeing it.
A little bit raw's fine.
‐Polished?
‐Well, polished.
Polished it is.
Alright, well, um,
I'll work off the tripod.
Come on.
‐OK, come on.
‐Get this off.
Let's get this off, silly.
‐Hey, Gary.
‐Yeah.
This is so exciting.
Yeah, it's gonna be fun.
‐Yeah.
‐OK.
WOMAN: How are you today?
Nice to see you again.
Son?
‐Having a snooze?
‐Yes, I nodded off.
Just dropping your, uh...
..your clothes off
from your apartment.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks very much for that.
No worries, mate. Alright.
I'll catch you later, alright?
Son?
Can...can you stay for a bit?
Just a minute.
I've got a heap of stuff
I've got to do...
Please, just...
Please can you stay
for a minute?
Please.
Sit down. Please sit down.
So, you remember me today, huh?
Yeah, I'm having
a good day today.
That's good.
Look, there's something
I want to say,
and if I don't say it now,
I may not get another chance.
I just want to say I'm sorry.
I know...
it won't mean a whole lot...
..and I know
it won't change the past,
but when I came back
from Vietnam...
..I was messed up.
I came back here and people
were calling me a baby‐killer
and a murderer
and all that shit.
I came back to you proud, son.
I served my country
and I saw some things
over there...
I did some things,
things that I'm not proud of,
but you've got do what
you've got to do to survive.
I came back here
and I was just messed up.
They put me on medication
because I was suicidal
and I was angry.
I started drinking
while I was on the meds and...
..that just made me worse.
So, why'd you drink, then?
'Cause I couldn't cope.
Even with the meds,
I just could not cope.
Look, I'm not trying to
make excuses for what I did.
I'm just trying to explain
what happened.
I'm not dodging responsibility.
I just wish...
I just wish you had've
known me before I went to war.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
NICK CAVE: ♪ I don't believe
♪ In an interventionist god
♪ But I know, darling,
that you do
♪ But if I did
♪ I would kneel down and ask him
♪ Not to intervene... ♪