-Adam: Don't get an audi.
-Ray: Why not?
Mate, audi drivers.
No good?
The worst fucking drivers
on the road.
I thought mercedes drivers
were the worst drivers.
Nah, mercedes drivers
number two.
-Yeah?
-Audi, number one worst.
Ray: Oh.
I reckon the thing is
with audis,
like, don't get me wrong,
they're great cars,
they're luxury cars,
but they're actually
not that expensive.
So I think the people
who buy them,
they actually want a beemer
or a mercedes
but they can't afford them.
Yeah.
But they still want people
to think they've got money
'cause, you know, they're
arseholes, so they get the audi.
Ah, I got you.
So if I buy one,
does that mean I'm an arsehole?
-Hey.
-What's going on?
Same old shit. You good?
Good as you can be
in this place, eh.
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Yeah.
Oh, this is adam.
-Hey.
Look, I gotta go shower,
but, um, you know, we'll talk.
-Oh, yeah. Catch you later.
-See you later, alright?
-See you, champ.
-What'd you call me?
-What?
-You heard.
Uh, you can't say that word,
mate.
-Why?
-It's just not a good word.
Yeah, ok. Sorry.
He's just a newbie, mate.
No offence.
What the fuck?
-'champ' means 'cocksucker'.
-Oh, fuck off.
How the fuck am I supposed
to know that?
Well, you know now, don't you?
(indistinct chatter)
-(door buzzes and opens)
-ray: Thanks, mate. Cheers.
-How are you?
-I'm good.
-How's the club?
-Yeah, good. Yeah.
Fuckin' sweet, I've never
visited anyone inside before.
Me neither.
(chuckles)
you got a good lawyer?
Yeah, I think he's pretty good.
But he's fucking exy.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Anything I can do?
Uh, I got a mate
looking into it,
so, uh, see what happens.
-But I appreciate it.
-Ok.
How's your kid?
Yeah, she's good.
She's, uh, growing up.
-Yeah. How old is she now?
-12.
-Yeah.
She's at that stage, uh,
she just wants to hang out
with her friends and that
and, uh, yeah,
feel a bit left out but...
Yeah, mate, I hear you,
but don't take it personally.
-It's how kids are built.
-Mmm.
You know, they need you,
which is great,
and then one day they don't.
And it's, uh...
It's hard in a way,
but, uh, they come back.
Yeah.
Hey, uh...
..I got a job for you
if you're interested.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna be in here
for a while, mate, so...
Yeah, no, the job's in here.
What's that?
(softly) the...The job's
in here.
Ah. Ok. Um...
It's a guy called johnny tran.
You know him?
Nuh.
It's...It's not for me.
It's for a guy I know.
And what's the job?
The guy's being
a bit of a dickhead,
so, you know,
just fuck him up a bit.
Nothing permanent.
-How much?
-10.
What do you reckon?
Yeah.
Alright.
(sighs) yeah.
How's the food been?
That good? (chuckles)
-what's your problem, huh?
-Nothing.
-What did you fucking say?
-Harris.
Yeah, you'll keep.
(indistinct radio communication)
adam: Reckon he'll do something?
Ray: Probably.
What do I do?
Get in first.
-Hit him?
-Mm-hm.
No, I can't.
Oh, well,
maybe he'll leave you alone.
You don't think he will, though?
Nuh.
That's fucked.
I mean, I didn't even...
How am I supposed to know that
you can't say fuckin' 'champ'?
He don't hear much, so, uh,
you better do something
about him.
Mate, I can't fight.
Mate, most fucking guys
in here can't fight.
Alright? They're just bullies.
You know, looking for people
who can't stand up
for themselves, right?
So if you don't stand up
and do something about it,
you're gonna have half the
pricks in here after you.
Well, I don't want that.
But have you seen
the fucking size of the guy?
Doesn't matter.
-Doesn't matter?
-Nuh.
Ok, then why do they have
weight limits in the ufc?
Mate, doesn't matter
how big he is,
doesn't matter how big you are,
right?
In a real fucking fight,
the only thing that matters
is the size of this thing here.
Yeah, well, mine's a little bit
on the small side.
-What is?
-My heart.
-Well, you're fucked, then.
-Thanks.
Sorry, mate. Cheers, brother.
(inmates chatter indistinctly)
(doors open and slam)
-(door slams)
-(man shouts)
-call your daughter?
-Yeah.
-Is she good?
-Yeah, she's pretty good.
-Called yours?
-No, mate. Not yet.
Sss!
(screams)
johnny: Shit! What the fuck?!
(johnny continues screaming
and groaning)
ray: What are you doing?
Meditating.
Why do you do that?
Helps me relax.
-Fair enough.
-Yeah.
I used to have, um,
really bad anxiety and shit,
so I've been doing it
for a couple of years now.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-You never meditated?
-Nuh. (chuckles)
you should give it a crack.
Yeah, I don't have anxiety.
(lights clang)
well, you don't need to have
anxiety to do it.
So how do you do it?
Uh... (clears throat)
ok, so you focus on
your breathing...
Yeah.
..And you count your breaths.
And so, basically
it's every time you breathe out,
you count.
So from one through till 10,
yeah, then back to one again.
-Keep going.
-Alright.
Ahh.
So, how long do I do it for?
Well, as long as you want.
It's a bit boring.
(chuckles) that's ok.
When you first start out, so it
takes a while to relax into it.
But, um...
Uh, ray,
can I ask you something?
Ray: Mm-hm.
Why'd you throw the hot water
in that guy's face?
Oh, it was business.
-What do you mean?
-Oh, it was a job.
Someone paid you to do it?
Uh-huh.
Why?
He pissed somebody off.
That's it?
It's enough.
(sighs)
no offence, but that's pretty...
It's pretty fucked up.
Yeah, that's the way
it is in here, mate, you know?
You go around pissing people
off, there's consequences.
I just don't think violence is
the answer, you know?
Yeah.
Sometimes it is.
Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe I'm just a pacifist,
you know?
(ray scoffs)
nah, you're just scared.
(woman in video moans)
(woman continues to moan)
(woman pants)
matty, customer.
-(indistinct chatter)
-(tools whirr)
can I help you?
-Are you matty?
-Yeah.
Just come to get a quote, mate.
Yeah.
What kind of vehicle you got?
What the fuck happened
to your eye?
Some fucking idiot king-hit me.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
What happened?
-Oh, I was crossing the road...
-(tool clatters nearby)
..Some jerk-off comes tearing
along, doesn't even slow down.
I nearly go over
the fucking hood.
-That's pretty fucked.
-Yeah.
And then the prick gets out,
blames me.
Next minute just...
Mmm.
So, when you crossed the road,
was it, like,
a...A pedestrian crossing?
Yeah.
So there were white stripes
painted on the road,
there was signs up and shit?
Yeah.
That's funny, matty,
'cause I went down there today
and I didn't see
any fucking pedestrian crossing.
Well, how would you know?
I didn't tell you
where it happened.
Let's go for a drive, eh?
Fuck off.
(table tennis ball bounces)
I can't hear him. I think we
should freeze just in case.
-Change it back.
-No.
-I'm fucking watching that.
-Do I look like I care?
-Give me the fucking remote.
-No.
-Give me that.
-What...
(grunts)
(both grunt)
-hey!
-Fucking dickhead.
Man: Good on you.
Change the fucking channel.
('bluey' plays indistinctly
on tv)
(door buzzes)
(inmates chatter indistinctly)
(chatter continues)
-hey, cunt.
-Oh, fuck!
Ugh!
(grunts)
(squelching)
(ominous music)
(inmates chatter)
(sighs)
(breathes hoarsely and groans)
officer: We've got
an inmate down in...
(insects chirp)
(animal squawks)
-come on, get out. Get out.
-Ah!
Get out.
(matty sniffs)
(matty cries)
no. Nah. No!
-Come here.
-Please, please.
I'll drop the charges.
Please, please, please, please.
Oh! (grunts)
-please! I've got money.
-Shut up!
Please! I'll drop the charges.
I've got money.
-Shut up.
-I'll give you anything.
Please, please! Please.
I'm sorry.
-You're comfy there?
-Please, please.
-You gonna drop the charges?
-Yes! I'll fucking drop them.
That's good.
But just so you know,
if you don't...
You see this face?
That will be the last thing
you ever fucking see.
You understand that?
-(pants)
-yes?
Yes.
Stop fucking crying.
It's embarrassing.
(truck drives away)
(indistinct chatter)
all dressed,
ready to hit the town?
Ray: Yeah, mate. Yeah.
Ok.
-Cheers.
-Mobile phone.
-Tobacco and lighter.
-Yep.
Pair of sunnies.
And a little bit of cash
to get you started.
Thanks, mate. Cheers.
Let's get over the gate
and we'll get you out of here.
Sure, mate.
Discharge for shoesmith.
-Shoesmith, time to go.
-There you go, ray.
-Yeah.
-See you next time.
-Hope not.
-(door buzzes and unlocks)
(doorbell chimes)
-hey.
-Hi.
Brit's in the loo.
Ah.
She's been acting a bit weird
lately. Just a heads-up.
What do you mean?
You know, she won't talk,
but something is up.
-How are you, sweetheart?
-Hi.
-Hmm.
-Mmm. Ok.
'bye.
-Ray: So, what's the goss?
-No goss.
Ray: No goss.
Is your little mate
gonna come over and stay?
No.
How come?
'cause her parents
won't let her.
Ray: Oh.
Why not?
'cause you're a criminal.
What?
I know you went to jail.
Who told you?
Doesn't matter who told me.
Why were you in jail?
Um...
I had a, uh, situation
with a guy.
What do you mean, a situation?
(ray clears his throat)
well,
I was driving down the road
and these two guys just decided
that they were gonna cross
in front of the car
while I was driving.
So, I...You know, I have to veer
to get around them, right,
otherwise I'm gonna
run 'em over.
As I go past them,
one of the guys slapped
the side mirror on the car,
so I pulled over and I'm like,
"mate, what's the problem?"
I'm trying to figure out
what this guy's so angry about.
You know, before I know it,
the guy's swinging at me,
trying to, you know,
punch me in the face.
I'm like, you know...
I gotta defend myself.
Like, I'm not gonna get
my head punched in,
so I hit him and, you know,
the cops were there,
unfortunately, pretty close
and they saw me hit him
and so they put me in remand.
What's remand?
Remand is, um...
That's the place
where they put you
when they're trying to
figure out
whether you've done
the wrong thing or not, right?
So, I didn't go to court,
I wasn't convicted,
I wasn't found guilty.
They just put me in there
so they could investigate
and found out what happened,
alright?
So, police investigated,
they found out that
I didn't start the fight,
it was the other guy
trying to hit me
and that I was just trying to
defend myself,
so they released me out of jail.
Why did you lie?
'cause I didn't wanna
worry you.
Yeah, but you shouldn't lie.
Ray: I know.
I should have told you.
And I'm sorry that I didn't,
you know.
-Ok?
-Whatever.
I am actually really sorry
that I...
You're just sorry
that I found out.
(sighs)
you wouldn't like it
if I lied to you.
Fair enough.
(doorbell rings)
-how you going?
-Good, thanks.
-I'm brittany's dad.
-Oh.
Um, brit said that,
um, you know, uh,
romy didn't wanna...You didn't
want her to come and stay
'cause you'd heard
I'd been in jail.
Oh, yeah. Well, look, we just...
You know, that was just
something that I'd heard, so...
Yeah. Look, no, I mean, I'm not
upset about it or anything.
But it's just I wanted to come
round and explain to you
'cause it's kinda like
everybody's kind of talking
and...And, um...
So, basically
what happened was, um,
it was kind of like
a road rage sort of incident.
Um, I defended myself, um,
and, unfortunately, the other
guy came off worse for wear,
you know what I mean, so he
pressed charges against me.
Oh.
Yeah. So...
Um, but, you know,
the cops investigated
and they found out
that I wasn't at fault,
and, um, yeah, so they dismissed
all the charges
and, you know...
Well, I'm sorry.
And...And you're right about
everyone talking.
Yeah.
-So...
-Ok, great.
Well, thank you for explaining.
Yeah, look, so, you know,
brit's still keen to,
you know, have romy stay over.
-So if you wanna...
-She'd love to come and stay.
Awesome.
But we've, um...We've gotta go
and see her grandmother,
who's really not very well
at the moment, so...
-Oh. Now?
-Yeah.
-That's no good.
-Yeah. Thank you.
-Alright.
-But, mmm, another time maybe.
Yeah, yeah, sure. Yeah.
Great.
-Ok.
So...
Uh, she's gotta go see
her grandma.
Uh...Because she's sick,
apparently.
So...
Whatever.
Song: ♪ I was lying in bed
was almost fast asleep
♪ about to drift off
into the deep
♪ wasn't the telephone ringin'
wasn't the doorbell
♪ wasn't a dream
as far as I could tell
♪ tap, tap window
♪ someone's throwing stones
♪ into somebody else's home
♪ I jumped out of bed
I stood on the cat
♪ I looked out the window
at the laundromat
♪ you were standing naked
in your uniform
♪ bundles of washing
all dirty and torn
♪ tap, tap window
someone's throwing stones
♪ into somebody else's home
♪ don't throw stones. ♪