♪ And I've never felt that way
♪ You won't take the lead
♪ But you're moving
at a different speed... ♪
What the fuck?
♪ ..don't ever seem
to understand... ♪
Fucking hell.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
What's goin' on?
Ray, where are ya?
I'm just having dinner.
Ray, I'm stuck on a balcony
and I can't get down.
I need you to help me.
What are you doing on a balcony?
It's a long story.
Can...can you come
and help me or not?
Yeah, alright. Where are you?
OK, great, great. I'll text you
the address, alright?
OK.
OK. Alright, hurry up, mate.
I need you to hurry, mate.
I'm in a bit of a pickle.
Yeah, I'll hurry. Yeah.
OK. Alright. See you, mate.
See you, mate. 'Bye. 'Bye. 'Bye.
'Bye.
♪ Still don't ever
seem to understand... ♪
What's up?
Shh!
I can't get down.
Why not?
'Cause I'm scared of heights.
What'd you climb up there for?
I'll explain later.
‐What you want me to do?
‐Come in.
‐What?
Have you got any rope?
Whose house is this?
Shhh!
I'll tell you later.
Have you got any rope?
Just climb down.
There's a ledge there.
‐So you've got no rope?
‐No.
Fuck.
Come on, mate.
Come on. Let's go.
So, what am I gonna do?
Climb over.
There's a ledge right there.
‐(SIGHS)
‐Come on.
Come on, mate.
(EXHALES AND WHISPERS) Oh, fuck.
Just don't look down.
Keep your eyes closed.
(WHIMPERS SOFTLY)
RAY: Yeah.
Now shimmy around to your left.
Yeah.
Keep going. Scoot around.
Keep going, keep going.
‐RAY: Yep. OK. Yep.
‐Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Now take your right foot.
Half a metre, there's a ledge.
Put your foot down. Half...
Right foot down.
There's a ledge.
OK. OK. OK, OK, OK.
RAY: That's it.
That's it.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Keep going.
Keep going. Feel it?
‐Fuck, fuck, fuck.
There you go. There you go.
OK.
‐Now take your left foot, right?
‐(DOG BARKS)
(DOOR OPENS)
‐Oh, fuck off, you creep!
‐No, no! Oh!
Oh, oh, fuck! Oh!
‐(BOTH GROAN)
‐GARY: Oh, shit. Fuck.
Gary?
What are you doing here?
WOMAN: Bloody perverts!
I'm calling the cops!
Not cool, Tat.
Not cool!
‐TATIANA: Sorry. So crazy.
‐WOMAN: Fucking creep.
GARY: I think
I fucked me shoulder.
(GROANS)
What was that all about?
Tat's got herself
a fucking girlfriend.
‐Well, I can see that.
‐Yeah.
Sorry, mate. I just needed
to know what was going on.
It's over.
The marriage is over.
How long did it take
for you to get over Ally?
Who says I have?
GARY: Oh, great.
(CHUCKLES)
You'll be right, mate.
(SIGHS)
So, where are you staying?
‐Darby's.
‐Oh, Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
(SIGHS) Why don't you stay
at my joint?
‐Nah, it's alright, mate.
‐In the shed.
Nah, it's alright.
I spent 20 grand, mate,
doing it up.
Yeah?
Mate, it looks like
the fucking Taj Mahal.
Huh!
Go to Darby's, grab your stuff.
Come over.
‐Yeah?
‐Yeah! Bloody oath, mate!
See you soon.
Yeah, OK.
‐Thanks, mate.
‐No worries.
‐(SIGHS)
‐(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES,
ENGINE STARTS)
(RAY DRIVES AWAY)
‐MAN: Welcome aboard.
‐RAY: Thank you.
Here he is!
Rafael, Ray.
‐How you going, mate?
‐I'm good, mate.
‐How are you?
‐Yeah, good.
‐How you doing?
‐Good to see you, yeah.
‐Pull up a pew.
‐Thanks, mate. Cheers.
‐(GROANS)
‐This is for you.
‐Oh!
‐Bit extra in there for you.
Oh, lovely, mate, thank you. Oh!
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYS SOFTLY)
You want a drink?
Uh, scotch on the rocks,
thanks, love.
‐MAID: Sure.
‐RAY: Thanks, love.
So...
..how'd it go down?
What's that?
Tran.
Oh, Tran.
Uh, I just napalmed him.
Yeah.
‐What?
‐Prison napalm.
Oh, OK.
Uh, so you get a cup.
You throw some jam in it.
Boiling water. Mix it up.
Boom.
So it sticks to the skin!
‐It sticks.
‐RAY: Mmm. Mmm.
Melts all the skin off.
Oh! (LAUGHS)
Ohh!
‐Oh, that's beautiful.
‐Mmm.
‐Wow!
‐Effective, yeah.
(LAUGHS) Here. Try this.
‐What's that, mate?
‐Caviar.
Yeah, I think I'll...
‐I think I'll pass on that.
‐You don't like caviar?
Uh, never...never tried it,
to be honest.
You know, there's a reason
it's so expensive, bro.
Why's that?
Because it tastes
fuckin' delicious!
(LAUGHS)
‐RAY: I wouldn't know, mate.
‐Really?
‐There you go.
‐Thanks, love.
RAY: Mmm.
RAFAEL: Mmm!
‐You kidding?
‐Good?
Mmm! So...
‐I've only got a small crew.
‐Yeah.
‐But I'm looking to upsize.
‐Mmm.
Would you be interested
in coming on board?
Yeah, I'm not really
a join‐a‐crew kinda guy.
‐You know what I mean?
‐(LAUGHS)
But, uh...you know,
I appreciate the offer.
‐Yeah.
‐You know, no offence.
But yeah, I'm more of a...
I prefer to freelance.
Fair enough.
Yeah, fair enough.
I might have some delivery work
for you, though, if you're keen?
Mate, whatever you've got,
throw it at me.
Anything you won't do?
Mate, if the money's right,
I'll fucking do anything.
(RAFAEL LAUGHS)
‐He'll do anything! Ooh!
‐Yeah.
‐Whaaah! (LAUGHS)
Oh, mate, that's great.
He's great.
(PHONE BUZZES)
Excuse me.
Here, yeah, Freddy.
Try that. Yep?
Yep.
Go on.
Yep. OK. Done.
‐How'd you go with that?
‐Yeah, loved it.
Really? You liked it?
‐Yeah, it's delicious.
‐Yeah?
(RAFAEL LAUGHS)
He didn't like it.
‐He hates it.
‐(LAUGHS) He fucking hates it!
‐(BOTH LAUGH)
‐I don't hate it.
‐I don't hate it. I like it.
‐You fucking hate it!
‐No.
‐Just admit it.
‐You can say you hate it, mate.
‐(LAUGHS)
Cheers, Ray.
Cheers, mate. Beauty.
Good to see you, mate.
(SIGHS)
Why don't you buy
some weed killer?
Mmm, I like to pull them.
How's Her Highness?
She's good.
‐Mmm?
‐She's got a boyfriend.
A what?
You don't know
what a boyfriend is?
RAY: She's 12.
Yeah, I know how old she is.
They don't kiss or anything.
So, what's the point?
Anyway, she doesn't want you
to know, so don't say anything.
RAY: Uh‐huh. Speak of the devil.
So I booked a lane at 2.
Bowling?
‐Yeah.
‐I don't wanna go bowling.
‐Why not?
‐I'm 12.
So, what do you wanna do then?
Just chill.
So, what's been happening?
Good.
OK, let's go.
‐'Bye, sweetie.
‐'Bye, Mum.
(RAY GROANS)
‐Hey, Dad?
‐Yeah?
How come Uncle Gary's
staying here?
He split up with his wife.
He got divorced?
Separated.
What's the difference?
Um...
Well, 'separated' is kinda like
you're not divorced yet,
but you don't live together.
How come people get divorced,
then get married again?
Um...
You know, they meet
somebody else,
fall in love, you know?
Are you ever gonna
get married again?
Yeah, if I meet
the right person, maybe.
I don't know. I've never been
lucky in relationships.
Why?
Some people are,
some people aren't, you know?
I think I'm just destined
to be on my own.
I'm not gonna get married.
Mmm? Well, you don't have to.
I'm just gonna have
lots of boyfriends.
Mmm. Do what you want.
Soon as you turn 30.
30?! I'm not waiting
till I'm 30. I'll be old.
Oh. (CLEARS THROAT)
29 then.
Oi!
‐(ALLY LAUGHS)
‐Holy...
(CHUCKLES) It's a baby.
Well, I didn't wanna
say anything
just in case you got fat.
Thanks. That's good of you.
How far along are ya?
Um...18 weeks.
‐Wow.
‐Mmm.
Boy? Girl?
Uh, we don't wanna know.
‐Fair enough, yeah.
‐Did you know with Brit?
Uh, well, I had to...
I had to know, so...
Yeah, you don't like surprises,
do you, Ray?
No, certainly don't.
How is Brit?
Yeah, she's good.
You know, 12 going on 20.
I miss that kid.
Yeah, she misses you too, so...
How's Brucey?
Um, Brucey passed about, um,
three months after we split up.
‐Fuck. I...
‐So, yeah.
Uh...shit, um...
‐Sorry.
‐Oh, look, no.
Look, it's for the best.
I mean, you know, he was...
You know, he went downhill
pretty quick
and he wasn't happy.
So, you know, it was...
‐It was for the best, I think.
‐(STAMMERS SOFTLY)
Yeah.
So, what about you?
You...you happy?
‐You look happy.
‐(CHUCKLES)
‐Um...yeah.
‐Yeah?
Yeah, no. Yeah, I am.
‐I'm happy.
‐That's good.
Are you happy?
I'll get there, you know?
(HORN TOOTS)
I gotta...
‐Hey.
‐Oh, your lift.
Alright, well, good to see you.
‐Yeah! (LAUGHS)
‐Alright.
I'm glad you're happy, darling.
It's all I ever wanted.
Alright?
Take care of yourself.
Yeah, you too.
‐Hey.
‐All good?
ALLY: Yep.
MAN ON TV:
What happened this time?
(RAY DROPS KEYS)
‐Hey!
‐Hey.
BOY: What's up?
(SIGHS) Not much.
What's up with you?
Same old shit.
Who are you?
I'm Adrian.
TV: ..of teaching science.
Pay attention, please!
(TV SHOW CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Feet off the table,
please, mate.
What?
Feet off the table.
‐There's no need to panic.
‐(CHARACTERS EXCLAIM ON TV)
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(ADRIAN CHUCKLES)
TV: We had different styles
and my solo career was...
WOMAN:
And when he did paddle away,
I sat there
holding Finlay tight.
‐(PHONE BUZZES, RINGS)
‐We both yelled, "'Bye, Daddy."
And waved to him.
"See you in New Zealand, Daddy."
(GROANS)
Hello?
WOMAN: Mr Ray Shoesmith?
Who's this?
I'm calling from
Crawley Police Station.
We've got your father down here.
Righto. I don't really have much
to do with him, so...
Well, we need a relative
to come in and pick him up,
I'm afraid.
So, if you can do it,
we'd appreciate it.
OK. Alright.
See ya.
(DROPS PHONE ON TABLE)
(SIGHS) Shit.
TV: I've been shivering.
(RAY SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(RAY CLEARS THROAT)
You've got my father in here,
apparently.
A name?
His name's Bill Shoesmith.
Just take a seat.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
‐Ray, is it?
‐Yeah.
Hey. I'm Constable Rogers.
‐Come through.
‐Oh, OK.
So, what happened?
Oh, not completely sure yet.
The firies are still
investigating.
I mean, it looks like
he's probably just
left the stove on
and gone to bed.
‐OK.
‐He's all good, though.
Ambos checked him over
on the scene.
‐OK.
‐Just through here.
(DOOR OPENS)
Bill!
‐Ray's here to take you home.
‐Who?
Your son.
My son?
‐Yeah.
‐You're my son?
Pleased to meet you.
Same.
Brucey?
‐Let's go.
‐Alright.
Just over the road there, mate.
(BILL MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY)
(TV PLAYS)
BILL: This isn't my house.
RAY: No, this is my house, mate.
BILL: I‐I wanna go to my house.
RAY: Yeah, I'm gonna
take you home tomorrow, OK?
‐BILL: OK.
‐RAY: You're right, mate.
‐GARY: How'd you go?
‐RAY: Oh, alright.
Do you remember Gary?
Are you my son too?
Nah. But I can be if you want.
(LAUGHS) Good lad.
Sense of humour. I like that.
‐You wanna sit down?
‐Yeah, yeah, sure.
Thanks.
‐You right?
‐Yeah.
‐You want some food?
‐No, no. I'm good, thanks, mate.
You know, the coppers
gave me some Macca's.
I can't remember the last time
I had Macca's.
It was alright, though.
‐Uh, what was your name again?
‐Gary.
Gary.
You wanna watch a bit of telly
or something?
‐Yeah, sure.
‐Yeah? Alright.
That's how you change
the channel.
‐That's the volume.
‐Yeah.
‐Alright?
Oh.
TV: Way back in 1975...
(SIGHS)
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Right on the buzzer.
Timed in just in time.
(SIGHS AND CLEARS THROAT)
I'll have to call
Social Services.
They'll have to come
and get him.
Just put him in the shed.
I'll go back to Darby's.
No way, mate. He's going.
Mate, I know you guys
had your differences
over the years, but...
..he's your old man.
But I can't look after him.
He set his bloody apartment
on fire. You know what I mean?
He needs somebody that can...
..watch him 24 hours a day.
You know?
I...I can't...
I can't do that, you know?
‐Yeah, fair enough.
‐Yes, well done.
(TV SHOW CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Anyway, not my problem.
What kind of girl
did Madonna call herself?
(SOMETHING CLATTERS)
(SOMETHING CLUNKS)
(SOFT RATTLING)
RAY: Drop the...
Mate, you scared
the fucking shit out of me!
Did you leave
the front door open?
GARY: No.
(SIGHS)
Old man's gone walkabout.
Let's go get him.
(CRICKETS CHIRP)
You wanna go that way, mate?
‐I'll...
‐Yeah, alright.
Hey, mate.
Mate, what are you doing?
I'm burning up. I'm burning up!
I just wanna go home.
Alright, mate.
I'll get you home, OK?
‐OK.
‐Alright.
Gonna chuck this shirt
on you, mate, OK?
Can't have you walking
around the neighbourhood
in your...in your birthday suit,
alright?
There you go, mate.
Come on. Come on.
‐Bit hot, were you?
‐BILL: Yeah.
('SUNDAY MORNING COMING DOWN'
BY JOHNNY CASH)
♪ Well, I woke up Sunday morning
♪ With no way to hold my head
that didn't hurt
♪ And the beer I had
for breakfast wasn't bad
♪ So I had one more for dessert
♪ Then I fumbled through
♪ My closet for my clothes
♪ And found my cleanest
dirty shirt
♪ And I shaved my face
and combed my hair
♪ And stumbled down the stairs
to meet the day
♪ I'd smoked my brain
♪ The night before... ♪