- [Narrator] Previously on
Wild Craft South Africa.
(men whispering and rustling around)
- But he didn't drop.
They took off at about
300 yards, he slowed down,
he stopped, turned around.
Ranged him again with the BDX.
Got the dot on him, pulled the trigger.
(intense techno music)
(gunfire)
(reloading the rifle)
Well he took off again and
we didn't see him all day
and we, we spent about
five hours looking for him.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And we covered a lot of area,
a lot of area just trying to
look for him.
But that's interesting thing,
you know, the previous days
I was excited about the animals I hunted
and I had excellent success
with them and this is,
this wasn't a success
but that's part of it.
You compare the enthusiasm
of doing a job well and
getting an animal down quickly.
You know, so they don't suffer.
And I think that's a good
accomplishment this time.
I think I did a good
job, everything lined up
but the results weren't there.
I realize it's a part of hunting,
like Joe told me earlier.
- Mm-hmm.
- If you don't miss, you're not hunting.
(intense instrumental music)
(upbeat beach music)
- Hunting was a conservation
tool that saved the wild
life of South Africa.
A nation nearly twice the size of Texas.
With over 471,000 square miles.
The variety of animals
across this land mass is more
diverse than anywhere else in the world.
But of course, South Africa
is much more than just
beauty and nature.
It's filled with more
than 50 million people,
has some of the finest
cuisine in the world
and of course South Africa
enjoys the universal sport.
You guessed it, soccer.
Soccer first arrived in South
Africa through colonialism
in the late 19th century.
With leagues all across the
country, the passion for the
sport is stronger now than ever.
It's not just the animals that
draw us back to South Africa.
It's the friendships, the
culture and the mystery of this
great red dirt destination
that tugs on our souls and
brings us back time and time again.
(High-tempo drum music)
- The final sunrise pops up and
I tried to push the anxiety
out but it was there.
There's just no getting rid of it.
(intense Indian instrumental music)
It had been a phenomenal
hunt but I really wanted that
exclamation point I needed.
I think for my own sanity,
that exclamation point at the
end of the sentence.
So, everybody else had found their kudu
that they were looking for.
They brought them back
to camp and we were still
looking for that one.
(rustling sounds)
I wanted to start feeling
sorry for myself already
with, you know, one full
day of hunting left to go.
Which is ridiculous but
that's where my mind was at.
(intense instrumental music)
- [Luke] Things were really
starting to take a toll.
Especially knowing that I've
got five, six, seven hours
left but those kudu move
on the fringe of daylight.
I mean don't get me wrong.
I can't wait to go home
and hug the kids and tickle
the misses but going back with
a kudu sure would be nice.
I'm not gonna be disappointed
in the experience if I don't
but it'd be a nice little
cherry on top, you know.
It's gonna be a six hour wait probably.
But the hopes are those last
five minutes panning out
and that's a very, very
stressful place to be in.
I knew that even if we found a decent bull
Thys was still not
gonna let me have at it.
He wanted a good, mature
bull and he wasn't gonna stop
until either the sun
went down or we had one.
Nothing short of that.
(xylophone plays)
Aside from it's natural
beauty and plentiful hunting
opportunities, South Africa
is also a country that's
seen it's share of conflict.
It was a discovery of diamonds
and gold in 1867 that made
conflict between the Boers
and British inevitable.
And it resulted in a long,
bloody struggle that would
forever change the
landscape of South Africa.
While Fort Richmond is rich
in game animals and beauty,
it's also rich in history.
With artifacts left behind from
a time and people long past.
- So what's going on up here?
- Well I brought you up here
Alfredo, show you something
really cool and share
some of my family history.
- Oh, awesome.
- So this hill we're climbing
here actually has a fort
built under it by the British
army back in the Boer war
in the late 1800's, early 1900's.
And this is actually the
center of our property.
- Oh wow.
- I mean, if we peek over
the top here my grandfathers
house is about 600 yards that way.
My house is about a mile that way.
And just over there is,
you know, our staff live
400 yards that way.
So this is the hub of our
entire farm and family
and our family actually settled here.
My history and family
history is actually from
British descent.
Afrikaans were on my
mom's side and English on
my dad's side, who owns this property.
And what it was is there was
this buffer zone created,
from Carlsberg to
Kuruman of English farms.
So, what happened is a lot
of farmers from the 1820's
settled in Africa came and
settled here and other farmers
which is our family history
came from England and
were granted land.
They were allowed to
stake out land and farm it
and farm it for a certain x
amount of years and then buy
the land from the state and
keep it and our family actually
owned quite a few farms down here.
There's two families
left of our generation.
- Wow.
- And yeah, we have a very rich
family history in this area.
We've been here since 1854.
- Wow.
That's incredible.
- Title deeded in our family since 1867.
- Wow.
- So we've been here a long time.
- Wow that's incredible,
1860's, oh my gosh.
- So we've been here a while.
- Yeah, so tell me about the wall.
I see that there's a low
wall that's surrounding us.
What does this represent?
- When the British came here
and there was a big Boer War
in the late 1800's, early
1900's and they actually built
a reservist fort here.
The first battle of the
Boer War is in Belmont and
if you go almost straight
east for about 18 kilometers
as the crow flies, was the
first big battle of the Boer War
and the British army built
a reservist fort here.
And that's what we have left
here, these ruined walls.
They've cracked over the
years, they used to be a lot
higher, they've fallen
down and withered away
over the years.
- Right.
- But this used to be a fort.
If you could look inside
there's different compartments.
- Right.
- And there were cannon
placements and then if you have a
look on the hill over there
and the hill behind me
the two higher hills.
- Yes.
- There were cannon
placements on either side.
What makes this hill the prime
spot for a fort is anywhere
on this hill you have a complete 360 view
of your immediate surroundings.
- I see that the wall continues
out that way and comes
around, it's not just this part here.
- Exactly.
It's circular structure with
different segments inside.
And then there's a defense
wall that runs right down the
bottom of it.
So, the barracks, tented
barracks were on the
bottom of the hill.
The British actually kicked
our family off the property.
My great great grandfather
actually stayed on the farm
because he was scared they
were gonna ruin his property.
He stayed in a little
workshop and we call that
the ref room, the refugee room.
(laughs)
They actually left and went
to go and stay with family in
Grahamstown while all that was going on.
But they built that wall
coming up so that you could,
under fire, come up into the
fort with you know, either
side if you needed to.
And the officers actually
commandeered the old farmhouse
and stayed there.
- Wow.
So what's the connection?
So how did your family get into hunting?
- So, my great grandfather
was a big hunter.
- Okay.
- And the family joke is always
that he could never shoot
anything when he went because
he used to take three things
with him at all times.
He used to take his old
.303 rifle with him,
he used to take his shotgun and a .22.
He used to take a .303 to
shoot springbok that were free
range, yeah in that time.
And he used to take his shotgun
to shoot birds and a .22
to shoot rabbits and a kudu
or a springbok would come by
and he'd aim at it and a bird
would fly up and he'd grab
the shotgun and a rabbit
would run by and he would
grab the .22.
(laughs) And he always used
to come home with nothing,
at least that's the family joke.
(laughs)
- That's funny.
- My grandfathers not
that big of a hunter.
He's a cattleman and this
is a working cattle ranch.
- Okay.
- My dad was a big hunter and
he got that from his great
grandfather or his grandfather hunting,
together with him as a boy and
that's where he got his love
of hunting.
- Oh that's neat.
- And that's where I
got my love of hunting.
I started hunting with my dad
when I was seven years old.
And then I was homeschooled
my whole high school career.
So from 14 til now all
I've done is hunted.
- Wow, that's awesome.
I have a lot of, I have
friends who, have that shared
hunting experience with their
father or grandfather and
that's a special type of
bond you develop I imagine?
- It is, I mean, you
know, Richard and Bat,
you know they've come and hunted here.
I've been able to share amazing
experience with them and
know what it means to
them because that's what I
experienced with my
father, hunting with him.
- Yeah, that's really neat.
- But now you know my family
history and I've showed you
this cool fort that, you
know, is built on our farm.
(techno western music)
- As the afternoon wore on,
Thys and I, you know we kept
trudging on and we were
trying some new dirt, some
stuff that we hadn't seen before.
We tried some places that
people had seen some decent
kudu bulls there before and
I knew that even if we found
a decent bull, Thys was still
not gonna let me have at it.
He wanted a good, mature
bull and he wasn't gonna stop
until either the sun
went down or we had one.
Nothing short of that.
So I had that in the back of
my mind and I was trying to
prepare myself to argue with
him a little bit if that came
but we were walking along,
us two tracking him, it
was mid-afternoon by this time
and I was looking off to my
left or right, I don't
remember but I bumped into Thys
And I probably about knocked
that poor little fellow over.
And I looked up at him when
I kinda regathered myself
and he was locked on
this spot ahead of him.
Like a pointer who's locked
on, you know a bird dog that's
locked on a bird somewhere.
(intense techno music)
(rustling noises)
(techno music intensifies)
And he was right there and
he looks up and he say's,
"cow".
Okay, cool.
And it turned it's head just
a little bit and I swear all
I could see were the tips
but apparently Thys saw more
and he said, "shoot it".
(intense techno music)
(gunshot)
I don't know how long I focused
on that but it felt almost
like a snapshot because at
that moment, all of the hours
of waiting and walking and
anticipating that visual of
having the kudu in the
crosshair's, it had finally come
to fruition, I was terrified
that it was gonna get out of
my graph just like that.
- Great one.
(breathes out heavily)
- Perfect.
When he turned I could just
see the exit wound here
behind the shoulder.
(laughs)
- The final afternoon, almost
40 miles on these boots.
- Well done.
- Just like that, 41 miles
and 40 some odd hours of
hunting kudu just (breathes out
quickly) compressed all into
one moment and I almost, almost lost it.
(breathes out shakily)
- There's another one.
- Yes and he was hiding.
I just saw the beard.
- And he was just gonna.
- And then I saw the two tips sticking up.
- I need a minute.
The adrenaline dump from
that moment was probably the
biggest adrenaline dump in a
hunting situation that I've
ever experienced.
- Well you earned him.
- Thank you.
- With pleasure, I didn't do much.
- He clearly thought he was
hidden there, didn't he?
- Yeah.
- Let us just continue
to move around like this.
- Yeah you saw him just
like, looking up at us.
- And there was just
a little bit of brush.
- He didn't think we could see him.
- There was a little bit of
brush but I thought, it's five
feet in front of him with a
300 win mag even if it does
deflect, it's not gonna deflect far.
And it clearly didn't.
- No the shot was perfect.
(breathes out shakily)
(breathes out heavily)
(patting sound)
- I'm all kinds of messed up.
(laughs)
- It's understandable.
(upbeat instrumental music)
- That one's horns we
saw, lying back like that.
- And I wanted to shoot him,
I'm very thankful at the moment
that you didn't let me do that.
- Nice ivory tips.
- How old is this bull?
Would you guess, eight?
(men speaking over each other)
- Between eight and ten, yeah.
- I couldn't imagine what
I was doing eight years ago
when he was born.
Get off, get off.
So stunning.
But you're right, when I was
looking through the scope,
I saw the mane, found his leg.
- Yeah.
- And that's just, cause I
could not see anything behind.
- But I'm glad we moved
out that little bit.
- We had to.
- Yeah.
- I mean, like I said I could
see the leg about to where it
hit the body but I needed to
go up another eight inches
and I just couldn't see him there.
- Where the brush was.
- After I had settled down
a little bit and got the
adrenaline dump and the
dry heaving out of the way.
Thys knelt down by the nose
of that kudu and you know we
were looking at the mane and
admiring some of the markings
and looking at of course, the
curvature of the horns and
talking about that.
But he asked me, he goes, "you
see these three little dots?"
which ended up being kinda
down here on the cheeks and I
honestly hadn't really noticed.
They were there but they were kinda faint.
You obviously see the
big Chevron right across
the nose is stunning.
When you're looking in the
green bush it's like the first
thing you see, that Chevron
stripe stands out at you but
he said, "did you notice
these three little dots?
Sometimes even four".
I said, "well, I hadn't, you
know, what's that all about?".
- I don't know if you've heard
it before but here you can
see it a little bit.
- What are those called?
- (mumbles) it's a little
bit better but they call
it "The Fingerprints of God".
- Really?
- So what they said is when
God created them he put his
thumbs here and his, those
three fingers, and then he.
- That's the coolest
thing I've heard all week.
- Do you see it?
- Yeah I see.
- It's like exactly where
your fingers would go.
- The legend says that when
God made the kudu, he put his
hands across the face.
And when he did that he put his
fingers on each one of those
little dots and he put his
thumbs together on the nose of
the Chevron and he said, "when
God finished making the kudu"
he went like this and he
said, "it is finished".
And when Thys told me that story,
all the emotions that I thought
I had just gotten rid of
came rushing right back.
It emulated what it meant
for me to come that far and
to be able to share that
moment with those men standing
around me right there
and that one animal.
(soft piano music)
- [Director] Mark.
- Some dipshit amongst you
forgot to give us the keys
to the camps today.
- So you shot the padlock off?
- Close.
- No, no, no, no.
- Was that the first
shot I heard? (laughs)
- Luckily, we had a general purpose key.
(laughs)
And we sorted ourselves out.
(laughing drowns out speaking)
- Joe, you enjoyed it so much,
- as a little token.
- A keepsake. (laughs)
- I can open any padlock with
that, thank you very much.
- You can open anything with that.
- I don't know if they'll let
you on the plane with that.
(laughs)
- A universal key.
- It opens most padlocks.
- Yeah.
Yeah, we could've taken
some videos and done a great
commercial for how secure
those padlocks are.
(clicking sound made with mouth)
- While y'all were out
breaking and entering.
(laughs)
Y'all missed some of the
best food we've ever had.
- Oh, no.
- Really.
- Well we were having, we
were having fun chasing
the warthogs, I mean, we
couldn't stop ourselves.
- Chasing them?
- That's not the.
- That's not the point
of this whole exercise.
- The point.
(laughs)
- Chasing them and scaring them.
- Were they running like this?
(laughs)
- Geoffrey do you have any
participation medals made?
(laughs)
- I couldn't convince myself
to pull ahead and squeeze,
I was shooting behind him.
- One of the funniest things
today was Douglas explaining
how the pigs run.
He says, "the pig runs and then it stops
and it looks at you
but only for a second".
(laughs)
- And that's your time frame.
- And that was it right.
(laughs)
- Well I had a good and
unusual day today for Africa.
- Oh yeah?
- Geoffrey and I went out this
morning to look for warthogs
but stumbled on a really nice blesbok.
And confirm that, my trust
in that BDX system elevated
just a little bit today.
- That's dead on.
- Dead on.
- I couldn't believe it, yeah.
I mean we had, what, 15
mile an hour crosswind.
- Yep.
Yep.
- 388 yards.
- Yep.
- 388.
- Hit it, I'm like,
it's poke are you sure?
He's like, hit it, then
I'm like, range's good.
(smacking sound)
- Wow.
- Done.
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- So we got camp meat.
- Awesome.
- We got some meat for the
camp but then after that,
nobody here can guess what I did today.
- No, that's wide open.
- See, I told you, nobody could guess.
I went to a soccer game.
- No way.
- Yep.
- Why?
- Cause my son was playing in it.
- Oh, that's awesome.
- Well that's cool.
- Yeah.
So, the communities here,
obviously we're not in America,
where football and basketball are king.
Soccer is the universal sport and.
- Futbol.
- It's called soccer.
- Yeah.
It's called futbol here,
soccer in the states
but anyway.
So all the communities here
they get together and they
have soccer tournaments.
- Where? I haven't seen a lick
of grass since I got here.
- Well there is none.
(laughs)
There is no grass.
- They're pitch.
- They play, they play on the dirt.
- Play on the dirt.
- That's all.
- Play on the dirt but
communities from all over come
together, I mean, Geoffrey
they been doing it.
- As long as I can remember.
I mean, I used to play
there when I was a kid.
Like, right where we are, you
know, few miles, probably 15
miles that way salt lake community
bout 20 miles that way is
Hayfield community and then
you know, they'll come as far
as Kimberley, you know.
This is 120 miles away.
- Yep. To play on a dirt field.
- Play on a dirt field.
- That's incredible.
- They're very competitive.
- Yep.
And there's no, there's no age limit.
- Yeah.
- If you're 14 and you're
good, you're on the team.
If you're 40 and you're
- There's a referee? I mean
is it like, highly organized
- Yeah.
- No it's.
- Amongst themselves there's a referee.
- And there's.
- Line referee's.
- Little bit of money involved.
You kinda gotta buy
your way into the game.
And then if you get beat
and you got enough money
you can buy your way into the next game.
I mean it's, but it's, no
it's serious and I mean it
draws a crowd and Fort
Richmond has a team.
- We have a team, yeah.
- And Bat's played on it a
couple times when he's come over
so he wanted to play again this year, so.
- How'd they do?
- That's great.
(exhales loudly)
- Sometimes you don't know.
It gets a little confusing at the end.
(laughs)
- We don't know whether the
won or lost cause there was
a hot dispute on the final score.
(laughs)
- That's when you gotta grab
the money and run. (laughs)
(men speaking drowned
out by background noise)
- Our team said it was a draw,
the other team said we lost.
There was a heated argument.
- Well there's no scoreboard.
So, it's like soccer everywhere.
- When is somebody gonna
ask me about my damn day?
(men speak over each
other in disagreement)
I've been sitting here.
- Pins and needles.
- Oh yeah.
- Okay, look.
- Tell us about (men
speaking over each other)
- The best for last.
- So there I was.
(laughs)
- Not yet.
(man speaks softly in background)
- No, it was a good day.
I tell ya, leaving this morning
going out of camp is just,
my guts were just, anxiety, right?
I told myself, you know what
this is free-range hunt, if
I go home without a kudu,
I worked for it, it's fine.
I'm cool with that.
But I think it would've taken
me a couple days to really
accept that just because
dammit I worked for it.
I deserve a kudu, right?
(laughs)
So we went back to where
we were yesterday that.
Thank you Mark.
That big bull that we saw and
was hoping that he had come
back after we bumped him off
yesterday and climbed up the
top kudu mountain and I'll
be damned, he wasn't there.
- Again.
He was back with his lady friends and.
- Unafraid.
And they go off aways and
we worked up, would you say
40 yards about?
- Yeah, more or less.
- I mean, that first time
we were right on him and Thys
Could see him behind the bush
and I'm like, okay.
- If you say he's there.
- If you say he's there, I believe you.
And we ease around the bush.
- Ease around the bush.
- There was nothing there
but tracks, how can,
what do they weigh 500 pounds?
- Yeah.
- A mature bull.
- How can a 500 pound animal
at 40 yards leave without us
hearing or seeing a thing.
- Cause you're not a very good hunter.
- No that's not true.
(laughs)
- That is a blatant lie.
- No I mean.
- They don't call them the
great ghost for nothing.
- Exactly.
- That's what makes it awesome.
So he, anyway, to shorten
up this part of the day.
He took off and we just
couldn't catch up with him.
He was gone and Thys said,
"you know what this one just
isn't gonna happen" and
we were on his track
for a long time.
We devoted a couple hours this
morning were on him for that
long and after we we ran that,
the bull that, my bull, out
of the country we came back
for lunch and I was licking
my wounds and again, as that
sun continued to kinda inch
toward the horizon, I mean,
I told myself I would be good
if I didn't shoot a bull, but.
I thought I meant it, I don't
I meant it cause my guts were
just knotted up terribly.
Wanna go home, see the wife and the kids.
- Yeah.
- It wasn't ready, my mission
was not complete, I didn't
(mumbles) so.
- You wasn't ready sun
to set on Africa was you?
- No, not at all.
That's a great way to say it.
- Yeah.
- Not at all.
I just, I wasn't, the experience
wasn't complete for me
quite yet and so, we rounded
this one bend, we were working
our way down this two track
and Thys grabbed my arm.
"Right there, cow, cow, cow"
and she couldn't a been,
by that point, I mean we
slipped right up on her.
She must've been a hundred
yards, ballpark, if that.
- Between 80 and a hundred, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
So she was close and we're
looking at her and looking at her
and all the sudden, from behind
her in the bush, he goes,
"I see a mane".
And then once he pointed it
out just to the left of this
bush I saw the mane sticking down
and I could see the front leg.
I'm like oh.
And I, you know, and from that
point I kinda looked to see
if I could see it through the,
I had the bino's up at that
point to see if I could see any, you know,
how big the horns were.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Listen to me, I can't even
spit it out, I'm so excited
(laugh drowns out speaking)
He goes, "I see his
tips, that's a good bull,
that's a good bull".
He's like, "you think you
can take the shot?", I said
no because I couldn't see
his head, which, so what?
- Yeah.
- If he says it's a good
critter, I'm down with that.
I trust him.
But I just, there was a bush
right in the sweet spot.
- I'm like.
- Yeah.
- I'm not comfortable with that.
I'm just not comfortable
so just like this morning,
you know, you talked about
training all the time.
We started pieing off,
just had the rifle ready.
He had the sticks ready
and we just kept pieing off
around the corner to get
a little better angle
and that bull stood.
I mean, he thought he
was invisible, right.
He just stood there and he was locked.
And I could see more of the
mane and more of the mane.
Then I got to see about 90%
of his chest and he goes,
"can you see him?". I
said, "yeah I can see him".
I can't see his horns so if
you say he's a good bull,
put the sticks down, got on
him, he goes, "can you see him?"
and right where I wanted to
shoot, pick that hair moment.
- You know.
- Yeah, yeah.
- There was a little clump
of brush and I thought,
did some, you know, redneck math.
(laughs)
- 300 win mag, the brush
couldn't have been more than a
couple feet in front of.
- Yeah, there was probably
three or four feet.
- If it deflects, so what?
It's not gonna deflect
enough and goes, take him.
(pow sound made with mouth)
And I cut it loose, cycled
another round in, and he's
running and Thys grabs
my arm again and goes,
"it's over" cause as he turned
you could see the exit wound
right behind and he didn't go, 40 yards.
I was a rock up until that point.
Do you remember how it went down?
- Yeah.
- I was, slung the rifle
up and I kinda went.
(laughs)
(laughter drowns out men speaking)
- He was like, "I need a moment".
- I need a moment.
- The adrenaline dump.
- Just sat there, we could see
him, he was in the rocks, he
was done and just, it
was, that's exactly it.
Those two words, adrenaline dump and just.
- Your hands were shaking.
- My lips started quivering,
my hands started shaking.
(breathes out heavily)
(men speaking over each other)
- It was like a combination
of, what did you say today?
40 miles more or less, this week?
- I had my phone in my
pocket and you know,
google's watching me all the time.
When we left camp at noon, we
had logged, and I didn't have
my phone in my pocket the whole
time but it was at 38 miles
for the week, on foot.
So, I think all that just.
- Well deserved.
Well deserved.
- Yep, nicely done.
- For four years I've come
over here and hunted kudu and
killed the kudu on the
last day, last light.
- Yeah.
- Four years in a row.
It's becomes so regular that last year
we kudu hunted one day.
(laughs)
the last day.
- We hunted other things,
we hunted buffalo, we hunted
all sorts and we're like,
let's go kudu hunting
and Richard was like, no.
I'm like why?
He's like, you know what happens.
(laughs)
like, let's leave it,
let's see how far we can
push this one.
(laughs) And leave it to the last day.
(laughs)
- And it did, last day,
last light, I took a kudu.
- And.
- So this year,
to come,
I was a little afraid that I would
be so busy kudu hunting I
wouldn't have the opportunity
to appreciate the excitement
that the friends I brought were
gonna experience and that
bothered me a little bit.
Somehow, first day, we walk
up on here on the hill and.
(intense western music)
- Pa is looking at something.
He's lying on that rock
flatter than a snake.
- On that middle hill?
- Yes.
He's lying flat on the top of a big rock.
He's staring down in that bush as if
there's something there.
(rustling)
- Yep.
- Yep, there he barked.
- I heard him.
- It's amazing how we
know he's in that thicket.
And you would never
know it if you sat here.
(intense techno music plays)
- I got him at 250 yards, let's just wait.
(rustles)
- 261, just wait for
him to turn broadside.
He's coming, he's coming.
(gunshot)
(reload noises)
(whistles)
(gunshot)
- You hit him again.
- Good shot, a bit far back
but he's bleeding good.
He's gonna go down in that thicket.
He's pumping blood right.
You hit him a bit far back
you caught back lung he's bleeding good.
- Yeah I pulled it.
(laughs)
- Hey, you know this
was the first day right?
(laughs)
- I know, let's break the
last day, last sunset.
Let's make it the first
sunset on the first day.
Let's start a new tradition.
(upbeat keyboard music)
Well done.
He just, he came out of nowhere.
I mean, we watched him forever.
I couldn't see he was a
bull for the longest time.
And then we sent Pa around,
he did that whole turn
and I could see it's
the one we were after.
And he stood in the thicket.
- For an hour.
- For another hour.
- Yep.
- Where we couldn't even see him then.
And then I don't know what
spooked him but something
and he just came straight towards us.
He broke from 380 yards
and your first shot
I think it was 160 something.
I can't even remember now.
- I can't believe we shot
a kudu on the first day.
(laughs)
- Well done my friend.
Let's grab our gear and walk down there.
- All right.
(upbeat music)
- Look how light he is.
- Yeah, he's very white.
Doesn't have the deepest
curls but he's all right.
He's got the good shape.
Thank you pa.
- Thank you pa.
(upbeat music)
- Geoffrey, this is what I like
so much about kudu hunting.
We're trying to get back to camp.
The hunters are probably
sitting there waiting on us.
(laughs)
And Pa sees this big bull out of nowhere.
- Well, it ties back into
now, now and just now.
We've said now but it's way past just now.
(laughs)
- I ain't even gonna go there.
We were perfect.
That's why you're the
professional I guess.
That's why I listen to you.
- Well, this time it just shows
you how important trackers
are as part of the team.
I mean you and I, we're just
walking along talking about
nonsense, talking about what
are we gonna eat tonight.
And he decided to climb a
few hills and look for kudu
and ended up seeing this
bull, hauled ass down the hill
and called us.
- So now you gotta give
him a raise, right?
Look at the nice ivory on the tips.
- I need to give him more than a raise.
(laughs)
But yes, it just shows you
how vital a part of the team
they are as well.
- Well let's get this thing
taken care of and a beautiful
part of this is we got
kudu backstrap's now.
- Tomorrow night.
- On the grill, it's a deal.
- All right, man.
- Let's do it.
(upbeat music)
- I like to ask everybody,
what was the most,
I guess you could say cool or memorable
experience of this week?
When somebody says, "hey you
just went to Africa and hunted
free-range kudu for a week".
What is that first hand reach.
What'll be the thing ties you here?
- What sticks out the most?
- Yeah.
- Wow, I mean cause that's
kind of a slideshow, you know.
- Yeah.
- It just starts a slideshow.
You know, first off thanks
for inviting me and sharing
your experience here and
what you've found here.
This is definitely a special
place and special people.
- And the camp ain't too bad either is it?
- Well I mean, I think the
camp really means a lot
to me because
I'm a big literature buff.
You know, I read a lot of outdoor writing.
Especially the old school
and if you know, if you read
Hemingway and Ruark, you know,
the American authors or even
the old time people over here.
- Yeah, you know I mean, they
talk about hunting out of
tent camps and of course it's
much more complicated for them
back in those days but as far
as I know, this is probably
the closest you can get to
reliving that kind of experience.
To be able to, you know
you're living in tents.
You have the comforts,
they had the comforts.
- Yeah.
- They brought a lot of stuff along.
If you read their books but
you know them just walking out
of camp and hunting
what you see out there.
- Exactly.
- What you find.
I mean that's, I think
that's a special experience.
- But still what's that, the
coolest thing for me was?
- Watching a herd of 12
zebras for 45 minutes.
- Yeah.
- Being, just being zebras,
you know, family with a,
momma with a little baby there
and just the interaction with
them and just watching the
whole thing and laying down
and getting up and going in
the dusk and the red dust.
- Watch them in their natural environment,
acting the way they would.
- Yeah, just yeah.
- You always feel like
part of the herd in that.
- Yeah you just, you feel.
- In that moment.
- Exactly. And people ask us
all the time, why do you hunt?
And for 45 minutes you
lived with the zebras.
- Yeah.
It was brief but it's special here right.
- You were part of Africa,
you wasn't looking at Africa,
you were part of it.
- Very, very cool experience.
- Yeah.
- Alfredo, what about you?
- There's two things that are.
- This is what I did this summer, what.
- Yeah, so there's two interesting things.
There's like a 400 foot
level and there's the,
an experience I had that was just.
- Does it ever bother you
that you might be a little
overly analytical?
(laughs)
- Nope.
- Okay, I'm just asking, just asking.
- That's why I have very few friends.
(laughs)
(men speaking over each other)
- I think you might have
made a friend this week.
(men speaking over each other)
(laughs)
- That's right.
So, like the 400 foot views
exactly about living with the animals,
living in Africa, being part of it.
It is so bizarre, I'm new to hunting.
I'm not veteran hunters like both Luke
and Joe or anyone here.
And so, all this fascinates me but
we were sitting,
chasing the blesbok the
other day and we're sitting
in the field and watching
the blesbok and the zebra,
together and then the
zebras went around this way
and we're watching them here.
And it's, we were there.
And everywhere you go, just
like Joe was saying, everywhere
you go, okay here's some
Steinbok, here's some.
- Duiker.
Here's this warthog, here's this.
And so, and all of them
are game, fair game.
- Yeah.
- That's really neat.
- The big picture for me was
the ability to share something
I'm so passionate about and people that
I'm passionate about.
You know, Geoffrey and Thys
and Mark and the staff here,
they're special people to me.
Being able to share that.
- Leon's not?
- Leon.
- Oh yeah, that guy!
(laughs)
- Good friend of yours.
- No I knew I was forgetting somebody.
(laughs)
- Sitting right here.
- It's always him.
- He came late.
(laughs)
- That's what happens when
you get to the fire late.
(laughs)
- But no, to be able to share
that with other friends like
Luke and Joe and Alfredo.
That to me is something special,
just set around this fire
every night and hear your
reactions to Africa and something
that's dear to me, find other
people that appreciate it,
maybe not as much but almost as much.
- It's life changing for me.
- Yeah.
- And it's definitely a
big peak and you know,
I'm not 25 or 35 and I've done
a lot of cool things and this
is a nice big peak and it
makes me look forward to even
more adventures and so
I want to say thank you.
I'm not ready to go home.
I don't wanna go home but I'm going home.
- I never thought in my
mid-30's I'd be homesick but
I got three little one's at home that I.
Sometimes, even though this
experience has been, I hate
the word too, but it's epic.
- Yep.
- Sometimes a man just
want's to go home and play
Barbie's on the floor.
(laughs)
And that's what I'm gonna do.
- You may take your animals
you killed and you may have
them mounted or you may
get a European mount.
Six to eight months later they'll
show up but I think one of
the most special memories your gonna find.
Cause you'll be home for a
week, week and a half and you're
gonna need to get your boots
out or something that you had
over here and you're gonna
pull it out and this,
this here is gonna fall out of it.
- Yeah.
- And you'll be right back here.
(intense instrumental music)
(light piano music)
(men singing native music)
- When you come to Africa and
you bring a knife with you
for whatever reason you made
need it, bring a Spyderco.
Remember a Spyderco belongs in Africa.
(men singing native music)
(knife sharpening sounds)
- Who makes them?
- Hunters HD Gold.
They'll put your prescription right in.
- You said they help you pick up animals
or everything just looks better.
- They're happy glasses.
- They're happy glasses?
- Yeah.
- They make you happy?
- Yeah, put them on.
(rustling drowns out talking)
- Oh yes.
- See, are you happy now?
- You can't not be happy.
- All right give me the glasses back.
- Your eyes are almost as bad as mine.
I can see you perfectly.
I can see that scope perfectly.
- Those don't even have
a prescription in them.
- Really?
- No, them are just regular glasses.
- Well I can't see the scope
perfectly without them.
- See, they're happy glasses.
- I wouldn't travel 8,000
miles, halfway around the world
with a rifle that I didn't trust.
I pick up a Mossberg I
expect this gun to be MOA
and it's never let me down yet.
Any Mossberg I pick up, this
particular barrel action has
been with me in the mountains of Idaho.
It's been in with me to New
Zealand and it's been with me
here now in South Africa.
This exact same setup.
I am not a graceful guy
going through the bush of
South Africa with thorns
and all kinds of other crap.
I need a rifle that's capable
of standing up to the beatings
that I am gonna inadvertently give to it.
Not only the barrel action
but the scope as well.
I like this look, for a
long time Mossberg has
had their marinecote.
Now I know they're changing
a lot of that over to the
cerakote finish which of course
is extremely popular right
now in rifles and handguns as well.
For this application, again
because everything except for
the animals seem to
have thorns in country.
Just a very simple polymer stock.
It can take the scratches,
it can take the abuse, when
I get home, I'm probably gonna
pull the scope, I'm gonna
pull the stock and I'm gonna
put the original, very sexy
laminate stock back on this.
It's a sweet looking rifle,
it shoot's really really well.
And again with this BDX
system, we're pounding steel up
to 400 yards with a 300 win mag.
I would feel very confident
with this gun, laying on that
rock right there and shooting
a kudu with a great rest out
to 400 yards with no
reservations whatsoever.
So, my suggestion to you if
you've got a safari coming up.
If you want to go to New Zealand.
If you wanna go any, if you
wanna go out west, spend your
money on the hunt and then spend
your money on the taxidermy
afterward, get yourself a rifle
that you know that's gonna
work and spend the money
on all the fun stuff.