- [Narrator] Previously,
on Wild Craft South Africa.
- [Leon] You still see him?
- [Joe] Yeah,
over by that bush.
- Take a few deep breaths, Joe.
Look up the side of the hill,
just behind that bush,
- Yep.
- he's going to come
walking up on the left-hand
side.
- Yep, yep, yep, yep.
- Hold on a second, I'm
gonna get you a range.
You know, it's often when preparation
and everything just comes together.
Deep breaths, just gently
squeeze the trigger
whenever you're ready.
- Okay.
- And often on a hunt, when
everything goes smoothly,
you don't actually learn anything.
(gunshot)
- Good shot!
Well done, Joe.
(laughs)
- That's the bullet that sealed the deal.
- Well done, good for you.
(laughs)
- Finally.
- Shake my hand.
- Finally got him.
- Finally got him, kinda turned a one
day hunt into a two day rodeo.
- The full experience.
- The full African experience.,
(upbeat music)
(music intensifies)
(upbeat music resumes)
- For the hunter, an African
safari is the pinnacle
of adventure.
The wonder and mystery of
this beautiful landscape
is something to be cherished.
The animals are powerful,
regal, and a true
gift to mankind.
Fort Richmond Safaris,
with their professional
staff, and amazing concessions, can bring
all of Africa together,
in an epic and unforgettable way.
It was very special for me to be able
to share one of my favorite places,
and hunts,
with my outdoor writing friends.
Like the adventurers of old, now they too
can tell the world of this magnificent
and magical place.
Several of us have
already found the trophies
to fuel the memories we set out to create.
However, it's the African experience,
and the camaraderie of the campfire that
ultimately becomes the truest, most
lasting, and most important trophy.
(slow music)
- All right, let's just
check to make sure.
I got into firearms late in life,
in terms of really learning,
wanting to learn how to use them.
And I have been fortunate
enough to have a lot
of training, top level training.
And I love shooting anything close,
to anything far.
- Right, so it's still early morning.
- Right.
- And blesbok is high on the list.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- We just saw them.
- You've just spotted them,
a nice little bachelor group of rams.
(upbeat music)
Here they go.
Nice bull, look at that bull.
- Now they are running the other way.
- Yeah, upwind, yeah.
- Well we found the blesbok.
- That's so beautiful.
They were just moving about, just grazing.
Just beautiful animals.
But there is an excitement
there seeing them,
like okay, yes, they're here.
They're close by.
Yeah, these shooting sticks helped out,
helped me out yesterday.
- They did well?
- Yeah.
- Performed very well.
- This is what I work with at home,
and um, along with this sling.
This sling is really
nice, because what I do,
is I insert my arm into here like this,
and then when I get on top of the tripod,
I put it like this, so I have a lot
of downward pressure on it,
and it keeps me really steady.
So that's, uh,
that's what I like about this combination.
This is a Versacarry rifle sling.
So very handy.
- [Mark] Very comfortable.
- Yeah, it's comfortable, and it's simple.
You know?
Easy to throw my arm through.
(intense music)
- [Mark] The sun is behind us, which is,
which helps.
We need our face.
- Yes.
- And we're gonna slowly move through this
treeline, and see if we can spot them.
- Sounds good, let's get going.
- Trick is to get as close as possible.
- Yes.
Of course.
- Kori bustard.
- Oh, wow.
Stop, stop, stop.
It's a big group of blesbok.
They are slowly walking.
We're gonna catch them when they come.
- Okay.
- Just very slowly.
- Get in position.
It's like they hit a brick wall.
They smelled us there,
and they go back.
- Yeah, I see that.
- They still don't know we're here,
so that's good.
- Okay.
- Let's just give them
some time to settle.
- That's fine.
(upbeat music)
- Still playing with your gun?
- Well, Time to go hunting.
- I know, got to get my
make sure my gun works
before we go hunting, right?
- Well, what you,
what you putting on it?
- Well, this is a dusty place.
I need to clean it.
This is Mil-Comm.
And this is a specific cleaner,
enzyme-based cleaner.
- So before you actually lube, or put
grease or anything like that on your
weapon, you need to clean it.
- And it doesn't stick to anything,
and cleans up nice?
- No, it cleans it good,
and then preps it,
preps it for the oil.
And you got two, you got a grease,
and the grease works really
good on the bolt lugs.
Because when you grease the bolt lugs in a
bolt rifle, you don't want oil that just
runs out all into the magazine and
everywhere else.
So you apply the grease
just on the bolt lugs.
- I was gonna ask you why you need grease
if you have oil.
- Well, and it's all non-toxic.
So you just,
- And you need a pocket knife.
- Oh yeah, I need to get that cut.
So it's all non-toxic, and you just
put a little dab behind each bolt lug.
Because this is really the only place
on a bolt rifle where it's critical.
And you lock it in, you've got
a little bit of lubrication there.
- Okay.
- And not so much where the,
because this is a really
dusty environment.
- It is.
- Attracts a lot of stuff.
You've got the oil,
which is the same stuff,
just much thinner.
You put this on all the outer surfaces,
but you also clean your bore with it.
When you clean your bore,
the more you shoot, it provides a barrier
that also allows it, when you're,
the fouling from the copper.
- Yeah?
- You know the copper jackets
and the gilding metal.
That barrier it provides in the bore
makes that material, that
copper and that gilding
metal, easier to remove.
When you're cleaning the bolt.
- Okay, so you shoot, and you
use it every time you clean it
it's like your last --
- And the more you use it,
the more it impregnates
itself into the metal,
and then, it makes it
easier to clean your bore.
- That's pretty cool.
- A lot of military units are using it.
It's good stuff.
You got a cleaner, you got oil,
and you got a grease.
So I'm almost ready to go hunting.
- Well pack it up, let's go.
(upbeat music)
- The cool thing about Africa is that it's
a myriad of emotions when
you get there, but if
I had to take those emotions and somehow
transpose them into a phrase that someone
could understand, or even a word that
someone could understand,
it's the unknown.
(music continues)
When you step off a
plane, and you put your
boot print into that
red dirt for the first
time, everything is different. The tracks
on the ground are different
from home, the people
are different from home.
The trees, the air smells
different, the sunsets look different.
Everything is so different
that it makes me feel
like I'm hunting on another planet.
And I know how cliche that is, but until
you actually feel that
for yourself, to feel
so displaced from what
you're comfortable with.
That weird feeling that
keeps me going back.
Something that's just
so totally different.
- We can do it.
- For whatever reason,
I took to hunting very
very early. My dad didn't hunt,
but he and my mom did
bring me up on a farm.
So I had that outdoor lifestyle, right?
I had an appreciation for animals,
pulling stuff from the
ground, and turning that
from the barn, from the
ground, the garden, into food.
And I think that was just
a natural progression
for me to take that to hunting.
My horizons continued to broaden.
And one state turned into two states,
turned into three states, turned
into different countries.
Turned into Africa.
So what's, you saw one
bull walking, and you think
he's a good one?
Can't tell?
The one that was under the tree.
- [Thys] That's the one that, he just got
up and slowly walked off.
- Oh, that's not cool.
- The distance is 1,229 yards.
- Negative, not even.
- It's gonna be, it's
gonna be difficult.
- Not even the 300 mag
- You don't think the Mossberg
can get it done?
- Is gonna do that.
Oh I think it'd get it done, I don't think
I can get it done.
(laughs)
- As the editor in chief of Gun Digest,
the short version would be
that I take all content,
whether that's for print,
digital, a little bit
for TV across all of our
mediums, and figure out
how that works together,
so we can get our gun
content out to the masses, right?
That would be the short
description of really what
I do day in and day out.
Most of that's done from the front room,
from the front office of the house.
But, if there were a long description,
what I love most about
it, it was figuring out
how to take a lifelong passion of shooting
and hunting, and turn that into a career.
Well, here's how I feel about it,
I'm not just gonna throw lead and hope
to get one in, because these guys
can track so well. I
mean that's, obviously,
that's why we practice. Only problem
with killing critters, the goal is to
kill it as quickly as possible, obviously.
- Take it out.
- So with this rifle, I'd take this rifle
anywhere in the world.
Especially chambered,
and 300 Win Mag. But with this wind,
and just the emotions
that happen when you're
hunting like that. Especially with a kudu.
I don't know what it is
about a kudu, it's just
the elusiveness.
- Everyone has a right gun
to chamber.
- Yeah.
You've heard the phrase
figure out what you want to
do with your life, turn
that into a career,
and you never work a day in your life.
I don't know if that's
true. There are plenty
of days that I get under
the boss' skin, and we
have at it a little bit,
that make it feel like work.
But on the flip side
of that, there sure are
plenty of days where I
get to do some really
cool stuff, get to see
some really cool new guns,
new ammo, new gear, you name it.
So look, on the copies
like this, especially
with the BDX system, where I can get down,
and get steady on a
rock. 500 yards, I'd feel
comfortable, if he was standing.
And the wind, you know,
was either straight on,
you know, it wasn't belly, but.
- Yeah, not like today.
- No, but off the sticks,
either standing or sitting,
no more kneeling, I'm done
kneeling through yesterday.
I think, you know, 300.
And then off end, get
them within 100, you know.
Those are the goals I'd
like to set for myself
as far as feeling confident
about the shot I could make.
And again, that's not the setup, it's me.
It's totally me, and my ability to get
what needs to be done.
- No, I mean,
that setup is perfect.
- Yeah.
- Hey Richard,
remember when I told you about this tree?
You remember what it's named?
- Shepherd's tree.
- Correct, the boscia albitrunca.
And there's two cool facts about it.
So, way back when,
these trees are ancient.
They grow extremely slowly. And there was
hardly any trees here. I mean,
if you look at the Boer War
photos of 100 years ago, they were
- It was all grass.
- It was all grass, it
was hardly any trees.
So it's called the
shepherd's tree, because
herd boys would be, these were the only
trees around for shade.
The second cool fact is coffee was a rare
substance back then in Southern Africa.
And they used to, the
old folks used to take
the roots and make a
coffee substance from it.
- Oh.
- Interesting fact about that, though,
you couldn't have too much, because it's
a natural laxative.
(laughs)
- Well, you know what I say about coffee.
- Yeah.
- Same thing your dad said.
If you drink that stuff, it's
your own fault.
- Your own fault.
(laughs)
- You can slowly put one in the chamber.
(gun clicks)
- Bullet inside?
- Yes.
(suspenseful music)
- There they are.
- Oh yeah, I see them.
- Look on the far right.
The big man is in front.
- Oh, yeah.
That's the one I want, huh?
He's looking our way, huh?
- No they're just looking around,
but they're relaxed, they're
starting to feed again.
- Okay.
- And that's what we want.
(music continues)
- They are quite spread out here, Alfredo.
- Okay.
- Just want to make sure
there's no eyes watching
us going in.
- Okay.
- They are still moving.
They are about 400 yards at the moment.
(music continues)
- I see the one that
- With his head down?
- Yeah.
- He's moving left.
- Under the tree?
- Yeah, a little left, right?
- Big male.
(whispering)
- It's just the rams, they
are chasing each other.
- Hopefully they'll chase them towards us.
- They're still coming back this way.
That's good.
Alfredo, we might be in luck.
- Good.
- They've changed their
direction of feeding.
- They're coming towards us.
- They're coming straight towards us.
- Awesome.
- I need to get you set up.
(upbeat music)
- You bring me back a
milkshake from Kimberly?
- Absolutely.
Strawberry pineapple.
- Gross.
- How are you?
How'd the morning go?
- Good.
Good good, got on a big kudu bull,
but it was quicker than I was.
- Yeah?
- Close, but no cigar.
- Check this out.
- Man, that's a critter.
- Yeah.
- Look at that.
Been busy today.
- It's not a Harley Davidson, but it's
a blesbok.
- Yeah.
- It's a very nice buck.
- Yeah, it's no warthog, but.
- Well, this is perfect.
Because I've been itching
all week to see what you do with the meat.
Everything else we've shot is coming
either late at night, or I've been
out still trying to catch my kudu.
So let's turn this body
into meat, shall we?
- Let's do it.
(upbeat music)
- Everybody has a stigma
of trophy hunting,
and we just lob the head
off, and take the hide.
- Yeah.
- The meat, and you know, yes, you shoot
an animal, and you take an animal's life.
For the horns and the hides the memory,
but the meat is for the body.
And when I say the meat's for the body,
it's just to sustain our bodies.
- That's a great way to sum it up.
Because it's hard to explain sometimes.
- It is. And to address the meat thing,
I mean, all we do is,
you know, a large percent
of it my family use, our
trackers, the community.
So we take a back strap, or a leg for
personal consumption, and a lot of it goes
to them, back to the community.
There's even a butcher in Kimberly that
buys meat from us from time to time.
And then a large part of
my business is hunting
with local South Africans for meat.
The same way you guys would hunt deer,
we hunt, you know, kudu
and blesbok and springbok
for meat as well. My mom has a sausage
business that we use
warthogs, because we have
so many warthogs, we try
and keep the population
in check.
- You even eat the warthogs?
- We even eat the warthogs.
- Those ugly ass critters.
- Yes.
- So, like, the warthog that
you took earlier this week.
- Yeah.
- That will get turned
into sausage, and we
make it as cheap as
possible for the community,
because meat is expensive.
So what we don't provide
them, it's difficult
for them to go to a supermarket
and buy quality meat.
So we give it to them
at, like, cost price.
When we make our sausage,
all we're covering
is, you know, the casings
and the spices and stuff.
- Yeah.
- But it's to try and
help the community out.
- And what I find interesting
is that everything
you're telling me, it's
not an obligation, right?
This stuff is good.
- It is, it is,
- I mean.
- It's fantastic.
- The kudu is obviously amazing.
I think blesbok is, or
excuse me, the gemsbok
has actually been my favorite.
- It has.
- That we had two nights ago.
- That was amazing.
- It's really good.
- And, you know, like
that gemsbok, that was
from an earlier hunt,
and we just took a leg,
and my wife did the
whole marinade, and the
normal process she goes through
And I mean, we did, deboned
it and barbecued it,
and it was delicious.
- I'd take that over a
whitetail any day of the week.
(laughs)
I promise you.
- I've had good whitetail,
though.
too. I like that better.
- I really enjoyed your elk.
- We all do. Can't beat good elk.
- I've, you know, visiting
clients in the state,
I really enjoyed your elk.
- That's cool, that's good.
So these guys are what we can in camp,
you can, you take what
you can for the family,
and then these guys take
it back to their families,
and whatever's left, the
sausage or the community.
- Exactly. And it's a whole
full circle, I mean, the
salt that we use to salt
the skins and the skulls
comes from our local salt
lake community. I took Joe
and showed him two days
ago, went down there
and I showed him.
So everything here, we, you know?
Full circle in our community.
- Fort Richmond Safari really provided
us with a unique experience.
I've hunted quite a few
different places over
the years, and this
one I had to rate right
up there at the top. The scenic
camp that they had out there in a remote
location was just extraordinary.
And I've been on maybe
20, 30 wall tent type
camps in the US that I've hosted.
So I know the kind of work that goes
into those kind of things.
But to have all of those
kind of comforts at
home in that unique
setting, with the animals
just out our front yard,
was just an experience
I'll never forget.
- I feel like we should
have a little bit of party,
because Alfredo and Mark are
not the last ones tonight.
Congratulations, gentlemen.
Not holding up supper any
more, appreciate that.
- No, but we're missing
a couple people here,
where the hell are they?
- It's quieter without them, who cares.
- Yeah, it is.
- Yeah.
- I get tired of Geoffrey's laugh.
(all laugh)
- Nothing worse than a guy who's not funny
who thinks he's funny.
- Yeah.
(laughs)
- But I wonder what's keeping them.
- What are they doing, though?
- Yeah.
- Has anybody heard from them?
- Have not.
- Not a peep.
- [Richard] That's probably not
good, then, they're probably
up to something.
- I need a zebra report.
- Zebra day.
Absolutely.
- Everything work out?
- Absolutely bud, it was a great day.
- Congratulations.
- We saw either 12 or
14, I counted them about.
- Yep, there were 12.
- Yeah.
- In a herd down in the valley.
We were, snuck up on a nice rocky point
on the cookie and sat there for at least
45 minutes. Watching them, letting it sort
out the big stallion
was laying down behind
the acacia tree with a
bunch of other zebras
around. Some laying down, some getting up.
And when I got up there, I said which one?
And Leon said no, let's
sit and watch them for
a while.
- He wanted it now.
- Oh, they didn't know anything about you.
- He wanted him now.
- Perfect.
- Yeah, at that point, not really
caring at all if you get a shot or not.
At that point, it doesn't really matter.
- I wouldn't go that far.
- Yeah, I bet, you bloodthirsty old man.
- It worked out, because I mean, because
we had plenty of time
to range them, you know,
297 yards, you know, with the BDX.
So I knew that going in for a long time.
- Well done.
- It was almost one of those times where
you're there watching them too long. First
I thought it was good,
because then I could
calm down, and
- Yeah.
- But then it's like now,
I'm starting to overthink
this, you know?
And then, when I finally
did put the rifle up,
the four stallions were moving around with
each other, and I safety off, and then one
would walk in the way, and say safety
back on.
- Ice the kicker.
- And it just, you know, yeah, exactly.
That happened six times,
at least, probably.
But then, finally, one cleared,
and put the little BDX dot
on him, and whacked him.
- Whack.
- Yep.
And he was a big,
big massive stallion.
- That's awesome.
- That's great.
- Yeah, and it was cool.
- Yeah, they don't really
look that big on the hoof.
But when you get up close to them, they're
much bigger than you expect.
- And you're really
grateful when the staff
shows up to carry him out.
(laughs)
Because you had no idea.
- Of course.
- How we're gonna get
this 500 pound animal.
- They're of course, going down,
Joe didn't like all the waiting,
and he pushed me down.
- Oh he pushed,
he pushed you down.
- [Richard] Classy.
I was gonna ask if that was a tattoo.
- No, no, sir.
(all chatting, laughing)
- It looks like a dragonfly from here.
- I bled like wounded animal.
- Like a gunshot.
(all laugh)
- [Mark] Gunshot wound.
- Yeah, I was trying to slow him down.
He climbs those mountains
so fast, and just
goes, goes, goes.
- Did you get a new tattoo
that I don't know about?
- No.
- Where have you been?
- Well, we've been looking for a Harley.
(laughs)
- A Harley?
- A Harley what?
- A Harley Davidson.
A big ol' tusker.
- Oh, and, any luck?
- No.
- Saw a lot of pigs today.
- Yeah.
- Saw some nice ones,
but, I mean Richard's shot
so many pigs, I said, you know, that's
- We're looking for the
- Oh, he's becoming selective, now.
- Muy pigs.
- A shovelhead?
- Exactly.
- Shovelhead, yeah.
- [Mark] No, he uh, you
know, he's shot so many pigs
these days, in the last
few years. So I'm like
no, you need to get yourself
a proper one, you know?
A stuff.
- [Luke] Like we did.
- Like you did.
- Did all right, didn't we?
- Yeah.
- You did.
- [Richard] Like your pig.
- [Luke] Yeah. Saw lots
of pigs today, but just
didn't see the right one.
- [Mark] Right.
- [Richard] What did,
uh, what did y'all do?
Anything?
- Got a story right there,
(all chatting)
a tattoo.
- What happened to your leg?
- What I heard walking up
- Were you not a doctor
was like someone got a tattoo.
(laughs)
- Richard, I almost bled to
- I can see.
- death, okay. So whatever you do,
never ever offend Joe.
(all chatting)
- He pushed me
down a mountain!
- Don't turn your back.
- Probably hit him with his cane.
(all laugh)
- Leon, it's a good thing you're a doctor,
you can take care of your own injury.
Yeah, I joke, we had a
good fall this morning,
but it also doesn't
help if you get pushed.
- I didn't think you felt that.
- Oh my.
That's why it always
helps to be prepared, Joe.
- Oh.
- Otherwise, I might
have just bled to death.
- So, you are actually a doctor.
Gotta come prepared.
Well, honestly it was
kind of a nasty fall.
But it's rocky terrain up there.
- Yeah, it's very rocky terrain, Joe.
One always needs to be
very careful on the hills,
and remember we had
the chat the first day.
(laughs)
What is the first rule, Joe?
That only you are allowed to fall.
That's it.
(laughs)
If you're gonna fall, Joe,
which way are you gonna fall?
Well, you don't grab anything.
- Yes, and the third rule?
- I don't remember.
- You always fall uphill.
- Oh, I wasn't listening to that part.
- Oh.
(both laugh)
Good thing you didn't fall, then!
- Yeah. Absolutely.
But I'm glad you went
first, and stepped on that
rock that rolled out from under you,
so I didn't.
- Yeah, I'm sure you
enjoyed the spectacular fall.
- Well, I knew to go around it, though.
- Very gracious.
- Yeah, exactly. So I got down safely.
- Just don't, don't turn your back, that's
all I got to say.
(all laugh)
- Did you not, like, have a band-aid?
You're a doctor.
- You're the doctor, exactly.
- I'm still here. Does
it look as if I've bled
death, no I didn't.
- I offered to stitch it up.
- [Luke] I would have
paid money to see that.
He said I will stitch
it up, but I don't have
anything to numb the pain.
- And I kinda, I think
that killed the deal.
- Nope, skipped it.
- What was the deal?
Why were you on the, what happened?
- We were starting down
the mountain, to go
and recover the zebra,
and it was extremely,
extremely rocky.
- Wait a minute, whoa, whoa, whoa, what?
- Zebra.
- Recover the zebra.
- I didn't hear anything
on the radio about a zebra.
- Zebra, zebra day.
- So you got, you got the mountain zebra?
- I got the mountain zebra.
- Oh, well done.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, thank you very much.
Cheers indeed.
Beautiful, beautiful, big-rumped animal.
A rug and a steak.
- Mhm.
- As they say.
- Yeah, absolutely, this is just
- That meat is amazing.
- Yeah.
- It's sweet.
- It's delicious.
- They are my and I know,
definitely Taylor's favorite.
- I don't know about you, Mark.
- And Mark told me last week, when we were
hunting together, mountain zebra is even
better than the plains.
- It is, because they don't
- I haven't tasted it before,
but he said it's much better.
- [Richard] Huh, I didn't know that.
- Because the plains zebra has that yellow
fat, where it's that weird smell.
- Yeah.
- And it's very good, as
long as you cut it away,
but mountain zebra don't have it.
- So are you saying that
because it's leaner,
it tastes better?
- No, no, it's not leaner, it's just that
the Burchell, the plains
zebra has yellow fat,
which is, I think you
guys call it like talon,
or something like that.
- Tallow.
- Tallow,
and it gives that funny
taste. But if you cut it
off the meat, it's fine. You know?
You skin it, and within a
day cut it off, it's fine.
- So, the mountain zebra's not as sweet?
- No, it's not less sweet, it just doesn't
have that fat that if
you hang it for a week,
taints the meat.
- Oh, I got you.
- No, it's white,
white color.
- It's easier to process.
- So, congratulations on the zebra.
Did you do anything today?
- I am gonna be in such
great shape when I get home,
the wife is gonna be happy.
(all laugh)
- Did mountain goat take you on a walk?
- He did.
Kudu mountain?
- Kudu mountain.
- Yep, we started up there,
saw a, what's your word?
Ripper, ripper, ripper?
- The stuof.
- Yeah, what he said.
(laughs)
No, we saw a good one, and he was,
you ranged him, it was like 1100 yards.
Stupid distance out there.
- Yeah.
We were playing around
with a bit of action.
- Yeah, there was
- No, he's at 1200,
will it go there?
- He was, he was bedded,
we saw a cow walking
off, and he was bedded,
but he was silhouetted
against the grass. And just, like, at 1100
yards, and you go dude.
- So, you need to go
- If you see horns at
at that distance.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- And plenty of it.
And so we got down, and
we were probably within,
at least 200 yards, I would say.
I mean, working our way, and Izzy found,
still amazes me how these guys track.
We walked 900 yards to the
tree where he was bedded,
just straight to it.
- I told him, you see,
he was just lying down
here, pick up the track.
- No, he was like
that tree looks like that tree.
(all laugh)
But the tracks were under the tree.
And so we followed them for probably,
a couple hundred yards, and I thought we
were doing a pretty darn
good job, but the wind
was certainly in our favor. There's no
way they winded us. But all of a sudden,
the four cows take off,
and then he was behind
them, and of course,
I had a two and a half
second shot, because my, um,
and they didn't run to
like, say, what was that?
They were like, I want to see what's on
the neighbor's property.
And they were gone.
- Yeah, but then we
realized why they call it
free range.
(all laugh)
He just hit that road, and kept going.
- No, so that was, I would
call, like the highlight,
I suppose. But we were in good bulls all
I mean we saw bulls.
- No, we saw a lot of things today.
- Throughout the day, sporadically.
So, I mean it was far
from a disappointing day,
just every one of them seemed to just go,
just gone.
- Couldn't get it done.
- That's one thing that's difficult about
hunting any herd animal. Especially now,
when you know we are
hunting kudu in the rut,
out of the rut bulls, kudu bulls
form bachelor herds,
very similar to yak.
- Yep.
- [Luke] And one difficult
thing about hunting
herd animals is you'll
be stalking this bull,
and you'll see a group of cows, and you'll
be careful. And then
there's some cows standing
50 yards, or 100 yards that way, grazing.
And you looking for
cover this way, but you
don't see her, or notice her.
And there's no cover there, and she alerts
everyone and goes.
- As Mark was saying
the other day when they were up there.
There were baboons there. And today,
we saw them.
- Oh, did you?
- And he said
- And you didn't shoot them?
- Are you sure that the
baboons, they keep warning
the kudu down there.
(all chatting, laughing)
- Kudu, kudu, kudu, come in.
Yes, baboon?
(all chatting, laughing)
There's two people walking towards you.
- Two hunters approaching from the west.
- They do, they sit on the rocks,
and they're like, sneaking.
When they bark, they do this
hop. They're like there.
- You guys better move quick.
- Human!
There!
- [Mark] Move quick, they're in range!
- They got BDX, be careful.
- Yeah, they do.
- [Luke] BDX is shit on one of those.
- No, but all in all, a good day.
- No, it was really
good, it was really good.
- We saw, I mean,
like I say, we saw baboons.
- So you killed
nothing but time.
- [Luke] I killed some serious calories,
I told you that.
(all laugh)
- Alfredo?
- I knew it was gonna be an ominous day.
- How'd you know that?
- Because they took my tracker
away from me, too.
I think Mark, myself, and
the tracker make a really
good team, and so we left without our
tracker. I don't know who he was
with, maybe you, Joe?
- [Luke] That was my fault.
They saw me shooting,
they were like that
idiot needs two trackers.
(all laugh)
My bad, thank you.
- So we're stocking some blesbok.
We crawled, actually,
we crawled today, too.
- Absolutely.
- Crawled quite a bit to stay low.
Found some, I was in a seated position
at about 170 yards, they started coming
towards us. And I was
ready with my shooting
sticks. But I couldn't see enough of their
body to be confident with
the placement of the shot.
So held off, they moved
on. We followed them,
and finally got to a spot where
one was presenting itself.
(intense music)
- Okay, we're at about 290 now.
- Okay.
- 290.
(whispering)
- As flat as possible.
Sit down as flat as possible.
- Yeah.
- Slowly, slowly, slowly.
We've got lots of time, get comfortable.
We're gonna see if they
are gonna come closer.
(whispering)
- I see two over here.
- That's what we're gonna get,
there's two males.
- Okay.
- We're gonna see if
they're gonna come closer.
Now, we play the waiting game.
- The grass is tall, and I can't really
see their leg, their front leg.
- Yeah.
- To get my shot.
- The second one from
the left is a big male.
- He's a big one.
- Big male, he's walking behind.
- Yeah.
That's the big boy, right?
- They're chasing each other.
- Yeah.
- You can shoot any one of those two.
- Okay.
- Let's see how close they come.
- They are really
- He's coming closer,
he's coming, get ready.
- Yeah.
- Let's see if they stand.
- Okay.
- Big males, those.
- Oh, fuck yeah.
(gun clicks)
- They're just playing,
give them some time.
Did you see the back of him?
- The one over here?
- Right in front of you.
- Okay.
- He's got his head down.
- Yep, over there.
- I just want to range him first.
- Yeah.
- He's picking up the grass.
Let's see if he comes out.
- He just poked up, right?
- Yep.
165.
Watch him.
- Yeah, he went behind the
- Past the tree, you see it?
- Yep, yep, yep.
- If he stands, you must take him.
- Range him.
- I have, 165.
Okay, he's looking away now.
- Alfredo, would you feel comfortable
standing and shooting?
- [Alfredo] Yes.
- They are slowly feeding to the right.
- I can stand longer than I can sit.
(intense music)
- Come with me, leave everything.
Bring your rifle.
Come, come, come.
Stay low.
(music intensifies)
Come, on the sticks.
Get on the sticks and be ready.
I'll tell you which one.
- Fucker.
- Stand still.
They're gonna come stand
here in front of us.
There's a male coming out here.
- Okay.
Just stand still, stand still.
- They're gonna be these
two coming out here.
See the two walking?
- Yeah.
- Not the first one, the second one.
He's in the middle now.
- Good.
(whistling)
(yelling)
- Under the tree.
- Yeah.
- The one that's at the
tree right now, right?
- 259.
One, two, third one, over
there is a little bush.
- One, two, third.
- Over the bush.
- Right, I see him.
(gun clicks)
- Range is 260.
He's looking at you now, the second one.
Do you see him?
- He's still at that bush, right?
- Yes.
- Can you shoot him?
- Yeah.
Fuck.
- Wait.
- Yeah.
- He's coming back.
Come, come, come.
Come.
There he is, next to the tree.
- Got the sticks up, standing, felt really
comfortable, um, felt
steady and everything.
And felt good about the shot placement.
Mark goes shoot him.
He's the one that's still there.
- Yes, shoot him, 185.
(gunshot)
Okay, again.
Watch him.
- Fuck.
- He's slowing down.
He's the last one now, he's gonna stand.
- Yeah.
- That's him, the last one.
Try to get a shot into him.
It's 320.
- He's facing left, correct?
- Yes, that's him, that's him.
- So I can shoot?
- Yes.
(gunshot)
- Nope, missed him.
(gun cocks)
They're moving the other way.
But he didn't drop. They took off,
and at about 300 yards, he stopped.
He slowed down, he stopped, turned around.
Ranged him again with the BDX.
Got the dot on him, pulled
the trigger, missed,
and then he took off
again, and we didn't see
him all day. And we spent about five hours
looking for him.
- Really?
- Yeah. And we covered
a lot of area.
- A lot of ground.
- A lot of area, just
trying to look for him.
I think I hit him right here.
- Slightly clutching on,
- Yeah.
- But shot good.
- [Luke] Blood?
- No blood.
- Oof.
- Yeah, yeah.
- So you gotta, you got
work to do tomorrow?
- Yeah, we got work to do.
- We'll round up some trackers,
and help you guys out.
- Well, hopefully
- Always a chance.
- I have all the confidence
in the world in these
PH's and trackers.
- Oh yeah, same here, yep.
- If I were you, don't
worry. They'll find it.
- Yeah. But that's the
interesting thing, you know?
The previous days, I was excited about the
animals I hunted, and I
had excellent success with
them, and this wasn't a
success, but that's part of it.
And, you know, you
compare the enthusiasm of
doing a job well, and
getting an animal down
quickly, so they don't suffer.
And I think that's a good
accomplishment, because it's
a sign that all the training
that I did works out,
and everything lines up,
and I did a good job.
And this time, I think I
did a good job, everything
lined up, but the results weren't there.
And so it's, you know,
I realize it's a part
of hunting. Like joe told me earlier.
If you don't miss, you're
not hunting, or something
like that.
- Not hunting enough.
- Just out of curiosity, and
I think we talked about this
last night, how many of
you think you practiced
enough shooting before you got here?
- You can always practice more.
- I think a key part of that, Richard, is
people think practicing
means going to the range,
sighting their rifles,
throwing 20 yards down range
- Shooting groups?
Shooting groups.
- Yeah.
- Yes, sight your rifle, take
as many shots as it needs
to zero your rifle.
Key practice is getting
to field positions. Shooting off sticks,
shooting uncomfortable from
a tree, seated position,
prone position, whatever the situation
may call for. And that's
keeping the pressure,
but yeah. Run 10 yards, and then see how
quickly it takes you to
stabilize and take a shot.
- Is that what you were
saying with the gemsbok?
You felt that, a little bit of anxiety.
- Massive amount of anxiety.
- To get the shot off as
quickly as possible.
- We just traveled 8000 miles, and if
I don't take this shot
right now, they're gonna
go away, and I'm never
gonna get a shot again.
- Exactly, and to try
and simulate that is key.
And to try and get yourself into the most
uncomfortable, realistic
hunting situation.
I think that's real practice,
that's practical practice.
- To sum it up, I mean, zeroing your rifle
- Is key.
- Well, zeroing your rifle
is key, but zeroing your
rifle is not practice.
- No.
- I think that's exactly what
you're saying, Luke.
- No, and the funny thing about it is the
people that, the tactical
community, or the
people that carry for personal protection,
defensive handgun owners, they seem
to have this thing where
they practice religiously.
- But they practice religiously doing,
practicing skills.
- Practicing skills,
but the hunter, so many
hunters just sight their rifle in, shoot
a couple groups,
and think I'm good to go.
- True.
- Exactly, I mean, Gunsite
does all the practical
tactical stuff.
- They don't even have
a shooting bench there.
- Exactly, but a lot of people go there.
- Yep, yep.
- But I bet you if you
ask them how many people
do their hunters courses,
they'll say, there's
a huge margin.
- Yep.
- The minority go there.
And that needs to change.
Hunters needs to practice that.
- It applies to everybody, I mean, even my
daughter knows it. I mean we were hunting
our pigs one day, and
I missed two shots, and
she turned and said
well, daddy, you should
practice more.
(all laugh)
- Pretty obvious what the problem was.
- I'm spotting the pigs
and you missed, you should
practice some more.
- Well done.
- One of the
- Your kids will let you know
when you mess up.
- True.
- I don't even think it's
just your riflemanship
skills.
- Yeah.
- I think it's a familiarity
with your gear, you know?
And sometimes hunters
experiment with gear.
We're trying some new gear here.
Just curious, how are you guys interfacing
with the equipment?
I mean, have you had any issues, or?
- No, not really.
- I'll tell you one thing
that's impressed me hugely.
- One of the biggest
problems that we get coming
here, and I mean all the PH's around here.
Mark, Leon, they can attest to it, is
when clients arrive, and unpack their bag,
I'd say at least 70,
80% of them.
- Wow.
- They're inches off. Sometimes
not even on the paper.
- Oh you mean with all
the rifles holding zero?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- And all TSA.
- Yeah, the bipolar gorilla, right?
(all chatting)
- I mean, you guys had
luggages arriving here, I mean.
- Wait til you guys
get back to the states.
- But one thing that
impressed me about that,
is we don't have one
rifle here that didn't
hold zero after taking it out of those
SKB Cases.
- Yeah, my rifle, we were
hitting steel at 400.
- Yeah.
- Out of the, no adjustments.
- Yeah, same here.
- I could not believe that.
- Cases, quality gun cases.
There's something, when you go back,
somebody says hey, you did that.
If I go, what's a big thing I,
do you think it comes
back to the practice?
You think that's the big thing?
- I would say, hike four
times as much as you
think you need to hike.
- Climb rocky cold here.
(all chatting, laughing)
- One thing I can say, is, you know,
you were talking about hike four times
as much as you think you need to.
- Yeah.
- Hike with your gear.
- And find out, find out what falls
off, hooks up, snags on
- Rifle slings.
- Don't worry about that,
the PH can carry it.
(all laugh)
- I got the best PH.
- He's got a load limit of
like 24 pounds, look at him.
- Hey, Leon.
- I still need to give up
the mountain gear, come on.
- No, I just, I think it all
goes back to the practice.
Because you spend all that
effort, and equipment,
and gear, and money to come over here,
and don't shoot well.
- Yeah, let me add to that.
Just because I've done it,
too. When you go on a big
hunt, such as this, I
mean, you can consider
this almost a once in a
lifetime hunt for a lot
of people.
- Yep.
- You want to get new stuff. And
you want it to be top of
the line. And that's great,
but if you can't work it
properly, doesn't have to
be fancy. But just get off, even if it's
your dad's old Mossberg Patriot,
old Winchester Model 70.
It doesn't matter what it is.
- No.
- Use it, and get off the line, grab those
shooting sticks, and sit
and stand, just use it.
We were talking about
that today, too.
- Yeah.
- Doesn't have to be fancy.
I'd take that rifle anywhere in the world.
Because if you look at the scratches on my
arms, I am not exactly graceful going
through the bush. So we decided that
the only thing that doesn't have thorns
in this country is the critters, right?
- Oh, but you shot again.
- Like a toothpick.
- Well, the common misconceptions.
One, I'm going to Africa on
a once in a lifetime hunt,
I gotta buy new gear.
- No, misconception.
- Two, I've hunted
whitetail deer all my life,
I'm a good shot.
- Mm, yeah.
- And three, I can't
afford to go to Africa,
because it's too expensive.
- False, false, false.
- False, false. Because I mean, this, yeah
it may be a once in a
lifetime experience, but
it's not a once in a lifetime
expense, by any measure.
- Right.
- Definitely.
And you and I had that exact
conversation today about
the Mossberg Patriot debate.
I mean, I know a lot of guys in the states
especially, have synthetic
stocks because of
weather issues.
And I get that, but everybody
has an old wood rifle.
And if you want to go buy
the wood classic, I mean that, you know
what I mean?
- Well, there's something
about wood and, wood and steel
in Africa.
- Exactly, what a good relation.
That's a few hundred
dollar rifle, you know?
It's under $1,000.
- Yeah. The rifle I
have with me, I used it
last fall to take a
Newfoundland Grand Slam.
- Yeah.
- Moose, caribou, and black bear.
I took it to Wyoming this
winter for a coyote hunt.
And now it's here, it's in Africa
for kudus.
- Yep.
- Warthog if you can just find one.
I just need one, just one.
- They make really great rifles.
And inexpensive.
- Listen, unlike Mark
and Alfredo, we didn't
go to Kimberly today, and
I did not get a milkshake,
and I'm getting kind of hungry, so can we
figure out what we're doing tomorrow?
What's the plan?
- Well we know what,
we know what we're doing.
- I'm starting to think,
we've got to find out what
deodorant you're using,
because every night, you tell us about
the animals coming towards you.
(all laugh)
- And he hadn't showered
since he's been here.
- Yeah, I noticed.
- Cheers my friend.
- Thank you.
- No, seriously, what's
everybody doing tomorrow, you?
- Early to bed, early to rise,
makes a man shoot the warthogs.
- There you go.
- And will it be blesbok?
- Yes.
- You're back after.
- We'll get a team out with you guys
in the morning.
- Yeah, good.
- And I suppose we'll be
after the old (inaudible)
again, (inaudible)
- Yeah, what he said.
- There's gotta be
still one kudu left.
- Yeah.
- We all couldn't have shot them all.
- All right, well listen, cheers.
- Guys, congratulations.
- Alfredo, good luck tomorrow.
And Leon, we are gonna get
the big warthog, not you.
(glasses clink)
(intense music)
- Howdy.
- I have a question for you.
- Yeah, sure.
- Do you want me to leave a bullet in the
chamber, or out of the chamber?
- Whatever you're comfortable with.
So, if you're comfortable with a bullet in
the chamber, I've got no problem with it.
- Okay.
- It's up to you.
(gun clicks)
- That's what I need.
- Good man.
(vocal music)
- Geoffrey, do you think
I have enough luggage?
- Well, when you talk to my staff, I think
you have a bit too much luggage.
- So this is what happens when you come
to Africa for a month.
You've got to bring a lot of stuff.
Especially if you're
running video, and taking
cameras, and getting all kinds of imagery.
But, the cool thing
about it is, SKB Cases,
most people think of them as rifle cases.
And to years in a row,
I've used SKB Cases,
I've come to Africa, got
my rifle out of the case,
and the zero was perfect.
- Richard, that's an
important subject you bring
up there, I mean, we
see hundreds of rifles
travel from all over the
world to Africa each year,
and most of those guns need
to be re-zeroed, whether
it's a few inches, or even off the page.
Now I will say that for a fact, SKB Cases,
we've had the least of that.
- Yeah, and that's because what I call the
bipolar gorillas that
work in baggage claim.
- Exactly.
- You know, at the airports and what not.
But here's the other thing with SKB Cases.
A lot of people like to bring canvas bags,
and duffel bags, and what
not. And they'll rip open,
and you can lose your stuff.
Just get a big SKB Case
like this, and put all
your gear in it. All your
clothes, and whatever.
Cameras, video recorders,
I mean they got you covered
for any type of baggage
you want to bring to
Africa, so you can have
a great hunt.
And then get your stuff home
without it being tore all
to pieces.
- Exactly, and these
little ones over here,
a lot of the airlines want you to travel
separately, your ammunition separately.
- Exactly.
- And these are perfect for that.
- And you can lock them
up, your ammunition
is secure, and you got
everything you need.
So, if you're coming to Africa, actually,
if you're going anywhere
and you're taking a rifle,
or important stuff like
cameras and optics, SKB Cases.
(music resumes)
- You mind if I check out your knife,
just to see it?
- Sure.
- I'm a bit of a knife buff.
Oh, that's a nice one,
the Spyderco Flipper.
Carbon fiber, that's beautiful.
And that blade is a good profile.
- I like the blade, because it's short,
and it's easy to handle.
- Yep.
So, yeah, I'm just
checking to see if there is
any glints on the edge
here. Yep, definitely
needs some work.
- It's a working knife, so
it might need some attention.
- Yeah, yeah.
So I'll just use this,
my Work Sharp tool here,
knife sharpener.
(knife scrapes)
So what I like about this is that it has
a guide built in, so you can keep that
consistent edge as you move across.
It has this coarse stone, they're diamond
encrusted stones.
And then go to the fine.
And then it has a ceramic
for very fine, and again,
it still has those guides.
- I like it because it's
light, and it's manageable.
- Yeah.
- Easy to carry.
And these plates reverse
to a shiny surface,
so they won't be abrasive on whatever, if
you carry it in a bag or whatever.
- [Man] Grab that dirt
(inaudible) dirt, dirt!
- You scratch my back
- Hey,
Like that.
- hey!
Hey!
Fuck!
(laughing)
- Oh, my nuts.
- Found my nuts,
found my nuts.
(all chatting)
- [Woman] I was just chillin, man.
- [Man] With a 600 millimeter lens.
- [Man] Uh, I got full nuts.
- [Woman] Full nuts, yes.
- [Man] All right, we're done.