- (uplifting music)
(rifle clicks)
(footsteps rustle)
(uplifting music)
(dramatic music)
(music drowns out excited chatter)
- [Geoffrey] Yup, yup!
(rifle fires and clicks)
(heavy breathing)
(dramatic music)
(upbeat music)
- [Richard] As a long-time outdoor writer,
I've had the opportunity to hunt some
of the world's most pristine,
exotic in game-rich country.
I've also been fortunate
to have been part of
more than a dozen African safaris.
Africa, it's the place
where I best connect
with my passion for wildlife,
and answer the call of a hunter.
(upbeat music)
My name is Richard Mann.
For guys like me, for hunters,
Africa's the place that unlocks
that deeply-embedded genetic coding.
On this safari for free range kudu
in Africa's northern cape,
I get to share this stunning country
and everything it has to offer,
with some colleagues and
friends from the United States.
With the help of Geoffrey Wayland,
my long-time hunting
guide, turned good friend,
and his trusted team of professionals.
I'm excited to see what lies ahead for us.
(upbeat music)
(lively rock guitar music)
- [Geoffrey] Do you see
anything yet, Richard?
- [Richard] No, I was looking, you know,
where we jumped that bull this morning.
- Yes, between that little valley there.
- Yeah, I was looking there,
I figured he may, may
have got in the hills
like you say they do sometimes, so.
But I haven't seen a thing.
[Geoffrey] Do you think two years ago,
sitting on this very hill,
we'd be doing what we doing now?
- [Richard] Above, like
this epic camp, you mean?
- [Geoffrey] I built it, I hope it's good.
Clients are gonna arrive today.
- [Richard] Well,
they're not just clients,
they're my friends.
I mean, you know this is
my favorite place to hunt.
Kudu is my favorite thing
to hunt, you know that.
- [Geoffrey] I know,
that's why you come back.
- [Richard] And that's why, yeah,
and that's why I invited 'em.
- [Geoffrey] I mean, I
met Alfredo at SHOT Show.
Don't know much about him, but--
- [Richard] We know he's probably
one of the best gun
photographers in the industry.
- [Geoffrey] He showed me
some stills of SHOT Show
that were unbelievable.
- [Richard] Yeah, he's an incredible,
but he hasn't hunted
much, he's new to hunting.
He's really into it, he's a perfectionist.
Like everything with his hunting,
he does with his photography,
he's a perfectionist.
- [Alfredo] Hi, my name is Alfredo Rico,
and I'm a free-lance
photographer and writer
for Guns and Ammo, and
it's sister publications.
I enjoy hunting whether
it's with an air rifle, 22,
6.5 Creedmoor, I don't care.
Hand me something, and tell
me go hunt it, I'll hunt it.
- I met Joe at SHOT Show as well.
He seems like, you know.
- [Richard] Oh, Joe's an old hand.
He worked at Cabela's for years,
in the media relations department.
He's hunted with all, about
all the outdoor writers.
- [Geoffrey] Oh that will be cool,
to hear some good stories
running around the campfire.
- [Richard] Yeah, I know,
he's been to Africa before,
so, and he's gotta really
dry sense of humor.
He'll tell you a joke, and
you'll get it like two days later
(laughter)
- I met Richard years ago,
along the outdoor writer trail somewhere.
And we just kind of, seemed to hit it off.
He's one of those gun writers that you'll,
I guess you'd call, entertaining,
would be a good word for it.
To have in camp and to go on hunts with.
And I can tell you, not
all gun writers are.
But Richard's always a
good one to have around.
- I've only emailed,
you know, communicated
with email with Luke, I
don't know him at all,
other than that he's with Gun Digest.
- [Richard] Well he's
the editor at Gun Digest.
He's a hunter, he's a
life-long hunter, bow hunter.
And I was on his first ever rifle hunt,
like eight years ago, in Texas.
We were on a white, I
think it was his first
rifle hunt, ever.
- I hope he didn't teach
you any bad habits.
- Yeah, right.
- Here we are on this deer hunt,
and I figured out how to make the AR work.
And shot my deer with it,
and we got back to camp,
and I said, look, guys,
this is hard to swallow
and admit, but, I don't have
any idea how this thing works.
Right, I can run it,
it's like a NASCAR drive.
I can run the car, if I open up the hood,
I have no idea what's
happening here, right?
And Richard pulled me
aside, a few of us actually,
and sat down, very serious,
is the only time I think I ever
seen Richard overly-serious.
And walked me and then
these other people through
how this AR works, and of course,
things have blossomed like crazy.
And once I got in the Gun Digest,
well, he was one of the first guys
who I brought on board to really get down
and be a hard-core technician for handgun.
- Hey Geoff, Thys has just radioed
and said the clients are on their way.
- Okay, perfect.
Richard, it's time to go now,
guys are over seeing camp.
Let's head down this
hill and go meet them.
(upbeat music)
- You ready? Let's pack up.
- You said now.
- Yes, that means it's now.
- Not in Africa.
Every time I ask you
to do something for me,
you say, "I'll do it now."
And then like an hour
later, I ask you again,
and say, "I said I would do it now."
- Well, I probably say
that I do it now-now.
We have now, now-now, and just now.
- Well what is the difference?
- Now is now.
Now-now could be in an hour.
And just now could be tomorrow.
- Or next week.
- Or next week, you know.
- All right, let's go.
(dramatic music)
- Get all the luggage sorted out?
- Finally, you know, right,
the game's the same without you.
I'm glad you're here.
Luke, good to see ya.
- This place is so beautiful,
not even you could ruin it.
(laughter)
- Welcome to Africa.
Hey, old man.
- Hi, Richard (chuckles).
- You're getting grayer than me.
- A little bit, I'm kind of getting there.
- C'mon, I'll show you the camp,
show you the PH's.
- (speaking in a foreign language).
Mark, how you feeling?
- You guys, our hunters our here.
- [Group] Welcome, welcome guys.
(chuckles)
- I'm glad to see you.
- We're great.
- You all know, Bat, my son.
- Good to met you, Batman.
- This is Alfredo Rico.
- Hey, hey.
- How you doing?
- Hey good.
- Joe Arterburn, and Luke Hartle.
- How you doing, Joey?
- Leon?
- Luke.
- Very nice.
- Hey, Luke.
- Alfredo, you'll be hunting with Mark.
- Okay.
- Joe, you'll be hunting with Leon, here,
will be your guide.
Luke, we got you with Marten, got taste.
- Why do I always get the guy
who looks like a mountain goat?
(laughter)
- [Luke] I am not geared for speed at all.
- [Luke] Not at all.
- So, you all, get acquainted with them.
They gonna get your gear, take
you to show you your tents,
and yeah, and when, as
soon as you guys are ready,
we'll get, grab rifles
and go to the range.
Get zero'd, and get hunting
as soon as possible.
(dramatic music)
- [Richard] A trip to
Africa is long and grueling.
And when you travel with firearms,
the stress is compounded.
You do not want to begin your safari
without thoroughly
checking your equipment,
to make sure it was
not damaged in transit.
On this safari, all of the hunters
are using Mossberg rifles,
and the Sigsauer BDX
digital optical system.
The system uses a ballistic
calculator and bluetooth.
To help hunters be more successful
by instantly determining hold over.
(upbeat music)
- Hi guys, welcome to one
of our shooting ranges
that we have here at
the airport, Richmond.
We chose this specifically
for the BDX system
that you guys are gonna be using.
This is our pan area, it
used to be an old lake bed.
And, it's about 650-700
acres of nothing but sand.
There's a small little
succulent that grows here,
that the animals really love,
but that's about all that grows here,
cause the soil is so salty.
We've got steel out to four hundred.
We've got paper at 50, check zeros.
And yeah, the BDX system,
I'll give that to Richard
to explain to you.
- [Richard] Yeah, so, obviously
I was hunting yesterday.
I did this a couple of days ago.
We come out and run through this course
with the BDX system, and
the rifle that I had,
we were perfect all the
way out to four hundred.
Does everybody here already zero'd
before you got on the plane?
- Yes.
- [Richard] Hopefully
the bi-polar gorillas
at the airport didn't destroy your zero.
(chuckles)
- Not a chance.
- [Richard] Yeah, so,
ideally what we'd like to do,
is you step up to the
bench, confirm your zero,
and then, we'll try to
make sure that the PH's
BDX range finding system,
whether it's the binocular,
or the range-finder, is
communicating with your scope,
and then, you're getting
hits to four hundred.
Or whatever it is that
you're comfortable with.
If you don't wanna shoot
to four, that's fine,
it's your hunt.
But just make sure that
they're communicating,
the devices are communicating,
and then make sure
that you and the PH are communicating,
so you know that he's ranged, etc., etc.
And we'll just one at a
time run you through it,
and as soon as you're
done, we'll go hunting.
- Cool.
- Sounds good.
- [Luke] The Sig BDX is
one of those products,
or a cluster of products, if you will,
that really revolutionizes,
and I don't use that word
lightly, revolutionizes.
Revolutionizes Kentucky hold-over.
- Okay, Luke, let's see
if the rifle still zero'd.
- You are.
- I'm interested to see how
the new BDX system works.
- Yeah, me too.
Would it be easiest if you called it with,
because we're paired up with your bino's.
- Yes.
- If you called it.
- I think I'll call
the range, and confirm.
- I will confirm, I'll repeat it back.
- But I think first,
let's go to a hundred.
See if the rifle zeros,
and then you'll check out the Sig system.
- You got it.
- Your phone works as the brain.
Put in your rifle's ballistic data,
that talks to the range finder.
Those two talk together and
talk to the rifle's scope,
to really help eliminate
some of the messiness
that goes on upstairs
in that moment of truth
when you're trying to figure
out what the holdover is,
and the animal's moving
and the wind's potentially busting around.
Anything you can do to simply that,
which the BDX system does, is a God send.
(rifle fires)
- Dead on it.
(rifle clicks)
- [Luke] All right, so
I'm gonna turn this on.
- [Thys] Let's go to 200.
(rifle clicks)
Okay, I have a confirmed range of 200.
You received it.
- [Luke] I do.
- [Thys] Okay, when you're ready.
(rifle fires)
(upbeat music)
(rifle clicks)
- [Thys] Ready to go.
Perfect.
- That's what it's supposed
to sound like, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- Let's take one at three, shall we?
- Okay let's do that.
Okay confirm to three hundred.
- Three hundred confirmed.
(dramatic music)
(rifle fires)
- Good, got it.
- Did I hit?
- Yeah, perfect.
- Perfect.
- That's good stuff, that is cool,
I have to think about
holdover, I can just see it.
- Good, and the system works perfectly.
- Oh, dude.
- You can see the radical changing.
- That's fantastic.
(upbeat music)
(rifle fires and clicks)
(lively music)
(rifle fires)
- Okay guys, rifles are sighted.
Everyone's comfortable
with the BDX system.
We've seen its working great.
PH's are paired up with plan scopes.
I think that's it, I think
let's get into the field.
There's kudus waiting.
- Great.
- Let's get on.
- [Luke] I've been waiting
a long time for this.
(chuckles)
- Let's do it.
(dramatic music)
- Then this morning, we're
gonna climb this ridge.
- Okay.
- Okay, we're gonna have to get on top,
plan getting a good look.
- Okay.
- You'll see something new.
- All right, sounds good.
(dramatic music)
- [Alfredo] It's on the first morning,
we went up Kudo mountain,
and I was carrying my 30
pound bag of camera gear,
and it was gonna be rough for me.
(dramatic music)
- [Alfredo] Gorgeous up here.
- [Alfredo] I was feeling winded,
and we were just at the base.
I later realized that we were starting
at about at a 35 hundred foot elevation.
(heavy breathing)
(dramatic music)
- [Mark] Alfredo?
- [Alfredo] Yeah?
- I'll check on George,
he spotted some Kudu.
- Oh, awesome.
- We need to go over this ridge.
- Okay.
- [Mark] What side of the hill are they?
Okay, good.
- Alfredo, just wait there for me, okay?
- [Alfredo] You know they're close,
and you just can't wait
to start stalking them,
and approach them, and to
see how close you can get.
(dramatic music)
(lively guitar music)
- [Joe] I've always been
enamored with Africa
since early days, reading
about it for years and years,
so, when this opportunity came,
I just immediately said yes,
I didn't even ask when,
or any other details,
just, yes, I'll go.
There's just something about Africa,
that, you know, having
read about it so much,
and then once you're actually there,
and you're start hunting,
and you start seeing
the animals, it really
starts to soak in that,
man, this is Africa, this
is kind of what you've
always been dreaming about.
(heavy breathing)
- My PH was Leon Du Plessis.
And Leon is my kind of
guy, my kind of hunter.
Leon's very knowledgeable
about what he's doing.
Very experienced about what he's doing.
But he also knows how to make
the experience enjoyable.
- So what we're gonna to do is,
they will stick to the cover,
because you do not see them in the open.
So slowly take a walk down the end
and see what we can find.
- Okay.
- [Joe] Our over-all strategy for day one,
was to set out from camp,
and I asked Leon what are we looking for,
and he said whatever we find.
I didn't think that was
such a great answer,
but turns out, he was right.
A kudu is high on my list,
but definitely was looking for zebra too,
so it was just sort of a
matter of going out there
and sorting through the
animals that we would see.
(upbeat music)
(heavy breathing)
(dramatic music)
Look at that kudu.
- [Joe] So we got to the
top of that first koppie.
and kind of followed along the ridge.
We got to the point of the ridge,
We kind of spooked some zebra
that were down in this valley,
and I just thought, this is Africa,
now I know why I'm in Africa.
- [Leon] Okay.
He is, yeah, behind the cow now.
(dramatic music)
- [Leon] See him?
(heavy breathing)
- [Leon] Yeah, pull a bit up.
(dramatic music)
(heavy breathing)
(rifle fires)
(dramatic music)
(rifle clicks)
- Whadday think?
- Let's give it a minute,
I think, let's just go over.
- [Joe] Good shot?
(dramatic music)
- So when I shot, it's
kind of on that hard rest,
so it kind of kicked me
out the sight picture,
so by the time I got back
down, the kudu were gone.
- It was a good shot, Doug.
No, it's not that one, it's the other one.
Okay, lets just grab some
water, and then we'll walk up.
- What's that?
- Let's grab some water,
and we'll walk down.
Be only two seconds.
(lively guitar music)
- [Luke] For whatever
reason I remember it vivdly
when Richard called to ask
if I could make the trip
to Africa, it was a Tuesday afternoon,
and he never actually just
calls, he'll text me and say,
"Can you talk."
And so then I pick up the
phone, and I call him back.
And oh, and he says, "Luke,
I need ya in two weeks.
"I need you to get on a
plane and go to Africa."
And I busted out laughing,
and I said, "And volunteer?
"My wife is gonna castrate me.
"There's no way I can go
to Africa in two weeks."
And his, of course, knee-jerk
response, knowing Richard, was
"Well, you've got three kids.
"You don't need them any more, any way."
(upbeat music)
(music drowns out conversation)
- Fat guy coming through.
(laughter)
- That's as easy as that.
- Float like a butterfly.
- Well, you make that look easy, too.
(chuckles)
- All right, then.
(upbeat music)
- I guess so.
I got plenty, you know.
(upbeat music)
- [Geoffrey] You see them?
(chuckles)
- Their tails really do
stick straight up in the air,
when they run, don't they?
- Yeah.
(lively music)
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
(board clicks)
- Hi dude.
- Hi guys, what's happening?
- (big sigh)
- Tired?
- My PH sucks.
(laughter)
- I told you that.
- I don't know what
your hiring process is,
but you need to revamp it.
It was good though, it was really good.
I mean, the BDX, placed
Sig Sauer in the critters.
- I'd told you, you'd like it, man.
- Did you see anything?
- Yeah, we were into kudu all day long.
Just nothing that we were looking for.
- So you're being choosy?
- You know they all taste the same.
- Well.
- Thys, can you not find him.
- Are you discussing me again?
- Can you not find him a suitable bull?
- Use smaller words, I
don't know that suitable
is gonna register.
(laughter)
- Well, the bulls on, they're everywhere.
It's undeniable that they're there, but--
- But have you've seen one?
Have you seen a bull and said,
"Luke, would you like to shoot this bull?"
- No, I have not offered that question.
- You haven't given him an option.
- I feel like we're been in the nursery.
So we need to broaden
our horizons with this.
- Maybe tomorrow, we must
just go to another part.
(laughter)
- Mm-hm, it was good.
- But it's been good, we've
seen a lot of animals.
- Saw my first zebra on the hoof today.
How does a critter that
white in this red soil,
stay that white?
I say, it seems impossible, doesn't it?
- [Richard] Go look,
they're actually black.
- [Geoffrey] But the other half is white.
- [Richard] You're
looking at the wrong end.
- You did see it off the right, though.
- Well, that's true.
- Dude, it got washed, it took a shower.
- It took a bath.
- Hi boys.
- Hi, man.
- Mr. Hemmingway.
- How nice to see you boys again.
Where's the horse that goes with that hat?
(laughter)
- [Richard] The horse he rode in.
- [Geoffrey] Where's the horse,
the six shooter that goes with that.
With a necktie?
- Oh I've got the six-shooter.
- I don't doubt that.
- Don't worry about that.
- Good day, bad day, long day, short day.
- Well, it was, I tell you what boys.
I went through the full
gamut of emotions today.
Started out on the highest high.
- Love when you saw Leon come
out of the tent this morning.
- Well, let's start after that.
(laughter)
- How it always started out great,
we were in the coolest
critters right off the bat.
I mean, we walked out, out of camp here,
and now we're probably
a couple miles from camp
up in the mountains, and
then kind of continue
over the hill, and then there
was a zebra down below us.
Then there were kudu over here.
It was just, you know, one of those
heart-pounding type of deals,
and so it, just really, really cool.
- I just knew guys, I told
you, you'd love it here.
- And you, unlike the states,
when you see something move,
you never know exactly what it's gonna be.
I mean, if you're hunting elk, right?
If something moves, it's usually an elk.
You might see a muley in there.
If you're out in white-tail,
it's gonna be a white-tail.
Here, it's like, it could be anything.
- Yeah.
- And I get excited, I grab
Leon's arm, and warthogs.
(laughter)
(excited cross-talk chatter)
- Remember, it's cool, it's something new.
- Warthogs.
- Normally it would be
the opposite reaction.
(laughter)
- Wait, you saw warthogs?
- I didn't see.
- And he didn't take your gun?
(laughter)
- I was holding on firmly.
- I know his reputation.
- It sounds like there's a story in it.
- Well, there's more to the story.
So we were kind of on a
rocky point overlooking them
and so I was moving
into shooting position,
and Leon was ranging them with
his range-finder, his BDX.
It was 193 yards.
I couldn't, I was gonna take a shot,
and if I were to shot that one--
- Uh-huh, you would have had trouble.
- I would have shot that top off a rock
that was in front of me,
so I had to re-position and get up higher.
And I had a pretty nice rest,
and Leon led me into him,
and it was sort of like,
you know, the one right behind the cow.
Shot, good solid hit, we
kind of, ya-hoo'd, you know,
but, one of those deals,
and so we settled back for a little bit.
- Mm-hm.
- Would you say, so we
had a drink of water.
- Yeah, we had a drink
of water, relaxed a bit.
- Relaxed a little bit, and
we down to look for him.
Thought he'd be piled up
down at the base of the hill.
(dramatic music)
- But he wasn't there, and
so then, the tracking was on.
(dramatic music)
- [Joe] All day, we've been
looking for that animal,
and we haven't found him yet.
And so that's why I said, you know,
the highest high to the lowest low,
it's just that we had to come in at dark,
and we have to go out, we're
gonna go luck for him tomorrow.
I'm expecting a sleepless night.
- Good evening, good evening.
(excited crosstalk chatter)
- And we made in.
- How are you guys?
- Excellent.
- Thought y'all gave up and went to town.
(laughter)
- We like nights.
- You guys staying out late tonight.
- You guys see anything?
- Oh, we saw a lot.
Beautiful mountain zebras, a whole herd.
Saw the blessed, sorry, it's late.
Blesbok.
- And that was just the afternoon.
- And what happened in the morning?
- Morning, kudu, kudu, kudu.
And then found a nice duiker.
- Oh yeah, got something.
(laughter)
- Yes.
- Mark, did you know,
there's a bit of a size
difference, though.
(laughter)
- Yeah.
- Did you misjudge that, duiker?
(laughter)
- You know what a gold-medal
duiker looks like?
- He was looking for the games rack.
Just one of their horns.
(laughter)
- The horn's like this.
- Straight-horn.
(laughter)
(heavy breathing)
- Okay, We should follow
the straight line.
- Okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'll live.
- And run across the open area.
And gonna catch them when
they get to the front.
- Yeah.
- See the turtle?
Tortoise.
(heavy breathing)
- [Alfredo] Yeah, I thought
you were calling me a turtle.
(heavy breathing)
- Flat on the bottom.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- Female.
- Okay, okay, beautiful.
(footsteps crunching)
- (Speaking in a foreign language).
- So this is the opening
that you are talking about?
- No, it was at the bottom.
- Oh, okay.
- But they broke left,
and they run up we know.
They're going for this thick bush.
- [Alfredo] A duiker is a pygmy antelope.
It's very small.
George, the tracker, first spotted it.
And I remember his face when he looked,
when he saw it, he goes,
oh, he turned around
with a big ole smile, and goes, "Oh wow."
- [Alfredo] All the way back there.
- [Mark] Yeah, way back there.
- Mark goes, that's a gold-medal duiker,
you need to shoot that.
Thing was is, that wasn't on our list
of three animals that we got to shoot.
It was outside that list,
so that meant, it would
come, the cost of it,
would come out of my pocket.
- We can come get ready, all
right, George, get ready.
- [Alfredo] And what went
through my brain was,
that's a small animal,
and probably the smallest animals
are gonna be the most costly animals.
And I was thinking, oh, am I gonna,
is that a three thousand
dollar animal (chuckles)?
- Trust me, it won't break the bank.
(laughter)
(dramatic music)
- This thing's off, so I
got to the front of it.
- [Alfredo] I was using Mark's sticks,
and I wasn't used to the sticks.
I was used to my sticks.
And with his sticks, you
have to grab the sticks,
and then hold the rifle.
My sticks, I put my rifle on the sticks,
I loop my arm through the sling.
And I bared down on the scope,
like this, when I shoot.
So it creates a very
stable platform for me.
And so I'm pushing down.
With Mark's sticks, I tried that,
because that's what I'm used to,
and the legs just spread apart,
and I was all wonky like this (chuckles).
And Mark looked at me,
like what the hell's wrong with you?
- Sorry, causing problems.
I'm used to doing this--
- Yeah.
(dramatic music)
(intense loud music)
(rifle fires)
- Oh!
- He's good, he's good.
Give him time.
- I'm glad that was not a kudu (chuckles).
- Why?
- Lot a give.
- Oh yeah.
- Dancing around.
- Yeah, yeah (chuckles).
- And he goes, he showed me the technique,
and I was still a little wobbly.
And I still had a circle going there.
And I was able to calm it down.
And pull the trigger.
- As a matter of interest.
- Yes.
- Duiker, very tough to hunt.
- Okay.
- Very elusive.
- Late afternoon, early morning,
best time to hunt them.
We're in mid-day,
we caught this very, very
good representative, eating.
- Okay.
- You can thank me later.
(laughter)
Well done, man.
Great to break the ice.
- Yeah.
Mark was very right about that duiker.
It was a beautiful animal.
It did not cost me three thousand dollars.
Fuck!
- Alfredo.
- Yes.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- And I said to you,
you can thank me later.
- Okay.
- It is a beautiful duiker.
- Not easy to hunt.
Beautiful.
(reflective music)
- [Alfredo] Wow, that's a lot of damage.
Beautiful.
Totally worth it.
And that just made me trust
his opinion that much more.
- There's no guessing here,
but you have yourself a gold-medal duiker.
- [Alfredo] Really?
- Really.
- Wow, so what's that mean?
What's a gold-medal, whadda mean?
I don't--
- It's a form of measurement they use.
- [Alfredo] Yeah, okay.
- The Safari Club International.
- [Alfredo] Okay.
- They will grade them,
either bronze, silver, gold.
Obviously gold is right in front.
- [Alfredo] Yes, right.
- And the measurement,
the form of measurement,
is by measuring the length of both horns.
- [Alfredo] Yes.
- [Mark] Plus the
circumference of both horns.
- [Alfredo] Right.
- And as you can see this animal has
what we call secondary growth.
- [Alfredo] Right.
- That last inch you see,
the lines very tight,
sign of maturity and old age.
- So, Alfredo, I've gotta ask you.
You hadn't been hunting,
you didn't grow up hunting.
- [Alfredo] No, I didn't.
- Your first trip to Africa.
Your first African animal, free-range.
Tent camp.
How does it compare to some
of your other hunting experiences?
- [Alfredo] I had to work
really hard for this one.
So, I liked that a lot.
The only other thing that's come close is
a Texas out I done, that I did work.
The first day, full day that we hunted.
We hiked nine and half hours.
23 hundred foot elevation,
and 103 degree weather.
And got nothing.
- So what's your plan tomorrow, Mark?
- See the buck?
Shoot the buck.
- Scout over and skeeto.
(laughter)
- Keep it simple.
- Keeping it simple.
- Scout them, and skeet them.
- That's what we should be doing.
(excited cross-talk chatter)
- Which means judge it and shoot it.
- Scout them and skeet them.
- You guys have a plan for tomorrow?
- I've learned--
- Well, Richard and I have a plan.
- Okay.
- We gonna try and help you guys.
- I have a plan, I'm going to go,
first thing in, I'm gonna
go look for my kudu,
and I'm gonna find it.
- Well, we just hunting
warthog, and stuff like that,
so, we'll tag along with you.
- I appreciate that.
- Try and get some extra
trackers, and eyes in the field.
- Oh great.
Yeah, when I find him, then I can relax.
- Yeah, it's understandable.
- We'll go on a dang
drive, have some more fun.
- Try and see a gemsbok.
- And then we'll see if that
one that looks like that.
(laughter)
- Straight horns.
- But the difference is, it's that--
- We're gonna need a,
the drawing on the napkin
(laughter)
(excited crosstalk chatter)
- Flashcards.
(laughter)
- Well, I hope you guys
have a great day tomorrow,
and Joe, I hope we find
your bull tomorrow.
I'll try my best.
I know Leon and the trackers
will try their best as well.
- I have all the faith in the world.
- Does anybody wanna go home early?
- Fuck, no.
(laughter)
- That's well said, cause I mean,
- I'm halfway around the world,
we've been hunting for like two days.
I feel like we've been
hunting together forever.
- Yeah, no, that's true.
- We're sitting on the rock today,
and I think I said, this
is some Lion King shit.
(laughter)
We weren't seeing any critters,
but I was so content, I didn't care.
(excited crosstalk chatter)
- [Luke] Getting to pull the trigger
is gonna be a bonus at this point.
- [Thys] You know what,
he was sitting there,
and you kind of get used to
the scenery and everything.
But, every now and
again, and when you said,
"I'm sitting here, looking at this scene,
"and it feels as though I
should say something profound,
"but nothing comes to mind."
Is just, Richard and I had this moment.
- [Thys] it's just a feeling.
- [Geoffrey] Luke, there's nothing to say
to describe what I was seeing.
- Next time just pick up that.
(laughter)
- I can probably pick you up like that.
- Ah, Sa-win-da.
(laughter)
- Right away.
- Right over here, the best in the world.
- I feel like we're still
building to that point.
- You know what, I'll
be taking the selfie.
(laughter)
- Well, Dave the reason--
- Let's do that tomorrow.
- You haven't take selfies tomorrow?
- Don't you do that?
(laughter)
- No.
- The video life of you will
be a hillbilly taking selfies.
- How do you do that?
- I'll show you later.
(laughter)
- [Luke] You gotta do it
yourself, I can't do it to you.
(laughter)
- It's the rule of the selfie.
- No, now I know what
you're talking about.
It's nice to know what
- The problem is, there's a stick involved
most of the time.
(laughter)
- You don't need any
instruments, you're hand will do.
- First of all, it's
called a selfie stick.
(laughter)
- Take your selfie stick
and do it yourself.
- That's a wrap.
(laughter)
- I can see where this is going.
- Yeah, it's going downhill pretty fast.
- So obviously, this is the
reason I invited you all
to come here, the hunting, the territory,
but most importantly, the
guys that you gonna hunt with.
- It's huge.
- Yeah, I've hunted with
a bunch of PH's in Africa,
and no place can you
come, and in 24 hours,
feel like you're hunting
with a buddy, your buddy.
Right?
- [Geoffrey] And as an
outfitter, Thys might
not be the best.
(laughter)
- [Luke] I still can't
pronounce his name right.
(laughter)
- [Geoffrey] But, as an
outfitter, one of the key things
is not how many animals you shoot,
it's whether you wanna come back or not.
And a PH personality and
how he bonds with you,
plays a huge role in that.
- Let me say it like this,
what I was trying to say before.
We came halfway around the
world, I feel like I'm home,
all right, and that's
what matters, really does.
- I'll drink cheers to that.
- Cheers.
- Cheers, cheers.
(dramatic music)
- [Mark] So, Alfredo.
- [Alfredo] Yes?
- There's a little tradition
we have in South Africa.
Being your first African animal.
- Yes.
- I'd like you to just lift up your cap.
And it's just a sign to show that
you're a successful hunter,
and it's your first African animal.
- Awesome.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
(African folk music)
(cartridge clicks)
- You see, here.
Dude, stick this on your hat, so you see.
- That's pretty cool, how's it go, oh.
- You got the clip.
- Wow, that's bad ass.
(African folk music)
(saw blade rasps)
- Mr. Mann.
- Yes, sir.
- See something?
- See you, you're looking pretty snazzy.
- Well, I gotta thank you for that,
hooking me up with the out back.
I mean, this Richmond
jacket is just so warm.
I mean, not only that,
there's a two part story, for being,
Fort Richmond Safaris.
- Richmond jacket.
- Richmond jacket, you know.
- We needed a little class
in your life, you know.
- Well, we all can't be as classy as you.
- Well, I wore this, the
elephant jacket here,
this is the third year.
I think it's kind of cool.
People think that just
cause you're in Africa,
that it's supposed to
be warm all the time.
It's actually winter, or late fall here.
- You know it gets cold here.
- Yeah, I mean it gets cold.
So, this jacket, or that one,
night time, early morning,
specially if you're on the back of a truck
or sitting up on one of
these hills glassing.
- It's perfect, yeah.
- Austrian-made.
This is high quality hunting gear.
- Extremely high quality.
I mean, I'm very impressed with.
- Well, you look good in it.
- Well, thank you.
- So, Geoffrey, I know, your clients,
especially first timers
when they come over here.
They're always asking you.
You know, what type of clothing.
Whadda, you gonna tell 'em?
- You'll gonna go all the way.
Boots, pants, shirts, and jackets.
- Loaded, toes to nose.
- Toes to nose.
- There you go.
- Well, talking about first time hunters,
let's go test your skills.
- That's life, folks, shit happens.