- [Narrator] Previously
on WildCraft South Africa.
- Luke, good to see you.
- This place is so beautiful
not even you could ruin it.
(laughing)
- Welcome back.
- Hey, old man.
- Hey.
- Looking grayer than me.
- A little bit, getting there.
- Come on I'll show you the camp,
show you the PHs.
- [Joe] A kudu.
Right off that point.
- [Leon] There's another
one coming down Joe.
He's the one we want to take.
Do you see him?
- [Joe] It is.
- [Leon] There's two of them.
There's a smaller bull
on the left hand side,
the one you pointed out.
- [Joe] Yeah.
- [Leon] There's one on the far right.
There he comes, there he comes,
right on the crest of the hill.
Right on the crest of the hill.
Here he comes.
- [Joe] Oh yeah.
- [Leon] He's still walking
you can see he's much bigger
than the rest of them.
- [Joe] Yep.
- No, no Joe.
Your barrel is in line with the rock pile.
- [Joe] Oh, I see it.
That's going to be a problem.
- [Leon] Joe try and
get up here if you can.
If you're ready you can take him.
(suspenseful music)
(gun shooting)
- Shot, good solid hit.
We kinda, yahoo, you know,
but one of those deals,
and so we relaxed a little bit,
and we went down to look for him,
and thought he'd be piled up
down at the base of the hill.
(dramatic music)
But it wasn't there.
And so then the tracking was on.
- It's a piece of bone.
(dramatic music)
Geoffrey, Geoffrey, Geoffrey?
- All day we've been
looking for that animal,
and we haven't found him yet.
So I mean that's why I said, you know,
highest high to lowest low,
is just that we had to come into dark,
and we have to go out, we're
gonna go look for him tomorrow.
I'm expecting a sleepless night.
(upbeat music)
- [Richard] An African Safari
is filled with many things.
It's filled with beauty, exotic wildlife,
and some of the most breathtaking
scenery on planet Earth.
But hunting in Africa
is just that, hunting.
And as all hunters know,
nothing ever really
goes as planned.
Setting out to locate,
stalk, ethically kill,
and utilize the resources
of a wild animal,
is almost always filled
trails and tribulations.
The woodsmanship skills of
the hunter and the guide,
along with the hunters
ability as a rifleman,
or what ultimately determines
the success of failure
of the hunt.
- I think the big thing
is because the trail
is split up there.
He might of not come
down, he might have stayed
parallel with the hill and just went.
- He was this way I did see it.
- [Leon] No I also don't
see any tracks there.
- Yeah.
- But there's a lot of
tracks going down though.
I think what we do,
Dougie, is just go down
into this valley and let's walk up.
- We looked and looked, and
we just weren't finding him,
we were going slow through here.
I'd get inpatient on Douglas,
with who was watching
track to track, blood drop, blood drop.
And I'd keep looking ahead, looking ahead,
thinking we'd see something.
But we didn't find him.
- You see the, there's the road,
okay.
Yeah it's far out.
Road, little bit of bushes,
that first set of bushes,
and the second lot.
(dramatic music)
Maybe what I can do is just ask if there's
a few more trackers.
See if they can just split out
and have a quick look for that.
- I have to find that kudu.
- Yeah that's what I'm saying.
- Yeah.
Where do you think that kudu is?
- [Walkie Talkie] Power on.
- Priority.
Jeff, Jeff, Jeff?
- Geoffrey brought additional trackers
and some other employees,
and we did a beat across
the pasture which was everybody lined up
and walked across hoping
to kick that kudu out
or at least find sign of it.
(dramatic music)
Down in the valley, we were
just about to go down it,
and a kudu ran out, and Leon
shouted, "It's limping."
(dramatic music)
So we hustled over there,
followed these tracks
for a little bit into this dry bush,
and heard this huff and there he was,
and seeing him pointing and
I'm trying to get on him,
and he takes off.
Which was good to see him
but discouraging that he
was in such good shape that
he could still run like that.
- You see him, Joe?
- Yeah.
Up in the rocks?
- Yes, on this side of the hill.
- It was trying to, it was
going up another rocky culpie
and so we ran ahead of
Geoffrey, and we got to where
we could kinda get a clearing
and we could see him,
he would stop, he'd look
back, and he would keep going.
And he was about half way
up, and I knew if he got
over that hill we were back to square one.
- Okay Joe what I'm
gonna do is I'm gonna put
the sticks up, I'll arrange them,
and soon as he stands I
need you to put a shot in.
- All right.
Leon kinda turned to me and said,
you know, this is gonna be fast, you know
if you got a shot just take it.
- You still see him?
- Yeah.
Right by that bush.
- Take a few deep breaths Joe.
- So we also, actually Leon took the time
to set up his shooting sticks.
Where is he?
- Look up the side of the hill,
just behind that bush.
- Behind.
- Come walking out the left hand side.
Hold a second I'm gonna get you a range.
Joe he's 167 yards.
- I got on it, put it on it.
- Deep breaths, gently squeeze the trigger
whenever you're ready.
- Okay.
Shot, whack, and the kudu went down.
(gun shots)
- Good shot.
Well done Joe.
- Finally.
- Shake my hand.
- Finally got him.
So impressed with you.
Awesome.
- And out was a big sign of relief,
but after what we'd been
through I wasn't gonna
rest until we got up there,
so we hustled right up there
and sure enough, behind those bushes,
there was my kudu, finally.
And I was able to put my hands on him.
Make sure.
- Yeah he's done.
Well done.
(laughing)
Congratulations.
- Finally.
- Well done sir.
- Make your rifle safe
there if you don't mind.
We've come along way to get this oak.
- There's that shot from yesterday.
- Yeah it's just a little
bit too far forward.
It's right on the shoulder.
If it had just been a little bit back.
- It didn't seem to
slow him down that much.
- No, it did not at all.
He came quite a ways.
- [Joe] How far would you say?
- [Leon] Joe, I think about seven
or eight miles this morning.
- [Joe] And up and down mountains too.
- Yeah, it's crazy.
We had a discussion yesterday
while we were tracking him.
Just looking at the
hooves, and you would think
animal this size would have bigger hooves.
- Yeah.
- But you saw the terrain
that they run in.
So it will be very difficult for him
to move around here if the
hooves were any bigger.
So the hooves are quite small actually
for the size of animal, but
it is because of the terrain.
- Yeah cause then when
I stopped and asked you,
you know what that track
was, you said, kudu,
and I said, a small one,
and Douglas said no big.
- [Leon] Yes.
- And I thought oh wow really.
Cause I guess I was expecting--
- Yeah because the other
thing that happened
is that you saw us with oryx track,
and remember it looked a lot bigger.
But the big thing is
what you must remember
with the oryx that it's
a desert dwelling animal,
but normally most of the
time they're in Namibia,
they were introduced here.
And the big thing is to walk in the sand,
it's like deflating your car tires.
So it will carry the
weight, and that's why
there's a bigger hooves to just spread the
weight over a bigger area.
- That makes sense.
But yeah you're right with all the rocks,
they gotta step in between them.
- [Leon] Yes.
- Like we're supposed
to, but with my big feet
I (laughing), I stumble.
- We stumble.
We stumble sometimes.
(dramatic music)
- As it turns out that shot hit about
two inches a little bit
forward on his shoulder,
just a two inches back
he would of been down.
So that was the difference between
instant elation and finding that animal,
and a night of worry, and
another whole day of tracking.
And the work that we put in.
I mean have all those people to thank,
especially Douglas and Leon
for their tracking and persistence.
And Geoffery and his
crew that came out there.
It was just amazing to
see those guys work,
and to bring this thing
to a satisfactory end.
(upbeat music)
- Geoffrey come here.
Explain something to me.
Kudu eat this.
- Yes.
- How do they not have
like, how do they eat this?
(laughing)
Would eat that?
- Hell no.
(laughing)
Well first get out, get yourself unstuck.
This is a vachellia tortilis.
When they're young like this it just looks
like a big bush, but if you scan over,
if you look at this tree behind us.
- Yep.
- That's called an umbrella
tree because you know
they come up and they spread open.
That is nasty.
I mean it got me right there.
These leaves come off really easy.
So what they do is if you have a look,
when they're really young
they have a lot of these
long white thorns to protect
them from over grazing,
so they can reach adulthood.
Yeah so this got softer thorn yet,
so this is new growth.
But over here the thorns are hard already.
It's a mature branch.
But if you have a look, all these hooks
run in one line.
- [Richard] They're all
pointing back toward the tree.
- And you can take your hand
and actually strip the leaves.
Another really cool part of this location,
is these trees, it's amazing
how complex nature is.
So in an area where
you have a lot of them,
and they start getting heavily browsed,
they'll actually produce more thorns
of these long white ones
to protect themselves
against over grazing.
- So that's why some
trees have longer thorns
than the other trees.
- Exactly.
- And then you think it's a different tree
but it's the same tree.
- It's the same tree.
And also in maturity,
the more mature and
established the root system is
the less thorns they need
to protect themselves.
Now what's really cool is,
in an area where there's
heavy over grazing, not
only the trees that are
over grazed themselves will
start producing more thorns,
the really neat part is
the whole area's trees
will produce more thorns.
- [Richard] To push the
animals out of there
to some place else to eat.
- Well just to have
them graze, browse this.
But who tells the tree
that isn't being browsed
to produce more thorns?
Aint that cool?
- The tree whisperer.
(laughing)
- The Lorax.
Now what about this one though?
- So this is the Acacia
Mellifera, the black thorn.
And this is the bane of our lives.
This is a very adult one and you can see
it's very established.
But this is the one that rips clothes
and just tears everything up.
But once again the leaves
come off very easily,
and all their thorns are
stripped in one direction.
- Yeah so you can go this way,
but you can't go that way.
- Yeah I wouldn't do
that without a glove on.
(laughing)
- But how do the kudu,
I know they get thorns
and stuff, I've seen them.
- So they wrap their tongue around it
and strip the leaves, but only
in that direction.
- In that direction.
That's cool.
That's really cool.
Can you demonstrate that?
With your tongue?
(upbeat music)
- Straight up Lion King shit right here.
I ended up hunting with Thys,
and I first saw Thys
when we got off the plane
at the airport.
He kinda looks like a little boy,
I mean his waist, he's probably
got like a 26 inch waist,
he weighs about 97 pounds soaking wet.
(upbeat music)
I tell you what after hunting with him
for a very short time,
and shoot by the end
of day number two, we were at some sorta
weird little bromance going on,
and it was just symbiotic.
And I learned later that Richard
and Geoffrey had paired everybody up
on a personality basis,
of course physical basis Thys
and I were not compatible.
Do you got any kids?
- I do have a little girl.
Three and half.
- What's her name?
- Mira Renee.
I bet you're totally whipped aren't ya?
Totally.
- Totally, totally.
- Yeah.
Me too.
- You probably know
how it is.
- I know exactly how it is,
I've got two girls myself, yeah.
- Yeah.
- I always thought I wanted
the boy first actually.
Just because girls bring
home a stupid boyfriend
or something I could pull out a $50 bill,
slide it across the table and say son,
dad's got a little problem
he needs you take care of.
But.
No it's good I wouldn't change a thing.
- Mine, I'm very surprised.
That she just wants, she keeps telling me
that when she's big, she's
gonna end up hunting with me.
For some reason.
She wants to shoot a lipid.
- Aim high.
Yeah, I like that.
- And guess where the shot
placement needs to be?
- She knows doesn't she?
- She keeps saying she's going to shoot
it in the butt.
(laughing)
The other shoulder.
- You've gotta couple of years to work
out the details.
(upbeat music)
So what sparked the interest
to be a professional hunter?
I mean is that, you grew
up you were riding around
with your Red Ryder BB gun and saying
that's what I'm gonna do when I grow up?
- No, not at all.
No obviously we've always been hunting.
It's, living in South
Africa it's a really,
really big hunting culture.
Especially for meat.
For every year, you and your father
will go out and collect something,
we save for winter, for this year.
- Sure.
- But no I actually studied architecture.
- No uh.
You're not (laughing).
- And around the time I was studying
we bought a game farm and my parents
also moved out there from Kimberley.
And, yeah, after that I came back,
my dad was engineer, I helped
him for like a year or two.
And then slowly started
taking clients out,
freelancing, and then
at the end of the day
I just decided the bush is better.
I couldn't take it sitting
in front of the computer
every single day.
- That makes sense.
I don't mean to laugh at ya,
I just think of architects, I just think
of refined and proper, that's not you.
- You don't think I'm--
- No this suits you.
(upbeat music)
What's a group of warthogs called?
A covie.
- A what?
- A flock of warthogs.
- No, I don't know.
- What do you mean?
Didn't you go to school?
- I didn't learn animals.
- [Luke] Clearly they are,
didn't you go to school?
- [Thys] Family unit.
- [Luke] That's lame.
- A family of warthogs.
- That's stupid.
Thought you went to school for that shit.
(upbeat music)
One of the things I
appreciate most about hunting
with Thys was just his willingness to stop
and take a break from, you know, stalking,
whatever we were hunting at the time.
And just experience Africa around us.
Hey what's the deal with these hay piles
in the trees anyway?
- This is called a social weavers nest.
- It's a nest?
- It's a nest.
- The social weavers build
an apartment complex,
if you will, out of grasses.
I don't even think
there's any mud in there.
- They're this small little weavers.
But they stay together.
Almost like an apartment building.
Hundreds of them.
If you look underneath.
- I feel, I feel like I
shouldn't have my mouth open.
(laughing)
- If you look underneath here
you'll see there's holes.
- So each one of those
belongs to a little?
- Oh yeah.
- Social weavers.
- Those are everywhere,
I just didn't think a whole
lot of it I guess right away.
Weird.
I have one complaint about Thys,
it was that he was being too picky.
We say what I thought
was a very, very good
kudu bull on the first evening.
And, you know how guys will often say,
don't pass on the first
evening what you would
shoot on the last evening.
- That's a bull but he's young.
(suspenseful music)
- Is that a good one or not?
- [Thys] On the last day maybe.
(suspenseful music)
He's nice and wide.
- You're just looking for those tips
to come around another couple of inches?
- If you look at him from the front,
you want to see his tips.
Those last points are still leaning back,
you want them to be upright.
On the last day maybe.
- Copy that.
We say a good kudu bull,
maybe I was a little bit
anxious to get a kudu under my belt.
Ended up not, Thys, he
said, maybe on the last day.
If you shoot something that first evening
than you're experience is done, right.
I wanna keep hunting.
I don't wanna go there and just shoot,
I wanna hunt, I wanna
experience everything
between day one and day the end.
- [Thys] He's just missing
that one, too small.
- [Luke] He's not quite there huh?
- [Thys] No.
- But it seemed like
everybody else was seeing
kudu bulls or seeing the
type of mature kudu bulls
that we wanted to harvest
and they were everywhere
but where we were at the time.
(upbeat music)
- Hopefully then we're gonna give these
just a little bit of time.
- Okay.
- And just relax.
- I noticed that they just took off.
- They keep moving.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they're herd animals.
I need to let them settle down.
- Okay.
So we'll be here for a little bit?
- Yeah, yeah.
Let them settle.
And there's lots of time.
- Okay.
- I don't want to push them too hard.
- That's fine.
So what's your background?
How did you get into this?
- I'm actually, when I started working,
I applied for a job
with a diamond company.
- [Alfredo] Diamonds?
- So, you know, for five years
I sorted diamonds.
- [Alfredo] Oh really.
- So I'm actually qualified
diamond evaluator.
- [Alfredo] Oh wow.
(laughing)
- And now we're hunting.
- [Alfredo] Yeah, so how did
that transition come about?
- It's just a passion I had.
- [Alfredo] Oh yeah.
- I think I got tired
of the collar and tie.
- [Alfredo] Yeah, yeah.
- And just one day decided, you know,
it's always been a passion.
- So what's it take to be a
professional hunter?
- Professional hunter?
In this country it's
pretty much like a course
you need to attend.
- Right.
- It's normally 10 days to two weeks,
very intense, it covers
a wide range of areas,
it's not just the hunting,
it's rifle handling,
working with clients.
Able to prepare food, first aid.
- [Alfredo] Right.
- [Mark] You know, it's a very wide range.
It's a lot of work to cram into two weeks.
- Oh yeah, I noticed your knowledge too,
of plants, trees, all the wildlife here
is really extensive.
- [Mark] It's also
very important.
Cause you know clients
are asking you questions
all the time.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- [Mark] And you need to try
and provide them with an answer.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- [Mark] So but I think what makes
a good professional hunter
is experience.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- It's not something you
can learn out of book.
- [Alfredo] No.
- So it comes with experience.
And over the years you sort of develop
information, you get information,
and I think what's for me the amazing part
is working with the different people.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- I have hunted with bus drivers,
you name it.
And yourself, what type of work do you do?
- I'm a photographer and
writer for Guns and Ammo,
and other publications that are related
to guns and ammo, the
Outdoors Sportsman Group,
they put out over 20 publications.
I shoot a lot.
And since I write a lot about rifles,
I get to shoot a lot of rifles,
and practice at the same time.
- [Mark] Why this rifle,
what made you decide
to use this one?
- I know a lot of people with
a lot of expensive rifles.
And I look at things from
a working person's budget.
What can a working person afford.
And I really like eking
out the most performance
out of a sub, $1,000.00 rifle.
This rifle was less than $500.00 retail.
And I sort of get a kick
out of trying to make them
shoot small groups.
And not by modifying them,
but just getting to learn
how they behave.
And so I haven't modified this any.
And this shoots,
an inch or smaller with the right ammo,
I'm running six hour, they're elite ammo,
which is a solid copper bullet,
and this thing I shot
five, five shot groups
and it was .83 inches at a hundred yards.
It's a very accurate rifle.
And it's been very, as you see.
- [Mark] Yeah, it's proved itself.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- [Mark] I like it because
from what I've seen
it's easy to handle.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- [Mark] And it's lightweight.
- [Mark] For those long
distances that we track.
- I couldn't ask for
anything more in terms
of for the price wise.
- Yeah.
(upbeat music)
- [Richard] While on
safari in South Africa
it's near impossible to let the trip go by
without taking in some
of the local culture.
Heck, that's part of the allure.
Whether it's the area's rich history,
the amazing people, or the
picturesque surroundings,
a safari is incomplete without seeing
as much as possible of
this remarkable country.
Of course as outdoor journalists,
we know that learning as much as possible
about our surroundings will
help us best tell the story.
- Joe we were just done
recovering your kudu.
And we needed some fuel, so I
brought you to the community
and I remember you asking me
why it's called Salt Lake.
- Yeah why is it Salt Lake?
- And I said, hey I'll come show you
why this is called Salt Lake.
So back in the late
1800s when this area was
first settled by the
British, and predominately
the Dougmore family.
They found a large salt deposits here.
Animals licking the soil,
and they actually sank water
wells down here for
water for their cattle.
But it was too saline to do anything with.
And, you know, over the
centuries people have
mostly used sea water
to evaporation for salt
or natural salt deposits, or salt mining.
And what they do here is
actual solely evaporation.
So if you have a look over there,
there's these squared pond like things,
and they actually pump the water out
from underground, and pump it in there
and evaporate over a few weeks,
and then it crystallizes.
- It's that salty?
- It's that salty.
So the water that's
underneath us right here
actually has between,
depending on rainfall,
between a 67 to 85% solidity.
And salt starts crystallizing
in the mid to high 90s.
And that just shows
you how difficult it is
to make sea salt, because
sea salt's actually
only about 14, 15% depending
on where you are in the world.
- [Joe] Really.
And what's this salt used for?
- So most of the salt
is used as feed salt.
And the problem with that
and why it is that way,
is this salt is actually very, very health
for human consumption,
but because of they open
and it's natural and
there's no protection,
there's a lot of sand that blows into it,
and actually taints it.
You know if you have a look
it's got a bit of a brown
color to it.
And it can go from almost
pure white to almost
look like sand depending on the
amount of wind there's been,
and how much containments
have blown into it.
But it's very, very
healthy, and what's cool
about this salt as well,
it's not just pure salt,
it's got a lot of added
trace minerals to it
that's actually very healthy for us.
- So this has been going on for how long?
- So they started in the late 1800s,
the Dougmore family and they
were quite a few that did this.
And around then there was about
250 people employed there.
And then from about 1950 to mid 1950s
there was about 50 people are employed
by the Dougmore family and
all they do is just salt.
And they produce about
5,000 tons of salt per year.
- [Joe] Really.
So it's still owned by the Dougmores?
- [Geoffrey] It's still
owned by the Dougmore family.
Same property that we're
hunting on at the moment.
- [Joe] Oh really?
- [Geoffrey] Yep.
- [Joe] Oh that's interesting.
- [Geoffrey] Yeah my neighbors,
been my neighbors for over 150 years.
(laughing)
- That's pretty interesting.
So then they pile it, they dry it there,
they pile it over here,
they bring it in here,
and bag it.
- Exactly.
So once it starts
crystallizing and they start
scraping it all together,
they got five, 10 loaders and stuff,
and back in the day it used to be done
by a shovel and a wheel barrel.
But now it's, you know, a forklift goes,
a fronting loader goes and picks it up,
and comes and dumps it
in these piles behind us.
And then we actually
caught them in the middle
of the bagging process.
They have a bagging machine run by a PTO.
And that's actually, the
front end is a crusher
that they can set to how fine you want it,
and then they bag it
with that chute there.
Weigh it and then stitch it.
And then yep this goes to our local crops.
A lot of it goes to for
water softeners as well.
- [Joe] Oh really.
- But I tell you about
95% goes to our crops
for feed salt.
- That's pretty interesting.
And it's, so what's
the origin of the salt.
I mean is it, is it prehistoric?
Or is just geology?
- The smart people say this used to form
part of the Indian Sea.
- [Joe] Oh really.
- And that's why that we
have these salt deposits.
And like the panru where
we had the shooting range.
That is, if we drove
it, it just as not quite
as saline but very salty.
When you wash your hands with the water
that comes out there it's actually sticky.
- Oh really?
- [Geoffrey] Yep.
- So you could have a salt operation too.
- [Geoffrey] We'll leave
that to my friends.
- [Joe] Yeah.
- Let's head on back to
camp and go have a whiskey
and celebrate your kudu.
- It's sundown, I could do that.
- [Roger] When you head out
into the bush of South Africa,
your mind is focused
on the animals you're hunting.
Whether it be a kudu bull,
mountain zebra, gemsbok,
or even dangerous game,
each hunt offers the
potential for a fantastic
wild encounter and an everlasting memory.
Failing to take photos or video
to help enhance the safari
memories is a mistake.
So to is an African Safari
without taxidermy plants.
During this safari we were able to visit
and learn from African San Taxidermy.
Which is one of the
largest taxidermy outfits
in the country.
Mounting a kudu is not the same
as mounting a whitetail deer.
And the San team knows African game.
- So once you have booked
your hunt with your outfitter,
we would suggest that you make contact
with a taxidermy in order to
explore all of your options.
Also to get the know of all the posts,
and the rules and regulations regarding
the export of your trophies.
It's very important for
the hunter and the PH
to have a great relationship,
but it's just as important for the PH,
the hunter, and the taxidermy
to have a great relationship.
In order for everybody to
keep everybody informed
with the new rules and regulations
when it comes to side fees and
the export of your trophies
as well as what your options will be,
which is very important.
Once you want to do a shoulder mount,
you must make sure that
the animal is capped,
if you wanna do a full
mount it's very important
that the PH knows the
instructions around that.
Pedestal mounts, everything
gets capped in different ways.
Your different options would be,
going from the least
expensive is your skull mount.
That's just your skull and
horns on a wooden plate.
Then you've got your shoulder mount.
Then you've got your wall pedestal mount.
You've got a pedestal
box, a floor pedestal box.
Where you have a shoulder
mount on a pedestal box.
And then you've got your full mount.
Obviously your most impressive.
And will bring your memories back to life.
Everything is based on
what you're looking for,
and depending on your budget.
Once we pick up your
trophies from the farm,
we will be finished with
all of the documentation
from the PH and the outfitter.
We will then bring the trophies here
to African San Taxidermy
where we will tag them
and check them into our
storage facility safely.
Once that has been done
we will send you an email
to just once again
confirm the instructions.
It's no need to worry as we will apply
for all of the necessary documents
to make sure that we export
your trophies safely.
However, it is very important to know
and to understand the
rules and the regulations.
Okay I think that taxidermy work
is very important.
Although photos are great to look at,
nothing keeps your memories alive like
a full mount buffalo.
(upbeat music)
- Where ya'll been all day?
- I'm really, really glad
that everything worked
out the way that it did.
- Fat boy must walk.
- You all couldn't even bring us lunch?
(laughing)
- I walked.
- We had a crisp walk today.
I got it done.
- What'd you do?
- Remember I was
telling you before I said, 99% of the time
I will get it done, but 75% of the time
I will screw it up real bad along the way.
(laughing)
- Just like, well I aint gonna say that.
Anyway what did ya do?
- I gotta speak more
kindly of Thys tonight
then I did last night.
- Oh.
- The pressure was on me tonight.
- Oh so he did something?
- He did something.
- I finally redeemed.
- He did.
Let's just say it's weird
when you gotta herd of 60
gemsbok looking at ya.
It's strange.
- 60?
- Yeah probably around there.
- Just all lined out the most,
it looked like a puzzle.
The most stunning thing, and each one
looks exactly like the next one,
and Thys said the one
on the left is a bull.
And so we were right at 300 yards.
And I'm sure I pulled the
shot just a little bit,
getting excited, and after the shot
I'm like, I don't think
I accounted for the wind
as much as I should of,
and that shot drifted back
about a foot, and that
start four and half miles
of hashtag goat rope.
- Oh yeah.
Little bit of a rodeo.
- [Thys] There was some tracking involved.
- There was some tracking,
and I gotta, there's so much
to learn from these guys.
I mean think about that,
it's nothing to be proud
of, obviously I wanted
to hanker him right there
and make it quick.
- Yeah.
- That's the end game, that's the goal.
But to be able to stay on that track,
and I had the phone in my pocket,
four and half miles.
- [Richard] Of tracking?
- Of tracking.
And we could see him occasionally,
he'd be out there, you know, 600 yards.
- Did he separate?
- He separated.
- Yep.
- Then he got with another bull
and they started tussling
around a little bit.
- [Richard] Even after he was shot?
- Yes, after he was shot.
And got in with some
bush buck and started,
that like rejuvenated him and he started
running with them.
- That herd mentality will do that.
- Yep.
- But today we saw the real three range.
- That was awesome.
- That thing was just
walking down the fence line.
At one stage Luke was like,
there he is, there he is.
I said, no it can't be him.
Like 50 yards further, hole,
it was him going through there.
- How can a 500 pound animal fit through
a hole that big?
With horns that are 40 inches long
sticking out of his head?
- Somebody shooting at
him that's what it is.
- I was on my belly.
- Somebody shooting at you,
you'd go through a real little hole.
(laughing)
- But finally, finally that
that exited the job end.
The last shot was 270 yards.
- Yep.
- 270 and he goes
- In the engine box,
perfectly behind the shoulder.
- Light one down.
Woof.
- Dropped him.
When you hit him where
you're supposed to hit him,
that shit works real well.
- He took like 10 steps.
- I started dry heaving it just,
that adrenaline though, you know,
and you get two and half hours,
four and half miles to think about,
I mean you question
everything as a rifleman,
everything great you've ever done,
all the great shots I made
at the range two days ago
hitting an eight inch plate easy
at 300 yards, and I blew it man.
- You tell people to practice
before they come over here,
and they don't know what practice means.
They go out for one day and think,
hey I can shoot pretty good.
- It's very hard to replicate the emotion
that you feel.
- And nothing against
Thys or any of the PHs.
But you've got a professional that's seen
thousands of people,
they seen more animals
killed every year.
You know the whitetail hunters back home
thing they've seen a lot of animals die.
No.
These guys see thousands.
You got this guy looking
over your shoulder,
that's hard to get out of your mind.
- At that's, I felt horrible, you know,
take every step, every step,
just guts are all ripped up,
but he turned around every now and then,
he was like, we're gonna get him.
And when he said it, I believed it.
- Yeah.
- I mean it's like we're gonna get him.
Again, we caught up with
him, and made the shot.
- I could not believe
the distance he went.
- It's impressive.
- But more importantly
where we left off last night
with the wounded kudu, what happened?
(laughing)
- That's the bullet that sealed the deal.
- Well done.
Good for you.
- Finally, finally got him.
Kinda turned a one day
hunt into a two day rodeo.
- The full experience.
- The full African experience.
And we had a little bit
of luck too I would say.
Wouldn't you?
- Yeah, luck for sure.
I think, you know, it's
often when preparation
and everything just comes together.
And often on a hunt when
everything goes smoothly
you don't actually learn anything.
- [Luke] That's a great point.
- [Leon] All of us just want
us to end it with one shot.
That's the, aim is everything.
Stalk up on an animal and take it,
but often there's some
learning or experience
in making a mistake, and then
going through the problems.
- Yeah that's what I was telling you,
at the end of the day, after everything
worked out well, the story behind it
is so much better,
and I mean the experience,
we you have that trophy
on the wall, you don't just
remember that one perfect shot.
- [Luke] You remember the emotion.
- [Thys] You remember the
emotion, the tracking, everything.
The whole experience of it.
- The tracking, I mean
we were going so fast
I had to do the midwest
shuffle just to keep up,
and they were on the track,
I mean think about that,
I was power walking--
- [Richard] Wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute,
can you show us what that looks like?
- I'll show you later.
(laughing)
- You're gonna have to do
that dance for us tonight.
- Something we do to keep warm,
remember the power walk.
- But no seriously, I
mean think, we're walking
at like, I don't know,
three miles an hour,
a brisk walk.
And they're tracking that fast.
There's tracks going
this way and that way,
and there was a herd
of 60 gemsbok in there,
this one.
- [Richard] Yep.
- [Luke] Dead nuts confidence, this one.
- Yep and just like with yours,
you see what a well organized outfit
when you get a situation like you had.
- Yeah.
- Pull out all the stops.
- [Joe] Yeah boy do I
appreciate that by the way.
For bringing out the extra
help, everything like that.
- [Geoffrey] My absolute pleasure.
- [Joe] Made me feel
a heck of a lot better
that we're gonna have a
good chance to get this.
That's what I asked you this morning,
what do you think our chances were,
and you said 70%, and
I said, I'll take 70%.
- [Richard] I was thinking like 55.
- But that was after...
- [Geoffrey] Do you no
longer have faith in me?
- [Richard] I'm a pessimist.
- Yeah, me too.
I must admit, I told him
after that rain last night
and everything, if you're
going to cut a track again
it's going to be--
- [Richard] But he was still bleeding.
- That's what I said to him this morning.
If there was no rain
yesterday, and it was a
clear blood trail, 95 to 98, maybe 100%,
but after the rain yesterday, you know,
it was yeah.
- Yeah that threw this running--
- Starting completely over.
- But the big thing is luckily we saw him,
by accident, and it led
on to the blood trail.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Four and half miles.
(laughing)
- I don't believe in accidents.
- Showoffs.
- Accidents are unintentional occurrences.
- But actually I was--
- If you hadn't been there,
you wouldn't of seen him.
- I was thinking about that too,
because actually we
were putting a stalking
on the bull that Geoffrey had seen,
and it was further beyond,
and we didn't really
think it could be him, but you could see
his horns shining in the sun,
so we had to go check him out
to basically eliminate it.
- [Richard] Yep.
- So that, that wasn't him,
and we're climbing and
kinda the same thing,
mountain goat doing his
kind of stuff all his life,
and as I'm huffing and
puffing, and it's like
man we're really gonna
go up there that fast,
and jump in these rocks,
rocks, rocks, rocks,
and so then we eliminate that one,
he says we'll runs off,
you know, no limping,
no anything, it's like
well that's not him.
So then when we head back we go up on top
of the copie, and basically
we're coming back,
and you know we gotta
basically start over.
And we actually just
bumped him out of a canyon.
And when he runs off, then these guys say
oh he's limping, and I
go these guys are just.
(laughing)
Yeah trying to make me--
- They're just trying to
make you walk more, right?
- Yeah exactly.
Now they want me to walk up that?
(laughing)
And so we go down to where he was,
and there was blood, and I go (chuckles)
and then I knew we'll get him,
cause I know how good these guys are,
these trackers are, that
if they've got fresh blood,
if it doesn't rain, you know, clear skies,
and I knew that I'm not leaving the track.
And I know they won't,
so, we're gonna get him
no matter how long it takes.
- Well done guys.
So all in all--
- Good day.
- Finally.
- Hey.
- What's happening.
- You always get in
for the camera or what?
- Late as usual.
- It's a hell of a drive for a milkshake.
(laughing)
- Told you.
- How's it going?
Sorry we're late.
- What have you been doing?
- Duty calls.
- Yeah we've been getting stuff down.
- We have not seen you all day.
No morning report, no evening report.
- We made the most of our daylight.
- We had an incredible day.
- Really?
- Just say no, you're so secretive,
no one listens, no anything,
you're always arrive late.
- Won't answer the radio.
We don't have no news.
(laughing)
- Just turn it off.
- That's right.
No interference.
(laughing)
We had an awesome day.
- Yeah, we were chasing this territorial
blackbuck, and we come across
these warthogs running,
and Mark goes, see that one in the front,
there's something wrong
with her, take her out.
I get on my sticks,
like a turret, meet it,
boom, it hits the ground, comes back up,
and runs straight towards us.
(laughing)
- [Thys] Charging!
- Chamber, boom hit it
again, it keeps coming,
boom, hit again, boom.
(laughing)
- I couldn't figure out
what was wrong with it.
The whole back side of the
warthog was covered in blood.
- Really?
- Yeah, just a young sow.
But there were three of them,
and she was leading them.
- [Leon] That's very odd.
- So I just made a call and said--
- No good call to make.
- Yeah something was
wrong with her for sure.
So you got charged by a warthog?
- Yes.
- I've never seen anyone.
- I feel like you were buffalo hunting.
- Oh it was so awesome.
I felt like I was in a video game.
(laughing)
It was so neat.
- Was he screaming?
- It was, you know, it's
the stuff that you practice,
stuff like one of my shooting
instructors is Jim Cober,
from the sites in Illinois,
and the last class
I had with him we were practicing movers.
So I just boom, boom.
It was neat that it paid off.
- [Richard] Yep.
- Yeah.
- And you just mentioned
before they arrived,
practice.
- Practice.
Yeah.
Apparently he practiced
more than Luke did.
(laughing)
- Do you wanna eat my
gemsbok or do you wanna
eat his warthog?
(laughing)
- Hang on now, hang on now.
Steak or sausage?
(laughing)
And that sorta clean kill.
- We're going to get him his boots.
- We're driving along afterwards,
we come in to a trackers
going back to his truck
for your gemsbok.
- [Thys] Oh yeah Paul City.
- Yeah.
So we gave him a ride to his truck.
Which put us on a detour.
And as we're coming back the sun's already
behind the mountain, and
I'm just enjoying the view
up top with George, the tracker,
and so I'm just enjoying
it, and I'm thinking
there's nothing gonna go
on, and all the sudden
Mark stops the truck.
"Hey, hey, there's a buck over there,
shoot him, shoot him."
And the funny thing is,
at that exact same time,
George is on my right, the
buck is on my right as well.
- The buck?
What are we talking about?
- A kudu.
- Oh!
Well done.
- So at that exact same
time the walkie talkie
starts going off.
(laughing)
- And it's me and you.
- Yeah we were talking at sunset.
- And it was on the inside
jacket of George's shirt,
inside jacket then he had
another jacket on top,
so he's trying to figure out which pocket.
(laughing)
I grabbed the rifle and
he finally finds it,
and then he steps aside,
and I just post up
onto the bar, the upper bar on the truck.
- And I grabbed the Sig
Sauer and I go 141, confirm.
And it's quiet.
(laughing)
- Shoot him!
- Yeah so I get on there
get a good beat on it, boom,
and it just goes like this,
and it stumbles, and it
just walks a little bit
more forward, I follow it, and Mark goes
shoot it again, I see
exactly where it's at,
get a clear shot again,
boom, and he just goes down.
- Just for reassurance.
- Well done.
- But assurance.
- [Luke] So that's
how you do it.
- [Mark] Yeah.
Two bullets a scene like this.
- [Alfredo] Yeah.
- [Joe] That's how you do
it, it doesn't take two days.
- [Alfredo] No.
(laughing)
- [Alfredo] You found yours?
- [Joe] We got him.
- Oh that's, congratulations.
- Same to you.
- [Thys] Well done guys.
- Yeah.
- Congratulations.
- So that was my, that's
why we're arriving late,
of course I have to do my photo shoot
with my lights and all this stuff.
And it's already dark, so
then that's why I explained
that I carry all this gear.
(laughing)
- [Geoffrey] Now I can
leave the bag behind.
- So now let me get this straight.
So you shot the warthog this morning.
- I shot it in the afternoon.
Like an hour before.
- Oh so you hunted all morning,
and then went to Kimberley to the spur,
got the motel, and then come back?
(laughing)
- [Alfredo] Yeah, yeah, I
came back, yeah exactly.
- Okay I'm just making sure.
- I was squeezing a siesta as well.
- [Richard] A siesta?
(laughing)
- Yeah so I had a fantastic day here
at Fort Richmond Safaris, thank you.
- [Geoffrey] My pleasure.
That you.
- Everybody did.
- Outstanding PH, outstanding tracker,
I can't ask for anything better.
- Thank you.
- I've never seen someone so excited
to shoot a running pig.
- Really?
(laughing)
- Well we just said it was a good day,
I didn't expect it to get this good.
- Kudu, warthog, kudu, warthog.
- Gemsbok.
- All free range in one day.
- Yep, absolutely.
- Not just any kudu, the kudu.
- The kudu.
- Yeah that's amazing.
- That's a big deal to get that kudu,
and you'll find him.
I will sleep much better tonight.
- Well cheers everybody
to a great day of hunting.
(guys talking)
- It was a great day.
(upbeat music)
(soft music)
- [Man] That fucking bull.
- Well it's a zebra.
(laughing)
- What is happening?
(African music)
- One of the largest misconceptions
of hunting in Africa is that you need
a big custom rifle, or
a big, large caliber
an expensive custom gun.
This offering from
Mossberg, Patriots Revere,
is the perfect African Safari rifle.
Inexpensive, but still has
the plastic safari look
with this beautiful wood stock.
So when you need an African Safari rifle,
you don't need thousands of dollars,
you need hundreds of dollars.
Mossberg, this perfect
African Safari rifle.
(African music)
(gun shots)
- Hi I'm Richard Mann and
this is a SureFire light,
now the thing about hunting is
some people hunt at
dark but 90% of hunting
occurs during daylight hours, however,
that hunting that occurs
during daylight hours
starts before daylight and typically ends
after daylight, that means if you're gonna
be a hunter and you're
serious about success,
you gotta have a flashlight.
And nobody makes better
flashlights than SureFire.
And there's three things
to think about when you're
buying a light, especially for hunting,
one, is LED, you want LED bulbs
cause they last longer
and they're more durable.
Two, you want lithium batteries.
Same thing, they last longer
and they're more durable.
And lumens, you need to have a specific
amount of lumens.
As you can see, this
SureFire has two levels.
One this is great for moving around camp,
and not stumbling over your own feet,
but this is good for seeing stuff.
So think about the amount of lumens
you need for light, and check this out.
This little SureFire here is rechargeable,
what's really cool about it,
put it right on your hat, eating dinner
around the campfire, using
both hands to skin an animal,
this light has you covered.
So, if you're a hunter, you need a light,
and it needs to be a SureFire.