Previously on Battlestar Galactica...
We haven't been properly introduced.
I'm Leoben.
I'm looking forward to spending
more time with you, Starbuck.
We have a lot to talk about !
It's gonna be fun.
Congratulations, Commander.
The Pegasus is your command.
I am picking up a large planetary body.
It's habitable.
We may have just found a world
that can support human life.
I know in my gut that settling on this
planet's gonna mean disaster for humanity,
and I will not say otherwise
just to win an election.
I take the office of president
of the twelve Colonies of Kobol
and I'm going
to sign my first executive order.
Requiring to immediately
establish settlements
on the planet we have come to know
as New Caprica.
If you want to move down there, go ahead.
Be my guest.
Go down and cat around with all the men.
Saul, I want you.
At last, a safe haven we can call home.
Oh, my Gods.
It's a cylon fleet, they found us.
We have to get out of here, sir.
We can't just leave all those people behind.
There's nothing we can do.
We're in no shape for a fight, sir.
- They'll be wiped out.
- We don't have a choice.
We need to get out of here right now !
Begin jump prep. We're leaving.
But we'll be back.
Cylons just jumped into orbit
and the fleet's jumped away.
They've left us.
On behalf of the people of
the twelve Colonies...
I surrender.
I'm looking for Kara Thrace.
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )= -
presents
Battlestar Galactica
Season 3 - Episode 1
" OCCUPATION "
- =( www.seriestele.net )= -
Transcript :
- =( www.sadgeezer.com )= -
Synchro :
Dapitch666, Goufrach,
Kha-nabis, Lovechange, NikoMagnus
-=( Lords of Kobol )=-
Do you know that every time
they take you out of this cell,
we come in here and we
change those little hash marks on your
little calendar there you're trying to hide.
Potatoes, gravy.
Even some carrots.
Heavenly father, we thank you
for the bounty of this table.
Yes.
Come on !
Don't stop.
You son of a bitch ! Son of a bitch !
Baby !
Oh, boy.
All right, we're armed.
They're inbound. Let's move !
I need a knife.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I must say I quite enjoyed that.
I'm so glad.
And...
when do I get what I want ?
I believe that's happening right now.
We reviewed your case today.
And I must say there was great
disappointment on the review committee.
Come on.
We gotta get you processed.
It'll take an hour or so.
Bureaucracy must be served.
But if you're lucky,
you'll get home by dinner time. Colonel.
Come on.
I'm not gonna hold
this door open forever.
Attention New Capricans,
Effective immediately,
potable water will be distributed
residence on even number
on even number days.
and odd number on odd number days.
Rationning will continue
for the five periods remaining.
Saul !
We're all in this together.
Oh, thank the Gods.
What did they do to you ?
It's all right, Ellen. I'm out.
That's all that matters.
Attention New Capricans,
Effective immediately...
Well, let's get out of here.
Okay.
Ready ? Now !
For frak's sakes...
Come on, come on ! Is that thing
gonna work or what ?!
Worked that time.
Go, go !
Frakkin' insurgents.
You look...
so lovely tonight.
I'll see you soon...
Kara.
Take your time.
134th day of the cylon
occupation of New Caprica.
Today is Mars day.
Somehow it seems appropriate
to honor the god of war
on a day when it feels like perpetual war
is the only realistic prospect for us.
We've had no contact with Galactica
since it left four months ago.
But I refuse to believe
that Adama has abandoned us.
Our insurgency has been
striking back against the Cylons
whenever and wherever possible.
Although at times these attacks
seem like futile gestures,
I believe that they are critical to morale,
to maintaining some measure of hope.
But in order for the insurgency to have
a more meaningful impact,
we need to strike a high profile target.
It is simply not enough to kill Cylons,
because they don't die.
They resurrect themselves,
and they continue to walk among us.
It is horrifying.
The cylon occupation authority
continues to exert
complete control over the city,
and we remain at their mercy.
The colonial government
under president Gaius Baltar
functions in name only.
Let's review why we're here, shall we ?
We're supposed to bring
the word of "God" to the people, right ?
To save humanity from damnation
by bringing the love of "God"
to these poor benighted people.
We're here because a majority of the cylon
felt that the slaughter of mankind
had been a mistake.
We're here to find a new way
to live in peace.
- As God wants us to live.
- And it's been a fun ride so far.
But I want to clarify our objectives.
If we're bringing the word of God,
then it follows
that we should employ
any means necessary to do so.
Yes, fear...
is a key article of faith,
as I understand it.
So perhaps it's time to instill
a little more fear into
the people's hearts and minds.
Let's...
Let's execute Baltar.
What ? What ?!
That's not gonna happen.
Just because he's your favorite toy
shouldn't be allowed to intefere
with the larger issues here.
- I think that I have cooperated...
- Gaius is with me.
Anyone who wants to challenge that
will have to deal with me.
Now it doesn't matter.
If we'd killed him at the beginning,
it might have worked.
But now, most humans think of him as a traitor,
and would actually cheer his death.
Fine, fine.
We don't kill Baltar.
We round up the leaders of the insurgency,
and we execute them publicly.
We round up at random
groups off the street,
and we execute them publicly.
Send a message that
the gloves are coming off.
The insurgency stops now
or else we start reducing
the human population to a more...
... manageable size.
I don't know, say, less than 1,000.
- We need to stop being butchers.
- The entire point of coming here,
was to start a new way of life.
To push past the conflict
that's separated us from humans for so long.
And what has it gotten us ?
It's not like they welcomed us
with... with...
Frak it. Never mind.
You're all living in a fantasy world.
Consider the irony in that.
Delusional machines.
What's the universe
gonna come up with next ?
Is it really worth it, Caprica ?
Is the love of that man really worth
possibly losing all of this ?
If you ever experienced love,
you wouldn't have to ask.
In recent months, the Cylons have been
recruiting and training humans
in an attempt to establish
a human police force.
It is hard to think of
anything more despicable
than humans doing
the dirty work of the cylons,
led to believe they were merely taking
the civilian security
out of the hands of the Cylons.
And members of the
human police have since
become an extension of
the cylons' corporeal authority.
And while their names are kept
deeply confidential, there is no question,
some of them
are people we might least expect.
Hundreds of us
have been rounded up by the Cylons,
held in detention, questioned, tortured.
Others have simply vanished.
In recent weeks,
we've been gaining access
to some very important documents
from a source
within Baltar's administration.
No one knows
who this mysterious benefactor is.
But he communicates with the insurgents
by means of a secret signal.
We pray every day for the men and women
who risk their lives to fight the Cylons.
They have everything to lose.
And such little hope of something to gain.
Hey, Jake.
There we go.
Looks like mommy's
gonna get some sleep tonight after all.
Sometimes I hate everything about this place.
Sometimes it's magic.
I gotta go.
I'll be back in a couple hours.
One of these days,
you're just not gonna come back, are you ?
You'll just vanish, and that'll be it.
I'll never see you again.
Nick will never know his father.
Couple hours. I promise.
All right.
- Good to see you, Colonel.
- It's good to be seen.
I know you're wondering,
so I'll save you the trouble.
The eye is gone.
Ripped it right out onto the floor.
Picked it up and showed it to me.
Looked like a hard-boiled egg.
Big boom today.
- Hope that was you two.
- Oh, yeah.
- Heavy Raider too.
- Good men.
- What's our next target ?
- Well, got these today.
They're security plans for the graduation
ceremony at the New Caprica police academy.
These are from the ministry files.
Where are you getting this stuff ?
- Who's your source ?
- I have no idea.
Source won't tell me what their name is.
It's probably safer for all of us.
We've been getting stuff like this for weeks.
Humans working for the Cylons.
Makes you wanna puke.
Yeah, well, all the top occupation brass
is gonna be at the graduation even...
President Baltar.
- Gaius Baltar ?
- Yes, sir.
I think we can get a shot at him too.
But it's gonna be tough
avoiding human casualties.
Don't avoid 'em. Send a message.
You work with the Cylons, you're a target.
No boundaries for the Cylons.
There's no boundaries for us !
Anything we can do
to nail that son of a bitch,
Gaius Baltar, is worth doing.
Where are we on the wireless ?
Nowhere.
Every day, we try and contact the Raptor,
and every day
the Cylons jam the transmission.
I've asked for the inside source to tell us
which of the cylon jamming frequencies
are the weakest, but so far, I got nothing.
You guys are dreaming.
There's no Raptor there, okay ?
There hasn't been one
for the past four months, either.
Galactica's not coming back.
They're not. Accept it.
Watch your frakkin' mouth.
There's a Raptor out there every day,
listening for a wireless call.
It's out there because
that was the plan if anything happened.
And it's out there because the old man
isn't just gonna leave us to the Cylons.
The old man left me to the Cylons, Colonel.
And if it wasn't for my wife
being a royal pain in the ass,
and refusing to let it go,
I would be dead a year now.
Any word on Kara ?
Nothing in four months.
Hi, honey. I'm home.
You kill me...
I download.
I come back, we start over.
Five times now.
I'm trying to help you, Kara.
I only want you
to see the truth of your life.
The reason why
you suffered and you struggled for so long.
That's why God sent me to you.
That's why God wants us to be together.
You're right.
And I hear you. I do.
So thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you for putting up with me.
- I'm so sorry.
- Put it down, Kara.
Just put it down.
I'm a patient man.
- You're not a man.
- I'm willing to wait.
- You just need more time.
- I don't need more frakking time.
It's never gonna happen.
Of course it's gonna happen.
You're gonna hold me in your arms.
You're gonna embrace me.
You're gonna tell me that you love me.
I've seen it.
You're insane.
To know the face of God
is to know madness.
I'm going to bed.
Be nice if you joined me.
Either way,
you'll be spending the night with me.
I do love you, Kara Thrace.
Good night.
Let me out !
Let me out of here !
I don't belong here !
Let me out !
- Racetrack, adjust your line of 20 degrees.
- Snowbird 3, get information.
Okay, Snowbirds,
let's nail this exercise.
How many times are we gonna
run this thing ?
What, you're not having fun yet ?
Snowbirds, Galactica.
Regroup in deployment formation
and proceed to position one.
Snowbird one to snowbirds.
Drop point in eight seconds.
Okay, snowbirds, let's get
this deployment bang on.
The Admiral's watching every move.
Roger, Kat.
We go on your command.
Bomb bay doors open.
All vipers...
break now, now, now !
Deploy drones on my mark.
Three... two... one. Mark !
Frak me !
Gods damn it, Snowbird four !
What the hell happened ?
Can the chatter, snowbirds !
This is the CAG. Abort maneuver.
I say again, decoy squadron,
abort maneuver.
Roger that, leader.
Snowbirds, fall back.
Abort drill.
Await further instructions.
Roger, get off my wings.
Galactica, Kat.
It is a mess out here.
We got decoy drones heading
every which way. Request instructions.
Roger that, Kat.
Abort acknowledged.
You're approaching bingo fuel anyway.
Bring your birds back home.
Belay that.
- Strike my last. Stand by.
- Launch a tanker bird.
Let them practice their in-flight
refueling before they recover the drones.
Have them run the exercise one more time.
Yes, sir.
16 times now, sir.
The next one will be 17, won't it ?
Yes, sir.
Launch the tanker.
All units, Galactica.
Recover drones and prepare
to run training mission again.
- We're launching the tanker bird.
- Tanker ?
Once you've tanked up, head back to position
alpha and prepare for training run 17.
Galactica out.
What the frak are they doing over there ?
This is the Commander.
Get the Admiral on the line.
Admiral, considering how long
our pilots have been in the air,
I suggest we recall the birds
and scrub the training exercise.
If we can't do this
in a training scenario,
how the hell are we supposed to pull
this off with cylon raiders on our asses ?!
- Tell me !
- What the frak do you want from me ?
I don't know how we can
do any of this crap at half-strength !
Collision ! We've had a collision.
- Give me your status, Kat.
- Bingo, Molar, speak to me !
I'm losing flight control !
I got red lights all across the board !
Kat, I'm in a lateral spin
and losing hydraulics.
- My wing's clipped.
- Galactica, Kat !
I'm declaring an emergency. Requesting
priority landing for two bent birds.
- Pull 'em in !
- Yes, sir.
Roger that, Kat.
Bring your birds back home.
This whole thing is frakking insane.
We got two ships at half-strength.
We got crews that haven't seen
action in a year and a half.
And you're acting like the only problem
is they're not working hard enough.
Have you taken a look at
yourself in the mirror lately ?
You're weak, soft !
Mentally and physically.
This isn't about me.
You've had four months
to get your act together.
And so far, all you've
been able to frakkin' do
is to complain and whine
about how hard it is.
Well, guess what.
It's gonna get a lot harder.
Do you understand me ?
Now I want you to turn around
and get your fat ass out of here.
Get your men ready !
Or I'll find someone who can.
Dismissed !
I don't like this one, Colonel.
I think we're the ones
crossing the line here.
It's the only way it's gonna work.
Kid's got access and clearance.
You gotta be square on this.
You can't back out once you start.
I'm not backing out.
It's wrong, Colonel.
You know that, don't you ?
He's a soldier, Chief. Not the first time
we've sent a soldier on a one-way mission.
You know that, don't you ?
This is different.
This is our best chance
to take out Gaius Baltar.
Maybe the only one.
We're sure as frak gonna take it.
Every since they killed Nora,
- I got nothing to live for.
- All right.
You look me in the eye, and you tell me
that you are committed to this.
I'm committed.
May the Gods be with you.
Some things you just don't do, Colonel.
Not even in war.
Well, maybe you'll feel different
when you're sitting in detention.
Duck volunteered, he's going.
It's a hard thing to say, but it seems
like I don't know who my son is anymore.
Same goes for the crew of the ship.
I feel pretty much alone.
Except maybe for you.
I wish I could go back a year and tell
that Admiral Adama about this conversation.
A year's a long time.
Can I ask you something ? Very personal.
Do you feel guilty about leaving
the people behind on New Caprica ?
I don't do guilt.
You know...
a year ago...
when you put me in the cell...
I was at a crossroads.
I sat in here for weeks,
just consumed with rage at all
the things that had happened to me.
And at some point,
I realized it was all just guilt.
I was angry at myself
for the choices I had made.
Betraying my people.
And losing the baby.
So... I had a choice.
I could either
move forward or stay in the past.
But the only way to move forward...
was to forgive myself.
You know, I don't think we can survive.
I don't think...
the fleet or Galactica or
the people on New Caprica
can survive...
unless the man at the top
finds a way to forgive himself.
Two of our pilots almost got killed because
they've been in the cockpit for 11 hours.
And he wants to bust my balls.
"You're soft."
Can you believe that ?
What ?
Oh, you agree. Is that it ?
Forget it, I'm not looking for a fight.
Oh, no, no, no, no. Don't do that.
You got something to say,
come out and say it.
He's right.
You are soft.
I'm not talking about the weight.
You've lost your edge.
Your confidence.
You lost your war, Lee.
And the truth is, you're
a soldier who needs a war.
And you don't wanna hear it,
because you've got it in your head
that your father's the soldier.
And you sure don't wanna be like him.
But you are like him.
You're more like him than you know.
That's one of the reasons I married you.
Okay, it's working.
- I think.
- Is it working or isn't it ?
They keep jamming us.
So much for our source on the inside.
Ten minutes left.
And lots of nothing
on the wireless, as usual.
Keep an eye out for Raiders.
Last listening bird almost
got popped by a pair yesterday.
I almost got it.
Frak ! Turn that thing down !
It's working.
Time's up.
Spin up the FTL and get ready to go.
Hold on.
I'm picking something up.
It's a colonial transmission.
It's a low power signal, but...
the recognition codes match.
Yeah, We got a link to the ground.
Okay, send the coded response.
Spin up the drive, and let's get
the hell back to Galactica.
I've got a signal.
- A Raptor just made contact with us.
- What's it say ?
Will make contact
with this frequency every twelve hours.
Prepare sitrep for command authority.
Have hope. We're coming for you.
We made contact.
I say again.
We made contact with the ground.
Colonel Tigh has formed
an insurgent group against the Cylons,
and is waiting for instructions
on how to coordinate the rescue effort.
It's gonna be okay.
It's really gonna be okay.
These are all the surveillance pictures
taken by the insurgents.
I think we can match names
to about 50 of these photos.
But our best guess puts
the total police force at around 200.
Two hundred ?
I wouldn't have believed
there'd be 20 people
who would turn against their own kind.
I want those names.
I want the rest of the names.
That's tough. The Cylons are afraid
the population will go after any human
who joins the New Caprica police.
As well they should.
I know I haven't lived a model life.
I made a lot of mistakes.
I'm gonna need your protection today.
Mr. President.
Morning, Gaeta.
It's time for the graduation ceremony.
Oh, yes.
The ceremony.
About the ceremony...
There's a been a change of plan.
I won't be going.
Security concern.
Don't look so worried.
There'll be other graduations.
Right. Okay.
I'll just...
let the staff know.
I think we should call off the strike.
There's no reason to go forward
if the Galactica's gonna come back.
What, and pass up a golden opportunity
to kill Gaius Baltar ?
Colonel, I fail to see the point.
Think with your head,
Chief, not with your heart.
The only way they stand a chance
of getting us off this rock
is if the Cylons are too distracted
battling a full-blown
uprising when they get here.
All right, if your source on the inside
says Baltar's not gonna be there, abort.
Otherwise, stick with the plan.
Baltar not at graduation.
Hey, Duck.
Good morning.
And welcome to all graduates.
You are the hope.
You are the dream of a new tomorrow
for Humans and Cylon alike.
And I salute you
for the risks that you have taken
for just showing up today.
Today, you begin a new career
and a new life
as provisional police officers.
And looking out across this room,
I see that the significance of this new path
is not lost on you.
Congratulations,
it's good to have you with us.
Congratulations, Sergeant.
Congratulations, Captain.
It's great to have you with us.
I'll see you soon, Nora.
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
...
We thank you to watch
Battlestar Galactica with our subtitles
...
See you soon for the next episode