The Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
presents
Battlestar Galactica
Season 3 - Episode 2
" PRECIPICE "
Synchro :
Dapitch666, Goufrach,
Kha-nabis, Lovechange, NikoMagnus
Everyone of importance
is being looked at right now.
You're no exception.
I can help you, Laura.
In ways I can not help myself.
I can protect you.
But you have to understand
the situation has changed now.
The insurgency has crossed the line.
Suicide bombings.
It's abhorrent.
It's contrary to everything
that we believe in.
So you...
you and I, we will...
we will publicly condemn these tactics.
They can not be legitimized
in any shape or form.
There's something that scares
the cylons after all.
I should think using men and women
as human bombs should scare us all.
Desperate people take desperate measures.
All right, look me in the eye.
Look me in the eye and tell me
that you approve of sending
young men and women
into crowded places with explosives
strapped to their chests.
I'm waiting for you to look me
in the eye and tell me that you approve.
33 people killed.
And their only crime was
putting on the police uniform
- Trying to bring some order
to the chaos out there.
- Order ?
By arresting innocent people
in the dead of night.
Detaining them indefinitely without charge.
- Torturing them for information !
- Wait a minute ! Nobody's been tortured.
- Tell that to colonel Tigh.
- Nobody has been tortured.
We're done here.
I hope you understand
the severity of the situation.
I ask you to obey the dictates
of your conscience...
which is what I've always done.
Of that I have no doubt.
Please give this lovely lady
her shoes back.
Then get her out of here.
Curfew is now in effect.
Severe penalties will be imposed
on anyone found on the streets.
Curfew is now in effect.
Severe penalties will be imposed
on anyone found on the streets.
You understand your orders, Captain ?
Everything clear ?
Yes, sir.
Good. Don't worry.
We have your back.
Did you hear ?
The cylons cut food rations today.
We heard.
How long before
the next Raptor transmission ?
Two minutes.
You know, they're talking about
shutting down the marketplace.
It's a security risk.
We'll shift target.
You were gonna hit the marketplace ?
The market ?
Full of civilians.
This is crazy.
You know, we need to figure out
whose side we're on.
Which side are we on ?
We're on the side of the demons, Chief.
We're evil men in the gardens of paradise.
Sent by the forces of death
to spread devastation
and destruction wherever we go.
I'm surprised you didn't know that.
Contact.
Ready for the sitrep.
Send it twice, just to make sure.
Here are the names of those
to be arrested and sent to detention.
I...
- I know some of these people.
- I'm sure you do.
They're all insurgents, Jammer.
We have to break the cycle of violence.
Ok, suit up.
You won't have to wear
those much longer, eventually
your people
will see you as heroes.
Not tonight.
Take numbers five through ten.
Okay, take the tents to the right.
Follow down the end.
Rest of you guys gotta keep quiet, okay ?
This is New Caprica police.
You're under arrest for colluding
with the insurgency.
You're wanting for questioning
in the graduation bomb.
Cally Tyrol, this is an NCP raid.
No ! Let go of me !
Get your hands up.
My baby ! No !
No, my baby !
No !
No, no, no, no.
I got you. I got you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, there you go.
Mommy's coming back.
It's okay. It's okay.
Their numbers are a little thin.
It says here Tigh commands
1 150 armed effectives.
That's a lot less than he should have
if you count all former fleet officers
and enlisted available down there.
Could be taking heavy losses.
They mentioned a cylon crackdown.
We should get a breakdown
of available pilots in the insurgent group.
Somebody's gotta
fly those ships if we're gonna pull this off.
Those ships aren't going anywhere yet.
"The cylons have removed launch keys from
grounded colonial ships. Location unknown."
- Came from Tyrol.
- Can we manufacture new launch keys ?
Forget it.
The specs on launch keys
are incredibly sophisticated.
It would take weeks just to do the R&D.
Best option is for Saul
and the people on the ground
to find the original launch keys.
Assuming they weren't destroyed.
No. No way.
The cylons would want to keep them safe
just in case they needed
to use one of those ships someday.
She's right.
Keys gotta still be there somewhere.
We can make a weapons drop
to the insurgents.
They know the lay of the land. They've been
hitting the cylons in the teeth for months.
Give them the tools,
they can find the keys themselves.
No. No way.
The only thing
you've got going for you so far
is that the cylon reduced their
defense perimeter to just 5 baseships.
You put heavy weaponry, they'll know
that we're in contact with the population.
Call in ten more baseships
and then your whole plan's fraked.
Funny. Thought this was our plan, sir.
Moving on.
The military plans that you have in your
hands are to be kept with you at all times.
Why'd they pick her up ?
She hasn't done anything.
We've got a baby, for gods' sakes.
- I don't know. I'll try to find out.
- How long are they gonna hold her ?
Detention is run by a separate ministry.
They don't give us any reasons why they...
Godsdamn it, Felix !
She hasn't done anything. We've got a baby.
I know, Galen.
I'm sorry.
How do you do it ?
How do you help them day after day ?
How do you look yourself in the mirror ?
I gotta get my son.
Cameron's watching him,
but she's got problems of her own.
Chief !
I'll see what I can do. I'll see
if there's something I can find out.
Why don't you try and do something ?
Please ! No ! No !
Hey, you okay ?
Jammer, what's going on ?
Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm okay, Chief.
- All right.
I heard about last night.
- What ?
- About Cally being on one of those lists.
Yeah.
- I'm really sorry
- Yeah.
Frakking human police, huh ?
Bunch of traitors if you ask me.
Some of those guys who joined up,
I bet they're in over their heads, you know ?
Especially now with
these suicide bombings and...
at first, I bet you they thought
they were doing something good.
Get the Cylons off the streets, let us...
- police our own.
- They're frakking idiots.
What did they expect ?
You don't know
any of those guys, do you ? Any names ?
Names ? No.
No idea.
- Damn.
- Well,
what's up with Cally ?
Why did they put her in detention ?
I don't know.
She hasn't done a gods damn thing.
I just talked to Gaeta.
Says he doesn't know squat.
Or so he says.
- Gaeta's a good guy. If he knows something
- He's a frakking collaborator.
You know what ?
One day when this is all over,
guys like Gaeta are gonna get strung up.
And guys like you and me,
we're gonna be there tying the knots.
Making them tight.
It's been a couple of ugly days.
I know you don't care about that, but...
life means something to us, so
I've decided to show you
just how precious life can be.
How even in the worst of times
it can restore your faith.
Remember that breeding farm on Caprica ?
I remember I blew the frak out of the place.
It wasn't a total loss.
We were able to salvage certain things.
Certain medical samples.
Like your ovary.
What's that ?
This is Kacey.
Kacey, this is Kara.
Your mother.
Hi.
Good girl.
Unbelievable.
What ?
Admiral's decided to put
some boots on the ground.
Wants to send an officer as a liaison
between us and the resistance elements
on the planet to coordinate the rescue op.
- Makes sense. What's the problem ?
- It's who he's sending.
- He's frakking kidding with this, right ?
- I wish he were.
Mr. Hoshi,
I want a Raptor prepped and
ready in five minutes on the hangar deck.
Inform the flagship I'm coming aboard.
I want a private meeting with the Admiral.
What are you gonna do ?
What I should have done a long time ago.
You can't do this. She's a cylon
- Well, I trust her.
- Well, that's a mistake.
Well, it'll be my mistake, won't it ?
You are gambling
with the lives of everyone on this ship.
And everyone on my ship.
I don't need a lecture from you
about the responsibilities of command.
We're done here.
I'm not finished.
This entire plan is a reckless gamble.
Yes, you certainly
have the right to risk the lives
of the men and women
under your command but
that's not the issue. The issue is that you
are risking the lives of the entire human race.
I'm trying to save the human race.
No. No, you're not. That's what you're
not seeing. Right now, the human race ?
Well, that's the 2 000 people
huddled in those civilian ships
that managed to get away
when the Cylons came back.
They're the safe bet.
They're the ones whose survival
we should guard.
Just like we did after
the attack on the Colonies.
Sharon can penetrate the cylon defenses.
- It's not about her.
- The centurions can't distinguish her
from the other humanoid models.
Did you know that ?
- Admiral.
- They were deliberately programmed that way.
The Cylons
didn't want them becoming self-aware
and suddenly resisting orders.
They didn't want their own
robotic rebellion on their hands.
Should appreciate the irony.
- Dad.
- I know what you're saying.
But we have a responsibility
to the people that we left behind.
Remember what Roslin said.
Our first responsibility is
to the survival of humanity.
We can't lose sight of that.
Over the last year, we've...
lost sight
of almost everything.
We got...
soft.
But if we go back to New Caprica now,
and we lose,
it's over.
Humanity just stops.
And admiral stars don't give you
the right to make that gamble.
You're right, son.
You should make plans
to resume the search for Earth
with the Pegasus and the civilian fleet.
- With Pegasus ? What about Galactica ?
- I know why we left those people behind.
And I know it was their choice
in the first place to be down there.
And I realize,
that the survival of the human race
outweighs anything else.
But this time...
I can't live with it.
Can't face it.
Maybe I'm a coward.
- But I'm going back.
- Dad, you won't have a chance.
I'm going back, son.
Once I fertilized your egg,
we transferred it to a human woman
who carried it to term.
She is pretty, funny.
Great smile.
You would've liked her.
Although her birth mother
died during childbirth,
Kacey's heart never faltered.
I guess she gets that will to live from you.
I've seen her path.
It's difficult,
but rewarding.
She'll know the mind of God in this lifetime.
She'll see patterns that others do not see.
She probably got such
spiritual clarity from me.
She'll be hungry soon.
There's food on the table.
You wouldn't let
your own child starve, would you ?
It's not my child.
- I don't even know if it's human.
- Half-human.
And you know that she's yours.
You just won't admit it.
Where the frak you going ?
Take this with you.
Don't leave me alone with this.
Frak.
I don't know who or what you are,
but I do know this.
I'm not your mother.
I don't care that it's effective.
I don't care
that the Cylons can't stop it.
It's wrong.
No more suicide bombings, Colonel.
- You understand ?
- What, are you working for the cylons now ?
I'm sorry.
There's no excuse for that.
You see,
little things like that,
they don't matter anymore.
In fact, not too frakking
much really matters anymore.
I've got one job here, Lady,
and one job only.
To disrupt the Cylons.
Make them worry about the anthill
they've stirred up down here
so they're distracted and out of position
when the old man shows up in orbit.
The bombings ?
They got the cylons' attention.
They really got their attention,
and I am not giving that up.
We are talking about
people blowing themselves up.
You know,
sometimes I think that you've got
ice water in those veins,
and other times I think
you're just a naive little schoolteacher.
I've sent men
on suicide missions in two wars now
and let me tell you something.
It don't make a godsdamn
bit of difference
whether they're riding in a Viper
or walking out onto a parade ground.
In the end, they're just as dead.
So take your piety and
your moralizing and
your high-minded principles
and stick'em someplace safe
until you're off this rock
and you're sitting
in your nice cushy chair on Colonial One again.
I've got a war to fight.
Let's go move in !
This way !
Off road, the rest.
Let's go to isolation. Move !
The detentions are just causing
more resentment and more enemies.
We're losing ground with the people.
- I know.
- We don't have another option.
We have to send the message
that suicide bombings won't be tolerated.
Excuse me, sir.
Can I talk to you for a moment ?
Yeah, sure, Jammer.
I'll catch up with you.
Sir, I don't know exactly how to broach this.
Nor do I know exactly what
I expect you to do about it.
But, I thought, you know,
since we were
anyway, since we were
back on the Galactica...
Yeah, Jammer, just spit it out.
We picked up
Chief Tyrol's wife in the last raid, Cally.
She's in detention.
I think she's on a list.
Frak !
Kacey ?
Kara ?
Hi, Cally. It's me, Boomer.
I wish I had a gun.
Are you all right ?
Physically, I mean.
What do you want from me ?
Look,
a lot's happened,
in everyone's life.
But I want you to know,
I want you and Galen to know
that I'm happy for you.
Especially since you started a family.
Something that him and I
talked about once before.
Can you get me out of here ?
I don't know. I have nothing
to do with internal security
Then frak you, Sharon,
you stupid fraked-up toaster.
How many times
do I have to shoot you, anyway ?
If you can't help me,
then just go away
and leave us alone !
All human personnel,
prepare to present identification
before passing through
security scanners.
Have your IDs out.
Keep coming.
Everyone have their work IDs ready.
Work IDs out.
Hey you !
Open your bag.
Stop her !
23 cylons critically wounded.
14 had to be euthanized.
They had casualties too.
Four human dead.
Who gives a frak about that ?
Pardon my language.
The power substation was crippled.
Almost half the city's without power, and our
best estimates put the repairs at two weeks.
Do you still think we're being too hard
on the human population ?
We have a very serious,
very straightforward problem.
Either we increase control
or we lose control.
That's a fact.
We think it's time
for stronger measures.
We agree.
We agree as well.
How about you ?
We agree also.
Most of us do, anyway.
Enough.
What's this ?
This orders the summary executions of
all the detainees listed on the next page.
- It requires your signature.
- My signature ?
You're the President.
Read it later. Sign now.
Just because you've
decided to do this
doesn't mean you need to
drag him into sin with you.
Don't you lecture me about sin.
I'm not the one who committed the first act
of cylon on cylon violence in our history.
What's she talking about ?
She crushed my head in
with a rock back on Caprica.
Interesting she didn't tell you.
It's something I had to do.
I'm not proud of it.
This is all very interesting.
Very edifying.
Sign the order.
- You don't need my signature.
- Well, actually, we do.
We're here as allies and friends
of the legitimate government of the Colonies.
You're the President, so everything
we do requires your signature.
In other words they're worried about what
"God" might think if they commit murder.
They're covering
their existential asses.
I won't do it.
All right, I won't do it.
You're going to have
to salve your consciences some other way.
Then we'll find another president.
Stop this.
This is crazy !
- Dear god.
- She'll be back.
But if he pulls that trigger now, you won't.
Sign it.
Sign it !
Sign your name !
there's nothing
you can do, gaius.
- Sign you name on that paper !
- It will be okay.
It's you.
Help me.
You have to sign it.
They'll kill you if you don't.
Sign it ! Sign ! Sign !
Sign your name ! Sign it !
I can't.
I won't.
You can't force...
sometimes you have to do things you hate
so you can survive to fight another day.
Raise your right hand and repeat after me.
I, Sharon Agathon...
do now pledge my faith and my loyalty...
to the protection
of the 12 Colonies of Kobol.
and will carry out
the lawful orders of my superiors...
- as an officer...
in the colonial fleet.
Congratulations, Lieutenant.
Never thought I'd live to see the day.
Me neither.
Looks good on you.
Belongs on you.
You know what this means to me.
One of the first things
they taught us at the Academy
was that symbols matter.
Uniforms, flags, banners,
even mascots.
They're like pieces of
your heart you can look at.
This uniform...
it means a lot to me, Sharon.
I know it does, Helo.
It means a lot to me, too.
I won't betray it.
We're checks-out, Lieutenant.
Thanks.
Can I ask you a question ?
How do you know ? How do you
really know that you can trust me ?
I don't.
That's what trust is.
Good hunting, Lieutenant.
That was really something.
Thought you might like that.
But you didn't do the twist this time.
What do you call, that deal you did
right at the end ? What do you call that ?
You mean the swirl.
The swirl...
Boy, that's really something.
Well, you said
you wanted something memorable.
How is Saul ?
Fine.
And when's his next meeting
with the insurgents ?
No point in denying it, Ellen.
We know he's their leader.
Why do you think
we let him out of detention ?
I thought it was because of the twist.
Well, yes, that too, for sure.
But having the Colonel out
and active with the resistance
presents us with certain advantages.
I don't know anything about...
Let's just consider your denials as read,
shall we ?
I want a specific place,
I want a specific time
for a very high level meeting
of the insurgency leadership.
And if I don't get it,
we pick up Saul again.
And this time,
he'll lose more than an eye.
Tomorrow, the Galactica is going to send
two Raptors, several marines,
and a ground liaison officer
is gonna brief us on the rescue mission
and help coordinate our evac plans.
I'll be damned. It's really happening.
Who's the liaison officer ?
- Sharon.
- I hope that's your idea of a joke.
Admiral Adama
has given her a uniform and a billet.
She is a serving officer.
Which is more than you can say about us,
technically speaking.
The old man's lost his mind, all right.
- Where's the rendez-vous ?
- They left that up to us.
Okay, here's my suggestion.
If they jump into Breeder's canyon
out here in the southern range...
Come.
- Hi, guys.
- Hey.
Ellen.
Anyway, like I was saying,
if they jump in here
- they won't get picked up on Cylon Dradis.
- That's a long way out there.
A lot of ground to cover by foot.
I realize that. I'm gonna
meet them halfway. Right about here.
There's good cover from the air.
It's pretty isolated.
Gotta be sure. Maybe the most
important meeting we're ever gonna have.
Colonel, I'm sure. This is the place.
The Cylons will not find them here.
All right, give me the map.
You got the message memorized ?
All the wireless freqs ?
All right, then give me the message, too.
I'll do that, Saul. Don't get up.
Thanks.
Colonel, I've assembled a team
of about six to eight men and women
about half a dozen times. We have provisions
for a couple of days if we need'em.
We have access to running water.
I know that place
like the back of my hand. This is gonna work.
Gaius ! Gaius !
Did you sign this ?
- Tell me you didn't sign this.
- Not now, mr. Gaeta. I'm very tired.
This is a death warrant.
Have you seen the names on this list ?
Do you have any idea
what they're about to do out there ?
Are you listening to me ?
I didn't have any choice.
What the hell's the matter with you ?
There are over 200 names on this list.
Have you even looked at the names ?
- Look at the names, Gaius !
- I've seen them !
I've seen them, all right ?
And there was nothing I could do.
Back to your frakking tents.
Everybody back to your tents.
Move, move, move !
And you do triple digits.
You can do that. Let me see...
Laura Roslin ?
Come with us, please.
Killing Tyrol's wife
will only embitter him against us.
He's the head of a labor union.
Let's just be honest
with one another. In your view,
you don't think there's
any reason to kill any of them ?
- Right.
- Well, we made a decision.
All of us.
Like when we listened to you
and Caprica 6 when we came here
to start this new and glorious
chapter in cylon-human relations.
This has nothing to do
with whether or not we execute Cally.
No one enjoys the thought
of mortal death, Boomer.
But she tried to murder you.
Maybe it's God's justice.
Need a lift, mr. Vice president ?
Guess so.
Haven't seen much of you lately.
Been busy these days ?
Well, not much to do in detention.
How long have you been held ?
Four months, I think.
I told Baltar I wouldn't have
any part of collaborating with the Cylons.
And he got a little pissed.
He's a little pissed at me, too.
Jump complete. Right on target.
Okay, hang on, guys.
I'm dropping down to the landing point
and there's some heavy turbulence up ahead.
Follow the river.
Make sure you hug the bank.
Okay, once we reach the rendez-vous point,
stay back and provide cover.
Go, panthers !
C-bucks rule !
Hey, Sam. Been a long time.
Funny. I feel like I see you every day.
Come on.
Lords...
Please don't take her life.
It was my mistake. Don't punish her for it.
It was an accident, Kara. Nothing more.
Kacey ?
Kacey, oh, my Gods.
Honey.
Let them stretch their legs for a minute.
Yes, sir.
Let's go. All right, everybody out !
Five minute rest break ! Come on, move !
Everybody out ! Five minute rest break !
Come on, 5 minutes ! Everyone out, let's go !
Tell me something, Laura.
Last year ?
You tried to steal the election, didn't you ?
Yes, I did, Tom.
- I wish you'd gone through with it.
- Me too.
We'll wait until nightfall
before we go back to the city.
There's a system of tunnels
we've been using...
Did you hear that ?
Get down !
Move ! Take cover !
Go !
You. Over here.
Run. Run.
Don't look back. Go !
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
We thank you to watch
Battlestar Galactica with our subtitles