Previously on
Battlestar Galactica
I have a message for you.
"The fruit born of two peoples
is alive."
A child named after
the wife and sister
of the all-knowing Zeus.
Hera... lives.
It's not true.
I don't suppose you will
tell me what this is all about.
I mean,
what's so important about this kid ?
She may very well be
"the shape of things to come".
The Cylons knew exactly
where we were gonna be.
- That doesn't mean Ellen...
- This is the map !
The map that I drew for you.
I gave this to you in your tent.
You were gonna burn it but
your wife offered to do it.
But she didn't, did she ?
I...
I want to explain.
He said he'd kill you.
- Who said ?
- One of the brother Cavils.
This is Kacey.
Kacey,
this is Kara...
your mother.
Our people
are gonna attack the air base,
detention center, power station
and other critical facilities.
The plan is to sow as much
chaos and confusion as possible
the moment
Galactica and Pegasus arrive.
No pegasus. Just galactica.
These are your orders.
Take the civilian fleet
and wait for me for 18 hours.
If I'm not back in 18 hours,
then find Earth.
You know the mission.
You should also know there's
only one way that this mission ends,
and that's with
the successful rescue of our people
off of New Caprica.
Good hunting.
Hoshi's working on updating our map
coordinates for the search for Earth.
Civilian captains want to meet with you.
They have questions...
... problems.
Talk to me, Lee.
I'm having trouble...
- ... accepting this.
- I know.
But we have to push forward.
Keep the fleet together.
Find Earth.
Right, that's our duty.
There's still
a chance they'll come back.
Your father has pulled off
more than a few miracles in his day.
I know that.
And I haven't given up hope.
Yes, you have.
I saw the look on your face
when you came back from Galactica.
Like you were never
gonna see him again.
Am I that easy to read ?
Just to me.
He's taking on too much
for one half-strength
Battlestar to handle.
And that's not opinion.
That's military fact.
He's not coming back from this,
none of them are.
All we can do
is make plans for the future.
We have to survive.
We have to find Earth.
If we don't, they'll be no one to
remember a man named William Adama.
Or a Battlestar named Galactica.
That is our charge to keep.
To keep humanity going.
No matter what the cost.
No matter...
- no matter who we leave behind.
- You can do this.
You can get us there.
You are Commander of this fleet,
and you will guide us to safety.
And you will do it no matter the cost.
Because you're an Adama.
Did I ever tell you
how proud I am to serve with you ?
Not in so many words, no.
Well, I am proud
to serve with you, Lieutenant.
And to call you my wife.
Now let's talk about...
map coordinates,
meeting with ships' captains.
I lost three men today
and if that sergeant wasn't
on her game, they'd have killed us all.
I know, godsdamn it. You don't have
to keep running your mouth about it.
- I get it, all right ?
- You get this.
If Sharon had been killed, not only
would we not get the launch keys,
but the Cylons would know that we were
in direct contact with Galactica.
Now this whole plan,
the fate of this whole city,
would have fallen apart.
Do you understand that, Colonel ?
I get it.
Good.
You know what has to be done here.
If you don't want to do it,
I understand.
But believe me, Colonel,
someone is gonna do this.
Now, it would be better
for her sake if it was you.
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
presents
Battlestar Galactica
Season 3 - Episode 4
" EXODUS "
part. 2
- =( www.seriestele.net )= -
Transcript
- =( www.sadgeezer.com )= -
Synchro : Dapitch666,
Goufrach, Lovechange, NikoMagnus
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
I had to do it, Saul.
I had to.
It was all for you.
And I want you to know
that I would have done
anything to save you.
I know, I know. It's all right.
- Everything's gonna be all right.
- No, you don't understand.
I got you out of detention, Saul.
It was me.
I got you out.
I went to see them,
the Cylons.
Finally got to the one in charge.
And I got him to notice me
the way men notice me.
I slept with him.
And I felt like puking every time
he put his filthy hands on me.
But I smiled
and I faked it
to save you, Saul.
But you listen to me.
I'd do it again.
Frak anybody, do anything.
Even gave 'em the map.
I didn't want anybody...
... to be killed.
I could use a drink.
You've always been there
for me when I needed you.
I'm exhausted.
I feel like I could just curl up here.
Should have listened to you, Saul.
Should have stayed on Galactica.
Don't worry about any of that now.
You just...
- ... you just go to sleep.
- I'm sleepy.
I love you,
Do you hear me ?
I mean, I told you and I told you.
But to what end ?
Too secure in your smug
superiority to listen.
Too comfortable
in your predictions of success to
even consider
the possibility of defeat.
And where are we now ?
And more to the point,
where's Laura Roslin ?
Where's Tom Zarek ?
At large.
Whereabouts unknown.
Free at any rate.
Probably with Colonel Tigh.
Solidifying the insurgency's
hold over the public's imagination.
What would you have us do, Gaius ?
Leave.
Pack up your Centurions
and go.
Please, go.
And then what ?
What would you do if we
really just left you here ?
You'd live out your lives
in peace and never trouble
yourselves with thoughts of us again ?
Or would you raise your children
with stories of the Cylon ?
The mechanical slaves who once did
your bidding only to turn against you.
Killers who committed genocide
against your race.
And occupiers of this city
until we just ran away.
Would you tell them to tell
the story to their children ?
And to their children's children ?
And nurse a dream of vengeance
down through the years
so that one day
they could just go out
into the stars and hunt
the Cylon once more.
Blood for blood.
It has to stop one day.
Oh, my Gods.
Nice job, Anders.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Okay, that's our cue.
You know what to do.
Rally your people and get them
to the evac points.
Okay, remember the drills,
and you'll do fine.
Go with the Gods. Go, go, go !
Tory, would you tell Laura
- I can't thank her enough...
- Tell her yourself when it's all over.
Wish we were all as calm as she is.
- Get them to their ship. Go, go !
- Yes, Ma'am.
Let's move, let's move,
All right, this is it.
We get to the detention center
and we do not stop
until everybody is out of there free.
Everybody knows their entry points.
Let's load up and we move right now.
Let's move, Connor.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Decoy squadron approaching
launch point.
Okay, this is it guys. Stand by.
All Vipers break...
... now, now, now !
Deploy drones on my mark.
Three, Two, One...
Mark.
Drone signatures match.
Cylons should pick up
the drones on Dradis
and read them
as two Battlestars any minute.
Transport all the prisonners...
What ? No, no, no.
Immediate evac from sector V as in...
V as in Victor.
I could use the Centurions warriors.
For nothing.
All for nothing.
We'll start over, Gaius.
- A new city to rise out of the ashes.
- No.
It'll be buried.
Buried like the cities of old.
Consumed by the wrath of God.
Two Battlestars just jumped into orbit.
Adama's back.
Kat, Racetrack.
Two Baseships on Dradis
bearing 0-0-2 carom 0-1-5.
They're launching Raiders.
Red squadron, Kat.
We've done our part.
Kick in the Turbos.
Let's get the hell out of here.
What's going on ?
Insurgents. I'll be back.
You can not leave us trapped in here.
- It's safest for you here.
- No !
Let's go, let's go.
Move, move !
Run !
Tom, you go that way.
Head to the shipyard.
- You're coming, right ?
- My ship's up there.
You have a sense of the dramatic.
Hey, wait, Laura.
Wait, wait.
- You were on Galactica ?
- I didn't do anything.
No, it's okay.
Keep an eye on her, all right ?
Don't let her
out of your sight, go !
- See you up there.
Jump preparation complete.
My board is green.
Ready to jump, sir.
Stand by to launch blue squadron.
This is the Admiral.
All hands,
brace for turbulence.
Baseships just closed
on the Battlestar targets.
There's no Galactica, no Pegasus.
Drones.
Decoys.
The whole thing's a trick.
Where's Galactica ?
Altitude 99,000,
falling like a rock.
Launch !
Launch them all !
Stand by FTL.
Clear for launch.
Well, this ought to be different.
- They're clear.
- Stand by.
Jump !
Vipers !
Everybody hold, hold !
Hotdog, redwing.
I see friendlies pinned down
outside the shipyard gate.
Roger. Redwing, target the guard tower.
I've got the gate.
Rolling in hot.
Incoming !
That's it ! Let's go !
Let's go ! Go ! Go !
Move ! Go !
Move !
Godsdamn it.
Come on, move !
Move, move !
Let's go !
Move, people, come on !
- Come on, move !
- Hurry up !
Fire in the hole !
All right, everybody,
let's move !
Head north to the shipyard, now.
Move !
Hustle !
Kara ?
Oh, Gods, no.
No. No !
I'm gonna get you out of here.
All divisions make
damage report to combat.
- Main batteries report weapons status.
- Dradis.
Back on line.
Cylon Baseships
coming out of the nebula.
Just as we expected.
Cylon Raiders are still
scattered to hell and gone.
They're coming after us
without fighter cover.
If we can draw the two
basestars away from the planet,
the colonists might be
able to escape.
Hang on.
Two more Baseships
just jumped into orbit.
- We've got four Baseships out there.
- No.
We can't hold off four.
Pass up the cord.
Hold still.
Connect the other side right away.
We've lost maneuvering thrusters.
We can't take any more hits to port or
we're looking at explosive
decompressions
- in sections 36 through 48.
- Jump drives.
Then that's it.
It's been an honor.
Galactica, Pegasus.
Let us take some
of this work off your hands.
Get your FTL up and ready,
and we'll take care of the rest.
- All right, fire up that main battery !
- Copy that, Sir.
Damn you, Lee.
Keep working on those FTLs.
Get 'em online.
Yes, sir.
The Cylons will re-deploy
as soon as they recover.
Thank you, Lee.
They're coming about.
Maneuvering to bracket us.
Steady as she goes.
Take us right into the center.
Won't last long in there.
No.
Put me down ! Wait !
Stop ! Put me down !
- Is it really you ?
- Baby, it's really me. But listen,
we don't have time.
We're going to the ships,
and we're gonna get the hell off
- this frakkin' planet.
- Okay.
- Where's Kacey ?
- Who's Kacey ?
- Kacey, she's my daughter.
- Kara, who's Kacey ?
- She's my daughter !
- Kara ! Kara, no ! Kara !
Godsdamnit, Kara, no !
Out of the way !
We've lost control
of the situation on the surface.
There's a heavy raider
standing by ready to evacuate us.
We're agreed.
Evacuate the entire facility.
I'll stay behind and set off the nuke.
You should go as well, Caprica.
And you.
I don't think you'll want
to be here after we've gone.
There's a place for you, too.
For me ?
Well, you were right and we were wrong.
Should be some reward for that.
Gaius, we should go.
I just want to sit here and die.
You're gonna get your wish, Gaius.
The ships are getting off the ground.
Jumping away. Only a few left.
FTL's back online.
Pegasus is taking
a hell of a pounding, Sir.
I don't think she has
a single plane in the air.
Lee left all of his planes
to guard the civilian ships.
He knew that was a one-way trip.
He'll evac before the end.
- You sure ?
- Land our birds !
Let's get the hell out of here.
All wings, Galactica. Come on home.
Combat landings authorized.
Repeat, come on home.
All hands, all hands, get ready to jump.
I believed in you.
Whoa, whoa. Gaeta.
I believed in the dream of New Caprica.
- Gaeta, we all did.
- No !
No.
Not him. He believed in
the dream of Gaius Baltar.
The good life. Booze, pills,
hot and cold running interns.
He lead us to the apocalypse, and...
and I...
- I turned out to be...
- ... an idealist.
There's no sin in that.
Everything you say about me is true.
Every word.
But you have to listen to me.
The Cylons have a nuke in this complex.
Nobody,
and I mean nobody is getting off
this planet alive unless I stop that.
- Gaius, she'll kill you.
- Then she'll kill me.
Or it'll be down to Mr. Gaeta.
Either way,
the human race dies with me.
Gaius, he...
Go ahead, shoot.
What are you waiting for ?
Please.
I'm begging you, please...
You have one chance to put things right.
Do you understand me ?
Get the frak out of here !
Stop that nuke ! Go !
Gaius, let's go !
Set main batteries to autofire cycle-B.
Lock engines ahead flank.
This is the Commander.
Abandon ship, abandon ship.
All hands, abandon ship.
Report to evac Raptors
and jump to rendezvous point.
Good work,
and I'll see you on the other side.
Okay, all right, people,
let's move ! Out !
Let's go !
You too, Commander.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Kacey ?
Kacey !
Kacey, honey, where are you ?
Ka...
I knew you'd be back. I saw it.
Give me Kacey.
Say the words.
- Let me take her.
- Say them.
- What words ?
- You know what I want.
I want to hear you say them.
And I want the rest of it.
Just like I told you.
Fine.
You win.
I love you.
Say it again.
Now the rest.
Was it everything
you thought it would be ?
That and more.
I'll never forget this moment.
Neither will I.
I'll explain later. Let's move.
- Are you sure she's in there ?
- Positive, I saw her go in.
Frakking liar.
It's her, Gaius.
The first of God's new generation.
Hera.
It's a miracle.
God spared her.
Hera.
Can I hold her ?
No.
She won't set off the nuke, not anymore.
Come on, Gaius, we have to go.
All right.
I'm ready to go.
All right, people, let's go. This way.
Stay on the starboard hangar deck
'till we can get you to the new ships.
Come on, people, all the way down.
All the way down, people, let's go.
Oh, my Gods.
Captain ?
- I thought you were dead.
- Yeah,
so did I.
Who's this ?
Yeah, I was gonna ask that myself.
- This is...
- Kacey ?
Kacey !
Oh, my little girl !
Mommy missed you so much !
Thank you.
Thank you !
When the Cylons took her, I thought...
but you saved her.
The Gods bless you.
Hey.
Thank you, sir.
Welcome aboard. Welcome.
Welcome aboard.
I guess you didn't
understand my orders ?
Never could read your handwriting.
Permission to come aboard, sir.
Hey.
Permission granted.
You did it.
Your brought 'em home, Saul.
Not all of them.
I'm sorry.
We're still double-checking
the fleet's manifests but...
it doesn't look like Maya
made it off of New Caprica.
What about the baby ?
I was there when the two guards
left to take them to their ship.
I don't know what happened.
I'm so sorry,
I let you down and I know that.
No, you didn't.
It's not your fault.
This is bigger than us.
This is life.
All hands, proceed to your support
teams. Stand by for ships assignments.
Thanks to watch Battlestar Galactica
with our subs.