Previously on Battlestar Galactica...
I can't figure it. All those weeks in
detention and suddenly, they let me out.
I want a specific place,
I want a specific time
for a very high-level meeting
of the insurgency leadership.
And if I don't get it,
we pick up Saul again.
And this time,
he'll lose more than an eye.
The child's life
must be protected at all costs.
The first cylon-human hybrid.
It truly is a miracle from God.
We lost her. We did the best we could,
but she's dead.
And that's all there is to it.
She's so beautiful.
You understand, Maya, that
this adoption requires absolute secrecy.
You have my word.
There's a Raptor out there every day,
listening for a wireless call.
And it's out there because the old man
isn't just gonna leave us to the Cylons.
Will make contact
this frequency every 12 hours.
Have hope. We're coming for you.
Cylons have removed launch keys
from grounded colonial ships.
Location : Unknown.
Best option is for Saul
and the people on the ground
getting their hands
on the original launch keys.
Admiral's decided
to put some boots on the ground.
Wants to send
an officer as a liaison between us
and the resistance elements on
the planet to coordinate the rescue op.
- Makes sense. What's the problem ?
- It's who he's sending.
This entire plan is a reckless gamble.
You are risking
the lives of the entire human race.
You should make plans
to resume the search for Earth
with the Pegasus and the civilian fleet.
But I'm going back.
We round up the leaders of the
insurgency and we execute them publicly.
We round up at random groups off
the street and we execute them publicly.
Send a message
that the gloves are coming off.
The insurgency stops now
or else we start
reducing the human population
to a more manageable size.
Let them
stretch their legs for a minute.
All right. Everybody out !
Five-minute rest break. Come on, move !
You. Over here.
Run.
Run ! Don't look back. Go !
Can I help you ?
- Here we go.
- Thanks.
- Sorry.
- That's all right, it doesn't hurt.
I appreciate you doing this. I can't
seem to get it right in the mirror.
Saul.
I want you to know
that I would do anything for you.
Yeah.
The list, Cally's on the list.
- They're gonna kill her.
- What list ?
- What are you talking about ?
- I got this.
I got this from the dead-drop.
From the source in the administration.
It's a death list
and Cally's name is on it.
They're rounding up people in the city.
Cally's in detention. They could
take her out at any minute...
They got this
organized by transport vehicles.
Cally's in the group heading
for map coordinate x-ray seven.
I know, but where the frak is that ?
- I mean, how are we gonna...
- Calm down, damnit.
You gotta start thinking
clearly here, Chief, or she's dead.
Now we've already figured out
their map coordinate system.
It's referred to in the list of cylon
freqs you got from the last dead-drop.
Holy frak ! You're right.
- I can extrapolate the coordinates...
- Cally's group has to pick up
a bunch of people in town first.
That'll take time.
Take four men and get out there
ahead of the trucks.
Chief !
Pull it together. You won't do her
any good if you get caught too.
Besides,
the last thing your son wants
is me and Ellen for parents.
Find that list, Chief.
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
presents
Battlestar Galactica
Season 3 - Episode 3
" EXODUS "
part. 1
- =( www.seriestele.net )= -
Transcript :
- =( www.sadgeezer.com )= -
Synchro : Aspirant Nemo, Dapitch666,
Kha-nabis, Lovechange, NikoMagnus
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -
Where the frak is it ?
Come on...
Damnit ! Gods damnit !
Where's that frakkin' list ?
It's gotta be here.
Frak ! Come on !
Here it is. Okay.
X-ray seven. 1, 4, 3...
Hey, Chief.
Good day for a walk, huh ?
Get your men together.
We're going to Pergamus' flats.
- Talk to me, Gunny.
- Don't like it, Lt.
Too much cover along this trail.
We could catch
enfilade fire from there,
there, and along there.
Let's move out.
I'm going to the rendezvous point.
Place your men on the ridge for cover.
Go panthers !
C-bucks rule !
Hey, Sam. It's been a while.
Funny, I feel like I see you every day.
Come on.
There's trucks.
Move down to the ridge.
Crispin, you here.
This is it, lock and load.
All right. What do we see ?
Oh, frak me.
- What ?
- They got Laura Roslin
and Tom Zarek with them.
Is there any sign of Cally ?
Not yet.
So Galactica's got a rescue plan
in place and ready to go.
My job's to get the launch keys
for the ships still on the ground,
then coordinate the rescue mission
with your evacuation plan.
When can we meet with Colonel Tigh ?
We're gonna wait until nightfall
before we head back into the city.
There she is.
Oh, my Gods, there she is.
What the frak's she doing ?
She's making a run for it.
The bullet heads are lining up.
It's a firing squad.
Sight in on the Centurions right now !
Cally's right in our line of fire.
If we shoot, we're gonna hit her.
Count to five. Open fire.
Two skinjobs, should we take 'em down ?
Where there are skinjobs, there are
bullet heads, bring up the RPG.
There's a system of tunnels we've been
using that run parallel and under...
Do you hear that ?
Go ! Go ! Go !
Get back !
Get down !
Go ! Go ! Go !
Thousand one...
Thousand two...
Thousand three...
Thousand four...
Thousand five.
Frak this, we gotta get out of here.
Stay put. Trust me.
Now !
Thanks.
They were waiting for us, Lt.
Right where we thought.
Sir,
you better take a look at this.
I found it on a dead skinjob.
It's your handwriting, isn't it ?
Yeah, damn right it is.
We were sold out.
Ellen.
Check them up, make sure they're okay.
- You all right, Tom ?
- Yeah.
Been a while since I had a woman
throw me to the ground.
Not quite as much fun as I remember.
Hurts, huh ? Good.
Then I hope it hurts a long,
long time till you go to Download City.
You're all right down there ?
Oh, my Gods.
It's good to see you, Chief.
Good to see you too, ma'am.
What happens now ?
Where do we go from here ?
We're going home.
Admiral Adama's on his way.
We're getting off this rock.
We're going back to Galactica.
Don't worry about it, Gaius.
It's all right.
- It doesn't matter to me, really.
- You can stop that right now, okay ?
My ego's not so fragile as all that.
These things happen.
Or they don't happen.
So what should we talk about ?
Should we talk about your day ?
How was your day, darling ?
How was your day at the office ?
My office.
Any news ?
No ?
Well, let me tell you
about my day because
it was a hoot.
I had the most fascinating chat
with one of the Dorals.
He's got this theory
about sanitation being the key
to regaining human trust and confidence.
Something about...
toilet paper.
No, lack of toilet paper, that's it.
If people could only wipe
their bums properly,
there'd be
a measurable uptick in the polls.
Four months of this, Gaius.
Four months of watching you slip
further and further down into this
well of self-hatred and loathing.
Do you know what I've given up for you ?
Do you ?
Do you know what,
with the occupation and everything,
I can't really say I've given it
that much thought recently.
Don't go.
Please.
That doesn't look so bad.
There's something that
I wanted to say to you.
I'm sorry that I left you alone.
I didn't mean for you to get hurt.
I was upset with myself.
And not you, okay ?
Grown-ups
do stupid things sometimes.
We get caught up in our
own little world until
it's almost too late.
You have no idea
what I'm saying to you, do you ?
Okay.
Time to take a nap.
Don't be afraid.
I know who you are, what you are.
Poor thing.
You must be terrified.
Do you have any candy ?
Candy ?
No.
Chamalla's so bitter.
Zeus sees all.
Sees you, number three.
Sees your pain.
Your destiny.
All the Gods weep for you.
There is no Zeus.
No other god but God.
Well, you don't believe that anymore.
You don't know what you believe
and that is why you're here.
It's not true.
I don't even know why I'm here.
- That's the stupidest thing I ever did.
- It is your dream
that brings you to me.
How do you know about that ?
I have a message for you
from the one you worship.
He speaks through me to you
just as he speaks in your dreams.
The message is...
the fruit born of two peoples
is alive.
A child named after
the wife and sister
of the all-knowing Zeus.
Hera lives.
That's not true.
The child is dead.
You will hold her in your arms,
and you'll know for the first time
what it is to feel true love.
But you'll lose everything
you've done here.
Wish I had some chocolate caramels.
Let's move ! We got some people
waiting for their ride down there.
Will you quit looking at me like that ?
Like what ?
You know like what.
Like we're never
gonna see each other again.
We will.
It's a good plan, D.
Take care of the Admiral ?
Take care of his son.
All right people,
you know how this works :
Pegasus crew on the port side
of the line, Galactica on the right.
Their enemies will divide them.
Their colonies broken
in the fiery chasm of space.
Their shining days renounced
by a multitude of dark sacrifices.
Yet still they will remain
always together.
Always together.
That's the third time
you've taken a look at your watch.
Got dinner plans ?
No, I was just...
I was just thinking
Sharon's probably on the ground by now.
I know.
These are your orders.
You'll find the rendezvous point there.
Take the civilian fleet
and wait for me for 18 hours.
If I'm not back in 18 hours,
then find Earth.
Yeah, right.
I'll see you at the rendezvous point.
18 hours.
- Try not to be late.
- I'm getting old.
I'm a little slow. But I'll be there.
Gods, I wish I could
talk you out of this.
You can't. You tried.
- You know, dad...
- Don't.
Don't make me cry
in my own hangar deck.
I'll see you there.
Permission to leave
your ship, Admiral.
Permission granted, Commander.
Attention !
Commander of Pegasus,
departing.
18 hours.
Hey. Hey !
Hey, Jake.
Yeah, you don't care who I am, do ya ?
All God's creatures in your eyes.
Here ya go.
Can't sleep ?
Bad dreams.
Didn't know you people had dreams.
Sure.
Everybody dreams, Doc.
That human or cylon blood ?
Cylon.
One of the fives got pretty shot up
today by the insurgents.
He's gonna make it.
You could've let him suffer.
That's not what I do.
What about the baby ?
Sharon's baby, Hera.
When that child died on Galactica,
why'd you cremate the body ?
It's the first cylon-human hybrid,
and you threw it in the incinerator ?
It wasn't my decision.
That was the President's call.
I was just following orders.
That's a very funny thing.
'Cause this stuff all looks the same.
She said,
"I hope it hurts you for a long, long
time before you go to Download City."
And then they just left me there.
They left me in the hot sun
with a bullet in my guts.
What a noble race you are.
How long were you there
before you died ?
Hours.
Eventually, I managed to drag myself
over to some spent shell casings.
And I used one of those
to scratch open my carotid artery.
Skin is a lot tougher than you think.
Now that's...
three for me.
Three downloads.
The first one, I just got a headache.
But I could handle it.
Now it's worse and worse.
This time it was like a frakkin'
white hot poker through my skull.
Not worth it.
None of this is worth it.
He's right, you know.
It's not worth it.
Which is what I believe
I've been telling you all along.
- Caprica, can you please control him ?
- Why don't you just shoot me...
if that'll remedy the situation ?
- We need to crack down harder.
- How ?
Our resources are stretched
to the max already.
I don't need to listen to this anymore.
Consensus used to be so easy.
Now look what they've done to us.
Don't lose hope.
Worst comes to worst, we can always
nuke the city and be done with it.
Better leave those dog tags here.
They spot 'em, they'll know who you are.
No, you have no idea
how hard I worked for these.
So our best guess puts the launch keys
somewhere in the detention center.
Just keep to the main streets.
Everybody'll think you're just a regular
skinjob and they'll avoid you but
there's a lot of people out there
looking to gut an unwary cylon going
for a stroll, so don't let anybody get
close enough to stick a knife in you.
All right. Thanks for the concern. It
makes me feel all warm and fuzzy inside.
How are you gonna find
those launch keys ?
When I get inside and hook into the
data stream, it'll feed me the location.
Once I get the keys, you need
to distribute them to the pilots
- who can fly those ships out of here.
- We got pilots standing by.
Anders !
Yeah, come in.
My Gods ! What's she doing here ?
Get her down below and keep her there
until after the next briefing.
Wait a minute !
No, no. Wait, listen to me. Please.
- I can explain.
- I suggest you keep your mouth shut.
Where is my husband ?
I want to speak to my husband.
Connor, let's go, get her down.
Okay, I'm outta here.
- Wait, Sharon.
- Yeah.
Do me a favor.
Just keep an eye out for Starbuck.
I don't know if she's alive
or if she's dead but
it's been four months.
I'll do what I can.
Yeah.
You must keep the child
hidden at all costs.
We keep her on the move
along with other high-value targets.
She'll never stay in any one location
longer than two or three days.
Sam, I need you
to really hear me on this.
Really.
There is no one, no one
of higher value than Maya and her child.
We cannot let them fall
into Cylon hands.
I get it.
How far do you want me to go ?
I mean, if it looks like the cylons
are gonna capture them...
Don't let it get to that point.
That's all.
I don't suppose you're gonna
tell me what this is all about.
What's so important about this kid ?
She may very well be
the shape of things to come.
That's either a blessing or a curse.
We've stored arms and munitions
in key areas through the city.
I can supplement that
with mortars, RPGs,
even a few anti-aircraft
missiles aboard the Raptor.
Great.
When we give the signal,
our people are gonna attack the airbase,
the detention center, the power station,
other critical facilities.
The plan is to sow
as much chaos and confusion
as possible the moment
Galactica and Pegasus arrive.
- Should help cover the evacuation.
- No pegasus.
Just Galactica.
Why ? Why no Pegasus ?
- What happened ?
- Don't know, sir.
Way beyond my pay grade.
What about your evac plans ?
We've designated and
assigned 500 block captains
to cover each sector of the city.
Each block captain
is responsible for rallying
and guiding the people
in his or her sector
along their escape route
to their designated ship.
Don't suppose you've been
able to rehearse any of this.
We've had three full-dress
rehearsals under the guise
of fire and natural disaster drills.
Be different when the balloon goes up.
Explosions, shooting, chaos.
There's gonna be some panic out there.
They'll do fine.
These people know that at some point,
they're gonna be responsible
for saving themselves.
All we need to do
is be ready and hope for the best.
- What about Maya and Isis ?
- I'm on it.
I've got my two best shooters here.
They're gonna be their escorts
and make sure they get back to the ship.
Gentlemen, I can't tell you why,
but it is imperative
that this woman and her child...
... get off this planet.
I trust you because I trust him.
Yes, Ma'am.
Saul !
We need to talk.
Toaster !
- She sold us out.
- What are you talking about ?
We were ambushed
at the rendezvous.
The Cylons knew exactly
where we were gonna be.
It doesn't mean Ellen had...
This is the map, Colonel !
The map that I drew for you.
I gave this to you in your tent.
You were gonna burn it but then
your wife offered to do it for you.
I got it off a dead skinjob
at the ambush. Do the math !
I...
I want to explain, Saul.
- Godsdamn traitor !
- Shut your frakkin' mouth !
He said...
He said he'd kill you.
- Who said it ?
- One of the brother Cavils.
I did it for you... Saul.
It was all for you, I had to.
I didn't have any choice.
Don't you see that ?
Drawer 3-7-8.
What are you doing ?
Oh, my God, it's you.
You're betraying your own people.
For what ?
- I'm a colonial officer now.
- You're not one of them.
- I gave them my word.
- That's not what counts.
It's who you give it to.
I'm gonna have to shoot you now.
Hera lives.
What ?
Your daughter Hera is alive.
Your new friends tell you that ?
They faked her death,
and they hid her from you.
Can't say anything on higher dreams.
I had strange dreams.
I was having strange dreams
that made me question my faith.
Made me question God.
And in the dreams,
there was a human oracle,
so I went to see Dodona Selloi.
I'm not gonna kill you but I'm gonna
wound you so you can't warn the others.
The oracle said that the fruit
born of two peoples...
... is still alive.
That Hera lives
and I would hold her in my arms
and I will know true love.
Put down the gun.
And when I find her,
you can hold her too.
Adama wouldn't lie to me.
You're wrong.
You're wrong !
Launch keys don't seem
to have been damaged.
From all the data points,
it looks like the ships all have
enough tylium to make at least one jump.
Congratulations, by the way.
I heard it's a boy.
What's his name ?
Nicolas,
after Cally's grandfather.
Hey, Chief...
you remember when you helped
Helo spread Hera's ashes ?
You actually saw the ashes ?
Yeah, of course, why ?
Nothing.
Just make sure Cally never lets
her kid out of her sight.
Sir ?
Listening Raptor just jumped back.
Sharon's got the launch keys.
Rec room, Racetrack.
Very well, sir.
It's on.
This is the Admiral.
You've heard the news.
You know the mission.
You should also know there's only
one way that this mission ends.
And that's with the successful rescue
of our people
off of New Caprica.
Look around you.
Take a good look at
the men and women...
that stand next to you.
Remember their faces.
For one day
you will tell your children
and your grandchildren,
that you served with
such men and women
as the universe has never seen.
And together...
you accomplished a feat
that will be told and retold
down through the ages.
and find immortality
as only the Gods once knew.
I'm proud to serve with you.
Good hunting.
Begin jump prep.
Action stations.
Set condition one
throughout the ship.
Standby for a combat jump.
We thank you for watching
Battlestar Galactica with our subs.
Team
- =( Lords of Kobol )= -