CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell rings)
(whistle blows)
(clinks)
(beeps)
(playing the blues)
(jazzy solo)
(clinks)
(honking horn)
(tires screeching)
D'oh!
(screams)
(groans, gasps)
(clears throat)
I hope you all are enjoying
your ride to and tour
of the Springfield Shopper newspaper
Groundskeeper Willie
and I will stay behind
to remove
all traces of asbestos
and the word "evolution"
from our school.
Next stop, Margaritaville! Uh-
-Oh, they're still here.
-Yes.
Now I'd like to ask each child
to pair up with
a buddy so no one gets lost.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Uter
since the last field trip.
(chuckling) Uter?
I don't remember any Uter.
(chuckling)
Silly name. Uter.
Dad, it's great that
you volunteered to drive.
But how did you
get out of work?
Don't worry, sweetie.
Daddy's got it covered.
(Homer on tape recorder)
♪ I work hard for the money ♪
♪ So hard for the money ♪
♪ Oh, I something,
something money ♪
♪ Come on
give me lots of honey ♪
Now, there's an employee, Smithers.
A smile on his lips
and a song in his heart.
Promote him.
(singing continues, warbled)
Turn tape over!
Hey, I know
how we can have some fun.
I spy with my little eye...
something beginning with "D."
-Dingus! (grunts)
-(groans)
God bless you, Nelson Muntz.
I'm no hero.
I just like to hit people
in the head.
-(tires screeching)
-(car horn honks)
Hey, you (bleep)!
You cut me off!.
Oh, yeah! (bleep) you!
-(car horn honks)
-Dad! That's an ambulance!
Oh, right!
-(horn honks)
-(bleep) ambulance!
Think you're so big
with your (bleep) siren
-and your letters on backwards!
-(engine revs)
Here we are, kids. The zoo.
Well, that's great, Dad.
Except you were supposed
to drive us to the newspaper.
(Homer echoing) D'oh!
(trumpeting)
(bellows)
Welcome
to the Springfield Shopper,
established in 1883.
The newspaper was founded
by Johnny Newspaperseed,
a 14-year-old boy
who roamed America
founding newspapers.
If he's so smart,
how come he's dead?
Over the years,
the shopper merged
with the Springfield Times,
Post, Globe, Herald,
Jewish News
and Hot Sex Weekly
to become Springfield's
number-one newspaper.
Wow! A bustling
metropolitan newsroom
funneling scoops
from all over the globe.
Hi! Are you interested
in a subscription
to the Shopper?
Low introductory rates!
No, please you gotta help ol' Gil.
What's it gonna take
to keep you on the phone?
Dance for you?
But you wouldn't even see it.
Yeah. All right.
(chuckles)
I'm dancin'!
(humming)
And this is our
comic strip department.
Who here reads Mary Worth?
Let's move on.
This is where we store
Ann Landers and Dear Abby
for their 23 hours
of daily sleep.
My advice is to free us
or let us die!
Check it out, Dad.
You can print out the headline
from the day you were born.
Ooh! Pointless nostalgia!
I'd sure hate to be him.
(laughs, groans)
And to protect Mother Earth,
each copy contains a certain
percentage of recycled paper.
And what percent is that?
Zero! Zero's a percent!
Hey, I smell cake.
Cake that says--
(sniffs) "farewell" and--
(sniffs, gasps) ..."best wishes!"
Your old man
has an awesome nose.
Oh, that's nothing.
He can hear pudding.
So, Mimi, this little shindig
is our way of saying farewell
to our favorite food critic.
What can I say except thanks
for the predictable champagne,
pizza that's hardly numero uno
and ice-cream cake
which reminds us,
why make 31 flavors when
you can't get vanilla right?
I wouldn't want
to be married to her.
I mean, again.
(Homer chomps)
Who are you, and why are you
ruining my retirement party?
I'll have you know,
I wandered off from the tour.
Well, at least
you like the food.
Oh, I like food, all right.
(singing)
♪ I like pizza, I like bagels ♪
♪ I like hot dogs
with mustard and beer ♪
I get the picture.
♪ I'll eat eggplant ♪
♪ I could even eat
a baby deer ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la
La-la la-la ♪
♪ Who's that baby deer
on the lawn there ♪
-Enough already!
-Sorry.
Hey, listen.
I just had a thought.
We're looking
for a new food critic,
someone who doesn't immediately
pooh-pooh everything he eats.
No, it usually
takes a few hours.
Uh, look...
I'd like to give you a tryout.
Write a 500-word sample review.
If it passes muster,
we'll put you on staff.
Thanks for the chance.
You won't never regret this,
Mr. Editing Guy.
You know, Homie,
the "e" doesn't work
on that typewriter.
We don't need no stinkin' "e."
"Restaurant review." No.
"Eatery evaluation." No.
(gasps)
"Food box - Go or no go,
by Homer." No.
Earl-- no! Bill Simpson!
(laughs)
Well, what do you think?
This is a joke, right?
I mean,
this is the stupidest thing
I've ever read.
What's wrong with it?
Well, you keep using words
like "pasghetti"
and "momatoes."
You make numerous
threatening references to the U.N.
And at the end, you repeat
the words "screw Flanders"
over and over again.
Oh, it's so hard
to get to 500 words.
Oh, look, Homer, I'm sorry.
No! You're right! It's a joke!
(chuckles)
Everyone laugh
at the funny joke! Ha-ha!
I'll be right back
with the real review.
(door slams)
(Homer whimpering)
Still not clean.
Stink of failure still on me.
(knocking)
LISA: Dad, I'm sorry the editor
didn't like your review.
I'll help you write
a new review
if you'll just let me
use the bathroom!
Still not clean.
Still not clean!
Okay, what restaurant
did we review?
Well, we went
to Pate Labelle last week.
-How about that?
-Great. Now let me think.
The food was--
Mmm-- not undelicious.
The food is delicious.
(gasps) That's brilliant!
Then I had the sweet,
sweet chocolate mousse.
Really,
the only word for it is...
(groaning)
Hmm. What's the English
equivalent for...
(groaning)
I'd say "transcendent."
How about
"groin-grabbingly transcendent"?
Er, I don't think so.
We make a good team.
A groin-grabbingly good team.
LISA:
Four hundred and ninety seven,
four hundred
and ninety eight words.
-Hmph.
-How about "screw Flanders"?
Bon appetit.
Er, both's good.
Not bad! Not bad at all!
We're gonna run
this on page one...
of section H2.
Whoo-hoo! Stop the presses!
-(gasps)
-(alarms blaring)
Okay, start the presses!
That takes four hours.
Whatever. I'll be at Moe's.
This is so exciting, Homie!
Your first restaurant review!
Marge. Shh!
It's important that no one
knows that I'm a food critic.
Hear that, Maude?
Homer's a critic!
Homer's a critic. Pass it on.
Did you hear? Homer's a critic.
Quit changing the subject!
Where is Uter?
Oh! We just want closure.
Arr! Here you are.
One critic's special.
Er, if anything appears
to be movin',
that's just freshness. Arr.
Can you believe it, Marge?
This job is the greatest.
They're paying me to eat!
Yeah. Now if you could
just get somebody
to pay you
for scratching your butt,
we'll be on easy street.
-Why, you little--
-(groaning)
Wow! My first published
article, whew,
although someone else's
name is on it.
He-he. Welcome
to the humiliating world
of professional writing.
But this is only the beginning.
Welcome to Planet Springfield!
The restaurant owned
by me, Chuck Norris,
Johnny Carson's third wife
and the Russian mafia.
Each Planet Springfield
is filled with priceless
Hollywood gewgaws.
(gasps) There's the coffee mug
from Heartbeeps!
And there's the cane
from Citizen Kane!
Wait a minute.
There was no cane
in Citizen Kane .
And there's that awful script
from The Cable Guy .
Lemme see. Stupid script!
Nearly wrecked
Jim Carrey's career!
You-- (grunting)
I'm gonna... what?
The food is exquisite!
And the view is... beautiful...
inspirational...
nauseating.
(groans)
Hey, Homer! Great call
on that chicken place!
And on that rib place!
I never knew
everything was so good!
Look, Marge.
I'm making a difference
in people's lives.
Yes, Simpson, your love
of food is contagious.
I've never felt jollier. (cracking)
Ooh!
There go my shin bones again.
Hey, Homer! Come here.
(gasps)
Are you gonna fire me
for swiping office supplies?
-No.
-Whew!
(clacking)
Some of your fellow critics
wanted to meet you.
This is Garth Trelawney, TV critic.
Why, you-- you made them
cancel Platypus Man...
Homer!
This is our theater critic,
Daphne Beaumont.
...and the Cosby Mysteries!
That show had
limitless possibilities!
-Homer, please!
-Sorry.
Jamie Killday,
farm supply critic.
Just got back from
the Gopher Poison show
in Paris. Let me tell you
something, people.
The days of clubbing them
with a baseball bat are over!
For you, perhaps.
Listen, we've been meaning
to have a talk
with you about your reviews.
Everything's a rave!
Nine thumbs up?
What the hell is that?
I've given out my share
of bad reviews.
Oh! The only bad review
you gave was
to a slice of pizza
you found under the couch.
It lost some points
'cause it had a hot wheel on it.
Oh, good Lord, man.
You're a critic!
You don't have to like
everything,
e.g., my latest review.
(clears throat)
"We see John Deere has come out
with this year's
line of rototillers.
Surprise, surprise,
they're green!
I say it's time to send
John Deere a 'Dear John."'
-Oh, that's classic!
-You don't have to patronize me.
Aaa-- okay.
Lord, thy daughters...
Goneril, Regan and Cordelia.
What is this, merry old England
or petticoat junction?
(laughing)
(audience boos, hisses,
heckles)
(groaning)
Hey! Lighten up. It's a comedy.
-No, it's not.
-It's not?
(groans)
Hmm. This pea soup
is as weak as the acting
and nowhere near as hammy.
Dad! That's so mean!
The other critics
told me to be mean,
and you should always
give in to peer pressure.
But what if someone bad
tells me to--
Always!
Huh? Huh?
Whoa! This material stinks!
I'm gonna have to punch it up
on the fly.
Oh, I got one!
How do you make a King Lear?
Put the queen in a bikini!
-(chuckles, groans)
-(audience boos)
Here's another one.
Knock, knock. Who's there?
"Juliet." "Juliet who?"
Juliet so much pasta fazool,
Romeo doesn't want her anymore!
-(laughing)
-(booing continues)
Whoa, tough crowd!
They're booing Shakespeare!
(chomping)
Uh, not bad...
if lasagna is Italian
for "pile of puke"!
Aah! I chopp-a you good!
(shouts in foreign language)
Well, I hope you cut me better
than you did
these string beans.
Hmm. I seem to be missing
a piece of my ear. Touché.
Who wants pork chops?
Mmm.
Sorry, Marge.
I'm afraid this gets my lowest
rating ever! Seven thumbs up.
You always liked my pork chops.
Marge, I'm sorry,
but your cooking's
only got two moves...
shake and bake.
You like shake 'n bake!
You used to put
it in your coffee!
People change, Marge.
My palate has grown
more sophisticated.
Oh, yeah? What's a palate?
Oh, it's a...
special time
in a boy's life when--
-Gotta go!
-(chair scraping)
So come to The Legless Frog...
if you want to get sick and die
and leave
a big, garlicky corpse!
P.S., parking was ample.
Dad, you're being cruel for no reason.
What will people think?
People will think
what I tell them to think,
when you tell me
what to tell them to think.
Not anymore.
I don't want to be partners
with a man
who thinks like that.
Nobody talks to me that way!
I'm Homer Simpson,
the most powerful food critic in town,
who will never
get his comeuppance!
You hear me?
No comeuppance!
We'll be right back.
I don't need Lisa
to write a good review.
The food at
The Gilded Truffle really...
uh-what's a good word?
(sucking)
Sucks! That's great!
And the bread was really...
Come on!
Help me out here!
-Ruff!
-Rough?
I don't know. You've been
pitchin' that all night.
-Chewy?
-Chewy!
That's inspired!
Homer, what gives
with this review?
You say "the salad
tastes like bark"
and the potatoes
were very "grrrrr!"
This reads like
it was written by a dog.
Are you crazy?
A dog can't type.
(mutters) Unfortunately.
Listen, you gotta shape up!
Next week
is the Taste of Springfield festival.
You'll be reviewing
every restaurant in town.
Remember,
people have certain expectations
about the "Life Ways" section.
Really? Like what?
Oh, I don't know.
Astrology, Broom-Hilda ,
vacation horror stories ,
articles about
chronic fatigue syndrome...
you know, chick crap.
(angry muttering)
Homer, he's outta control.
He gave me a bad review!
So, my friend
put a horse head on his bed.
He ate the head
and gave it a bad review!
True story.
Arr, well, I've had it with Homer!
His bad reviews
are sinkin' our businesses.
Then, why did you put yours
in the window?
Arr, it covered up the "D"
from the health inspector.
Well, I say we ban Homer
from our restaurants.
No. That would be impolite.
I say we kill him!
Now, hold on a minute.
Are we restauranteurs,
or are we murderers?
Does that answer your question?
We'll kill him at
The Taste of Springfield festival.
We'll give Homer
all he can eat,
till he can eat no more.
Then, he'll get
his just dessert.
This will be Homer Simpson's
last lagniappe.
Come on!
You're gonna kill him with a pastry?
I've seen this man
eat a bowl of change.
This eclair has
over one million calories.
Twenty-five pounds of butter
per square inch.
-(all moan)
-Covered with chocolate
so dark, light cannot escape
its surface.
(clamoring)
No, no, no!
This is just a picture.
But Homer Simpson
will find the real thing
both delicious and deadly.
Ah, yes! Death by chocolate.
(laughs)
Oh.
And poison.
I'll stick in some poison.
(all laughing)
Homie, my woman's intuition's acting u
Something bad's going to happen
if you go in there.
Oh, Marge, something bad
usually happens to me
when I go in anywhere.
(whistling)
-D'oh! Ohh! (grunting)
-(bat squealing)
A bat. Now, that's a new one!
So what are you up to,
young lady?
I'm reviewing the festival
for our school paper.
Oh. Well, I'm glad to see
my ex-partner
is doing so well without me.
(groans)
(chomping)
Pedestrian.
Uninspired.
I didn't say stop.
Lard ho!
Arr, 'tis a good sign.
Homer's unfastened
the top button on his pants.
Uh, no, he's been walking
around like that since Thanksgiving.
I'm surprised
he just doesn't give it up
and go for sweat pants.
He says the crotch
wears out too fast.
Yarrr! That's gonna replace
the whale in my nightmares!
Well, don't worry.
The giant eclair will knock
Homer off the food page
and into the obituaries.
(both laughing)
Wait a minute.
They're gonna kill Dad!
Ooh!
Oh, that's a spicy meat-ball!
So if we don't find Dad,
this crazy French guy
-is gonna kill him!
-(sighs)
Only your father could take
a part-time job
at a small-town paper
and wind up
the target
of international assassins.
We can find him faster
by splitting up.
You take fried foods,
you take salty snacks,
I'll take desserts. Break!
Ohh! So full.
Belly button moving from
innie to... (creaking) outie!
(chomping, smacking)
Ooh, that looks
scrumdiddly-doodly-duddley--
-Get lost!
-A rude Frenchman?
Well, I never!
(gasps)
Ooh! Sweet!
(smacking lips)
(panting)
Ooh!
(chuckles)
Dad, no!
It's gonna kill you!
Ehh, I've had a good run.
(grunting)
Don't, uh--
Um, it's low-fat!
No!
Whew! That was close.
Thank God
it landed
in that smoking crater!
(humming "La Marseillaise")
-Huh?
-Take him into custardy, boys!
Hah! Attempted murder one.
Now, boys, what would you say
to some Belgian waffles?
Actually, I was in the mood
for some frittatas.
Ha! Lou and his frittatas!
(laughing)
Frittatas! Ha-ha!
Oh, he likes eggs.
Oh, Lisa, you saved me!
And after all the bad things
I said about you.
What bad things? Why?
Oh, Lisa, the important thing is
I didn't get my comeuppance,
and I never will.
Uh, Dad?
I know, honey.
The important thing is... run!
-(elephants trumpeting)
-(all shouting)
-(Homer groaning, whimpering)
-(blows landing)
HOMER: I'm finally getting
my comeuppance!
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services