(theme music playing)
CHORUS: ♪ The Simpsons ♪
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeping)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh! (screams)
(brakes screeching)
(moaning)
(evil laughter)
These Swedish furniture designers
sure have some far-out ideas.
I mean, a green table?
I wouldn't have thought of that
in my wildest dreams.
And these bean bag chairs
look so comfortable.
(sighing) Oops!
Hey, there's someone else in here.
SEA CAPTAIN: Argh, she swallowed me whole.
You put it together yourself.
All you need is me, Allen Wrench.
(laughing)
He's named after what he is.
(clanging)
Cool costume.
(in mechanical voice) It's not a costume.
They found me inside a meteor.
Excuse me, where are your hamper lids?
(in normal voice) Hamper lids?
Uh, third floor.
(in mechanical voice) Help!
I need tungsten to live.
Tungsten!
Whoa...
Ooh, look at all these
clever pencil holders.
Ooh! I want to get the Kronk.
Mmm. You don't want something
that overshadows the pencils.
How about this... Popli?
Mom, no!
Everyone at school picks on
the Popli kids,
even I do!
I just hate them so much.
Yes, I will have the polpenlugen
and don't skimp on the doodlemunch.
How ingenious!
The forks are made out of Lego.
Hmm!
Hello, Simpsons!
Hey, Apu, Manjula.
You guys are still married?
Oh, yes, sir, quite happily.
Pay up, Marge.
Say, what you got there?
I don't know, exactly.
It's from the room of lamps
that do not look like lamps.
(electrical surging)
(cooing)
Oh, little Maggie, aren't you cute
with your little bow?
(singsong babbling)
Maggie loves baby talk.
-That was Hindi.
-(chuckling) Oh. Sorry.
So, have you two thought about kids?
Well, sure we have, but the decision
to have a child is not to be made lightly.
(blowing raspberries)
(giggling)
On the other hand, monkey see, monkey do.
(chuckling) Kids are the best, Apu.
You can teach them to hate
the things you hate.
And they practically raise themselves
what with the Internet and all.
Well, perhaps it is time.
I've noticed this country
is dangerously underpopulated.
Are you sure you want a child, Apu?
You know I do.
I mean, there comes a time in a man's life
when he asks himself,
"Who will float my corpse
down the Ganges?"
Oh, Apu, take me now.
APU: Oh, Calcutta!
Hey, Apu, sitting
in the ice cream cooler, eh?
By chilling my loins,
I increase the chances
of impregnating my wife.
Whoa-ho, too much information.
Thanks for the mental picture.
Why don't you tell us
what you really think?
Would you stop spouting
those hackneyed quips?
Could you be any more...
Hello?
(laughing)
Look, just give me some ice cream.
Um. How about one not touching your ass?
-(pager beeps)
-Oh!
Manjula has begun to ovulate.
Ew...
Thanks for sharing...
more than I wanted to know!
Here goes nothing.
BOTH: Baby...
Baby...
Oh... lemon.
All that sex for nothing.
Well, that is a pretty grim assessment.
You know, Homer, you might want
to open those cans before they explode.
But the cans seal in the flavor.
OK.
So, how's the tribe coming along?
Any papooses?
No. Still no luck.
Tell me, Homer,
did you have to take any...
special steps when you
decided to have children?
"Decided"?
(laughing)
That's classic! "Decided."
Babies just happen.
Well, not to us, they don't.
Oh, Homer, we have tried everything.
Oysters, gravity boots,
Sanjay's bed, every possible position.
Really?
On top and underneath?
Eh... yes.
Well, don't worry, I can help you.
I'm all about ideas.
Kids! Come and get it!
Now, this situation is guaranteed
to end in pregnancy.
I'm willing to play the high school jock,
but did you have to cut
the roof off my car?
Hup-hup-hup-hup. That's an Apu question.
You're "Greg."
"Uh, gee, Betsy, it's such a nice night.
-Why don't we go all the way?
-(Homer mouthing along)
"But Greg, my dad will kill me.
"And you have that scholarship
to Ivy League State."
"Loosen up, baby.
Tomorrow I'm shipping off to Vietnam."
I thought I was going to Ivy League State.
My mistake. Stay in the moment.
"Just promise not to forget me
on your dinosaur-bone- digging-up trip."
(sighing)
(kissing)
And that's my cue to exit.
Homer!
I just wanted to invite
you to the wrap party.
And that's my cue to exit.
(Homer humming)
BOTH: Baby...
Baby...
Pirate?
(sighing)
No, no, wait a minute!
Pirates are wild!
We are pregnant!
(both laughing)
APU: Oh! Oh, get lost.
Man, the last nine months sure were crazy.
I'll say. I learned the true meaning
of Columbus Day.
I enjoyed a brief but memorable stint
as sideshow Marge.
I became the most popular girl in school
But blew it by being conceited.
And then I learned
the true meaning of winter.
Apu, do you still find me attractive?
Of course I do, sweetheart.
You are beautiful and silky
and manageable.
You're reading that off
a conditioner bottle.
I... That's true.
But you still have a...
(water splashing)
Ooh! Oh.
My water broke.
Oh, we must drive to the hospital.
Cleanup in aisle three.
Oh, finally.
Gil's moving up to the big leagues, boy.
Aah!
Aw, my back...
(all snoring)
Apu, come quick!
You're missing the miracle!
Oh?
Oh, my sweet husband,
say hello to your firstborn child.
Oh. You shall be the jewel of our lives.
Aw... Now, say hello
to your other seven children.
My... what?
(laughing) We had quite a discussion
about the funniest way
to reveal them to you.
You have octuplets.
It rolls off your tongue
and into your heart, "octuplets."
(laughing)
Apu, you should have seen your face
when they showed you
those babies. (laughing)
Yeah. It looked just like that.
Apu, say hello to Poonam, Sashi
Pria, Uma, Anoop, Sandeep, Nabendu
and Mama's clear favorite, Gheet.
APU: How did we get eight?
Apu, I must confess.
When we were having trouble conceiving,
I took fertility drugs.
(moans)
I, too, I am afraid, am guilty
of monkeying with nature.
I slipped fertility drugs
into your breakfast squishy.
Mm-hmm...
Well, that would only account
for quintuplets.
Did anyone else slip
this woman fertility drugs?
Mine tasted like strawberry.
Mmm. Ovulicious.
(shutters clicking)
Would you say you and your babies
have a "love-eight" relationship?
(all chuckling)
(chuckling) Absolutely. Yes.
No. Say it. We need a sound bite.
We have a "love-eight" relationship.
ALL: Aw.
Yes. Kent Brockman, Channel Six.
How would you respond to people who say
this kind of multiple birth
is more suited to, say,
a possum than a human being?
Wha-- Who would say such a thing?
Well... Pundits, wags...
I'm not the one on trial here.
No one is on trial.
This is a joyous occasion for all,
and the outpouring of support
has been so lucrative.
Yes. We have already received
lifetime supplies
of baby powder and Pepsi-B.
Free baby cola?
Apu hits the jackpot
and I'm stuck with
these useless one-tuplets.
Gee, sorry for being born.
I've been waiting so long to hear that.
(forklift beeping)
How do you feel about this avalanche
of free merchandise?
Oh, the companies are so generous.
Except the Q-tip people.
They only gave us three crates.
They can rot in hell.
But the good folks at Sony...
(loud kiss)
Their giant TV will really
help us love our babies.
I'm here at Shelbyville Hospital
where a local woman has just given birth
to nine, that's right, nine babies.
(both gasp)
Some say eight babies is a blessing,
but they don't know the joy of nine.
Would you say you're on cloud nine?
BOTH: We're on cloud nine!
ALL: Aw.
Oh. They even have
a better sound bite than us.
Nine babies? That's barbaric!
Nonuplets? Now, that's something
you don't see every day.
Let's get this stuff to the real heroes,
the Shelbyville Nine!
Oh.
Wait! That's our ottoman!
(sighs)
Don't worry, my little curry-face.
We don't need corporate handouts.
Our children will live on love.
(babies crying)
(groaning)
(crying)
(singing to the tune of
"Rock-A-Bye Baby" in Hindi)
(crying continues)
(snoring)
Apu! It's 4:00 a.m.
You are late for work.
Oh. I just had the most
beautiful dream where I died.
Oh, no, you don't, not till
they're out of college.
Listen, I'll die when I want to.
(wheels squeaking)
Thank you. Steal again.
(door sensor rings)
Well, morning, Apu.
How are the little blessings?
Ooh, they're a ravenous swarm of locusts,
just eating and screaming
and grabbing and poking
and pulling and drooling
and two have cradle rash.
How do you get cradle rash
when you sleep in a suitcase?
(chuckling)
They can be a handful...
-of joy.
-Shut up!
They'll fill your lives with...
Just shut up!
Can't put a price on a miracle.
I can't believe you don't shut up.
-(clicking)
-HOMER: Oh, look at that.
Ooh, a gingerbread house.
Hansel and Gretel are set for life.
You know, I saw Apu today.
He's really frazzled.
Boy, that Hansel sure can eat.
Ah! My corneas!
You were saying?
Apu told me all eight babies have colic.
Although, he thinks one or two
might just be going along with the crowd.
Eight kids. Hmm.
I'm sterile, right, baby doll?
Yes, dear, from the nuclear plant.
Beautiful.
(doorbell ringing)
Knock, knock.
Hmm.
Apu?
Manjula?
Marge, I've got a bad feeling about this.
(both gasp)
Welcome to my nightmare.
I know you had your hands full
with the babies
So I baked you some banana bread.
Oh, hallelujah, our problems are solved.
We have banana bread.
Well, you don't have to be sarcastic.
Oh, look, who's here.
The family with one baby.
How do you manage?
Marge, they've turned into jerks.
I'm very sorry. We've been rude.
Can I offer you something to drink?
-No, thanks.
Apu, they're doing it again.
-OK, break it up.
-(babies cooing)
Maybe you two should get a nanny.
Yes, and what would
I pay her with? Banana bread?
Sorry, sorry. It's just
we haven't slept in days
and we're running out of money and...
Banana bread?
What the hell were you thinking?
Banana bread.
I apologize, apologize again.
As a token of forgiveness,
-please take this baby.
-Mmm.
No! Marge, no!
(doorbell ringing)
Mr. Nahasa... Pasa...
Aw, forget it.
Listen, you look like
you could use some help.
-Come with me.
-OK.
But you don't know who he is.
Who cares? There's only one of him.
What if your babies could live in a place
with round-the-clock child care,
all expenses paid, full medical,
dental, tutors, the works?
I would say that there must be
some sort of horrible catch.
The zoo?
What? Everybody loves my zoo.
You don't love my zoo?
I dare you to look at a kangaroo
and not laugh.
I dare you.
Well, they're usually funnier.
Look, I'm not going
to put my babies in a zoo.
Don't say no till you see the habitat.
The habitat?
I mean, the nursery.
Oh, my goodness.
Not too shabby, eh?
They'll have the best of care.
And all I ask is
that you let the local folks
share a little glimpse of your blessing.
But is it right to put such young children
on display?
-MAN: Sure, it is.
-Uh?
Butch Patrick?
That's right.
I was TV's Eddie Munster.
And being in the public eye
didn't mess me up one bit.
Mm-hmm.
Well, obviously.
Hey, one question, Eddie.
-Butch.
-Eh, right, right.
If your mother was a vampire
and your father was a Frankenstein,
how come you are a werewolf?
Huh. I never thought of that.
Doesn't make sense, does it?
But what does make sense
is putting your children
in the hands of Mr. Kidkill here.
Please, please... Larry. Larry Kidkill.
I don't care what Butch Patrick says.
It just doesn't seem right.
We wouldn't be giving the babies away.
We'd be moving in with them.
They'll have a traditional
"zoo-ish" upbringing.
Mmm. Mmm.
Well, maybe we could try it.
-MANJULA: Whoa!
-Hey, what the...
Hey, I'm a notary.
So, I got that going, too.
(Apu babbling)
(cooing)
Oh... you like that, don't you, Poonam?
Yeah, who's a clean baby, huh?
(cooing)
Ah, now, this is a happy family.
You liking this thing?
How's this humidity, good?
Why am I asking?
I can see on the meter it's good.
Oh, everything is perfect.
Yeah, nothing's too good
for my little angels.
Hup! It's almost showtime.
Showtime?
(gasps)
All right, people.
If you're not in a diaper,
get off my stage.
Off, off, off, off.
I can't believe we're going
to see the octuplets.
You already saw them.
Yeah, but now their umbilical cords
have fallen off.
-(drumroll)
-Ladies and gentlemen,
get ready for the eight wonders
of the Third World.
Welcome to Octopia!
(pulsating techno music playing)
He can't talk, but, man, can he rock.
Say hello to the baddest baby
in the whole damn town...
Animal!
♪ Welcome to the jungle ♪
♪ We got fun and games ♪
AUDIENCE: Aw.
♪ We got everything you want... ♪
How can he rebel?
He doesn't even know where he is.
(dramatic music plays)
Uh-oh, sounds like
one of the babies has a fever.
(gasps)
Dance fever, that is.
Oh! (chortling)
Let's hear it for Dazzle!
(swing music playing)
She's no Liza, but it works.
(lively music playing)
And now the standup who can't even sit up.
Give it up for Punchline!
(audience applauding)
(laughing)
He's thinking what we're all saying.
But all the laughs in the world
won't protect you
from the stern discipline of...
the Baron.
("The Ride of the Valkyries" playing)
(audience booing)
Boo, Baron.
And... the rest.
♪ R-O-C-K in the U.S.A. ♪
Good night, Springfield.
We'll be back in an hour.
♪ Rockin' in the U.S.A. ♪
BOTH: Huh?
(baby burps)
Good babies.
Good, good babies.
Work with Dazzle.
She's a lox out there.
How could you do this to our children?
I know, the lighting cues were a mess.
Don't worry, the guy's been fired.
Our babies are not circus freaks.
We're taking them home now.
Hold on, Alpo. We got a contract.
Not anymore.
(grunting)
Laminated.
You monster!
Terence, Christopher.
Will you show these two to the exit?
(speaking French)
I'm afraid there's nothing I can do.
The zookeeper paid you off, didn't he?
Paid me off?
What, are you crazy?
So we'll never see our children again?
Well, they might give Dazzle back.
The buzz is, she's got one more show
to turn it around.
Well, if the police won't help us,
we'll simply have to take
the law into our own hands.
Yeah, yeah, a lot of people
are doing that these days.
(insects chirping)
These animals certainly
act different at night.
(snarling)
(chuckling)
(grunting)
Oh, my little treasures.
We'll get you out of this terrible place.
(gasps) She's waking up.
Don't worry, I brought some chloroform.
Pleasant dreams.
There... and there.
You idiot! Those are Colorforms.
-(screams)
-(exclaims)
(alarm blaring)
APU: Nabendu...
Pria... and Sashi.
Now let's go!
(gorilla gibbering)
OK, this is getting weird.
(tires screeching)
Oh, my precious babies.
We'll never let you go.
Oh, let's get this awful thing off.
(struggling)
Let me... OK, whatever.
Hold it right there, scumbags!
(gasps)
Please, Mr. Kidkill,
look into your heart.
I know these babies have
a lifetime contract.
But what if I put together
an even better act for you?
Something sensational!
It's not just you prancing around
in a monkey suit, is it?
Not anymore.
You've got yourself a deal.
(Homer yelping)
♪ Highway to the danger zone ♪
Quiet! You're breaking character.
Are those real cobras?
"Some are real,
Some are just robots filled with venom."
Now, that is a true friend.
You know, if he can handle that,
maybe we can handle this bunch.
We'll do our best, chutney-butt.
(snakes hissing)
OK, OK, don't panic, Butch.
Release the mongoose!
♪ Highway to the danger zone ♪
(whimpering)
(screaming)
(baby laughing)
HOMER: Ow! Oh!
Stupid mongoose! Get the snake! The snake!
Do I look like a snake? Ow! Ow!
Why isn't he listening to me?
Ow! (screaming)
Show's over! Show's over!
Next show at eight o'clock and ten!
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services