CHORUS:
♪ The Simpsons ♪
(theme music playing)
(bell ringing)
(whistle blowing)
(beeps)
(playing the blues)
(honking horn)
D'oh! (screams)
(brakes screeching)
(all screaming)
(shredder whirring)
MAN: Tonight, on
Guinness Book of World Records,
a man who holds the current record
-for least amount of faces, with none!
-Help me!
You'll also see
the world's smelliest tumor.
Ew... these records used to be real
accomplishments. Now they're just gross.
Plus, you'll meet a dog
who can't predict anything.
Then, three other things.
When we come back we'll show you
the contents of a supermodel's stomach.
What an age we live in.
Oh, look at all that sweet 'n low.
Hey, remember the '50s?
Remember television,
Coca-Cola, and Dick Clark?
(gasps) I remember television!
Come join me, Wolfguy Jack,
at Greaser's Cafe
where it's 1955
every day of the year, baby.
MAN: Actual year may vary.
Consult calendar for current year.
A '50s-style restaurant.
What a neat idea.
Why don't we eat there tonight?
Ah, we'll go next month.
(music playing)
(women screaming)
-(women screaming)
-(exclaims)
Dennis the Menace?
Yes. I was America's bad boy.
I once hid my dad's hat.
-(laughs)
-Uh-huh.
And another time,
I accidentally stepped
in Mr. Wilson's flower bed.
(laughs) That was a two-part episode.
(laughs)
I have to go.
California, here we come.
It's not a real car, Grandpa.
Allen Ginsburgers?
Unamerican cheese sandwich? Polio dogs?
It's clever how the names
remind you of the '50s,
and at the same time,
tell you what there is to eat.
Wow, look at this old-timey gizmo!
(giggles)
I feel like I've gone back
in a time machine.
Dad, they have those everywhere.
What an age we live in.
(laughing)
(Wolfguy howling)
(coughing) Oh, man.
Oh, my throat doctor says
I'm not supposed to do that anymore.
OK, is everybody ready
for our nightly dance contest?
Dancing?
Oh, no, you're not getting me
on that dance floor.
Don't try and make me.
If I have to get a divorce I will.
Our grand prize tonight is a vintage 1955
Harley-Davidson motorcycle.
(gasps) Oh! I need a dance partner!
(gasping nervously)
-What about you?
-OK, Daddy-O.
WOLFGUY: Hey, hey, set your socks on hop
and your tutti to frutti.
Here we go with "Mental House Rock"
by Johnny Bobby.
♪ Doctors threw a party at the loony bin ♪
♪ You got to be crazy
if you want to get in ♪
♪ Napoleon is playing his imaginary sax ♪
♪ The dance floor is filling up
with maniacs ♪
♪ Let's rock ♪
♪ Do the Mental House Rock... ♪
Ahhh! Ooh!
(grunting)
(screaming)
♪ Let's rock ♪
♪ Do the Mental House Rock ♪
Whoa!
Wow... a '50s nostalgia cafe.
♪ If you won't dance with the doc ♪
♪ He'll give you electroshock
Zap, zap, zap! ♪
Well, well, well, I've never
seen such reckless disregard
for a wife's well-being in my life.
You just won yourselves a motorcycle.
Whoo-hoo!
(crowd cheering)
It's mine.
Finally, I've won the respect
of my fellow ma--
Get away from it!
OK, hep cats, let's twirl some
more platters at Greaser's Cafe
where the '50s are never going away.
Well, that dream is over.
At least we still have
each other, right, honey?
Honey?
(howling)
(coughing)
God.
(imitating engine)
Man, you're bending the hell
out of that kickstand, Dad.
Why don't you just take it for a ride?
Promise you won't laugh?
Yeah, I promise.
-I don't know how.
-(laughing)
You're kidding? (laughing hysterically)
(laughing continuing)
You don't know how...
Will you teach me?
(laughs) Of course.
(snickering)
♪ You showed me everything ♪
♪ Oh, you took me by the hand ♪
♪ Puppy dogs and Lincoln logs
and castles made of sand ♪
♪ You gave me the courage
to spread my newborn wings ♪
♪ Like mayonnaise and marmalade
and other spreadable things ♪
♪ So I guess you are my hero ♪
♪ And there's something you should know ♪
♪ I want to make it clear
so I'm gonna sing it slow ♪
♪ If you weren't a man ♪
♪ And my father too ♪
♪ I'd buy you a diamond ring ♪
♪ And then I'd marry you ♪
(owl hoots)
All right, class, today,
we'll be sitting quietly in the dark
because teacher has a hangover.
-(Harley engine roars)
-Oh, it's like a chain saw in my head.
(exclaims) Oh!
-Later, Homer.
-Sweet hog, Mr. Simpson.
Remember to rebel against authority, kids.
SKINNER: Don't listen to him, children.
But we already did,
now I can't get it out of my head!
-Ow!
-Thank you, Nelson.
The sermon today is on John 4:13.
(Harley engine revving)
I think it was Jesus...
(engine revving)
...who said, "blessed are those..."
Oh, the heck with it!
Church dismissed.
(cheering)
(engine on idle)
Will you turn that engine off?
Quiet, Marge.
The motorcycle and I are trying to sleep.
-(revs)
-I know, I know, just tune her out.
MAN: And now, back to your
Tuesday morning movie.
Oh, I don't know what's come over Jimmy.
He won't do his homework,
he only salutes the flag with one finger,
and he comes home every night
with other people's blood on his shirt.
He's a rebel, I tell you.
A rebel without a cause.
Just like that boy
in that popular movie we saw.
(yelling)
Yeah, that's the life for me, Marge...
cruising and hassling shopkeepers.
When will you teens learn to be
uncool like everyone else?
-Never, pops.
-That's right, never!
Yeah, you can arrest me,
but you'll never defeat the Cobras.
Nothing can defeat a motorcycle gang.
A gang.
-That's the answer.
-Answer to what?
Hey, don't make me hassle you, Lisa.
(sputters)
You know, if you want to be in the gang,
eventually you're gonna
have to get motorcycles.
Yeah, we know.
Hey, Homer, can I join?
This gang's for rebels, Flanders,
-not conformos.
-Yeah.
-That's right.
-Buzz off.
Well, if I were a member,
we could use my rumpus room as our lair.
That guy just don't get it, do he?
My rumpus room
with the new bumper pool table?
-Bumper pool!
-You're kidding me.
(indistinct chatter)
The first meeting of Hell's Satans
is called to order.
I move we reconsider our club name.
Make it something
a little less blasphemous.
After all... (chuckles)
we don't want to go to hell.
How about the Devil's Pals?
-No.
-Or the Christ Punchers?
The Christ--
I don't think you understand my objection.
I'm the president
and the decision is mine.
We're Hell's Satans.
Besides, I already made our club jackets.
Oh, machine wash warm.
Tumble dry... ooh la la.
(rings bell)
Wait up, guys.
I got to empty my grass bag.
Hell's Satans, huh?
I'm watching you punks.
Can't hassle us, pig.
We're going the speed limit.
Oink, oink, oink.
(laughing and oinking)
You'll make a mistake some day,
and then you're going straight to juvie.
You can lock us away,
but you'll never defeat the Cobras.
-The Cobras?
-I thought you were the Hell's Satans.
Well, uh... Oink, oink, oink.
Oh, how can I be down a thousand bucks?
(bell pings)
Get away from my store,
you young hoodlums.
And what if we don't, pops?
-He's got a broom.
-Let's get out of here.
-Forget the pennies. Go, go!
-(moaning)
You promised me, no more brooms.
I know this is not your way,
but we're in America now.
(gasps) They printed my photo of our gang.
Oh, looks great.
Can't take a bad picture of that guy.
(gasps) You took a picture of me
when I was asleep?
If you'd been awake,
you would have said no.
You can see the bind I was in.
"Her turn-ons include thievery and liquor.
Her turn-offs include
underpants, pedestrians, and justice." Oh!
(people screaming)
What in the world?
(screams)
We're the Hell's Satans
out of Bakersfield.
You're the Hell's Satans?
What a fun coincidence.
My gang's name is also the--
Shut up!
You stole our club name.
According to our bylaws,
we got to stomp you.
(shrieks)
-Take off that jacket, man.
-OK.
-(gasping)
-Now, eat it.
(whimpering) All right.
(Homer chewing and swallowing)
Hey, hey, chew with your mouth closed,
please.
(muffled) Sorry.
Done.
OK, Meathook,
I think he learned his lesson.
Oh, man.
-Now you got to eat that, too.
-Oh!
You got anything else with our logo on it?
Caps and frisbees, sir.
You've got to eat them, too.
And some pogs.
("Me and the Boys" by NRBQ playing)
-Ew!
-Ah!
You keep it.
I think it's great
you've chosen to "crash" here,
but do you have to be so messy?
Yeah, it's part of being
a low-life. (spits)
(grunts)
Hello, police, can you send a SWAT team
to 742 Evergreen Terr--
Forget it, Simpson. Those pig noises
you made really hurt my feelings...
looking like a pig as I do.
But you have so much inner beauty.
Well, uh, be that as it may...
uh, the gang is wanted
in eight other states
and we have a little saying around here,
"Let Michigan handle it."
-(beep)
-(shudders)
(both growling)
(grunting)
-(grunts)
-Stop that!
If you want some food
I'll be happy to make you some breakfast.
I'd kill for some waffles.
He has. Remember the IHOP in Oakland?
(both laughing)
Hey, this is a lot better
than that rancid filth
we find in the dumpsters.
Thank you, Ramrod.
Marge, how did you get my jacket so clean?
I've tried everything to get those blood
and puke stains out.
I've tried hitting 'em,
I've tried yelling at 'em...
All it takes is the right cleanser
and a little elbow grease.
Do you have anything that will get
this emblem back on my jacket?
I tried spitting at it, you know, but...
Just put it on my sewing pile.
OK, I'm doing another load of bandannas.
(Bart humming)
Hey, hey, that's leave-in conditioner.
-You're done. Next.
-(shivers)
Dad, I'm tired of bathing in the yard,
plus I think Rod and Todd are watching.
No, we're not.
OK, bikers, that's it.
Benjamin Franklin once said
that house guests are like fish
that... that... huh?
They're gone. Whoo-hoo!
And those bikers saw
that hard look in my eye...
you know that hard look I get sometimes,
and they ran away like schoolgirls
with their tails between their legs.
(screams like a girl)
Way to go, Dad.
Hey, where's the food?
And why aren't I at school?
Yeah, someone really
dropped the ball here.
Marge? Marge?
Dad, there's a note
on the back of your head.
Really? Read it.
Hmm. "Thanks for letting us
crash in your pad.
We had a very nice time."
Aw, that's sweet.
"PS: We've taken your old lady."
D'oh!
(Marge screaming)
Could you at least tell me
what you're planning to do with me?
Oh, don't worry. You're completely safe.
-None of us finds you sexually attractive.
-None of you?
Really? I could have sworn that Ramrod...
Mm. Well, did you see
that picture of me in...
And you still don't...
Sorry.
Hmm. Well, good, I guess.
Now don't worry, I'm gonna search
high and low for your mother,
but just in case I don't find her...
I want you to contact this agency.
Korean love brides?
I just don't want to be alone.
(loud rock music blaring)
♪ Well, look here, baby... ♪
HOMER: Excuse me, has anyone seen
a woman wearing...
(music stops)
(grunting)
That's more like it.
I'm looking for-- (yells)
(music resumes)
(moaning) Ahhh!
(groans) I'll show you.
(clearing throat) OK, we kind of got off
on the wrong foot there.
Long story short, my "old lady" was--
Uh? Whazza-- (moaning)
Some people never learn.
-(blow landing)
-HOMER: Ahhh!
All right, Satans,
-we roll out at dawn.
-Where are we going?
To the bikers' jamboree
in South Dakota. You'll love it.
Mickey Rourke's coming
and we're going to jump him.
You know, there's more to life
than boozing and roughhousing.
(all gasping)
Haven't any of you ever had a dream?
Yeah, I had a dream.
I was in this beautiful garden
pounding the crap out of
a shopkeeper and then--
No, no, I mean the dream
of a good job, a loving family,
-and a home in the suburbs.
-Oh, man.
To get all that you'd have to
kill, like, 50 people.
No, you don't have to kill anyone.
Not if you have jobs. And the first step
is an eye-catching "resumay."
No, I believe it's pronounced resume.
Actually both are acceptable.
Yeah, I did see some bikers
ride by here with a blue-haired woman
about ten minutes ago.
Said they were gonna spend the night
at Crystal Lake Campground,
section K, space 217.
I'm sorry I can't be of more help.
I guess I'll never find her.
And when you get a job interview
try not to call your employer a punk...
-or a skank.
-Makes sense.
Oh, don't call them skanks.
Uh, Miss Simpson,
I killed my pencil.
Broke. You broke your pencil.
I broke him.
That's right,
and what else have we learned?
Oh, oh!
That, uh, violence is wrong.
Excellent, Ramrod.
Civilized people solve
their disputes with words.
(screams)
Homer, stop! No, you don't understand!
(screaming)
-(groans)
-Marge... What do we do here, Marge?
He's using violence.
Talk to him.
Use your words.
Homer, Homer, stop it.
We've given up our violent ways.
We just wanna live peacefully...
-with your wife.
-No!
My wife is not a doobie
to be passed around.
I took a sacred vow on my wedding day
to bogart her forever.
Oh, Homie.
There's only one reasonable way
to settle this...
you and me, in the circle of death.
Oh, I just swept the circle of death.
(both growling)
(chanting) Fight, fight, fight, fight.
(both grunting)
Uh-oh. (screaming)
(Homer grunts)
We both knew it'd come to this.
You and me, chopper to chopper.
(yelling and grunting)
You know what I'm gonna do
after I kill you?
-Take your wallet.
-Never.
It was a gift from Newsweek.
(screams)
-(Homer whimpering)
-MARGE: Homer!
(grunting)
Give me back my wife.
OK, OK, you win.
I don't blame you
for wanting her back so bad.
A woman like that only comes along
-every couple of miles.
-Ah.
Hey, can we at least keep her
till the orgy in San Berdoo?
-What do you say, honey?
-No!
No dice.
(engines idling)
Good-bye, everybody.
Bye, Mrs. Simpson.
-Good-bye, Marge.
-Bye-bye, Mrs. S.
We'll stop at the nearest town
and mail our "resumays."
Resumays... it still sounds weird to me.
Why are we stopping here?
Taking care of some unfinished business.
-MAN: Hey...
-HOMER: (screams) Go, go, go.
(theme music playing)
Shh!
Captioned by
Visual Data Media Services