[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog ♪
♪ And Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[BEATBOXING]
Thanks for helping me record,
Finn.
No problem, Marceline.
Now, I'm gonna sing something
really personal,
so don't laugh at me.
I would never dream of it,
Milady.
[LAUGHS]
Now, start a slow beat and
keep it steady or
it'll mess up everything.
You got it.
[BEATBOXING]
Badda-badda, badda-badda.
♪ Daddy, why did you
eat my fries? ♪
♪ I bought them,
and they were mine ♪
♪ But you ate them ♪
♪ Yeah, you ate my fries,
and I cried ♪
♪ But you didn't see me cry ♪
♪ Daddy,
do you even love me? ♪
♪ Well, I wish you'd show it ♪
♪ 'Cause I
wouldn't know it ♪
♪ What kind of dad eats
his daughter's fries ♪
♪ And doesn't look
her in the eyes? ♪
♪ Daddy,
there were tears there ♪
♪ If you saw them,
would you even care? ♪
[BEATBOXING SLOWLY]
[SIGHS]
Huh?
Finn, you messed the beat up!
Marceline, if you're thinking
about your dad so much,
then why don't
you go see him?
He's not worth the effort.
Not worth what effort?
Well, first,
I'd have to draw
a circle with a happy face in
the center and then, uh,
douse it with bug milk.
Oh, yeah?!
[SIGHS] And then you're
supposed to chant something
like, "Maloso vobis com
et cum spiritum!"
[LAUGHS]
But I-I don't really
want to see him.
I'm still mad about
the thing with the fries.
[INDISTINCT MOANING]
Huh!?
What?!
Whoa, whoa!
Aah!
Marceline!
Finn, what the
heck did you do?!
I...
reunited you
with your family?
[GROWLS]
Is this kid
your evil servant?
I'm not evil,
Marceline's Dad!
I'm super good!
Super good?
[GROWLS]
[GASPS]
What are you doing?!
MARCELINE'S DAD:
Stealing your soul!
[SCREAMING]
Dad!
Ugh, you always
do stuff like this!
[LAUGHS]
Oh, Marceline.
I never know what's
gonna set you off.
MARCELINE'S DAD:
Whoa, is this the family axe?
Hey!
Did you turn it
into some kind of lute?
MARCELINE:
Give it back and get out!
'Kay, I'll go.
I've got business
to attend to anyway,
sucking up all
the souls in Ooo.
What?!
No!
See you kids later.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
My bass!
I've unleashed
evil onto Ooo!
We've got to stop him,
Marceline!
Fine, but I'm only coming
with you to get my bass back.
[WIND WHISTLING]
Hey, how do I kill
this guy anyway?
Finn, you can't kill my dad!
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
I didn't mean --
No, you literally
can't kill my dad.
He's deathless.
Oh.
[LAUGHTER]
Huh?
Who the fluff are you?
Um, well,
I'm sure not the
guy who's gonna
suck out your soul.
Good, 'cause that's, like,
my number-one fear.
Really?
Well, I know a
little exercise for that.
Want to try it?
Well...
First, close your eyes.
Okay. Aah!
You could've killed me!
Ah, but I didn't.
And now aren't you
thrilled just to be alive?
Yeah, I guess.
So what?
So, this next part will
be all the more horrifying.
[SUCKING FEROCIOUSLY]
[SHRIEKING]
There, below us --
a gathering of fluffy people!
Mayhaps they've
seen your father!
Marceline,
release the Finn bomb!
[WHISTLING]
Phosh!
[FLUFFY PEOPLE STAMMERING]
They're all freaked out.
It's because they're
scared of him.
[MOANING OMINOUSLY]
Mmm. My dad's been here.
Come on, let's go.
FINN:
No!
We've got to help this guy.
[MOANING]
I've got some soul food
that Jake packed for me.
You like, uh, collard greens
or country fried steak?
[MOANING]
Look, you want to help him?
Help me get my bass back!
How will that help him?
My dad stole my bass guitar,
Finn!
And when I get it back, I'm
gonna break it over his neck and
slam my dad back into the
Nightosphere!
[MOANING]
Oh, clam!
But first,
you got to return the
souls your dad sucked back to
these sad little husks,
right, Marceline?
[BLOWS]
Uh, sure.
Yeah, yeah,
we'll do that.
MAN:
So, I popped his head like a
cork and I says, "That's what I
think of expanding
Earth theory! "
[LAUGHTER]
MARCELINE'S DAD:
[LAUGHS] All right...
ALL:
Huh?!
I've got a joke, too.
What wears a dark suit,
is completely evil,
and is about to
suck out all your souls?
Your mama!
That's right --
I'm your mama.
[SHRIEKING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
MARCELINE:
Red rock pass.
If my dad wants
to get through
the mountains,
he'll have to go through here.
We can work together and
smash him with this rock.
And once he's smushed,
all the
souls will go back
to their rightful bods.
MARCELINE'S DAD:
[WHISTLING]
♪ Stompin' on ants ♪
♪ Suckin' their souls ♪
♪ Souls, souls, souls ♪
[AIR WHOOSHING]
[MUNCHING]
[GRUNTING]
Huh?
[HISSES]
So, finally taking a
run at your old man, huh?
[SHOUTS]
Daddy!
[LAUGHS]
Karate kick!
[HISSES]
Marceline,
keep him right there!
Hyah!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Oh.
[GRUNTS]
Karate chop!
[HISSES]
You can't destroy me!
N-no.
D-Dad,
I don't want to destroy you.
Look,
just stay out of my life!
You're not even alive!
You blew it, dude.
We're supposed to be a team --
A team who's sport is "Stop your
dad from sucking souls" ball.
[SIGHS]
I just want my dad
to care about me.
MARCELINE'S DAD:
Of all history's greatest
monsters, you are by far the
most evil thing I've
encountered.
Offer your soul to me,
dark one.
Wenk! Wenk!
No!
You can't have my soul!
I don't even --
Look, just get in here.
[GROWLS]
Wenk! Wenk!
Keep your crummy soul!
Wenk! Wenk! Wenk!
Wenk! Wenk! Wenk! Wenk!
Gunter, who told you
you could fly?!
Wenk.
[AIR WHOOSHES]
Huh?
No one sucks the life from my
penguins except me-- and maybe
polar bears because
that's just nature, Gunter.
You darest encroach
upon my domain!
You've raised my
frosty dander!
And for that I shall...
[GURGLES]
Aah!
I've have soiled my tunic --
completely by choice!
[AIR WHOOSHES]
Yes!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh, man!
He's growing huge!
[AIR WHOOSHES]
I'm gonna take him down!
Finn, you're like
an ant to him.
Oh, yeah?!
Well, this ant's about
to get in his pants!
What?
Uh...
You know, because I'm gonna
make him uncomfortable while
I release those souls!
Rrraaaaahhhh!
Give up those souls, Marceline's
dad, in the name of justice!
Huh?
Oh, Marceline.
Still following me?
I'll stop following you if
you give me back my guitar!
Now, Marceline...
No one flicks me in the
butt without my consent!
[SHRIEKS]
Whoa, whoa!
Aah!
[GRUNTS]
Whoa!
[GRUNTING]
The souls!
Lumpy Space Princess,
he got your soul, too?
What? Nah.
I totally saw Hot Dog Princess
get sucked in here,
and I wasn't invited?!
I was all, "What the lump?!"
So I'm crashing this party!
Uh...
well, I'll save you.
Yeah, I'll save all of you!
Unh!
Hyah!
[SCREAMING]
Unh!
In your face, Dad!
Give back that axe,
Marceline.
You don't respect it enough.
Well, you don't
respect anything,Dad!
Dad, I'm outta here!
But --
MARCELINE'S DAD:
Fine! Go!
I'm too busy sucking
to deal with you!
No, wait!
Marceline,
keep talking to him!
When he's talking,
he can't steal souls!
I said I'm out of here!
Diversion.
Need diversion.
[GASPS]
♪ Daddy, why did you eat my
fries? ♪
♪ I bought them,
and they were mine ♪
♪ But you ate them ♪
♪ Yeah, you ate my fries,
and I cried ♪
♪ But you didn't
see me cry ♪
♪ Daddy,
do you even love me? ♪
♪ Well,
I wish you'd show it ♪
Oh, my Glob, you guys --
drama bomb!
Marceline,
do you really feel this way?
Dad, I...
♪ Look her in the eyes? ♪
Marceline,
of course I love you.
Dad...
I'm sorry I ate your fries.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
It's okay, Dad.
It's --
it's really okay.
No, it's not okay.
They weren't even very good.
They were really cold.
I love you, Marceline.
Don't you ever doubt that.
I love you, too, Dad.
Oh, Marceline,
I am so --
[SHOUTING WILDLY]
[SCREAMING]
Maloso vobis com et cum
spiritum!
[HOWLING]
I'll see you in the
Nightosphere, you sick freak!
[GASPS]
Yes!
Finn!
How could you do that?!
How could I save the day?
How could you embarrass me like
that and then stab my dad?!
How could I embarrass-save you?
Whoa! Marceline!
[SIGHS]
I'm glad he's back
in the Nightosphere.
That was emotionally
exhausting.
I'm also exhausted
emotionally --
or, wait,
I-I mean, physically.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING,
SOULS SMACKING]
[CHUCKLES]
I've been meaning
to ask you --
What's with that
pocket on your shirt?
Oh, Jake's in here.
'Sup, Jake.
[FARTS]
FINN:
[YAWNS]
Man, why am I so sleepy?
Dude, we've been up for
like seven days.
For realsies?
Yeah, for realsies.
JAKE:
[SLOP!]
Remember?
First, we rescued the
Slime Princess from the
Ghost-ship Vortex.
Then we slayed
that fire dragon.
- [GROWLS]
- [GASPS]
And that took a
couple of days.
FINN:
And we went to LSP's
Quinceañera.
Oh, no way!
You guys made it!
JAKE:
Helped Peppermint Butler
with his goblin problem.
I swear I found
him like this.
I don't know
what happened.
We'll take care of it,
Peppermint Butler.
We rescued
Wildberry Princess
from the Ice King.
Aah!
I just want to be happy!
JAKE:
Then we captured
that Bandito.
[GRUNTS]
Thanks, you guys.
JAKE:
Saved that house.
Thanks, you guys.
JAKE:
And fed that duck.
Quack!
We've had a busy week.
I'm exhausted.
But happy.
Ha ha!
Good night, buddy.
Good night!
That's right, Finn.
Adventure till you drop.
[YAWNS]
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHS]
Hey, Jake?
Yeah?
Can you sleep?
No.
I can't sleep, either.
Yeah, what's going
on with that?
I don't know, but I've
got the
strangest feeling...
That we're
being watched.
Why is that horse
staring at us?
That's supercreepy.
Man, I just want
to go to sleep.
Maybe he's gone.
Not gonna be able to
sleep with that
horse watching me.
Let's just close the shade.
Ha ha.
Outta sight, outta mind.
Good work, Jake.
See you in the
morning, pal.
Ha ha!
[GASPS]
Why won't it stop?!
All right, man.
[YAWNING]
Let's just go push
him off that hill
or something.
Wait.
Maybe we can,
um, just politely
ask it to leave.
Sure, man.
Hey, get out of here, horse!
I want to go
to sleep,
and you're creeping
me the math out!
Whoa, man!
Let me try,
diplomat-style.
Pardon me, horse.
I beseech thou to
split from my
land this night.
But I welcome thee
to come back
from some luncheth
some other day, okay?
[SQUEAK!]
Forget it, man.
This horse is whack.
It's got poo brain.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
You're right.
We can try pushing it now.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
FINN:
Move, horsey, come on!
Aah!
[GRUNTING]
Come on, Jake.
Are you even pulling?!
[GRUNTING]
I'm super-pulling!
This horse is a
ridiculous weight!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Math to this.
What now, man?
I didn't want to have
to use my powers
on you, horse,
because
I'm so sleepy.
But you pushed
Jake too far!
[ROARS]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[SQUEAK!]
He shouldn't creep us
out from way over there!
Let's get back to bed, buddy.
Oh, yeah.
I'm so ready for bed.
I want to marry my bed.
Me, too!
[HOOFBEATS]
Huh?
[GASPS]
No more. No more!
Where you going?
JAKE:
I have an idea!
[ROARS]
I did it! Ha ha!
He can't stare at
us if he's blind!
Look, man.
[GASPS]
Wha...
Why?!
Stupid blindfold!
What's your deal, screwy?
Why are you messing
with us, huh?
FINN:
Jake!
That horse is whack
with poo brain.
Yeah, I know, Finn.
I diagnosed this
horse with
whacked-out
poo brain five minutes ago.
Dude,
poo brain means
we can lure it away from
here using music.
Everything brainless
likes music.
That's true.
You're a genius!
[SQUEAK!]
All right, horse,
prepare to be lured.
[PLAYS BEETHOVEN'S
"MOONLIGHT SONATA"]
Follow me, horsey.
FINN:
Jake, it's not luring!
Huh?
Hmm.
So Beethoven's not luring
enough for you, is it?
Well, how about
some Mozart?
[PLAYING MOZART'S
"EINE KLEINE NACHTMUSIK"]
Huh?
[HISSES]
Whoa!
Whoa! Aah! Aah!
Wha! Oh! Oh!
Stop!
You're luring snakes! Stop!
Huh?
Oh, nuts.
Let me try to lure
a mongoose.
Stop, man.
[GRUNTS]
N-o-o-o! Aah!
[SIGHS]
Dude, let's kill the horse.
What?!
I'm so tired, Finn.
No, man. We're not
killing the horse.
Okay, we won't
kill the horse.
We'll dress him up
like a bunny. Ha ha!
And get a giant hawk --
Aah!
- to kill him!
Wha?
[SCREECHING]
No, man.
That is wrong.
Eh.
Did I say that the
hawk would kill him?
I meant that the
hawk would
swoop down gently
and take him
away to a land
of sunshine and
love stuff and
take care of him.
Whoa.
That sounds awesome.
What do you think?
It looks like a bunny.
[WHISTLES]
FINN:
Come and get it, hawk!
JAKE:
Any hawks, come and get it!
Easy, stupid,
not-moving bunny.
Come on, hawks!
Let's go!
Ah!
Jake, I think I see
a hawk or two.
[HAWKS SQUAWKING]
Cause more commotion
to help the hawks.
Yeah!
Aah! Blblblblblbl!
Take the bunny!
Hey! Hey! Blah!
There they are!
They see our
commotions!
Right here!
Right here! Yeah!
- Yeah!
- JAKE: Right here!
- FINN: Here!
Aah!
[HAWKS SQUAWKING]
Grab a good hold
and fly away!
[BOTH SCREAM]
[GRUNTING]
The bunny! The bunny!
[HAWKS SQUAWKING]
What a beautiful sight.
We did it!
Back to sleep!
Ha ha!
Ahh!
Good night, buddy.
Aah!
It's in our house now!
That's obvious, Finn.
You don't have to
say that out loud.
Hey, this is all your
fault, dude.
If you weren't so
darn handsome,
animals wouldn't always
be staring at you.
You're just mad at me
for being...
handsome?
Well, you're the one who told
me to lure snakes.
Aah!
I told you to
lure the horse.
YOU lured the snakes.
There's even one here
in my underpants!
[SIGHS]
Wait a minute, dude.
Don't you see what this
horse is doing?
It's tearing us apart.
Oh, man. You're right.
We have to get rid of this
horse, for us!
I know, Bro. I know.
Oh, Finn,
this horse is
bringing us
together now.
This horse is a blessing.
What?!
Dude, you've lost it.
You...
Wait. Wait.
The horse is tearing
us apart again.
You're right.
It's about time I
showed this
horse who's the man.
What are you going to do?
Say that to me again.
Do.
Doo-doo.
I'm gonna kick that
horse in the bottom.
Oh, my Grod.
[WARBLE!]
The Ice King?!
I should go.
You were spying on us?!
That's none of your business!
He was trying to learn
our bedtime secrets.
[GASPS]
Were you?
[POP! WHISTLE!]
[GASPS]
He was!
Did you find out that I
sleep "in the nude"?
[HUMMING]
It's none of your
business how nude
I sleep, Ice King!
None of your business!
Gentlemen,
I'll see you later.
Hmm!
[WHISTLING]
[GROWLS]
Here's your sword, dude.
Thank you.
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLS]
Ugh!
Jake!
Jake, look out!
Whoa!
[TING!]
Tell us why you
were spying.
[GRUNTING]
No!
Ugh!
Aah!
Snakes!
Quick!
Chuck them at the Ice King!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[THUD! THUD! THUD!]
[WARBLE!]
What's he doing?!
He's using his ice powers!
[RATTLE!]
Ow!
Ouch! Hey!
Hey!
Is that all the
ice you have?
Hyah-yes!
Well, you should
really have more!
We don't need any more.
What if you
have guests?
Guests bring
their own ice.
Whoa! Oh!
Tell us why you were
watching us or we'll --
we'll cut off your
stupid head!
Yeah, and make it quick
'cause we're
both really sleepy.
Okay! Okay!
I'll tell you!
I was watching you...
to learn how to be happy.
Wha?
Huh?
It's true.
I would like to be happy,
like you guys,
but I have no idea how.
So you dressed
up like a horse?
Have pity on me?
I've been so sad
and miserable.
I cry all the time.
But whenever I
see you two,
you always look
so happy.
What?
They're just hopping
over each other.
So, yes,
I decided to spy on you,
dressed as a horse.
But I guess
my plan failed.
All I observed was you two
arguing over...
How to get rid of me.
[SNORING]
[POP!]
Hey!
Are you sleeping?!
Oh!
Is this it?
Sleeping?
Could it be that all I need is a
good night's rest?
Ahh.
I'm...
Still not happy.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander
through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪