(THEME SONG PLAYING)
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
FEMALE REPORTER: It's been 66 days
since the alleged murderers
of Vinci city manager Ben Caspere
engaged police in one
of the deadliest shootouts in state history.
The so-called Vinci Massacre
was determined closed
by Attorney General Geldof,
who used the conference
to announce his candidacy for governor.
Benjamin Caspere was a corrupt individual,
and he was killed
by the dangerous psychopaths
who engineered the tragedy in Vinci.
In examining how to protect
the state's most overlooked places,
I can finally only come to one conclusion.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(ENGINE STARTS)
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)
No comment yet from the governor.
In other news,
construction is expected to break ground
next week on the state's central rail line.
Help you with something?
Security, hmm?
Frank Semyon.
Stick with what you know.
You didn't have to quit. I told you that.
None of that went down right.
State came in.
Better to walk before they make you run.
We'd have helped you with that.
Geldof closed the case. You're clear.
He's saying the Mexicans did Caspere?
(SIGHS)
Anybody come to you asking about that?
Caspere, the Mexicans?
You and Teague, he talk to you much
when you were working together?
What did you come here for, Lieutenant?
Learned some things about Dixon.
Wondered if you knew anything.
Anything about what things?
He had a lot of photographs, some other stuff.
Might've been into some people.
(SIGHS)
Bought another Charger.
RAY: Yeah. I, uh...
I appreciate a good rut.
Well, I gotta tell you... Sorry about this,
but, uh, these row houses
are reserved for municipal employees.
And now that you're not one...
You fucking evicting me?
Hey, I got them to give you 60 days.
And I wanted to come tell you myself.
Come on, Ray,
you don't want to live here anymore.
I gotta go to work.
Sure.
(DOOR OPENS)
-(DOOR CLOSES)
-(EXHALES)
Gracias.
-(INDISTINCT TALKING)
-(BABY CRYING)
(TV PLAYING)
This is short $200.
I told you about this.
What do I tell Mr. Frank?
If he can buy beer, he can pay the rent.
Tell him to have it tomorrow,
or I'll put you on an ICE bus.
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Okay.
-(DOOR CLOSES)
-(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Jesus Christ.
MAN 1: Sexual harassment's a political tool.
You pay a compliment, a chick lawyers up.
MAN 2: That shit's about looks, too.
Difference between something like
what I'm here for and flirting
is how good-looking a dude is.
(SCOFFS) How's that fucking fair?
Now, this reflex
to project blame upon the victim
is going against
the sorts of habits we want to encourage.
Detective Bezzerides,
how do you feel about your actions?
Can I just ask,
what the fuck are you doing here?
(CHUCKLES)
Who wouldn't want her
sexually harassing you? Am I right?
See, that kind of thing there
could be considered inappropriate.
What? It was a compliment.
Oh, it's all right. It's all right. I understand.
But, uh, I don't know.
I mean, what can I say? I...
...just really like big dicks.
Yeah.
It's not just length.
Everybody's always talking length,
but it's fine.
I mean girth, too.
I really want to have trouble
handcuffing the thing, like...
Um, I'm not sure...
Uh, you know, that might be taken...
What?
I thought you wanted me to share.
This is a safe circle, right?
- Hell, yes, it is.
- Hey, let her share, man.
MAN 1: Yeah.
MAN 2: Yeah.
UNION REP: This man just received
a commendation for bravery
for one of the worst firefights
in LA County history.
I don't think anyone would argue
Mr. Woodrugh's facility for killing.
All right, damn it...
We're amenable to putting
this entire matter behind us. Hmm?
I just want to forget
that this terrible thing ever happened
and get on with getting my life back.
I did not do anything.
And I am innocent.
Black Mountain. Pandhar Village.
I wasn't there.
I wasn't at Pandhar.
How many men did you kill then?
How many at Vinci?
LINDEL'S ATTORNEY: We want any violation
involving this incident dropped.
And we want Miss Lindel's
earlier probation violation expunged.
That was your publicist, right?
Got the tabloids to try smearing him?
And now you feel okay
about dropping the allegation?
I've learned a lot in therapy.
I'm listening to my higher power.
I saved lives in Vinci.
Oh, and did they fully account
for whose bullets killed those civilians?
Yeah, they did.
I just don't want what happened to me
to happen to anybody else.
Detective Woodrugh
works insurance fraud now.
So you got him off the street.
Congratulations.
GILLETT: Are we still talking?
You're going for the deal, so take it.
She is a fucking liar.
GILLETT: I think we're past
all the name-calling.
We could still pursue
a civil case, Mr. Woodrugh.
Detective Wood rug h.
Rate's changed.
I need you to offer me
an old-times'-sake price.
Frank, man, this economy?
Start me a tab, Lloyd.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Frank Semyon?
Who are you?
Our name is Gonzales. We work here.
How's that, friend?
We had an arrangement with Santos.
Nobody's seen him.
Long time now.
We heard.
So, it is time to ratify our arrangement.
We never had one.
And I don't need partners.
Door's in the same place, amigo.
Can I help you, Cisco Kid?
(DOOR OPENS)
(SNORING)
(GASPS)
The fuck?
Frank, what the fuck are you doing in here?
Ship seems a little loose today.
Micro naps, Frank.
Michelangelo took them.
You remember Archeron Waste Management?
You sold it off.
After we sprinkled that corridor valley
with heavy metals.
So?
So, it's closed.
The guy I sold it to, Ali Komunyakaa,
who I never saw finish a beer,
gets drunk
and drives off a hillside in Ventura.
All of a sudden.
Not everyone
has our physical fortitude, Frank.
Like Caspere?
(SIGHS)
Ben was king fuck of pud-pulling.
You deal with pimps,
you get pimpish results, Frank.
Couple months back,
you said that there were outside
interests looking at the poker room.
Who?
Foreign interests.
Some fuck. I don't remember.
I haven't been in touch since.
Your boy hasn't moved to Oakland.
I've noticed.
No.
But you moved to Glendale.
Shame, that.
Hmm.
And your kid Tony.
My family ain't your concern, boychick.
You've been running girls
through the poker room.
Not so much as a heads up to me.
Penance is an extra five 3 month.
Get out of my office, Frank.
Next time, wait for an invitation.
I'll let you get back to your process,
then, Michelangelo.
Mr. Semyon.
You don't direct me, Khe Sanh motherfucker.
I'm Chinese.
Then go stand in front of a fucking tank.
GENA'S ATTORNEY: Mr. Velcoro
was a person of interest
in a state investigation into corruption.
HARRIS: Which yielded nothing.
GENA'S ATTORNEY: And after the firefight
in Vinci, he resigned under scrutiny
and pending a charge on substance abuse.
HARRIS: That's anecdotal hearsay.
There's no record of my client
being reprimanded for drug use.
JUDGE: Would you submit to a blood test,
Mr. Velcoro?
Absolutely, Your Honor.
Finally, Your Honor,
we are contesting Mr. Velcoro's paternity
and wish to establish
whether he even qualifies for father's rights.
- HARRIS: Objection.
- Fucking assholes.
JUDGE: You're not helping your case,
Mr. Velcoro.
GENA'S ATTORNEY: Mrs. Brune
was the victim of an assault
during the period of conception.
She believes the rapist to be
the biological father of her child.
I raised that boy. Am raising him.
It doesn't matter where he comes...
Our position is that it matters a great deal.
- I trusted you.
What does that mean?
I'll instruct the parties to refrain
from addressing one another. Period.
Now, I'm going to order
a paternity and toxicology test.
I'm ordering supervised visitation
until both the paternity
and toxicology results are in.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
What, I gotta get a stranger
to chaperone me and my son?
JUDGE: I've delivered my verdict.
Don't push me, Mr. Velcoro.
Any revision at this point
would not be in your favor.
She never looked at me like that before.
Like she hated me.
You really gonna test clean?
Yeah.
Yeah, 60 days now.
I want to fight this however I can.
Then pull some more cash together.
Tax-free or not, this is gonna get expensive.
FRANK: You need more money?
RAY: I need more money.
We're war rationing.
RAY: More work, then.
I can, you know, do double shifts at the Lux.
This is for your kid?
Hmm.
I might have a job for you.
The guy who bought the waste company
we used in the corridor died.
Place has been cleaned out.
I'm gonna start listening to the hot feeling
I got in the back of my neck.
I want you to tail Blake.
I want to know what his life is outside of me.
I can do that.
What's your feeling?
Running girls?
Am I in confession?
No.
Just, uh, never seemed like you.
Maybe you're just not very perceptive.
Ask you something?
You think those Mexes really did Caspere?
I don't know.
It was bullshit surveillance and...
The crash pad was a fucking meth factory.
Caspere died
with five million of my dollars, cash.
Stan's killed.
I'm squeezed out of the rail corridor.
The enemy won't reveal itself, Raymond.
Stymies my retribution.
It's like, uh...
Blue balls in your heart.
I'll see about some shifts at the Lux.
But follow Blake.
He's gotten too smooth for my peace of mind.
Oh, Paulie. Oh, no.
I'm getting married.
I love her.
Her name is Emily.
How pregnant is she?
Almost four months.
Mother of God.
Of all the stupid...
You're a good-looking white man.
And you want to get in shootouts
and become somebody's husband.
You could do anything you want.
Okay.
If I was a man, I'd have had the world.
Dumb bastard.
No, no.
No,no,no.
No. Fuck. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TV PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
PAUL: You took it.
How the fuck could you?
Took what, Paulie?
-(BANGS)
- You know what!
The money!
The money I brought back from Afghanistan!
Twenty-fucking-thousand dollars, Cynthia!
That bag?
Oh, Paulie.
You've been back four years.
I thought that was something you left for me.
Something I hid for, what, you to find?
That's my stake.
I'm having a kid.
Well, how would I know that?
I fucking bled for that money.
What did you do with it, slots?
Now listen.
You knew I was out of work.
I had every reason to expect a little help.
I'm making a family.
I know that don't mean shit
to somebody like you,
but it fucking matters to me.
Don't you fucking tell me
I don't care about family.
I was a dancer,
but I carried you.
And I brought you up alone.
You could have been a scrape job.
You wouldn't even know whose it was.
You ruined my career,
you ungrateful asshole.
I carried you for nine months,
and I've been carrying you ever since
with your weirdness.
You're strange.
All your good friends, the boys.
- Yeah, I know about you, Paulie.
-(SHUDDERING)
Yeah, I know.
You shut your fucking mouth.
You fucking poisoned cooze.
(GRUNTS)
-(CRYING) Paul.
-(CAR DOOR OPENS)
-(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
-(ENGINE STARTS)
Paulie?
- Wait.
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR DEPARTS)
I got this last week.
The police never found anything.
And you... You said you'd look into it.
She left this, what, at a PO box?
Attached to my old address.
The bill took a while to find us here.
When I paid it, they gave me the contents.
You settling in okay?
(TV PLAYING)
WOMAN: What's it mean?
ANI: Looks like a party.
Did you follow up with Sheriff's?
They got nothing. I hear nothing.
I didn't want to hand this over.
I thought...
When we talked,
I thought I could trust you.
Shit.
Fuck me.
Ain't you been warned about that kind of talk?
Sorry you're down here.
And I know you don't believe it,
but I never put you under that bus.
Sheriff already knew about you and me.
I took full responsibility.
Yeah, sure. You're a real prince.
You'll be out of here in a few months.
Look, somebody was trying to do you, girl.
And if you had a few more friends,
it might have been harder to get done.
Hey, hey.
You remember that foreclosure
we served a couple months back?
The missing girl, Vera.
Yeah.
You said you had looked into
her old roommate's phone records,
found an address
where Vera last called from?
Yeah, it was, uh, up north.
Could you get me that?
You're here now.
Help me out with this, and I promise
to do a fearless
and searching moral inventory.
(SCOFFS)
All right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
RAY: Loyalty's important
and usually painful.
One day you might find cause to ask yourself
what the limit is
to some pain you're experiencing,
and you'll find out there is no limit at all.
Pain is inexhaustible.
It's only people that get exhausted.
(INAUDIBLE)
- Tony, how are you?
- Osip.
- Always a pleasure.
- Hmm.
Approval is always essential.
Let me see.
-(TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING)
-(LAUGHTER)
These books are bullshit.
Whatever they were actually making here,
I can't figure it out.
That's expected. We can wipe that clear.
How about you? How are you doing?
Where is this Santos character?
Used to own the place.
Wherever he is, he ain't coming back.
This is backslide city, Frank.
I know what's going on out there
in the poker room now.
We're not just running some club. Come on.
What's happening now is we are surviving.
- All right? We are rebuilding.
-(BOTTLE POPS)
You were almost
-out of this kind of thing when we met.
-(SIGHS)
It was like you had a design.
That design does not work
once someone has stolen all of our money.
The design does not work
when I am knee-deep in dirt.
You don't bring a kid into a situation like this.
To what? Where is this going?
Excuse me?
I thought this was
a you-and-me thing, first off.
It is, but it has to be
about something more than this.
God, Frank, I helped, I know,
but I don't want to be
some fucking gangster's wife.
You know that word bothers me.
Because, me, I didn't ask for this world.
Hook“ as...
"Gangster?"
I was born drafted
on the wrong side of a class war.
So fuck that gangster shit.
You're a pimp now, Frank. A dealer.
I don't mix with those people. You know that.
I'm trying to stay above water
long enough so that we can...
Those people, everything they do,
they would do anyway.
Crime exists contingent on human desire.
These were the avenues left me.
And what's the expiration date for all this?
Our child?
Our child is part of the design.
And being legitimate is part of the design.
Right now it's on hold. You love me?
Then you're with me.
And maybe...
You love me if you're not with me.
I understand.
But say so,
so we don't have to be
on these goddamn eggshells.
Like I'm not me and you're not you.
(GLASS THUDS ON TABLE)
I don't think I can have kids, Frank.
I've been pretending
that it might not be that way.
I thought maybe...
But I went to the doctor alone.
I had more than one.
I had more than one operation, I mean.
- I had three.
- Three?
- The fuck are you...
- In my 203.
We don't think I can have one, a child. I can't.
You...
(SCOFFS)
You. But Why now, huh?
Maybe I'm less appealing
in current circumstances.
Why not tell me this
when I'm on top of the world?
Well, now I'm me.
And you're you.
And here we both are, out in the open.
So, who loves who?
EMILY'S MOTHER: This chicken looks good.
Did you use that recipe or...
- EMILY: I did, yeah.
- Carlotta's recipe?
I did.
I hope it comes out as well as she makes it.
- Here.
- Very nice.
Oh.
Thank you.
You know, we were just saying
that it'd be a good idea
for Mami to come stay with us a while
after the baby comes.
EMILY'S MOTHER: And the wedding?
Speed up, I say.
You're doing it, get on with it.
And you're gonna want me here.
You have no idea what you're in for.
Long nights. No sleep.
Might get kind of cramped.
I'll take the sofa in the living room.
I don't complain.
An entire week on a boat, I'm four.
Down in the hull eight days.
- Mama.
- What?
Is he gonna arrest me?
Thank Jesus they got you off that motorcycle.
Much better. And you wear a suit now.
Mmm, he's very handsome.
JORDAN: A couple of months back,
when I talked about adoption.
Jordan, I don't want...
I was thinking about you as a kid,
what it would have meant
if somebody had looked out for you,
if somebody had taken care of you.
There's no bandwidth for that right now.
I'm with you, Frank.
I love you.
But I don't want to see you
lose who you've become.
And I don't mean the money.
And I want to thank you
for seeing me like that.
It fucking tears me up
the way you're having to live now.
My problem is with you not coming to bed.
With both of us
being half in the bag each night.
I will find a way out.
The adoption, you were so definite.
I think you were saying no
to the kid that you once were.
You were saying
he was somebody else's problem.
I'm going home.
You should make some time to join me.
(POURING DRINK)
(SINGING) Waking up is harder
Spent all day in state's evidence control.
Then Vinci PD.
Nobody had an answer.
They just vanished.
Well, looks like them.
But these would have to be taken
before Caspere died.
How you been?
Drinking more.
My hands get fucked up.
Shake, like. You?
Talking to myself a lot.
Sticking to booze, though. That's new.
(SINGING CONTINUES)
So, the diamonds from Caspere's
safe deposit went missing from evidence.
It ain't exactly unheard of.
This girl's missing.
Disappeared shortly
before Caspere's body turned up.
What did we keep hearing
about? Escort parties.
Powerful men.
I couldn't make them all,
but that's a state senator.
Look at this one.
RAY: Caspere.
This ain't the type of party allows cameras.
What do you think? Some kind of blackmail?
You really think we cleared the Caspere case?
Those Mexicans?
They had items from Caspere's house there.
Fingerprints. What do you care?
These people put you in a cage, Bezzerides.
This girl's gone missing.
Nobody cares.
The interior's poisoned
and suddenly worth billions,
nobody cares.
Bunch of people got shot to shit,
nobody fucking cares.
Well,
I'm not a cop anymore.
And you're not a detective, last I heard.
Nope, you do security
for some comeback mobster,
and I log evidence.
I do consultation.
And you should get out.
You're too good for them.
You hear about the kid?
I mean, fraud investigations?
He was a fucking god warrior that day.
Yeah.
I talked to him.
He's miserable.
Belongs in the field.
Then he should quit, too.
Why didn't Dixon
make that place for a cookhouse, huh?
I don't know.
'Cause he's a wet brain alky.
- I have this new program, see.
- Hmm.
Because my powers of influence
are so meager in this sublunar world of ours,
I try to limit the people I can disappoint.
And I make sure to know the difference
between my obligations and somebody else's.
WOMAN: (SINGING) Breaking up is harder
- Than it seems
-(BILLS RUSTLING)
Don't do that. It was... It was...
It was good seeing you.
I didn't realize you had been on my mind.
(SINGING CONTINUES) Pictures on the mantel
Speak your name
Softly like forgotten tunes
Just outside the sound of pain
(TV PLAYING)
Some Lee Marvin movie on TCM.
Maybe something light.
I don't care what we watch.
What's it matter?
Your boss moved off all this.
- Pretty cleanly, too.
- That's my point.
We closed the Vinci investigation,
and Geldof announces a governor's run
with 3 suddenly massive war chest.
So, he had his hand out. That what this is?
You holding your hand out? Where's my out?
A real Attorney General
could do a lot of good in this state.
Has she got to you with her missing girl?
And you, what,
are you just looking for trouble?
I need to be in the field.
I'm not happy either how things played.
DAVIS: Geldof's actions are
the clearest indication of collusion
between the Vinci power structure
and the larger state institutions.
And it wouldn't hurt your job prospects
having dirt on the future governor.
I'm putting together
a confidential special investigation.
Stated goal is to track down Irina Rulfo,
the girl who pawned that shit,
brought you all to this place.
You know she was never brought in.
What's the real purpose?
Finding out who killed Caspere.
Uncovering evidence of collusion
between Vinci PD, mayor's office,
AG, and any other state bodies.
You know I'm not a cop anymore.
You have your PI license. I checked.
I could detail you as a state attorney's
investigator into a missing person.
I need people
who aren't gonna ping on our radar.
Word gets out what we're looking for,
they could shut it down like last time.
I got a job.
Thanks, but no.
That job gonna get you your kid back?
- What do you know about him?
- I know it's not looking good for you.
State Attorney's office could intercede
on your behalf with Family Services.
Recommendations, testimony.
I could make sure you keep your boy.
Well, they never found
the camera and the hard drive.
I don't think the person who shotgunned me
was one of those maniacs
at the shootout either.
While we're talking...
I want to look at some of this land up north.
Might have a line
on those hooker parties, too.
A lot of money there.
If it's a place deals go down,
we need to look at it.
You can't be cleared for this.
DAVIS: She's taking vacation time.
I'm placing her as a confidential investigator.
Means I don't have to register her.
I can follow up on the diamonds.
Why Caspere had them. Why they're missing.
Why the girl had photographs of them.
I guess my million-dollar question is,
why me?
You're out of the system.
You know Vinci PD.
Properly motivated,
you're a good bet to get the dirt.
ANI: Think it over, Velcoro.
Never too late to start all over again.
-(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
-(ENGINE STARTS)
You let me keep my kid,
I'm in.
Get started. You're on the clock.
I want daily reports.
Wasn't it you who thought
I was the worst of these people?
Saw that rumor
about you killing a guy was bullshit.
Figured maybe the rest of it was, too.
How'd you decide it was just a rumor?
I thought you knew.
They caught the guy.
I assumed maybe your ex told you.
What do you mean, caught the guy?
A few weeks back,
guy got pulled in for sexual assault in Venice.
DNA matched six unsolved rapes,
including your ex-wife's kit.
He'll get life, sounds like.
Get results.
I'll make sure you keep your kid.
(EXHALES)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(SHUDDERS)
JACOB: Frank, thanks for coming.
My position is you people owe me some land.
I'd have a hard time
convincing my board of that.
Imagine word of how that corridor's
gotten bought up over the past five years.
How exactly it came to be so cheap.
I can't see that being of any interest.
A waste removal service poisons park
and farmland along the central valleys.
A major California landowner
committed to real estate development
steps in.
You're reaching.
Archeron Waste Management is dissolved.
The guy I sold it to ran himself off the road.
You know anything about that?
There might still be something for you.
Why I called.
Let me ask, have you ever heard of Caspere
possessing a collection of...
Films?
Home movies.
A hard drive full of them.
If you're interested in doing something for us,
it could put you back in the corridor.
Somebody's got that hard drive.
I know the police
never found it in either of his houses.
What about the Mexicans?
Did Caspere?
I'm no detective,
but it might be a good place to start.
If you believe they're the ones that did it.
(SNICKERS)
Five parcels,
gifted,
I find that hard drive.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
Oh, yes, I remember you. Correct?
How can I help you?
I'm here to help you, Doc.
I'm here to help you
keep all that cosmetic work intact.
I can't imagine
we have anything to talk about, sir.
I fully cooperated with you last we spoke.
Well, maybe that's on me
not asking the right questions.
You and Chessani, girls, human trafficking.
You do their implants, nose jobs.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I'm a psychiatrist.
With a secondary concentration
in reconstructive surgery.
You, Chessani, Caspere,
you went back farther than you made out.
The girls, spill.
Your compensatory projection of menace
is a guarantor of its lack.
And it says something about the depths
of your misperceptions.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
RAY: Kind of day I've had,
seeing you pop a few stitches
might start to make up for it.
Pin-eyed motherfucker.
Hooker parties.
What you'd call affluent men.
Caspere attended.
Go.
I just do work on girls.
Make eights into 103.
Make sure they have
the proper prescriptions, that's it.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
The parties are a safe place,
a conclave for men of influence.
Talk motivations,
or I'll dig into that face-lift and yank.
(GROANS)
Caspere concocted the idea of the parties
with Tony Chessani.
Tony's a pimp with political ambition.
His father doesn't participate
in the gatherings.
Tony's service makes him friends
with those men of affluence you mentioned.
Lays the groundwork
for deals that Caspere facilitated.
What else?
I think both men used the occasions
to compile potential blackmail material
on their guests.
Rumored Ben had footage
of various important people.
McCandless.
Who?
He's the president
of Santa Clara Railroad Company.
It's smaller now. Called Catalast.
You go back with the Chessanis.
You put his first wife in a mental hospital.
Yeah, I did...
I did everything...
(SPITS)
I did everything I could for Helene.
Certain traditions of the Chessani patriarchs,
she had a difficult time with.
They are,
you might say, a highly inventive family.
(WHIMPERS)
(WAVES CRASHING)
ATHENA: Might be tough to get back
into that scene.
ANI: But not impossible, right?
Look for the pieces that are solid,
that haven't been hollowed out yet,
with, like, a smooth surface.
Say you lost your job, whatever.
Just some story.
You need to work the next party.
I don't... I don't know if I can get in touch
with those girls.
They weren't exactly stable.
I'm getting really good at this.
Not like hers.
If you can get a line on an invite,
I need to look into it.
This girl's missing.
There's other stuff.
Something else?
After that shooting?
You haven't talked about it.
Dad asks
and says that you won't call him back.
I'm busy. Work.
I wondered why
you were so hot to hit the beach today.
I tried weighing
if it was worth the price of a lecture.
I'm not in a spot to give those.
Did I tell you I got into CalArts?
You...
That's great.
- Awesome.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations. Jeez.
- Thanks.
I should, uh...
I should buy you dinner.
Maybe I can reach out
to a couple of the girls that I knew before.
For the straight-up purpose
of getting me into that party, okay?
Aren't you supposed to be behind a desk?
I just started my vacation.
Going anywhere special?
Yep. Guerneville.
You homesick?
For a place you hate,
you never really got that far away.
MAN: An excess of boron produces the color.
Now, most of your colored diamonds
are of low quality,
but something like these with such a rich hue,
it's very rare.
And the cut, octahedron,
these must almost certainly be stolen.
I told the other policeman the same.
What other policeman?
A few months back, a detective came by
with pictures of identical diamonds.
Wanted to know if anybody had come around,
maybe trying to sell them.
I told him I read the pawn sheets regular
and I haven't seen them listed.
He tells me they don't want
the stolens on any sheets.
(SIGHS) So, he gives me his card,
says to let him know if I hear anything.
- You still have that card?
- Yeah.
He was a portly man. Smelled like bourbon.
Flatulent, too.
Hmm.
PAUL: The thing is, when Dixon
came around about the diamonds,
it would have been
before we found the safety deposit box.
So he knew about the diamonds
before we found them.
And in which case,
why not put them on the hot sheets?
My ex-partner got this address
where the missing girl last called from.
Spot was on Caspere's GPS, too.
Mmm.
Seems like a happening place.
Used to be this commune here
on the River Valley.
GENA: Why did you say...
Uh...
So that man that you tracked down,
that was a lie?
No, I...
- I don't understand.
- They caught him weeks ago.
Called me in.
Richard came with me.
He's a serial rapist.
DNA matched the kit
that they took on me back then.
Did you just make it up?
What you said?
(STAMMERING)
Why?
Why would you do that?
So... So, what?
So you can make me think that
you were protecting me or something?
It's...
It's not... It's not what I...
That ruined everything, Ray.
That ruined you.
That's why I have to have the paternity test.
I have to know.
I have to know so I can
put it all where it's supposed to be.
I don't want to live this fantasy
about Chad with you anymore.
He should have the truth when he's ready.
This... (SIGHS)
This fake story
where we're made a family has to end.
He set me up.
Frank.
I don't know what that means, Ray.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
You serious?
About the adoption?
It meant something to me, what you said.
I want to thank you for telling me that.
(SIGHS)
- We both could have used different parents.
- Hmm.
Don't worry about kids now.
This is between you and me.
Seems like nobody's been home.
Want to call local? Get us in here?
(BIRDS CAWING)
(PANTING)
Now we're following birds.
Carrion birds.
(CAWING CONTINUES)
You smell that?
What, bird shit?
(FLIES BUZZING)
(GROANS)
It's arterial spray.
PAUL: Jesus.
The ceiling's clean.
No water stains.
I like it here.
Really.
We didn't need all that room.
Don't talk like that. Come on.
There's a guy, McCandless, Catalast...
Leave business.
We should sell the clubs.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Buy a farm.
Grow organic produce.
(LAUGHS)
- I could see us as farmers.
- Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
You would run for a plane
the first time you smelled shit.
Trust me.
I worked as a picker.
I was, uh, 14.
Fifteen.
You don't want to grow anything.
What about this guy?
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
There's something
I might be able to do for him.
If I can,
we can get it all back.
Do you trust him?
I trust self-interest.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
Stay here.
I'm fucking coming! Shut the fuck up!
Got a fucking problem?
You alone?
Yeah. Why?
You and me need to talk.
(ORCHESTRAL POP MUSIC PLAYING)