Ohh, yeah!
♪ Powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ To save the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ Here's the time to shine
when you're fighting crime ♪
♪ Power it up ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
♪ They can do the walk,
gonna do it all ♪
♪ We don't play ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
Oh! Yeah!
Ohh, my head.
Aah!
Buttercup! Buttercup!
I'm awake.
Can you remember anything
about last night?
Ugh, why?
Whoa.
What did we do?
Ohh!
I can't remember anything!
And I remember every
grocery list I ever made.
Hey, relax, would ya?
I remember last night
like it was yesterday.
We had a slumber party,
ate a ton of candy,
um... Ate more candy,
then we...
Hmm...
Kidnapped an angry bull
and put him in our kitchen?
There's a bull in the kitchen!
But he's not angry.
He's making breakfast.
Okay, okay, okay.
Maybe Bubbles knows.
Hmm.
Where is Bubbles?
Bubbles?
Hey, dude.
I can't find her anywhere.
We lost Bubbles!?
Okay, okay.
Let's not panic.
We just have to
retrace our steps.
We had a slumber party,
and, um...
Oh, yeah!
I remember now.
I was being my usual
supercool self...
♪ Party, party ♪
whoa!
♪ Party with my girlfriends ♪
♪ Ha! Party, party ♪
Hey, Blossom.
Great party!
Oh, thank you!
I'll allow myself
one piece of candy.
Mmm. I see why
they call it "fun size."
Hey, girls.
Don't stay up too late.
Remember, we're going to splash
city water park in the morning.
We'll be the first kids in
history to ride the rocktopus!
Now, now.
Go easy on the candy, girls.
No!
I mean, don't worry, professor.
We won't eat too much.
We promise.
All right, then.
Be good girls.
Hit it!
♪ Yum, yum, yum, yum ♪
Whoa!
♪ Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum,
candy, candy ♪
Ooh!
Raisins...
They're nature's candy.
Hmm. Well, that's a,
um, healthy alternative.
Candy!
♪ Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum,
candy, candy ♪
♪ Yum, yum, yum, yum, yum, yum ♪
♪ Candy, candy, candy,
candy, candy, candy ♪
We ate so much candy.
I don't remember anything
after that.
How are we gonna find Bubbles?
Hello?
Blossom! Hey,
I'm running some errands,
so I'll be back to pick
all you girls up in one hour.
Oh, okay, professor.
S-sounds great.
One hour?!
What are we gonna do?!
I knew we should've stopped
eating all of that candy!
We should've gone to bed early!
We should've listened
to the professor!
Ugh! Pipe down,
captain shoulda.
Sorry.
But how are we gonna find bu...
Bubbles?!
Mojo!
What are you doing here?
Me?
This was your doing!
Although I do admit,
the adorable kitties
were my idea.
I came by last night to enact
my latest, most ingenious plan.
I, mojo jojo, have once again
proven myself
a master of disguise.
And I have assembled the most
evil of pizza toppings...
Forbidden artichokes
of the Sahara,
transylvanian wurst pepperoni,
broccoli of the doomed,
and pineapple, 'cause I like it.
One bite, and the powerpuff
girls will fall beneath...
Hey, wait!
I'm not finished!
I said they'll fall...
They'll fall...
They... my power...
Curses!
Mojo!
Yeah, yeah,
but what about Bubbles?
Mojo does not know.
But he did hear something
about a monster and a bridge.
I remember.
We saved the bridge.
But the monster
must have taken Bubbles.
Let's fly!
No, no!
No, wait!
Hey, I thought
we saved the bridge?
Oh, no, not you guys again.
Hey!
What did you do with our sister?
Stay away from me, you maniacs.
Maniacs?
You were the one
destroying the bridge!
Me? It was you!
Wow, guys.
This thing is really comin...
Whoa!
I guess we know
who the real monster is.
Plus, this bridge was supposed
to be fixed by this morning.
Now those orphans
can't visit puppy island.
Darn.
Maybe next year, kids.
Aww!
Oh.
All right, all right.
Look, we're trying
to find our sister.
Did you see where she went?
I overheard something about
always wanting to fight a bull.
Oh, yeah!
Bullfighting!
How can we fight
without our muse?
Without El toro?
Bullfighters crying?
What a bunch of dorks.
Mata-dorks.
Ha. Nice one.
Hey, dudes with hats!
Have you seen my sister?
La flor de la lucha!
She has returned!
Uh, we were here last night?
None could forget
la flor de la lucha.
El flashback-o!
Ehh,
you don't look so tough to me!
So why don't you just
bring it on, mister...
Aah!
Hey, Mr. bull!
What does that mean?
I think it means, um,
he forgot his keys.
Blossom, churro me!
Sure thing!
Om-nom-nom-nom-nom-nom!
Touchdown!
Yay!
Ha, ha! Whoa!
It's raining roses!
Ha, ha!
But El toro disappeared
after the fight.
Help us find El toro!
Well, first I'm gonna need you
to talk quieter.
El toro isn't lost.
He's in our kitchen.
He wasn't cooking, was he?
Yeah, I think so.
I opened a jar of marmalade
for him.
Marmalade?
He'll be gone for days.
No bullfighting today!
Today just isn't our day, kids.
Aww!
Oh, come on!
We're running out of time
to be first on rocktopus.
I think finding Bubbles is
more important than rocktopus.
Stop saying that!
I didn't even
say "rocktopus."
Whatever.
Let's just go.
All right. Where?
Hello.
I am still here.
La flor de la lucha did say
something about an arcade.
Oh, yeah!
The arcade!
Bubbles was in the ball pit.
Bubbles!
Where are all the balls?
Oh, you're too late.
Those balls got changed out
this morning.
Have you seen our sister?
She was in there last night.
Well, whatever was in there
got smashed...
...Rearranged...
...Melted down...
Ohh!
...Bedazzled, embroidered,
squashed again,
and turned into novelty hats.
No!
What are we gonna
tell the professor?
The truth, Buttercup.
I'll try anything once.
Ha, good one.
Oh, girls!
Where have you been?
You had me worried.
Professor, we're sorry!
You said not to eat too
much candy, but we did.
A-a-and we destroyed
a bridge.
And Buttercup became a matador.
And these orphans
kept following us around,
and... and...
And now Bubbles is...
A hat.
I'm a hat?
Bubbles!
We were so worried!
Sounds like you all
had quite the night.
We shouldn't have
eaten so much candy.
We feel terrible.
In more ways than one.
Blech.
Well, it seems you girls
certainly learned your lesson.
Now, then, I believe we can
still make it in time
for splash city.
Actually, professor,
we have a better idea.
Thanks for the tickets to
splash city, powerpuff girls!
I am really proud of you girls,
giving away your tickets
like that.
Eh, rocktopus
ain't going nowhere.
Rocktopus!
Well, since the day's free,
why don't we get some ice cream?
Hello? Little help?
My cuticles are getting dry!