Ohh, yeah!
♪ Powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ to save the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ here's the time to shine
when you're fighting crime ♪
♪ power it up ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
♪ they can do the walk,
gonna do it all ♪
♪ we don't play ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
Oh! Yeah!
Ah, yes, the annual
school field trip to the zoo.
And so you see, children,
that is why you should not try
to kiss a giant python.
Oh, boy.
Call for help.
Um...
Are there any questions?
I have a question.
When do we get to see a unicorn?
Aw, geez, bubbles.
Not this again.
There's no such thing
as unicorns.
There is so!
I can prove it.
Behold...
A real life unicorn horn.
♪ Totally real unicorn horn ♪
Stand back, everyone,
I shall summon one.
Come on, bubbles.
Everyone knows
the only mythical creature
that actually exists is bigfoot.
All righty, um...
Who wants to go
to the gift shop?
Yay.
Maybe everyone was right.
Maybe unicorns aren't real.
A unicorn!
Aaah!
We're going to be
best friends forever,
and I'll name you "pointy".
Bubbles, the bus is
about to leave.
Whoa. How'd that horse
get loose?
Buttercup, this isn't a horse,
it's my magical, mystical,
best friend unicorn.
Uh, hate to break it to you,
bubbles, but that's no unicorn.
That's a plain ol' pony.
No way. Ponies have
shorter legs. It's a Colt.
A Colt?
What's a Colt?
A baby horse.
Then what's a filly?
Uh...
A horse with... Attitude?
Either way,
it's definitely not a unicorn.
It's just...
sad.
Well excuse me!
I may not have a horn,
but I do have a heart!
And in that heart,
I know I'm a beautiful unicorn!
You can talk?
Yes, I can talk.
But who cares?
I'll never be anything more than
just Donny, the wannabe-corn.
Whoa, drama bomb.
We'll get the professor
to turn you into a real unicorn.
What?
Bubbles, I don't think
that's a good idea.
Of course it is.
You'll be a real, live unicorn!
Yeah!
And I'll be friends
with a real, live unicorn.
Yeah!
And everyone will see
how wrong they were!
Bubbles!
You're an incredible person!
It'll be the most awesomest
thing that ever awesomed.
Speaking of awesome,
the townsville pickle museum
is having its grand opening.
Here we have the world's
oldest pickle.
And this a pickle made entirely
of used toothpicks...
My toothpicks.
And here we have our hall
of pickledents,
which are pickles
in the shape of presidents.
This one resembles Dolly parton.
Hey! Dolly parton
was never president!
Well, not yet, anyway.
Gee, bubbles, I don't know.
Professor, please!
Well, I suppose I could
try and turn him into a unicorn
using the transmorgrifying ray
I just happened to finish
this afternoon.
But it hasn't been
properly tested.
Professor, he needs this.
I need this!
Well, it's up to you, Donny.
Is this something
you want to try?
As long
as my b.F.F. Bubbles
says it's a good idea,
I am down.
Completely trust you, brah.
I've detailed out
a comprehensive list
of possible risks and side
effects from this procedure.
Okay.
I need you to be aware
of all the consequences.
Yep!
This is your body,
and it's a serious choice.
Got it!
Thoroughly weigh your options...
Uh-huh.
As you read through
this document in it's entirety.
Eh, I skimmed it.
This is gonna be
the best day of my life!
Thank you, bubbles!
You're welcome, Donny!
All right, girls,
vision-safety time.
So...
How beautiful am I?
Um, well...
You look very...
Majestical.
Honestly, that's not as bad
as I thought it was going to be.
Oh, man.
I feel different already.
Aah!
Um, professor?
Bubbles, what have you
done to me?!
Best two out of three?
No! Ragh!
I hate science!
Wait!
Donny, come back!
O...Kay.
Now it's as bad as I thought
it was gonna be.
How could you hate science?
That's what you got out of that?
Hey, what is that?
Don't look at me!
Oh, no.
No, no, no!
Not again!
Huh. Bigfoot.
I knew it.
This is the crystal pickle
of despair.
Legend has it that if it breaks,
bad luck would rain down
upon us forever.
A freak!
I am not a freak!
Oh, that reminds me...
I've gotta mail a letter.
Ooh, uh, hello.
Donny, you have to calm down!
Calm down?!
Look at me.
I'm a freak.
We are no longer b.F.F.S!
No!
Whoa.
He's a freak.
He is not a freak!
He is my friend!
Well, your "friend" is
terrorizing the city.
Just let me talk to him.
I knew this was a bad idea.
Donny!
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
I put you in danger
just because I wanted
to be friends with a unicorn
and prove to everyone
they were real.
Well, they're not real!
You were wrong!
We were both wrong!
Listen to me.
Unicorns are real,
and this proves it.
Because I summoned you.
And you appeared.
Stop blowing that stupid horn!
Donny, in your heart of hearts,
you know you are
a real, live unicorn!
No! In my heart,
I know I'm a monster!
Oh, no! Bubbles!
I...Didn't mean to.
Oh, no.
What have I done?!
Aah!
Whee!
Museums sure are exhilarating.
Bubbles?!
Are you okay?
Wha...
Where's Donny?
I'm sorry, bubbles, he...
Huh?
He's turned back into a pony!
But how?
Um, you guys...
I can't believe
this is happening!
Oops. My bad.
Donny.
Will he be okay?
He'll be just fine,
lady bubbles.
We heard the call
of your summoning horn.
Sorry we're late.
Somebody didn't want
to use the GPS.
I knew a shortcut.
Well, I thought I did.
Stallions.
Wait, which ones are stallions?
They're like colts, but...
Oh, forget it. Who cares?
B-bubbles?
Donny, I'm so sorry.
I feel terrible.
I'm sorry, too, bubbles.
I blamed you, but, heck,
I didn't think about
the consequences, either.
I know you were only
trying to help me.
I mean, dude, I so wanted
to be a unicorn, too.
But, Donny,
you already are a unicorn.
Uh, okay, bubbles,
I get the sentiment,
but, honestly, this is getting
kind of redundant.
No, she's right, Donny.
Mom? What are you doing hanging
out with a bunch of unicorns?
You're old enough now
to know the truth.
I had to wait until you went
on an intense journey
of adolescent
self-discovery.
Whoa! What is even
going on right now?!
I mean, you probably could've
figured it out sooner
if you'd ever
cut that hair of yours.
What is that, a zit?
It's a horn!
Oh, Donny, I'm so happy for you.
This was the best day ever!
And be sure
to grab a pickle-chute,
available at the gift shop.
Oh, what a world!
Oh, thank you,
mythical unicorns.
Donny, it's time for you
to say good-bye.
We're all needed back
at the unicorn coalition
alliance brigade headquarters.
It sounds made up,
but it's totally not.
Bubbles, you are my b.F.F.
For reals.
It's beautiful!
Use this to summon me anytime.
Or just shoot me a text.
You know I will all the time!
Ugh, hopefully not all the time.
Bye-bye, Donny!
- We'll miss you.
I actually connected
with you guys!
Told you unicorns were real.
And so,
the day was saved thanks to...
♪ The unicorn coalition
alliance brigade headquarters ♪
♪ it sounds made up,
but it's totally not ♪