Ohh, yeah!
Oh! Yeah!
Sensitive thugz
is the best band of all time.
All time.
And my main man Dax
is like the baddest boy
the world's ever seen.
He takes guff from no one.
Except the people he lets in.
And their manager, Kevonne, has
such an eye for organization.
He'll keep
their profiles growing
long after they become obsolete.
That was "I want to listen
to your problems, gurl"
by the sensitive thugz.
And now, the moment
you've all been waiting for.
It's your last chance
to win tickets
for their sold-out show
tonight.
Get those phones out
because the tickets will go
to the listener who
can answer this question...
If chance, the lead singer
of the sensitive thugz,
could have any animal as a pet,
what would it be?
Hello, what's your name?
This is Bubbles
from central Townsville.
Chance would have a wallaby
because they're sweet,
but also tough, just like
the sensitive thugz.
True dat, girl.
Congratulations, Bubbles!
Because you
and one guest of your choice
are seeing sensitive thugz
tonight!
Ahhh!
I did it, I did it, I did it!
You won, you won, you won!
I can't believe I won!
Now you just have to decide
who to take!
Yeah, 'cause you can...
Only take...
One of us.
Oh, yeah! 'Cause there's
only... Two tickets.
So... Bubbles.
Who are you, uh,
thinking of taking, huh?
Um... I guess... Um...
I'll take...
that phone call.
Hello, this is Bubbles
from central Townsville.
Mayday! Mayday!
Mayor?
What's the matter?
There's something wrong
with my plane.
It doesn't seem to have...
A pilot.
Aah!
Don't worry, mayor!
We're on our way.
Let's go!
The mayor's distress signal
was coming from somewhere
near monster island.
That's a dangerous place!
Look!
There it is!
Hey, it's the mayor's plane!
But where's the mayor?
This place is creepy.
What's that?
Oh, my gosh!
He's so cute!
But not as cute as you, girl.
Be careful!
He might be dangerous!
His name is Frederick,
and he's not dangerous.
Yeah!
Fight, fight, fight, fight!
Come on.
We have to find the mayor.
Aw, man! That fight was
just getting started!
That spiky monster was
gonna do something big!
You see?!
Good thing you found
the mayor's tracks, Frederick.
Hey, Bubbles!
Did you know that chance's
middle name is also Frederick?
Oh.
No, I did not.
Well, there's a lot more
sensitive thugz knowledge
where that came from
that I'd be happy to share
with you later tonight.
She'll just yammer on
about that dorky nonsense
forever.
Hey!
At least I'm a fan.
A fan of your own voice.
Oh, is that right?
Well, let me tell you something.
Girls!
We're never gonna find the mayor
if you keep fighting like that.
Now, be nice to each other.
Fine.
Okay. Now hug.
Say "I love you."
I love you.
Now say "I'm a buttzilla."
I'm a buttzilla.
You're a buttzilla.
Hey! What? Wait!
Blossom!
Say you're a buttzilla.
Aah!
That was...
Um... Unexpected.
I think he smells something.
Um... Where are we?
It looks like we're inside a...
Volcano!
Jinx!
You can't talk till someone
says your full name, dude!
That's for calling me
a buttzilla.
Aww. Are you two
getting along now?
Sure are.
Isn't that right, Bloss?
That is just so very great!
The mayor's hat!
He must have been down here.
She seems... Nice.
Bubbles, we really got to work
on your definition of "nice."
Don't you think
using your ice breath
is kind of like talking?
Bloss-sister?
Oh, snap, girl.
You best recognize
the rules of jinx.
Don't worry, Bubbles.
I got this.
Hey! Lava lady!
You're not so hot.
Dax would be proud.
Yeah, girl.
You know I am.
Yay!
That was awesome, Buttercup!
Yeah, well.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Hoo-hoo!
Ohh, it's about the sensitive
thugz tickets, isn't it?
Well, if you're
gonna be like that,
then I'm just gonna give
my other ticket to Buttercup.
Yes!
Sorry, Blossom.
I just think that...
She said your full name, girl.
Now you can unbottle
those feelings
and spill out your heart, girl.
Buttercup jinxed me as payback
because she called herself
a buttzilla alone!
She doesn't deserve the ticket!
Whatever, dude!
You're just jealous!
I totally deserve that ticket.
You do not!
Oh, and the volcano
is about to erupt.
So you guys never
stopped fighting?
She never stopped first!
That doesn't even make sense!
Buttercup, I am not
taking you anymore.
What?
Yes!
It seems like the only person
I can count on is frede...
Rick.
Frederick!
Come on, bubbs!
You... Gotta... Decide!
Pick... One...
Of... Us!
Eeeeee-nough!
Frederick!
All right. There's only one way
to settle this.
Rap battle.
Bubbs is the judge.
Wait, what?
Unh! Yeah!
Well, my name is
Blossom, and I'm here to say...
No! No rapping!
You two have gotten so greedy
that you forgot why we're here!
We need to find the may...
Frederick! Help!
Wow, super helpful.
Glad to have you
part of the team, pal.
Aw, man!
Being devoured by monsters
is really low
on my list of ways to die.
Bubbles...
We... I was being selfish,
and I completely lost focus.
And we've been really lame
with the fighting
and the jinxing and...
And...
We... we're sorry that
we got you into this mess.
Aaah!
Hey, girls!
H-how did you even...
When did you...
How did you not get
eaten by those monsters?
Oh, these monsters are darling!
They go nuts for my pickles!
So all you had to do
to keep the monsters tame
is feed them pickles?
Yep! Ooh,
and that was the last one.
Okay.
Time to go.
Sorry we were being
such buttzillas.
It's all right, girls.
But I do think I know who
I'm gonna take to the concert.
Please be me, please be me.
Is it me?
It is me, right?
Tell me it's me.
You can tell me it's me.
Hey. This song goes out
to our number-one fan, Bubbles.
Oh, my gosh!
It's called "I'm a crazy
dangerous monster"
when it comes to holding
your hand, girl."
Yay!
I'm a crazy monster, girl
Ah, lunchtime
at the school cafeteria.
Cute ribbons.
Ooh, glitter!
Scrapbooking is so awesome!
Yay!
Dudes!
It's sloppy Joe Tuesday!
They should make this a holiday.
Um, what happened
to your forehead?
Oh, that? Funny story.
Check it.
So there's this guy
at the construction yard, Mac.
So he says his forklift
can crush anything... anything!
And I'm all like,
"I'm stronger than that."
And anyway,
I arm-wrestled a forklift.
Oh.
Interesting.
Uh, hey, Buttercup.
Do you want to, uh, sit with us
and, you know, chew?
We're talking about
scrapbooking!
Uh, yeah.
No.
That's not really my thing.
I'll just grab a seat
over there.
Pfft.
Scrapbooking.
Hey.
You're Buttercup, right?
Who's asking?
I'm Maylyn,
head of the derbytantes.
Dig your head scrape.
You get that from fighting
a monster or something?
Forklift.
Dig your skates.
Yeah.
We never take them off.
We grind on skates.
We skateboard on skates.
We even do pottery on skates.
Best work yet.
Thanks!
Whoo! Whoo!
We also play deathball
on skates.
Whoa. Back up.
What's deathball?
You should find out.
Hey, Buttercup.
Who are your friends?
Do they want to come
scrapbooking, too?
Deathball.
Hey, girls.
Princess morbucks?
I see butterbutt has
left you for new friends.
No, she's just off...
Playing deathball...
With some people.
Well, if you need a replacement,
I know a stunningly
gorgeous redhead
with loads of sass
and gobs of cash.
Mike drop!
We don't need a replacement.
Come on, Bubbles.
We'll see Buttercup later.
Sure you will.
"Later."
Where's Buttercup?
Deathball!
Ow!
Where's Buttercup?
I miss Buttercup.
Deathball!
Buttercup, Buttercup, Buttercup!
Hey, guys. You see that
butt-whupping I just gave?
Oh, yeah.
You did great.
Thanks.
So... What's up?
Well, we noticed that
you've been hanging out
with your new friends a lot,
and we thought
that we would come by
and bring you some lunch
and stuff.
We brought leftover lasagna.
Everything chill
over here, Buttlyn?
Uh, Buttlyn?
That's my new nickname.
Everyone in the gang has names
that rhyme with "lyn."
This is Maylyn.
'Sup?
Jaylyn.
Yo.
And bobbysuzerae... Lyn.
Hi, guys.
Come on, Buttlyn, let's bolt.
See you cats on the flip side.
Buttercup, wait!
I should have called it
death-lasagna.
We've lost our sister,
haven't we?
Don't be silly, Bubbles!
Buttercup is just being,
well, Buttercup.
I guess.
Hey, super gal pals!
Looks like there's an opening
now that your sister
ditched you.
Ahh!
She didn't ditch us.
Yes, she did.
And I want to be
a powerpuff girl.
There is an opening, after all.
She does have a point.
No, she doesn't.
Bubbles, she can't even fly.
Powerboots!
Big deal.
You don't have any superpowers.
Powergloves!
Well, you don't even
have a costume.
Power-threads!
So am I in or what?
Just... no.
Look, Buttercup is our sister.
And we're a team.
She'll always be there for us,
no matter what.
Hmph!
Oh, really?
Well, then, let's find out.
Initiate monster attack.
Monster needed 2.3 miles.
Showtime.
Fear me
for I am an evil monster!
Feel my wrath,
oh, citizens of Townsville!
Trouble!
Let's go, Bubbles!
But what about Buttercup?
She'll be there!
We'll just see about that.
Man, this is the most fun
I think I've ever had.
I know, right?
No thanks to you losers.
Awesome!
Oh! Scoundrels.
Whoa, no!
My sisters need me!
Whoa.
What's your hurry, Buttlyn?
We're about to order some pizzas
and huck 'em on the rooves!
I'll hang later.
Duty calls.
But the pizzas will get cold.
We'll order more.
I got to go.
Sorry, Buttlyn.
Can't let you do that.
Maylyn, what do you mean?
Princess moneyface or whatever
is paying us to keep you away
from your sisters.
Moneyface?
Moneyface.
Morbucks?!
Yeah. Yeah.
Moneybutt.
She paid us
to hang out with you.
So you're not really my friends.
No, we are.
You're cool and all,
but we need monies
for skates and junk.
You understand, right?
The only thing I understand
is that my sisters need me.
Now get out of my way.
Where's Buttercup?
She'll be here any sec.
Huh?
Yah! Hah! Ugh! Yah!
Huh! Ha! Nyah!
Need someone to lend a hand?
My offer's still on
the very expensive table!
Fine.
Whatever...
You... Want!
I want to be a powerpuff girl!
Okay!
You're a power...
Puff... Girl!
Yes!
And soon I'll be
the only powerpuff girl.
Excuse me.
I think we're done here.
Monstering complete.
That was a four-star performance
if I ever saw one.
You better give me
a good rating.
Oh, the folly of my ways!
This is for Blossom!
This is for Bubbles!
This is for me!
This is also for me!
Skates.
Buttercup.
That kid's all right.
Buttercup didn't come.
Maybe she...
Thanks for making me
part of the team, girls.
I got you a little something
as a token of my appreciation.
Ooh. Pretty.
Hey!
It's an necronium diamond...
Indestructible.
Ah, because
a true superstar... me...
Knows when it's time to go solo.
After all, I'm pretty much
the most beautiful,
most talented,
most powerful, most...
Most annoying.
Buttercup!
Stand back!
Hey, girls.
Look what I got
for my half un-birthday.
This is going to be too easy.
Aw, man.
Wait. Check this out.
It came with the suit.
You'll
never save your sisters now.
You like that?
'Cause it's true.
Yeah, not really true,
like, at all.
You see, the derbytantes,
we protect our sisters,
and that includes
sisters of sisters.
I thought you were
working for moneypants.
Why should I trust you?
Yeah, you're supposed to be
working for me.
Buttercup earned our respect.
You just paid for it.
Come on. If there's
one thing we're good at,
it's thrashing stuff.
Rock and roll, ladies!
Blades up, girls!
Anyone for a game of deathball?
Deathball!
Okay, we'll call it a draw.
Aaaaaaah!
Buttercup! I thought you were
gone forever and ever
and ever and ever and ever!
Sorry I got so carried away
hanging out
with the derbytantes.
I guess I forgot
who my real friends are.
We're not just friends,
we're sisters.
Yeah! And we're sorry
we replaced you with morbucks!
Wait, what?
And so, once again,
the day is saved
by the powerpuff girls!
And deathball!