Ohh, yeah!
♪ Powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ to save the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ here's the time to shine
when you're fighting crime ♪
♪ power it up ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
♪ they can do the walk,
gonna do it all ♪
♪ we don't play ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
Oh! Yeah!
Now, class, I've got a really
cool surprise for you.
Is it an ice-cream party?
No.
Early-dismissal party?
No. Even cooler than that.
Hmm.
Ufo party?!
What is it, Ms. keane?
Ms. keane has left the building.
My name is sansa syntax,
the grammar wizard!
And it's time to begin
this year's language unit!
Yay.
What?!
That's the opposite of cool.
Who can tell me a little bit
about the magic
of dangling participles?
Why don't you check
your spell book?
Very funny, buttercup.
But please save your comments
for later.
We need to get through this.
Now, do any of you know
when to use "you and I"
instead of "you and me"?
Don't ask me. Eye don't know.
Buttercup, please!
I know this isn't what you
wanted to do today,
but I am trying hard
to make it fun for you guys.
The grammar unit
is really important, and...
- Grammar?
- More like
okay, buttercup!
That's it!
There is a time and a place
for goofing off,
and it's not in my classroom.
I hate to do this,
but I'm going to have
to send you to the...
Principal's...
Rainbow!
Wow. What was I saying?
Uh, probably nothing important.
Oh, yeah!
I was just about to give you
a hug,
because you're just such
a special little lady.
Special?
I thought I was being bad.
Yes!
You're so good at being bad.
You always do what you want,
and it's so much fun!
Let's all do what we want!
Yay!
I want to sit upside down.
And I want to eat candy.
What about the grammar lesson?
I thought it was, like,
really important or whatever.
Grammar can wait till next year.
Now, how's about that
early-dismissal party?
Okay!
Yay!
Whoo!
Early-dismissal candy party!
Today is awesome!
Today is the absolute worst!
We made dioramas
in geography class,
and I worked really hard,
and the teacher gave me
an a-plus!
And that's a problem why?
He gave everyone an a-plus!
I sneezed in a box.
Aah!
If grades are meaningless, then
I am meaningless!
I can't live in this world!
Mellow out, man.
Everyone's just having
a good time.
Check this out.
I can get away
with whatever I want.
Buttercup, that was hilarious!
I want to give you a big hug!
No way, Barry!
Get ahold of yourself.
Barry wants a hug!
Hug party!
Buttercup, I think something
is amiss in townsville.
He-e-y!
I wanted to go first.
Hey! I wanted to go first, too!
Yay!
Hey. I want to go outside today.
And I want to let you
go outside today!
Yay!
Huh. Have you seen bubbles?
I never thought
I would say this,
but I can't handle
any more hugs.
Why is everyone acting
so insane?
I'm not sure.
Let's go ask the professor.
He's the sanest person we know.
Ya-ay!
Whee!
Oh, you can't get me! Look out!
Yay!
Hello, girls.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you in the lab?
Oh, I've decided to stop
sciencing for a while.
Now I have way more time
to hang out with sprinklor.
You're gonna get wet.
But, professor, isn't sciencing
kind of important
for, you know, society?
Whoa.
Relax, dudes!
Kick those heads back
and soak up
some of this sweet rainbow.
The rainbow?
That's why everyone's.
Acting so tweaked?
Okay, girls!
Let's go investigate
this "miracle of nature."
Have fun, girls.
If you need me, I'll just be
here spending some "q" time
with my new bestie.
Oh, look out!
He's gonna get you!
You're gonna get wet.
♪♪
What is this place?
Whee!
My dream!
And my nightmare.
Wait for it!
Wait for what?
Wait for it.
Waiting...
It's party time!
♪ Je ne sais quoi ♪
Yay!
I'm allegro,
that happiest panda
in the world!
Want a hug?
O.M.G.! Yes!
I can't...
Can't what?
Even.
Can't even what?
Oh, like,
she literally can't even.
Whatever.
It's just a cruddy bear.
Hey, allegro.
We're looking
for the owner of this rainbow.
You know him?
I do!
Because it's meeeee!
Want a hug?
Dude, no! Stop asking that!
Uh-oh. Someone seems unhappy.
Yeah. We're unhappy.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Your dumb rainbow's
making everyone act
like huge weirdos.
So get your creep party
out of our town!
Allegro doesn't understand.
Don't you want everyone to party
and have fun?
No! Because it's chaos.
And everyone gets an a-plus
and I worked so hard
on that diorama!
So hard! It matters!!
Shh. We know you worked hard.
Work? Oh, man.
You guys are bumming
allegro out.
You need to get with the party.
Party lobsters!
Jerome, teach these girls
how to lighten up.
Guys!
Are you okay?
Dude.
I am more than okay.
I feel slightly more cheerful
than I normally do.
Huh?
Ya-a-ay!
Now things are getting fun.
It's party time!
♪ Je ne sais quoi ♪
Ugh. Gross.
Come on, buttercup.
You love to party.
Isn't this what you wanted?
You guys, stop!
This isn't you!
The town needs us.
I'm sure they're fine.
I guess buttercup just doesn't
want anyone to have fun.
That's not true.
But there's a time and a place
for having fun
and doing what you want,
just like Ms. keane
was saying earlier.
Whoa. I guess she was right.
I was trying to be funny
and screw around
when she was trying to teach.
Uh-oh.
Introspection bums allegro out.
Oh, man.
Having fun is okay,
but not if it hurts
someone's feelings.
You're ruining my chill vibes.
Party lobsters, fix her!
You're harshing the party vibe.
I know! Give me a hug!
Ugh. No way, man!
I'm having a moment.
Hug me!
Hugs make everything better!
Dude, no!
Just one little hug.
Back off!
What the...
Hug me!
Give me a hug!
Get away from me, you creep!
Come on. Just one little hug.
I said no!
Huh?
Whoa.
Buttercup, what happened?
I just want to party.
Uh-oh.
Party, party.
Wow.
Guess the party's over.
Nice.
I hope the town
is back to normal.
Well, now that
the town is back to normal,
we can continue
our grammar quest
into the realm of conjunctions,
the most used conjunctions
being "and," "or," and "but."
First, let's reveal
the mysteries of "but."
There are many times
when "buts" are useful.
Does anyone have
any "but" questions?
Yes, buttercup?
Are you going to make fun
of my lesson again?
No way.
Actually, I was wondering
if you could remind me
of the difference
between "you and I"
and "you and me."
Wow. I am impressed, buttercup.
You're actually taking
this seriously for once.
And here I thought you were gonna
make fun of something I said.
I would never.
And so, once again,
the day is saved.
Thanks to the powerpuff girls!
And the importance of grammar.
"But" questions!
Whoo!
That felt good.
♪ powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ saving the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ battling evil toe-to-toe ♪
♪ saving the day,
a powerpuff goal ♪