Ohh, yeah!
♪ Powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ to save the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ here's the time to shine
when you're fighting crime ♪
♪ power it up ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
♪ they can do the walk,
gonna do it all ♪
♪ we don't play ♪
♪ who's got the power? ♪
♪ We got the power ♪
Oh! Yeah!
"Dragon wizard
skateboard fighters"!
- Greatest...
- Video game...
Ever!
"Dragon wizard skateboard
fighters"!
I've studied
all the secret codes.
I'm gonna customize my character
with a bunny hat.
I'm gonna blow stuff up.
You get it.
Okay, rock paper scissors.
Go!
1, 2, 3!
Scissors?
Man, I always lose this game.
Hello?
Emergency at city hall?!
Man, I was just about to flip
a 1080 off that dragon spike.
Okay, mayor, how can we help
so we can get back to our...
Game?
Uh, mayor?
Looks like someone had
a wicked party.
Mayor?
What happened?
"Dear mayor..."
"By the time
you read this, I'll be gone."
By working as your assistant
every day for the past 12 years,
I have accumulated
over 1,000 vacation days
"that I'm required to use
on a 1,000-day vacation."
1,000-day vacation?
Sweet.
"I couldn't bear to tell you
face-to-face."
Goodbye, mayor.
"You'll do just fine."
"Miss bellum."
Whoa, blossom, you do a really
good miss bellum impression.
Thanks!
But
apparently, it's worthless now.
Oh!
Miss bellum was my everything.
This may surprise you, friends,
but I've grown
quite dependent on miss bellum.
Eh, eh, eh, eh.
Ooh!
Whoo!
I'm already beginning
to forget her face.
What will I do without her?!
Yeah, that's rough.
Well, got to go.
Video game's calling.
Don't worry, mayor.
We'll help you with
whatever you need.
Well, I do have a few things.
This to-do list
doesn't look so bad.
We should be done with it
by the end of the day.
7 da... ooh, 8 days later...
Whoa.
This list sure is extensive.
You said it, bubbles.
This is ridiculous!
We got to get back to fighting
dragon wizards on skateboards.
Breaking news... Bianca Bikini,
one-half of the notoriously
overdressed, fashion-obsessed
fashionista gang, has
broken out of albatross prison.
She has vowed to free her sister
and destroy the powerpuff girls.
I will destroy you,
powerpuff girls!
Police warn that she is
armed and fabulous.
Ooh! I am fabulous!
But not in these dreadful
horizontal stripes.
I'd kill for something
a little more couture.
Dry cleaners?
It's not boutique chic,
but it will do.
How can I help y... ow!
We'll never
get through this list.
We need to find the mayor
a new assistant, pronto!
Evil is back in
sty-y-y-le!
How 'bout this lady?
A powerpuff girl?
She looks good to me.
Wait. What are her
qualifications?
Hey, lady,
you have a job or what?
A job? I don't job.
You're hired.
Mayor, we got you
a new assistant.
Everything's great.
Got to go.
We are video games.
Bye-bye!
So, you're the mayor?
I know. Can you believe it?
Well, I can't believe
you're wearing that outfit.
Disgraceful.
And you're my new assistant!
Anyone recommended by
the powerpuff girls
is okay by me.
Those girls are just
so responsible.
Anyhoo, let me give you a tour.
We'll start with
the least interesting part.
This is the master control room.
These panels control
all the power
to the entire
city of townsville.
The entire city?
So you could
shut off the power to, say,
the prison of albatross,
where, say,
the extremely trendy
barbarus bikini is being held?
Well, that's an oddly specific
and suspicious question,
but, uh, yeah, I suppose so.
Hmm.
Oopsies.
Ooh! Fluffy ball!
There's so many colors.
Uh, come back here, you.
Get ready to crush
the powerpuff girls, Barbie.
Jailbreaks are so in season.
Ugh! Barbie, I love you,
but you can't annihilate
the powerpuff girls
looking like that.
Ooh!
You read my mind.
Shoplifting spre-e-e-e-e-e!
I'm really tired.
Well, it's taken bubbles
two hours
to customize her character.
But it was tough
to find an outfit
to go with the bunny hat.
Well, hello,
passe-puff girls.
Looks like
you're all pooped out.
Revenge is the new black.
Don't tell the pickles,
but you may be
my new best friend,
magical color ball.
Ooh! My heinie!
This just in...
hey! That's my new assistant.
Bianca bikini,
fiendish criminal...
Criminal?!
has just broken
her sister out of prison...
Prison?!
and has kidnapped
the powerpuff girls.
Kidnapped the powerpuff girls?!
More news at 11:00.
Next up, cute kittens playing.
Kittens!
Wait, kidnapped
the powerpuff girls?!
Sweet salami,
what am I gonna do?
I know.
I'll call the powerpuff girls.
No. I should call the mayor.
No. I'm the mayor.
Ooh! I should call miss bellum.
Oh, this is all my fault!
If I weren't so irresponsible,
this wouldn't have happened.
Founding fathers,
what should I do?
True courage comes from within.
What?
You want to be a man?
Then put on a skirt
and get out there!
A
true hero must embrace his destiny.
I know what I have to do.
Get my picture taken.
No! It is time
to mayor up.
Oh, right!
Uh, "mayor up."
Uh, thanks, Sam.
Time to get this party started!
Ooh, Barbie, killer idea
to bring this fashion video game
to the hideout.
You're right.
This tasteless bunny hat
has got to go.
Delete!
No!
I'd kick your fashionista butts
if I wasn't so tired.
Not in those mid-'90s throwbacks
you're wearing.
That vat of molten polyester
is gonna put you puffs
out of style permanently.
Prepare to dye, powerpuff girls.
And by that,
I mean tie-dyed.
Get ready for the clearance bin,
fashionistas.
Is it the polyester fumes,
or does that action guy
look like the mayor?
Dude, that is the mayor.
Kee-yaa!
Aah!
Ooh!
Whoa. Split-kick combo.
Nice.
Help, mayor!
Hold on, girls!
You want to know the real reason
ladies wear heels?
Ha!
Get over here.
Oh, no!
Tie-dye!
I'm... I'm... Tacky!
Powerpuff girls,
are you all right?
Mayor, you saved us.
Well, girls,
I'm just glad you're safe.
Whoa!
Ow!
All right girls,
time to level up.
Ooh.
Mayor, are you all right?
Oh, girls, uh, what's going on?
Uh, where are we?
Don't say anything, mayor.
We're sorry.
We were being irresponsible
in our responsibilities
of being responsible
protectors of the city.
Basically, we really
junked this one.
So, thanks for saving us,
Mr. mayor.
I saved you?
Seriously, where are we?
And so once again,
the day is saved,
thanks to the powerpuff girls
and the action mayor.
I knew you'd do just fine.
♪ Powerpuff girls
fighting crime ♪
♪ saving the world
before bedtime ♪
♪ battling evil toe-to-toe ♪
♪ saving the day,
a powerpuff goal ♪