Ohh, yeah!
Oh! Yeah!
Hey, there, groovy people.
Today is the Townsville
zen-aissance fair.
It's all peace and love and...
ugh! I hate this place.
Why did you guys drag me
to this lame-fest?
Where's the monster trucks?
Where's the alligator wrestling?
Where is anything cool
around here?!
Buttercup, you always have
a really bad attitude
about everything.
Hmm. Thanks!
You have to learn
how to relax a little.
Oh!
Like this guy.
"Let chillaxi
help you relaxi!"
Check it out.
He's got a free class tomorrow.
I've got a better idea.
Ooh!
Why would I want to take a class
that teaches you to sit
on your butt and be boring?
Meditation isn't
just sitting and being boring!
It's about achieving inner peace
and not getting distracted
by what's going on around you.
Wow.
He's good.
Attention, citizens
of wimpsville... I am...
Manboy!
Manboy?
All the power of a man
in the body of a boy.
Ewww!
This town used to be
a man's town!
Where men were men!
And boys were men!
Townsville needs to get back to
its manly roots.
And if that means destroying
this hippie carnival,
then so be it!
Unless there's somebody here
man enough to stop me!
Nah, we're good.
This day finally
got interesting.
If you're lookin' for a fight,
ol' Buttercup can satisfy
your need for a beatdown!
Why don't you go play
with your dollies, Princess?
"Princess"?
Did you just call me Princess?!
Uh-oh.
Listen Princess, I...
waaaah!
Think you can fight me
like a man, Princess?!
Don't... Call me... Princess!
Unh!
Your girly ways are no match
for my manbot.
I control him
purely with my manly will!
I see great pain in your future.
Aah!
That'll be 5 bucks.
Don't... Call me... Princess!
Whoa-aaah!
You throw like a girl!
Nobody calls me Princess!
You!
I'll show you Princess!
I see more pain in your future.
What? Oh, no.
No, no, no!
Oww!
5 bucks, please.
Buttercup...
Whoa!
What happened?
You happened!
This is
the third time this month
you've had an episode like this.
Your uncontrollable anger
is beginning to be
a serious problem!
Oh, please.
It's not like I hurt anyone.
Isn't that right, Bubbles?
Oh, man.
I did that?
Maybe I do have a problem.
It's okay, Buttercup.
I think I've got an idea.
Welcome to chillaxi's
dojo of chillaxitude.
In this class,
I will teach you how to find
that missing piece of inner
peace you've been peacing for.
Is there gonna be a quiz?
Nope.
Ooh!
Can there be a quiz?!
Mnh, that's not really the...
Mr. guru, on the quiz,
can I use my lucky bunny pencil?
- No.
- Aww.
No, like,
there isn't gonna be a quiz,
so there's no need
to use a pencil on it.
That's okay, Bubbles.
I brought pens.
Uh, why did you bring pens?
In case there's a quiz.
I always have pens.
So, you just walk around
looking for quizzes?
I don't understand the question.
Now you see why I'm so angry
all the time?
There are two sides
of all of us... fire and water.
Fire is all about force.
Water is force without effort.
To be at peace, one must find
balance between fire and water.
Nice presentation.
Okay.
Now show me your flow.
Fl-o-o-o-ow...
Fl-o-oh-oh-ohh!
Oof!
I think I see your problem.
You are very gifted,
but your anger is blocking you.
What do you know about anger,
anyway?
I know plenty.
I was once the greatest
rv salesman in the world.
But I had a mortal enemy...
the tube man.
Rv sales were my life,
and that tube man
made a mockery of my career.
Raaah!
When I came to, I had beaten up
every tube man for 50 miles.
Whoa.
I bet you felt great
after that, huh?
No, Buttercup.
My rage burned a hole
inside of me, just like you.
I want you to have this.
Uh... Jewelry's not really
my thing.
Every time you feel your anger
burning inside you,
I want you to concentrate
on this pendant.
Now... Show me your flow.
Whoa. Whoa!
Feel the flow, dude.
Fl-o-o-o-o-ow...
Very good.
You're on your path
to inner peace.
Awesome!
Whoa!
Unh!
I mean, namaste.
Nemesis, thy name is Buttercup!
No girly girl bests Manboy!
This city will know
its true glory
after I defeat
its false champion... Buttercup!
Aw, man.
That was gonna be so cool.
Buttercup's been like this
all week.
It's kind of weirding me out.
Thanks for grooving with us,
beautiful people.
We'd like to thank tom's
tofu hut for providing lunch.
So... Buttercup...
I'm no longer Buttercup.
I'm moonbeam sunshine.
That's an oxymoron.
Attention,
citizens of wussville!
Great.
Not him again.
I, Manboy,
born of brawn and musk,
declare this
the city... Of... Mansville!
Oh, yeah?
You and what army?!
I'm glad you asked.
This army!
A steak army?
Ew!
Ugh. Men...
Fear not, dear sister.
I shall solve this
with the power of love.
What is even going on right now?
What darkens your cloud,
he-child?
You!
You're not going to
wreck my plans again.
And this time...
It's personal.
But not too personal,
like in an emotional way!
I will not fight you.
It's not my way anymore.
Well, a man's got to do
what a man's got to do.
Where am I?
What truth do you seek?
I tried being angry...
fail.
I tried being nice...
double fail.
Hit me. That's not
my thing anymore.
Fire.
What are you...
fire.
Hey!
Fire!
All right, you asked for it,
captain wiggles.
Water...
And fire.
And fire!
You see...
Fire and water...
you must be both.
Unh!
Buttercup, stop playing around!
Aah!
Time for
a well-balanced beatdown.
Here's some water...
And some fire!
Tenderizing these steaks
is too easy.
Oof!
Okay, one more time.
Fire plus water...
Yeah, you already said...
fire plus water...
yeah, I know, but...
fire and water!
Okay, but...
look, that's all I got!
I'm just a tubeman!
Okay, hair beast, let's tangle.
Water and fire.
Aw, man, I...
Whoa!
Aaaaah!
Oof!
Hey, there, groovy sisters.
Buttercup!
I guess we'll have to get used
to a more peaceful Buttercup.
I'm a changed powerpuff.
No more bad attitudes.
Except for
the zen-aissance fair.
And what's up
with all those lame hippies?
And I don't even like tofu!