WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
You guys aren't anxious?
I'm anxious.
Pretend we're at a party.
That big beat, right?
This week took some time.
Jerry's gonna sit down.
Jerrynho is hotter each day.
Very cool.
- Damn, you're all dressed up today.
- Yes!
Oh, girl! Episode two.
Where were you?
Fashion week.
In my bedroom.
We are honoring last week's party.
I said she's dressed up, not you.
Get over yourself.
I'm not talking to you.
I'll send our chat history.
Don't do it.
I'm exposed!
I want to see episode two now.
Is everybody ready? Because episode one
was nerve-racking, right?
It started very well.
Luan expressed his feelings to Bia.
They fought, got together and had sex.
He also apologized
for doing a lot of things last...
- Making up...
- Love vows.
...vacation.
I'm dying to know what happened
to Murilo and Tay.
Because they started like that,
and now, what?
Do you think they can fix this?
The episode ended
with Murilo hooking up with a girl
in front of Tay. Will she forgive him?
A second pair of eyes never hurts.
Hashtag call me, and I'll come.
She hooked up with a guy too.
She just dismissed him.
She just hooked up with that guy
to tease him, guys.
No, girl, no!
He hooked up with that girl to tease her!
You can love one,
but feel attracted to others.
You know when you're determined
to forget a person?
- She might go back to him.
- Yes, right, but...
In a relationship, the point is
finding somebody worth waiting for.
- No!
- Obviously!
Relationships are based on this.
I won't wait, I'm a whore.
Let's watch. Hit play.
I LOVE YOU
Did you see Murilo's picture?
Look!
Tay woke up,
Murilo got out of the bathroom...
- Murilo, are you busy in the kitchen?
- Yes.
"Are you busy?" "I am." Take that.
I hate people who hold grudges
when they drink.
Bitch, really? Do you need
to be that rude, Murilo?
I'm cool, I woke up great this morning.
You had sex... All relaxed.
Oh, yummy!
- You nailed it.
- Not saying anything...
That's it.
She said you were teasing her.
He's playing the cool guy. Do you think
he's really cool with that or not?
We don't know if he's cool...
Looks like he's pretending.
Do you believe he's cool with that?
- I think he's pretending.
- Me too.
If he were,
he wouldn't have brought that up.
You know when you tell someone
you never think about him?
Yeah, that's exactly it.
You know when the person
wants to show they're cool and say,
"Fuck, did you see that mouth I kissed?"
Telling friends to hit on her...
This is a boy thing.
Gay people don't act like this.
I don't say, "Hey, did you see
I kissed..." Oh, cut it out.
I do it.
"That mouth."
Girl, after what happened yesterday,
how are you and Murilo?
What are you gonna do?
There's no feelings involved in kissing,
but sharing the energy of sex is hard.
It's hypocrisy.
I'm gonna go with you.
There are both sides.
On the same bed? That's fucked up.
She hooked up with another guy.
But not in the same house.
I think "hooking up"
and "having sex" is the same thing.
- I think sex is a plus.
- But, for example, you like the boy...
One thing is he doing it,
another is you seeing it.
Now, get this. To begin with,
they weren't together. Right?
It doesn't matter
if it was on their bed...
Since they had a history,
there must be respect.
For me, this would be over.
If I break up with a guy,
I'm an artist, I...
Honey, I'm a singer!
I'm an exception.
Yeah. I'm an artist.
Artists can do anything.
They can dye their hair.
If I know, like, I'm not with him...
A lot of situations have happened, right?
I break up with him and I messed up...
Can I ask you?
Explain this artist's poetic license
to me... Wait, artist,
as in a person who works with art, right?
I need, Titto. I need to do these things.
- What things?
- Things?
From time to time,
you have to go wild, so there's music!
- Or else, there's no...
- Content?
Yes! There's no content.
So, that's it? So, you have to fuck up
to write music?
- Yes!
- What about you, Pabllo?
For starters, I don't even date.
But if you have something more serious...
A crush you see twice.
I had, but I realized
that I don't belong to this world.
I live on the edge,
I'm more like Carol from Niterói.
I need to live crazy moments.
You do?
- Yeah.
- Okay!
Let's see their crazy moments.
I have trigger warnings
seeing those beaches.
I love it!
I loved seeing the girls
working their asses off.
"Sweetie, this is not a spa",
mom used to say.
You have to work, and enjoy it.
Working what, Pabllo?
Their 'bigooties".
- What's that?
- Big plus booties, 'bigooties'.
Very good!
Big booty.
I thought they did a great job.
I think the bar owner, your sugar daddy,
was rough on them.
Because they did their best. Seriously.
Carol, the manager likes a good funk?
Guys, stop that, I just...
- I said I like serious men...
- With a job.
Yeah, but not that I wanted him, got it?
You said good things about him.
You said you had a crush on him.
I don't remember.
Right! Did you see it?
I'm Ricardo, manager of the bar
where you're going to work.
Jeez, he's serious!
You like serious men like him, right?
Would you take a ride on his boat?
Wouldn't you hook up with him?
I'm from the favela, man,
I was born there.
If he invited me on his boat, I'd go!
But would you hook up with him?
- Would you, Carol?
- He's older.
I like men my age.
I love hooking up
with older men, you know?
You have to speak loud!
Pabllo?
As long as he's a man, he's my type!
If he's alive, you're good to go, right?
Oh, baby, if we hook up...
You do hook up with girls.
- Well...
- Don't deny it.
Whatever comes my way.
I think we have to be...
What about you, Jerry? How old are you?
I'm 26.
What's the average age for you?
Bro, it's 18...
- Eighteen?
- I'd go for an eighteen-year-old.
Hello! I'm eighteen-and-a-half.
- Eighteen?
- Yes, my ex...
was 18 last year.
My boy was 50.
He had trouble getting it up,
- but everything went well.
- How old are you?
- I'm 26.
- Pabllo?
I'm 25.
Bro, I'm much older than everybody here?
I have nothing against your age, okay?
I'm here in case you want me.
I have nothing against your age.
Look, there's a series going on!
Oh, my God! It's Vanessinha!
That chick worked with me!
Is Vanessinha good, girl?
- Yes!
- But she falls for Ramon's sweet talk?
She's very smart.
- Is that Vanessa?
That's Vanessa!
Vanessa's arrived, honey.
Look. The crying.
Don't let her make you lose your mind.
Don't lose it in front of her.
Anna!
- Who's that coach?
- Anna!
It's not Anna!
- But she's a player, you know?
- Dive in.
What's happening?
Honey!
Honey, you've just got in the game.
- Hit pause!
- This is called...
That's booze!
I love it! He was expecting Tay to make
a scene about that sex event.
But she was absolute
and it's bothering him.
Like, she doesn't care.
But I didn't get that part
about her being not sure.
- I think that's on him!
- She's sure!
She was an icon.
But that made him uncomfortable.
If you want psychological counseling,
help, advice...
I charge... Three grand an hour.
- Three grand?
- I solve any problem.
Anything.
Oh, but don't put her
in the house after, okay?
Tell her to chill.
They had to put you seated...
on a pillow, the guru of the house.
I solve... I solve anything,
I read hands...
I didn't get why he was crying.
I don't get this situation. At all.
He likes her, they'll be together...
He had sex...
Actually, he wouldn't do that.
He's annoyed
because Tay didn't do anything.
He doesn't get he's the one playing games,
he's getting a taste of his own medicine.
- Yes.
- I like Murilo a lot.
I love drama.
I'm a Pisces, but I'm not that dramatic.
Relationships must have this drama.
I don't understand...
Girl, if there's no drama, it's not good.
Both have to cry!
I think he's being noble.
He's apologized to Anna...
He's getting it off his chest.
He's expressing his feelings, that's cool.
But he had to do that to Tay.
I didn't get it when he said "prick"...
Maybe not yet...
He's blaming Tay!
He's crying because he likes her!
Tay is playing games?
Who had sex with the girl?
I don't think he's playing,
I think he's sorry.
And this is good.
Good for him.
Why doesn't he tell her?
I think he's crying because
when we use our temple...
Tears of arousal.
...our body, in a wrong way,
- we suffer.
- She's a minister!
I deserve this, holy shit.
Go preach away from here.
Do you think he's crying
because he's sorry or...
I think he wants her.
I've been there. I liked a person
and had sex with another.
The thing ended,
and I was disgusted with myself, you know?
This is called moral hangover.
I think he's crazy about her
and doesn't know how to approach her...
Do you think he's crying...
because he's sorry or because
she doesn't want him anymore?
He's seeing... That's it.
He's afraid she doesn't want him anymore.
Yeah.
By the way she's acting.
If she were your friend?
If I were with Titto knowing
he's a player?
Forgiveness and little forgiveness.
Twenty-two.
- Titto.
- So, I support you.
Suffer for this? Oh, for God's sake.
- We're fancy, huh?
- Let's go!
I love boats.
Have you been in one?
No, only in vans.
And boats?
Girl...
There's a kombi which goes up Vidigal.
If it talked...
I was never able to,
because I wasn't rich. Now, I am...
working here,
lifetime contract with Amazon.
- Now you're getting a boat?
- Yes!
Yes, I'm waiting till quarantine is over.
Look!
Pause!
Nobody standing on the board.
I think this sex modality is curious.
No, guys, really?
Something happened on that board?
It's hard to keep your balance.
- Love balances everything.
- He's cute!
Pabllo falls in love easily.
He knows the way things are here, baby.
What was the most unusual place
you guys had sex?
I'm a very normal person,
I like comfort, I like beds, you know?
Girl...
- One unusual place, say it.
- Yeah, I'm getting...
Unusual!
The most unusual
was at an apartment's balcony.
A very open balcony!
- Fancy.
- Very fancy, I'm fancy, très magnifique.
Hardcore fancy.
Jerry, your place?
Get you in the alley
In the alley, you won't escape.
Alley!
I was very young,
it was 2:00 in the morning...
Looked, smiled, sex.
...at a party... My mom's friend's party.
Mrs. Rosemare always throwing
the best parties.
And there was no place...
I'm going there on Christmas.
- And you, Carol?
- I can't tell.
Where was it? Tell us!
You were tied?
Guys...
So, I was at a party, I made friends.
The party was on a street.
I went downstairs to go to the bathroom.
The house...
It had floors,
I went down to go to the bathroom.
When I got out...
one guy did this with his arm.
I was high on wine,
at that time I used to drink...
He was too.
Guys, having sex high on wine...
He said, "Let's go
to the last floor and all..."
Up or down?
Upstairs. I saw there was nobody...
I said, "Let's go."
I went upstairs with him.
But the rooftop was under construction,
there was a lot of building supplies,
you know? Some cement bags.
She was all dirty with cement.
The last cement bag was open,
and I didn't know cement sticks on you.
My back was very sweaty,
I laid down on the cement bag.
I was with the guy. Man, when I got up,
I moved my hand like this
that thing didn't come off, you know?
You made a plaster with that sweat
and the cement, you could repair a wall!
Man, I know I had
cement all over my back,
on the back of my head.
That thing wouldn't come off.
"Look, the brick is walking."
Was it good?
I had to... Yes!
- John?
- Airport bathroom.
Airport bathroom?
Because you can't do that in a plane!
I'm six feet and four inches tall.
Imagine two people inside a bathroom!
What about you, Lexa?
- In the staff van.
- In the staff van?
Oh, that's fancy,
it's got air conditioner.
- You?
- I go to the church.
Answer!
The most unusual place?
I, in my early teens, with a lot of
hormones, anything gets you...
I went to the photo booth, in the mall.
- What?
- Remember those places?
You'd insert a coin, adjust the seat
and took the picture... I'm old, I'm 34.
There was a booth,
you pulled a curtain and got in.
Guys, I can't take this.
Jeez!
Gosh!
Oh, my God! What's this?
Look at John, man. What a whore, bro!
I wish I was in that event.
I know the outfit I'd wear.
I'm that person who fixes everybody up.
Pabllo, you wanted to be there?
Who would you kiss?
All of them!
- What about you, Carol?
- I like this thing here, watching...
Yeah, right!
What about you? Would you kiss?
That depends on the mood.
You have to choose one.
- One?
- Yes, pick one.
- Tay, Nath, Bia or Anna? Now.
- Anna.
Anna got there a hit, right?
What about you, Lexa?
I want to see everybody kissing.
- Have corn flakes and sleep?
- Sure!
I'd be that person too, that's for sure.
I'd give it up for this.
I'd go to the bedroom with Nath
and her boy.
I imagined you'd want to hook up
with everybody, men, women, and pets!
Guys, I... I'd get there horny.
He'd fuck an ashtray
and have sex with the pool...
- Not yet?
- Is it gonna be me all the time?
Is it gonna be just me?
She was moaning.
Fuck, I love Tay!
If you knew how much I'm hurt!
- Kissing is no big deal.
- Guys!
I'm gonna tell you, he was very honest.
Yes, he was.
He shifted the paradigm.
I felt her pain.
Like, she was really hurt.
Exactly. You can get both of them.
He was very honest with her.
They are both hurt!
They like each other.
Man, Tay makes no mistakes...
Tay was very classy.
But put yourself in Tay's shoes,
Lexa, so what?
That situation is hard,
but I admire him for telling her.
Expressing his feelings.
But that's the thing. It looks like
she gave him an opportunity.
But that depends on him,
if he's gonna be ignorant,
- irrational or...
- Murilo's disciplined, you know?
He will
embrace the opportunity.
He has to embrace it. If he gets upset...
If it were a friend of yours
that you love, what would you tell her?
"Girl, you wanna be with him?"
I'd ask her that too.
But...
You can't interfere. Shut up!
But do you think Murilo is a smart guy?
Yes!
He's a disciplined boy, you know?
If she's... He wants to be with her,
that's clear.
If she's clear about that, if he is
trustworthy and honest until the end,
he's gonna embrace the opportunity.
She's given him that opportunity
when she said, "Let's take things slow."
But I think now they're beginning
to communicate.
They didn't communicate in the beginning.
If he doesn't understand it
and becomes ignorant...
From what I recall, last summer,
Murilo didn't do anything that bad.
Both of them walked the line.
They respected each other.
Let's see!
And she said, if he did what Luan did,
she'd set him on fire.
Then I get here,
we have a real nice moment...
If it were any other girl
that I had hooked up with and said,
"Man, let's be promiscuous?" "Yes."
I'd say yes.
- I didn't say that.
- But we have a history, you know?
Don't put words in my mouth.
We have a history.
Who's this girl?
She was hearing the talk
and said, "Yeah, I really think so."
Tay, our time is gone, okay.
Our time is gone.
Let's not have this conversation.
Let's have fun.
I didn't get that last part
because he said that... That thing.
I thought he'd say
a lot of pretty things...
Exactly.
Hey, Luan, don't let me
mess things up again.
Bro, gag me, tie me, please, right now.
Man, tie me, please, tie me.
Tie me, please.
Gag me, please. Knock me out.
I'm gonna do it soon, you'll sleep.
What? Huh? What?
Who?
Murilo. Here. On you, right now, fuck!
Get fucking real!
What's this?
He said, "Didn't you feel him bumping
his dick into your knee?"
Murilo...
Beatriz, his dick
was bumping into your knee.
He said Murilo bumped his...
Get real, bro!
I was watching! I was waiting.
Get the fucking leg off!
Do you think I was feeling his dick?
Bro, weren't you feeling it?
Fuck you!
Stop it, Luan.
That's not possible!
I would stop talking. It's not worth it.
Do you think he's gonna bump his dick
into my knee, and I'm feeling his dick?
- Fuck, into my knee!
- No, you aren't!
No. You're not normal, you're a saint!
Stop it, Luan!
Girl, there's nothing to do.
You gotta laugh at that situation...
Depressing!
Do you want more dick?
- For God's sake!
- Do you miss a dick?
You know what bothers me the most?
He wants to play the tough guy with her...
What an ass...
He didn't go talk to the guy!
But that was obvious last summer's end.
When they had that fight...
He plays the tough man and when somebody
confronts him, he chickens out.
It was Murilo.
Regardless of what Murilo did,
if it was on purpose...
Luan's attitude toward Bia
was completely wrong.
He should have talked to Murilo.
He should have gone to talk to him.
I've already told you. He's an ass, bro.
Why did he have to argue with her?
She was doing absolutely nothing.
He didn't talk loud to her,
he whispered in her ear...
So Murilo didn't hear!
When Murilo was far,
he started to scream at her...
He manned up!
If she wanted to talk and tell her friends
what was going on, she didn't know...
- She's lost and there's booze involved...
- Poor girl, she was completely lost.
I can see her situation.
Her friends must support her,
she must stand up for herself.
Regarding Tay and Murilo, he said
stupid things.
Men got lost in that party.
They had the chance to get along,
to express themselves...
They were wrong!
They fucked up!
Yeah, I think Luan and Murilo...
made a huge mistake. Because Tay
gave him a chance, and...
He screwed up!
...he wasn't rational, he didn't get
the opportunity she was giving him,
and he wasted it all, you know?
What I think about Murilo and Tay
is that they didn't have that breaking up
every relationship needs.
They're having it now.
I think they won't be...
Like the breaking up Nath and Ramon had.
And they are cool.
Really cool!
They don't have any problems. They need
that kind of breaking up to be cool.
Because, in the past,
they didn't get along very well,
because they always had a fight.
Now Murilo always respected Tay a lot.
So, this is mutual.
We're on episode two,
we still have a long way to go, man.
Let's see what's going to happen
on the next, go.
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
Bro, there's no more "you and me"!
No!
My Gosh!
I'm shocked!
This is going to end up in a lot of sex.
So, I was mistress of a guy...
Slut!
Girl...