- Jerry's anxious!
- Wait!
Everybody was dancing back there...
Let's do it...
I'll just clap.
What will happen?
MC is missing...
Is missing... yeah!
Hi, how are you? Is everybody fine?
How was the week?
- It was great!
- It was okay.
Everybody's anxious to see
what's going on today?
I wanna see it. That pregnancy...
I forgot about that, man!
There's that possible pregnancy.
Remember that Renatinho arrived...
kissed everybody,
hooked up with Anna.
Will they be a couple?
They won't be a couple,
but they'll make out a lot.
Anna was the last one I saw him kissing.
Anna and Renatinho learned that
they're free, so they're free as a couple.
They ended up having sex.
Was that it? Oh, that's true!
He kissed a lot
and ended up with Anna.
Yes, it's true.
What about Murilo and Tay?
What do you think?
Do you think it's really over?
Do you think Murilo's gonna play games?
I wonder if Tay's gonna play games.
What do you think?
I told you they learned
they have to be friends because
when they see each other
making out with somebody else...
Yeah...
She said she's detached.
- They can't do that.
- She's free now.
Guys, since the first half
of the vacation,
there have been a lot of fights,
and now I think they need to be friends.
They don't work well close, nor far away.
In my opinion, that couple,
especially Tay, can't take it anymore.
She can't.
Murilo will try something.
- She's really tired.
- Yes.
- Are you ready?
- Let's go!
- Yes!
Let's go!
Are you ready?
I have the remote today!
Delicious!
Come, Christian Grey!
Let's go!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
They had bread and beer.
Hey, Mu, look.
I was thinking about
getting the car, going downtown,
and go for a ride on the lagoon.
Thank God. Let's go.
I was thinking about
going with Renato, Anna, and Murilo.
Do you agree? We'll see what we can...
Jesus, awesome, buddy!
If there's a stand up paddle board
put in the car...
Bea?
- Are you okay?
- I feel sick.
Bea, let's go for a drive.
Just me and you.
- Jeez.
- Can you do it?
Get out of the house just a little.
I can.
- Bye, guys! We'll be right back.
- Bye.
- Bye. Drive safe.
- Thanks.
It's a beautiful day.
I don't like your queasiness.
I don't understand it either.
- That's not normal.
- No.
Do you think you could be pregnant?
No.
Oh, my God, now I'm worried.
I don't like these queasiness.
You're feeling sick every day,
not because of medicine, booze or food.
I don't know.
I think this could be the booze.
You feel sick when you drink?
- No.
- So, it's the first time this happened.
You know, we should stop
by a drugstore and settle this.
At least, if you're not pregnant,
you should see a doctor.
Oh, girl, that's terrible. No.
We should stop by a drugstore.
- We could.
- Just to be sure.
I smell bread.
Oh, let's check our weight.
- Oh, where is it?
- Here.
Good afternoon. Hi.
I'd like a pregnancy test, please.
Are you nervous?
I'm starting to be. Actually, now I am.
When you buy the test, you get...
I didn't come to...
- To think about it.
- Yes.
We just said that,
"Could it be?" You said, "No."
At least we end this doubt.
Think about it, girl. What am I gonna do?
Damn.
- Hey, Bia, Tay!
- What?
We're leaving, we'll be right back.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
I'll take the front seat!
- No way!
- Damn!
Bullshit, dude.
- I don't see a board.
- It must be inside.
- Guys...
- Let's take a look!
I told you!
Look at his cousin!
Let's talk to him.
- Look at his cousin!
- That's not possible!
You're fucking with me.
Are you okay? Nice to meet you, I'm Ramon.
- Welcome.
- Take it easy.
Let me ask you something.
Don't you have a SUP board?
You made us come here,
we came all the way to Jurerê
- to buy...
- Which huge floaty do you have?
- We had arranged...
- A flamingo.
A flamingo! Oh, not the flamingo.
Fuck, it's the flamingo!
Oh, damn, dude!
Fuck!
- Guys!
- Fuck!
You were complaining,
look at this huge flamingo.
Dude, this is the mother of all flamingos.
Just don't destroy our flamingo.
I wanna stay here.
How will we take this?
Let's put this up there.
Everybody, help us put it there...
on the top of the car!
Damn, we're fucked!
Let's go! I need your help!
CAUTION
DANGEROUS CROSSROADS IN 200 METERS
Look back, see if there's a crowd
waiting for us.
There's a one-kilometer line back there.
Let's take the flamingo!
Bro, let's take the flamingo!
Let's go! Hey!
Let's go!
Say goodbye!
It's simple saying "no".
Right? Forget the stress.
Asshole.
- Damn!
- Stop it!
I wanna throw it on the wall.
It's nothing. It's wrong.
Leave it there.
It'll be ready soon.
I'm anxious, I can't leave here.
Yeah, so...
-"Not pregnant."
- Phew, amen!
- Amen!
Oh, my God, I knew it!
Look who's here, a new member!
One picture.
Go Renato.
Fuck, this thing is huge, man!
I'm shocked.
Let's go to the water.
Go, I'll put my foot.
Oh, shit.
- I have to talk to Anna.
- About?
Things, bro. We used to talk about
being together in the house,
and when we got out...
- Having fun.
- Yes.
We would hook up with whoever we wanted.
But on second thought,
I think that's fucked up.
I don't even know what I want, you know?
I'm enjoying being with her here.
Although, sometimes,
there are some things that...
- Like?
- She wants to...
do things in her own time, you know?
She does things in her own time.
Yeah, in her own time.
She does that...
So I'll stop hooking up with other chicks.
But it doesn't work this way.
We came here to have fun!
- Exactly.
- And you're doing it in a cool way.
I wanna have fun, you know?
That's why this thing...
is like this, you know?
That's the ideal, bro.
Keep it this way.
If something happens after this. If...
- That Renato, man.
- What's up?
Sometimes it's very difficult
to understand you.
- Why?
- Just because...
Sometimes you seem to be open
to some things, then you change.
Sometimes, I think you wanna be with me...
then, all of a sudden, you don't.
It's a little difficult.
And I don't know what to think.
This is what affects me the most.
Not knowing what you want.
I have more doubts than you.
Could be. When I thought I knew,
we had a bad fight.
That makes me drift apart even more.
It's not about drifting apart.
It is.
It's just...
Sometimes, you don't know
what you're saying. When you're wasted.
- You either.
- You say things,
- Mu, what happened there...
- and I am...
- You freaked out.
- No, I didn't.
- No, I did not.
- Yes, you did.
The boys are downstairs?
I guess. I'm going downstairs,
I need to pee.
I'll be right down.
- Is it here?
- Yes, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's work, girls.
- Come get some air.
- Let's go.
- I'm lazy.
- Me, too. We are so pretty.
I was born lazy.
Hey, Murilão! My favorite inked man.
How are you?
I have some news. I think it's good.
Oh! You son of a bitch!
I'm in Floripa.
Let's go wild on this island.
Give me your address.
I'm coming!
Fuck, I can't believe he's coming.
Son of a bitch!
Are you okay? What's up?
Hey, Grijó, you punk!
I'm waiting for you, dude.
Let's go!
Where are you, brother?
Fuck, I fucking miss you, man!
Fuck, man!
Come on over, things are gonna go wild.
I can't believe this, my brother's coming.
Fuck!
This is gonna be crazy, dude.
Now you're talking, dude.
Good evening!
Welcome!
The taxi is here.
This must be him.
Here!
I told you I was coming.
Let's take over the world, dude!
Fuck, bro, this is great!
What's up?
How are you, bro?
Fuck, my man!
Fuck, bro!
Beautiful house, brother.
- Hi, man.
- Ramonzinho, Renatinho.
- Pedrão.
- Are you good?
- Come on. No way, bro.
- You're home, man.
Fuck, bro!
We're here, dude!
Let's take over the world?
Let's meet the girls.
- I'm working, baby.
- I know.
How are you?
- What have you got for us?
- Sex on the beach,
gin and tonic, strawberry...
Lime caipirinha and beer.
- Lime, man!
- Two of those.
- Two gins.
- I didn't see hot guys!
- You didn't?
- I saw people.
- Okay, two gins...
- Take it easy.
- ...two sex on the beach.
Give me one glass.
- I'll be back to take more orders.
- It's for Andrei.
The hood.
- Thanks.
- I'm watching, you know?
Thanks.
That's an exception, right?
A kiss like this.
Oh, that's disgusting, my God.
You may order.
May I? Excuse me.
- No touching or I'll be jealous.
- I want a lime one.
I want a lime one.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
- You're so fresh!
Two... Caipirinhas, right?
Two caipirinhas.
Where are the other tokens?
You didn't pay attention, you idiot.
No comment.
I have a lot of questions.
If you cheat on me...
That's it!
Can we start dating after this?
I didn't hook up with anybody,
I was stalling
- to hook up with you.
- Andrei!
I was cheated on again.
If you take Bebeto, you take Romário too.
You two are a set.
You take Bebeto, you take Romário.
Fuck!
Oh, it's not possible.
My man is here.
Ask any one of them
if I hooked up with anybody!
What?
- Girl, there's another guy with them.
- He's Murilo's friend.
Come here, Nath.
- Pedro.
- Who might you be?
My friend from Brasília.
- Welcome, Pedro.
- Nathália, Grijó.
- Nice to meet you.
- Grijó, my friend from Brasília.
Hi, how are you?
Nice to meet you.
Let me introduce you to the girls.
Come here.
- Hi.
- Tay, Pedro.
Nice to meet you.
Who is this?
- Say you're Ísis Valverde.
- No!
- Let's go, dude!
- She's hot, right?
Too bad she's hot, right?
She's great, she's hot, I like her.
One for all and all for one!
Fuck!
I need to talk to you later.
Okay, later...
She's the girl, right?
A glass of orange juice, please?
Orange juice?
Do you want ice?
No, I want to drink an energy drink
with vodka, no.
Thank you.
Do I let the girls go?
They've already worked a lot tonight.
You said they did a good job.
Do you think that's work?
That's the afterparty.
- That's fucked up, buddy. Let them go!
- Let us go!
- Let them go!
- Girls, you're free to have fun.
Hi!
Good evening, ladies.
Good evening!
Are you taking that guy home?
- Am I not supposed to?
- What?
Am I not supposed to?
No, it's up to you.
- I was gonna take him, but...
- I didn't hook up because of you.
- But I didn't know about this.
- Bro...
but what did you tell me when I got here?
Come here. We have to make a deal.
No, what did you tell me when I got here?
"If you hooked up with a girl,
I'd grab her by the hair."
But now I wanna understand.
But, look, we made a deal,
we can do whatever we want, and...
when we want to be together, we'll do it.
But we are free.
It's our deal, since the beginning.
I can't tell you tonight,
"Let's stay together," because
I can tell you this now
- and, in two hours, I'll tell...
- It's not this.
- Exactly.
- I'd rather tell you this tonight.
- I'm confused.
- So am I.
I'd rather take my time
and think about what I want.
And I think you understand
- I do.
- that I'm playing fair with you.
Just say "Okay".
Anna's boy needs to drop
by a birthday party near our house.
No, he'll go later.
Anna said that, "Wait."
- Anna?
- Yes.
- Anna or Nath?
- Anna.
Anna? Nath's boy.
That Anna's boy.
- Isn't she with Renatinho?
- She invited the boy.
Renatinho dumped a chick,
I told her, "I'll tell Renatinho."
Fuck, that's fucked up.
They are not a couple.
No.
We don't need anything,
we just need ourselves.
Where are the afterparty people?
There's a party tonight
in the lagoon house,
on us!
Let's go! Hit it, DJ!
You want to see a lot.
- I'm from Rio.
- I'm from Niterói.
- That's rad!
- Excuse me.
Sure, sit down.
I'm here in the corner.
The three of us fit in here.
We can fit three!
Oh, I'm cool.
I just drink and smoke cigarettes.
He's kissing a girl there.
- Who?
- Look.
If he sleeps with her,
I don't know how I'll react.
You'll react
by fucking another guy tomorrow.
It's Renato... Is it that girl?
If they do it in my bed, I'll be pissed.
Me too!
It's not just your bed,
it's Nath's too, right?
If he's going there with that girl...
I waited to have sex with a guy.
He got here, I had sex with him
and I don't know.
I don't care
if he hooks up with everybody,
I joke around, like...
I said... Stop looking at Bia!
Girl, looks like you're a little hurt,
and you don't wanna admit it.
You are a little jealous.
Jealous of the situation.
I think it's impossible that you
- don't feel anything.
- But when he wants me, I don't.
- So, what is it?
- Ego.
Go, Ramon is coming before you, go.
Ask him to go to the sex room,
if anything happens.
Ask her to leave.
Girl, you're doing this.
You can't hook up with another guy,
you're getting in his way.
You're getting in his way now.
Tomorrow you kiss another boy.
I don't want it in my bed.
I didn't check.
She'll leave.
- You're hurt.
- No!
You gotta be honest, you know?
Don't give a shit about him tomorrow
because he'll do the same.
Wait, you are hooking up with whom?
Renatinho.
I don't feel anything.
How can you have feelings
for anybody in four days, girl?
You can't.
Man, this is...
Fuck, Tay. Listen.
Oh, girl, I won't listen, girl.
That hurts. I know.
Oh, I don't wanna be here.
Oh, girl, I wish I hadn't listened.
Come on, you wanted to.
I know, I wanted it this way.
- It happens.
- I saw him doing
what he does to me.
It happens.
You didn't want him, you ended it,
now you just move on.
- It's no use being sad.
- That's fucked up!
Someone wants to use it.
- Nath.
- I get it.
Let me see how it is. Turn around now.
Top-notch, girl!
Look at this, Ramon, look at this.
Look at this.
Wow!
I wish I had an ass like that.
Easy. The camera.
The camera. Wonderful, go.
Look, girl, look. The trending cover.
No, man. Andrei!
- Hey, man, what a shame.
- Come, boy, leave.
- Go!
- No!
See? There you go.
Meaning she likes him.
That's crazy, I thought
she was totally free,
- but no.
- I think she's upset.
- She doesn't like him.
Renatinho.
No, she's crying, she's sad because...
I think she invented
an imaginary rule in her head,
an imaginary limit he crossed.
Buddy, you don't even believe that.
No, it's difficult for "Dr." John Drops.
Guys, it's obvious, she's upset.
She's hurt, I thought she was free.
I agree. She's hurt.
Hearing your ex having sex
must be upsetting.
Guys, that's obvious.
She's upset because of her "F.B."
not because she likes him.
No, dude.
- What's "F.B."?
- Fuck buddy.
I agree.
She had a permanent "F.B." in the house...
- I agree.
- ...but they were free.
I don't agree.
But he crossed the line
and took a girl home and hurt her.
I think it's like this.
She doesn't like the guy, just his dick.
- What?
- She just likes his dick.
She doesn't like him!
She does...
She doesn't like him,
but she likes the sex.
If she could detach his dick,
she'd take it?
- Is that it?
- Exactly.
I wanna hear somebody
who almost said nothing.
- What?
- What do you think
about this situation?
If I were in her shoes,
I would handle it differently.
Or I would let the guy fuck and be cool.
Or I'd do like Anna, hook up
and leave, but I think I would stay.
I wonder if we are too detached.
Oh, girl, I don't believe it,
that "we're all detached".
- Here, in this show, I pretend I am...
- You are!
...but deep inside I also am!
That's not possible.
Guys, let me speak.
Pabllo is the most detached person
I've ever met.
She should be studied.
Love, a whore's love...
"Whore's Love" suits her perfectly.
Now let's understand
one subject we didn't talk about,
a big problem,
Bia's pregnancy test, if it were positive.
The show would end.
Tell me what you'd do, if you were Bia.
I would call my mom and say,
"Hi, Mom, I'm pregnant."
I would have the child
and give it away to his family.
- I swear to God.
- Stop it!
- Really, Carol?
- I swear.
I mean it. Really.
You'd carry a baby for nine months,
when you had him,
- you'd give...
- Man, I said that
- because... All men I've met...
- She'd do that.
I said, "Man, don't try to play me, bro."
Some men try to play you.
"I'd like to have a daughter..."
But I wouldn't have a daughter
with a jerk, you know?
With a guy I had sex with...
Girl...
...and he did it to fuck with me.
Hear me out.
You're so amazing that no jerk
would make a difference to your life.
Anything created inside of you
would be wonderful.
But guys...
my best friend had the same problem,
I went with her to buy the test.
That feeling is very weird,
the person forgets everything
and goes to buy a test.
- It's terrifying.
- Girl, it's terrifying.
In Salvador, we say,
"Even hot palm oil doesn't get through."
I never saw this in any other reality.
I'm gonna hit play, guys. Let's go!
Play!
Look, be careful with that woman.
Look what she does.
- What?
- Here. Look at my arm.
Who did this?
- Nathália.
- What's that?
Don't joke around with her.
She might scratch your arm.
If she sees you
surrounded by too many girls!
Yeah, that's what she does.
Why have enemies!
She sticks her nails into your arm.
Hair pulling...
Glasses in the face.
- He's sad!
- What?
You're sad today. Quiet.
I am.
- Feeling sorry?
-"I am."
Guys, let's clear the table.
No comment.
What were you doing?
Let me see, Murilo.
Where are yesterday's pictures?
This one is not...
I threw our picture away.
You kissed and did some blow.
He didn't do any blow!
Bullshit.
- Damn.
- It's not here yet.
It's even better.
Put the new pictures there.
You can throw this away. Where is it?
Where is it?
Here, you can throw this away.
Can I? Okay.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Who threw it away?
I threw it away because we had a fight.
No, return it, put it back!
- No, Tay.
- Why did she do that?
What an angry girl.
That's bullshit.
That's bullshit!
Oh, my God.
Because we broke up
the day I got the picture.
- Sometimes, I'm just like you.
- You're such a baby.
He said, "Throw everything away."
He didn't mean that,
he wasn't serious about this, right?
Don't ask me anymore.
Throw yourself away.
- I've already done it.
- Old news. That was way back.
Since we got together.
Oh, my God, what's that for, guys?
Look, mark my words,
Anna won't do the dishes anymore.
Anna doesn't feel like talking. Bullshit.
I'm gonna have to talk,
wanna come with me to help me?
I can't avoid this anymore.
Tell me, what's the problem?
You...
- What?
- You're the one who wants to talk.
I'm fine.
No, not fine.
I was talking to you, and you...
I don't know,
I was minding my own business...
I don't know, I didn't see this coming.
I didn't see this coming,
but... It happens, it happens a lot.
You bring a girl, hook up with her,
have sex with her, it happens.
That's because, like, I say, fuck...
Bro, I was upset because
I have feelings for you, I realized
this affected you somehow, you know?
If you were in my shoes,
how would you react?
If you're fine with this, I am too.
If you're not, it's not.
That's simple. There's no mistake.
I just don't want this to affect
our relationship, you know?
Yesterday I wasn't in the mood
to say anything. What was I gonna say?
I wasn't in the mood, you know?
This won't affect us, sorry. I did this,
but this won't affect us because,
before we hooked up,
we were becoming friends,
so, it's gonna be the same way.
It won't change.
I did this. It won't happen again.
I made a mistake,
but I'm cool, I'm not upset.
These things happen,
you're home, your home is my home,
we do whatever we want.
That's fucked up.
I didn't want this today,
you know?
It's not worth it, you know?
I know, but...
I wasn't gonna be this fucking way...
We go out every day,
if we bring people home,
we won't talk to each other again.
- I know.
- You know?
That's why we have to come to...
Fuck, you know?
What bothers you? What doesn't bother you?
But that's the problem,
it just bothered me.
It bothered me you had sex.
You won't have sex again?
This can't happen, I have to accept it.
You know?
We go out every day,
we have afterparties...
You wanna be with others,
I wanna be with others.
We can't deny ourselves.
Like it or not,
I'm sorry for us.
Tomorrow is a new day.
Like, I slept, woke up, and it was fine.
Like...
Listening to that was a consequence,
like, what am I gonna do?
That's it!
It's all right.
I swear. Okay?
It's okay.
"Baby Shark"!
Baby Shark
When I was 16...
Did you sing "Baby Shark"?
Bye. See you later, don't take too long.
Bye.
Oh, that's the phone.
I'm gonna see.
What's up, guys?
Today I need the boys
at the bar, night shift.
- See you later.
- Let's work, guys.
You know what I'll do?
I'm gonna call Amanda.
At least I'll have company at the bar.
I didn't have one yesterday.
I'll have one today.
I want one too.
Get out.
Come on, fag.
I'm gonna call somebody.
Don't you have someone?
I don't know.
Oh, work it out for yourself.
Let's go!
Girls, we'll be right back. We're working.
That's okay, man.
Let's get to work.
- I hear the phone ringing.
- Jeez.
I hear the phone.
All I need is Ricardo saying
he needs us to work at the bar.
Hi...
- Hi, girl!
- Not possible!
How are you, my love?
I'm fine, I miss you!
- Me too!
- I'm gonna ruin my makeup.
- What's up?
- Do you know where I am?
No, where?
- Who's this?
- Where?
Is this Rayanne?
Where, fuck? Are you in Floripa?
- In Floripa!
- You're messing with me.
- Guys, it's Nath's friend!
- You and Matheus!
I can't believe this!
Okay, I love you guys.
Bye.
Oh, Lord.
Oh, my makeup.
Guys, Ray and my gay friend are here.
Your gay friend, awesome!
Guys, you're gonna love them, I swear.
Ray mocks more than me.
Be careful with our boys,
Matheus hits on them.
- Good evening!
How are you? Welcome!
Four beers.
That's it, you have to toast!
- Let's drink!
- Good evening, girls. Can I help you?
How are you? Nice to meet you.
What about that carioca accent?
- Did you like it?
- Yes.
- Oh, good. Alana, right?
- Kiss!
When's the shot time, when everybody
takes off their shirts and throws it up?
Look. Ramon!
You have to make a deal with him.
One shot so the waiters take
the shirt off, and we get drunk.
Make a deal with him.
With the buddy!
I'll arrange this.
Go, Nath!
Oh, guys, I really don't like this.
Of course I do!
I think I drowned.
You had sex.
You're rushing things, Nath.
Cheers to our night, it's gonna be epic,
better than that one.
Better than that one.
Better... Better than that one.
Let all hell break loose.
God bless!
Let's take a picture!
Let's go!
What happens in a night-out
stays in a night-out!
How are you?
Hi!
No, I'm very happy, really.
I love it!
There's a hot guy wearing a white t-shirt.
A hot one!
Get one for me and one for you.
You know it, right?
I counted the guys I hooked up with.
He must be around.
We fuck for free.
Line up and come, one at a time, baby.
Hi!
How are you?
When did you get in Floripa?
I got here today.
Hey, chug, go!
Fuck! Man, don't do what they say.
Don't drink this way, you'll die.
You'll die!
Shut up.
Are you gonna start or not?
You kiss everyone here...
You think I want all the girls in here?
Andrei's here, where's Nath?
Andrei's here.
Nath can't hook up
with another boy anymore.
Oh, I'm gonna do nothing.
Andrei's here.
Really? I thought so.
There'll be another scandal.
It's fucked up!
Nath has a big problem, right?
Big problem.
Anna told me, "What now?
What are we gonna do?"
Oh, I'm gonna do nothing. Me, nothing.
But she...
She doesn't give a shit and she's right.
He's always at parties, you know?
Take it or leave it.
Boys just leave!
I want it.
Bro, this...
Where to?
Nath, you do whatever you want, man.
Of course, I wanna kiss you,
- but you're gonna be upset with me.
- No!
Of course not?
Your hook-ups before...
No, it was after.
After or before, if you had hooked up...
I'm here for the party, I'm here for you.
If you're happy with him,
you have to choose.
Girl, are you okay?
Don't come closer.
- Are you okay?
- Sure.
- Why?
- What?
Did Nath hook up?
This is hard.
- What do I tell him?
- What?
I'm with somebody.
I already have two.
- What?
- I already have two.
Do you wanna listen?
- What?
- Do you wanna listen?
Bro, I'm playing like you.
I'm angry with you.
- I found mine.
- Where?
Looking here,
I found him, girl! I found him.
Wearing a cap? Jeez, girl!
Yes, I love it.
It's just us.
Guys, look at her mouth!
No!
I love it, girl, all smudged.
First rule of a night-out, girls.
You want to kiss?
Wear a nude lipstick, a gloss.
If you wanna strike a pose,
wear a red lipstick.
I came with a nude one.
You'll look like a clown.
- What?
- I came wearing a nude one.
John always has nudes.
- And that guy too.
- I only sent you twice.
This week, right? Okay.
He got sad.
Whose? Tay's?
- What kiss?
- He got sad.
It made my mouth water.
I applaud Nath with my feet, laid down.
Nath was fucking awesome.
Nath, you named this episode,
I'm shocked, honey. Queen of Goiânia.
And Tay also was free there.
She hooked up with one, then another...
Bia is cooler, right?
I believe, for her and Murilo,
it's over for her.
It's over.
I disagree.
- It's over!
- I agree.
It's over, and she gets it.
- Lexa?
- Hunting in the night-out.
- Are you anxious?
- I am.
I'm almost dying here!
I'm very anxious, I think Tay's sad.
- No!
- Yeah, right!
Kissing a lot!
She's gonna look for Murilo.
He loves her, she loves him.
- Pabllo?
- Here, to Murilo and Tay.
I think she's fine at that party.
She'll kiss one more.
I believe she can score three points.
- You wish you were her, right?
- Sure.
But, if she wants Murilo later,
that's okay too.
- That's okay!
- Jerry? Hit play.
Let's see it!
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
You know nothing
about what'll happen tomorrow.
You know? That's life!
What's that for, Murilo?
You came, man!
I wanted so bad for you to come.
I was hit and I felt it.
I'm fucked!
We're in Floripa!
Take it easy.
It's a mess but we can manage it.
Renato and Anna drawing attention again!
They're becoming a couple
like Murilo and Tay.
They're far from this.
Renatinho hooking up, Anna hooking up.
- That's good.
- Tay and Murilo started this way.
I didn't see who Anna was hugging.
- Oh, that's it.
- But it was a new guy and she...
I think it was Ramon.
A new guy, and she said,
"I'm fucked!"
Why? Renatinho was getting there?
You heard what they said, I think
it was Renatinho, he said, "She hit me."
Jeez, bro!
Will there be a lot of hits?
Guys, I wanna ask something.
What, honey?
How many episodes do you need
to start believing me?
I believe you.
This is what life is all about
Guys, my car is here, okay?
Pabllo, are you coming with me today?
I am. Wait, I just...
That police car is here for John.
That's bad. Jeez, seriously.
After this show, I'm gonna sue you.
- Why?
- Bye, guys!
- Guys, don't fight.
For God's sake.
You can fight, but not here.
With you by...