WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
- The last episode.
- No, the last episode!
- Are you gonna cry?
- Yes, I am.
I'm gonna cry!
Oh, my God,
the last day!
What's up, guys?
What's this, Carol?
It's the last day. I'm very sad!
Guys, everybody is so beautiful!
So, how are you guys? I'm very sad, guys.
It's the last episode of this season,
and it's so iconic.
But I'm sad it's gonna end.
Me too, I'm already sad. Really.
What are you gonna take in
from this season? Which good things?
A lot of things,
that I have to be more patient...
People are single,
so what do I have to learn!
What about you?
I learned that I need
to be detached and free.
This season's motto is to be free.
I'll miss you guys!
Carol, my friend!
I think we learned
to listen more to each other.
- At least I learned to listen more.
- That's because of Renatinho and Anna!
- I've learned...
- Always talk to the person.
To be honest with other people!
I love being honest.
I love it! I think, in a relationship,
when you're honest...
Tell me where you got
the inspiration for that look, Pabllo.
This one I got from Pride...
You and Lexa are matching!
Yes, the pigtails
- and the necklace.
- Carol's wearing a single ponytail.
But Carol is a mix of sorceress
and "I sucked a golden bar." What's that?
Anyway...
I learned we can't fall for anybody
while on vacation in Floripa, you know.
That's it.
She's fancy,
but she's drinking chocolate milk!
- Titto, what about you?
- What?
What will you miss?
I'm gonna miss the moment I had peace,
the moments you weren't by my side.
I'll tell what you told me
before the show.
I think deep down,
you love each other very much.
- You know?
- Our love's so intense, it makes no sense.
Right?
What were the most interesting gossips
in this season?
There were many!
No, first, the bad breath
when they woke up and kissed.
Who wakes up and kisses in the mouth?
- And talks so close?
- Man, I've done that.
When I wake up, it looks like I sucked
a dog's ass. I want to brush my teeth.
I think that hit with the elbow
to Murilo's face proved the thing is real.
I won't let you go.
You can hit me.
We learned and also saw,
I think people from home saw that too
and watched Luan's situation,
which set an...
Actually, we really could see
the whole picture.
- And we can't forget the ménage...
- The ménage was epic!
- Renatinho...
- Trigger warning?
Renatinho...
Anna was a new member
at the house and represented.
This is the sex room!
I wanna watch the next episode.
What about you?
Hit play, please. Do it!
What? Let me get the remote here.
Turn it on with your heels.
Oh, bullshit.
I'm a little happy he left.
He caused all that situation...
Me too!
- ...in the last episode, so...
- Bye, Ítalo!
Ramon, help me, how am I gonna tell Luan?
Girl, what?
"I kissed guys."
She doesn't have to explain anything!
She wants to get back together.
She intends to stay with him.
- She's thinking about Luan.
- Wait!
That happened on this vacation,
but the vacation is at an end,
and she'll return to her reality
and there's Luan.
He just left the house...
but he's still in her life.
They must talk.
She made clear that, after the show,
Luan's her reality, you know?
No, she knows that at some point
she'll have to work things out.
The guy aborted mission vacation,
now she'll meet him and say, "What now?"
But when he left, he said,
"Have fun." Didn't he?
He did, he said...
- Lexa's right.
- Even a parrot can say something!
For God's sake.
People say things they can't handle.
If I can't handle it, I don't say it.
No, but I think they need
to have this conversation.
- Absolutely. They need this.
- But not in this mood of fear.
Imagine this, everything ended,
they're at home, having popcorn,
he watches her kissing two guys...
- But, guys!
- I'm not saying that's wrong or right...
He's really jealous, imagine...
But why did he leave the house?
I hope he's seeing a shrink.
- Yes.
- Me too.
- We weren't talking outside, right?
- No.
So...
I kind of didn't know
what was gonna happen.
Me neither, that's why I said
I didn't wanna see you.
I said, "No, man,
we'd better not see each other,
"let's do it in the house."
Oh, but I wanted to see you, to talk...
I wanted to too. But I didn't think
that was the best option, you know?
Because...
Carol, how do you like it
seeing them working things out?
I'm loving it, man.
I think it's cute when Carol
is paying attention... Hit pause!
Carol, she doesn't pay attention
to things, she falls asleep sometimes.
Sometimes...
She's so excited, she liked that couple
so much that she watched, rooted for them.
What do you think is gonna happen
from now on with that couple?
Titto, I believe in love.
- Really?
- You believe in whore's love, right?
I want you to understand
that I believe in love.
I believe in love, I bet on love...
Anyway. Man, when I saw them,
you know, right?
I said, "Guys, they'll stay together."
Then they fought, you said, "They won't!"
I said, "They will!" And look now!
I think there's a great chance
they stay together, because
I think all the situations that happened,
those arguments...
those crises, I think their relationship
matured because of all those things.
I can see
that they're much more mature...
The level of the conversation!
...and they're mature enough
to talk about the relationship
and the things that can change,
improve, their mistakes...
Now, they're talking to find a way.
- It's a walk, a peaceful walk.
- Discovering new places.
I never came here.
- I've only heard about it.
Oh, guys, they made a video.
Oh, my couple! My favorite couple, guys!
That's a fucking great couple.
We'll get in the water naked.
The good thing is this place is deserted.
Oh, I'm gonna cry, guys!
Oh, that's cute!
I'll tell them to invite just me
for their wedding.
-"Just me"?
- You didn't bet on their love.
Baby, the important thing
is always believing in the best,
I bet on happiness. If that's happiness,
- cheers!
- You?
Mostly you. You don't get
in the church, my brother.
Hey, are you going there yet?
- You're dressed for the wedding now.
- I'm the maid of honor!
I'll even sing...
Imagine Carol getting in the church!
I'll even...
No! She'll get in and say,
"The debauchery's gonna start."
I'll sing at the altar!
What are you gonna sing?
Pretend this is the mic.
"The debauchery's gonna end!"
He proposed to me
But I don't get it
I'm a fucking slut
I live in the moment
Your family...
This is not for you guys, you'll marry.
Out of the blue!
Naked?
- Swimming naked?
- Yes!
Oh, it's there! Go, sister. Go.
Are they both naked in the lagoon?
It'll happen!
Have sex, girl, real good!
Jeez, that boto vibe, right, sister?
The lagoon of Floripa.
Somebody has to work, right?
- You have to pay all...
- It's not easy!
Good evening.
Bro, is he drinking
other people's drinks, man? Ramon...
Did he do that?
No, it's worse, he has his own drink.
- I think that drink is his.
- He's drinking behind the manager's back!
He fixed one for himself.
- Not in secret!
- He's like this!
With the tray.
Girl... he's just like us,
with our former bosses.
Bro, this is getting to the end.
He's raising hell, man.
It's his.
Did you do like Ramon when you worked,
you took one drink and drank two?
No!
I didn't do that!
When I worked in the bakery...
God, that's my dream!
- You worked in a bakery?
- I did!
Girl, you worked in a bakery?
No way, girl!
The cold cuts were expensive.
There was a very expensive cheese.
So, I would go and slice some for me
and eat it. But that was too much.
My dream is working in a bakery.
I used to eat soft cheese all the time.
Tell us a story from Malhação.
When he was ugly, really ugly.
While doing the Malhação soap opera,
the weirdest job I did was painting gates.
What was your craziest job?
Man, I sent my résumé to Bob's,
but never got the call.
I was never accepted.
Yes, Bob's.
So now, when I go to Bob's Burgers,
I bring a ton of friends,
and I buy milkshakes for all of them!
Did you work at Habib's?
Yes, girl, at Habib's.
Those are the best sfiha!
I used to work at Habib's.
- They accepted me, but...
- What we say here doesn't go on air...
We'd be fucked.
I quit because I was not allowed
to wear jeans.
I don't blame Habib's,
but Marcos, the manager.
Go back there, girl, go back!
How long ago?
My career started
four, five years ago...
- So, five years ago.
- Is Marcos there?
When I went back there to visit friends,
he wasn't there anymore.
Let's hit play!
Let's hit play,
I wanna know what's gonna happen.
Do you think Ramon
will do the dishes till the end?
I didn't work, only Murilo did them.
I doubt it, I trust Anna.
- I did nothing at the bar.
- You said, "I'll make the drinks."
You nailed it, you always do, every time.
Shut up, girl.
Stop being so full of yourself.
Stop it, girl. Stop it, stop it.
Do you get one for me?
- What are you talking about?
- Stop being so full of yourself.
- We're family!
- Not a family. You don't listen,
fucking prick!
Impolite, rude, stupid, ignorant!
I'm not the only one who thinks this way.
I'm a woman and have the guts to say it.
Tay and Murilo are not giving a shit,
they just want to be together. Look.
No, it's not. It's not like this.
I didn't say he's a prick to me.
He is to you.
- You didn't?
- Not to me. He is to you!
I say, "As a friend,
Ramon is another person."
The same way, Murilo was a prick to me...
- but he was never to you guys.
- And she was a prick to me too.
She started a fight out of the blue!
Ramon was always a prick to you,
but never to me!
- Of course, not to you.
- But he was to you.
The problem's not
about Nath and Tay, right?
But Nath's dragging Tay into that, right?
Guys, it started with Anna and Mu,
with Ramon, Ramon and Nath, Nath and Tay?
I did this, and you argued with me?
Drink it, sit down.
Drink it and sit down, my ass!
Out of the blue?
Jeez, that's nonsense.
Somebody please explain it to me.
I didn't understand anything, girl.
It started with Anna and Ramon,
then Ramon dragged Nath into it.
Nath started to drag Tay into it.
Then she provoked Tay saying,
"I have the guts to say it,
"and everybody here knows
-"I tell it how it is"
- She said Tay called Ramon
- a prick too.
- That he was a prick to Tay,
- but not to the rest!
- Then it all started.
A drink was thrown in somebody's face,
which I think is extremely rude.
Now tell me, have you ever
lost your temper
and thrown a drink at somebody?
- No, never!
- Tell the truth, John?
- Have you ever done it? On purpose?
- Yes!
Yes, I have!
I know I'm wrong, Don't judge me, okay?
No judging!
You'll say I'm like Nath.
We'd never do that!
John Drops,
you're here to judge them.
I don't wanna be judged by you!
I know I am wrong.
I won't judge you.
This is what happened.
I was talking to someone,
and then we started arguing.
He was a former friend.
He started telling me
a lot of horrible things,
things I didn't agree with. I was drunk,
okay, guys? I threw the drink like to say,
"Stop talking, I wanna talk."
Instead of saying it, I threw the drink.
- So you attacked him.
- Was I wrong?
- I wasn't wrong.
- It happens...
everybody makes mistakes.
It's wrong!
It is, but it happens.
Okay, everybody makes mistakes.
But throwing a drink feels really good!
I was singing...
I'm Carol from Niterói...
Then a smart ass
threw a glass of beer at me.
I had another concert, later...
Did he wet you?
Yeah, he did.
I went to the dressing room,
got all buckets of ice and water,
I put all of them together,
removed the soda,
carried that all the way there
and threw it in his face.
"Removed the soda."
I think that Nath throwing the drink
in Ramon's face
tells us more about her,
and how much she likes Ramon.
We said she was very classy
the whole season, you know?
- I take back what I said.
- I think she waited...
She didn't wait,
that's not the first nuisance she caused.
Nath's totally clueless.
He taught me what I deserved and needed.
And I don't need a boy like him!
You said you didn't like him!
I didn't care when he brought girls here.
You fought with Murilo?
"Jerk, you're disgusting..."
- We dated!
- Whatever! We defended each other!
Oh, Nath, come on!
You told me you didn't like Ramon.
For me it wasn't wrong...
Why's she doing that?
You don't defend me.
You never said...
A true friend
- not only defends you.
- I agree.
A true friend scolds you too.
See, she's fighting with Tay.
What bothers me in that situation
is that Nath doesn't listen
to what people are saying.
Nobody can give her any advice,
she doesn't stop talking.
She's never wrong.
You can't help people like that.
And I think it's bad when she demands
people to take her side,
even if she's wrong.
A true friend supports you during both
- good and bad times.
- Exactly.
- Like this.
- It's different.
Your friend will scold you and say,
"Hey, you're totally wrong."
I've already admitted being a phony.
So are you.
If I were, I wouldn't say it.
Finally, right?
You hate that...
Jeez!
Fuck!
I don't like him at all!
Yeah, that's it.
I'm very sad to see
two friends get to this point.
- Girl, Nath is wasted.
- I didn't like it! I'm not happy!
Yes! Nath is totally wasted!
The girls are trying to open her eyes,
then they begin to say
something they might regret!
That's it!
Nath doesn't even remember what she did!
But I think Tay
is being reasonable, you know?
"When I start being true to Murilo."
It's all wrong.
- Why?
- You have to be honest, always!
She's wrong, everybody agrees with that,
but I think we can't be judgmental.
I was like this, I had this attitude,
I didn't listen to anybody,
I thought I was right.
But we mature, right?
You have to be honest all the time!
All the time!
- Fuck!
- Fuck! What an awesome party!
Girl, I know it!
I sang at P12, bitch!
- P12 is the best!
- My God, I know!
- So?
- I don't know, I wish I was him.
Did you get something?
- Nothing?
- No. I got money.
You get money making close-up,
anything in your life. I wanna know
- if you hooked up with a guy.
- No, I had fun.
Have you been to P12?
Yes, I have and I was dating at that time.
I performed there.
Go-go-boy performance?
That party was a real trigger warning
of the vacation.
Man, what an awesome party!
See the gay people dancing? I like daytime
parties, you can see who you'll kiss.
Matheus is there too, John,
the gay guy is there! Did you see him?
He is there!
I wonder who will nail him.
Oh, Renatinho's up there! Look, Renatinho!
Renatinho, my love!
Ítalo's there, Renatinho's hooking up
with Anna, and it's all cool, is that it?
Man, it's the last day. Theoretically,
everybody knows each other, so,
there's no such thing as saying,
"Oh, not today." Baby, tomorrow
is another day, you gotta go back to work,
to college... I would kiss everybody.
Triple kiss!
Oh, that's delicious!
Hey! That's it!
- Fuck!
- Go Matheus!
Matheus nailed it!
#NAILEDIT
The gay people nailed it, baby.
- Look at that glass!
- God!
Buddy, what a dream kiss!
Pabllo threw the glass on the floor
and the butt in my face.
- I don't know what hurt the most.
- He represented! Guys,
I chose to love Matheus.
I'll toast to Matheus. I broke my glass
because of you, Matheus, gorgeous!
And also threw the butt in my face.
Girl, you celebrated the World Cup goal.
- They nailed it!
- There's a hook-up vibe at this party!
- I wanted to be there!
- And it's cool. Everybody's really free!
I love afternoon parties, guys.
I wanna see that at night!
Good evening, guys! I wanna see
everybody full of energy, partying a lot.
I present to you, Kevinho!
You know what's up
I'm gonna...
De Janeiro
Let's go to the cage
Everything's fine
A thin mustache and a hair cut
She looked at me
I looked at her and said
Come with Kevin and Chris
Sit, sit, sit, sit
Everybody jump and sing!
It's Kevin and Chris.
It's now!
Go, Lexa, go!
Oh, my knee can't take it!
That's it!
- Guys, I don't wanna sit down.
- I'm old, jeez!
John broke the couch!
He really did!
I can't see it.
Let's have a toast to us too.
Come on, guys. Just to celebrate our end.
I raise my glass to welcome Lexa
and Jerry Smith, who nailed it.
They nailed it, right?
They did a great job.
You totally nailed it.
I want to say I'm very happy to share
these moments with you. This vacation
was wonderful. Please, say what you want.
I'm very happy to be with you,
to get such a warm welcome
from all of you.
Thanks for your kindness.
I'm very happy
to be in this amazing season.
- All together.
- Thanks for the laughter.
All the stories, all those moments,
you're so wonderful! I already admired you
and this show made me like you
even more. I loved seeing people fucking!
I loved commenting with you on everything.
Thank you so much!
I'd like to thank you because I could be
watching this alone and talking by myself.
We got free drinks!
We got free food and drinks!
Unfortunately, we can't go out
to parties, or on trips, but we...
got a taste of it watching them...
We stuck to the social distancing.
We did it. Nicely put!
Welcome, Jerrynho and Lexa.
I'm very grateful
because Amazon brought us back to watch
Wild and Free: Florianópolis Season Two.
- Hope we have season three!
- Guys, I'm very happy. I smiled, I cried.
- You slept.
I slept very little.
You have no idea how happy I am.
I'm Pabllo's biggest fan, she knows it.
I'm Titto's biggest fan,
I'm your biggest fan, you know, you know.
I'm really happy. Thanks, Amazon.
Thanks, God. Thanks, Universe...
- You're welcome!
- ...for this.
Wild and Free!
- Is that it?
- Thanks, guys!
This is what life is all about
Making love every day
- It's not finished yet, hit play!
- It's not finished yet, wait!
- There's still gonna be lots of sex!
- I learned that from Lexa, right?
Out of the blue! I love it.
Debauchery! Let's get wild!
"Debauchery! Let's get wild!"
- Looks like New Year's Eve with family.
- Delicious! If I don't see you again...
- Happy New Year, Merry Christmas!
- I love retrospective moments.
- Everybody looks back.
- I don't like it, I feel like crying.
Oh, that's my crush!
- What a beautiful image.
- I feel like crying.
Don't cry, Pabllo!
They became my children, you know?
Really, you get to love them.
Nath...
I began to like each one of them.
- Fuck, I'm getting the chills.
- I wanna go to Floripa!
- I wanna go now!
- Invite me.
Oh, fuck! The last afterparty!
We're back, this is gonna blow
I'm back!
What a delicious afterparty!
She's totally naked, with just
shaving cream on her privates.
Girl, did you see what an awesome party?
The Afterparty was the best!
Afterparty was the best!
The first good afterparty!
There were naked people,
Carol's sleeping, crazy!
- It was like Carnival.
- Yes, like micareta.
It was an orgy!
It was not a micareta at all!
Seriously, I wish I was
at that afterparty more
than at the party.
Oh, girl, I wish I was at everything,
at the house... At the party, at the...
Guys, it's coming to an end,
but I need help with one thing.
Where will we have
- the next one?
- Dude, I can't believe it!
Man!
Oh, my God!
- Season three.
- There's gonna be
- season three and contract renewal!
- A lifelong contract, fuck!
I'm gonna work here one more year!
Jerry, where do you want
the next Wild to be?
- Wild in Bahia.
- Oh, imagine Wild in Trancoso!
- I'm from Salvador.
- I want Wild to be in Recife.
It should be in the northeast.
Wild in Niterói.
I think Wild should be in BH,
it's the city.
BH really is a party city.
BH is awesome. It'd be great
because it's near my home.
- Rio would be really cool.
- I think it should be overseas
- because imagine how they'd be overseas.
- Wild in New York.
Wild in New York,
Massachusetts, California.
But let me tell you something.
They'll go to New York,
you stay here, you know that?
We're not going?
- Make no mistake, okay?
- No!
Let me tell you...
- Guys, I have two things to say.
- Lexa has two things to say.
No, I'm great, I'm awesome.
My drink's finished.
What a season! I wanna know where
that vacation is gonna be, and cheers.
Now I'm anxious to know
where it's gonna be.
The re's the saying: "If you stay,
take my dick, if you leave, my father's."
- I'm taking Amazon's glass home.
- I just want you to understand that my...
Amazon, invite me to season three, please!
- I hope to see you guys next time.
- The guy
- broke the leg of the couch.
- Go, Tay, nail it!
I'm gonna miss this!
I think there will be season three.
Girl, I'm sure. Amen, bitch.
I wanna see if they change everybody
and choose other people like us.
Subtitle translation by
Creative Supervisor