There's more fighting today!
There's hooking up!
Oh, my God!
My week went by slowly.
I prayed for today.
Oh, my. Me, too.
There'll be fighting.
Lots of things!
Things will happen. Murilo, Tay, Bia,
Luan, who rubbed it
on somebody's knee.
Who had her knee rubbed up to.
I don't wanna see it.
We don't know it for sure.
Oh, my God, I'm anxious.
I'm anxious, because last episode
left me like this,
very sensitive, something like...
I wanna see it right now.
Are you all right now?
I'm still catching my breath.
Looks like the truck's still here,
it hit me.
Murilo tried
to get back together with Tay,
but it must be hard seeing
her boy with another girl.
She's adamant.
That's what's bothering him.
But they're classy, they're not arguing.
There was that disagreement last week,
but she knows how to avoid this,
and he has nothing to say.
I'm anxious to know about Luan and Murilo.
That's the problem.
That scene over there, at the end,
- made me feel...
- And Bia was in it too, right?
Poor girl, she was kinda lost.
Too much booze.
And you saw that
Bia believed Luan too, right?
So, she thinks Murilo rubbed it...
into her knee.
- These glasses are... for COVID?
- Yes.
Holy shit, bro.
- I'm pretty with these glasses.
- She's mocking us.
I liked them and decided to wear them.
You're right. That's the power.
Guys, I wanna watch this episode.
I'm gonna take the glasses off.
Hit play. Let me see here. Let's go.
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
Is it gonna be only me?
You had sex with a girl. Easy.
I heard her moaning.
I'm still hurt because of that.
If you knew how much I'm hurt.
- Kissing is no big deal.
- That's it.
I'm fine now.
I know what I do and what I don't, bro...
It's not taking me anywhere.
It'll make me feel worse.
But that really hurt me.
In a way I didn't think I'd feel.
It's good I found out
I really have feelings.
Tay, you're playing with me, man.
You're playing with me.
No, I play with my feelings.
- You're playing with me.
- I play with me.
I play with me, Murilo.
- You're playing with me.
- No, with me.
- No.
- With me.
No, because it's not just you!
You're not alone in this.
But why would I be messing with you?
- Why would I be messing with you?
- I fucking love you.
- I love you too.
- You don't because...
You don't.
I do. If I didn't, I'd be in the pool.
I don't believe that.
Fuck, what a night!
What's up, brother? How are you? Okay?
I'm at home, having a good time,
and I was thinking about you.
Things are crazy.
I wish you were here to party with us.
Floripa is not the same
without you to party with me.
I miss you...
I miss our parties in Rio.
Just want you to know...
that you're missed.
- Who is it?
- My brother from Rio.
I was over there making up for lost time
and I texted.
- Renan?
- That's right.
That's my boy.
Fuck, man! I had to text him
this pool is beautiful, man.
Let me take this.
Take it... I'm gonna get the towel.
Take this.
Let me see our pictures.
This was the whipped cream...
You and Anna are very funny.
That's us.
What about this one?
There were more pictures of you.
We took one that was... Look.
This.
Come here.
Where's the camera?
- It's over there.
- Is there film?
I'll use it well.
It's coming out.
- Let's take it.
- Let's go upstairs.
Let's do it.
DON'T BE AN ASSHOLE
Later!
Bye.
Look, a car's coming. It's a cab!
Oh, my God!
- Look at her hair!
- Let me see it!
Let me see!
Oh, I'm scared.
Hey, Father Blond.
Bullshit!
Come, bitch!
Hey!
- What's up?
- Welcome.
At lunchtime, man.
Let me introduce you to Tay.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- How are you?
- You're pretty. What's going on?
- He is stylish, look at the eyebrow.
- Where's that thug?
- The eyebrow.
Go there. Already?
- Good morning.
- Have I talked to everybody?
- Welcome to our world.
You wanna introduce the shower, Anna?
Come on!
Hey, isn't Anna missing?
Leave me alone.
You're the real life rabbit I know.
This one is the house bunny.
You have sex all day.
No, that's over.
It happened when I was 27.
- How old are you?
- I'm 27.
Great!
It's over... So, now
I'm 27 years and one month old.
I'm growing old.
Were you in a relationship?
- That's right.
- I was with her everywhere.
Then you'll be welcomed
to the bachelor's life.
You'll be fine in Floripa.
And drown your sorrows.
When did you break up?
Did you break up to come here?
- Two days.
- Did you break up to come here?
She broke up with me.
She knows you're here?
How long were you together?
Eleven days.
Oh, fuck!
I was thinking it was much more.
I wonder if you're an intense person.
Feelings have to do with time?
No, that's okay, but...
- Do you want me to repeat?
- No.
- Jeez, girl.
- Nathália, right?
Look into my eyes.
Do feelings have anything to do
with time or intensity?
- Intensity.
- I rest my case.
What are we gonna do today?
Today, there's that rock party
here in Flo...
At the lagoon. It's a party.
Rock party?
We're gonna rock tonight.
But is it rock music?
It's not rock music.
- It's a party.
- Oh, rock music. Okay. It's just...
We got the invitation to attend today.
That's the best way, kid.
I'm gonna get you the shorts.
Sure.
Anna!
Yes!
Come here quickly
so that I can tell you something.
Come here quickly, Anna.
I'm gonna tell you something.
Anna, if I go there...
Tell me.
He's calling you.
When you are ready,
come here so I can see you
to decide my clothes.
Got it?
I stopped here to dress up.
You have too much makeup on.
That's how you talk to me?
Bro, this is not necessary, right?
I prefer your face.
How?
- I have too much makeup on, is that it?
- Yes.
I thought you were hot.
I was sure.
Hey, look who's coming over there!
Let's go!
Hey, Renan, get in the bus, please.
Renan is the first one to get in the bus.
Go, kid! Did you warm up, fool?
Let's go!
Go.
Girl, you don't...
- Hey, man, awesome.
- That's great.
KEEP GOING
So, guys, our moments
will be forever ours...
And will be never theirs.
Never theirs.
One for all, all for one!
What's up, princess?
What's up, my man?
You can take it.
Bia, dirty stuff!
Idiot, I just kiss.
What did you think of Renan?
At first, you didn't want to,
now you get out of the bus holding hands.
I'm hard to get... He moves his hand fast.
When I realized, we were holding hands.
He's gentle, right?
It's hot, right?
At first...
I didn't know.
Then I felt like hooking up with him.
Then he stayed there looking at me.
Playing hard to get.
I think he wants to marry me.
He watched me getting ready,
then we kissed. Girl, he's a good kisser.
He's kinda cute.
But take it easy, you know?
You were crying and screaming,
"I want a boy!"
At least I kissed.
What about you and Murilo?
I don't know if that's gonna work out.
I'm really trying.
"Let's go." I'm gonna give him
a second chance.
But sixty percent of me
doesn't want it anymore, you know?
I don't stop thinking about it.
I don't think that's why, girl.
That was the question.
You weren't very comfortable.
There were things... That was, like...
That was the last straw.
I think you wanted a good reason
to say, "See? We can't."
You wanted a reason.
And he gave that to me, right? The reason.
Bro, you're awesome.
Bro, you're... You're awesome.
- That's why I'm quiet.
- Bro, "awesome".
This is the word I have for you.
But I'm out.
I know, that's why I'm quiet.
I know.
You are...
I'm gonna go with Bia.
Ramon's friend has lost his mind.
"You were my first option."
Hey, not her! Not her.
No, but no kissing.
You're tripping!
No, she's talking about... It's just you!
"I'm gonna tell you it's a difficult
situation because I want you so bad."
Get a grip!
I'm gonna kiss her.
She's drunk. I'm gonna kiss you instead.
I'm gonna kiss her!
Fuck, she's talking about something else!
You're paranoid and you're tripping!
I'm not.
Now you're tripping...
So, get a grip. Okay?
Shut up, you're tripping,
you're full of shit.
So, get a grip.
This is very weird.
Fucking weird.
That look on your face, I can't...
Dude, Tay wants to get me jealous
because of the rookie, you know?
Can you believe that?
Renan?
Man, I don't know.
I didn't see it, bro.
- I swear to God.
- Really?
Bro, the talk is gonna...
I don't believe this, man.
What about you and Bia?
Tay hit on Bia.
But, bro, Tay hit on Bia.
She tried to kiss her,
I said, "Bro, are you crazy?"
She's trying everything.
Everything.
She's stuck to Ramonzinho...
- And I don't know...
- I said, "What the fuck is this?"
"Oh, it's nothing." Go fuck herself!
"It's nothing", my ass. Show some respect.
We are brothers, we help each other!
Beatriz is very simple.
She doesn't imagine things, bro.
Bia is a good person.
- But Tay was kissing the neck...
- Tay is mischievous.
Tay is mischievous.
Fuck, I won't be mean, bro.
I won't be mean.
Tay was kissing Bia's neck, bro.
Go fuck herself.
Bro, that was it, seriously,
I tried and all...
I tried...
All the time, I was quiet,
but dude,
I can't anymore.
Let's go!
Hey! Let's go, let's bounce.
You saw it!
She's my friend.
Guys, everybody is wasted,
no reason to argue now.
There's no reason, got it?
She grabbed Beatriz, bro. Who am I?
- Man, you're tripping, man!
- We're friends, Luan.
- For God's sake!
- You're friends?
- Jeez, girl.
- I'm gonna kiss her then.
Oh, it's not allowed!
- It's not allowed!
- Kiss Murilo.
"Kiss Murilo?"
"Kiss Murilo..." What?
No, girl, forget it.
She tried to grab you.
No, you're tripping!
- You're tripping!
- I was hoping you...
My friend over there
is getting things off her chest.
Do you think she wants to fuck me?
Speak Portuguese.
I'm speaking Portuguese.
If you're starting to think...
Speak Portuguese.
Hey, Luan. Stop.
Hey, you're making a scene. You're stoned.
Luan, I only think about
Murilo having sex with a girl,
- I'll never forget this!
- Girl!
My heart hurts.
Girl, come here, look at me.
- No, forget this.
- He had sex with a girl.
I tried to get over it,
but my heart is in pain.
Taynara! Stop!
Look at me! This is bullshit!
I didn't do anything, man.
I didn't do anything.
I'm gonna mind my own business.
I'm shocked.
Man, Tay lost her argument
because of that.
I told you, she was very classy all the...
- In the previous days.
- But, booze is to blame.
- That's because of the booze.
- Booze, love.
I don't drink.
I think booze just helps you
do the stuff you wanna do.
Booze makes you feel comfortable.
Whatever you're feeling.
Imagine what she's been through
in that house,
repressing her feelings.
But I think she had no reason to do
that to him, he didn't do anything.
That's crazy, Tay coming at Murilo.
At least she missed that kick,
- that's something good.
- Guys, he's not wrong.
She's wrong, but not because of Murilo,
because of Anna.
That's complicated.
Bia forgave Luan when he apologized,
and she was very cool about it.
She was very cool about it.
Luan was the one who couldn't forget it,
he's very insecure.
But Tay decided to forgive Murilo
and she doesn't let it go,
she teases him all the time.
She lost it when she kicked him.
Now Luan is making no sense, really.
He's setting the friend of the girl
he's hooking up with against her...
Like, he created a fanfic.
I guess, seriously,
I guess he's thinking about breaking up.
He wants to be free.
I think he wants to be free
and he's making excuses...
- Making excuses to be rid of that.
- Exactly.
I got it, but it goes against
what he said, his apologies...
saying he wants to...
He wants to do whatever he wants,
but he doesn't want to lose her.
- Exactly.
- Then he makes excuses...
- creating situations...
- It looks like, I don't know,
there's a gap, because
- I don't get anything.
- There was a lot of misunderstanding...
- A lot.
- Let's see what...
- I'm curious.
- Please!
Play.
I'm gonna make my cigarette and smoke.
Because, bro, life is wonderful.
You know, bro? Life is wonderful.
- Jeez, what a scene.
- Guys, that made no sense.
I was completely lost.
That boy was seated, I was asleep.
Out of the blue, she started to...
Out of the blue,
she started to cry, to talk about...
They weren't in a relationship.
Get it off your chest, cry,
let it go.
Girl, I wouldn't wish this
on my worst enemy. I swear to God.
Seeing somebody you like
- having sex with other...
- Girl, it hurts a lot!
It's been two days, I'm trying.
But tonight was the last straw.
It hurts!
It seems like every time I lay down,
I see that scene, girl.
You're an older man.
Smoke and tomorrow you talk to her.
Bro, we've talked...
- No, take it easy...
- We've already talked.
He talked to her when they were sober.
She's stoned,
she wants to play hard to get.
- Bro, I'm very calm.
- Look at me!
There's no way.
It's not worth it.
Bro, Murilo is different, I said...
The same thing I told you, I said,
"Fuck, bro, Murilo looks like me."
Why did she have that crisis?
I just ask... like...
From the bottom of my heart.
I didn't do anything.
Put yourself in her shoes.
- Go there, go talk to Luan. I'm done...
- No, damn. That's it.
I'm done, I've already fucking said it!
I've already put myself in her shoes.
It's over. There's no reason
she insists... There's no reason, bro.
It's easy to say
that's water under the bridge,
but that stuff happened two days ago.
Bro, I've said what I think about it.
They both did what they wanted...
She forgave him, why is she rubbing it in?
You know, bro? I never judged her.
I never said,
"You hooked up with that DJ."
You know? For fuck's sake!
Did she fuck anybody?
She could have... Bro, if she wanted to,
she could have fucked, you know?
But why didn't she fuck? She respects you.
- Because she didn't want to.
- Bia, seriously...
Seriously, that's your opinion.
And, Bia, I respect it. I respect it.
Give me a hug.
- I respect your opinion.
- I respect yours.
That's it, it's over.
You judged me, unfortunately.
I judged you?
- That's okay, Bia.
- I judged you?
I've just exposed the facts.
That's it.
Judging somebody... Guys, I don't judge.
Who am I?
Baby, why are you here?
- Why are you here?
- This is not gonna happen.
What's wrong?
What is it?
Yeah, please, excuse me?
Can you excuse me?
But what happen...
Why are you being rude?
I don't understand.
There's no "you and me" anymore,
it's over.
- What do you mean?
- Bro, that's right.
There's no more "you and me".
Okay? Go have fun.
- Why are you saying this?
- Bunch of idiots.
Leave me alone, bro. I'm silent.
Can you do this?
You saint.
No, I'm mad!
Fuck you, everybody.
- Not me.
- Not you, because you're my buddy.
But you go fuck yourself,
Tay, Bia, Luan too...
- I did nothing.
- I know, but go fuck yourselves.
I did the least, right?
I didn't do anything.
You guys made me get sober.
Don't do this, girl.
Why is he pissed?
- Why are you pissed?
- What did I do?
You were born...
I was born! Hi!
Amen, thanks!
Why are you pissed at Bia, Murilo?
Bia, am I pissed at you?
No!
I'm not fucking following...
I took care of that girl
when she was wasted.
You're all crazy.
Fuck!
That's it, fucking shit!
Why are you there?
What did I do?
- Explain it to me.
- Nothing.
Nothing, you're a saint.
- You're a saint.
- I really am. Thank God!
Amen!
What did I do to you?
Can you take your hand off me?
What did I do?
Nothing, you're a saint!
- You're a saint.
- I didn't understand.
I really am, amen!
Can you explain what happened?
Why are you sleeping here?
We'll sleep together.
Can you take the hand off?
Don't do this.
- Don't do this.
- Don't do what?
Don't do what?
Beatriz, go fuck yourself!
You go fuck yourself, man!
Fuck, what a wacko!
Fuck you.
Fuck you. Never mind.
He's asking for it.
What's this?
You wanna kill me?
Do you know what this is?
Bia, don't tease now.
What was that for, man?
Lock her in the bathroom.
We're together.
I'll never let you mess up.
But, man, she teased me this way...
- I know, bro.
- I was asleep.
I was asleep, bro.
- I don't understand.
I won't let you mess up.
We're bros.
Relax, man.
We're bros, relax.
Count on me.
That's it.
Relax, dude.
Hold Bia. Aren't you afraid
of getting your ass kicked?
He's not crazy.
Cry if you want to, bro.
You know?
What's going on, bro?
I don't even know what's going on.
I didn't understand anything.
You know?
Nothing, bro.
I didn't understand anything.
- Where's Ramon?
- I don't know.
Okay, I'm cool.
Chill. Let her talk.
Please, let her talk.
Chill.
Obviously. She's a whore.
Chill, bro.
I just wanna sleep.
- I was asleep, bro.
- Did I do anything?
- I'm with you.
Where's Ramon?
Guys, did I do anything?
Girl, I did absolutely nothing.
Gosh!
Bro, I don't give a shit
about what you do or don't!
What do you think I was doing?
I didn't say anything about this.
You were sleeping to me.
What do you think I was doing?
No, you're always a saint, right?
Hey, Luan, let's get some sleep,
you're tripping.
- Let me hug her.
- Go get some sleep, no!
For God's sake, Luan!
Are you gonna hit me, bro?
Are you gonna hit me? You can hit me.
You can hit me.
What's this... Bro!
Excuse me. Don't you do this to her!
Murilo,
can you take your hand off me?
I was washing...
I won't let you go.
You can punch me, I won't let you go.
What's this? Don't do this!
What's up, bro?
You hit me with your elbow. Fuck!
Get a fucking grip!
Nobody did nothing, Luan!
Seriously.
Stop it! Go.
Everybody, bro.
Bia, look at this, Bia.
- Mu, gargle it.
- Bia. I just held him.
- I saw it.
He hit me with his elbow.
He fucked up my mouth.
ASSHOLE
There's gonna be a fight.
Okay, here we go.
Do you wanna talk about what happened?
I have to apologize to everybody.
But what did you do?
- If you're crazy...
- I was hurting.
But hurting is...
- Yeah, it was repressed...
- That's what I say...
- get it off your chest at that moment.
- I can't.
I told this to Nath yesterday,
"Stop repressing your feelings."
So, I didn't get why everybody fought.
I didn't get this.
I didn't fight because I don't do it.
Everybody was on a different bed.
I don't understand why...
Anna hasn't slept with me yet,
but that's okay.
- Poor girl...
- She'll pay for this. "Poor girl?"
About the situation, you know?
- You could love each other.
- I went upstairs...
I was wasted, obviously.
I said, bro...
- I think she wasn't in the mood.
- I agree.
What now?
About my life or the food?
You're gonna mess with me.
Okay, I'll play.
My next move is minding my own business.
You fuck up and then keep cool.
Stay quiet, at least for two days.
Until I'm not embarrassed.
We have to get things off
our chest, but...
at the right moment.
It's easy.
How do I erase this?
What?
Who did this?
- I don't know, it's messed up.
-"Asshole."
I hope it's my friends.
He made this "Don't be an asshole."
No, "Asshole." It's just this.
- Can I write here?
- Sure.
- Whatever I want?
- Yes.
Okay.
Good morning, baby.
It's awful.
"You learn by fucking things up."
You learn to live by fucking things up.
What would you do in my place?
I wouldn't have given a second chance.
I would have broken up the first time.
First thing he did.
The first time
he called me a bitch and all.
You know why, guys?
This applies to Tay too.
There's nothing without respect.
Girl...
with no respect, there's no way to fix it.
First, there's respect, then trust, love.
There's gotta be respect, guys.
It's the foundation.
How are you gonna eat with no table?
- I think he had to...
- Guys, this is an abusive relationship.
It is a lot.
I told Bia, I've never seen
anybody so...
And... I...
I can't handle this.
It's like...
Yeah, girl, you're in it.
You're involved...
I've been there... Twice.
It was really bad.
It's hard to end this.
You have to want it really bad.
When the anger's gone,
when things are calm, you like the person,
and he says he loves you,
cries, says he's gonna change...
You get back together.
The next party, the same old shit.
Always!
I lived this for six months...
How many fights in four days?
There was that thing in the pool,
that other thing he said...
Luan makes things up to argue with her.
Makes things up.
She does nothing
and he makes something up!
And nothing happened!
Now it's forbidden to bump?
Jesus Christ.
It's forbidden to bump.
I don't want this anymore.
- I love him very much.
- The last straw was...
I was in the bus.
You saw it too.
You went to help Tay.
She was crying, and you were helping...
- He went there...
- He talks to her as if she was a dog.
"Are you really
gonna stay there, Beatriz?"
-"Fuck, yeah, she's my friend!"
- I remember this.
"Kiss Murilo..." What?
- I'm... I'm kissing...
- She tried to grab you.
No, you're tripping!
I thought you were my friend.
I remember saying this to him.
I remember, we were in the bathroom,
I was crying...
- He got angry about that.
- And he went to the bathroom...
You were helping her.
Guys, what am I doing with my life?
If it wasn't for Murilo yesterday,
we'd be fucked.
I would've locked myself in the bathroom.
I would've run.
I said, "Let's lock ourselves
in the bathroom?" They said, "No."
Look at my face.
I think we...
You don't wanna talk...
I don't feel like it.
I wanna be alone.
I have to think about myself for once.
Amazon Prime Video analyzed the footage
and came to the conclusion
that Luan could not remain in the show
after his attitude.
Hey, guys.
Sit down. Do it, bitch.
I made a terrible mistake.
I don't remember what I did, but I did.
I don't even know if I wanna watch this
because this is not me. I'm very sorry.
I'm gonna let you enjoy your vacation.
I'm gonna take care of myself.
Mu, we're bros!
I don't wanna get in anybody's way.
I'm very sorry.
I'm gonna pack and I'd like to hug
each one of you before I leave.
I made a mistake, but I love you all.
I really thank you.
Fuck...
You can cry, bro. Be my guest. Cry!
There's a reason
things happen in our lives.
Everything that happens is a lesson.
Don't forget this.
Never let this moment die,
because this, bro,
will turn you into a better man.
Cool?
Take each one of us with you, bro. Okay?
That's fucked up...
I don't want anybody sad.
Thanks, guys! Enjoy this fucking shit!
We're in this together, brother.
Good luck, man. Now you're on your own.
Go, brother. God bless you.
How is it gonna be in the house?
If people thought
there was a script, baby...
They were wrong.
Regardless of this being a reality show,
if that happens in real life...
You're in there, you go to the beach,
you and ten friends, then one guy hits
another one, you send him home!
- I'd leave.
- You'd leave or you'd send the guy away!
I do or he does.
Everybody's already had
a friend who's been
in a toxic relationship.
Somebody who had an abusive boyfriend
and, if I were told about this, I'd say,
"Girl, I don't know."
Then you start to cut the couple off.
Until she understands her boyfriend
is the problem. It's fucked up because...
You have to be honest and say...
- You have to tell her.
- ...I'd tell.
What do you think?
I was in an abusive relationship
for many years.
It always starts with little things.
They start to talk
about your clothes, your makeup,
hide your perfume because
the scent is strong.
Tell me, when did you realize you were
in an abusive relationship?
I used to forgive him.
One day, the person makes a scene.
The other, he cries,
gets down on his knees,
"Oh, forgive me, because I don't..."
Then you feel sorry for him...
It's what Carol said,
people really begin to move away.
Today you know this, but when...
How long did it take you to understand
that you were in an abusive relationship?
When did you realize it?
Man, I knew I was in something wrong,
but you believe
the person is gonna change.
But I reached a point I thought,
"I don't wanna go through this anymore."
Then I broke up.
- I really broke up.
- If you know someone
who's in an abusive relationship,
open her eyes, say something...
Tell the person,
a lot of people still think
that you shouldn't interfere
in couple's argument, but you should.
He said he's gonna try to help himself.
He's gonna take care of himself,
and is giving Bia the chance
to enjoy her vacation, you know?
I thought Murilo was very noble
when he embraced Luan like a brother,
and said, "Cry, man. You made a mistake."
Even after being hit three times.
This is what friends do.
He was very noble for saying,
"Man, go see a doctor."
I think it's very important to say
that there's abusive relationship
in the LGBTQIA-plus community.
Every kind of person goes
through this sort of relationship.
It's nice when we look for help.
Look it up on the Internet,
you'll find this kind of help.
We can't go through this
and judge the person.
Bia, for example, because,
many times she wasn't aware
what was going on.
I'm sure she's not aware.
We're watching, you know?
She just realized there.
I believe, I think everybody does too,
that Amazon had to do that.
It honored the whole story...
And he had to understand and leave.
I think that was the most predictable.
We were talking about this.
He couldn't stay there anymore, man.
- And violence is intolerable.
- Now I hope...
- the vibe...
- Do you think she's gonna go wild?
- Now the vibe will be relaxed!
- Let's move on, guys? Let's see it. Go.
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
You only live once, baby.
Oh, stop it, it's me!
Stop it! I wanna leave!
She broke a glass, man!
"I wanna leave!"
Jesus Christ, man. I...
Guys, who's that girl kissing?
- Is it Tay?
- It's Anna and Tay.
I knew this was gonna happen.
They were very close since the beginning.
I didn't see this coming.
- I love kissing my girlfriends.
- Yeah!
But Anna didn't give Tay any signals.
She didn't give any signals
she wanted to hook up with her.
- I kiss my girlfriends too.
- Guys, that's no big deal.
Come on. Look, really,
kissing between friends is normal.
Bro, I can't believe this, man.
- My car is here.
- Go, Carol!
Girl, let's have sushi today.
- Let's have it! Here we go!
- It's on me!
Lexa will buy it, she's a rich singer.
Lexa will pay, she has...
Oh, oh, and shake the ass, oh, oh
When you hear the bass
I'm gonna throw it in...