There's more fighting today!
There's hooking up!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
Oh, my God!
- It's been so long, guys.
- Let's do one thing. Lower...
- Thanks, Titto.
- That's indecent.
- Come here.
- I don't want it.
Guys, the week went by slowly.
I prayed for today.
- Me too.
- There's more fighting today.
Things will happen. Murilo, Tay, Bia,
Luan, who rubbed it into somebody's knee.
- I'm very anxious.
- Who had her knee rubbed into.
We don't know it for sure.
That's the question.
God, I'm anxious.
I'm very nervous because last episode
left me like this, very sensitive.
- I wanna see it right now.
- She came dressed to a party.
It's a mix of Katy Perry and Ana Hickmann.
- Thank you.
- You're wonderful.
- Lexa nailed it too.
- Carol is out of it.
I'm into... How can I call it?
The WHO Princess.
Little WHO Princess. It's a mix
of Cruella and the Minions. I love it.
- I'm following all recommendations.
- That's right, girl.
She's wearing a dream dress, see?
Now, Jerry, it's a trigger warning
because we look very much alike.
Soldier of the future. Did you guys
arrange to come together?
That's a sign. God.
Are you all right now?
I'm still catching my breath.
No, I'm not. Looks like
the truck's still here, it hit me.
Murilo tried to get back with Tay,
she put her foot down.
But it must be hard seeing
her boy with another girl.
I think it's bothering him she's fine.
Yeah, and they're classy,
because they're not arguing.
There was that disagreement last week,
but she knows how to avoid this,
and he has nothing to say.
Now, I'm very anxious to know about
the situation between Luan and Murilo.
- That scene at the end...
- And Bia was in it too, right? Poor girl.
- Too much booze.
- There was kind of a trip.
And you saw that
Bia believed Luan too, right?
So, she thinks Murilo
rubbed it into her knee.
Guys, I wanna watch this episode.
I wanna see what happens.
- Let's watch it. Hit play.
- I'm gonna take my glasses off.
This is our review. No cuts.
Whatever we say, everyone will hear it!
It's about this, girl.
I know. John is gonna be cancelled...
Let's hit play.
- Titto has to struggle, baby.
- Cancelled on Twitter?
Oh, my God, seriously.
Is it gonna be just me?
You had sex. You gotta take it slow.
I heard her moaning.
- I'm still hurt because of that.
- If you knew how much I'm hurt.
- Kissing is no big deal.
- Okay, fine.
I'm fine now. I know what I do
and what I don't, bro...
That's not gonna lead me anywhere.
It just made me feel worse.
But you must know that it really hurt me.
In a way I didn't think I'd feel.
Oh, that's cute.
Tay, you're playing with me, man.
No, I play with my feelings.
Guys, did you see... There, in love?
- Completely.
- She was clear she still likes him.
- He's not hiding that either.
- No, it's clear.
- I think they're breaking up. You know?
- Oh, that's enough.
I don't think so.
I think they're gonna get married.
And we're gonna be invited.
I'm gonna tell you not to come.
I'm gonna tell them not to invite you
because you're not being supportive.
No, because it's not just you!
You're not alone in this.
But why would I be messing with you?
I love you, motherfucker!
My God!
I love that "I love you", like that.
- I got goosebumps.
- Me too. I love that mood...
- I love that fighting mood...
- You know why?
- It ends in "take this!"
- But, I wonder if they're gonna kiss...
I think she's gonna avoid that.
Has anybody ever said or heard
a "I love you, motherfucker"? Like...
I have.
- Have you heard it?
- And I kissed him afterwards.
And you kissed?
She blinked and said, "What?"
No, girl, they're gonna kiss.
Let's see this, go. Hit play.
- I love you too. It hurts to say it.
- You don't...
If I didn't, I wouldn't be here now.
I'd be in the pool.
- What an awesome scene.
- I think she's playing games.
"Do you think I'd be here
if I didn't love you?"
- She's playing games.
- I'm loving watching this.
- I wouldn't do it.
- I think she was honest.
I wouldn't kiss him.
I would, with my eyes closed.
- Where's the camera?
- There.
Is there film?
Let's make good use of it.
I love the vibe
of taking pictures together.
Won't it come out?
- It's coming out.
- Let's take it.
Let's go upstairs.
Okay!
Before that picture is developed,
they'll have had sex, right?
Before the picture is done
they'll have sex.
- It happened.
- Guys, it happened!
Has any friend of yours ever had sex
with somebody by your side?
- Yes.
- Have you, guys?
Oh, girl, no.
I have.
- Carol, how was it?
- I moved into a very small house.
His friend was there.
Should I send him away?
- What did you guys tell him?
- We had sex.
Did you tell him to sleep?
No, the guy was watching TV,
and I was by his side with his friend.
- But I wasn't moaning, you know?
- He was watching TV...
Let's say it was this big. Right?
- It was smaller.
- Okay, this size.
- Were you here by this side?
- It was from where you are up to here.
I'm the guy or the friend.
Were you there with the guy?
I was closer. Take it easy...
- There was a couch here.
- I'm here watching TV.
- And the mattress...
- Here?
- And the guy didn't see you having sex?
- I don't know. I was covered.
- It'd be good if John got in that house.
- If I managed to get in that house...
He wouldn't be able
to get in that house. He's too tall.
You were a fighter!
But he had a lot of sex, brother.
Carol? Do you want to tell us
something else? That's cool.
No...
Look, a car is coming. It's a cab!
- Oh, my God!
- Look at her hair!
Hey, Father Blond.
Hi!
'A' plus!
- Jeez, he's fine.
- He seems to be...
- Congratulations.
- ...naughty!
He acts like a player.
Good morning!
- I think Anna liked him.
- I think he's wonderful.
John gives himself completely.
I love it.
- Girl, what a good kiss, right?
- That was a good kiss, I think.
Bro, you're awesome.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
What's this, bro?
What?
Is that for real?
That's why I'm quiet.
- Bro, "awesome".
- I know.
Jeez. Guys, do you see what I see?
- Wait. Hit pause!
- Do you see what I see?
Did you hear what she said?
Ramon's friend has lost his mind.
Ramon's friend said to me
I was his first option.
Look!
No, but no kissing.
Jeez, bro. What a trip.
It's just you!
Dude!
He said he really wants me.
He said "first option"?
- Get a grip!
- I'm gonna kiss her!
Jeez, man.
- What did he say?
-"I'm gonna kiss her."
Yes, to Anna. I guess he's thinking
about breaking up with her.
He wants to break up with her,
he wants to be free...
- and he's making excuses...
- Making excuses to be rid of that.
Instead of saying, "I want to be free."
I got it, but it goes against
what he said, his apologies...
He wants her,
he wants to do whatever he wants,
but he doesn't wanna lose her.
- He wants to own her. It's like this.
- Then he makes excuses...
- Girl, that's gonna be very fucked up.
- They're gonna fuck things up.
- It's now, honey.
- Tay's crying.
- Tay is drunk.
- Renan is doing... She is crying.
- No, forget this, for God's sake.
- He had sex with a girl.
I tried to get over it,
but my heart is in pain.
Taynara!
Stop, Taynara!
The person that's wonderful
is Ramon, like...
Ramon is sharp.
Ramon with his hands up.
Ramon is lost.
I'm gonna mind my own business.
I'll be quiet.
- I'm shocked.
- Tay lost her argument because...
- She was very classy the last few days.
- Imagine what she's been through.
She was repressing her feelings.
I don't understand,
because he didn't do anything!
That's crazy, Tay coming at Murilo, but...
At least she missed that kick.
That's something good.
Ask me if I've ever hit somebody.
Tell us, have you ever argued
because of jealousy?
Because you were jealous of your boy
or a girl was jealous of her boy with you?
So, I was the mistress of a guy,
I was a mistress...
Holy shit.
We respected each other a lot, you know?
- Yeah, I imagine.
- Yeah, we really respected each other.
And we had some arrangements, right?
Like. Yeah, turn off your phone
when you get in my house.
- Forget the world outside and all.
- Lover's code.
Yes. Then he got there,
we went to bed and started making love.
- That's beautiful.
- We started making love.
- Then, the phone started ringing.
- Yours?
His wife was calling him,
and we were having sex.
The thing was inside me
and he picked it up.
-"The thing was inside me"?
- The phone rang, and he picked it up.
- And the thing was happening?
- He picked it up.
I didn't understand
about the fight being jealous.
- Oh, you're getting there?
- You were jealous.
Then I said, "Are you crazy?"
He was on the phone on top of me.
I took the phone off his hand
and threw it on the floor.
Then he got up and screamed at me
for the first time. He was a calm person.
Then he got up and said, "Are you crazy?"
- You said, "My grandma is crazy."
- Then I got scared.
He scared me, screaming at me.
I thought he was gonna hit me.
He'd never shouted.
And I pushed him down the stairs.
But that was because I got scared.
- Because you got scared?
- The question is, is he alive?
It's very disrespectful.
I had been with him for three years...
"How disrespectful you answer
your wife's call while you're fucking me."
You fucked him for three years?
- Yes, man. It was a long affair.
- Let's see what...
- I'm curious.
- Please!
Play.
Baby, why are you here?
- Why are you here?
- This is not gonna happen.
- Oh, seriously.
- Jeez, he's mad at her. Why, bro?
She didn't do anything.
What is it?
- Is he crying?
- It looks like it.
It's always like this. When he realizes
what he's done, he starts to cry,
- and makes a scene...
- Excuse me?
Oh, guys...
Can you excuse me?
Guys, boring!
Why are you being rude to me?
I'd have gone away and...
There's no "you and me" anymore.
- What do you mean?
- No way.
There's no "you and me" anymore.
God. What... What an idiot.
- Why are you saying this?
- Idiots.
Jeez, sis.
Leave me alone, bro. I'm silent.
Can you do this? You saint!
Saint?
Bia, don't go after him.
For God's sake, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Fuck you and everybody.
You're all crazy. All crazy.
"I am Nathália. You're all crazy."
But have you noticed all that tension
got worse because of Luan?
- All that tension...
- I gotta tell you.
Congrats to Ramon and Nat
for their relationship, bro.
I gotta tell you.
Nath, I'm sorry if I judged you
last vacation, that's it.
Why are you sleeping here?
We're gonna sleep together.
Can you take the hand off?
Did he hit her?
- Did he hit the bed or her?
- He hit her.
Don't do what?
Beatriz, go fuck yourself!
You go fuck yourself!
Fuck, what a wacko! Fuck you...
What's this? Bia!
What's this?
You wanna kill me?
Bia, don't tease him right now.
- Stop it!
- Lock yourself, girl.
Bia went to the bathroom.
Guys...
Guys, that's terrible.
Jeez, man.
No, Luan! For God's sake, Luan!
Oh, Lord.
Are you gonna hit me? You can hit me.
You can hit me.
What's this... Bro!
What's this?
What's that? Oh, my God!
Murilo, can you take your hand off me?
Pause!
I agree with Titto when he said
Luan wants to possess the girl
and wants to hook up with others.
He's making up situations
to hook up with others, you know?
He didn't know
how to arrange that with her.
He wants to be free
but doesn't want her to be, you know?
He makes up situations,
so he can hook up with other chicks.
Man, it's... That was expected.
That was coming...
Last week, with the knee thing,
the way he talked to Bia,
the pussy thing, that was a sign
he wanted to control Bia.
It's all wrong, it's disgusting,
a damn thing, you know?
It's like Titto said, when he's sober,
he's nice, but when he drinks, bro...
Pabllo, what would you do
if this happens with you?
Jeez, I'd say, "Let's seek some therapy...
"because It's not only affecting you,
it's affecting the atmosphere,
-"friends." That's horrible.
- It's even more toxic.
That's sad, guys.
I won't let you go.
My God!
What's this? Don't do this!
You hit me with your elbow.
My God!
Fuck!
- There's no reason for that, man.
- Guys...
this was a fucking assault.
Guys, security!
He hit remorselessly.
A hit with an elbow like that
can knock somebody out.
- He injured Murilo.
- He's bleeding!
Murilo's mouth is bleeding.
- Oh, poor Mu, man.
- I feel sorry for Murilo.
- Jeez, poor Mu.
- He was trying to help...
- Murilo is showing her...
- His mouth's injured.
What would he have the courage
to do to her?
He's looking for Luan.
How is it gonna be in the house?
Bro, he hit Murilo's face
with his elbow twice, man.
He can't be a boyfriend, nor a friend.
Seriously... I don't remember
who said he has a problem, right?
Maybe he has a problem with Murilo.
Murilo was hugging him
while he was crying.
But the guy was helping him,
so that he wouldn't screw up.
Remember Murilo fought
with him last vacation.
You take two hits in the face
with an elbow, are you gonna be still?
- That guy lost his mind.
- If people thought there was a script,
- they were wrong.
- But, really...
If that happens in real life...
Sure this is real, but it's being filmed.
You're camping with ten friends...
one guy hits another,
what do you do? Send him home!
- Either I go or he goes.
- Obviously.
But I think everyone has been in
or has a friend
who's been in a toxic relationship
with an abusive boyfriend.
What happens that's really fucked up...
You then start to cut the couple off.
Until your friend understands
she's not the problem...
- But you have to be honest with her.
- That's it, I'd tell...
Carol, and you?
I was in an abusive relationship
for many years.
I didn't know I was
in an abusive relationship.
Carol must be 126 years old, I think,
and she doesn't tell us.
When I was young, you know?
It always starts with little things.
And my friends started
to cut me off, got it?
Because of the other person.
He starts to talk about
your clothes, your makeup,
hides your perfume
because the scent is strong, right?
When did you realize it?
Girl, I was used to forgiving him.
One day, the person makes a scene,
the other, he cries,
"Oh, forgive me, because I don't..."
Then you feel sorry for him.
You're in that relationship for years...
I had a friend who took one year to
realize her husband was cheating on her.
Even while cheating on her,
he was very abusive,
he made a lot of trouble...
He was disrespectful.
We didn't want to go her place.
If he arrived, we'd leave.
I tell people who are watching this.
If you know somebody in this situation,
give the person a hint,
open the person's eyes, tell the person,
because there's a lot of people
who still think
that you're not supposed to interfere
in a couple's argument. But you are!
Bia, because, many times
she wasn't aware what was going on.
- I'm sure she wasn't aware.
- We're watching, you know?
There are a lot of women that,
unfortunately, don't have that option.
Because, unfortunately,
women have difficulty
in being financially independent,
you know?
That's why I support all women
to be independent, you know?
And the most important, Jerry, for us
who are straight. We have to end this.
If a friend tells sexist jokes
that embarrass women,
even if he's your friend, you have
to make him realize he's talking bullshit.
You're free to say he's wrong.
Sometimes you have a neighbor
going through this.
So, it's nice to understand
what's going on these days around us.
And really help, you know?
So, I hope this episode
encourages people to understand
what's the right thing to do.
That we can educate people.
What would you do if you were me?
I wouldn't have given a second chance.
I would have broken up the first time.
Guys, this is an abusive relationship.
I can't handle this.
It's hard to end this.
You have to want it really bad.
You have to really want it.
Bia knows it, right, man? You see
she doesn't say anything. She's hurt, man.
Everybody is trying to understand.
But they can't understand,
there's no explanation.
That's the crazy thing about that.
There's no explanation.
Amazon Prime Video concluded that
Luan could not remain in the show.
- Way to go, Amazon.
- Yay! Cheers.
That's it, guys.
Amazon Prime Video concluded that
Luan could not remain in the show.
Yeah. That's complicated.
Hey, guys.
Sit down, bitch.
I made a terrible mistake.
I don't remember what I did, but I did.
I don't even know if I wanna watch this.
I'm very sorry.
I'm gonna let you guys
enjoy your vacation...
Damn, very well.
Mu, we're bros, okay?
I don't wanna get in anybody's way
in the house. I'm very sorry.
I'm gonna pack and I'd like
to hug you all before I leave.
Jeez, cool.
I made a terrible mistake, but I love you!
He manned up.
Oh, guys, I feel like crying.
- It seemed to be honest, guys.
- I think so too.
He had a cool attitude right now,
you know? He understands he needs help.
- He said he's gonna try to help himself.
- He needed that, and he had the attitude.
That's very hard, when you're wrong,
to admit that you're...
It's because you have to be humble.
People don't like to be humble.
They wanna act like,
"I'm fucking awesome."
- But he nailed it...
- What he did was horrible,
but he had a cool attitude now
for saying that.
We have to understand
that the house's atmosphere was horrible.
Because of Luan and Bia. She could not
have fun and he will take care of himself.
Bia has the chance to enjoy her vacation.
Then the house will be cool.
I thought Murilo was very noble
when he embraced Luan like a brother,
and said, "Cry. You made a mistake."
Even after being hit three times
in the face, man.
He was very noble. Once again,
he realized that guy had a problem.
What do you think?
I think Murilo is the oldest in the house.
So he's way more experienced.
You can see by his conversation with Tay,
it's different from other couples.
I expected that. But it was very nice
because we know that, deep down,
Luan had a problem
that nobody understood why.
And he forgot everything to stand for it.
I think that, if it were Ramon
instead of Luan, or anybody else,
he'd do the same thing.
I thought that was very cool.
I want Murilo hanging out with me!
Bia will have fun!
Do you think she's gonna go wild?
Now the vibe's gonna be relaxed,
a good vibe!
Let's run a sweepstake.
Who thinks Bia will...
Would you hook up with anybody, Carol?
Oh, I get over really fast.
I don't have time to waste.
I cry and do it.
-"I have sex crying," right, Carol?
- Yes, right.
Play!
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
What?
In my face?
There are some guys
who think you're an athlete,
that you open the spaghetti...
Lexa...