- I'm here.
- It'll begin.
I've missed you guys.
You're spitting in the back of my head.
My God, such an upgrade, Mrs. Prime Video.
It's beautiful, right?
- Great.
- Such an evolution.
- I'm shocked.
- I'm anxious for the second season.
Last summer I was on Titto's lap.
Now I'm here.
Thank God. I said I'd only come back
if we were far apart.
I'm very happy to be here with my friends
and watch the second season.
We brought in two backups
who I really love.
My wonderful friend Lexa,
and my baby Jerry Smith.
- Girl, ready for the action?
- Friend, I totally am.
You're not ready for it.
- Just the way I like it.
- Jerry, ever been to Floripa?
- Yes.
- Yes?
Not to Floripa,
I've had good times in Santa Catarina.
- Why did you go there?
- Do you like videogames?
"Do you like videogames?"
She said it's her seduction strategy.
She invites the boys
to play videogames and attacks.
I saw the first season.
As you can see,
our living room has changed.
We are following all
the health authorities' COVID guidelines.
But Titto is devastated.
He thought he'd seduce me this season.
Save it for next season.
We can exchange some nude pics.
- What's this bullshit?
- Are you sending nudes, Carol?
- No.
- Receiving any?
- So, so.
- I don't do that.
- What's with the face, Lexa?
- I want to know all the gossip.
I get nudes anytime I want,
I've got my go-to guy.
Girls, I'm anxious to find out
what they've done this summer in Floripa.
I miss being able to gather
and snuggle up to people. Right, Titto?
Yeah, I miss it.
Remember, they are not actors.
It's real life, anything can happen.
Let's stop talking and play the episode?
- Yes, let's.
- Let's go!
One, two, three. Go, Brazil!
A FEW MONTHS EARLIER...
- Shut up, man!
- You sexist!
We have no limits here.
We're blasting it out.
- Girlfriend, Ramon has company.
- In my bed?
If you're fucking me,
you won't talk like this
- with one of my friends.
- I wish I hadn't met you.
If you can't handle it, fuck off.
"Aren't you falling for her?"
He said, "Not at all."
I'll beat up one or the other.
That's the way shit works.
- No, no.
- Calm down.
You're a show-off, brother.
Piece of shit!
THIS SUMMER
DEPARTURES - ARRIVALS
Look at her!
Girlfriends!
I've missed you.
Hey!
You look great!
Look at that tan! You look so thin!
- Girlfriend, you look so thin!
- You look amazing, like always.
- Back to the game.
- Where's the booze?
- Booze!
- Shots!
- Where's Blondie?
- I don't know. She sent an audio.
Hey, Tay. How's it going?
I couldn't get off work in São Paulo,
so I can't join you.
Have lots of fun for me.
- Say hello to everyone.
- Seriously?
I want you to rock. Kisses, bye!
Fuck.
- What are we doing without her?
- How could she not come?
- Awful.
- Thankfully, Anna is coming,
or our team would be shorthanded.
- The team would be depleted without Anna.
- Anna is cool and likes funk music.
Big blond hair.
- She's blonde!
- Yeah!
- That's right.
- We should tell her that.
"We're replacing you,
because you didn't come, bitch."
- Friend, how are you and Mu?
- Girl, we broke up.
Murilo had a few bouts of jealousy,
that really put me off.
He started acting like...
What really drove me to break up,
was that he was going to come to Sorocaba,
but cancelled for the third time.
Not cool, I'm no idiot.
We never spoke again.
-"Bye bye forever."
- Other priorities.
How are you and Ramonzinho?
- Ramon and I are good friends.
- Are you hooking up?
I think not. I hope not.
"I think not."
- She is not sure.
- I agree.
- This "I think not"...
- Yeah.
I didn't buy it.
But don't cry over him, for God's sake.
- None of us.
- If you cry over him... No, I can.
I won't cry over him.
Bia, what will happen with you and Luan?
- I don't wanna get involved.
- Look, guys,
I'd rather not talk about it now.
There's a lot to tell.
- Really?
- So much, I don't know where to begin.
- We'll talk later.
- Are you single now...
- Yes, I'm single.
- All right.
- One for all...
- And all for one!
- I missed this.
- We're here!
Guys, it looks awesome!
- Look at this entrance.
- Our little house.
- The good daughters return.
- Let's start from here.
I'll hop on one leg.
It's here, right?
It's here. Let's scream together.
One for all, and all for one.
We're here.
- Look at the bunny.
- A little bunny!
- Gotta have the bunny.
- Guys, I've missed this.
- Look what's on our deck.
- What?
Damn!
- Man!
- That's where I'll sleep.
That's where we'll sleep.
- This is where everything started.
- Yes. Now, new stories...
This is where it started,
where Bia first kissed Luan.
- Murilo and I had made out.
- Five minutes later, it was a mess.
- What happened between you two?
- After we left,
- we talked, you know.
- You said you'd talk.
He went to Santos, I went to Vitória,
we tried to stay together.
The distance was a problem
and a lot happened
that we both didn't like.
- That's it.
- Relationships are hard.
Both must really want it.
It's hard enough in the same city,
long distance is even harder.
- Hey!
- Someone want a drink?
- Finally!
- Hey!
Welcome!
Give me that.
Glad to see me or the bottle?
- Both!
- How are you?
- Making an entrance.
- I'll open it.
This is beautiful.
- Come on, guys.
- A toast!
- To a perfect vacation.
- Wait up. We have...
our war cry,
"One for all, and all for one."
- Please, guys.
- One for all...
And all for one.
It's the guys. That's Murilo.
- Wonderful!
- We're here.
Look at Ramon...
Who wants to see them? I don't.
I missed you, Floripa!
Stepping in with the right foot.
It's ours!
- This is the life!
- I've missed it!
- Where's little João?
- Where's João?
- Hey.
- Hello!
- I'm in. I told you.
- Hey, Mu.
- How are you? Great.
- Okay, you?
- How are you?
- Hey, handsome.
- How's it going?
- Cool, you?
- All good?
- I've missed you.
- Me too.
- You haven't.
You smell great.
- You're shivering.
- Of course.
Things are getting serious now!
I want to see everyone fucking wasted!
- Thanks, man!
- Let's have a toast.
- All right!
- To Floripa...
Yeah!
- This summer will be sick!
- Yeah, man!
Ice cubes falling!
I haven't drunk in a month
and I'll get shitfaced today.
We need a party in this house.
- Lot's of after parties, drink every day.
- But what about João?
João is not coming, but let's have fun.
We are here to party!
- One for all...
- And all for one.
One for all, and all for one!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
I want to know what we're doing today.
There's a party today on Daniela's Beach.
- Awesome!
- Rocking it already!
What will it be?
Arriving with a bang. What is the plan?
The plan is to have a neon vibe
for us to get wild.
- Fuck yeah!
- Awesome!
You want to just get to it.
I won't hook up with her right away.
I want her to have fun.
The first time, she had less fun than me.
I don't want to be that guy.
- Just have fun.
- That's right.
Don't worry too much.
Just go with it.
The party today will be...
- Just the first.
- The first of many.
- I've missed this!
- I've missed it.
Look what's pulling up.
You missed this? Let's go!
- Let's go, man!
- Let's go!
- We're moving!
- The bus is here!
- Awesome!
- There's history here.
Let's go!
- Hey!
- It's here!
- I've missed it!
- Let's go!
Awesome!
- Oh, man.
- Yeah.
It's hot here.
- It's so hot, man!
- I'll sleep alone again, son of a bitch.
You won't.
Let's go!
- My nose!
- Did you get hurt?
- I've hurt my nose.
- Give me a kiss.
Floripa!
One for all, and all for one!
- Get your drink, kiss whoever you want.
- I am fine.
- I can't kiss you?
- No.
- Why not?
- But I'd like to.
But you don't know why?
Because...
I barely know you.
If we could only...
Can't you make an exception?
- No?
- I can't resist.
- Hey.
- What's your name?
- Pedro.
- Nice to meet you. This is Nath.
- I remember you!
- You remember?
Come on.
Nath is scheming this.
What's your name again?
- Go, girlfriend!
- Take it.
- Are you from here?
- Yes. You?
- Goiânia.
- Goiânia?
We're here, Floripa! Fuck!
- Yeah!
- Fuck!
Look at me. Do the hair thing.
Look at me. I think I bumped my arm.
I did.
You smell great. I'm from here.
I'm from Brasília, but I live here.
- I'm from Goiânia.
- From Goiânia?
Practically neighbors.
Look here.
What now?
Give me a kiss.
- Look at that.
- Oh, my God.
Where's my kiss?
- I need a drink.
- You are gorgeous.
Thank you.
Just the girls.
Man, this picture will be sick!
What's that, Beatriz?
- Fuck yeah!
- The pussy is showing.
- Stop!
- Your pussy was showing.
- Of course, such a big pussy.
Now just the boys. Give it to them.
Give them the camera.
Your pussy is in the picture.
- Why didn't you cover it?
- Who am I?
Why didn't you tell me?
Come on!
That is Beatriz!
Why didn't you say anything?
It's ridiculous for everyone!
- Your pussy was showing!
- Why didn't you tell me?
You do what you want, you are free.
That's it. It will show.
Guys, please welcome Zeeba.
I know who she is, man!
This is fucked up, man.
- Yeah.
- This is crazy, man.
- How's your heart?
- My heart is hers now.
- Forget it.
- We think we'll be able to resist.
That we just want to have fun.
Then you look at her and say, "Man."
No, man. It's just that...
We've been through a lot.
She forgave many things I did.
She is the person that...
Man, I doubted it.
- And you shouldn't have.
- Yeah.
"Is she a saint or a whore?"
I doubted it, man.
We live with so many people
that make us doubt it.
My friends said I was distant.
Because I fucking love her, man.
Welcome to Summer, Floripa!
Let me tell you something.
I've made many mistakes. I really did.
I want you to be the mother of my kids,
I want you forever.
Fuck it.
I've cried so much, you've no idea.
Me, too.
I'm sorry about everything.
I know I was wrong.
I didn't act like a man. Forgive me.
I swear, I said I was going
to just go wild,
and be the stud of the house,
but that's not me anymore.
It doesn't matter.
We need to be great by being ourselves!
I love you in a way
you don't understand yet.
I love you.
- He clearly likes her, but...
- Yeah.
I'm no therapist, but he likes her
in the wrong way, possessively.
"The thing is hanging out."
He didn't want her there.
She could be showing everything.
He has to see that she is free.
- I agree.
- She is an outgoing woman.
Maybe they have to see
that as a couple they don't match.
They like each other, that's a fact.
That's for sure.
But I feel that Luan is very possessive.
And Bia is not like that.
- It's still too soon.
- He has to grow.
I think he's very insecure towards her.
- That's it.
- I don't know how healthy that is.
Yes, he is possessive.
Let me tell you...
Even committed guys treat me right.
Everything was wrong.
There was no commitment.
- But I've never seen anything like this.
- Me neither, this was heavy...
- I've never seen it.
- He said her pussy was showing?
- That was low, right?
- It was low.
But Pabllo, if some boy said to you,
"Your pussy..."
-"Your pussy is escaping."
- I'd laugh and say, "Get a grip."
I would say...
- Say it to me, Titto.
- John, I must say...
- I'm here. Say it.
- Man, I need a water tank.
- Say it.
- John, your pussy is showing.
Pabllo, help me out. It's dripping.
- Oh, girl.
- John would say, "I don't have a pussy.
"Caterpillars become butterflies,
buttholes turn into pussies."
- And he said, "You're free."
- He told her off.
"You can do what you want."
Then I could show my body.
Exactly.
His approach was wrong, touching her.
I think he did that to show other boys
that she's with him, you know?
- Horrible, very dated.
- Jealousy, possession, ego.
I think he lied.
She wasn't showing anything.
He lied to get her out of there,
because he didn't like it.
He wasn't comfortable.
We can't forget the new member, Anna.
She introduced those boys to Nath.
- I liked Anna.
- Let's play it, I wanna see it.
Wait, I missed something.
With all this partying, I remembered João.
I thought we could call him.
- For God's sake, call now!
- I'll call him and we'll understand...
what happened.
- Damn, dude!
- Dude! What's up?
- What's up?
- It's an honor to get your call, bro!
- I'll put you on the big screen.
- All right, I'll turn the phone around.
- How are you, man?
- Buddy!
- Hey, João!
- My God!
Thank God, I'm great. I miss you guys.
Man, we see everyone partying
and think of you.
Tell us what happened.
Why are you not there?
Guys, you're not gonna believe this.
I was in Floripa,
about to get in the house,
and I got real sick.
I had a headache I never felt before.
I fainted, I was in a coma for eight days.
Are you serious? Swear to God, man?
I swear to God, man.
I've never been this serious in my life.
But are you okay now?
A hundred percent, cured and alive?
Yes, thank God.
I met Death, patted him on the back
and said, "Maybe in eighty years."
- What an icon!
- Dude!
Looked at Death's face and said,
"I still have many people to fuck!"
Holy shit, tell me about it, bro!
That's crazy.
Thank God, everything is okay.
The pain is over.
Now that you're famous,
are you still crying to get laid?
Jesus!
That only happened once
and it had never happened before.
Those were tears of arousal.
Very good!
I posted that, "Tears of arousal."
João, don't worry.
You don't need to cry with me, okay?
We're just gonna laugh,
we're gonna cum together.
I'm shocked. I have a wig too, you know?
João, did you meet Anna before?
We found her hot. What did you think?
Man, I met Anna.
Look at his smile. Naughty!
I'm like this because we kissed
before the show started.
I have a reputation, right? Tell me.
Johnny, we'll let you go.
Do you want to leave anyone a message?
Brother...
A special kiss to all Brazilian women.
- Phony!
- Take care, bro!
- God bless you!
- Kisses!
- Take care.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye.
- See you. God bless.
- Hot thing!
I'll miss him and his hot brother.
Let's see what happened,
if they fought or not.
I think there's gonna be
some tension on the bus.
Off to the after party!
You go!
- Hey, welcome! I know.
- With chocolate sauce.
Can I come in?
Gotta get my toothbrush.
Mine is there, too. I can do it.
There is a jerk for everything, right?
Bia and that guy should sleep
in the sex room, right?
They're already having sex
in the bathroom.
The bed. Wanna see it?
- The plastic. Right?
- Yeah, it's hard.
What's that?
We could go to the bedroom.
There's whipped cream and all.
- Whipped cream... My clothes are a mess.
- Let's go to the bedroom.
- Let's drink some more.
- We can drink tomorrow.
- I wanted to have sex here, too.
- Let's do it.
Okay, but I...
But not only here.
You're going to blow me?
I don't want it to only be sex here,
I want to have children with you.
All right, let's talk.
Good morning, Floripa!
Gather up, guys.
Say it.
- We have a message.
- Oh, my God.
- Message? Wait for Thais.
- It's our manager.
- No way.
- What's up, guys?
- It's Ricardo!
- I want you to see our new bar.
It's on Praia Mole. I'm waiting for you.
- See you.
- Let's go see it!
- We're coming!
- We're not working, just seeing it.
We're going to rock today, that's it!
We're gonna party
and get to know the bar, partner.
I think she'll...
Is it on the beach or at a bar?
I think our new gig is at a bar.
Girls, let's go!
Let's go. The van is here!
- Let's go to work.
- Let's go! Beach, sun, Floripa!
Move it, come on.
- We're coming.
- Let's go.
- It's Friday.
- It's Friday, let's have fun!
Today is gonna be the day.
Life is hard, but the beach is easy.
- My God! Look at this!
- That's crazy!
- What's this bar?
- Hey, Ricardo!
Hey, Ricardo!
He's inked!
This is the bar I'm managing.
What do you think?
- Wonderful.
- Look at this view.
I'm thirsty!
You can drink tomorrow.
Girls, have fun.
Boys, let's get you uniforms.
- All right. Thanks, Ramon.
- Have a good day at work.
- Thanks, Mu.
- I don't want to work!
Good afternoon, welcome.
Make yourselves at home.
A beer?
No problem.
One for all, and all for one.
I'll chug it.
Let me help you, love. Kidding.
- I wish.
- Are you allowed?
- I'll try and get glasses.
- I'm not.
- I saw you drinking.
- I wish.
- Are you with her?
Sorry?
That girl over there looking mad
is my girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend? Where? Who is she?
The one with the rainbow shirt?
She's wonderful!
She's not my girlfriend,
but we're together.
Where's the token?
It's yours. I was looking for you.
Luan!
- Listen up, guys.
- Oh, my God.
It's almost another shift.
You can enjoy the party a little.
Get the boss a beer,
because I'm on my way!
Now I want a real toast!
We're here!
Let's get wasted! Fuck!
- It's over, man.
- Cheers, guys.
The shift.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Guys, listen up...
- Habla.
- I have cool plans for us.
- Now, in this state?
No, tonight.
I have bad news and good news for you.
The bad one first.
You're already drunk.
- The good one?
- It's an open-bar party.
We're going to Slott tonight!
We're gonna do this!
- Is this good or bad news? Yes.
- Open bar?
That's it. We're gonna drink a lot.
- Why aren't you coming?
- You didn't kiss me.
- You were talking to those hoes.
- My God.
- I'll be right back.
- Are you tipsy, Anna?
Mind your own business!
- I'll wait.
- Did you see my speedos?
As tacky as your trunks and your hat.
Let's see.
Is it a set?
- Wanna see the set?
- No, thank you.
I always say he needs to be quiet.
- He's great with his mouth shut!
- And with his hole shut too.
- Come on, man!
- Whoa, my God!
- Nath. just kidding.
- Get off!
Look who's back.
It's hot, it's hot
I don't just wanna kiss, I also wanna...
- That's you.
- Are you serious?
- You complained and came back.
- Why? Do I have a girlfriend?
Where's the music?
- We'll talk later.
- Why later? Let's sit and talk now.
Now you want to be my girlfriend?
- Fuck! No.
- Then give me a kiss.
Luan, seriously.
I just can't.
Don't you get it?
I get it. I see you want to be single.
- Did I say that?
- We can't start a relationship overnight.
- Man, it's not that. The point is...
- Until I feel this is different...
- It's about respect.
- Was I disrespectful? Did I kiss anyone?
- Not yet, but I'm afraid you will.
- Not yet. Maybe I will.
Depends on what happens.
If we're not okay,
I may kiss another girl.
So far, it's all good.
If we're not okay,
you'll kiss another girl?
Yes, but I won't hide it.
If we're fighting, we'll talk it over.
- I won't just go...
- You won't fuck around like last time,
- and came back to me?
- Cut the drama.
- No, that's what happened.
- All right.
- You never told me.
- Let's do this...
Have fun.
Isn't that why you're here? Let this go.
I'm not here to play anyone. Forget it.
If you are questioning it...
I'm totally cool.
- What do you mean? I'm not questioning.
- I'm totally cool.
- The point is I don't want...
- Look, I'll say it again.
I want you to be worthy
of the love I have for you.
- If you're not worthy, fine.
- All right, then.
- I won't bother you anymore.
- You were sneaking out...
Look. I won't fucking bother you again.
You're talking too much.
- You're saying we're not a couple.
- You're not going to stress me out.
I wanna keep it light.
It's good just when we have sex.
I won't bother you anymore.
"It's good just when we have sex." Okay!
- Girl, I don't know what to do.
- What happened?
I tried to be honest
and say that I acted weird today,
because I'm afraid of what might happen.
But he doesn't understand our history.
I told you, if Murilo had done a third
of what he's done, I'd kill him.
And never again, girl.
You can find good sex anywhere.
If the sex is not good,
you teach and it's perfect.
- Fuck no.
- Sure!
- You can find good sex, Murilo.
- I don't wanna be played again.
- If it weren't good, you'd find another.
That's the reality.
- It's great.
- The flesh...
is weak, partner.
Listen up. The bar is closing.
We drank enough and there's a party.
- Let's go home?
- Home!
- I'll have stroganoff.
- Oh, there's stroganoff.
Stroganoff.
Let's go. We have more partying to do.
At home, finally.
I'm going too.
It's perfect.
You thought Lu would get undressed?
- Now?
- No!
In this case...
We'll do this? Take it off, girl.
What's he gonna take off?
I can't.
- Do like Luan.
- Fuck, girl.
Take that off, Ramon.
Are you ashamed of your dick?
I'm cool.
Crazy girl.
- Where's my lighter?
- In the box.
I want it back.
I can't lay down on here.
- What do you think?
- I bumped into you.
- You're hard to get, right?
- Sometimes.
Sometimes. Other times, I'm easy.
I was easy to get with you.
- What?
- I was easy.
- I hit on you.
- What?
- In Green Valley. You were hard to get.
- Me?
- Sure.
Of course not! I kissed you.
If I'd known I'd meet you that day,
I wouldn't have come.
But I was in bad shape then.
But I understand, you know?
After everything passed, I got it.
- First, I hated your guts.
- And badmouthed me all over Brasília.
- Brasília? No way.
- Sorry, Goiânia. Right!
Come on, guys, the bus is here!
Let's go!
Come on!
A player plays.
- Let's go!
Let's go!
Good evening, guys.
Come on, guys!
Leave the glass, Bê.
How are you? Been here a while?
I'll just hook up with you.
Of course I want to.
Do you want babies? Want a family?
Oh, you're still a baby. How old are you?
How old are you? Thirty-eight?
Fuck!
Are you gonna play tonight?
- All three DJs are brothers.
- Damn.
- Anna liked one.
- I want the other.
The one with the long hair?
Leave him for me. Keep the other.
- No, we both kiss him.
- We'll exchange then.
- Deal!
- Yeah!
- You're asking too much.
- When I ask, you say nothing.
You say nothing.
Actually, she's with him. She said,
"I'm gonna kiss you" and turned around.
Wasn't it?
- She's with him. Today was insane.
- And are you with me?
- Sorry?
- Are you with me?
With you?
Am I?
Maybe.
Come dance.
I kissed.
I'm very drunk.
- What about Bia?
- I'm not in this.
I saw you guys talking,
getting closer to each other...
- What's going on with you two?
- Mu, I talked to her, bro.
I said, "Do you wanna be with me?"
It seems something is stopping her.
- I'd love to be with her.
- Sure.
So far, I'm always the one
approaching her, kissing her,
talking to her, seducing her.
She hasn't come to talk to me once yet.
She thinks it's all about her?
What the fuck, bro?
She's with me, I'm the man, bro.
I am a whole new level.
- Fuck. I go after her all the time.
- It's true.
I see it, that's what I'm saying.
The only way for Beatriz and me is
to pretend we are strangers.
Murilão! The party is ending,
and there's an after party at the house.
You're invited!
Who's coming?
Hey, DJ, let's go!
You, too?
Is everything okay?
Can't get better.
- Yeah, Mariana...
- I've just waited.
- I just waited.
- I told you.
- It happened.
- People brought me here.
Some people do worse, you know?
Murilo, you didn't wait!
- You didn't wait.
- I'm not talking to you.
I'm not talking to you, okay?
Be cool, and stay out of my life.
Okay?
I'm cool. I'm not talking to you.
Hold your horses, girl.
- Girl, it takes one idiot.
- Everybody here is free.
Everybody is free.
When you know the whole story,
when you hear both sides,
you can give your opinion.
- I'm cool.
- No, no.
Leave him, he's talking to himself.
I'm talking to myself.
And you're the only one freaking out.
What a jerk, girl.
He thinks he waited for Tay.
She is hooking up since she arrived.
Wait for what?
He waited for shit, girl.
- He's playing the fool.
- Come on.
No, listen.
- I know...
- I just thought...
Guys, you should feel sorry.
You either shout or are rude.
- Come, Ramonzinho.
- I'm home.
Look at this gin
I'm gonna drink at home...
Make yourselves at home.
With the rock.
Man, Murilo didn't have to treat me bad,
especially in front of everybody.
- What did he do?
- He did it again.
- Everything will be fine.
- He may be horny for her now...
- What did he say?
Now or in the bus?
"Mind your business, you don't know me."
I had a huge fight with Murilo on the bus.
Did you know?
Man, what do you want?
I'm not going to ignore this, brother!
- I'm not going to ignore this!
- Stop!
Stop!
Murilo is doing this to the wrong person.
It's the accent.
A shower fixes everything. Food does, too.
- Sausage and tomato?
- No, it's spicy.
Hey, who's carioca?
- Why did you do that?
- Are you hungry? Here.
I can't. I can't do this.
We're in the best place, I think.
Cool.
- Laying down here is the best!
- Oh, yes!
How about a hot shower?
Goodbye.
Do I look like I'll sleep with someone?
I didn't give you the...
Where's my couple?
- I think it's over.
- I don't think so.
- Murilo is taking revenge.
- This could be the end,
- or they could fall in love again.
- Triggering their first fight.
- It'll trigger their first fight.
- It'll be their first fight.
- Or their first great moment.
- If he saw her with another guy,
and said,
"Fuck, now I need to find a girl",
- because she'll take the guy home.
- But why?
I felt that too.
This Tay and Murilo thing is wrong.
They're dragging people in.
- The girl's single and having fun...
- The girl with Murilo.
- She just met a guy.
- It's not her fault.
- There's no right or wrong here.
- It's Murilo and Tay's problem.
- The girl is just having fun.
- I'd be filing my nails.
Anna hooks her friend up with boys,
she takes her side.
- The fact she said...
- Anna's not drunk. That's the difference.
She said, "Who are you waiting for, man?
Are you gonna pretend you were waiting?"
But here's the thing about Anna.
Since she arrived this summer,
- she observes, she knows everything.
- Very open-minded.
She's analyzing everything.
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
I don't need to find them having sex
in my bedroom. Now everybody is free.
Fuck!
Our time is over.
Our time is over, okay?
For God's sake.
To have to tolerate this...
Ah, fuck it!
Damn!
- I'm shocked!
- He cried.
He cried and went to Anna for comfort,
with whom he had fought!
- Was that Anna?
- Yes.
- Was it?
He's crying because he saw Tay
with another guy.
But it's a different day, honey!
Booze only brings the feelings
you have for others to the surface.
- Our contemporary poet!
- Had a drink today, Jerry?
- Let's hit the group chat.
- Let's.
- Remember to text me.
- Carol, get the cab.
Six feet, right?
Come on, girl.
Bitch, he's gonna be shocked.
She'll kiss everyone.
Girl, she doesn't lie.
She's everything.
- I hope...
- You understand...