WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
THE REVIEW
I'm an angel.
Hi, everybody.
What's up, guys?
Doesn't she look like a cupcake?
That "hello guys"
is the best in the world.
Looks like Pabllo has
a pineapple on her head. I love it.
Do you like it, baby?
Sis, what's going... Guys, I'm leaving.
I'm not at her level.
You came straight from there!
You came from Ibiza!
Real humble.
To fit the mood!
I can't help noticing
that Jerry is hot, he's so chic.
Thanks a lot. Do you like it?
Look at that look!
But Lexa is awesome too, right?
And Carol!
I'm showing off everything.
Can you dance?
- Yes.
- Carol's a strawberry, I'll bite her.
Show some respect!
What's this, Lexa?
I'm dancing.
If I do that, my pants tear.
Lexa bathed in olive oil
to fit in these pants.
Jesus Christ.
Carol, you look great.
My highlighter is the same color.
Thank you.
You idiot.
Guys, I'm embarrassed.
I wanna leave because I cannot compete.
Pabllo's on another level.
Pabllo, get up.
I'll ask for a crane to help you.
- Guys, look at this.
- It's something else!
Jesus Christ.
That's what...
- Turn the volume down.
- Show it.
Oh, Pabllo.
No, what about the hair?
Beautiful hair.
Barbie. That's my reference today. Got it?
You're our Barbie.
Barbie from Florianópolis 2.
You're the best, sister.
I'll go there.
You know what's worse?
The disagreement bus.
I started the vacation
wishing to take that bus,
but if I get in it, I'll fight.
Because, even Tay, the most even-tempered,
got so mad at Murilo.
She got mad at everybody in the bus.
- I'm shocked!
- So am I.
I don't have the guts to get on this bus
because of my wig.
I'm shocked with Tay
because she was even-tempered, classy,
and just when we think
we've seen it all in Florianópolis,
we got Luan, who left the house.
I wonder if Bia
will finally enjoy her vacation.
I think she will.
Hit play!
The remote's mine.
I know, then hit play, honey!
- Can I hit play?
- Sure!
Are you guys excited?
Guys, I also made a decision, you know?
I asked to leave the house.
What?
What did you say?
Look at Tay! Tay is sad.
He asked to leave to go to a party!
- It's a joke.
- Tay's sad.
He said he did it.
Come on...
I knew it, bro!
The beer is here.
- Jeez, motherfucker.
- Not funny!
Not funny!
Tay almost died.
Look at her face now!
I really ship that couple.
She likes him a lot.
Bia didn't believe that at all, girl.
She's still shocked!
- Fuck!
- That's cute!
Poor girl, she's shaking!
I feel sorry for her.
Exactly.
I'm shocked!
Now, really...
He's being an asshole to her right now.
We have to remember
she kicked him and didn't apologize.
It's true.
I think he lost an opportunity there.
Go, girl!
Out of the blue. I love it.
Guys!
It's like that, you see?
A kiss and bye!
It's okay to kiss your friend.
That's it. Awesome! High five!
I won't complain either!
Buddy, it was great!
They're gonna pretend nothing happened
and kiss the boys!
No, like, Anna got closer,
and Tay couldn't resist!
Carol...
you're at a party, Lexa comes and says...
Don't say... Do you kiss her?
I don't go to parties,
I go to funk parties.
Wherever you want, bastard!
It never happened.
Look who I'm talking about, Carol.
She's beautiful, wonderful,
perfect, but no.
Haven't you ever hooked up with a woman?
Me neither.
Girl, I'd never say "no" to you,
you're hot, you're great.
To Lexa, Pabllo, and Carol,
I'd never say "no".
And neither to you two.
And neither to this glass, to this bowl.
I'm here!
Anna and Tay again.
Again, I love that couple!
Guys, I wonder if I ship them.
The ship's name's Antha.
No, bitch, no!
Did he hook up with Tay?
Guys, are you following what's going on?
- She's fixing Renan up for Bia.
- For Bia!
The plot twist has arrived.
Tay said, "If I didn't have anybody
in my life, you'd be the first, but...
"Bia's single.
"She's free, available,
and wants you very bad."
But you heard that Tay
threw shade again, like...
"If I didn't have anybody, it'd be you."
God, let's see
if it's gonna be really him.
Guys, she's playing the cupid
for her friend.
No...
she took them to the altar
and to their honeymoon.
Look at his face.
He's happy, really happy.
That's what I said, Mu, he's a nice guy.
Go.
Go!
If there wasn't Luan,
I'd hook up with him immediately.
Luan fucked up big time.
Go, Bia!
Fuck it!
Kiss him.
Damn!
More friends like Murilo.
- Go get it!
- I think Anna...
looked and said,
"Since I already kissed him,
I'm gonna kiss Bia."
Yeah, Anna is very free.
I think. Because Anna...
Regardless of whom she kissed,
she needed to release,
I think she needed...
to lose that disgust of Luan.
That negative energy.
She lost that...
Bia is wonderful, goddess...
I think everybody is absolute.
The spell was broken.
What about Murilo? Wonderful!
Did you see what he did?
Guys, Murilo is very detached.
He saw his chick kissing another chick.
Now he touched her hand!
But, guys, take it easy, okay?
We know things are handled on the bus.
It's great at parties,
with free booze.
- Yeah. So far so good.
- Handled on the bus.
Gosh!
Oh, glory.
His jaw is tired, you see?
A cramp in the cheek.
Like at carnivals.
He was surprised...
It's like, "Bro, I'm gonna have
to meet Luan later, man."
He hit on Tay too.
Guys, can you think about this?
At this time?
I don't think so.
He's thinking what's coming next.
Guys, I'm very excited
because I'm dying to know...
what happened.
I think it was wonderful.
You'd do worse, right?
I would.
Was the kiss good?
- Did I fuck up?
- Of course not!
You're free!
Guys, for God's sake, hit pause.
We need to stop a while and praise Nath.
Always!
She's sensible.
I'm like Nath.
Nath is my hero from Goiânia,
I say "Goiânia" and think about Nath.
I'm shocked with her.
Nath really changed.
This season, she came back changed.
She's great!
But I think she understood
the word "free," you know?
Vacation's for you to be free.
When Titto and I kissed,
I thought, "I'm gonna have
to finish this."
It was great.
I'm a good kisser, right?
Obviously!
You see? Come here.
Pabllo, you at that... If you were Bia,
you'd fuck him?
Oh, girl, I think I would.
I think so because...
Luan's already gone, I'm beautiful,
why not?
- And Carol?
- What?
Would you fuck him?
You're not asking me that.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
MC Carol says, "I have sex,
but I don't kiss."
Bia says she kisses, but doesn't have sex.
And how do you have the feeling
you wanna have sex?
The size of the forgiveness!
Isn't this what she says?
But before she sees the size
of the forgiveness?
She says, "Put out this dick, bro."
I ask for a picture.
- I liked...
- At a party!
How's it?
I don't go to parties!
At a funk party!
I do this, "I wanna talk to you."
Then I give him
my cell phone and say,
"Add your number there."
The other day,
I set a date, you know? And...
Fuck!
I don't like that.
The disappointment is terrible,
the size of the forgiveness...
- Really?
- Holy Mary!
I'm gonna tell you something.
To gay people, to babes, to everybody.
Don't expect anything, guys.
We romanticize the size of the dick a lot.
I want a huge one?
Maybe I do.
I want one which fills in everything?
What?
Some people don't know how to use...
That's it!
I had a lot of moments
that weren't twenty-three,
twenty-four, twenty-five, girl?
Twenty-five?
But that's the size of...
Twenty-five is the size of a foot.
No, I've never had a twenty-five.
He's an alien
to have a 25-centimeter dick.
Do you use an air pump to inflate that?
Guys, let's see...
if she's gonna have
this forgiveness today.
There's inspiration here.
Yes.
You're a miss? "Miss Chievous."
I didn't get anything.
What happened?
We'd just praised Nath a lot.
She didn't like the girl Ramon was with,
and asked her,
"You're a miss? 'Miss Chievous'."
Fuck, Nath!
We can't support you when...
Didn't you miss Nath?
You said you did, she's back!
I don't know. I missed her.
I wanted her to make a mess.
Guys, you can't be sensible
all the time, right?
I know it's bad...
but, guys, I missed that Nath.
You can't only be sensible.
There's no way!
Nath made the best mess
in the first vacation.
We certainly have to look
at the funny side.
I'm gonna look like
the boring uncle.
You have to look at the funny side,
but when a joke insults others,
- it's not funny!
- No...
Wait, man, let me finish.
Speak, rabble-rouser.
- When you're not insulted.
- Obviously.
If it makes everybody laugh at you,
it's an insult.
She made fun of that girl
in front of everybody.
I don't like this, my opinion.
I agree.
What's this? "I'm talking?"
Give it up for her.
Using your fake nails, sorry.
You're right!
I agree with you.
But Nath put up with a lot of things.
We thought she'd gotten over him.
That Ramon and Nath were mature.
We know Ramon would never do that...
No, Ramon is cool.
Wanna see it?
It's about time!
- Wanna see it? I push this girl.
- Get a grip.
You're tripping, Nath.
Baby, that girl is sitting on Ramon's lap.
She doesn't want any trouble.
I think Nath controlled herself
and thought, "So far I was very ethical,
"I'm tired of holding everybody's horses."
Don't laugh!
She's not right.
I laughed, but she's not right.
She doesn't have
to take it out on anybody.
- I agree.
- But like now...
Finally, we agree. Nath made a mistake.
Nonsense.
Bad!
I think she had
to work things out with Ramon.
I won't cover up for anybody.
But she might still like him.
Of course she does.
Guys. I don't know. I...
If I hooked up with somebody...
We are not together...
We've hooked up,
but I see you with another girl.
Sis, be happy,
I'll hook up with others too.
Yes, It's not like that
if you feel something.
Jerry. Do you think Ramon
feels the same about Nath?
He has a crush on her.
But I think he's way cooler than her now.
That attitude of his
made her feel
that way about him.
His confidence?
Yeah, all that confidence... Damn, man.
He's happy, hooking up...
I think... He forgot me... That's when...
It's because he's not honest.
He doesn't express his feelings.
That's funny, right?
And there's no bed for me?
Everyone gets a bed, right?
Oh, that's great.
I love that position.
It's makeup sex, right?
A car got there.
He bleached his hair. Do the L, Lacerda.
Guys, that's Renatinho!
He's Ramon's friend, he invited him.
He bleached his hair, you know.
Fuck, you're rad.
I wonder if he's gonna win Anna's heart.
Because Anna is detached, baby.
Go, Blond boy!
Fuck!
Does he know everybody?
It was a joke, right?
Sure. Whose idea?
They're friends, right?
Renan is Ramon's friend.
Jeez, he's great. He's cute, neat.
- Who?
- The newbie.
The blond guy.
I know it.
Bro, if anybody shows up wearing anything,
John will say, "I wanna fuck him!"
Leave my hormones alone.
- Let me introduce.
- Hi.
- Renato.
- Nice to meet you.
Is it Milena's boy?
Jeez!
"Hey, man, jeez, dude. I know her."
"Aren't you Milena's boy?
Jeez, dude. I know her."
Jeez!
That's heavy!
I guess you haven't met.
Grow up, dude. Go... I'll tell you later.
Fuck.
Man, but ex is ex.
The atmosphere is heavy.
She has the scoop...
She must have the full scoop.
Easy there, honey.
The soap is here.
Here.
I'd give him the conditioner and bye!
Hairstylist Leila.
Nails, moisturizer...
"Baby, it's here, figure it out."
She's not interested...
She's taking it seriously.
"Tell me when you're done.
"I will come back to rinse it."
I'd rather the other guy
than the rookie.
I think Renan
is going to lose Anna to Renatinho.
If he's quick, he can kiss her right now.
I would have kissed him.
It's close.
I'll lay over there.
Did she say that?
Wonderful!
She said, "This guy wants
to hook up with me in the shower.
"But I want to do it in the bed, so..."
She chose to be in control.
I got it!
Fuck, come here, boy.
I got it, they went
to the sex room, obviously.
I wanna see sex, fuck.
There's gonna be sex.
- Anna's an icon!
- Girl, you made the sound.
Guys, Anna's an icon!
Bitch, she's awesome.
I hope Anna's on top,
because if she is, well...
Wait...
If it's not Anna, who's on top?
- No, it could be him.
- There's no way!
As far as I'm concerned...
- I thought it was that.
- Hit play.
It could be him.
No, there's no way it could be him.
What ass is that without legs?
Fuck, she's like...
Naughty girl show your power
Yeah, go, young girl, rock...
Fuck, I'm very shocked,
Anna really nailed it.
She hooked up with whoever she wanted,
with Tay, and had sex.
I think it's great.
- Was it good?
- Yes.
- Did you cum?
Did you cum?
That boy is skinny, but he's got it!
He must have a big dick.
Renatinho, say whatever you want.
You can say whatever you want.
When I was almost cumming...
I had a cramp.
I swear. I had a cramp at the time.
My whole leg froze, ridiculous.
Crazy talk.
He had a cramp in his leg?
He had a cramp in his leg.
I've been there.
- Here.
- In the thigh?
I think... Basically, here...
on the side, in the ass.
- Cramp in the middle of sex?
- Yes.
- So?
- You have to hold on and keep going.
- You didn't stop?
- No.
I defeated the cramp.
What a big cramp, right, my brother?
What about you, John?
No.
I'm picturing myself in Anna's shoes.
What position?
Legs up missionary.
- What's this?
- You have to simulate.
We're gonna have to simulate.
He doesn't know.
With you?
Some people don't know.
Go, Jerry.
Is that it?
Jeez, Jesus Christ.
- Come. I'm ready.
- Fuck.
Bro, that missionary is messed up, man.
Carol, have you ever had a cramp?
- Yes, of course, guys.
- Me too.
I've had pain, the other day...
Where?
In the legs, in the knee, in the kneecap.
Now it's called "patella".
Why?
I needed a painkiller the next day.
But why? Because you were riding?
Or because of a blowjob?
No, because of the positions the guy does.
- Hey, John.
- I love this topic.
The position John was talking about,
spreading the legs,
some guys are unbelievable.
They think you're an athlete,
that you're like spaghetti.
Like what? What are you like, Carol?
...and put your leg here.
Like "Spaghetti"!
"Spaghetti".
The guy wants to fuck on a cement bag,
bricks, rocks...
On the cement bag,
I was in a spread-eagle position.
You lay down like this.
Anyway. One day, I got a...
I'm picturing it.
I've pictured the moment!
I've pictured Carol
right in that moment too.
The cement bag was open, sis.
It was open, sticking to the skin.
All covered in cement!
All covered in white dust.
Just throw it in the oil.
Fried chicken.
Breaded, right, girl?
Jerry, when you have a cramp,
call me.
It's all about this!
She showed what she came there for, right?
That's it. She nailed it.
She nailed it.
"If another friend comes,
I'll hook up with him too.
"I'm free."
I think she only hooked up
with the other guy because she felt...
No...
That bro was giving attention to Nath.
- Do you think that was it?
- Yes.
She looked...
She had a look on her face.
Then she thought,
"I'll hook up with others too."
But Anna does that
in a very beautiful way, very subtle.
She thought, "I won't waste time.
"I'm doing nothing too,
I'm gonna hook up with another guy."
- There's not much to say.
- Exactly.
No, here's what I think,
I think she's very...
She's very honest.
If she were Nath...
If she were in Nath's shoes,
the girls that are
more connected than the boys.
Nath, she'd hook up with him on purpose.
So there'd be that atmosphere.
But she wanted it.
I think she did that because
she wanted it.
Anna didn't do that for show.
But I'm not saying she did that
to show to anybody,
she waited for the guy's approval.
I think she didn't wait for this.
And she didn't need his approval, right?
Renato came to me and said, "First chick
"in the house
who drew my attention was Nath."
He told me too.
Then he just said, "What do I do?"
No, he fucked her, took a sip,
and went to hook up with Nath.
No, hey...
He couldn't hook up with Nath?
Would you hook up with him?
Not today, but tomorrow...
That's it, buddy.
But I get fucked up all the time.
I couldn't hook up with Luan.
Tay would hook up with Renato,
and I can't with you.
Why can't you hook up with me?
Tay told me...
You know what?
Would you hit on her anyway?
She said something, wait.
"I'd hook up with him tomorrow!"
No, I think he misunderstood.
He misunderstood.
Yes.
But, at the same time,
I understand his pain.
Because he likes her, you know?
But he asked her
to put herself in his shoes!
- Then she answered.
- But, you know...
He misunderstood.
Let's see what's gonna happen.
Press play!
Look, he misunderstood...
He really did.
Look...
She figured that out.
Poor girl!
I feel sorry for her.
Poor girl.
God!
Guys!
It's over, honey.
What did she misunderstand?
We thought she had cried
because Murilo kissed Anna.
But the whole problem was
because Murilo misunderstood everything.
He understood Tay wanted to kiss the guy,
not today, but tomorrow!
I was cut off like this.
Girl, do you think...
Do you think that person
will think about it?
But other people take the blame.
I once had my leg cut because of this.
Really?
Really. Those things,
one chick did this, bang!
The bottle hit my leg.
She was not my friend.
I wish I could fight at home,
throw things on the floor.
They must use plastic cups.
Like, "I can't take
this bullshit anymore."
And bang!
Poor girl!
But I think she had an outburst.
- She got angry.
- But man...
I'm not defending Tay,
but she was classy the whole time.
She was very cool, I think...
I think it was a huge misunderstanding.
Again?
She kicked him!
I forgot about that!
That's a lot of flamboyance!
Hit play, please!
Come with me.
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
One for all and all for one!
Take it or leave it, let's go.
Guys, today things are gonna get wild!
Triple kiss!
When I wake up,
it looks like I sucked a dog's ass.
I want to brush my teeth, man.
That's disgusting!
Jeez!
- Hello.
- Good morning, customer service.
What a beautiful voice,
do you only work there?
I just work here only.
You know how it is, right?
5:00 in the morning!
Fuck, come here.
Today it's gonna be messed up!
Creative supervisor