Come, my daughter!
I was always by your side.
Sure, sis, but still...
You can't!
I'm bringing my daughter!
Good afternoon, good evening, Brazil!
- We're here.
- Oh, my God!
We're here!
We're here
They've got the same hairstyle.
- It's Pucca and big Pucca.
- Cute.
Two Puccas!
Titto!
Your style goes with the plant.
- We always match.
- You're beautiful!
Looks like we're going to the same party.
The neon party.
You're going to the fairy party.
Episode seven already!
Our binge-watch, guys.
Look, Carol is crying,
tears of arousal... I mean,
- she's crying.
- I'm moved.
I'm not ready to say goodbye to you.
Guys, don't joke around, jeez!
I'm not ready to say goodbye to Tay.
Easy, woman,
there's still one episode left.
You don't understand.
Guys, do you remember what happened?
Anna heard Renatinho having sex!
It was very sad!
- We ended with Tay hooking up with two...
- True.
How's it gonna be in that house?
It is now episode seven, Murilo and Tay...
- They are not a couple anymore.
- I say friends with benefits.
- Like us.
- Like us, Pabllo.
Let's hit play!
Let's go!
WILD AND FREE: FLORIANÓPOLIS 2
Hello, baby.
- Good morning.
Anna hooked up with that guy yesterday?
What about you?
I hooked up with a girl.
That's bad.
How was work yesterday?
Was it good?
- Fucking good.
- Really?
It's always good to work there.
I don't know why I really like that bar!
Hey, Renato!
We're rude, we don't cry,
we say, "Yeah, brother, thanks!"
- Bye.
- Bye, baby!
Bye, it was great having you here.
Did we get my other bag?
We'll deliver it to you later.
Be good, okay?
We're together, buddy.
In the front seat?
Oh, backseat, right?
What's up, brother?
Are you cool? How are you, man?
Thanks, brother, thanks for everything.
We're together!
Go, win, buddy.
Did you kiss anybody?
Yes, but there were few men yesterday.
You? "Few men."
Jeez, I did at the last minute. I swear.
Then he came out of nowhere.
Did he save your night?
I said, "Wow."
I spent the entire night with him.
But yesterday was cool.
I bet.
I decided where to party tonight.
I'm gonna take you to Stage.
Yeah! Let's go wild!
Nath, is Andrei going?
- Your hands.
- Yes.
Okay, then.
The guy's stuck to Nath.
I think we have a new member, right?
I have this feeling.
Let's finish cleaning up in here,
- we rest a little...
- The night will be great!
Holy shit. They're gonna dance too.
It's good there during the week!
The bus is here. Let's go.
Because today things are gonna get wild.
- Wild?
- Wild! Now?
Things are gonna get wild!
Things will get wild?
No crying!
You have to dance to funk music.
Yeah, this is important.
You're kinda sad, aren't you?
You're not kissing anybody.
Girl, I don't know, man. Like,
you and me, we go everywhere,
we go out, we're always together.
You guys are a couple right?
Easy, it's been intense, but...
You fell for that guy,
you wanna marry him.
Man, I'm enjoying it a lot,
I'm having fun!
But I didn't come here
to date or get married.
I came to have fun with you guys!
What are you gonna tell him?
How is it gonna be?
I'm gonna explain the relationship...
Explain the situation.
I'm gonna say,
"We should work things out,
"but now is not the moment."
- Girl, but...
- He has to understand!
I didn't come here
to stay with him, it happened...
- It happened, it was very natural.
- It's being good!
- He's cute, he's very cool.
- I wanna have fun.
I wanna have fun
and I want the same for him.
Now we share the bed, me, you and him.
We can't do this.
He's cute and...
Okay, but I'm gonna settle this.
Bebeto and Romário are coming back.
I won't leave you alone.
Oh, I don't wanna leave.
Let's watch the sunrise.
Let's watch the sunrise, it's happening!
Let's get off!
- Don't fall.
- My head.
You won't fall. Trust me.
Jump.
- Ramon!
- Relax!
Relax. Trust me. You're gonna love it!
You're gonna push me downhill.
Ramon, for you, Ramon.
You don't know...
what's gonna happen tomorrow!
So, don't start saying
"Nothing's gonna happen,
it won't work out!"
Everything is gonna be fine
in your life, dude.
That's it, brother.
That's it. That's life!
What are you smoking?
That's life!
He has to have...
He has to have his moment.
Grateful to the Universe!
Seriously grateful!
Grateful to be here now...
at this moment!
I didn't do anything.
Ramon picked me up and I was sleeping.
- Relax.
- He's pissed!
- He's pissed.
- No, he's not.
I was gonna hug him, he...
There you go.
Andrei, come sleep here...
You're safe!
I didn't do anything!
If you're upset, fine!
I was asleep, okay?
Nothing happened.
You wanna be upset, fine!
Ready?
- Baby.
- Hi.
Let's go outside to talk.
Tell me why you got upset yesterday.
I got upset because
I was taking care of you
and... I was drunk...
I was asleep, and Ramon carried me in,
it was not my fault!
- I know this.
- But you were angry.
Yes. I was pissed.
Okay. I'm having fun.
I told everybody this,
but I didn't plan this, you know?
To be with somebody here...
It's the first time the four girls,
no, the three, are free...
Last vacation, everybody had company...
and that doesn't mean
we're not gonna meet again.
Okay.
It doesn't mean I won't call you,
or invite you to go where we'll be,
but I need to know what I'm feeling.
I need to miss you, you know?
Let's see what happens...
Let's get away from the sun.
I'm gonna pack.
Okay.
Take care, okay? Enjoy...
Just like Rayanne says,
I go to the bakery and fall in love.
Incredible.
Enjoy. Take care of her for me.
I will, I'm gonna talk to Anna.
Relax, she'll be calling you soon!
I'm gonna talk to her.
Thanks.
I'm gonna start by apologizing
for my bad attitude,
but...
every action has a reaction.
And I've always been honest
about the feelings I have for you...
What I wanted to have with you. Anyway,
I wanna know more about you.
If you're getting closer to me because
you want affection or you feel alone...
I'm not alone, I have the girls.
By alone, I mean
somebody there for you... You know?
Not that you don't have anyone.
Everybody is with you.
I just wanna figure this out.
Tell me something that will...
comfort me... Not comfort me, but...
That thing about not being a couple,
that's what I've always told the girls,
I didn't want to force this.
I think we both know
what we feel for each other.
Honestly, I didn't really want to hook up
with any of those guys.
It was just the moment,
I thought, "Oh, I'm not doing anything."
I was trying to explain
when I threw the photo away.
I told you, "Bro, I threw
that picture away yesterday."
Like, when everything happened.
But you wouldn't let me speak!
Let's work things out.
That's what I have to offer.
We don't have to force things,
just let it be.
It's not about forcing anything, you know?
I just don't wanna be let down.
That won't happen.
I don't wanna see you
hooking up with another guy.
That's not gonna happen.
This would never have happened.
I just didn't want to label it.
We don't have to label it.
I never wanted to kiss another guy.
It's not a label.
It's just being together.
Nothing else.
We have to be partners.
Okay.
Can you kiss me in the neck?
I came here earlier to ask
for something, when we were at home...
So, today we're gonna go
to a forró party at DeRaiz.
We're going to DeRaiz?
We were talking about that place today.
You can wear flip-flops there if you want.
Let's go. DeRaiz, let's get wild!
I can't believe we're going to DeRaiz.
The bus is here. Let's go, man!
Let's go! Go!
We're gonna dance close.
Today, there's forró music
Oh, man!
We're gonna dance.
It's catuaba!
It's my best friend!
Oh, my God!
I wanted you to be here so bad.
Wow, they're already kissing.
Jeez.
Crazy! She's the first one!
Nath.
Renatinho.
That's what I fucking like!
Ramon.
Murilo.
Does she know Renato?
This is my guy from Rio.
It'll be fine.
- I'm not going.
- Go use flamingo with her!
- With Milena.
- I'll use it tomorrow!
No way.
Have you met?
You know you've met this guy.
- What's your name?
- Milena.
He wants to go camping.
Let's go camping, guys?
Invite everybody!
Everybody!
Easy, don't talk about this.
Guys! Let's go camping tomorrow?
Go camping.
Going camping, no.
Fuck!
I need to relax!
Are you serious?
Yeah, shake your ass.
I can't.
I shake it a lot.
That chick who got here was the one
you hooked up with in Rio?
I hooked up with her a couple of times.
- With Milena?
- Yes!
No, we hooked up a lot, but...
we stopped, the thing ended...
You guys moved on.
We moved on and I met Anna, you know?
It's gonna be awkward
if you talk there today.
She said, "Oh, let's..."
You can't have fun.
What's your story with her?
We don't even know.
We talked and decided to let it be.
But I get it.
A guy from Rio got here,
they have something.
He doesn't know about anything.
They must be together a long time.
I got here and hooked up
with a bunch of girls.
So you know?
It's cool.
Come and see.
I'm not gonna go camping.
We'll sleep together.
You're smiling, naughty girl.
I don't like you.
That's okay.
I don't like blondies.
And I don't like you.
Can I talk to you?
No. Sure you can.
I'll have sex with him.
Will you forgive me?
He's my... He's my brother from Rio.
Bro, relax. Look, enjoy!
It's my moment.
It's not because I don't want it.
I'm very happy with what's going on.
- I know, enjoy.
- Thanks.
What about you and Ramon?
We're just having fun.
Do you like him?
No, I don't, but I miss him.
I don't know how to explain what I feel.
- I'm jealous...
- Friendship with benefits.
Sometimes I don't care
seeing him with other girls,
sometimes I do.
I can't explain!
When he gets close to me, I...
You've seen it. I showed you.
That's fucked up, I'm afraid.
I like him,
but we know each other's place.
Guys, listen up!
The party here is over,
so let's keep partying at home.
Let's do it!
Let's go! Funk!
Hold my skirt,
or I'll put my hand there.
Girl, I like it.
Let's go!
Go, man!
- She fell on the driver.
- Nath did?
Yes, on the driver.
Guys, let's go to the sex room.
This is the sex room!
- Anna is on fire.
- She really is.
Guys, for God's sake.
It happens. Don't judge her.
We won't!
Will she remember it tomorrow?
Of course, she's very sober.
- Really?
- She's just tipsy.
Yeah, that's what I said. For us...
Yeah, it's normal for her, not for us.
I have friends who do that,
but discreetly.
Yeah, it seems she does that all the time.
Is Renatinho there too?
He's not interested.
He's pissed.
- I'm shocked!
- Ménage!
Ménage!
He's a friend with benefits.
And now Renatinho slept all by himself.
It was almost like Brazil
versus Germany, a 7-0.
Some people have plenty,
- some people have nothing.
- He slept holding his dick.
The competition is ruthless. I don't know
who was the one that made out the most!
Would you invite Renatinho, Carol,
if you were Anna?
Man, I've never done those things.
I think, when there's a crowd,
you can't...
A friend to everyone
is a friend to no one.
You can't fuck
ten people at the same time.
- Speak for yourself.
- You don't have to do this...
- What?
- Speak for yourself.
Can you fuck ten people,
at the same time?
You must have a huge dick, man.
I can't fuck ten people all at once.
If you think sex
is just about penetration...
That's it!
What is it, Carol? Did you choke?
Fuck!
Guys, what about Nath? She broke up
with Andrei, and hooked up with Ramon.
- What do you think now?
- I ate my words.
I ate, swallowed and puked them.
Nath always surprises me.
An icon that surprises.
I gotta tell you, I'm very curious
about them going camping.
- You didn't take that seriously...
- Is that gonna happen?
They're gonna go camping for sure,
and Ramon said they'll sleep together!
Meaning...
There's gonna be sex!
Her tent will shake.
Hey, girls, let's go!
Let's go! It's time.
How am I going downstairs?
Help me, because this bag is yours.
Go, pull it from the back.
Pull it like this.
That's why she's your girl.
Let's go, get it later.
Go Praia do Rosa, forget it.
Let's go.
Renatinho, what about you?
Did you get upset when...
Oh, bro, like...
Yesterday was, like... The final strike.
I got hit and felt it...
There were two, right?
I'm cool now, you know? Yesterday was...
That's because
you settled things, right?
The same day, you decided...
We were gonna relax yesterday,
use the Flamingo later, at night...
That's what I said to her
and everybody, I said,
"Bro, you just had to wait, you know?"
You should've said to Renatinho, "My man
is here and I wanna be with him."
But she was so excited
because of her friends,
- she was happy!
- She wanted her friends to come so bad!
I swear, I am.
Yesterday, fuck... I was a little hurt.
Sure, that's fucked up to see.
It was one party, like,
I had nowhere to run, you know?
I had nobody to hook up with, you know?
I had to be cool there,
pretend things, to not get in her way.
And you didn't, bro.
My intention was, like...
the chick is fucking happy,
I'm not gonna... You know?
Get in her way.
Go and show everybody,
let the world see things.
Do a striptease, show your boobs!
Praia do Rosa, I'm here!
I'm here!
Oh, hey, that's crazy!
That's crazy, we're here.
Renato! Praia do Rosa, Renato,
Renato, Praia do Rosa.
It's a blessed place, huh?
Let's get the things. It's wonderful.
I know nothing. That's new.
It's on the beach.
Look at this view!
- Floripa!
- What a view!
Damn, that's bizarre!
That's crazy!
I couldn't wait.
Guys...
where are we gonna sleep?
- Down there!
- There?
Down there. Let's stay...
Where do I dry my hair?
We'll have to finish...
In the woods.
Where will I put my eyelashes?
We're gonna stay down there.
Let's go, then.
- Is it here?
- Yes, it's here!
That's it, didn't you want
something roots?
Think about the tent.
Let's go? Don't let it spin. Look.
Hey, you're gonna need help
to set up the tent.
- Pull that.
- Here!
Like this.
Are you sure?
It's mended here.
Is it wet? Okay, I forgive you.
Look, one little cold thing!
Fuck!
Let's toast!
To this wonderful place, bro.
The moon, the sea, the sand, man.
To these people
who are here, that's us, man.
We're in Floripa!
Let's get wasted at the beach.
Wasted watching the moon!
One for all and all for one!
Praia do Rosa, fuck!
We have to stick together!
Yeah, crying.
Guys, we could do something, right?
- We could.
- We don't have anything to do, a party...
That's happiness, right?
Last time I came here,
I went with a brother to a bar.
- Which one?
- Bukit.
Let's go there!
"Fuckit"?
I think we should...
get dressed and go to this bar.
- I agree!
- I'm ready.
That's it, guys, we'll go to Bukit
or shall we call it "Fuckit"?
We're gonna go fucking wild!
Go, Carioca, lead the way.
One for all and all for one!
I have to tell you
something really serious.
- Fuck you!
- It's my last party!
- No way!
- For real!
- Why?
- Because I have to go.
It's our last party, you know?
Fuck, that's bad news.
A toast to you.
It tastes like medicine.
Are you leaving tomorrow?
I want us to have
the best night ever, you know?
No, that's crazy. Like it or not,
you're like a brother from outside,
that I used to call, to have fun.
You have good stories here.
If I'm here today,
that's because of you, you know?
Bro, you're here because,
I know you're used to this.
And you live your life to the fullest,
everybody loves you,
everybody wanted you
to join us until the end, so...
- I fucking love you.
- I'm sad, but...
I want this night to be
the best we've ever had here.
The best night!
I'm gonna have to drink.
Let's go get fucking wild!
Are you fucking crying?
We're here.
I'm crying.
I said I wouldn't cry anymore.
I'm crying because of you again,
fucking bitch!
Tonight is gonna be crazy.
Are you listening, Rê?
The affection we had, the hook-ups,
don't affect our friendship,
you know that!
Except the times
we got mad at each other...
but I fucking like you. You know?
Yeah, I agree,
you feel sorry a lot. You do.
Because I worry about you.
I worry a lot.
It has nothing to do with it,
it's something else.
You know that, right?
His sign is cancer!
He cries a lot, very emotional.
I really do, fuck!
Who? She who?
She who?
What's up? Holy shit.
But it's for Nath, it's for Nath, relax.
It's for Nath. It's just a friend, relax.
No, if Anna does that...
- It's not.
- If she does that,
I'm gonna play her game.
It's not, it's for Nath.
I told him.
Believe it, it's for Nath.
Trust me.
Fuck!
It's a friend who came along.
I'm gonna introduce you as my guy.
Yeah, relax, Nath's the one who wants him.
Come, Ítalo, cut the crap.
Ítalo is one of the boys too,
and this is Diogo.
Nice to meet you.
This is Ítalo.
What's up, brother?
I'm fine.
Welcome. Make yourself at home.
Hey, make yourselves at home!
That's it, they're home.
There are the girls too,
they're back there.
Honestly, make yourself at home.
I'm gonna fill up my glass.
If you play me...
Do you think I'd do that?
It's easier you do this to me.
Only if you give me the glass. Ítalo.
- I'm being honest with you.
-Ítalo!
Am I that kind of woman?
Stop that!
Look how many girls
are at that table.
Come here!
Bro, go there!
In the bathroom?
You're gonna hook up
with that chick, right here, wearing pink.
Invite everybody...
Go there, invite everybody
to the afterparty.
How are you, girls?
We're gonna throw an afterparty.
At Praia do Rosa.
Here at Praia do Rosa!
- What?
- What part?
Look, I'm from Rio...
I'm from Rio,
I don't even know where we are.
I know I'm at Praia do Rosa.
We're having a fucking blast,
I want you to come very much.
It's my last night here.
Come on, let's go.
It's my last night here. I'd like you
to stay and have fun with us.
Come on. Do we have a deal?
- Do we have a deal?
- And the boys?
Do we have a deal?
Tonight, we have an afterparty!
Oh, fuck!
He doesn't hunt!
Crazy girl!
Her energy's different...
To your crazy boy.
No, bro, her energy,
what she can offer everybody,
you know?
- That's it, Muzinho.
- It's so much joy.
It's so much empathy and partnership!
- What?
- No, you won't.
That's right, the girl
checked you out, and you...
- Wait.
- Fuck that!
The other girls are looking at us.
Stop being jealous, man.
You're fucked!
What? No, but it's...
But, if you wanna
hook up with a girl, do it.
But the thing is, I am a player.
Express this, then.
No, but I express it! I do!
What about Ítalo?
I can't understand what happened now.
I joke around, damn,
like I did with Renatinho.
You used to get confused
later, in the end.
You got upset
when he had sex with other girls.
It was because I didn't expect that,
it wasn't because I liked him.
Then I didn't know how I was gonna react.
You didn't expect
he was gonna fuck somebody?
- No, girl!
- Really?
No, I didn't!
I was sure!
He used to ask me at every party we were,
"Are we gonna be cool?"
- I'd say, "Let's kiss everybody!"
- You first,
then would come others...
Yes, obviously!
And I always said,
"Let's go to the game!"
That's because
I can't be like Ramon, Renato...
- Who takes girls home, I can't.
- I can't either...
But, girl, Ítalo's a piece of shit,
- he's no good.
- I know.
I know when it comes to womanizers!
We've been together for one year.
I have this feeling of ownership.
I had sex with his friend,
and he freaked out.
Then he gave me
the opportunity to do the same.
And what about Renato leaving?
He's cute. I'm sad. He's sweet,
he won the house over.
Will you kiss him?
- No.
- My plan is gonna be...
You and Ítalo here,
he and Mi by your side.
- Yeah.
- I knew it!
I'm sure this is gonna happen!
It's a mess, but not totally.
Did he have sex with Mi?
The three of us. I had with her...
Come here!
Hey, there's a hot dog
for everybody down the street.
Are you in? Or do you wanna go home?
Let's eat a hot dog!
Now you're excited, right? I knew it.
I was waiting for it.
Let's go!
Let's enjoy this hot dog.
Anna, look.
She tripped, I didn't do anything.
She really tripped!
- I took two guys there, nobody touched me.
- Is it my fault?
Bro, you gave her the opportunity.
Don't lie!
Anna, I said, "Let's enjoy the hot dog."
She said, "Let's go." She did that.
Okay, so enjoy your hot dog.
The girl came holding his hand.
- Who?
- That girl was holding his hand.
But he's wrong.
I took two guys to the box
and I didn't hook up with them.
I said it was for Nath,
it was a friend of a guy Nath wanted.
- Listen up.
- What did I do?
You were holding her hands! Why?
Arm in arm!
You two were arm in arm until that point.
- But I let her go.
- Stop lying.
I'm not lying! The thing is,
she gave me her arm, I let go of it.
Sure, I saw you let go of it!
- I looked back and walked away.
- I let go of it!
Who's with me right now?
But that fucking girl held your hand.
What if it happened to me?
You freaked out with those two boys!
You threatened me, like, "If you..."
She crossed the line.
I'm taking the blame
for something that chick did.
It's on her because she held your hand,
but you allowed that!
No! I let go!
- No! I saw it!
- When she held my hand, I let go of it.
When she did it, I let go of it!
If she had held my hand,
and I had accepted it,
then you could be like this,
but I let go of her hand!
I saw you were both arm in arm.
But that was when you looked.
- So I'm wrong?
- Yes, you are!
- You're right?
- Stop tripping! I'm with you.
Do you have hot dogs for everybody?
Let's eat!
You can prepare them because we're hungry!
Put the sausage! Put the...
I think that's funny,
everybody's gonna sleep on the sand!
The guests sleep on the sand.
If they want it. Or leave!
Seriously.
- Please.
- What do you want?
- Are you looking at me?
- Damn, Anna.
- Easy there.
- Look, stop!
Anna Retonde!
- Did you hear that?
- Look at me!
Stop it, Anna!
You saw her mocking me, right?
Tripping, you're tripping.
Nathália's not alone there!
Stop it, what's that, Murilo?
- You don't have to go there.
- Murilo!
She's the same that held his hand.
So, girl.
She's disrespectful to you and herself.
You're not the problem,
you can do what you want!
She mocked me.
But did you joke around?
- You did.
- I said, "Call them."
- I was joking.
- Hey, I'm gonna be upset.
I don't interfere...
Okay. No, but I don't like these...
Let's call the night nicely?
Please.
Now I'm gonna leave Nathália alone?
- You made fun of her or not?
- She did.
- She did!
- I think she's seeing the joke.
- No, be honest!
That's why I came here.
- I was joking.
- We also joke, but...
we wanna know what you said.
Did you say...
I don't remember...
It was five seconds ago!
No, we just wanna know
what happened, because...
- Man, I owe you nothing.
- You do!
- Let's go!
Easy!
What happened?
They ruined the afterparty?
Murilo, afterparty is over!
Nathália's here.
Tell me, are we gonna get there?
Murilo is a pitbull.
We arrive at our mansion 2.0.
Afterparty!
I don't want anybody...
Let's drink.
Can I talk to you?
About what happened.
- Spit it out!
- I agree!
Before anything...
I invited the girls to go there,
and we went there to have a snack.
- We treated her very well.
- Yes, I know.
Everything was fine until then.
Put yourselves in her shoes.
Put yourself in my shoes too.
It's very easy.
It was like Bia said, Renato.
You could enjoy your last day with us.
Or with a nice girl.
- We took you in, welcomed you.
- Look...
- Listen...
- We just said that!
Okay, fine.
- Hold this, baby.
- But look...
Let me finish. You guys said,
"Oh, they're gonna sleep
on the ground." They heard it.
- I said you'd sleep on the ground...
- No!
- ...if you brought...
- No, you said the girls...
You said they'd...
Fine, but dude...
- Guys, let him...
- ...you were invited to the place.
We took the boys to the box...
You say you wouldn't accept an insult
and you'd do much worse.
What did I do to the girl
who said I was a whore?
Don't I have the right to respond?
If I said... And you thought
I said it to you, I apologize.
I apologize for what happened,
but you have to understand me.
Because she said I was a whore
and mocked me. It's not about Ítalo!
Was he involved? It was about him and her.
- It was about him and her.
- Because...
- I'm in our house, if she mocks me...
- ...look...
- ...you have the...
- I defended Taynara
- when they fought, Bia...
- ...you...
...they are my friends.
You have the right to be pissed.
- Got it?
- Let it go!
I understand your side of the story.
It's your last night, drink! Chug!
It's all settled. Look at the moon.
Here...
He's very upset at you.
I know it.
Nobody is soft here, you know?
I never said you couldn't be pissed
at them for calling you names.
To me, everything happened...
at that moment...
when you said
the girls would sleep on the sand.
I understand, I just wish...
you had understood and prioritized us.
Yes, bro, but...
- But...
- I wish you had prioritized us.
But it's because...
She mocked me twice.
She couldn't take it and walked away.
I understand you guys.
I'm cool.
Me too.
But that's over, that's cool, you know?
- I understand your side.
- I'm cool.
- That's it. Let's have fun.
- Let's do it.
I told Milena to sleep on this side.
This is the couple's side,
this is the sing...
"Mine," my ass,
I'm gonna sleep with Milena.
Ítalo, wake up!
Switch places with Milena,
that's the double bed, look.
Switch it, buddy, switch places.
Last day.
I said I'd be awake.
- Thank you.
- I said I'd be awake.
That's crazy.
Fuck, look at the sun!
Look at that!
- Hey, Murilo!
- Hey, Mu!
Look at that!
Look at that size.
It's Renato's last day!
That's it, bro, always.
It's the best place to say goodbye!
Yes!
- Praia do Rosa, sunrise.
- Look at this sun, dude.
So blessed.
The sun.
Look who's coming.
Fuck!
Fuck! Just a kiss!
A kiss!
That's a mistake.
It wasn't a kiss!
Get out of here!
I'm gonna miss Renatinho!
I think each one of them had...
something to stand for.
Renatinho wanted to get lucky
with the girls on his last day!
It didn't happen because of that mess
that happened with Ítalo and the girl.
Renatinho got upset...
but I also understand her side...
because, imagine the atmosphere
if she went to the camp, you know?
I understand both sides.
I think Renatinho rushed things
and ended up with nothing.
He invited all those people,
- and nothing happened!
- But he had sex a lot!
He's forgiven!
- That's his day.
- Yes, it's cool.
Nothing better than that goodbye, right?
With that sun, the landscape, the friends.
This must be fucking awesome.
You've seen it, the energy's running out.
I have a feeling I can't get enough of it.
Girl, I have this feeling
since the first episode!
- Hit play!
- Honey!
IN THE NEXT EPISODE
Tonight is gonna be epic!
Take it or leave it!
Fuck, do you know what it is?
Getting off, my ass!
What's this?
Floripa!
- Nath. What happened, man?
- They got everything off their chest.
Damn, imagine,
we complimented Nath every day...
- Nath, don't do that!
- ...then, in the last episode...
But we don't know what happened!
Sometimes, you feel like throwing drinks
at somebody.
And once again, in the bus, right?
Damn, what a vacation!
Let's go, buddy, let's go.
Come, baby, stop it. Just today.
- No, don't do this!
- What's this?
Throw the drink in my mouth,
but don't throw it at me.
He can really carry me.
I'll open my mouth.
John can carry 190 pounds, imagine...
You weigh...
You weigh 190 pounds?